(Distant siren wailing)
Move... please.
Matty.
Get out of my way! Get out of my way!
(Man)
Don't move. Help is coming, kid.
That's my boy. That's my boy.
- Matty! Matty!
- Dad.
Matty! Matty!
Don't, don't move, okay?
No, no, no! Just... Don't move.
Somebody get us some help!
- Dad, what happened?
- Matty, it's gonna be all right.
- Just don't move. Don't move, okay?
- What happened?
(Man)
Take it easy.
Your boy...
He pushed me out of the way.
He saved my life.
(Coughing)
Oh, Dad! Oh, it burns!
Oh, Jesus!
Close your eyes, Matty.
- Dad!
- Close your eyes.
- Dad! Dad!
Dad. Dad. Dad.
(Stuttering)
I can't see.
I can't see. I can't see!
I can't see!
(Sirens approaching)
(Matt)
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
It's been, uh...
It's been too long
since my last confession.
My dad, he used to come to this church
back when I was a kid.
He was a fighter. Old school. Boxer.
Lost more than he won.
Had a 24-31 record before he, uh...
But he could take a punch.
- Jesus, he could take a punch.
- Language.
Sorry, Father.
Yeah, guys he went up against
used to say it was like hitting oak.
And nights when he was outmatched,
my dad's strategy was to let 'em hit him
till they broke their hands.
(Chuckles)
He never got knocked out, my dad.
Knocked down, sure.
But he, uh, always got back up.
He was always on his feet when he lost.
Every now and then, though, uh...
Every now and then, he'd get hit and...
something inside of him would snap.
My grandmother, she was the real Catholic.
Fear of God ran deep.
You'd have liked her.
She used to say,
"Be careful of the Murdock boys.
They got the devil in 'em."
(Chuckles)
And you'd see it sometimes...
in the ring.
His eyes would go dead...
and he'd start walking forward
real slow...
hands at his sides,
like he wasn't afraid of anything.
(Sighs)
And the other guy, he'd see that look,
and he'd try to get away from him.
Nah.
My dad, he'd catch him
and... trap him in the corner.
Let the devil out.
Yeah.
Now, I didn't understand it, you know?
What he was feeling deep inside,
I didn't understand it.
Not back then.
But you understand it now?
Perhaps this would be easier
if you tell me what you've done.
I'm not seeking penance
for what I've done, Father.
I'm asking forgiveness...
for what I'm about to do.
That's not how this works.
What exactly are you going to do?
(Girl)
Help!
Help! Help me!
(Girls screaming)
Hey! Hey!
Man, shut up.
I'm getting $1,000 a head for y'all.
So, you be quiet...
I let you have a bucket.
You don't...
- (Crackling)
- (Screams)
(Girls screaming)
- (Man speaking Russian)
- No!
(Girl sobbing)
No. Please, no.
Scream all you want.
Come on, let me hear you scream.
Scream loud.
- (Girl) It's okay.
- (Turk) Nobody gives a shit down here.
(Laughing)
(Screaming)
(Grunts)
(Man yelling)
(Grunting)
- (Bone cracking)
- (Man screams)
(Clicking)
(Footsteps on freight container)
(Grunts)
- (Water splashing)
- (Girls gasping)
Head towards 48th. Stay in the lights.
Flag down the first officer you see.
- Now!
- (Girls screaming)
(Grunting)
Sync & corrections by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
(Automated female voice)
Foggy, Foggy, Foggy.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Foggy.
(Beeps)
Hello.
(Foggy)
Good morning, sunshine!
- What time is it?
- Half past get the hell up.
Let's go. We gotta meet
- the real estate agent in 45.
- (Groans)
What was that? Was that a moan?
- Do you have somebody in bed with you?
- (Groans)
The paralegal?
Is it the para over at...
Never mind, I don't wanna hear about it.
No, I do wanna hear about it!
What was she like?
(Exhales sharply)
Violent.
I gotta get the blind thing going.
It's so unfair.
Oh, hey! Real estate agent, not your type.
Very homely. Might be genetic.
No need to be charming.
And she kinda told me she thinks
blind people are "God's mistake."
That's a horrible thing to say, Foggy.
I know! In this day and age?
All right, shake it.
I gotta go bribe a cop.
Ah, Foggy.
Kidding, NSA, if you're listening.
But seriously, yeah,
I gotta go bribe a cop.
Officer of the law.
Defense attorney.
We're supposed to be enemies.
First off, we've been enemies
since we were four, Brett,
so let's not blame it on career choices.
Secondly, I'm not
a particularly good defense attorney,
so helping me is like helping yourself.
And finally, these are for Bess.
Please stop giving my mom cigars, Foggy.
What? She'll outlive us all.
Look, I'm not asking you
to do anything immoral.
Just give me a heads up
if something, you know,
interesting walks through the door.
You're right. It ain't the careers.
Thanks, buddy!
(Sighs deeply)
You've got a reception area,
a conference room and two offices.
Corner suite has a view of the Hudson.
You can flip a coin
with your partner for it.
Uh, he can have the view.
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to...
- Of course not.
- (Chuckles)
Susan Harris.
Midtown Property Solutions.
Matt Murdock.
(Chuckles)
She just curtsied. It was adorable.
Well, it's nice to know
chivalry isn't dead.
Susan, would you mind
walking me around the space?
Of course. My pleasure.
As I was telling your associate,
this office was barely touched
by the incident,
which is why it's on the market already.
The neighbors weren't so lucky.
"The incident"?
Is that what we're calling it now?
Well, it sounds so much better than
"death and destruction
raining from the sky,
nearly wiping Hell's Kitchen off the map."
Shorter, too.
Owner figuring in the delightful view
of cranes and scaffolding?
Feels like we're getting
pre-incident prices.
They're a quarter of what they used to be.
Hell's Kitchen's on the rebound,
Mr. Nelson,
and in 18 months,
you won't be able to
rent a broom closet at this price point.
We'll take it.
(Chuckling)
We will talk about it.
Because we're not sure
we can afford even this palace,
unless we make some changes
to our current clientele policies.
My partner and I
are having some disagreements
over the direction of Nelson and Murdock.
I believe we're here
to defend the innocent.
And I believe the innocent includes
everyone not yet convicted of a crime.
You know, as the law states.
He tends to use fancy terminology.
And my partner fails to recognize
that, as defense attorneys,
we're never gonna be able
to keep the lights on,
waiting on a horde of innocent souls
to stumble into our loving arms.
At this point, I'd settle for just one.
(Shuddering breath)
Drop the knife!
- No, no, I didn't...
- Drop it!
I didn't do this! I didn't...
I didn't do this!
- Get on the ground!
- I didn't do this!
- Now!
- Oh, God!
(Sobbing)
Oh, God!
No, I didn't do this.
Oh, God! I didn't do this!
Oh, no!
I didn't do this!
(Cell phone ringing)
(Chuckles)
- Hey, buddy.
- (Brett) Homicide.
Female suspect found at the scene.
Definitely qualifies as interesting.
She's been charged yet?
Assistant DA hasn't made the call yet.
Do you have a name on the suspect?
Yeah. Page.
- Karen Page.
- (Door opening)
Okay, can we please take the handcuffs off
the 110-pound woman?
Miss Page, can you tell me
who these men are?
We're her lawyers.
Uncuff our client
and give us the room, please.
(Karen sighs)
Thank you, Detective.
(Door lock buzzes)
Miss Page, my name is Matt Murdock.
This is my associate, Foggy Nelson.
Do you mind if we sit down?
She gave a vague shrug.
I say we go with it.
We understand you're in some trouble.
We, uh, may be able to help.
(Foggy)
Can you tell us what happened?
Why don't we start
with what we know, then?
(Sighs)
You were found in your apartment
with one Daniel Fisher.
Who appears to be
the victim of a homicide,
and currently,
you're the only suspect, Miss Page.
Who the hell are you guys?
I'm Matt.
He's Foggy.
Who sent you?
No one sent us.
So, what?
You're just a couple of Good Samaritans?
Today's just my lucky day?
I bribed the desk sergeant
with a box of cigars for his mom.
(Matt) Our practice is relatively young,
Miss Page,
and we are aggressively pursuing
new clientele.
You gotta stop giving Bess cigars.
She likes to smoke, Matt.
It's a free country.
So how long have you been practicing law?
What time is it?
It's 12:22 a.m.
About seven hours.
(Scoffs)
Well, if you go from
when we passed the bar...
I was going from
when we got our own desks.
Oh, then, yeah.
Seven hours.
You've never done this before?
If you were to hire us, then, yes,
you would be our first client.
Technically. Yeah.
Well, I don't...
I don't have any money.
Well, it was lovely to meet you,
Miss Page.
(Matt clearing throat)
You don't have any money
and we don't have any clients.
Maybe we can help each other.
Tell me, how did you know Mr. Fisher?
We worked together.
(Sighs)
And your place of employment?
Union Allied Construction.
I'm a secretary.
Daniel worked downstairs in Legal.
(Stuttering) I didn't know him very well.
But he was always nice, you know?
But it's hard to meet people in the city,
so I asked him
if he would have a drink with me.
You asked him?
(Voice breaking)
Like I said, he was a nice guy.
We met at the Three Roads bar,
on 49th Street.
We had a few drinks,
and the next thing that I remember
is waking up on the floor of my apartment
covered in blood.
His blood.
No, I'm not stupid.
I know how that sounds.
But I am telling you we met at the bar.
We had a few drinks.
And I don't know what happened after that.
It wasn't me.
Please.
(Heart beating steadily)
Please, you have to believe me.
(Sniffles)
I didn't kill him.
I believe you, Miss Page.
(Sighs)
There's plenty of room over there.
Do you mind?
28,957.
Tell Rigoletto he'll get his money.
Mr. Rigoletto has retired.
His books have been acquired
by my employer.
Ah. Well, you tell him the same thing.
I'd like to show you something.
Do you have a moment?
What is it about college girls
and Monet T-shirts?
Open composition and
the spontaneity reflecting
this transformative time
in their lives, perhaps?
Or maybe they just
like the color blue.
Call her.
(Line ringing)
Hey, Dad, what's up?
(Man)
Hi, baby, I'm just checking in.
You need anything?
Uh, yeah,
I actually have a ton of laundry.
I was gonna swing by this weekend
and use the machine.
And then, maybe we could
catch a movie after your shift?
Yeah, yeah.
That'd be great.
Uh, look...
Baby, I got...
I gotta go. I love you, baby.
Love you, too. Bye, Dad.
Now, you see this man here?
If we're being honest
with each other, Mr. Farnum,
I find his methods unpleasant.
But such are the times we live in.
Give us a wave, Mr. Rance.
I told you that I will get you the money.
Such a small sum
is of little interest to my employer.
Your position, however,
that's something we can work with.
(Man sighs)
What do you want me to do?
I'm friends with Gary Feinstein
in the DA's office.
I'll give him a call
first thing in the morning,
see where their heads are at.
I'm guessing
they're gonna puff their chests,
but they have to know murder two's a risk.
We end up at manslaughter,
we get the right judge,
- maybe she's out in five to 10...
- We're not taking a deal.
No, this is why they have deals, Matt.
So the straightforward cases
don't waste everybody's time.
I don't think she did it.
She's the sole suspect,
found at the scene, covered in blood,
with the murder weapon
and no defensive wounds.
If they offer anything it'll be a gift,
and we will take that gift.
We do not want this to go to trial.
They don't want this
to go to trial, either.
Why hasn't she been charged yet?
They have 24 hours.
And it's the weekend.
They're gonna take
every last second
to collect the evidence
before they move.
They've got the evidence.
You just laid it out yourself.
This is a good arrest, Foggy.
We should already
be reading about it in the papers.
There's something not right
about this case. I can feel it.
You can feel it?
All right, I'm just gonna say this once,
and we can move on.
You don't necessarily
show the best judgment
when beautiful women are involved, Matt.
How would I even know
if she's a beautiful woman?
I don't know.
It's kinda spooky, actually.
But if there's a stunning woman
with questionable character in the room,
Matt Murdock's gonna find her
and Foggy Nelson is gonna suffer.
(Chuckling) All right, I don't disagree
with anything you're saying.
- Thank you.
- But I need you to back me, anyway.
(Groans)
All right. Fine.
Let's start with the obvious, then.
If she didn't do it, who did?
We're dead in the water
if we don't give them an alternative.
Agreed.
We need to take
another run at our client.
She may not be guilty, Matt,
but that doesn't mean
Miss Page is telling the truth.
(Muffled screaming)
(Shrieks)
(Cop grunting)
(Gagging)
(Panting)
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
(Both grunting)
(Screaming)
(Cop groaning)
(Panting)
(Screaming)
(Indistinct)
I'm gonna make this easy, Detectives.
Get the ADA in here
to release Miss Page
and we'll recommend
to our charming, media-friendly client
that she not plaster the airwaves with
how she was nearly killed in your custody.
And I'll agree not to make cooing noises
for the rest of this meeting
when I think of the civil suit
that we have on our hands.
How do you know they're not charging her?
Besides the fact that you were required
to do so four hours ago...
if you were gonna do it at all?
That's an excellent question.
Along with how the security cameras
on Miss Page's detention area
went on the fritz
right before the assault.
Yeah, we'd like to speak to Mr. Farnum
about that, as well as what...
Get in line.
He'll be arraigned in the morning.
Get my client released.
Don't make me ask again.
(Whispering)
I'll call the ADA.
But you take that tone with me again,
I don't care if you're blind,
I'll kick the shit out of you.
Really?
We're going there?
(Scoffs)
That was pleasant.
It doesn't make any sense.
ADA had everything they needed.
Unless they had too much.
What?
What am I missing?
Maybe someone else
was in her apartment that night.
Maybe they have evidence.
That's Brady material.
They'd have to turn that over.
Only if she were charged.
She hangs herself in her cell,
this all goes away.
(Exhales sharply)
Let's get her some clothes
and get the hell out of here.
Couldn't find any milk.
I hope it's okay.
(Matt)
We have tea now?
(Foggy) I stole it from
the financial office next door.
(Sighs)
How are you holding up?
Better.
Thanks for getting me out.
(Foggy)
Don't thank us yet.
Just because they released you
doesn't mean
they won't eventually bring charges.
(Matt) Which means it's crucial
you don't speak to anyone
other than the two of us
about what happened.
I don't have anyone to talk to, anyway.
Do you have somewhere
you can stay tonight?
My apartment's not far.
You can't go back there.
Miss Page, our immediate priority
is to keep you safe.
And in order to do that, we're gonna need
to have a frank discussion.
Okay.
Do you know who's trying to kill you?
No.
Do you know why
they're trying to kill you?
Yes.
- (Recording machine turns on)
- (Karen) I, uh, work...
Worked in the financial department
at Union Allied.
They're overseeing
the bulk of the government contracts
for the West Side reconstruction.
I've seen their signs
all over Hell's Kitchen.
The last two years
have transformed the business.
There's new owners, new grants,
new contracts.
Yeah, the world watched
half of New York get destroyed.
That's a lot of sympathy.
And Union Allied benefited
from every dollar of it.
I was the secretary
for the chief accountant.
And one of my jobs...
was to coordinate the pension claims
for the company.
About a week ago, I was emailed a file
called, "Pension Master."
It must have been meant for my boss,
but I made the mistake of opening it.
I'm guessing it wasn't the pension fund.
It wasn't the size of the pension fund.
I couldn't believe the numbers.
But it was still being designated
as company pension.
And it was constantly adjusted.
Money coming in and money going out.
- Going where?
- I don't know.
It was coded routing numbers,
but we are talking a lot of money.
What did you do with the file?
Well, I told my boss, Mr. McClintock,
about it, and he laughed it off.
He said that it was a theoretical model
that they were screwing around with.
I knew something was wrong.
I just... I thought maybe
it was just him, you know?
Embezzling or whatever.
So, how did Daniel Fisher
figure into this?
Danny worked in the legal department.
And I didn't know him very well.
But he was nice,
so I asked him to meet me after work.
I don't know how they knew.
They must have people watching me.
They must have people everywhere.
All I did was ask him for a drink.
And I start to tell him
about what I found
and things got blurry.
Like I was drugged.
And the next thing I know,
I wake up... back in my apartment,
covered in blood.
They killed him...
because of me.
And he had a family.
A little boy.
- I need to get out of here. I'm sorry.
- We can't advise that, Miss Page.
No, you don't understand.
Either you're with them or you're not.
And if you're with them,
then I'm dead already.
And if you are not, then I cannot
have anybody else die because of me.
- We can protect ourselves, Miss Page.
- No, you can't. Not from them.
- Miss Page...
- No.
- We can't let you go home.
- Please, just...
(Sobbing)
She can stay with me.
Just for tonight,
until we figure something out.
I'll keep you safe, Karen.
I don't have much in the way of food,
but there's a Thai place on the corner.
If we order now, it should get here
by the time I make up the bedroom for you.
It's a little dark in here.
I never...
Uh, light switch
is on the wall to your left.
So, uh, (sighs) want some food?
Uh, no, I'm not...
Would you have a shirt
I could borrow, maybe?
This one's a little wet,
and I'm a Hellions fan.
(Chuckles)
Then don't tell Foggy.
Let me grab something for you.
And, really,
I can't put you out of your bedroom.
I'll be just fine on the couch.
From what I understand
about my living room,
that might not be true.
Holy shit!
(Matt)
Went up a year ago.
I'm told the co-op nearly rioted,
some oversight from
the developer's agreement.
Upside is, nobody wanted it
and I got a corner apartment
at a hell of a discount.
Thanks.
Can I ask a personal question?
I haven't always been blind.
I guess that's what
everyone wants to know.
That or, "How do you comb your hair?"
How do you comb your hair?
Honestly, you just...
You hope for the best.
Thank you.
You wanna sit?
How did it happen?
Car accident.
When I was nine.
Must have been rough.
No. I made it through.
Do you remember what it was like...
To... To see?
I, um...
Yes, I remember.
I can't imagine what that must be like.
(Chuckles)
You know,
I'm supposed to say I don't miss it.
That's what they teach you
in trauma recovery.
Define yourself by what you have,
value the differences,
make no apologies for what you lack.
And it's all true, for the most part...
but it doesn't change the fact that I...
I'd give anything
to see the sky one more time.
Do you mind
if I ask you some questions now?
Uh...
- Go ahead.
- You just nodded, right?
(Chuckles)
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Here's what I don't understand.
(Clears throat)
I'm the man in charge of the pension funds
and I find out one of my secretaries
has discovered my illicit activity.
To make matters worse,
she's now telling people
about said activity.
Which, obviously, I can't have.
So I decide to take action.
But why don't I kill you?
They tried.
Yeah, the second time.
In the jail.
But the first time,
they left you alive. Why?
What were they trying to do?
Frame you?
Now, the second time,
maybe that's a change of plan.
Something doesn't go their way,
something sloppy at the crime scene.
Two lawyers show up out of the blue
before their people can get to you.
So they figure, okay,
maybe Karen hangs herself in her cell,
and this thing gets swept under the rug.
But the first time...
The first time,
they're not trying to kill you.
They're trying to discredit you.
They're trying to scare you.
And the only reason
that they would do that...
is if you have something that they want.
So, I've been trying to think about
what that could be,
and the only thing I've come up with...
(Heart beating)
is the Union Allied pension file.
Did you keep the file, Karen?
(Beating grows faster)
No.
As soon as I asked my boss about it,
he took it away from me.
The IT guys, they came
and they wiped the computers.
Believe me, a part of me wishes
I'd made a copy for myself...
but I guess I'm just not that smart.
Ah, well, it was just a thought.
It's freezing this high up.
Next time we're meeting at Per Se.
I'll domesticate you boys yet.
This would be a balmy day
in Samara, Leland.
Yes, it's perfect Chechnyans-kidnap-
a-preschool weather, Vladimir.
(Sighs)
Can you at least pretend to be cold?
It's unsettling.
(Laughing)
(Speaking Mandarin)
Anyone here speak Chinese?
Nobu?
The man is Japanese.
I know, I know.
I just thought that...
Forget it.
(Elevator door opens)
Oh, please tell me he's right behind you.
Unfortunately, my employer
is attending to other matters.
He apologizes to you in particular,
Madame Gao.
(Speaking Russian)
We do not deal with lap dogs.
Tell Mister...
We don't say his name.
Woof, woof.
(Man) He would like to know
why you're short on the cargo totals.
There was a problem on the docks.
Barrett and our men were attacked.
Some moodak in a black mask.
(Laughs)
And you bought that?
- (Speaking Russian)
- (Leland) Okay, calm down.
Fine, we'll go with
the man-in-black story.
Our men would not lie.
I said I'm on board.
I'm glad to hear there's some new blood
running around out there.
Heroes and their consequences
are why we have our current opportunities.
Now can we review
the latest numbers and...
Tell me more about this man.
Took Barrett and our guys out
while they were loading the container.
(Speaking Mandarin)
(Chuckles)
She wants to know if this man
stole the shipment for himself.
No.
He let the women go.
He took out your men. How?
Caught them by surprise.
Beat them.
- With his bare hands.
- Four men with his bare hands?
That is what we were told.
Perhaps you should
have been there yourself.
(Scoffs) Again, I have to ask,
why do we care?
Every time one of these guys
punches someone through a building,
our margins go up 3%.
We should be celebrating.
This is different.
My employer will be...
displeased...
we're being inconvenienced
by a lone vigilante.
Then he should tell me to my face.
This is on you. Deal with it. Quietly.
We must be quiet, yes.
We would not want another
Union Allied situation, would we?
Big, loud, lot of questions.
We're handling it.
Like you keep saying
you're handling Prohaszka?
We're in the process of negotiating
with Mr. Prohaszka.
Negotiating?
Maybe we handle our problem same way.
Sit down with this man in black,
break bread.
I think what Anatoly's trying to say
is that it would be in our best interests
for Union Allied to be tidied up
as expeditiously as possible.
As I said...
we're handling it.
(Thunder rumbling)
(Door creaking)
(Sniffles)
(Breathing heavily)
(Sighing)
(Screaming)
(Clicks)
(Both yelling)
- (Bones cracking)
- Ahhh!
(Straining)
(Jack)
Get up, Matty.
Hey.
Let's go, finish up.
I'm tired, Dad.
Hey, I don't want you to
end up like your old man.
I never studied.
Look where it got me.
Come on, Matty.
Get to work.
(Both grunting)
(Grunting)
- (Bone cracking)
- Ahhh!
(Metal clinking)
(Groaning)
(Grunting)
(Panting)
(Groaning)
Who...
What the hell?
I'll get this into the right hands.
No, you can't.
You can't take it to the police.
You can't trust anyone.
Then we tell everyone.
(Breathing heavily)
DNA evidence
will put Rance at the murder scene.
B and E gone sideways,
his records altered in support.
Mr. Farnum's bail has been arranged for
through the usual channels.
Leland's to cover our exposure
on the financials
and McClintock takes the fall
for Union Allied.
(Man on phone) We can't have McClintock
speaking to the authorities.
Pills.
He overdosed less than an hour ago.
The remaining concerns
will be attended to shortly.
Rance was a professional.
How was he subdued?
I'm looking into it.
What about the girl?
Should I make the appropriate arrangements
for her, along with the others?
No. Everything she knows
is already in the papers.
Her lawyers, Nelson and Murdock.
Ambulance chasers. They're clean.
Start a file. They may be of use.
Understood.
- (Karen) Here you go.
- (Both chuckling)
- (Karen) So I know it's not much...
- (Matt) Hmm.
in the way of repayment.
But it is, um, my grandmother's recipe,
and she made me promise
only to serve it to my future husband.
(Matt chuckles)
You know, it's, like,
filled with virtue or something.
I thought I detected
a whiff of virtue in there.
Not that I'm complaining,
but you really should be
thanking the nut in the mask.
He's not a nut.
- I mean, he's a little weird, maybe...
- We're just glad you're okay.
(Foggy)
Hear, hear!
Well, if it weren't for you two,
I'd still be in that cell.
Hmm.
Job's easy when your client's innocent.
All you did was tell the truth.
Yeah, but you listened.
Oh, and don't get us wrong,
we're still gonna bill you.
Just as soon as we figure out
how to make bills.
(Laughs)
I did notice that you could
use some help around here.
And I owe you.
Maybe I could clean the place up a bit.
Is this place messy?
Our firm is very prestigious
and discerning, Miss Page.
Do you have any prior experience
hiding electrical cords
(chuckling) up in ceiling tiles?
Uh, no, but...
I'll work for free.
- (Matt) Yeah, you're hired.
- (Karen chuckles)
(Foggy)
You just got hired!
You can leave the lights off.
(Mouse clicking)
- (Basket thuds)
- (Girl screaming)
(Matt grunting)
Hey! Come on!
Ahh! Daddy!
Daddy!
(Speaking Russian)
No! Daddy!
(Indistinct conversations)
(Overlapping voices)
(Boy)
Daddy!
Help!
(Boy screaming)
Sync & corrections by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com