Previously on The Shield:
Hooker murders are up
for the entire East Side.
Would you forget about making
a name for yourself...
...as the great serial killer hunter.
-He had a knife.
-Gentleman?
I go to put the condom on
and the asshole...
...he smacked me and
he tried to raped me.
Bag it.
The street ain't seen blow this
strong since Grand Master Flash.
You're certain there were six bricks.
Six or seven,
definitely more than four.
Where's Mackey?
Where is it?
What are you talking about?
Hey, treat yourself to a full
cavity search if you like.
I need my Ding Dongs...
-...and you took them, didn't you?
-Right.
Stay away from me and
stay away from my desk.
You gotta be shitting me.
Christ, how old is this one, 13?
Man.
Hooker?
Face down like the other four?
Looks that way.
I warned you about this guy.
Yes, you did.
Couple up the hill saw a green car
cruising back and forth an hour ago.
-They get a model?
-Just said it was green.
-And the driver?
-Too dark.
Car had a busted taillight.
-What side?
-Didn't say.
Go back. Grill them.
Every detail.
This happened on our turf.
You give me the resources,
I'll get this guy.
What kind of resources?
Every warm body you can spare
for as long as possible.
-Personnel is stretched thin as it is.
-I need 48 hours.
I can't do it.
A predator was standing right here
less than two hours ago.
How committed are we to catching him?
For the next 24 hours,
she's your one and only case.
Medical examiner tells us...
...the victim is approximately
12 to 14 years of age.
A 12-to 14-year-old hooker.
Frank, you and your boys round up
every pimp and pro you can find.
Bring 'em here for me to talk to.
Neighbor saw a green car pass by
an hour before the body was found.
The right rear taillight was broken.
Check in with every gas station, car
wash, valet guy in the neighborhood.
June, put together a reward flyer.
Photo of the girl, description of the
car, mention the broken taillight.
She had keys in her purse. Vic, you
and your guys find a locksmith.
See if you can track the numbers.
-Excuse me?
-Sit down with a locksmith.
You want me, I'll be out finding
the prick who did this.
Come on.
Either we get our unsub
in the next 24 hours...
...or we probably don't get another
chance until he kills again.
Let's go.
Vic!
Yes, Herr Wagenbach?
You got a problem with me running
the show, take the night off.
I thought you wanted
this case solved.
I do.
No. You only care about
being the one who solves it.
When I do, I don't want
it thrown out of court...
...because of your Gestapo tactics.
Let's get something straight, Dutch.
Somebody comes into my backyard
and kills a girl, I get involved.
I'll crack this case
with or without you.
Looks like it'll have to be with.
This investigation runs through me.
You find something,
you report it immediately.
I bring the guy in, you'll be
the first to know, Dutch boy.
People see me as a joke around here.
They don't know the real me.
I'm not sure the squad's
ready for the real you.
-I'm not a joke.
-I know that.
Now they'll know it, too.
I'm gonna get this guy!
It's a little early in the game
to be making promises, isn't it?
The one thing they respect is success.
I guess we'd better
nail this guy then.
What do we got?
Body found at midnight...
...green car seen in
the park at 11:00.
The victim has no identification.
Prostitute. Age 12 to 14.
Had a sweet tooth.
Had birth-control pills.
They don't make 12-year-olds
like they used to.
I was wondering what was going on
with the whole Strike Team thing.
The apartment turned
up empty for cocaine.
We have no hard proof
of Mackey's guilt.
That doesn't mean Vic and his guys
didn't steal the drugs.
-I know, but without hard evidence...
-I saw them pocket the cocaine.
You can get the car thief to testify
she found the coke.
-It's not that easy.
-Why not?
Because I'm not gonna put you in
a position to carry that weight.
But you want Mackey off the streets.
More than you know, which is why I
won't let you be the one to do it.
-Captain, I don't understand.
-Exactly. You don't understand.
So take my advice and let this go.
-Captain, I saw them...
-Julien.
Let this go.
-How you doing?
-Been working my ass off.
-Might be time to take a vacation.
-I can't afford to.
Had to drop my price.
-Why?
-Would you pay top dollar for this?
I guess it could be worse.
Found her a few hours ago.
Know who she is?
Looks like the girl who works
kitty-corner from Tracy.
-Where?
-Across from the burrito joint.
Know who pimps her out?
No.
But Tracy would.
Thanks.
This guy has a thing
for working girls.
Make sure somebody's
watching your back.
I thought that's what you did.
I don't want to see
you get hurt again.
I won't let it happen twice.
Does anyone know who this girl is?
Look at it! Who knows her?
That's Sally.
Sally who?
Sally Struthers?
-All in the Family.
-I know who Sally Struthers is.
Maybe she saw one of those
"Save the Kids" ads.
Whatever, that's the name she went by.
Good news is, our timeline's
starting to come into focus.
Her friends said Sally usually started
her shift around 10:00...
...but didn't show last night.
Another one said she saw her
going into a drugstore on Vermont...
...at 7:00 p.m.
When you're a young
girl on a Friday night,...
...hat would you do
between 7:00 and 10:00?
Shop. Eat. See a movie.
Jim Wright, FBI.
Someone called the Bureau
asking for assistance?
I did. Dutch Wagenbach.
You got here fast.
This is my partner,
Claudette Wyms.
Good to meet you.
So...
We've got an unsub killing hookers.
Been there. Done that.
This girl was only 12, 13.
You did the right thing calling us.
Most local cops are afraid we're gonna
come in, step all over their toes.
Not me. I can't wait
to pick your brain.
Let me be clear.
This is your case.
I'm just here to help.
What are you boys chewing? A little
grilled Snoopy, side of Woodstock?
We're clean.
-Think about tryin' a rib eye?
-What do you want?
-You remember your friend Sally?
-Nope.
-Really? Never pimped her out?
-You know absolutely nothing?
-Less than nothing.
Really? So that apartment
over on Weston...
...where you keep all that
fenced electronics...
...you don't remember that either.
What do you say,
you wanna make Robbery Division's day?
Yeah, sounds sweet.
Very sweet.
I'll call in the warrant.
Lady, where's the phone?
-It's over there.
-Yeah, okay.
-Yeah, you were pimping her out?
-She came to us. We did her a favor.
-So you never took a cut?
-20 percent.
Plus a few free pokes a week.
Wipe those smiles off
your faces, shitheads.
You don't score points with me
bagging 12-year-olds.
What kind of work she do
before tricking for you?
I heard she'd worked this sex club.
She was a kid.
So?
So what kind of work could she do
for a sex club?
-You'll have to ask them.
-Don't worry. I will.
I'm impressed you were able
to pick up on this guy.
I've done a lot of
research on criminology,...
-...behavioral science unit.
-It shows.
Dutch!
I got a gas station
attendant here who says...
...he might have seen
your green car.
Detective, I got a guy
who saw our flyer.
Said he sold drugs to
the victim earlier.
Gotta love it when a case gets warm.
So I'm working,
and I see this suspicious white guy.
Suspicious how?
He was white.
So I go out to get a good look at him,
and he turned away.
The dude didn't want me
to see his face.
-Tell me about the car.
-It was green.
Two-door, four-door? Ford, Chevy?
You do work in a gas station, right?
I just run the register.
You sold Sally drugs tonight?
She had a thing for ecstasy.
You're admitting to a crime.
I'm a minor. My lawyer can
argue it's for personal use.
Was Sally for personal use, too?
She was a customer.
Did you know she was a prostitute?
How do you think she paid me?
I hooked her up with
five hits around 8:30.
Five? She always buy that much?
Said it got her through the night.
So...
-How much is this reward?
-Reward?
"For useful information."
You know, like the flyer said.
That's why I'm here.
So what's my reward?
Dealing drugs to a minor,
statutory rape.
-How does six months to a year sound?
-What?
-No license plate?
-Better, I got evidence.
-He paid with a credit card?
-No, man, cash.
See, he paid with $20 at the
automatic teller. He only pumped $17.
He never came back for his change.
Who doesn't want their $3 change?
So you kept the $20?
No, that was part of my night deposit.
I saved his change, though.
You saved $3 in change?
Yeah, you can dust
'em for fingerprints.
-But he never touched them.
-No, but it's his $3.
That's gotta help somehow, right?
Captain, we've got a problem.
What?
The toilets in the women's bathroom
aren't working.
-What do you mean not working?
-They're clogged.
Don't look at me.
So, we have no working
toilets in the barn?
Right.
-You call maintenance?
-Can't send someone 'till tomorrow.
-Call a plumber.
-Who's gonna pay for it?
Use my credit card.
Just get someone down here.
Buddy!
Imagine meeting you here.
Excuse me?
You remember me. Vic.
Your best friend from Boston?
I've never been to Boston.
Come on!
Come on, Ted.
You remember,
we went to high school together.
-Give me my wallet! I don't know you!
-Right.
Now you're about to
tell me you weren't...
...about to go into that sex club.
-Sex club? That's a sex club?
-Yeah, Ted.
Members only.
And tonight, I'm your guest.
Thanks for taking me
on such short notice.
Ted is one of our best clients.
We like to keep him happy.
Sounds like you do a
great job of that.
Will you be watching
or taking part tonight, Vic?
Watching. I like to test the
waters before I jump in.
You'll be watching Sun-Lee tonight.
Excellent.
MRS. Afterwards,
we have tapes if you're interested.
I'm sure I will be.
I won't pull any punches.
She's critical.
She? You mean the pipes?
You eat well?
Get a physical once a year?
-Flush out your pipes regularly?
-I see where you're going.
Right, maintaining a healthy
sewage system is no different.
-Can you get them working or not?
-I'll see what I can do.
Why have you been making noises
about contacting IAD?
-Who told you that?
-You think word wouldn't get out?
It was just a question.
Why do you want IAD?
'Cause I saw something.
-Saw what?
-You don't want to know.
Forget about the "what," then.
Who are you talking about?
You know what?
I'm not talking about anyone.
The more I say,
the less people wanna listen.
People here prefer to
cover things up...
...and hope I'll just shut up
and go away.
What about my wallet?
I ever see you within
five blocks of here,...
...your wife will get a
very unpleasant call.
Screw!
-Hello?
-Yo, Billy.
It's Vic.
I'm sorry to call you so late.
Look, I got a probable cause
for a no-knock warrant.
What was that all about?
I saw what I saw. I
just can't let it lie.
Goddamn it.
You don't know what you're doing here.
-I know right from wrong, Captain.
-I told you to let this go.
I may answer to you,
but I also have to answer to God.
And I will never be at peace with Him
or myself if I turn my back on this.
You think you really want to do this?
Because here's
what's gonna happen.
Most cops here will treat
you like a traitor.
You're gonna take more shit
than you've ever taken before!
You're gonna be testifying
against Vic Mackey, and trust me...
...he doesn't care if
God is on your side.
Are you ready for that kind of heat?
I'll have to be.
Warrant! Police!
Get against the wall, hands up!
Down! Get on your knees right now!
Get down on the ground on your knees!
On your knees! Get in line!
Come on, girls! What's wrong with you?
-Line up on your knees!
-Where are the tapes?
Come on, hurry up!
Hurry up!
"Cherry Popper Films"?
Boy, you really take the cake,
don't you, lady?
Come on, back up!
All right then, let's go!
Come on, now.
Vic!
What do you want to do with the girl?
Keep her in the clubhouse for now.
Where the hell are
Shockley and Peters?
Robbery-homicide call.
What? Come on!
They're supposed to be going over
witness statements for me.
It's a robbery-homicide, Dutch.
Look out!
For God's sake!
Wait, get the files.
Jesus. Get my files and the Rolodex!
Get what you can!
Put it on your desks.
Come on!
Get me that other file over there!
Which one? This one?
You got a big problem
with these pipes.
Just what I need.
A goddamn flood in my workspace.
-I made a quick profile of our killer.
-What do you got?
Our unsub's late 20s, early 30s.
Sporadic employment,
feels unappreciated, worthless.
Why does he pose them face down?
Symbolizes the domination
he yearns for.
He's probably impotent, though.
At least with a live girl.
Dutch, we got a hit off the flyer!
Tipster says he saw a guy with Sally
in a green vehicle.
-We get the caller's address?
-Right here.
Yes.
Tom Ross.
The flyer said that this
would be confidential.
How'd you get my address?
Tip line's routed through 911.
If this guy's a killer,
I don't want him coming after me.
Your name doesn't
leave this room, Tom.
-Just tell us what you saw.
-Okay.
Basically I was out
last night driving...
...and I was stopped at a light
behind this green car.
There was a guy driving and it seemed
that he was having a struggle...
...with a girl in the passenger seat.
The girl from the flyer?
I think so.
I was behind them, but...
...it looked weird enough
that I wrote the license plate down.
Did you notice
if one of his taillights was broken?
I think so.
Yeah.
Run this plate,
cross-reference with the owner.
-Give me a DMV photo.
-Computers are down.
What?
They had to unplug
them due to the flood.
Goddamn it.
Then call Central, have them run
the plate number, fax over a photo.
The fax machine's unplugged, too.
Then send someone over to Central,
pick up the photo personally.
Who should I send?
Could you just take care of
this thing for me, please?
Each of my workers had
documentation saying they were 18.
-From what, a cereal box?
-I said, I want to see my lawyer.
-What do you got here?
-Busted an underage sex shop.
Looks like a cherry popper ring, too.
Cherry popper?
Preteen girls losing their virginity.
The filmmaker's next on my hit list.
What's the connection to Sally?
She worked there a
couple of months ago.
A couple of months ago?
How does that help
me with last night?
It doesn't.
So you've just been doing
your own thing on your own time.
Don't chew up my ass just because
your case is coming up short.
You couldn't give me a
little goddamn help...
...with tracking down
the victim's keys?
I was putting a teenage sex show
out of business.
And I'm trying to catch a killer,
asshole!
Jesus Christ.
We gotta watch these,
find out who's behind 'em.
-Man, you gotta be kidding me.
-I know. I can't stomach this shit.
Yell if you find anything.
Hi, Steve.
I'm Detective Wagenbach.
What's going on? Why am I down here?
Your name came up
in an investigation of ours.
Investigation? Of what?
Do you drive a '97
green Saturn, Steve?
Yeah.
Is that a good car?
I guess, yeah.
Reliable?
No problems with it?
I had some work done on the brakes.
What about the taillights?
Taillights?
You got any broken
taillights on your car?
No.
You sure?
I don't think so.
'Cause we checked your car out.
You checked out my car?
Why?
You got a broken right taillight.
Okay.
Hi.
What happen me now?
You get to play blackjack with Vic.
Not in trouble?
Only if you take me for all my money.
Who made you work for Mrs. Park?
Mrs. Park help me.
She pay ticket. $10,000.
She's not helping you.
She help me star in more movies.
19.
You understand that what you did...
...that's not a real movie.
It start, though.
15.
Vic is forced to hit.
10. That's a bust.
You win.
Sun-Lee win?
Yeah.
Were you popular in
high school, Steve?
I had friends.
That's not really the
same thing, is it?
You can always find some other
dork to eat lunch with.
Doesn't make you popular, you know?
Guess not.
The reason I'm curious
about your high school years is...
...you've got a sealed juvie record.
You're not supposed
to know about that.
We know about it. We just don't know
exactly what your crime was.
How about clueing me in?
No.
A little embarrassing, is it?
Either tell me what I'm doing here,
or I'm leaving.
I don't have to tell
you anything, Steve.
Fine. I'm going, then.
You're not going anywhere.
Sunshine. How you doing?
This bathroom emergency thing's
a real nightmare.
Don't worry about it.
High tide's not for a few more hours.
Listen, there's
something you should...
-Forget it.
-No.
Too late. Come on.
-I really shouldn't.
-You're breaking my heart.
I can get fired for telling you.
Not if we keep it
between us, sunshine.
David just had me put
a call in to IAD.
IAD? Goddamn it!
I can't believe he
would do this to you.
It's not me I'm worried about.
I didn't do anything.
I just know that your guy's
already not fitting in.
He makes a mistake like this...
As his training officer,...
...I just don't want any of
that mud sticking to you.
-I'll talk to him.
-Don't be too hard. He's a good kid.
He means well.
He's just confused.
I'm not supposed to talk about it.
-You're going to IAD about Vic?
-It is really none of your business.
You're my partner. It's my business.
Can we just let this rest, please?
Look, Vic is a great cop.
You don't testify against
a fellow officer...
...without looking
them in the eye...
...and hearing their side.
I don't know what your
deal is with him,...
...but it doesn't change
what happened.
You're wrong about Vic.
Give him a chance to explain...
You can't explain stealing evidence!
That's right, Danny.
He stole two bricks of cocaine,
and I saw him do it.
And whether you realize it or not,
you helped him cover it up.
Now stop asking me about this.
The file says you haven't
held a steady job...
...in more than three months, Steve.
-Economy stinks.
-You must be angry.
Nobody likes to feel unappreciated...
...worthless.
I don't feel that way.
No, you're a powerful guy. Where
were you last night around 11:00?
-At home in bed.
-Anyone to corroborate that?
That I was in bed?
I wish.
You wish what?
That there was a girl in your bed?
That you could get it up with a girl?
-What are you talking about?
-What's so private...
...about this sealed
juvie record of yours?
-It's sealed.
-What's hidden?
You're a peeping Tom? A stalker?
Like to kill cats? What?
I broke into my high school.
-I trashed the place.
-Sure, I can see that.
You like to destroy things, don't you?
Dutch!
We just found Sally in one of these
goddamn Cherry Popper tapes. Come on!
While your lawyer's on the way...
...we're gonna have a
little screening party.
We're gonna watch that tape
until one of two things happens.
Either you're gonna tell me
everything you know about Sally...
...or I'm gonna have to turn it off.
But if I have to turn that tape off...
...there are no more rules
in this room.
Turn it off.
I got her from Kurt Schmidt.
He makes the movies.
And how do I find Kurt?
You okay?
That was Sally.
She's a kid.
She was.
-The asshole that made her do that...
-Don't worry.
He's mine.
Good.
Ramirez just called in.
A 14-year-old kid saw the flyer,
says he's Sally's boyfriend.
-Why would someone do that to her?
-That's what we're trying to find out.
You were Sally's boyfriend?
Yeah.
When was the last time you saw her?
Last night. We met at
this ice-cream place.
What time was that?
She left right before 10:00.
Are you sure?
Yeah, that's when her curfew is.
She has to be home by 10:00.
Where did she live?
I never saw her house.
She said her parents were traditional,
didn't let her have boys over.
She was your girlfriend for how long?
A few months...
...but it only started
getting serious last week.
Serious?
That's when she finally kissed me.
She was young,
she wanted to take it slow.
Did you have any idea
what Sally did for a living?
She was a freshman, right?
Hi, Vic. Play cards?
A little later.
Right now, I need you to show
me the guy who made your movie.
How come?
To help me with my case.
I helped you out, right?
You think you could help me out, too?
-Yes.
-Good.
Vic mad at Sun-Lee?
No. Not at you.
You should be with your
family, being a kid.
Which one is he?
He.
That man put me in movie.
I can't talk about it.
Look, I just haven't been a good
listener or a good training officer.
I was scared to believe you.
-Believe him, then.
-No.
I want to believe the truth.
If you just tell me what the truth is,
I promise I'll listen.
So she's at the ice-cream
store here at 9:45.
She heads to work at 10:00.
The fastest way to her corner's here.
Which means she was picked up
somewhere on Cassandra Street.
-Yeah.
-Forget a full confession.
All you have to do is get him to admit
he was on Cassandra at 10:00.
You get him to say that...
...with all the circumstantial
evidence, you got him.
I'll get him to say it.
Ding Dong?
No, thanks.
I think we're almost done here, Steve.
-Kurt Schmidt?
-Yeah?
You're under arrest.
-For what, man?
-Makin' movies!
-Get off me, man! I'm an editor.
-Cherry Popper movies, you sick prick.
You can't prove that.
I got tapes and witnesses, asshole.
The only question left...
...is whether you took a header into
the concrete trying to resist arrest.
-You got a girlfriend, Steve?
-No!
I remember my 20s.
Rough times.
Too old for the college girls,
too young for the mature ones.
What do you mean?
Not being able to get
a date, get laid.
Pisses you off.
Aren't I, like,
entitled to a lawyer or something?
Entitled?
You, entitled?
What about Kitty Weir?
What about Rosita Pedrazo?
What about Mary Esposito?
What about Sheryl Watkins?
What about Sally, Steve?
What were they entitled to?
Don't show me those.
You don't like looking
at your own work?
Is that why you place
'em face down?
So you don't look 'em in the eye
after you kill 'em?
You think I killed those girls?
-I know you killed them, Steve.
-No way!
Fine.
Fine!
You didn't kill 'em.
But at least don't lie to me
about where you were last night.
I'm not!
We have a witness...
...who saw you in your green car...
...on Cassandra Street...
...with the broken taillight...
...at 10:00.
So don't lie to me.
At least tell me the truth
about this one thing.
Witness?
You're not talking about Tom, are you?
Tom?
Yeah.
Tom Ross.
Is he the one who says he saw me?
Jesus. It's Tom, isn't it?
This one just raised the bar.
Raised the bar?
For practical jokes.
It's a prank, man.
We're always trying
to one-up each other,...
...and he probably heard
about these girls...
Dude, man, you scared the
shit out of me with that.
-A prank?
-Shit.
Is Tom here now?
Please tell me he's here.
He's here.
Great. Dude, you gotta do me a favor.
You gotta help me get him back.
When you see him, you gotta act
like you're super-pissed...
...and tell him he's under arrest
for something.
Like...
-Obstruction of justice?
-Perfect.
It was just a joke, man!
The broken light? It was on the
flyer, so I broke Steve's.
-Do you realize what you did?
-Have a sense of humor, dude.
A little girl's killer
is still out there...
...because you're the class clown!
Easy!
Sally's murderer is still out there...
...and I'm standing here
with my xxxx in my hand...
...because this guy
thought it would be funny...
...to rake his buddy over the coals.
All right.
Screw him.
-We've still got time.
-I just wasted seven hours. Gone.
I'm sorry. I gotta take this.
Dutch.
You got a job to do. Do it.
Connie?
Jesus Christ. What happened?
He's the killer maybe, right?
He's an insurance salesman
from Fresno.
-What did you do here?
-He was acting strange.
So you shot him?
I didn't want him to hurt me.
-How much you been smokin'?
-No.
You gotta help me, Vic.
Christ, Connie!
Can't you say that you shot him?
There's at least 10
cops who can place me...
...at the barn when
this went down.
I thought that he was gonna kill me!
That story's not gonna cut it!
I'll lose my son.
Vic! Please!
Think of something!
What is it?
No. Clean yourself up.
I gotta call this in.
You thought of somethin'!
I know you did!
-I'm sorry, Connie. My hands are tied.
-All I have is Brian.
Don't let me lose him.
You'll need a better story.
Okay.
All right, you had sex.
You asked him to pay.
He said he didn't have to pay,
that he was gonna make you pay.
He started hitting you.
He took out his gun.
You fought him off.
You took it and shot him.
Do you have that?
I asked him to pay.
He said he didn't have to,
and he hit me. That's good.
Your friends, they'll believe that?
Only if you have the
bruises to prove it.
Okay.
-I can't.
-It's okay! Come on!
-I can't! No.
-Do it!
-Hit me!
-No.
-Hit me! Come on, hit me!
-No!
Please?
Vic, please.
Please.
Hit me.
So where does that leave us?
We know she disappeared
on Cassandra Street.
So far, no witnesses.
Anything from the park?
I did a full sweep. Nothin'.
-Maybe forensics'll...
-No.
This guy didn't leave any forensics
on the first four victims.
He's only gonna get better,
not sloppier.
Then I'm callin' the rest of the units
off this one.
What?
A huge brawl started
at Council Rock High.
Sixty students from rival schools.
-I need everyone I can get over there.
-You promised me 24 hours.
I'm sorry, Dutch.
I just don't have the bodies.
So a dead hooker gets 21 hours?
What would she get
if she was a mayor's daughter?
Claudette is gonna go
back into rotation.
Now, you show me some new evidence,
clues, a viable lead...
...and then we'll talk.
You're assigning
the same amount of manpower...
...to find a serial killer
as you are to fix our pipes?
Getting mad doesn't
change how life works.
She deserves better.
I know.
You did all you could. It's not over.
I need an aspirin.
Dutch, you're soakin' yourself.
You okay?
Sure.
Dutch, you think
we could find some time to study?
What?
For the sergeants exam.
I feel like I'm, you know,
kind of fallin' behind.
Sure.
Why don't we do that right now?
I'll just drop my pissant serial
killer thing to help you study.
Because what you want always
comes first, doesn't it?
It comes before me,
comes before everybody else here!
Even comes before a dead
13-year-old girl...
...we're all supposed
to just forget about, come tomorrow.
So grab your books.
Let's find a nice, quiet spot!
We'll study for that test right now.
Yeah?
We had sex.
And then I asked, told him to pay.
He said he didn't have to.
That's when he started hitting me.
You did good.
I'm scared.
You're halfway home.
Just tell the detectives
the same thing.
I'm gonna change, Vic.
I'm gonna clean up...
...be a mother to Brian.
It's gonna be okay.
Get clean,...
...change,...
...be a good mother.
I'm gonna do it.
Sun-Lee.
I go now?
I called INS. I'm sending
you back to Korea.
-But you say you help Sun-Lee!
-I am. This is the best thing for you.
You don't know what
like for me there.
I know what it's like here.
Parents never take me back!
If they won't take you,
the authorities will.
You'll be sent to a foster home,
to school. Someone'll look after you.
-Sun-Lee come back. I will!
-Maybe.
But even if it only buys you six
months, I can live with that.
I'm sorry.
Watch your step here.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
She looked like Sally.
Almost was Sally.
Dutch.
You showed me somethin' today.
What do you mean? I failed.
No, you didn't.
We took down
some bad guys doin' some bad stuff.
You did that, not me.
We both did it.
We'll get your guy, too.
Just won't be today.
No, it won't.
Serial cases are a marathon.
It's not sprints.
I remember workin'
the Green River case in 1984.
Forty-nine bodies.
I had 50 times your resources.
1984.
We made our first arrest last year.
Doesn't hurt if you don't let it.
Place should be clear by morning.
Here's your bill.
-$800?
-Yeah. Cash only. I don't take credit.
I'll have to go to an ATM.
No problema, amigo.
I'll be here all night.
Gracias, amigo.
Hey.
What's up?
Did you steal drugs
from those Armenians?
-Not you, too.
-Look, Vic.
I owe you too much to ever repeat
your answer to anyone...
...but if I helped you get away
with it, I gotta know the truth.
Did you steal drugs?
You can ask me this after what
happened the other night?
The goddamn bust of the year...
...and your partner's
got you as mixed up as he is.
Just give me some time to get
things sorted out in my head, okay?
-Danny.
-Please.
I just want some space.
What I said to you...
...was inexcusable.
This case...
...was very important to me.
When I was a kid...
You know what?
At least I had a childhood.
I lived.
It's just pathetic to
complain about it now.
It's even more pathetic
to use it as some kind of excuse.
I don't have an excuse.
I was wrong, and I'm sorry.
Good night.
Dutch.
You hungry?
'Cause I make a mean grilled cheese.