Previously on The Shield:
What are we doing, Vic?
Hey, but we had to.
-Christ, come on.
-Enough, come on.
Terry was gonna turn you in,
Vic wanted him dead.
-Vic needed him dead!
-No!
I know.
Now, Shane, listen to me.
You're gonna ride this out. Right?
Our fellow officer was
dying in that hospital.
-I said a prayer for him.
-Prayer?
Look, I give you some money,
you skip a couple of tricks.
Get yourself some soup.
I don't need your money, Vic.
Here, you look.
Get yourself some soup.
Don't worry about me, Vic.
I get by.
Sure?
Okay, come on. Take your seats.
Today is warrant-sweep day.
I know. We all hate sweeps.
We all hate sweeps.
But as long as they've got open
warrants, we've got to serve them.
You've all been assigned several
suspects. Find them. Bring them in.
If you see one of your regulars,
bring them in too.
We've probably got an open warrant
for them as well.
Word on the street
will spread quickly.
We've only got three
to four hours.
And listen, these are
the worst of the worst.
So watch out for yourself
and your partner.
That's it. Go find them.
These are all over the place.
Hey, anybody got an Echo Park
for a Koreatown?
Here. But you gotta take
Alvarado Corridor too.
Here. Let me see that. Is that Virgil?
Beautiful. Asshole took a swing at me
last time, in front of some kids.
-I got this one.
-Sarge says you got a visitor.
Police! Freeze, sucker!
What's the matter?
You all right?
-He had a knife.
-The john?
Okay, let me see.
-Jesus.
-He seemed normal, you know?
-Yeah.
-Even paid upfront.
I go to put the condom on,
and the asshole...
...he smacks me,
and he tries to rape me.
What?
I know a rape, for chrissake.
All right, what then?
I kicked and scratched
till I got away.
I got some of his licence plate.
I want this prick to hurt.
-Dutch.
-Yeah.
I need a favour.
Connie here had a bad night.
Aceveda dumped a ton of warrants
on my desk. I was wondering...
-You want me to serve them for you?
-No, I'll kick down my own doors.
Can you get her to a hospital,
find out who cut her up?
-Sure. Why don't you come with me.
-I'm fine.
We'll get you patched up. You can
tell me what happened on the way.
Go on. I'll check in...
-Are you coming too?
-Yeah, I'll check in on you later.
Hey, Dutchboy, thanks. I owe you one.
-Freeze! Police!
-Get down!
Get down!
Get down on the floor right now!
-Hey, remember me?
-Yeah, I remember.
On your face.
-I'll tell you what.
-Hands up.
You tell me when these bracelets
get too tight.
Yeah, just like that.
-Yo, man with the tools.
-Hands up!
Put your hands on your head.
Hands on your head. Get out here.
Come on.
-Damn. You're...
-Derrick Tripp.
Derrick Tripp, yeah.
-Jersey's in town to play the Lakers.
-Put your hands back up.
You miss the exit
for the Staples Center?
No, man, I'm just chilling.
Yeah, well chilling with cheebas is
a problem here in L.A. Grab some wall.
Come on, man.
It's just a private party.
That's some party favour.
-I got stalkers.
-Is that right?
-You got a permit for this?
-Left it in Jersey.
Well, that's a shame.
What are we gonna do about this?
Get those geniuses back down
to the Barn.
-All right, let's go. Get up.
-You stay put.
Let's go have some fun.
Check this out.
It's gonna be a zoo
when we haul this guy in.
-Yeah.
-Never liked him.
-He always gives the Lakers fits.
-Not tonight, he won't.
Yeah? Why is that?
How'd you like to change
the course of sports history?
What do you need it for?
We're conducting surveillance
on an apartment across the street.
-How long you gonna be here?
-Out by tonight.
-You gonna break anything?
-Don't plan on it.
It's a bitch to collect from the city,
you know?
Here's a deposit.
-Drop them in the mailbox.
-Appreciate it.
Come on.
What are we doing here?
Keeping you out of the limelight
until we get a handle on this.
Did you do that sneaker
commercial in one take?
No way. That was some CGI mojo.
One take, all real.
You're the man.
Sponsors ain't gonna be too thrilled
to hear about this.
I got a morals clause
in my contracts.
Let me see if I can help you out.
Give me one minute.
-Hello.
-Hi, there, captain. Vic Mackey here.
-What are you up to now?
-I got a problem.
Just arrested Derrick Tripp
on weapons charges.
The basketball player? Exciting.
Right. He's playing against
the Lakers tonight.
We're meeting Matthew's teacher at 7.
Don't forget.
I certainly won't, sir.
Would it help if I dropped off
clothes at work?
-Certainly would.
-Okay, then.
I'll tell him. Lemansky's got
the address.
-Is that it, or should I keep talking?
-That won't be necessary.
I'll see you soon.
Captain's a big fan. He'll come down
here and make this thing go away.
-Cool.
-In the meantime, just chill out.
You, you're nuts, man.
Without Tripp's penetration and
outside shot, the Lakers are a lock.
Damn, I gotta call my bookie.
You know what I love?
I love what you said to that
ref in game six last year.
I had to say something.
That call was weak.
Looked like a foul to me.
Where was you watching it from?
Your 20-inch black-and-white?
Hey. We stopped by Big 5.
How about a couple autographs?
-The captain's on his way, right?
-Any minute now.
I don't usually sign for free.
-You're kidding.
-150 a pop.
-Even little kids?
-People send their kids up to score.
"Derrick, please sign this for me."
Then Daddy turns around
and scalps it on the Internet.
Got that.
Derrick, sign this one
for my son, Matt.
It's on the up and up.
-Yeah, man.
-Cool.
Fifteen million a year, and you
gotta charge for an autograph?
Wouldn't you say that's weak?
The papers print 15 million...
...but after my agent, taxes,
lawyers, publicist...
...and business manager,
15 mil it ain't.
Wow, that's rough.
So, what's that, like 6 million?
-Ain't 15 mil, is it?
-No, it isn't.
So look, I put a call
into Murphy, man.
Spread's six and a half.
Lem and Ronnie are in for a grand
each. I'm in for five. How about you?
-I'll pass.
-Are you kidding?
Nobody knows about this.
It's like free money.
The Lakers can clinch home court
for the playoffs.
It's about...
It's not about the money.
Well, it is to this asshole.
Hundred and fifty a pop. I'm surprised
the guy can sign his own name.
-What do you care?
-I don't.
What are we gonna do about
the rest of our warrants?
Already took care of it.
Vic Mackey called,
told me to turn myself in.
Line forms over there.
Goddamn warrant sweeps.
Problem, Nathan?
I'm one person doing a two-man job.
Look at this.
I know. Fortunately, I have
my MVP running the show.
MVP?
Most valuable policeman.
I wouldn't schedule these sweeps if I
wasn't sure you'd anchor the desk.
You're not gonna let me down, are you?
Of course not, sir.
That's what I wanted to hear.
-Capt. Aceveda?
-Yes.
Marsha Kramer,
attorney for Derrick Tripp.
The basketball player?
No hits on killers raping hookers
at knifepoint.
What about the partial plate?
The one our bag-bride scribbled on
her hand while running for her life?
Six hundred matches. I'll have
her look at every single one.
Hooker murders are up
for the entire East Side.
Past few show some similarities.
You're studying killings
on the entire East Side?
The whole city. You never know
when a disturbing pattern will emerge.
I think I'm witnessing
a disturbing pattern.
I wanna make sure
nothing slips through.
You're just looking for something
big and juicy.
Three months ago, Griffith Park,
beaten with a pipe.
Six weeks ago, Eagle Rock,
strangled by hand.
Two weeks ago, liquor-store dumpster,
choked with a rope.
Different locations, different
weapons. Some pattern.
They're all posed facedown.
You're stretching, son. Try yoga.
Connie was supposed to be victim
number four. We need a task force.
You need more evidence than that.
I'm taking it to Aceveda.
All he's gonna do is say no.
No.
Let's find the guy
who attacked Connie,...
...try to tie him to
the other murders.
Sounds like a plan.
Please, this is a mistake.
Where have I heard that before?
-Got another one for you, Nathan.
-I see that.
Hey, excuse me, excuse me.
-Haven't I seen you hanging around?
-Step back.
No, I have, haven't I?
Hanging around outside The Abbey.
-Abbey?
-You know, West Hollywood.
-How come you never go in? It's fun.
-You've got the wrong guy.
Whatever you say, officer.
Stand back and wait in line.
I told you, he's not here.
I gave you a description.
Why can't Vic take care of this?
We're helping you, hon. Keep looking.
Hey, wait.
That's him.
-That's the asshole.
-William Greeley.
"Trespassing on federal grounds
as part of an environmental protest.
Three years ago. Charges dismissed."
Not exactly a criminal mastermind.
You sure?
Of course I'm sure.
I'll call for a warrant.
So you and Vic are...
...friends?
Interesting.
Vic and me have a bond
that transcends sex.
Don't move!
Police! Freeze!
What is this?
-William Greeley.
-Yeah.
Put some clothes on, man.
Bolt cutters!
Hey, stay out of there!
You got no right!
You wanna bet on how many heads
he's got icing down in there?
No, thanks.
It's not mayonnaise.
You keep away from my children!
No!
Vic? Vic, a word, please.
Sure.
-Who's your friend?
-This is Marsha Kramer...
...an attorney representing
Derrick Tripp.
Mr. Tripp was last seen
in your custody.
We served a warrant
to one of his homeboys.
He was there. The drugs weren't his.
He was freed.
He was a good guy,
signed a couple autographs.
-Something wrong?
-Tripp is missing.
-Missing?
-He's not answering his cell phone.
His friends, family, teammates,
management, me...
No one has heard from him.
Weird.
Virgil Lewis said that it looked like
you were taking Mr. Tripp somewhere.
Is this the same Virgil Lewis I busted
sucking on a joint as big as your arm?
I think Virgil's memory might be
a little hazy.
I left Tripp a while ago.
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
-This is totally unacceptable.
-Vic.
They stitch you up okay?
Between this and my caesarean,
I'm a goddamn road map.
-Jesus Christ.
-Those detectives won't let me leave.
I gotta go see somebody, soon.
All right, calm down.
Go back there and chill out. I'll
find out what's going on, all right?
Go on.
I'd never hurt anyone.
-What kind of work do you do, William?
-I was an actuary.
What about now?
I walked away six months ago.
Needed some time off?
Pressure getting to you?
Well, it's easy to lose your
perspective working every day.
What does this have to do
with anything?
What do you do for fun
with that free time?
-I have some hobbies.
-I know. Nice sperm collection.
Well, thank you.
Jag?
-Nope.
-Rolls?
Please. Lamborghini.
Sure, that's a sweet ride.
Where the hell's this captain?
Should be here within the hour.
I ain't waiting no hour.
Where do you think
you're going, sport?
This captain's kicking
the charges anyway.
I'll leave him will-call tickets
for the game.
-You're staying here.
-See, this meeting's too big.
-I ain't gonna miss it.
-Who's it with?
One of my little L.A. Honeys I bang
when I'm in town.
Maybe she would prefer
conjugal visits.
Hey, bring her on down here, man.
There's a bedroom.
What? It'll help pass the time
till the captain shows.
If the men's room at Spago's worked
for her, I guess this will do.
-You're a real classy guy.
-Here.
Here, yo, use my cell phone.
-Where were you last night?
-Home.
Anyone vouch for that?
-I live alone.
-You go out?
-Yeah.
-Where?
Well, you know, maybe I didn't go out.
I don't really remember.
-Well, which is it, William?
-What about December 15?
Were you out then?
I don't know. Probably at home.
-What about February 5?
-Home.
Always home. Filling up those jars
is a full-time gig?
Back to last night...
The name Kitty Weir mean anything?
She was a streetwalker on Sunset.
I don't know what you're saying.
-Dutch.
-March 3, Rosita Pedraza...
...on Cesar Chavez.
You killed her too, didn't you?
-Dutch!
-I'd never kill anyone. I'm pro-life.
Jesus Christ.
You're all over the map.
This freak's straight out
of an FBI textbook.
What happened to the original plan?
Nail him for last night's assault,
use it as a building block.
Classic façade of innocence and
charm with bizarre sexual fetishes.
This kind wants to talk.
I have to lead him down the path.
Trust me, his ego won't
let him shut up.
-Could we close this one case, please?
-I mean, Ted Bundy, anyone?
The attack on the hooker comes first.
Dutchboy, I asked you to find
Connie's john...
-...not Jack the Ripper.
-You're observing me?
Fred Astaire never danced
around so much.
-Let me see if I can jog his memory.
-No. You tried that with me once.
Not again.
Now, you asked Dutch for help,
you got it. We'll get the guy.
Don't make me regret it.
Hey, Connie.
They got your guy.
You gonna let me watch?
-Watch what?
-You kick the shit out of him.
I think we'll have to settle
for jail time.
I want him to feel the pain I felt.
-Look, why don't you come lie down.
-I can't lie down!
You know what?
I have to get out of here.
I have a need, all right?
The detectives need you to stay around
to contradict any statement he makes.
Now stay in here, and I'll take care
of your need. Got it?
Yeah.
Just stay here, okay?
Hey, hon.
Hey, little man. There he is.
Come here.
Who was that?
It's a case I'm working on.
Got my clothes?
Thanks.
Hey, Matthew, what a treat
to see Daddy during the day.
Let's hope we get to see him
tonight?
-Hope so.
-Hey, I can't miss that.
Gotta see little man's teacher
and talk to her.
You know, we've got a play date.
Okay. Thanks for the fresh cape.
Let's go help Mommy outside.
Come on.
Derrick here?
Shane Vendrell.
So he's here or...?
Yeah.
Where?
Hey, girl.
God, I missed you.
Save it for Spago's.
When are you gonna get traded
to a West Coast team?
I'm here now, ain't I?
Go get the sheets warmed up.
Okay.
-Be right in.
-Okay.
Damn. That is, like, the hottest chick
that's ever been, man.
Her? Please, dog. Adriana's a par.
I got this one in Seattle,
a goddamn birdie.
She's probably spread her legs
for half the league.
It's too bad you can't make
a jump shot.
Hope y'all got your earplugs.
I'm going in.
He's pretty confident.
I'll be over here.
-O for two.
-How many warrants left?
Counting this no-show, one more.
Neighbour here makes
quite the racket.
She says she's gonna call us
when he gets back.
Who's up?
Felipe Tejada.
-Officer.
-What?
I really need your help.
All right, just give me five seconds.
Why?
Look, I'm sorry about
what I said before.
You've got three seconds left.
Okay. I passed a bad check. I paid
the fine. I got a suspended sentence.
This warrant is a mistake. All you
gotta do is call my legal-aide guy.
That would take another five seconds.
Please. Look at me.
And now look at the
other guys in here.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Stand back.
Gotta be careful with these guys.
They're all a bunch of con men.
This is a nightmare.
I'd never hurt anyone, let alone rape.
I don't even use prostitutes.
I don't have to. Women need me.
-Really?
-Yeah, it's a fact.
Survival of the species.
Meaning what?
Well, men find large
breasts attractive.
They signify that a woman can
amply nourish her young.
Conversely, women respond
to some of my assets.
Well, I've seen you butt-naked, son.
-Your assets don't impress.
-No, no, no, no.
You see, penis size is overrated.
I'm talking about my testes,
the true seed of male virility...
...the engine that drives the train.
I am packing a pair
you gotta see to believe.
Found an old girlfriend.
Greeley's got a hair-trigger temper...
...and an inoperable brain tumour
driving him schizo.
That explains a few things.
Doesn't explain why he's dumping
the bodies facedown.
Will you forget
about making a name...
...for yourself as a
serial-killer hunter?
We need to corroborate
the hooker story. Period.
He wants to tell us.
-Can't this wait? I'm right out front.
-Yeah?
Yeah, well, listen to this crap.
God.
Any word from the captain?
No.
Call him again. I'm almost done here.
Baby.
The only reason he has
any teeth left is...
...that I'm making a
killing on this thing.
-I upped my bet to 10 grand.
-Later.
Vic? Vic.
No! Give me my Evan!
He's fine! Please! My baby!
-Guy's a crackhead!
-He's dusted! Evan!
It's cool. Why don't you give me Evan.
No, he's on fire. He's burning up.
He's red-hot!
He's fine! Please!
-I gotta cool him down!
-I'm a doctor. I can cool Evan down.
You don't look like a doctor.
I get that all the time.
Give him to me.
-My baby!
-No, it's too late!
-Don't do that!
-He's dying!
Don't do that!
Come on, man!
Where's the guy?
He's still under.
Nice save, Vic.
These nut-jobs have a way
of finding me. Be careful.
This one tried to strangle me
on the way over here. Come on.
Vic, I need a piece.
All right, hold on, hold on.
Smoke it by the window.
I can't have my office
reeking of rock.
When am I gonna see you again?
You know the drill.
Just remember, Section 101,
red tank top.
How can I miss that body, right?
-Okay.
-See you at the game.
See you.
See you, Adriana.
-She's a sweet girl.
-Well, boys...
...tell the captain he missed me.
Another booty call?
One of your sponsor's Viagra?
Shoot-around's at 5.
You're not going anywhere, Romeo.
-Get this captain on the phone.
-He's not available by phone.
-You said you called him. Where is he?
-Police business. You'll have to wait.
You been yanking me all day?
Sit down.
Ain't no captain coming, is there?
I said, sit down. You're bugging me.
You got your autographs,
a little peepshow.
Game's over. Colour me gone.
Hey, colour you staying, nigger.
You'd love it if I popped you.
Got your name in the papers
right next to mine.
Come on, come on.
Let's hear what my lawyers
have to say about this.
Badge will look real nice
on my mantelpiece...
...right next to my
Rookie of the Year trophy.
-Shane, get off him!
-Come on, come on, come on.
Hey, hey, I said, wait.
Vic, please.
Give me the lighter.
Come on, give it.
Okay, here.
Blow it out the window.
Aceveda.
The hospital just called.
Baby checked out fine.
-Good job.
-Good.
I am curious. You saved that kid
from the same apartment complex...
-...where Tripp was last seen.
-Crazy?
I lost my wallet during the bust,
went back to look for it.
-Some luck.
-Yeah, you're telling me.
There's no smoking in here.
My mistake.
Derrick Tripp's Jersey's
leading scorer.
They'll be hurting without him.
No clue where he is?
Come on, captain, you know
how these rich pricks are.
He's probably got his face
snorkel-deep in some broad's snatch.
Give him a few hours,
he'll come up for air.
You know how these celebrities are.
He's probably with a female admirer.
Give it a few hours. He'll turn up.
Step away.
I made some calls.
The warrant was a mistake.
I apologise on behalf
of the department.
See, that wasn't so tough, now,
was it?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
The only inconvenience is, I'm leaving
without your phone number.
-Excuse me?
-I just meant so that I could...
...thank you for doing me this favour.
Who knows? Maybe I can return
the favour someday.
If so, you know where to find me.
We know about your brain tumour.
No wonder you're angry.
I'm not a killer.
William, tell me more
about your sperm.
So many people waste it.
With condoms...
...masturbating indiscriminately.
It's a holocaust.
So you collect it?
My tumour may render me
impotent one day.
And with so many women needing me...
You'll still be able
to impregnate them.
I want my essence to be passed
on to the next generation.
Who doesn't?
I know I do.
Can you give me a second, sport?
-No.
-It's okay, Dutch.
It's not okay by me.
Come on, buddy.
Help me out here.
We need our privacy.
Have a seat. I didn't see your name...
-...among the sergeant's applicants.
-Well, I've been putting it off.
Don't. If you pass, you'll get
my recommendation.
You'll receive a
post immediately...
...instead of waiting on
a list for months.
Why the big endorsement?
I'd like you in a leadership position.
You mean you'd like to promote
a woman.
It's not how you get there. It's what
you do once you have the chance.
-I'm offering you the chance.
-I'll think about it.
So I saw the bad-check writer
was released.
For all his whining,
turns out it was a mistake.
But you had to go and check
that out. He got to you.
-No, I just believed him.
-Well, don't make it a habit.
You do favours for these guys,
it comes back to bite you in the ass.
Yeah?
-Ricky Harris?
-Yeah?
Come with us.
We have a warrant for your arrest.
Yes.
No problem. All right?
Just give me a second.
Damn it!
Pull that stuff up.
Get that stuff out.
-Hurry up.
-Is it okay if we come in?
Yeah...
You mind if we take a look around?
There's nothing here.
Let me see your hands.
Put them on top of your head.
-You got any drugs in here?
-No, I'm clean.
-Who are your buddies?
-Nobody.
Come on, look, I'm ready.
Let's just...
Tattoo man, what are you doing
by that couch?
-Just standing.
-Yeah?
-Go stand over there.
-I'm not doing anything.
-You heard me. Move.
-I thought you wanted him.
One Tango 13, requesting backup.
30151 l2 Sutter.
Everybody's cool. Let's just go.
Tattoo man, you heard me.
Get over there.
Don't you dare move!
I will blow your brains out!
Get on the floor! On your stomachs.
Put your hands behind your head.
Move it. Check the couch.
Whatever he's got in there,
I got nothing to do with.
Shut up.
One Tango 13, code three.
What good's your 15 million now,
asshole?
-It's only six take-home.
-Shut up.
-What's going on?
-This guy's totally out of control.
I hope you hate your jobs.
They're about to disappear.
Thinks he's goddamn Shaka Zulu.
When you can fill 20,000 seats
at 200 a pop...
...you'll get the cash and tail.
Until then, drag your lily-white ass
back home to Simi Valley.
Hey, I live in Hollywood,
you mother...
Come here.
-Christ, what's the matter with you?
-What?
The guy resisted.
Resisted what? I told
you to babysit...
Somebody needs to teach him a lesson.
By doing what? Executing him?
Well, why not?
I mean, isn't that what we do now?
I told you, that's over.
We killed a cop.
Lem and Ronnie failed to clear
the room, and Two-Time killed Terry.
Get over it and don't
bring it up again.
Your partner's very uptight.
He overcompensates.
He could learn a lot from you.
You're very maternal.
You have kids, don't you?
Two.
-Boys?
-Girls.
I knew that.
They still at home?
One's a schoolteacher.
The other's a newspaper reporter.
-You see them much?
-Not as much as I'd like.
You ever think about having more?
Well, it would have to be soon.
I'd have to find the right man.
What's he like?
Compassionate, responsible...
-...honest.
-I'm those things.
What if I told you
I could give you a son?
Where were you last night?
If I don't spread my seed,
it dies with me.
You found a prostitute?
Come on, Will.
If we're gonna make this step...
...you gotta show me that you're...
...the type of man who's gonna take
responsibilities for his actions.
Isn't that what a good father is?
She tried to put a condom on me.
Why would she do that?
So you cut her?
I never had to do that before.
Before?
There were other women?
How many?
I wanna trust you.
You'll make 12.
You raped them to spread your seed?
After they're pregnant,
they'll forgive me.
The prostitutes, did you kill them?
No. God, no.
I spread life, not death.
-Okay.
-So when can you and I consummate?
-That's not gonna happen.
-You promised me something.
You may have thought you heard that,
but I didn't say it.
Yes, you did, right here.
You promised me a baby.
You give me that xxxxx!
That's mine, damn it!
-Give it to me now!
-Get off me!
My balls.
You all right?
The bigger they are...
-So no serial killer?
-I don't know.
If there is one, it wasn't him.
-Heard about your gun bust. Nice.
-The wait for backup was...
...the longest two minutes in my life.
It always is. Still,
you kept your cool.
Aceveda wants me to take
the sergeant's exam.
I suck at tests.
I get so much grief for being a woman
in this place. I can't not pass.
-It's not that hard.
-For you maybe.
Hey, could you tutor me?
I could dust off my old notes.
-All right, get out.
-Get out?
I don't even know where
the hell we are.
-That's your problem.
-You're an asshole.
Yeah? Well, that's my problem.
-My lawyers are gonna make sure...
-You're gonna keep your mouth shut.
Your homeys are still in custody.
One visit to the evidence room, and
that ounce of weed becomes a pound.
Play any road games in San Quentin?
-You done with me yet?
-Tell me something.
Why would you risk everything,
slumming with those losers?
They was my boys before I made it.
Who else am I supposed to trust now?
The fans?
-You?
-Listen, if they were your boys...
...you'd pull them up instead
of letting them drag you down.
Take the subway three stops down
to the Staples Center.
That's Derrick Tripp.
Can I get your autograph?
Isn't that that basketball player?
Check him out, man.
We certainly hate to lose you, Nathan.
It's the end of an era.
I guess I just lost that edge.
Of course, I'll give two weeks.
Not necessary, really.
I need to train my replacement.
I have a system tracking suspects
from processing to the cage that...
Nathan, we'll manage...
...somehow.
Hey.
I heard you gave sperm boy
a nice whack.
I could use a good ass-kicker
on my squad.
-Be careful.
-Hey, thanks.
We wouldn't have gotten him
if it weren't for Dutch.
Yeah, but you were the closer.
You all right?
Let's go.
Hi.
At the station, you implied
that I was gay.
-Aren't you?
-No.
I'm not.
-I know what you mean.
-You do?
Sure.
I wasn't gay either, until the day
I just admitted that I was.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's safe.
The class loves to paint.
-Cleanup's always the problem.
-I've seen it.
Thanks again for the art supplies.
-I got them on sale.
-The kids had a ball.
Excuse me, we're here
for a reason, right?
Of course. Sit down.
I'm concerned about Matthew.
He's not socializing properly.
He's a little shy.
He'll grow out of it.
I'm afraid it's more
than just being shy.
Matthew's way behind
the other children.
So he's not Michelangelo. So what?
What I'm trying to say is,
I think there's a problem.
-What kind of problem?
-I can't tell you exactly.
Well, who could tell us exactly?
I think it's something that
a developmental paediatrician...
...should diagnose.
A neurologist, maybe.
Trampling New Jersey, 101 to 78...
...clinching home-court advantage...
...throughout the playoffs
for the Lak ers.
Kobe Bryant had a game-high
35 points. Shaq chipped in with 29.
Derrick Tripp was a no-show
after getting stuck in traffic...
...returning from a charity event.
Only in L.A.