Previously on The Shield:
Mr. Esteana claims you used
excessive force during his arrest.
Fourth complaint since I came here.
You don't like the timetable,
you take it up with Gilroy.
In this building, I'm in charge.
Maybe in your own mind, amigo.
But in the real world,
I don't answer to you.
Not even on Cinco de Mayo.
-What's your take on Vic Mackey?
-I don't judge other cops.
Mackey's not a cop.
He's Al Capone with a badge.
The guy I saw Mackey talking to
is a drug dealer named...
Named Rondell Robinson.
You suggesting
Mackey's working for a dealer?
I'm suggesting
he's working for Mackey.
-Who's he?
-Moses Hernandez. He's in Justice.
We're talking about a case that puts
Mac behind bars for a along time.
What are you getting out of this?
I just want a dirty
cop off the streets.
It's all about trust,
then why did he end up dead?
Yeah.
Knock knock who's there?
Strike Team, Mr. Drug Dealer.
And on top of that, Terry here
is losing his cherry tonight.
He's coming with us.
-911. What's your emergency?
-I've got an officer down!
-Could you repeat that?
-This is Detective Vic Mackey!
-An officer's down!
-You have an officer down.
The goddamn police radio
in the van isn't working.
-What's the officer's condition?
-Condition? He's dying!
-We're in a...
-I have the address.
-Where are we?
-An ambulance is en route.
I'm coming!
Detective?
He was about 10, 15 feet
in front of me and Shane...
...when I hear this gunshot,
and I see Terry go down.
Jesus.
Shane and I turn the corner, and we
see the guy in this back bathroom.
He gets off a few rounds.
We hit back.
At least you killed the prick.
Hey.
Terry's a tough son of a bitch.
He's gonna be okay.
What happened?
-Terry's down?
-Yeah.
-How is he?
-Took a head shot.
Yeah.
I didn't clear the room.
I was point. The first thing
you do is clear the room.
We both missed him.
At 1:29 a.m.,
Detective Terry Crowley...
...was admitted for a single
gunshot wound to the face.
Surgeons made...
...every attempt to resuscitate him.
Shit.
Ultimately,
their attempts were unsuccessful.
Detective Crowley was pronounced dead
at 2:13 this morning.
No!
Damn.
I'm responsible.
Responsible how?
It was my operation,
and I called the shots.
What could you have done differently?
Terry asked me to move him up.
-He was part of your team.
-He wasn't ready for this.
Eight years as a cop,
a stint in robbery, two commendations.
-Sounds to me like he was ready.
-Strike Team's different.
Really?
We knock down the doors
other cops don't want to.
My guys accept the risk because
they know I will take care of them.
We go out on a mission, I expect
every single one of them to come home.
Anything else is unacceptable.
-Why so long?
-They're asking questions.
Yeah, how many questions
can they have?
How would it look if I.A.D.
only took five minutes to decide?
They have to be thorough.
Aceveda's gonna use
this to shut us down.
Aceveda's a water boy.
He can't do dick.
Why is it taking him so long?
This is the last time.
I answered your question.
-Detective Vendrell.
-Yeah, that's me.
Just tell them what happened.
Yeah.
-What are you doing back here?
-Not our crime scene anymore.
-I.A.D. gave us a friendly shove.
-You didn't shove back?
Assistant Chief Gilroy gave the order.
-Gilroy? He's there?
-He was.
I don't like spending five hours
getting evidence for someone else.
Are we on this case, or aren't we?
David.
Sir.
Your office?
Thanks for your good work
this morning, Claudette.
It hasn't been wasted.
No, just our time.
Sir.
Where the hell were you last night?
What do you mean?
Detective Crowley got shot.
I left you a message.
Yeah, I got it.
So?
You didn't say I had to come down.
I shouldn't have to. A fellow
officer was dying in that hospital.
I said a prayer for him.
-A prayer?
-Yeah.
What?
I've been on the job for three weeks,
I didn't even know that guy.
Rule number one, he was a cop.
That means you knew him.
Two deaths, two investigations.
David, please. You can't have your
cops investigating your cops.
If you clear the Strike Team,
that's gonna smack of favoritism.
If you actually find something,
you'll have a civil war on your hands.
Let Internal Affairs do their job.
Has anyone sent Department sympathies
to Crowley's family?
I spoke to his mother an hour ago.
Someone from our side
should speak at the funeral.
-Perhaps you...
-No. He was your man.
I'm sure you'll represent us well.
You're the first
Mackey brought aboard...
...when he assembled the Strike Team.
-We worked things together.
-So there was a comfort level.
-Yeah.
-Same with the others?
-Vic knew them, too.
-Detective Crowley?
No, he was recommended by someone.
I don't recall who.
So Terry was an outsider?
No, he was a new guy,
but once Vic puts you on the team...
...then you're on the team.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Strike Team's getting
the third degree.
Yeah, looks like it.
You're assigned the
crime scene, right?
We're off it now.
The guys are curious.
I said I'd find out what's going on.
Any idea?
Looks to me like Vic
and his cowboys...
...went in undermanned
with a half-ass plan...
...and managed to get a guy killed.
Then again, I'm off the case.
Later, okay?
Tell him this is L.A.,
not the Wild West.
-I'd know those fingernails anywhere.
-How you holding up?
I lost a guy. I don't like it.
-I saw you at the hospital last night.
-I saw you, too.
-You had a crowd. I didn't want...
-It's all right.
Look, I don't want
you to think that...
I don't.
If you need a break from all this
and want to talk, come find me.
That's good to know.
Anytime someone kills a cop...
...scumbags get it into their heads
that it's open season.
-Police rule number...
-Three.
Cop goes down, we re-establish
our dominance on the street.
Someone mouths off,
they hit the pavement.
Someone resists,
we make sure they make a pit stop...
...at the emergency room.
We gotta make sure these assholes
know who's in charge. Right?
Loud and clear.
What happened to your hand?
I put it through a window.
Last night during the raid?
No. After, when I found
out about Terry.
Is it all right?
Yeah.
Cut up pretty bad, though.
Any tendon damage?
Can we just get this
the hell over with, please?
Mackey sent Terry to get killed.
You don't know that.
Please.
Cops get killed in the line of duty.
Did you tell anyone
Terry was trying to take down Mackey?
Did you?
-David...
-I didn't, and Terry's dead.
I followed protocol.
Protocol.
Things that Terry
wanted, a job, a car,...
...I'm not authorized
to sign off on.
-So you broke the circle.
-I sent his requests up the ladder.
-This is the Justice Department.
-So they can be trusted?
-I've got to go to I.A.D.
-Why?
To let them know
exactly why Mackey wanted Terry dead.
-You can't do that.
-They'll let him walk, Moses.
If they have motive,
they'll dig deeper.
You initiated an
off-the-books...
...investigation into
one of your own men.
You come forward, your career's dead.
We sent Terry to his own death.
What am I supposed to do?
What do you hope to accomplish?
It won't prove that Vic set Terry up.
You'll lose the power you've
worked your whole life to acquire.
I'm not gonna let him
get away with it.
There is an epitaph
for an unknown soldier that goes:
"Do not stand on my grave and weep.
For I am not there, I do not sleep."
"With my brothers in the field,
I kneel.
Their lives, my merit.
"My death, their zeal."
I believe these words do express...
...the sentiments
of Detective Terry Crowley.
A good man and an
exemplary police officer...
...who served his community
and his department...
...with dignity, loyalty, and courage.
In the brief time that I was
fortunate enough to work with him...
...I came to know him
as a man who embraced life...
...adored his friends and family...
...and loved being a cop.
"I am the resurrection and the light."
"He that believeth in me."
"Even though he were dead."
"Yet, shall he live."
-Amen.
-Yes, Lord.
"The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want."
"He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures."
"He leadeth me beside
the still waters."
We will miss his service
and his good nature.
And I know I speak on behalf of
the entire force when I say...
...Terry, our lives are your merit...
...and your memory gives us zeal.
"He leadeth me beside
the still waters."
"He restoreth my soul."
"Yea, though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death."
"I will fear no evil."
"For thou art with me."
"Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me."
Fire!
-Baby, I'm sorry! Mama's sorry!
-It's all right, now.
-Mama's sorry, baby!
-It's gonna be all right.
What are you doing?
-What?
-Save it for the car ride, Shane.
What's the matter with you?
I didn't expect to see
his mother here...
He had a mom. So what?
So what did we do?
What we had to.
-Christ, come on, man.
-Enough. Come on.
I'm cold, man.
Look, we made him one of us,
and what did he do?
-What did he do?
-He turned rat.
He tried to stick us both in a cage...
...with the same goddamn animals
we fight every day.
Now, did I enjoy it? No.
Did it need to be done?
You're goddamn right it did.
Now, listen to me...
...we're gonna ride this out. Right?
I'm so sorry for your loss.
-Sir, step back.
-It's cool. I called you.
-Step away from the body.
-I need the money he owes me.
Don't make me warn you again.
-He's got my cash.
-I'm not gonna warn you again.
-I need the money he owes me.
-What'd she say?
-Let's go!
-What?
I'm a good Samaritan here!
What were you doing to the body?
I heard he had the $100 he owed me...
...so I come here
and see somebody shot him!
So I went down the block
and called for 911...
...and come back here to get my money.
Jesus, Julien, this guy's still alive.
This is 1-Tango-13.
I need a R.A. to respond.
Keep fighting, man!
Keep fighting!
I'll collect from you later!
Let's go.
Shane barely touched his pork chops.
I don't think he's doing well.
He's gonna be fine.
He don't seem fine.
It hasn't even been a week yet.
I'm coming, sweetie.
It's like he blames himself
for the whole thing.
It's not normal.
I mean, it's not like he killed Terry.
Ace of clubs.
I'm sitting poolside
with this guy named Frank...
-Transvestite?
-He's buying drinks.
That ugly one?
Yeah, the guy that I
always hang out with.
-50 years old!
-You gotta be joking me!
You holding out on me, Shane?
I got the fresh meat.
This here's Terry.
He comes to us from Robbery.
-Robbery?
-You mean, like, the fag squad, man?
They ran out of fresh asses
over there...
...so I figured I'd try you
prom queens on for size.
If you're looking for fresh asses,
I'd cross Shane off your list.
Stop it, mister. Stop it!
It looks like it'll be a blast
to run with you guys.
-Just make sure you keep up.
-I'll try.
Don't let these pussies
haze you too bad either.
We love you pretty boys from Robbery.
-Know how to play pitch?
-No.
You bring your wallet?
Don't let them stick you with Shane.
He always loses.
-'Cause you're cheaters.
-And he's a crybaby.
-You're all...
-Shut up!
Don't trust one of these guys.
You know what?
He's the worst player in here.
To infinity and beyond!
Okay, Captain Infinity...
...let's get you ready for school.
Come on.
Body was over there. We found one
shell casing a few feet away.
How's the victim?
Paramedic says
he's swirling down the drain.
-Who said that? Randy?
-Yeah.
Sounds like Randy. Cynical bastard.
Does the rookie ever talk?
Yeah, he talks.
-What does this tell you?
-Ma'am?
You're our first eyes and ears
on a crime scene.
What does this one tell you?
Overturned carts, footprints,
clear sign of a struggle.
Actually, the struggle occurred
after we arrived.
A guy was going through
the victim's pockets.
After repeated requests to stop,
I pulled him off the body.
Knocking over the churro cart
and getting sugar spread all over?
Yes, ma'am.
Actually, it was my fault.
I should've...
I hope this isn't the way you teach a
trainee how to preserve a crime scene.
This is how murderers go free, son.
Don't take it hard. She's in a pissy
mood 'cause it's her birthday.
Did we...
Is this scheduled?
No.
Frances came by
to give me her preliminary report.
I wanted you to get a
sneak peek at it, too.
We wrapped up the interviews.
I'll fast-track ballistics...
...and get you a final copy
in the next couple of weeks.
Bottom line, it wasn't
a model operation,...
...but it wasn't a crime, either.
Vic and his boys look
okay on this one.
Really?
The drug-dealer's girlfriend
confirms the team's account.
She puts the gun that
killed Crowley...
...in the dealer's hands
seconds before the shooting.
Thanks for the fast work, Frances.
She must be good.
Two men killed,
a dozen rounds fired...
...no ballistics,
and she's already making her call.
It's a preliminary report, David.
I just don't want us accused
of whitewashing anything.
The last thing we need...
...is another chapter
in the Rodney King-O.J. book.
I don't wanna be a chapter
in that book, either.
I'll make sure she doesn't
get lazy on this one, okay?
It was a great eulogy, by the way.
It was very nice.
-If my dad dies, it's all my fault.
-Why's that?
Dad wanted me to go to college
around here. Live at home.
He's a vendor.
He doesn't make much money.
But I wanted Stanford.
I had gotten a scholarship,
but it didn't cover everything.
There was still books, housing.
When he found out,
he said if that was my dream...
...he'd make it happen.
That's when he stopped paying.
-Stopped paying what?
-Protection money.
This bully in the neighborhood
made all the vendors pay.
-My father wasn't licensed, so...
-So he didn't go to the police.
I told him he couldn't
stop paying the guy...
...but he said it was
the only way I could go to Stanford.
He was so proud when I had gotten in.
I begged him to pay the money, but...
The thug that did this to my dad...
...can you guys really get him?
We can try. Who is he?
His name's Marlon Demrall.
-Marlon Demrall?
-Yeah. So?
-You need to come with us.
-Thanks, but I'll pass.
You can go peacefully or not.
Let's go.
How 'bout I don't go at all?
What's the emergency, brother?
Questioning in a shooting.
-When?
-Today.
I didn't shoot nobody today.
-What're you doin' to him?
-Come on, man.
Get the camcorder!
They're taking Marlon away!
-What is wrong with you?
-Stay inside.
-Let him go. He didn't do it.
-He's my son's father!
I didn't shoot nobody.
Right, yeah. You didn't do anything.
You a brother?
Or did you become one of them?
Look at what you're
doing to a brother!
-He's not my brother.
-Let go!
Mama! Get the camcorder!
They're taking Marlon!
You got nothin' to do today?
He did not...
You ain't nothin' but a Uncle Tom!
Uncle Tom?
That's right. If the Oreo
wrapper fits, wear it, brother.
Shut up.
Don't go making it black
and white, Marlon.
Take pictures!
Smile for the camera!
Goddamn cops!
But I'm like, where am
I supposed to find...
...a dental dam at
2:00 in the morning?
What's a dental dam?
It's a rubber for your mouth
when you go down on a chick.
Are you serious?
If you need a dental dam,
I gotta question what your face...
...is doing down there
in the first place.
She had made a specific request.
Sounds like a petri dish
with legs to me.
I'd invest in a couple
of syringes of penicillin.
So I find this all-night
Vietnamese store that carries them.
Leave it to Charlie to put
the dental dams with the toothpaste.
Are you serious?
I rush back.
I slap this thing on,
and I am goin' to town.
I swear, I'm like Gene Simmons
on that.
I was like the tao of poon,
I swear to God.
And she's like,
"I don't feel anything."
And you're like,
"Really? 'Cause that's my dick."
Have you ever actually tried
to use one of these things?
I guess you and me
dated a different breed of woman.
Down and dirty. No pun intended.
Don't make me hurt you.
-What time is lunch here?
-Shut up.
You worked me up an appetite.
Tom here could use a bite, too.
-Sir to you.
-Yes, sir.
Uncle Tom is looking very hungry.
Detectives, meet Marlon Demrall.
-Pleasure.
-Shut up.
Is that the only word
you ladies know?
Enjoy.
Happy birthday, by the way.
-You told her?
-No.
Yes. By accident.
Come with me, Marlon.
Whatever you say, birthday girl.
Hey, Lowe.
You gonna grab a beer with us tonight?
Can't. I've got other plans.
What's with your partner?
Can't spend quality time
with his fellow boys in blue?
I'm just going to church tonight.
God can wait.
Tonight, my friend,
you get your first b-and-b.
-What's a b-and-b?
-It's a tradition we have here.
Nothing like your very first one.
Be at the motor pool at
the end of the shift.
-You skip out on us, it's your ass.
-Let's get out of here.
What's a b-and-b?
It's stupid and juvenile
and the sooner you get it over with...
...the sooner you'll be accepted
by Jackson and the rest.
Why should I care what they think?
Rule number seven...
...those guys might be
overgrown frat boys,...
...but might someday be
the only thing...
...that comes between
you and a bullet.
What y'all got to eat around here?
How 'bout a nice churro?
You like churros, Marlon?
Yeah, that sugary shit is all right.
But what I'm really jonesing for
is a cheeseburger.
Let me see if I can accommodate you.
My man.
Come on, sweet thing.
Now I know you got a smile for me
underneath all that.
Dutch?
-Dutch?
-Captain.
I could use your help
with an interrogation.
-I'm in the middle of a case.
-Claudette's got it under control.
All right.
That's what all this is about?
Look, you could have saved me a trip.
Read my lips.
I did not kill Poncho. Okay?
Nivan Gonzalez.
-He's still alive at the moment.
-Whatever.
I didn't shoot
nobody this morning,...
...but I'll turn you on
to who did, though.
-Will you?
-Yeah.
-But I want something first.
-And what is that?
A cheeseburger! I'm hungry as hell!
Talk first, then you eat.
Come on.
All right.
I had a protection thing
going on with those churro chumps.
It was a good gig, too.
Till last month.
This new Mexican gang comes in,
packing some serious heat...
...tells me they movin'
in on my business.
And what gang was this?
Call themselves the Los Magnificos.
See, that's what's wrong
with this country.
I'm prime example numero uno.
I'm trying to make a serious buck,
and then comes some wetback...
...that's taking away my job.
-Your job?
-My job.
Your job was illegally
shaking down churro vendors.
Look, a job is a job, lady.
Now, I like mine well done.
Just like me. With everything.
No onions.
They give me a rash.
I don't find you funny.
You lookin' for me?
We'd like to ask you some questions.
About what?
About how Terry died.
You I.A.D. now?
Seems right up your alley.
I don't feel they
checked every angle.
-So now you got questions.
-I've got a few.
What's stopping me from having
my P.B.A. rep tell you to blow me?
Nothing.
If Vic Mackey
wants to hide behind a lawyer...
...then that's the way it'll be.
You got questions? Fine.
Ask your goddamn questions.
-Why'd you go in without more backup?
-A battalion of cops makes noise.
It's called the element of surprise.
lmagine my surprise
when I heard your guy died.
Those of us who venture out past
our desks sometimes get shot at.
More firepower wouldn't
have tipped him off.
Who should I have had
watching our backs? You?
I'd hate to have
to change your diaper afterwards.
Better than burying one of your own.
So you fired at the dealer,...
...the dealer returned
fire, hitting Terry.
No. Like I told I.A.D.,
Two-Time shot Terry...
...then Shane and I returned fire.
Sounds textbook to me.
That's all we got.
Thanks for your time.
That's all we've got?
Was that supposed to make him
spontaneously confess?
No. It's supposed to
make him feel safe.
Now we go after the
weak link in the chain.
Who's the weak link?
What was that all about?
Aceveda is spinning
his wheels, as usual.
Enter.
What can you tell me about a new
gang called Los Magnificos?
They're not so new...
...they been clawing up the food chain
for the last six months.
Someone from the gang
pulled the trigger on my churro guy.
Any bushes you can beat?
Looks like we've been invited
to the party, ladies.
Let's go.
I hear it's your birthday.
Happy birthday.
I need to ask Shane a few questions.
-Me?
-I need 10 minutes.
I'll send him to catch up with you.
I'm cool.
I'm gonna grab a Coke first.
Do you need anything?
No.
How's the paint brush, Van Bro?
Don't be coming around here
unless you lookin' to buy.
And no more freebies.
You want info,
you have to buy something this time.
All right.
-Lem, pick the poison.
-What do I know about art, man?
Ronnie?
I like the one with the clouds.
You got a place for it?
Yeah, I guess.
All right. How much?
Gimme $100.
And don't be hangin' it
in no bathroom, neither.
Looking for a Los Mag.
Shot up a churro vendor.
The people say
amigo didn't want to pay his freight.
He ignored a couple of warnings.
Los Mags sent in a baby banger
to do the dirty deed.
Earned him his stripes.
Initiation shooting?
Things they got these kids doing.
Did you have to bake a batch
of brownies back in your day, Van Bro?
Getting into life was a lot more fun
than getting out.
I heard you lost a
man a few days back.
-Yeah.
-Tough times, Vic.
I don't know. Maybe someday...
...somebody even win this war.
I intend to.
-See you around, baby.
-All right, man.
This little vato ready for the barrio?
The wannabe getting initiated,
he's our shooter.
I'll take him.
Anybody else gets caught in our net,
it's gravy.
-Are we goin' in?
-No. His punk ass wants a beating.
I say we let him have it.
What's he saying?
"Welcome to the life."
You were going to be his backup.
We were his backup.
Why is Terry dead, then?
Wrong place, wrong time.
Aren't you and Vic supposed to be
these kick-ass top cops?
How does somebody you're backing up...
...get blown away by some
pissant drug dealer?
I.A.D. cleared us.
I didn't clear you.
It just went bad. That's all.
You lie.
He squints when he lies.
You do.
-No, I don't.
-You're squinting now.
All right. Play time's over.
Last one down the hill
gets to drink the backwash.
All right. We're a go
in three, two, one, go!
Go.
Police!
Stop right there! Freeze!
Bienvenido a la vida.
You let Terry get killed.
-Why would we do that?
-You know why.
I.A.D. cleared us.
You know a drug dealer
named Rondell Robinson?
No.
You're squinting.
You don't know him?
I know who he is.
I meant I don't know him personally.
So if I had a witness
that saw you and Vic...
...acting real friendly
with Rondell Robinson...
-...that would be a lie.
-That's right.
So he didn't see
the three of you at a car wash?
Vic was just puttin' a scare into him.
Lettin' him know
that we were watching him.
-So you lied.
-No, I didn't.
I meant something else.
Terry knew you were in bed with
Robinson, so he had to die.
-Terry was in our team.
-He was your errand boy.
-Bullshit.
-You led Terry there to die.
No, not true.
The one guy who disapproved...
...is the only one who didn't
come out of that house alive.
-That's a coincidence?
-Believe what you want.
Terry was gonna turn you in,
so Vic wanted him dead.
-Vic needed him dead!
-No!
God.
The shot.
-That's what the last shot was.
-The last shot?
Two-Time's girlfriend said
that she heard the last shot...
...10, 15 seconds after the others.
When we approached Two-Time, he moved.
Vic couldn't leave it to chance.
Vic fired once more.
That's the shot that killed Terry.
-No way.
-Vic fired that shot, didn't he?
-No.
-Stop squinting!
I know.
You're wrong.
I want Mackey.
-You don't have to go down with him.
-That is not how it happened.
Stop lying to me.
I know what happened.
I have a witness, Shane.
He connects you and Vic
with Rondell Robinson.
I have a witness.
Give me Vic and your problems end.
Just give me Mackey.
What the hell's going on here?
You've had him here for two hours?
-He's making up sick shit about us.
-Wait for me downstairs.
-This whole thing is a joke.
-Grab a sandwich, Dutch-boy.
I know what you did.
Up until now, I've tolerated you.
You come near my men again,
I'm gonna lose patience.
You listening?
I know.
The churro guy you shot's in surgery.
They don't know if he'll live.
Tell her you didn't shoot this man.
If you tell me who had you do this,
I might get you into juvie court.
If you wait and he dies, you'll
be tried for murder as an adult.
Please tell her you didn't do this.
-Of course I didn't.
-You see?
I shoot someone,
he don't almost end up dead.
Bitch ends up all dead.
That's your alibi?
If you'd have shot him, he'd be dead?
Hell, yeah. That's my alibi.
Guess what?
Churro guy's actually gonna make it.
Good.
You're not gonna believe what went
down between Aceveda and Mackey.
-I don't want to know.
-Yeah, I know, but this is...
Anyone gets between those two...
...will end up with a hose full
of piss running down his leg.
Good news and bad news.
Bad news is...
...the churro vendor just died.
Good news for your son, though,...
...someone else is taking
credit for the killing.
Thank you, Jesus.
Some guy named Marlon
walked in off the street...
...said your gang was trying
to muscle in on his business...
...so he decided to
show all the vendors...
...your gang couldn't
protect them.
Marlon didn't do no shooting.
He did. Everyone's talking
about how he showed your boys up.
That old man stopped paying us.
That's my shooting!
-He's just looking to piggyback a rep.
-Olman, no.
You're trying
to take credit for it now?
Stop...
I told you if I shot him,
he'd be dead, right?
People need to know.
Los Mags own these streets.
-Who asked you to do the shooting?
-I ain't never telling you that.
These are my brothers now.
Do you know what this means?
Means I earned my way in.
No. It means you're going to jail.
At least I'll have family there.
Tell me you didn't reopen an
investigation that wasn't even yours.
There were unanswered questions.
You accused Mackey
of working with a drug dealer.
-Who's your witness?
-Anonymous tip.
Anyone who can corroborate it?
Is there something
I don't know...
...that explains why you're
still pursuing this?
Well?
No.
Then it ends here.
Christ, David.
You're doing a good job.
Chief said so the other day.
Don't lose focus now.
I won't.
Good.
Thanks for getting
Captain Ass-lnvader off my back.
It wouldn't kill you
to show him more respect.
Come on.
Vic, the men here take
their cues from you.
I'm just saying dial it down.
I don't do my best work
with him nipping at my heels.
Which is why I'm
watching out for you.
Good.
Question is, are you
watching out for me?
Meaning?
My guys tipped you off that Terry
was looking to take you down.
Ben, the bust just went bad.
My source at Justice
is all over my ass.
He wants to know if you made us
all accomplices to a murder.
I told him you'd never do that to me.
Would you?
Terry got overeager.
He got himself killed.
End of story?
End of story.
It better be.
Is this from you?
No. I know how you
feel about birthdays.
Denture cream.
Thank you.
'Cause I'm getting old.
I don't see a card.
Anyone want to take credit for this?
-Not me.
-I didn't think so.
-How's the birthday girl doing?
-Don't say that word.
-I came to take you dancing.
-I don't want to go dancing.
Now we gotta do something, honey.
-It's your birthday.
-So?
So, it's ladies night at the Crimson.
I have it on very good authority
that Franklin Green's gonna be there.
-His divorce final?
-Two weeks ago.
I can't let Franklin Green
see me looking like this.
Which is why we'll spruce up first,
then go to the Crimson.
-We too old to be chasing men around.
-I'm not.
Neither am I. Come on.
Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
Who said that Jesus
freak couldn't drink?
Your b-and-b's almost
complete, buddy boy.
You had the beer.
Now it's time for the blow.
-You're kidding.
-I kid you not.
She's a badge sucker.
What's a badge sucker?
A badge sucker, man.
She digs cops, okay?
She's like the neighborhood
welcoming committee. Listen.
A better hummer you're not gonna find.
-Trust me.
-No...
-I cannot...
-No, stay, listen!
Sit down!
This isn't torture, okay?
We've all gone through this.
Julien, say hi to Betty.
-So this is the new guy?
-Go!
Welcome to the force.
-Handsome.
-And he's lucky, too.
-Wanna go for a walk?
-Fellas, I cannot. No.
Come on, now. I can't!
Go!
Give it up, man.
Wait. Come on.
-Come on.
-All right.
Let's get you over here.
Relax, Officer.
This is a lot more fun than roll call.
You don't have to do this.
Yeah.
She love him long time.
Go!
Thanks a lot.
You don't put me in
an interrogation room...
...without giving me all the facts.
I wanted them to think
you had nothing.
Then I could take my shot.
You didn't think
they'd respect me enough to fear me?
No. I didn't.
That's pretty shitty.
Sorry.
You really think Vic had something
to do with Terry dying?