Previously on The Shield:
I went through the books.
Think I saw Mackey talking to
his drug dealer, a guy named...
Named Rondell Robinson.
You think Mackey working
for a drug dealer?
I'm suggesting the drug
dealer is working for Mackey.
What are you getting out of this?
I just want a dirty
cop off the street.
You wanna be Mayor someday?
You better learn how to lie
hell lot better than that.
I know what's wrong with Vic.
I just don't want us accused
of whitewashing anything.
The last thing we need...
...is another chapter
in the Rodney King-O.J. book.
I don't wanna be a chapter
in that book, either.
My source at Justice
is all over my ass.
He wants to know if you made us
all accomplices to a murder.
Terry got overeager.
He got himself killed.
End of story?
End of story.
You know you did it.
Up until now, I have tolerated you.
You come near my men again,
I'm gonna lose patience.
You listening?
I know.
Damn, girl! That's what I'm
talking about.
Don't shake that in my man's face.
-Who are all these white folk?
-They're from the record label.
Yeah. Give me that, girl. Yeah.
-How does she move like that?
-That's what the guys like.
Sir...
You've had too much to drink.
Who are you?
-I'm a cop.
-You undercover?
Security. So behave yourself.
Everybody put your
hands together...
...for all the ladies
shaking it up in here.
Word up!
Word up, y'all.
I wanna thank everybody for coming
out to my album release party.
"Back From the Ashes,"
you know what I'm saying?
Feels good to be
back behind the mike.
Hey, Kern!
-Do that duet with Tyesha.
-Rondell in the house.
Where Tyesha at? Where Tyesha at?
Come here.
This is Kern's party, y'all.
My release party ain't gonna be
for another month.
-Trouble.
-You can hear me sing then.
-Tonight's Kern's night.
-Where my money, Kern?
Yo, there go the thief right there.
I want my money, homey.
Where my money, Kern?
-Hey, yo. Hey, hey, hey.
-I want my money.
-My beef ain't with you, playboy.
-What?
-If it's with Kern, it's with me.
-Hey, back up.
This is a private party.
You can't get into trouble.
Do I have to call in the cavalry?
Step back.
Police can't protect you
forever, Kern. Remember that.
-Get out of here. Go.
-It's T-Bonz, homey.
-Punk ass out of here, man.
-You heard me. Go.
-Get lost, bitch.
-Who you calling a bitch?
Stay down! Shit!
Danny, you all right?
Hey, man, those fools were shooting
up in here.
-Lemon!
-Somebody call 911!
Rumble in the jungle.
-What happened?
-Two dead, six wounded.
T-Bonz and his crew
were looking for a fight...
...and Rondell and some of Kern's guys
gave it to him.
-Don't tell me.
-Rondell was the shooter.
It's just what we needed.
Hey. Hey, Vic.
You're missing all the fun.
Dutch, how many times
I got to tell you,...
...you can't feel up
the witnesses.
-Took one in the ass. Bet it's not...
-It's not the first time. Good one.
Look who's the last one
to a "shots fired" call.
All safe and secure, captain.
Shooting stopped.
Nothing to worry about here.
You two were moonlighting?
Our shift commander signed off on it.
Any suspects in custody?
Well, the night is young.
Let me do my thing.
Do you mind if I include others
in this investigation?
You sign the checks.
Pete and Dutch team up.
Strike Team will assist
as they see fit.
Any problems with that?
Just that time's a-wasting.
I won't put up with shooting galleries
in Farmington.
Find out who pulled the triggers
and bring them in.
Knute Rockne, he ain't.
I may have to put up with you
working under my roof...
...but it's still my roof.
So just do your job...
...and stay out of my way.
Sounds like good
advice for both of us.
Let's get to work.
-The guy throwing the party...
-Kern Little.
And this T-Bonz,
they weren't the shooters?
-Not that I saw. Just their pals.
-Can you ID any of them?
I can look through the books.
This will spill into
the street quick.
Let's talk to both generals,
get them to stand down their armies.
-Starting where?
-Kern Little.
-Who's Kern Little?
-Listen, Dutchboy...
...don't get your clogs all dirty.
We'll deal with Kern Little.
-Who is it?
-Open up, Rondell.
-What's up, Vic?
-Why'd you shoot up the Chez Club?
Hey, man, T-Bonz and Kern
got this war going on, man.
-I'm just backing up my boy.
-Who's that? Kern?
Hey, this thing high-def?
Yeah. Don't get your
prints on it, man.
Sweet.
Look, me and Kern, we been hanging
since we was kids. We're still tight.
Don't you mean Kern financed
your entry into the drug business?
Yeah. No comment.
But that's the rumour.
What's the beef between
Kern and T-Bonz?
T-Bonz was on Kern's
record label.
Then he started selling
a lot of discs.
T-Bonz split, start his own outfit.
Hey, bad blood ever since.
-Hey, what's with all the vinyl here?
-Hey, hey, hey, it sounds better.
Would you put those back
the way you found them.
That's my Blue Note collection.
I got them chronological from...
-Did you hit anybody last night?
-Look, if somebody got smoked...
...it wasn't me. I was just shooting
to be shooting.
Give me your piece.
Come on, come on, just give it to me.
Keep your dealers inside
until I give the all clear.
I don't want more
targets on the street.
Vic, man, come on.
Business is going to take a big hit.
Then take it.
You get to deliver product...
...only so long as this neighbourhood
doesn't resemble the Gaza Strip.
Now, that was our deal. You remember?
Yeah, I remember.
Set up a meet. Me and Kern Little.
-Man, why you need me to do that?
-You two are buds.
-I want it to be on friendly terms.
-Anything else, man?
Yeah. I need two shooters
from your side.
Come on, man, you kidding.
Come on, man. No.
Is it gonna be you?
And I run your gun through ballistics?
Or you got some names for me?
-Welcome to the Barn.
-Make yourselves at home.
Just doing my job.
And staying out of your way.
-You look great.
-Stay focused.
Now, he owns three different
car dealerships.
Him, a chain of grocery stores.
There's more money here
than in Mexico City.
-Which one's Machado?
-Right there.
This whole thing is his baby.
You better say hi
before he disappears.
-Okay.
-Remember how we talked about it.
-I'll wing it.
-David...
-I'm joking.
-This could be your one chance.
-You ready?
-As I'll ever be.
Senor Machado. I'm David Aceveda.
Our young police captain. Welcome.
It's an honour to meet you.
This is my wife, Aurora.
What a wonderful
housing development.
It's a step forward in improving
our neighbourhood.
-I'm glad you both could come.
-Thank you for including us.
I'm in your debt.
Don't think me overly generous, David.
As you'll discover,
I often have ulterior motives.
You see, you're actually in a position
to help me.
How so?
My nanny hasn't
seen her husband...
...since he left the
house a few days ago.
He's a day-worker.
Waits for jobs by the home
improvement centre in your district.
Well, is this absence
unusual for him?
Not exactly.
They are an emotional couple.
They fight, he leaves, he comes back.
But he has never been gone this long.
My nanny's quite upset, which means
my wife is upset, which means...
I don't have to tell you
what that means.
Just give me the
pertinent information.
I'd be glad to help.
Looks as if I am now in your debt.
-You listening to this?
-It's sweet.
Sing me a song about last night.
Man, that'd be a short-ass song.
As soon as I seen them dudes coming
with them big guns...
...I just got Tyesha the hell up
out of there.
Nice place.
I told everybody my first studio
gonna be in Farmington.
You can't record a hardcore
hip-hop song working in Bel Air.
You got to keep it
in the 'hood, baby.
How am I sounding, baby?
What?
Like 2 million CDs, double platinum.
-Tyesha, this is officer...
-I'm Vic. Just call him Lemonhead.
-Hey
-Hey. This is Rocco.
It's a madhouse out there. How'd you
get past all the photographers?
We called ahead. Kern let us use
the security entrance.
Kern's not under arrest, is he?
Unfortunately for those
tabloid hacks, no.
-We just needed a statement.
-Which I gave.
-And his help with this war.
-Well, it's not Kern.
It's his boys trying to protect him.
T-Bonz is just plain crazy.
Everybody knows that.
Don't worry about T-Bonz,
we'll deal with him.
I need you to give the word
to your crew. The war is over.
Right after T-Bonz gives his word.
I mean, T-Bonz's the one that
spilled blood on my turf.
I'm nothing if not a man of peace.
Dutch?
I'm running known associates
on the shooters Mackey brought in.
We ever getting DSL around here?
This is Ellie Ruiz.
I need you to help her out.
-I'm working the Chez Club.
-Shockley can handle it.
I need you to help find
Ellie's husband, Manuel.
I can't believe we're doing this
for some fat cat's nanny.
You'd be happier if
it was a mistress?
It's abuse of power.
You're upset
you got pulled off a big case.
We're Aceveda's errand boys.
Meanwhile, watch him cash in
on our hard work.
So looking for a missing
migrant worker isn't important?
-You do all the talking.
-Why me?
You speak Spanish.
How can you be a cop in L.A.
For 12 years...
-...and not speak any Spanish?
-All my partners spoke Spanish.
-Besides, I know a phrase or two.
-Right.
Yo no say means: I don't know.
You hear it enough, it sinks in.
Missing hombre?
Yeah.
Manuel Ruiz?
-There.
-Hey, hey!
Hey, hey. You, amigo. Amigo.
What's your name?
Come on. You wouldn't be
sneaking away if you yo no say.
Now, you know Manuel, don't you?
Yes.
-I don't believe it!
-What?
Back up!
Let's roll, man!
Don't you make me break a sweat
trying to catch you!
What the hell are you doing out?
-Business.
-Rondell ordered you off the street.
-No, not us.
-Run on home.
What I'm gonna tell the boss?
I am the boss.
-What I'm gonna tell Rondell?
-Don't worry. I'll tell him for you.
-What's up, man?
-I saw two of your guys on the street.
-Man, it's a free country.
-Nothing's free.
I'm your landlord, Rondell.
I let you use space that I own.
Now, you can't follow by my rules,
then I'll find someone who can.
-You got me?
-I got you.
Now, smart-ass, who else
you got dealing and where?
Manuel got picked for a job
on Tuesday, along with another man.
-Eduardo Salcido.
-Salcido.
Any connection between this Manuel
and Eduardo?
-They were best friends in Mexico.
-Even snuck into the country together.
Something happened
on that truck ride.
Ever since, Eduardo's been
telling people he's gonna kill Manuel.
We know who hired the two of them?
-Truck logo said Jamison Contracting.
-Well, track it down.
Find out if they ever
showed up for work.
All units, code 213,
intersection of Alvarado and Pine.
That's our corner.
Goddamn it! He had to leave his guys
on the street!
Punch it!
Police!
Down there.
Call EMT!
Oh, no.
The mayor knows the little boy, Vic.
You're shitting me.
Belongs to his golf buddy's
second cousin or some such thing.
Whatever. He's invested.
Any word on the kid's condition?
He's busted up pretty bad.
So I got nothing good
to tell the chief.
How do I explain
these four dead thugs?
A war. Two rappers.
I know who they are.
Look, I'm handling it.
I told the chief the Strike Team
would make a difference.
That these things will stop.
I'm not seeing the difference.
Temporary setback.
The chief allows me to appropriate
funds for you based on results.
If I can't defend you,
I can't afford you.
Vic.
-Thought you should know.
-Know what?
Kid was DOA.
I'm handling it.
Knock, knock.
Have a seat.
-All right.
-Tough guy.
This war ends right here
with a handshake.
This fool stole my money
and my woman...
...and you expect me
to be a gentleman?
-What, Tyesha was your woman?
-Hell, yeah.
-We're not signing autographs, ladies.
-Okay.
So basically, this is a dick wagging
contest over a piece of ass?
This ain't about no piece of ass.
It's about $2 million
that fool owe me.
Two million dollars?
-What 2 mil?
-Tyesha's money from the last CD.
I broke her. Where my cut?
First up, calm down, money.
I'm a businessman.
I can be fair.
But $2 million,
you must be smoking crack.
I'll give you a finder's fee.
Straighten you out.
I'm doing your punk-ass a favour.
You owe me at least 10.
You know what, T?
I'm gonna keep it real with you.
Tyesha wasn't even selling records
till I hooked her up. And that's real.
-Is that real?
-Hey, look, look, look.
Your 10 lawyers can do battle with his
10 lawyers or we can settle this here.
-I'm gonna get my money, bitch.
-Over my dead body.
-Damn, that sound like a good idea.
-Shut up!
Here's the deal.
Kern, you take tonight,
come up with a number.
You revise yours down a bit.
You bring me the numbers...
...I'll decide what's fair.
And who you supposed to be?
Judge Judy?
I'm an impartial arbitrator with the
power to throw your asses in the can.
Now, I'm calling a 24-hour cease-fire.
Your boys break it, I break you.
Same goes for you.
This war ends here.
They come here of their own accord.
Nobody's coercing them.
Family of five moving to another
country just to eat isn't coercion?
You know why they come here?
Five words: Free market's rule of law.
Those things create prosperity,
which creates jobs people want.
Forty dollars for a full day's work
isn't prosperity.
It's exploitation and
you wouldn't do it.
-Excuse me.
-Can I help you?
Yeah. We're looking for a worker
named Eduardo?
Throw a rock, you're bound to hit one.
Have you seen this guy?
-Yeah. Jose.
-Manuel.
Yeah. He showed up a few days ago,
worked for one day, got paid...
...never saw him again.
What did he do?
Have any idea what happened
after he left?
Don't know, don't care.
Mind if we ask around for Eduardo?
-Ask away.
-Thanks.
Eduardo?
-Eduardo?
Eduardo?!
It's not me. I think he's working
down over there.
Hey! Stop!
I said, stop! Hold it right there!
-Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, San Salvador is that way!
These the triggermen at the Chez Club?
Some of them, I think. Happened fast.
Rondell Robinson. You saw him
firing the gun in the club?
Yeah.
-Beautiful.
-You know who he is?
Yes, I do.
Let's make this short and sweet.
Wherever you think I was, I wasn't.
-Whatever you think I did, I didn't.
-That's your story?
Cover to cover.
I wouldn't plan on
selling movie rights.
Guess I'll just have to settle
for starring in it.
You're a murder suspect, Rondell.
I've got a witness saw you
pull the trigger at the Chez Club.
Yeah, right. What witness?
A cop. And a jury's gonna love her.
I got a phone call coming, right?
You've only got one
thing left to deal.
-That's who's giving you protection.
-I don't need no protection.
Even if we can't tie you
to one of the dead bodies...
...discharging a firearm
in a crowded club...
Bye-bye, Rondell.
So about that phone call.
If you think that you
can sell drugs...
...and commit murder in my district
because a cop's protecting you...
...you're dead wrong!
-I thought I told you to lay low.
-I was listening to Miles Davis...
-...when this captain shows up.
-He get anything?
No. I always keep my crib clean.
But he's got a serious bug up his ass
about some cop protecting me.
Just keep your mouth shut.
I'll handle Aceveda.
We have indications Manuel's
disappearance may involve foul play.
-Really? You don't know for sure?
-We have a suspect.
He won't be able to elude us for long.
Once we capture him, we'll know more.
Thank you for making this a priority.
You keep me apprised?
Of any developments.
Is there something else?
At the risk of having
an ulterior motive myself...
Yes.
I know police officers aren't accorded
the same respect in this community...
-...as they were a decade ago.
-An unfortunate development.
However, Latinos are a plurality
in Los Angeles...
...and in this district.
There is going to be a seat opening up
on the City Council next year.
It's traditionally been filled
with a black candidate.
I think it's our time.
I agree.
With your backing...
...I could win that seat.
I could be of great use to you.
I like you, David, quite a bit...
...but I don't think I can sell a cop
to these voters.
Not here, not now.
Who knows? Maybe in time,
things will become much different.
Until then, I'm sorry.
What would you think of a man
who exposed corruption?
Brought down dirty cops
from inside the department?
I'd think he was committing
professional suicide.
But couldn't you sell
him to the voters?
Absolutely.
-We got a call about a kidnapping.
-They took my boy, Thurman.
When did you find out
he was kidnapped?
Today.
I got a ransom call asking
for $10,000. I don't have it!
-When did you last see Thurman?
-Three weeks.
-How long has he been missing?
-Since last night.
-The last time you spoke?
-A month ago.
Then how do you know he's only
been missing since last night?
Cemetery called.
Somebody dug up his body.
-Thurman's dead?
-Going on three weeks.
Code four, cancel
that backup, please.
Roger that. Ten-four.
Ma'am, if the kidnapper calls back,
call us.
You're not gonna help me?
To be honest,
they'll push it to the bottom.
Detectives, they have more important
things to do.
But it's a crime, isn't it? Digging up
my son, holding it for ransom?
-Yes, ma'am.
-So you two will help me, then, right?
Julien, you stay with her.
I'll ride solo.
-Ma'am.
-Good.
Hey.
-I got a little problem.
-What's that?
The guy you ID'd today,
he's a C.I. Of mine.
-Really?
-Yeah.
He's the guy who gave me
the shooters.
He was firing in self-defence.
None of his shots killed anybody.
I was hoping maybe your memory
could get a little fuzzy on this one.
I don't know, Vic.
Aceveda's all over this one.
But if it ever goes to trial?
I don't know.
Let me think about it.
That's all I ask.
-That's Thurman right there.
-I went to high school with him.
Did you know him?
He and his friends
used to beat me up.
It's okay.
He made me a better student.
I hid out in the library until I grew
9 inches my junior year.
He was killed robbing a liquor store.
Thurman?
He was a thief. He did drugs.
I was afraid to tell you.
I would've helped you anyway.
I mean, maybe he didn't find
his path here on earth...
-...but he's with Jesus now.
-You believe that?
I know that.
-Hello?
-You got the money ready?
Yes. Where's my son's body?
Bring the money to
the cemetery at 10.
What?
Bring the money to the cemetery
at 10:00 sharp.
-I can't understand you.
-Bring the money to the cemetery...
...at 10:00 sharp or Thurman's body
will be chopped to pieces...
-...and you'll never see him again.
-Henry! Is that you?
Face front.
-Did you hate her that much?
-No.
She's all right.
We dated for a while, you know?
-Then why did you do it?
-Why did I do it?
Why did I do it?
Knew she had
life insurance on her boy.
I wanted to take my new lady
on one of them cruises.
Dottie spent all the insurance money
on Thurman's funeral.
Can you make it Thursday?
How many problems
can a 5-year-old have?
Enough that he's got an appointment
with a developmental paediatrician.
-Matthew thinks he's a dog now.
-A German shepherd. So what?
You're not here.
You don't see everything.
See what?
The problems.
Why do you have to fight me on this?
I'm not.
Okay, I'll try.
I'll try, okay?
I'm really losing it.
Why don't you go take a bath.
I'll put the kids to bed.
Okay.
Good night. Thanks.
-Get down.
-Hey. I'm a cop.
Get down. Don't scream.
I said, I'm a cop!
And I'm a cop killer.
But not tonight.
Tonight's to show you
how we're gonna do it.
What do you want?
Forget what you saw at the Chez Club.
Understand?
Yeah. I understand.
Come on.
-Hey, hey, hey!
-You piece of shit!
-Something wrong, officer?
-You think you can get to me?
Girl, you better take
some kind of pill. Damn.
You listen to me. I'm a cop.
You don't scare me.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You do look scared, though.
Hey.
-I'll catch you outside, okay?
-Meet you out there.
What was all that between you
and my C.I.?
Did you tell him I was the one
that ID'd him?
Of course not.
What the hell is going on?
He sent guys after me.
They put a gun to my head...
...and told me to forget what I saw
at the Chez Club.
-You should take the day off.
-No, maybe I should go after them.
-Let me take care of this.
-Know what, I can take care of myself.
-You went after a cop?
-Vic, I just scared her, man.
Cops are off-limits.
-Shooting at somebody shooting at me.
-I was taking care of it.
I didn't know.
I had to do something, man.
Take your drug money
and bail yourself out.
And then what?
In the year and a half it'll take
to go to trial, I'll make it go away.
Look, I can't take no chances, Vic.
The biggest chance you could've taken
was to piss me off.
And that's exactly what you did.
-You see him?
-No.
But I got you a Spanish-English
phrase book. My gift to you.
Third day in a row you're checking
the Real Estate section.
-What's the deal?
-None your.
What's that, Spanish?
English for "none of your business."
-We're partners. Share.
-Wanna share? Here's the Sports page.
I'll find out. I'm a detective.
There he is.
Bingo, gringo.
Eduardo Salcido?
You and Manuel hopped on the same
truck. You went to work together?
-Did you kill him after work ended?
-No.
-So you killed him on the way to work?
Where is he? How come his wife
hasn't heard from him?
Spare me the Yo no sor. We know.
-Know?
-About the grudge.
You hated Manuel. You told
people you wanted to kill him.
He my friend.
-Used to be. Till the trip.
-What happened on that truck?
What truck?
The one that snuck you and Manuel
across the border.
-What made you wanna kill him?
-Nothing.
-You fight? He steal? What?
He did something.
-Nothing happened.
-Was it personal? Did he hurt you?
I'm not the one who killed Manuel.
So Manuel is dead.
Stay here, Eduardo.
-You ask me, he was raped.
-What?
I know I sound like Dutch
with one of his theories.
But my first few years on the job...
...I practically lived in hospitals,
taking statements from rape victims.
-He's got that look.
-The look?
Nervousness, isolation.
But it's mostly in the eyes.
Raped in a truck sneaking into the
country? How is that possible?
It's possible.
What do you mean,
sounds like one of my theories?
What's with the getups?
Avoiding cameras.
-So, what's the problem?
-This is the goddamn problem.
-He poisoned my baby.
-Threw some meat over the fence...
...next thing, he's choking to death.
-T-Bonz?
-Of course, it's T-Bonz.
-He's got to pay.
-She supposed to be in the studio...
-...finishing her album right now.
-How can I work after this? Look.
It's game-over time for T-Bonz.
Be a man.
I know.
You know how much
this setback is costing me?
-Get that off my table.
-The goddamn bastard has to pay.
-That's T-Bonz breaking his truce.
-You gonna be a man...
...or do I have to find someone
to do the job?
Look.
I told you, this is why we here.
I know what I got to do, all right?
All right?
-I just need you to help me do it.
-Do what?
Do the deed.
T-Bonz. I know where he's holed up at.
But I can't get to him.
-A man with a badge could, though.
-Why would I do something like that?
Money. I'll make that rent Rondell
paying you look like chump change.
Pay you double if I get to watch.
You want this war to end, right?
Then help me end it,
or more blood is gonna get spilled.
Give me the address.
-Was Manuel the one who raped you?
-No rape.
-He hold you down?
-It not happen.
-Catch you sleeping, you wake up...
-No.
Somebody did that to me,
I'd smash their head in.
I'd stab them, shoot them,
push him off a roof.
He raped you in that
truck, didn't he?
We'd understand
if you killed him.
I murder Manuel.
You killed Manuel?
Good.
Where?
Working con el Senor Jamison.
-We were on the roof and he fall.
-You pushed him?
No. He...
We were carrying...
Air conditioning unit.
Look out, Manuel,
but he didn't hear him.
He slipped and he fell.
-He slipped and he fell.
-I murder him.
That's not murder, Eduardo.
That's not what Mr. Jamison say.
What else did Senor Jamison say?
This is private property!
This is private property.
-It was an accident.
-A man was accidentally buried here?
I asked about Manuel's wife...
...his family, and no one seemed
to know.
He had no papers, he was illegal.
Burying a man on
your site is illegal.
-I wanted to alert the authorities.
-Too much of a hassle?
It would have shut down business
for weeks, put these guys out of work.
-What would they have done then?
-Please.
You told Eduardo
he was guilty of murder.
This is what you call
planting rice and beans.
Told you not to talk, asshole!
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to have...
This ain't no police station.
What's going on?
Man, please, dog. Whatever you
thinking about doing, don't do it.
T, what happened to that trash talker
I fell in love with?
Come on, man, I'm begging you.
Come on, man.
Come on, you dog killer, let's go.
-Come on, man.
-You broke the truce. Time to pay.
I'll give you money, dude.
I'll hook you up, Mackey. I got money.
I just need one phone call.
I'll give you whatever you need.
-Let's end this, dude. It's over.
-Why you crying, T-Bonz?
-What's he doing here?
-I paid for front row seats.
Mackey, man, please, dog.
Please.
-Come on, Mackey, man.
-Get in.
-You too, Kern.
-What?
-The two of you guys are shacking up.
-Are you crazy?
-He's definitely crazy.
-You two are so keen...
...on killing each other, fine.
I'm cutting out the middle man.
-We had a deal, Vic.
-Hey, I'm never for sale.
Now you know.
-I can respect that, but I'm saying...
-Shut up! Get inside!
You two can't make peace,
I'll see one of you in the morning.
-This how you gonna do it, man?
-Close it.
I should've thought
of this yesterday.
Yeah.
-Hey, why you got to be such a bitch?
-Because of pricks like you, Freddie.
-I got rights, you goddamn dyke.
-Hey. Save it for your new roommate.
-Yeah, I got a VIN number for you.
-Rondell Robinson just made bail.
-Yeah? Well, that's his right.
-Hundred grand in cash.
Lot of money for a
kid from the ghetto.
Maybe he's got a rich uncle.
-You all right?
-I'm fine.
You just been a little
jacked-up today.
Well, I'm fine.
If you don't wanna talk about it,
that's cool.
But I'm gonna say a prayer
for you tonight, though.
Thanks.
Heard you made bail.
Hey. Your peaches are about
to go bad in there.
Where's my stuff?
Where's my TV, man?
Donated to the Lynwild Boys' Club.
You should've seen the looks
on these kids' faces.
Man, it was like Christmas.
My goddamn records, man?
You went after a cop, Rondell.
You should thank me, dude.
I talked him out of doing
a hell of a lot worse.
The district attorney is content
that Manuel's death was accidental.
I see.
This Mr. Jamison,
what is his punishment?
He'll plead guilty to tampering with
evidence, be fined and released.
Senora Ruiz, I am truly sorry
about your husband.
This man, Jamison, worked for
a large company, no?
Yes.
Then I can sue them for much money?
Thanks again, David.
I'm glad I could help.
I have given some thought
to your proposal.
-And?
-I'm intrigued.
I have a few months before I decide
who I'm going to back.
Show me what you can do.
-They no think I murder Manuel?
-No.
Muchas gracias, Detective Dutch.
Tell me something. You hated Manuel.
You made threats against his life. Why
go on the same job with him that day?
When the truck come,
they pick Manuel, they pick me.
I have to work.
So, what's next, Eduardo?
I don't know.
The reason I ask is, I've got this
retaining wall that's crumbling...
Looking for me?
Heard you were
kicking some ass today.
No more than usual.
Do you trust me?
-What?
-With your life. Do you trust me?
Yeah.
Well, then you believe me
when I tell you...
...you don't have to look over your
shoulder no more.
I took care of it.
-You took care of it?
-You got no more problems.
Christ. I don't know what...
Hello?
What?
Where?
All right, I'll be right there.
I gotta run.
Doctor Shapiro to Cardiology.
Nurse. Hi. I'm look...
I got it.
Okay. Where's Megan?
She's getting x-rays.
Mom's with her.
He didn't mean it.
A 5-year-old does not bite his
18-month-old sister on the face...
...and make her fall on her head.
All right, go be with Megan.
It's gonna be okay.
Your sister's gonna be all right.
I don't hear nothing.
Assholes like these don't
wake up before noon.
T-Bonz!
Nobody else coming out of there.
Told you he was a bitch.
I'll have my cleanup crew
come clean that mess, man.
Shit.
-Give me that.
-Fine.
I'll take care of this.
You hungry?
Goddamn starved.