7-Adam-15,
show us on scene
for our hold-up alarm.
Whoa!
Put your hands up!
Nice and slow.
Show us your hands.
Keep your hands up!
Stop right --
You with the bag,
stop where you are
and show us
your hands.
You can see me?
Yes.
Too much of you.
The wizard said this bracelet
would make me invisible.
♪♪
Wait.
You don't see me.
You see the bags.
Oh.
Sir, put your hands up.
No. Wait.
Sir.
It's not -- That --
Keep them up.
Don't even -- Don't --
There it is.
Well, on the bright side,
we can tell
he's not concealing
any weapons.
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
♪♪
This is so much harder
than I thought it would be.
If you have an itch, it's okay.
You can scratch it.
No, no, no, no.
This is the longest I've gone
without looking at my phone.
I think
I have a problem.
I wasn't gonna say
anything.
How's it going?
You know, it's going.
Honestly, I don't know.
I-I am not a painter
like you.
Unless you include
painting houses.
Well, I'm not
a painter yet, either.
I've only taken
a few classes.
Believe me --
I am way out of my comfort zone.
Okay, that's what you said
about French cooking.
Then you got that cookbook
and you mastered cassoulet
in three days.
Oh, okay.
Now that one I cannot ignore.
Time for me
to go to work.
Let's see what you got.
No, no, no.
You have to wait
till it's finished.
I'm on tenterhooks.
Hey, you.
Ooh!
Hi. Good morning.
Uh, did you get my e-mails?
I did.
I haven't had time
to read all the articles
you've sent on coddling felons,
but it's on my to-do list.
Hmm.
Never had a girlfriend
give me homework before.
Well, I give it
because you are as quick
to label people felon as you are
to call me your girlfriend,
when we've only been
on four dates.
Oh, I --
Look, we both know
the prosecutorial system
needs fixing,
and you are in a position
to do that,
which is why I'm...
helping to educate you.
Well, if you feel
this strongly,
why didn't you go
to law school?
My parents wanted me to,
so that was
out of the question.
I'm serious.
I know you love
what you do,
but lots of cops
get tired of the violence
and go to law school.
You could be
part of the solution.
Try not to sound
so condescending.
Yeah, it's hard for me.
Mm-hmm.
I have to get to court.
Did it really bother you
that I said "girlfriend"?
I'm fine with it
as long as you're fine with me
defining you
as my work in progress.
I never know
when you're joking.
Good.
Keeps you on your toes.
♪♪
Oh, hey, Lucy.
Hey.
Hey, uh, did you know
that Bailey
is painting
Nolan's portrait?
Is she?
Gosh, I had no idea.
You only talk about it all the time.
All the time.
Okay, forgive me for being proud
of my girlfriend.
Look, you got to give me
some lessons.
Like, how are you dating
so far out of your league?
Oh, that --
that's kind of his thing.
Oh. Fair enough.
Seriously, I mean, Bailey --
she's a firefighter,
an army reservist, a capoeira
instructor, and a painter?
You're forgetting
motorcycle racer,
mixologist,
and runner-up for Nobel Prize.
Really?
No. I made the last one up.
But a part of you
believed it.
Yeah.
No uniform today.
What's the occasion?
Oh, you will find out
soon enough.
- Lookin' good, sir.
- Oh! Hey!
Alright, alright.
Settle down.
The suit's for court.
Right now, I want you to focus
on the other person
not in uniform this morning --
Detective Harper.
Anyone want to tell me
why a T.O. would be wearing
her most comfy maternity clothes
out on patrol?
Plain Clothes Day.
Okay, what's that?
Today, Detective Harper
will be with you as your shadow,
not your T.O.
Her only job
is to observe.
So act as if
you're on patrol alone
and handle it yourself
accordingly.
Okay. I mean, that actually
sounds kind of awesome.
Oh, by all means,
enjoy it.
And don't let the fact
that it is the day
when the highest percentage
of rookies wash out
bother you at all.
It is?
Final order of business.
Officer Hong has a dental
emergency this morning.
Nolan, you'll be working
the front desk.
Oh, no problem.
I could use a quiet morning.
With Smitty.
♪♪
I'm sorry, sir.
I can't sign your fix-it ticket
until you actually...
well, fix it.
And when I walked out
of the bank, my bike was gone.
Take it as a sign.
If God wanted us
to ride bikes,
he wouldn't have made
those seats so uncomfortable.
I feel like you're just trying
to avoid writing a report.
I am.
Miss,
if you get in my line,
I can help you
in a minute.
And what can I do
for you today?
My son was mugged for his
skateboard on the way to school.
Oh, I'm sorry
to hear that.
Uh, let's get you started here.
Thank you.
Hey, hey.
I gotta talk to somebody.
Okay. Well, these people
have been waiting a long time.
If you'll just get
into the line...
But it's important!
And their case
is important, too.
I-I understand. If you'll
just step into the line, sir.
Thank you.
I apologize for that.
Alright, um, can you tell me
what happened?
Seriously, I have
a much greater respect
for what you have
to go through now.
The makeup that I have to wear
for my reality show --
it's killing my skin.
Oh, right.
"You're not here."
Okay,
so this is my shop.
Me.
Alone.
Guess that means I get to choose
what to eat for lunch.
And what to play
on the radio.
I'm thinking bluegrass all day.
Then it'll be
your last day.
Expired tag.
I'll run the plate.
It says it belongs
to a Natasha Marsh.
North Hollywood address.
Okay.
Let's go say hi.
Morning, ma'am.
Do you know
why I pulled you over?
No, I don't.
Uh,
your tags are expired.
Can you, uh, grab your license
and registration
and step out of the vehicle,
please?
I need to get out
of my car for expired tags?
Oh, no, don't worry.
You're not in any trouble.
It's just that there's a lot
of traffic on this street,
and I'm riding solo
today,
so it's not only for my safety,
but for yours, as well.
It will only take a minute.
Okay.
Here you go.
Right this way.
Alright,
let's see here.
Now, ma'am,
were you aware
that you were driving around
with expired tags?
My husband usually
takes care of that.
Okay, well, look, I'm gonna
give you a warning this time,
but just know,
the next cop that pulls you over
might not be as forgiving, okay?
I understand.
Thank you, Officer.
Alright.
That was intense.
Would have been
a lot faster
if I hadn't had to help
most of the people.
Well, I'm in the quality,
not quantity business.
Well, you're failing
spectacularly.
Sir, I can help you now.
Sir? Excuse me?
Sir?
He okay?
No.
He's dead.
Control, this is Officer Nolan
in the Main Lobby.
We have a person down.
Male in his 40s not conscious,
not breathing,
and cool to the touch.
Repeat -- we have a D.B.
in the Main Lobby.
You've been quiet.
What?
Do you think
that I'd be a good lawyer?
No.
And that's a compliment.
Wesley's a lawyer.
We like Wesley.
Eh, we accept Wesley
because we fear Lopez.
It's just...
a progressive D.A.
can change a hell of a lot more
than we can.
We're not here
to change things.
We're here
to catch criminals.
Look, if you want to change
the way society works,
become a billionaire
and eradicate poverty
in Los Angeles.
What the hell's
that guy doing?
Shots fired at Spring and First.
We need additional units.
Start RA and airship.
Suspect seen driving
a gray Camaro
last seen going east
on Spring.
♪♪
I don't have a pulse.
Put your hands right here
to stop the bleeding.
Airship 3 en route.
ETA to scene, 2 minutes.
There it is.
Control 7-Adam-19,
show me in pursuit
of suspect's vehicle
headed east on Spring.
♪♪
He's going
for the freeway.
Cut him off
before he gets there.
Yeah, I got it.
Don't lose him.
Yeah, I won't.
♪♪
Right. Get to the right.
No, that's the sidewalk.
So what?!
♪♪
7-Adam-19, I've lost sight
of the suspect's vehicle.
Last seen headed
to the 110 Freeway.
Do you see him,
Airship 3?
Negative.
♪♪
We got a problem here.
Did I do something wrong
back there?
I told you to cut right,
and you didn't.
As a civilian,
you are not allowed
to drive
on the sidewalk.
As a cop, you do it
to catch a killer.
Benches and -- and parking
meters are replaceable.
Right. Sorry.
Anything come back
on the shooter's plates?
Yeah,
stolen this morning.
And I'm sure we'll find the car
dumped within the hour.
What have we got?
Drive-by.
The victim passed away
before the paramedics came.
Did you get a look
at the shooter?
Not a good one.
Then we start with her.
Was this just road rage, or did
someone target her for a reason?
So, the guy in the hoodie
sits next to our victim,
injects him
with something,
and then walks away.
M.E.
is rushing toxicology,
but given how fast
the victim reacted,
it's got to be
a poison of some kind.
A killer willing
to commit murder
right in front
of our eyes
is either really brave
or really desperate.
And neither of them is good.
No.
Hey. Sorry I'm late. Had to get
TID squared away on that 187.
Just heard they were
delayed because they had
to come here first?
People are committing murder
right under our noses now.
Under my nose.
I'm sorry your first stint
as Watch Commander
is under
these circumstances.
No worries.
I'll hold down the fort
until you're back.
Alright.
Officer Hong is managing
the front desk now.
What do you want me
to do?
Stay on
the poisoning victim,
coordinate
with the detectives.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
Look, I've learned
my lesson, okay?
Trash cans, benches,
bus kiosks -- it's all property.
I'm not gonna hesitate
next time.
Not bus kiosks.
Those things are shop killers.
Alright, so, the guy
that had the camera --
his S.U.V. was registered
to a business, Mad Profitz, Inc.
Are you sure
he was filming us?
I mean, this is L.A.,
the Land of Paparazzi.
Maybe Doja Cat was getting
a boba tea or something.
No, I know for a fact
that he was there for us.
How?
'Cause he's tailing us
right now -- him and a driver.
What?
Oh, well, let me flip around.
I'll pull their ass over.
No, no.
Don't let on that you know.
I got a better way
of flushing them out.
Speed up here
and make a right on the corner.
♪♪
Hey. LAPD.
What are you doing?
Detective Harper.
It is so good to see you again.
Wait. You're --
You're that TV producer.
Morris.
Hey, man.
You look good.
D-Did you know
about this?
No. So, what's up, man?
Y'all been filming us?
Well, look, I mean,
you wouldn't give us access
to the station,
and we needed B-roll,
so your mom said,
"Get it done."
Unh-unh. No, no.
This ends now.
W-What you all
are doing is --
It's perfectly legal,
and you know it.
Look, as a producer
on the show,
you should
really appreciate
the production value
this gives us.
I mean,
quick question.
Is it at all possible
we could reshoot
this whole
car-chase thing?
I'd really love to get
a few more angles.
♪♪
Let's go, Boot.
Yeah.
Hey, man,
thanks for jammin' me up.
You might be filming my last day
on the job.
So good for you.
♪♪
There was a murder
at the front desk?
Not just a murder.
A poisoning.
In a police station?
Who does that?
Uh, the villain
in a Bond movie?
Any motive yet?
According to the family,
the victim was paranoid
someone was following him
because he was about to testify
before a grand jury.
In what case?
I'm trying
to find that out.
I heard
you caught a homicide.
Yeah.
It's been a busy morning.
Hey, guys. I ordered
way too many egg rolls,
so help yourself.
Okay, thanks.
Lucy, your drive-by
wasn't road rage.
It was a hit.
The victim was on her way
to testify
before Matteo Rubio's
grand jury.
We've got a problem.
Your drive-by shooting
and my front-desk poisoning
were both scheduled to testify
before the grand jury today.
In what case?
The RICO case
against Matteo Rubio.
Grey's a witness in that case.
He's on his way to testify now.
♪♪
Straight to voicemail.
Forget my head
if it wasn't attached.
That's what my dad
used to always say.
Now you're making me feel old.
Oh, boy.
I'm a police officer.
You're carrying a concealed
weapon into a courthouse.
You're right.
I was.
But now I don't have to,
'cause you're right here.
♪♪
Come on. Come on.
Stand clear.
Clear.
I need you
to focus on me, Sergeant.
Can you do that?
What? Yes. Yes.
Clear.
Are you having
any trouble breathing?
No.
Pupils fixed and dilated.
I'm calling it.
Time of death -- 16:42.
Did you hit your head
at any point?
What?
Did you hit your head?
No. No.
Um, I-I-I don't think so.
What do we got?
Knife wound to the face --
gonna need stitches.
GSW to
the left shoulder --
looks like a
through-and-through.
Vitals are good.
Alright. Alright,
let's get him up to the O.R.
Surgeon needs
to get in there,
make sure
there's no internal damage,
clean everything up,
okay?
Okay.
Hey, Doc, how is he?
He's lucky.
Hey.
They're gonna
fix you up, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Um...
Um...you --
you need to alert
Captain Maddux.
Yeah, already did.
Everything's squared away.
You just focus
on getting better, alright?
Tim?
Yeah?
Who was she?
A hitter
for Matteo Rubio.
And we think she's the shooter
from our drive-by.
She was so fast.
Here he is.
How is he?
They just took him into surgery.
Uh, he's in shock.
Wound seems superficial,
but they won't know for sure
until they open him up.
And the shooter?
She didn't make it.
Okay,
so, is the threat over?
I don't think so.
The killer at the front desk
was definitely a man.
I don't understand.
Grand juries are secret.
How did Rubio get his hands
on a witness list?
I'm gonna circle back
to A.D.A. Del Monte.
We need to find out who else was
set to testify against Rubio.
Okay, good.
Take Lucy with you.
Hey, I'll stay here, text you
when he's out of surgery.
Thanks.
Alright, listen up.
Everybody, listen up.
I want 'round-the-clock
security.
These people were bold enough
to go after a cop.
They're not just gonna
stand down now.
Got it?
- Okay, copy.
Because this is
an officer-involved shooting,
I'm gonna need to stay here
as Grey's union delegate.
Okay. Do you know
what you have to do?
Yes, sir.
Uh,
procedurally at least.
I-I don't know
what I'm gonna say to him.
He was with you
after your shooting.
Yeah. He's the reason
I made it through.
Yeah.
So do what he did.
He's always been there
for us.
Now it's time
to return the favor.
And update me the moment
he gets out of surgery.
Yes, sir.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna try and I.D.
our deceased shooter,
see if I can find out
who she was partnered with.
What Tim said --
You've killed someone
in the line of duty?
Yeah.
A month into my rookie year.
I didn't know that.
I don't talk about it much.
I get it.
Um, we work jobs
that bring us face-to-face
with death every day.
But it's different
when it's because of you.
Army Reserve.
I did a tour
right when I signed up.
Every time I think
I got a handle on you...
Listen, do you want me
to stay with you?
I can call in a sub.
No.
You go back to work.
I got Wesley
to keep me company.
Okay.
Love you.
Alright. Love you.
Okay.
Yeah, thanks.
That was Tim.
Grey's in surgery, but the wound
is not life-threatening.
Thank God.
This feels petty to ask,
but I'm not passing
Plain Clothes Day, am I?
It hasn't been
a good start.
But I could still
finish strong, right?
I'd focus on getting to the end
of shift with no more drama.
Uh-oh.
Rolled right through
a stop sign.
Afternoon, sir.
You know why I pulled you over?
Mr. Hayes.
I heard you were a cop.
I thought it was a joke.
No, um...
I think about you
every day,
what I'd say to you,
what I'd...do to you.
Okay, sir, stop.
What?
You'll arrest me?
Go. Get -- Get closer,
get closer.
- Sir, stop.
- I can say whatever I want.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Look at you.
You're -- You're a disgrace.
That's Patrick Hayes' dad.
The kid Aaron was accused
of killing?
Alright, stay back.
Are you kidding?
This is gold.
I would never hurt Patrick,
okay?
He was my best friend.
Excuse me, sir.
I am Detective Harper.
This is Aaron.
He is my trainee.
Do you know who he is?
He murdered my son.
I know
about the allegations.
Allegations?! Yeah, you might
have fooled the police,
but I know what you are.
I see through you.
Who are you with? TMZ?
Yeah, you never get tired
of feeding on my grief,
do you, you vultures?!
Morris, what are you doing, man?
Get him out of here.
Alright.
Out of here now.
You know them?
You set this up!
No. Mr. Hayes, listen.
I-I swear, okay?
My mom's doing a show,
but I don't have anything to do
with this, okay?
Y-You're making money
off of this?!
Conversation.
You're making a show?!
♪♪
Morris:
This is a live arrest.
Mr. Hayes,
I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
I'm sorry.
All the other witnesses
have been taken into
protective custody.
We need to put
undercover officers on
their home addresses.
Odds are good the assassin
will target another witness,
and we need to be set up
to catch them.
I can't do that.
You know that.
You know the grand juries
are secret.
That's why the D.A.'s office
handles all witness security.
You're doing
a bang-up job so far.
Look, I'm gonna chalk
that one up
to misplaced anger
over what happened to Wade.
The best way to keep
our witnesses safe
is for them
to catch Rubio's hit men.
If the list helps them do that,
why not share it?
Because it doesn't work
that way.
Look, I'm sorry.
I am, okay?
But the case against Rubio
is far from guaranteed.
I have to protect it.
Now, if you can bring me
some sort of definitive proof
that he's behind
these attacks,
well, that's
a different story.
Then that's
what I'll do.
Fine.
It's not right.
He's not dangerous.
If it was any other cop, he
would have never thrown a punch.
I created that situation.
We should let him go.
It's your arrest,
your call.
Can you get me
Dexter Hayes' belongings?
What are you doing?
I'll handle it from here.
It's Plain Clothes Day.
I mean, you're not supposed
to help me.
Plain Clothes Day
is over.
Look, nothing good
will come from you
talking
to Patrick's dad again.
Okay.
Go do your paperwork
somewhere else.
I'll find you after.
What's going on?
The murderer couldn't
bother to stick around
to see me go to jail?
Uh, no, he actually asked
that I release you.
And I will recommend
that the D.A. not charge.
It's the best we can do.
He shouldn't even
be a cop.
Aaron's a liar,
a sick human being.
I took him into my home.
Every time his parents went
on some month-long vacation,
where -- where do you think
he lived?
He was like
another son to me.
He...
That was all a lie.
And he killed my boy.
Look, uh, there is nothing
that I can say
that is gonna make you
change your mind.
Best thing I can do is
to offer my sincere condolences.
Lucy.
Can I grab you for a second?
Uh...Make it quick.
Right here.
What's going on?
What is this?
The list of witnesses
in the Rubio grand jury.
Wow. I-I --
But you can't tell anyone
you got it from me.
I'm serious.
Del Monte would fire me
on the spot.
Maybe even prosecute me
for leaking
confidential information.
Stop. You can't do this.
I won't let you.
But you need this
to catch the guy.
People are dead.
And if this --
We can't catch a criminal
by becoming criminals.
I...
We'll find another way.
Okay.
They just I.D.'d
Grey's shooter.
Sir.
Hey. Hey.
Come in.
How you feeling?
Like I got shot.
Talk to Luna yet?
She's in Montreal.
And I figured this is a
conversation you want to have
in person
when she gets back.
You know, uh,
a wise man once told me,
"This is not something
you want your family
to hear on the news."
You're right.
I'll call her.
And she will tear my head off
once she knows I'm okay.
When I became
Watch Commander,
I promised
she and Dominique
wouldn't have to worry
about me anymore.
It was out of your control.
She'll understand.
She'll want to install cameras
in your office
to keep an eye on you,
but she'll understand.
Yeah.
Hey, let me take care
of that.
Um, yeah, it's official --
everything hurts.
Do --
Do you need anything?
No, no, no.
I don't --
How do you do it?
I mean,
we're the same age.
Ish.
So how do you go out patrolling
the streets
and chasing suspects,
getting into shootouts
day in, day out?
Tylenol and Icy Hot.
Huh.
It wasn't
like this before.
The last time I got shot,
I pulled out my own I.V.s
and checked myself out.
Now I-I can't even
imagine it.
Maybe that's the --
Maybe that's
the difference.
I was never that guy.
I don't know what it's like
to be a cop
and not go home aching
at the end of every shift.
So what you're saying is,
I need to accept the fact
that I'm old.
Mm.
I used to think about it
all the time coming up...
...how I'd react
to taking a life.
♪♪
Then year by year
went by,
and, uh...
...I guess I thought...
...I made it.
I'd never have
to go through this.
You didn't have
a choice.
She was going
to kill you.
And any of us
would have done the same.
Right.
That doesn't help now,
but it -- it will later.
What will help now?
Nothing.
This part's just hard.
♪♪
Any movement?
No.
Alright,
thanks for coming out.
Our target is six houses up
on the right --
851 West Waverley.
It's a ShareBNB rented by our
deceased suspect, Jane Becker.
Now, Becker had a partner --
unknown male.
It's possible he's in the house
we're hitting.
Cut the power.
LAPD!
We have a search warrant!
Open the door now!
♪♪
Alright, house is clear.
Advise DWP
to restore the power.
Do you smell smoke?
Yeah.
It's a little hot outside
to be having a fire.
Looks like
we just missed him.
And he burned up some evidence
before he left.
Yeah.
Not much to work with.
Mm.
Kellen Myers.
What's going on here?
It's -- It's almost midnight.
Y-You know I'm an officer
of the court, right?
You're a paralegal,
and you're in serious trouble.
I'm calling a lawyer.
Great.
You can show her these.
Your bank statements
for the last six months.
You received four payments
of $2,500 each
from Cayman Cities
Holding Corporation.
That's Matteo Rubio's
dummy corporation.
You sold him the list
of the grand jury's witnesses.
Rubio? I-I don't even know
who that is.
I don't have time
to play games!
Two people are dead,
a cop's in the hospital,
and you're an accessory
to all of it!
I didn't know.
I-I thought they were just
gonna scare people.
I-I-I had no idea
anyone was gonna get killed.
Listen to me.
You have one chance
to make this right.
I need you to tell me
who they are,
where they are, and what exactly
did you tell them.
♪♪
They wanted a list of the names
of the witnesses.
And the prosecutor.
Any luck getting through
to the D.A.'s office?
No.
Phone lines appear to be down.
That can't be a coincidence.
I'm calling Chris.
♪♪
The D.A.
hasn't even considered
postponing
tomorrow's testimony?
Two people are dead,
and one of the killers
is still out there.
Yeah, all the more reason
to keep the grand jury convened.
Get Rubio behind bars
as soon as possible.
You think the case still has
legs with two dead witnesses?
Well, it's a setback,
but we did our homework.
You know,
we have our evidence.
Most importantly,
the rest of the witnesses
are in protective custody,
so...
He's not answering.
Try again.
♪♪
Hey, it bothers you
that I didn't share intel
with the LAPD,
doesn't it?
No.
I mean, yeah.
We're on the same side,
right?
Mostly.
But LAPD leaks like
a sieve,
so we gotta play everything
close to the vest.
That's my phone.
Lucy.
Chris, um,
where are you?
At the office.
Why?
Is Del Monte with you?
Yeah.
Okay, listen.
Someone is coming to kill him.
What?
You have to get him
out of there.
Chris?
The lights
just went out.
They just cut the power.
How far away are we?
Three minutes.
Chris, you need to hide.
I got to warn Del Monte.
No, Chris.
♪♪
Hey, Chris,
where are you?
I can't find my phone.
Sean, get down!
♪♪
Are you hit?
No. You?
No.
We got to move.
Out the back. Let's go. Go.
♪♪
Go, go, go, go, go.
Police!
Drop the weapon!
♪♪
Chris?
Lucy?
It's safe to come out.
Is Del Monte with you?
Yeah, I'm here.
♪♪
Are you okay?
Yeah.No.
I could really use
a drink.
I know today was rough,
but if it helps,
it was not the worst
Plain Clothes Day story
I've ever heard.
It's not?
No.
But it was
the most unique.
And because
I pulled the plug,
you're gonna have to do it
all again next week.
Great.
Hopefully I won't make
as many mistakes.
Yeah,
that would be good.
Yeah.
No. Unh-unh.
Point another camera
in my face,
and I will arrest you
for invasion of privacy.
Just wanted to say bravo
for today, guys.
The footage we got
was money.
Harper,
the camera loves you.
How would you feel about having
your very own makeup team?
Morris,
can I talk to you?
Have a good night.
I will see you tomorrow.
But I better not see you.
Aaron --
No, man.
You need to shut up
and listen, okay?
That film that you shot of me
and Mr. Hayes today --
it never sees
the light of day.
Well, Aaron,
it's too good not to use.
I don't care.
His pain is not a commodity,
and neither is mine.
Then why did you decide
to do the show?
Because I need
to get my life back.
But this --
this won't do that, okay?
So you're gonna destroy
those memory cards
or you and me --
we're gonna have a real problem.
You threatening
to hurt me?
No.
To fire you.
Those cards belong
to Thorsen Media,
and last time I checked,
I'm the only person
in this conversation
with that name.
♪♪
How are you doing?
Oh, I'm fine, Lucy.
♪ Trouble only finds me
Um, we should check
your vitals.
No,
you don't have to --
♪ Whenever I'm alone
That's actually
very nice.
Pulse is good, steady.
Well, that's me --
good and steady.
Your heart rate's
a little fast.
It's still
strong and manly, right?
Oh, yeah. 100%.
♪ Who's tearing who to parts
Um...
why did you try to give me
the witness list?
Were you doing it
because you thought
it was the right thing
to do,
or were you trying
to impress me?
♪ Never let you down
I, um...plead the fifth.
♪ Like you let me down
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Hitter flipped on Rubio.
Lopez picked him up
20 minutes ago.
Another mob boss on his way
to life in prison.
Good. But there's gonna be
some follow-up you need to do.
I know. Talked it through
with the Captain.
I know all about the Sergeants'
staff meeting on Mondays,
the Captains' meetings
on Fridays.
They provide lunch
from Molly's Steakhouse.
Never order the fish.
See? I got it.
And you'll be -- you'll be back
before you know it.
♪ If only for a moment
It's not I don't think
you can do it.
It's just --You just have trouble
letting go.
I know.
But this is good.
You know, it's like a trial run
for retirement.
♪ It's just
that I'm not over it ♪
You're colluding
with Luna now?
That has been going on
for a long time.
Oh, my goodness.
Dinner is served.
That's my cue.
Thanks, man.
See ya, take care.
Yep.
Grilled chicken, rice,
and veggies.
I ordered a burger.
♪ Let me down
You're colluding
with Luna now, too?
No! No.
Does that mean
you don't want it?
Maybe later.
Alright.
I'll just set it right here
for you.
Thank you.
Alright. Good night.
Nolan.
A few months ago, you were
determined to be an F.T.O.
Lately,
you hardly mention it.
Change your mind?
Oh, no.
No, not at all.
Um, I've been working hard
behind the scenes,
getting myself ready.
Tim's been giving me lots
of great advice.
I've been hoping my work as
the union rep would help me out.
It will.
So will focusing
on one area.
Robbery, narcotics, hostage
negotiation, whatever you want.
Become the department's
foremost expert at it.
Specialized knowledge jumps you
to the front of the line.
Yes, sir.
Good advice.
I will let you
get some sleep,
unless there's anything else
you need?
No, I'm good.
Thank you.
♪ Oh oh oh oh
Um...
you're gonna want to replay
that fight over and over again,
looking for a way
it could have ended differently.
There will be plenty of time
for that.
Tonight, just sleep.
I'll try.
♪♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Busted!
Oh!
What are you doing up?
Waiting for you.
How's Wade?
He hurts,
but he'll be okay.
And you?
I'll be okay, too.
Just...reopened some wounds
I thought had healed.
Do you want
to talk about it?
No.
Okay.
Then come to bed.
Honestly, I-I don't think
I could even sleep right now.
Oh.Do you want to finish
the portrait?
God, no. I don't even want
to look at it anymore.
Why not?
Because it's awful.
Oh.
I refuse
to believe that.
You are
the most talented person I know.
It's actually annoying.
Well, my winning streak
has officially ended.
♪♪
Oh, thank God.
What?
It's terrible.
I barely look human.
You could
at least pretend.
No, I couldn't.
But this is great.
This is great.
Oh, this is so great.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna hang this up.
It's -- It's proof that
there's actually
one thing in the world
you can't do.
Come.
Oh, God.
God, he's got one eye
looking at me
and one eye
looking for me.
Let's call him John-John.
It's gonna
watch us sleep.
♪♪