Help! Help me!
Oh, my God, Pete.
What happened?
You were the only one
I could call.
Okay, stay here.
I'm gonna call 911, alright?
No, no, no.
It's too late.
Will you, please,
just do me a favor?
- Of course.
After I die, could you please
roll my ashes up
into a blunt...
and smoke me?
Oh, you ass!
I almost had a heart attack!
It's jerky.
Happy Halloween.
# Whoa, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh #
What?
# Like I know
you want me to do #
There's something seriously
wrong with you.
You didn't inherit
Dad's love for Halloween?
That guy was
the king of pranks.
He loved messing with me
all the time.
Yes, my favorite prank
was when
he abandoned me
at the age of 10.
Wow. Very dark.
Nice.
So, aside from giving me
a coronary,
what are you doing
in town?
Are you kidding? L.A. is lit
during Halloween season.
I got five parties
lined up.
You didn't bring Chastity?
No. She's, uh,
stuck in Tempe.
They're doing a haunted house
at the strip club.
But I was wondering
if you still have
that open-door policy
on your guest room?
A little notice would have been
nice, but, yeah, sure.
How long would you like
to stay?
Oh, just a couple days.
Weeks. Months. I don't know.
But I do need some clothes.
And deodorant.
And a toothbrush.
Uh, I don't have anything.
Of course not.
W-Why -Why would you?
Hmm. Can you grab
the blueberries?
We don't have any.
Wha--
I just went shopping.
Hey, when you
finish something,
you need to put it on
the shopping list.
I didn't eat them.
I didn't.
Okay. Fine.
Just -Just next time,
put it on the list.
Oh, hey, did you figure out
what costume you're gonna wear
to the West Hollywood parade
tonight?
Um...not yet.
I sent you
a ton of suggestions.
No offense...
but they all sucked.
Um, o-okay. Well, just because
you say "no offense"
doesn't mean
it hurts less.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Margaret from 604.
You're a cop, right?
Yeah.
Uh, what's going on?
Hey. Stop!
No, no!
Those are delicate instruments!
Oh, go screw yourself!
Whoa. Police.
Hey.
What's going on?
They robbed me!
Okay, that is not
at all true.
Mrs. Crouch hired us
to rid her home
of an aggressive spirit.
You mean a ghost?
You guys are ghost hunters?
Yeah, we are. The spirit
in Mrs. Crouch's apartment
is rather just stubborn,
so we said that
we would do a follow-up.
For another $5,000.
She already paid them $10,000.
Our prices are in line
with industry standards.
You didn't get rid of my ghost!
Now, give me my money back!
Okay, here's
what's gonna happen.
Mrs.Crouch is gonna stop
trashing your stuff,
and you guys are going to
give me your information
so I can pass it on
to a detective.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, what are you
doing here?
I just felt like
swinging by
and seeing the best detective
in the city.
You have a client
in lockup?
That too.
Well, don't forget to pick up
candy for tonight.
And not
those variety packs
with that pathetic,
fun-sized nonsense.
We serve full-sized bars
at the Lopez-Evers abode.
Uh, good morning.
Good morning.
Um, I need a favor.
What's up?
My neighbor is being
taken advantage of.
There are these, uh,
paranormal expert,
ghost hunters,
whatever.
They're charging her
10 grand
to rid her apartment
of ghosts.
That's ridiculous.
10 grand should at least get you
a quality exorcism.
That said, making a case
against them could be tricky.
Yeah, tarot, fortune-telling,
necromancy, ghost hunting --
all the psychic arts
are legal in California.
But she's an old lady
on a fixed income.
There's no way
she can afford $10,000
on "psychic services."
Well, now, that changes
the equation.
Yeah, elder financial fraud
is a crime.
I'll look into it.
Thank you. You're the best.
Excuse me.
Hello.
This is Lucy Chen.
Um...confirming
what appointment?
Excuse me?
Your mother did what?
She pre-paid for me
to have my eggs frozen
at a fertility clinic.
I thought you and your mother
weren't talking.
She's definitely
talking now.
Seriously, what makes her think
she has the right?
Alright. Nolan...
Can you tell me what today is
and what "ACH" stands for?
Today is Halloween, and I have
no idea what "ACH" stands for.
No candy
for partial answers.
Harper?
Anything can happen.
Basically a reminder
to be extra careful
'cause today is Halloween
and Halloween is unpredictable.
Correct.
And since Officer Thorsen
has range qualifications today,
you're back riding with Nolan.
Oh, just like old times.
Yeah, without the fear of
the whole blue-page thing.
Uh, what kind of unpredictable
can we expect today?
Good question, Chen.
Lot of liquid courage.
Lot of 211's.
Teenagers snatching
little kids' candy.
Masked people running into
liquor stores.
Do they have a gun, or are they
just late for a party?
Muzzle discipline
is critical.
And?
Can you remind us how you got
your uniform torn
three Halloweens ago?
Uh...
if you get dispatched
to a loud party,
make sure they know
you're not the stripper.
We'll try to get you home
on time,
but it's Halloween, so...
Anything can happen.
Exactly.
Alright, be safe out there.
This is nice,
being together again.
It's actually a relief
riding with someone
who can handle himself.
A compliment?
How far we've come.
I am in a good place.
You know, work's good,
James is great.
I have a wonderful relationship
with my daughter.
And, I don't know, this job,
it's -it's changed everything.
Nice.
Lila excited
for Halloween?
Oh, beyond.
She's changed her costume
like 10 times this week.
And how do you
and Donovan arrange
for trick-or-treating?
We're supposed to alternate
years, but this morning,
Lila told her father and I
that she wanted to do
a family-themed costume,
like we used to wear.
That sounds...
complicated?
Yeah.
But, you know,
she has her heart
set on it,
and Donovan and I are in
a good place, so we agreed.
Hmm.
That's very enlightened
of you.
Thank you.
I mean, what's the worst
that could happen?
Seriously, why would you
jinx me like that?
Um, I should probably
take this.
Go ahead.
Hey, Chastity.
How's it going?
Terrible.
Are -Are you sitting down?
It's -It's --
It's about your brother.
He's missing.
Oh, no, he's --
He went to the store
last night,
and he went to go get
corn nuts and Fanta,
and -and no one's seen him
since, and I'm just --
I'm worried that he may have
fallen off the wagon.
He's -He's on the wagon?
Yes, and I would have called
the Tempe Police,
but they're still mad about
the glitter bomb and --
Okay, no, no, Chastity,
um, Pete's fine.
He-He's not on a bender
and he's not missing.
He's here in Los Angeles.
He's with me.
That son of a bitch.
O-Okay. You want to tell me
what's going on?
What's going on is, I am going
to kill your little brother
the next time I see him,
but before, I'm gonna rupture
his delicate parts
with a pair of stilettos
and close up all of his
openings with a hot glue gun.
O-Okay. You --
You do realize you--
you've described about
six crimes to me, right?
Ugh.
You have to hand it to her --
she's very creative.
Mm-hmm.
Happy Halloween.
Be safe out there.
Thank you.
I'm just saying,
I am only 29.
My eggs are nowhere near
their expiration date.
But clearly, my mother thinks
that I'm a pathetic loser
who's never gonna find
a partner
before her fertility clock
ticks down.
Or she's just looking out
for you,
knowing how busy you are.
Wha--
Why are you taking her side?
I'm not taking her side.
It's just --
It's a biological fact
that you have a ticking
reproductive clock.
Mm. Don't be smug about
the fact that men
can have kids
well into their 90s.
I'm not even 30
and apparently,
I need to flash-freeze
my ovaries.
It's just insurance, okay?
Look, you don't get
car insurance
hoping that
you crash your car.
The policy is a waste
of money, alright?
If your mom wants to pay
the bill, let her.
I'm gonna pretend
you didn't just compare
my fertility
to a car wreck.
I can't find my daughter.
Selina.
She's dressed
like Stitch.
Uh, ma'am, she's --
she's right over there.
No.
There were two kids
dressed as Stitch.
Okay. A parent probably
just grabbed the wrong kid.
Um, hi. My name is Tim.
What's your name?
Alton.
Okay, did your mom or dad
accidentally leave
without you, Alton?
My dad.
Okay, and what's
your dad's name?
Daddy.
Okay, I got this.
Hi. Do you know
where you live?
Oh, great. You are so smart.
Where?
In a house.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Okay.
This is gonna take a little bit
longer than I thought.
You didn't tell her
I was here, did you?
Yes, of course I did.
She was freaking out.
She thought
you'd gone missing.
Are you not aware
of the Bro Code?
'Cause rule number seven
clearly states
that when a girlfriend
asks where your bro is,
the answer is always,
"I don't know!"
God, you're the worst
half-brother ever!
I was about to say
the same thing.
Oh, good.
So you agree.
I'm the --
Okay.
You -You know what?
I can't -Pete, I got to go.
I got to go.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
415 unknown,
Third and Gardner.
People are running.
Stand by.
Get out of there!
Over there!
Zombie!
Ma'am?
Ma'am, we're here to help.
What's your name?
Ma'am, can you hear me?
#
Ugh!
You ready for round two?
Yeah?
#
Come on!
7-Adam-15,
one in custody.
On some kind of 11-3.
She's having a seizure.
You're the ones
who brought her in?
Yeah.
She tried to eat us.
Is -Is she
having a seizure?
Most likely a drug-induced
seizure.
Any idea what she took?
Given the super strength,
I'd say PCP,
but honestly, I've never seen
anything like this before.
It's got to be
some new designer drug.
Ugh. I hate Halloween.
I'll reach out when
the tox screen comes back.
Thank you.
Police.
Would I lie to you?
Invest now, buddy.
Get in on the ground floor
and I'll make you rich.
What? I'm busy.
Sir, you're the prime suspect
in a kidnapping.
Let me call you back.
Did you just
take a child
from the Mid-Wilshire
police station?
Yeah.
My son, Alton.
Sir, that is not
your son.
Hey, Selina?
Hey, could you take off
your hood, please?
Hi.
Holy crap.
I swear, I had no idea.
Hey, are you okay?
More candy.
You can ask your mom.
Let's go.
Noooooooo.
I want to stay here.
My mom doesn't let me
eat sugar.
Hello.
I'm Detective Lopez.
Oh, we are picking up
some very strange
readings in here.
Must be the ghosts
of all the con artists
I've sent to prison.
10 grand to pretend
to clean an apartment
full of ghosts
is a good hustle.
It's not a hustle.
Shh.
Just listen.
Mrs. Crouch
is on a pension,
and you two are draining
what's left of her future.
You have two options --
give her a refund,
or I'll start digging around
and see if there's
a pattern of abuse.
We are not
con artists.
Paranormal phenomena
is real science.
Now, we detected a presence
in Mrs. Crouch's home.
We set up infrared thermometers
all over the apartment
and recorded
a substantive drop
in the ambient temperature
in the bathroom.
A temperature drop which is
evidence of a spectral presence.
Or a draft.
And our UV camera
picked up this.
There. That is the spirit
we were trying to clear
from Mrs. Crouch's home.
That's a digital glitch
or your own shadow.
Spoken like
a true innocent.
You have to understand
that before it was
some marketing gimmick
to sell candy and costumes,
Halloween was the sacred day
when the veil between
our world and the next parted
and the spirits moved freely.
You misunderstand.
I'm not saying I don't believe
in evil spirits.
I'm saying
I don't believe in you.
Detective...
Mrs. Crouch
is in real danger.
And we need to get back there
to finish the cleanse.
Not happening.
I gave you a chance
to do the right thing.
You want to do this
the hard way, we'll
do this the hard way.
This will be quick.
As long as I get that free lunch
you promised me,
I am good.
Everything's in the fridge.
Help yourself.
Hey.
I love this shirt.
It makes me look like
a lumberjack.
Hey, I know you.
Nice to see you again.
What's with
the lecture face?
This isn't lecture face.
I don't have lecture face.
That is 100%
a lecture face.
I'm-a make a sandwich.
Pete, what's going on
with Chastity?
Why are you really here?
So she didn't tell you?
No, she hung up on me.
She's pissed.
Well, that's because
she's
I'm sorry, she's what?
Pren-She's nent.
She's fragrant?
She's pregnant.
What?! Pete!
So, you -you walk out
on her and let her believe
you've gone missing?
What are you --Oh, so I freaked out.
Relax, okay?
What -What exactly
about this makes you think
that I'll be a good dad,
okay?
I-I-I don't floss.
I've never had a vegetable.
I-I have the IQ
of a hummingbird,
which I'm told they're
the stupidest of the birds.
The biggest favor
I can do for this kid
is to just walk away.
You can't be serious.
You have a kid, right?
W-Would you let me babysit?
Uh, I'd be more likely
to put her in charge of you.
See?
So you're gonna do to your baby
what our dad did to me?
Yeah, I know Dad left you,
but he stayed for me,
and look how that turned out,
alright?
I just know if
I stick around,
I'm just gonna
screw it up.
Sorry to interrupt, but our
zombie suspect is conscious.
Sorry,
did you say "zombie"?
We'll finish this later.
And a hummingbird is
a proud and noble animal.
That poor kid.
Imagine having that idiot
as your father.
Guy was just clueless.
There are a lot worse
out there. Trust me.
I'm living proof that some
people should not be parents.
You think
you'll ever have kids?
Uh, honestly?
I, uh, thought I would've
had some by now.
Isabel and I,
we made all these plans --
pop out three kids,
watch them grow up,
have kids of their own.
But...
Things don't always
work out.
Which is why you think I should
make contingency plans.
Watch out!
Control, 7-Adam-100!
Possible 51-50!
Olympic at Citrus.
Male, 30s,
is now attacking my shop.
Get an additional unit
and an RA. Code 3.
Uh, Amber, hi.
I'm, uh, Nyla.
This is John.
What drug did you take?
Amber?
She was speaking earlier --
random words here and there.
It's clear that whatever
this drug is,
it has had a catastrophic effect
on her nervous system.
The damage to her brain
might be irreparable.
We should check back
with the tech guys,
see if they had any luck
opening Amber's phone.
We need to track down
her dealer.
Biter?
Yes.
We had one, too.
They ID the drug yet?
No.
Guys, honestly,
have you ever seen
anything like
this before?
You all okay?
Nothing broken,
nothing bleeding.
Yeah,
but plenty is sore.
The Intel Unit says
this new drug is called Bomb-X,
and it's being sold on something
called ClipTalk.
That's a new
social media app.
Once we figure out which
hashtags are trending,
we'll be able to whittle it down
to our dealer.
Until then,
we're just playing catch-up,
and a lot of innocent people
are getting hurt.
What do you
want us to do, Sarge?
Nothing.
I called in extra personnel
for the midnight shift.
I'm going
to brief them now.
You're all end of watch.
And what are you doing?
Stay with you.
Sergeant Reeves is covering two
districts on this crazy night.
The least I can do
is help.
Thanks.
It was all a big
misunderstanding.
No. The Edwards
took advantage of you.
Uh, no, darling.
I was wrong.
My ghost hasn't
made a peep in hours.
All that tinkering
they did worked.
Or they could have caused
the paranormal activity,
in which case, they also
could have made it stop.
Sometimes,
people prey on seniors.
You know what they do
even more often?
Underestimate us.
I'm not an idiot.
No, ma'am. I didn't mean
to suggest that you were.
As soon as strange things
started happening,
I did my research.
Let me tell you,
there's no way this building
isn't...haunted.
Dare I ask
what you're in for?
Hi.
Pete.
I hate you.
Okay.
Yeah, you make me think.
I don't like thinking.
Yeah, well, thinking sucks,
but sometimes,
that's the price you pay
for being an adult.
Yeah, well, you know, I'm not
gonna ghost Chastity, okay?
If she wants to have a baby,
then I'll man up, you know,
I'll take care
of my family,
but I-I don't know
what I'm doing.
I don't have any skills.
Start with what you know.
Yeah, but all I know how
to do is, you know, gamble
and, like, do drugs,
and, you know,
I don't even do that anymore.
Well, let's start with that.
Okay, gambling.
Um, you, uh --
you need patience,
uh, strategic thinking, uh,
uh, optimism,
being able to read people.
Your knowledge
of the drug trade.
You could...
Uh, you...
You.
You could help us.
Hey, do you know anything
about buying drugs
through ClipTalk?
Yeah.
Only, like, everything.
Really?
Yeah. You, uh --
You want me to help you
get drugs?
I --
I don't think
I could do that.
I don't think NA would be
too proud of that.
I -It's not for me,
and I would never do anything
to endanger your sobriety.
I just --
If you could give us
any insight on Bomb-X,
you could help
a lot of people, Pete.
Alright.
Check this out.
It's actually pretty easy
to do.
So you just go on here,
and his name
is Flamebroiled6060,
which is street slang
for getting lit.
Pete.
Yeah?
How'd you like to make
500 bucks?
Can I hold your gun?
No.
Please?
Come on.
You never let me
hold the gun.
I think your building
is haunted.
I did some research,
and while our ghost busters
may be frauds,
this place is destined to be
a Netflix documentary.
What happened?
In 1912, the building
was constructed
as a textile factory.
A year later, seven workers
died in a fire.
1927, a speakeasy opens
in the basement.
It closes within the year.
Employees kept quitting,
driven out by the sounds
of people screaming
as they died.
That's awful.
The building shuts down during
the Depression,
doesn't open again
until the '60s,
when a charming,
young musician
decides to use it
for his recording studio.
Brian Wilson?
Charles Manson.
Mnh.
In the aughts, the building
was purchased
and converted into
the hipster catnip apartments
we see before us.
A worker goes missing
during construction.
A week later, he's found
in one of the walls,
surrounded by
scratch marks,
as if he tried to
claw his way out.
Okay. Let's move.
I know an underpass
that stays pretty warm
this time of year.
No, we are not moving.
Look, this is all creepy
and just not great,
but ghosts aren't real.
The only real problem
are the con artists
that are preying on
Mrs. Crouch.
She's the one who pointed me
to the building's history.
And unfortunately,
she doesn't want our help.
But elder fraud goes way down
when a trusted friend
or a family member
or nosy neighbor...
Well......takes an interest.
So I'm 99% certain our
ghost hunters won't be back.
Man. I hope I have a neighbor
as caring as me
when I'm old and alone.
Rough week
on the dating market?
It is so much worse
than that.
My mother has literally paid
to have my eggs
harvested and frozen.
I wouldn't laugh
if I were you.
Life sneaks up on you fast,
Miss I-just-went-through-puberty.
Hey, if she wants to pay
for it, why not?
Egg freezing costs
thousands of dollars.
Now you can do it
for free.
The real cost
is my peace of mind
every time my mother asks me
when I'm gonna take
her grandkids
out of the deep freeze.
So then don't freeze your eggs
and just adopt.
It's not like there's
a shortage of kids out
there who need it.
Well, I got to get home
for Jack's first Halloween.
Call me if you need
recommendations for movers.
We're not moving.
Uh-huh.
#
Oh, hey, look,
it's Mom.
#
You're late.
Well, given that
I was just informed
about our family-themed
costume today,
I think I deserve
a little credit.
Okay.
But you look super cute,
baby girl.
Thanks.
You make a great
Rey Skywalker.
Oh. Are you just
saying that
because I am
a real-life badass,
or because I look good
holding a lightsaber?
Uh, both?
Hmm, that was
a good answer.
Hmm, okay.
Thanks for coming,
though.
And for wearing
the whole costume.
It really means a lot
to her.
Well, thanks for the invite.
It means a lot to me.
Nyla, is that you?
Mrs. Dolinsky.
So great to see you two
back together again.
I never liked
that Penelope.
Uh, I'm still dating
Penelope.
Yeah, we're --
we're not back together.
We are just reunited to fight
for the Rebel Alliance.
Happy Halloween.
This is gonna be
a long night, huh?
Yep.
Hey, thanks for
coming with me.
I know it's not really
your thing,
and I really appreciate
the company.
I promised myself
I'd try new things.
Or old things, I guess.
You couldn't have picked,
you know,
costumes from
this century?
Well, you know,
Bonnie and Clyde are not old,
they are iconic.
Mm.
Gosh, why is it
always so cold
in this bathroom?
'Cause like 20 people
died in here.
Oh, my gosh.
Don't even --
#
What --
Oh.
That's why it's always
so cold in here.
Give me a hand.
Whoa, uh, that's...
creepy.
You heard the history.
This building has been
repurposed and subdivided
so many times,
I bet there are little
nooks and crannies
all over the place.
Okay. You stay here.
I will be right back.
Yeah, like I'm
really gonna let you
just climb through the gates
of hell by yourself.
Have you ever seen
a horror movie?
Fine.
You can come.
Yes!
Okay.
Okay, stay close.
#
Oof.
Watch your step.
Tamara:
Someone's been back here.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-oh.
Now do you believe I didn't
eat all the blueberries?
The ghost who's been living
in our walls did.
So Pete set up a controlled buy
with the Bomb-X dealer.
And you know your way
around ClipTalk?
Oh, yeah. I used to use it
to get ketamine
and Molly
and shrooms and --
Something you might
not want to admit in
a room full of cops.
Uh, I mean alle--
allegedly did...that.
Anyway, who's gonna
actually buy the drugs,
like, in real life?
No offense, but you fit
the profile.
Yeah. Totally.
I get that.
I just -Uh, the thing is,
I don't really want to be,
like, touching the drugs,
because once I get
my hands on it,
I don't think I could trust
myself around it,
'cause I don't really have
great self-restraint.
We'll have eyes on you
the whole time, alright?
You'll never have a chance
to use the drugs. I promise.
If you're uncomfortable
for any reason,
we'll find another way.
No, no.
I-I got it.
And you'll -you'll be
looking out for me, right?
I'll be looking out
for you.
Thanks for stepping in.
And good luck.
Alright. So you're
gonna get wired up
and go in, take the cash
that we give you,
and buy the Bomb-X.
Here's the important part --
Clean him out.
Buy everything.
That way, he has to go back
to his supplier.
Okay, and then
we follow him.
That's when
At that point, you are done.
One more thing.
You have to be
strip-searched. Twice.
Uh, before and after.
In front of two witnesses.
You cops really do like it
freaky, huh?
It's so the dealer's defense
team can't claim later
that you had drugs on you
before you made the buy.
Alright.
Let's get this over with.
Might as well start
with the holes.
Pete, Pete, Pete, Pete, Pete!
Yeah?
Not here.
What the --?
No?
Not here.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Happy Halloween.
She's out.
She did hit a record number
of houses this year.
Is she okay under there?
Uh, I asked her if she wanted
to take it off, but, uh,
she threatened me
with bodily injury.
Freshen you up?
Yeah. Sure.
Why not?
Oh.
I am not used to walking miles
in $6 pleather boots.
Maybe next year, we can steer
her towards a family
that wears
comfy track suits.
Mm.
Like "The Royal Tenenbaums"?
Exactly.
We used to love that film.
Yeah.
You know, I'm sorry
it got awkward today
with people thinking
that we were back together.
But seeing her so happy
made it worth it.
Look, I know that we're
supposed to split holidays,
but she's just growing up
so fast,
and I hate the idea of missing
any more time with her.
I know what you mean.
Maybe we can
come up with, um...
a new schedule.
Something a bit more fluid.
I'd like that.
To us...
and being more...
fluid.
So it's not a ghost.
There is someone
living in our walls.
Happy Halloween.
I'm getting major
stalker vibes.
Mm.
Oh.
Yeah.
For Margaret Ward, 604.
What was that?
Um, I don't know.
I hope it was
the pipes, though.
Okay, um, we're gonna
go check it out.
I'll call it in.
Okay.
Watch your head.
Peepholes.
Eww.
Yeah.
Look, Margaret's doing
laundry on Halloween?
We should invite her
to go out with us.
Yeah, right after we warn her
she's being creeped
by a stalker.
Margaret!
Look out!
We need
to get in there.
There has to be
a door or hatch.
He got in there somehow.
You stay here.
Hey! Police!
Drop the weapon!
No, no, no, no.
Come on.
Yes! Yes!
Yes, yes!
Thank you.
This is
Sergeant Tim Bradford.
Today's date
is October 31st.
We're conducting
a "Buy-Walk" operation,
using CI number 081316.
Tonight's buy
targets a narcotic
with the street name
of Bomb-X.
After the buy, we will tail
the suspect to his SOS.
You guys, uh -You guys
still hear me over there?
You bet, Pete.
We can still hear you.
Alright.
I'm, uh -I'm going in.
Hello?
Do those burgers
come flamebroiled?
I know you?
Yeah, we, uh --
we texted a few times.
You "eggplant emoji 70"?
Yeah. Uh, "eggplant emoji 69"
was already taken.
Okay. Let me see it.
Put the money
in the car.
I'll tell you where it is.
Six pack, right?
Yeah, well, what started
as a small get-together
has now turned into
a bigger party.
Like, "boat" big,
if you know what I'm saying.
You want a boat?
A full boat?
I don't have that much
on me.
Well, how much do you have?
I got 80 left.
That's four grand.
You got that kind of cash?
How fast
can you get the rest?
That was awesome!
You did great!
Yeah.
The -The drugs?
Right.
Just looks like
a super-fun time.
Yeah. A fun time that
turns you into a zombie
and melts your brain.
Right. Yeah.
Got to say, not bad.
Air Three has the dealer on
the 10 East towards downtown.
We got to go.
Right.
Listen, Pete, um...
great job.
I'm really proud of you.
Thank you.
Can I have the money now?
I'm serious.
It took guts to do what you did.
No, I know.
I'm serious, too.
Could I please have
the money now?
Okay, Officer Jan will drive you
back to the station.
They'll strip search you again,
make sure you didn't keep any,
and they'll pay you.
Great. Normally I'd say,
"Lucky you,"
but I was sweating balls
out there.
Okay.
Let's go.
Control, 7-Adam-100.
Suspect just stopped outside
the Los Angeles Theater.
What's the ETA on Metro?
7-Adam-100, Metro
landing in 15 minutes.
This is ridiculous.
We're in the middle of an op
and there's no backup?
It's Halloween.
Alright,
so what do we do?
Do we go after him
or wait for backup?
We go after him.
There's other exits
on that building.
We can't chance him
getting resupplied
and those drugs
hitting the streets.
Right answer.
#
Ready?
Police!
Stay right where you are!
Show me your hands!
Now!
Turn around!
Interlock your fingers
behind your head.
Sit down.
#
You okay?
Ask me later.
Control, we need an RA
to our location.
Three suspects in custody.
Mm.
Oh, my God.
Ah.
How much did we drink
last night?
I don't remember.
Mm. So too much.
Daddy?
Don't -Don't come in.
Uh, I'm getting dressed.
Can I have pancakes
for breakfast?
And syrup?
And can I have some more
of my candy?
Whatever you want,
sweetheart.
I-I-I-I don't want to
confuse her.
Yeah.
Or get her hopes up
that we are back together.
No.
So what do we do?
Uh, you -you go make
her pancakes.
I will do what
any mature single parent does
and hide in the closet.
#
Did you get any sleep?
Considering we went to bed
an hour ago, no.
Look, last night was something
out of a nightmare,
and if you're not feeling safe
being here right now,
we can get a hotel
or something.
I've slept in a lot
of creepy places.
Never had a badass superhero
protecting me,
so this is the safest
I've ever felt.
Aww.
Oh.
Hey!
Hey.
I just wanted to let you know
that if you hear any noises,
it's TID processing the scene,
not ghosts.
Yes. Because ghosts
do not exist.
Agree to disagree.
So, uh, did you decide what
to do about your eggs?
Uh, I-I'm gonna make an
appointment for a consultation.
And then we'll see.
Sounds like a solid plan.
And the fact that babies
are crying machines
who never sleep for more
than three hours in a row
and you can't tell whether
they're smiling or have gas
and every time you change
their diaper, they pee on you.
Don't let any of that
dissuade you
from the joys of motherhood,
okay?
Well, when you put it that way,
I mean, I...
I can't wait.
Me either.
Kidding.
I don't want to have a kid for
at least, like, another year.
Again, kidding.
God, you're so easy.
Seriously, though, Jack is
the best thing in my life.
And I wish the same for you,
whenever you're ready.
Thanks.
I know you were just kidding,
but, um,
we should probably talk about
birth control, and --
and -and --
and just general sex education
would be good.
I'd rather be
possessed.
Take it back.
It was a joke.
Fine.
I-I take it back.
Thank God.
I fed her pancakes,
candy bars, and soda.
I'm a terrible father, but she
won't be coming in here.
Thank you for the shirt.
I will get it back to you later.
Of course.
#
I bought a ring.
Excuse me?
An engagement ring.
Donovan, last night
was fun and all,
but we really shouldn't --
For Penelope.
I was...
planning to propose.
And you still should.
I mean, Penelope is great,
despite what
Mrs. Dolinsky thinks.
And she is really sweet
with Lila.
What about last night?
We fell into
a comfortable routine.
And now we both
have to move on.
Hey, look, we messed up, but
that will never happen again,
which means it's in the past,
so let's not let it blow
up our futures, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
#
So...
you...
you're going out
the window?
Yeah.
#
Well, I am all packed.
You didn't even bring
a toothbrush.
Are you just taking
a bunch of my clothes?
No.
Hey, man, uh,
thanks for, like, uh,
you know, all your help
in making me a CI.
That was really cool.
I didn't know you could make
money buying drugs.
Yeah, yeah.
Even so,
I might skip listing that
under "skills" on your rsum.
Hey, uh, not to get
all sappy and crap,
but, uh,
thanks for believing in me.
Uh, I kinda believe in myself
now a little bit,
and I've decided I'm gonna be
a responsible adult
and go back to Tempe
and fix things up with Chastity.
And I'll be the dad
that, you know,
our dad could never be.
Pete, I have no doubt.
I see you!
I'll get that.
We're wild and free
Thank you.
There he is.
Pete, listen to me --
Hey.
Just hear me out, okay?
I have a whole speech
prepared,
and it's not gonna
be that great,
so please don't get mad,
but I-I don't have
a lot to offer.
But you already know that
because you know me.
Pete --
No.
Please --
Please just
let me finish.
Okay.
Chastity Evelyn Sneed,
I want to be
your baby daddy.
I do.
I want to be the best dad
that I can be for our child.
So will you please --
Stop talking.
I'm not pregnant.
Wait, what? Seriously?
Seriously.
Yes! Oh, my God!
That is fantastic news.
Whew.
Wait, I'm actually --
I might be a little sad.
Nah. Not even a little.
I feel great!
We should celebrate.
You want to go to Vegas
or something?
Yes!
I'm -I'm sorry.
Pete,
you just finished saying
you wanted to start being
a responsible adult.
Yes. Yes.
That was New Pete.
But I'm Old Pete.
Old Pete is back
'cause new Pete
is no longer required.
And Old Pete
wants to go to Vegas
and go to a strip club
and make it rain.
What do you think?
Should we go?
Yeah.
Cool.
Bye, John.
Good luck, Chastity.
Thanks!
Later, nerd.
Thanks for having me.
I'll see you soon.
Maybe no rush on that.
No, I-I will be back.
Call first?
Nope!