Previously on "The Rookie"...
- Bailey.
- Jason.
- I'm John Nolan. And you are?
- Her husband.
I'm trying to protect this city.
So you think putting
a 16-year-old into juvie
is gonna turn the tide
in the war on drugs?
I am in a good place. James is great.
- What did you find out?
- Jason Wyler
is the most charming man on the planet.
He whispers in all the right ears,
and whoever is his enemy,
ends up on the wrong end of a shank.
What is happening? Why am I...
He's framing me.
Hearing that she's finally
facing some consequences,
- it does well for my spirit.
- I know who you are now.
And I'm coming for you.
Let's talk about what's next.
Well, it's pretty straightforward.
You can go to trial, fight the charges,
or take a plea.
And if I fight and lose?
Most likely, you'll do prison time.
And if I take a plea?
I feel confident,
that we could get
a mandatory treatment program
and probation.
But I would still have
a drug charge on my record,
and at minimum,
I would be out of the Army Reserve
and I'd probably be fired
from the LAFD.
I would lose everything
that matters to me.
Except for you.
What?
It's nothing.
It's not nothing.
And I can't take another round
- of gaslighting right now.
- Okay, so,
the Department frowns
on officers fraternizing
with convicted felons.
They can frown all they want.
They can't fire me.
Everyone who's important
knows you're innocent.
But just dating me would hold you back.
I gotta give it to Jason...
he really planned this perfectly.
You know, there is still
a third option.
We prove your innocence
and we take him down.
Morning.
Um...
What were you doing up all night?
Legal research.
Researching what?
Do you remember that, uh,
kid I was telling you about... Tyler?
- Oh, the one who robbed the liquor store...
- Yes.
and then gave the store owner
a heart attack,
and the clown from the DA's
office blamed you for it?
No, I don't remember that.
Anyway, good news...
um, the store owner
was released from the hospital.
She's gonna be fine.
Amazing. I bet Tyler's relieved.
Yeah, but he's not
out of the woods yet.
I have been up all night
trying to research ways that
the state can show him leniency.
I've just got to convince that clown
to charge him as a minor.
Well, Tyler's lucky he
has you looking out for him.
- Aww.
- I knew I was.
Oh.
I mean, not that long ago,
I was on the streets,
as desperate as he was,
and then I did the smartest
thing I think I've ever done...
Steal your car.
Okay. Agree to disagree.
No, seriously. Crime totally pays.
And Tyler's lucky to have you.
You're cute!
This is nice.
Actually spending the night together.
Doing couple things
in the morning before work.
Yeah, who knew we had
to share custody schedules
before we hooked up?
I actually should get going though,
I gotta...
I gotta do a thing.
That sounds ominous.
No, it's fine. I just have to have a,
a talk with Curtis Jones.
About Tyler.
Wait. Is he still leaning
on Tyler's family for money?
Yeah, and I-I need to convince Curtis
to cut his losses and let it go.
Okay, well, I'm coming with you.
- No.
- Yes, I'm...
Nyla, no.
No, you can't be there. Look, if,
if word gets out that a cop
is hovering on my shoulder,
they'll stop trusting me.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but you're dating a cop,
so that's gonna get around.
I know, which means
I have to work extra hard
to stay independent.
Look, if I lose the trust
with the community,
I'll never get it back.
I hear you, but I don't like it.
And Curtis is a dangerous guy, and...
If anything were to happen to you,
I'd be sad for, like,
at least a couple days.
Funny. Funny.
But I can handle myself.
Alright?
I'll call you after.
I wish we could open an official
investigation on this.
No, sir, I get it, there's not even
circumstantial evidence
connecting Jason
to planting those drugs.
Thank you, again, for authorizing my...
- "vacation."
- Of course.
Take as much time as you need.
So, what's your plan?
Find the money.
I mean, those drugs cost upwards
of 10 grand,
but according to my skip tracer,
Jason's broke.
He had to pay restitution
for his embezzlement conviction,
and he's been working
a minimum-wage job
ever since his release.
So chances are, he's mixed up
in something illegal
that gives him access
to money or drugs or both.
And I'm gonna follow him till
I find out exactly what it is.
Call me as soon as you have
something actionable,
even if it's a simple parole violation.
Once he's in custody,
he's more likely to crack.
I gotta go. Caught a homicide.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- Thank you.
Say, listen, Nolan,
there's something
you need to think about.
If Bailey assumes fault
for the drugs...
I know, if I can't prove
Jason planted those drugs,
I'll have to choose between my career
and the woman I love.
No biggie.
Thanks.
ADA Sanford.
Officer Chen.
Did you hear the news?
The store owner from
Tyler's case pulled through.
- I heard.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm as relieved as you are.
Great. So,
let's continue, with the positivity.
Charge Tyler as a minor.
He committed a crime with a gun.
It was unloaded.
Look, I'm not saying that
there shouldn't be consequences,
but he's 16.
He's not old enough to drink,
vote, join the military,
and you want to lock him up
with a bunch of grown men?
- Look, studies show that...
- No, please,
don't quote studies at me.
And definitely don't start lecturing me
about the science
of stilldeveloping brains
in men under 21.
I wasn't gonna do that.
Look, if Tyler becomes a CI
against his crew,
I can definitely give him a break.
Uh...
Wait, s-sorry. Let me...
Let me just get this clear.
So, instead of risking his life
in prison,
you want to risk his life
on the streets?
Do you understand that he is
a low-level drug runner?
He is the bottom of the food chain.
Nobody in his crew is
gonna even trust him,
with any real intel.
- Everything okay?
- Yes.
Mr., uh, Rookie ADA here
was telling me
how he was gonna make his bones
- by ending a kid's life.
- Okay.
You're clearly feeling a
little dramatic this morning,
and I have to go to court.
I will be following up with you!
Can you believe the nerve of that guy,
calling me dramatic?
I mean... Um, do not start.
Exactly how many cups of coffee
did you have this morning?
I'm just going to apologize
to you right now.
Um, it's gonna be a really
long day for you, and...
And I'm sorry.
- Aaron.
- Mom, what are you doing here?
Hi, baby. Mwah.
Look at you in this uniform.
How handsome.
Look, I said no yesterday,
and I meant it, okay?
- Uh-huh.
- So please stop asking.
But you're not thinking it through.
- The hell I'm not.
- Whoa, what's the problem?
Nothing, just having a
conversation with my mother.
Now I know you did not just speak
to your mother in that tone.
Ma'am, I am Nyla Harper,
Aaron's training officer,
and he is going to apologize
to you right now,
or I will write him up, for conduct
unbecoming of an officer.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
And thank you, Nyla.
Of course, Mrs. Thorsen.
- It's Yvonne.
- Yvonne.
See you in the shop.
Oh.
I like her.
- Look, Mom...
- I like her.
I'm sorry for going off, okay?
But I don't want to be a part
of this reality TV show.
Sweetie, it's only gonna help you.
How?
By disrespecting the memory of Patrick?
By trivializing the time
I've spent in prison
for a crime I didn't commit?
Not if we control the narrative.
Mom,
I love you, okay?
You've been on my side
through everything, but,
the answer's no.
Now I have to go.
I think this may be
our strangest date yet.
Really? Stranger than
fighting a Russian spy?
We're surveilling your
excon current husband
who has framed you for a drug crime.
Estranged ex-con current husband.
Oh, good.
- Hey, Randy.
- Skip Tracer Randy here!
Yes. I know, Randy.
I said your name.
Oh, well, maybe you know
12 Randys, I don't know.
Would you like to know what I found,
or do you want to keep
making me feel bad
about how I put myself out
in the world?
No. No, Randy, you're right.
I'm sorry. What did you get?
Jason listed an SRO downtown
as his current address,
but the man at the front desk says
he's only seen him once or twice.
So he could be staying somewhere else.
That could be a
violation of his parole.
Mm-hmm.
- That is correct.
I'll call back if I find anything else.
Thank you, Randy.
Well, that makes sense.
Jason is a total snob.
Is this really the best we can do?
Just spy on him until he hopefully
does something overtly criminal?
Welcome to police work.
We're never gonna catch him
by being reactive.
He's too smart.
We have to get in his head.
If that's, really,
what you want to do,
I know who to talk to, but it would
officially cement this as
1,000% the strangest date yet.
Well, when you put it that way...
At this point, you should
probably deputize me.
Hello.
Who did you bring for me, John?
Oscar, this is Lieutenant Nune.
Bailey.
I'm Jason Wyler's...
- Wife.
- Well, I'd salute you,
but I can't get my
arm over my shoulder.
I'm told you're an expert,
in narcissist psychopaths.
Guilty as charged.
Literally.
We need your help
to get inside his head,
figure out what he's gonna do next.
And I would love to do that.
I just need to figure out
what I get out of it.
Oscar.
I wrote a letter,
to get you transferred out of here.
And that's what I got yesterday.
Let's discuss what I get today.
Today, I go to the Warden's office
and rip up yesterday's letter.
- You're bluffing.
- Let's go.
Okay, fine. I'll help you.
Um, alright, where do we stand?
Jason and I were married for a year,
before he went to prison.
During that time,
he was psychologically abusive,
he tore me down constantly,
and terrorized me,
when I asked for a divorce.
Two weeks ago, he got out of jail and,
set out to ruin my life.
He planted drugs in her car
and got her arrested.
Okay, so...
He's highly intelligent,
he's very good at getting
inside people's heads,
and pitting people against one another.
He's also deeply insecure.
That's why he's constantly
pounding you down,
making you small.
It's the only way
he can make himself big.
How do we use that against him?
Well, best way to throw
him off of his game is...
Demean him.
Make him feel stupid.
Belittle him.
Of course, he's gonna retaliate,
like, ten-fold.
How did he get his hands on those drugs
- in the first place?
- Probably a contact in prison.
Whoever it was he was paying
for protection on the inside.
But he wouldn't have gotten
the drugs for free.
Well, it's not hard to get money,
I mean,
if you're willing to con someone.
In fact, there's an entire network
of nightingales out there
that are just waiting
to help rehabilitate
some poor, misunderstood man.
Speaking from experience?
I get a little money in
my commissary account.
They get a romantic fantasy.
I mean...
Everybody wins.
Now, your boy, though,
he's playing the long game.
He's probably targeted
a dozen or so women
just to find the right one.
The warden will have
copies of all of Jason's mail.
- We can start there.
- Yeah.
Alright. Thank you.
Thanks.
You called us?
Yeah, a jogger found a
female DB under the overpass.
Blunt force trauma to the head.
Dump job.
Looks like she's been here
about 24 hours.
Found an ID on her.
Rebecca Price, 18 years old.
Sounds like you got it handled.
What do you need a sergeant for?
I don't. I need Lucy.
Do you know her?
No. Uh, why?
Your roommate does.
Alright, how do you want
to handle this?
I don't know. I've...
I've never delivered
a death notification
to someone I care about.
I know what to do as a cop,
and I know how to do it as a roommate,
but, you know,
those are different approaches.
Just be a friend.
And if you need a cop, tag me in.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Come in.
Forget something?
No.
They found a body, this morning.
It was your friend. Becca.
What?
No.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
No, i-it can't be her.
It wasn't Becca.
- I'll call her.
- I'm sorry.
It definitely was her.
There was a photo of the
two of you on her phone.
Oh, look.
Here's one of mine.
A desperate plea
to respond to my lawyer.
Fun memento.
Here's one from Jason
to an Evelyn Reed.
"When we met, I was so broken."
"You healed me."
Oh, he's still using
the same material he used on me.
I can't believe I was this stupid.
No, you weren't stupid.
You were just...
Trusting.
Here's one from Evelyn back to Jason.
"Dear Jason,"
"I must have read your
last letter a thousand times."
"Though steel bars may
separate our bodies,"
"they can't separate our souls."
Barf.
But that does sound like someone
who would do anything for him.
What's her address?
Did Becca ever mention
someone she was scared of?
No.
But we haven't talked in a while.
Almost three months.
With school and
moving in here, I just lost track.
Okay, any idea where she was crashing?
She mostly lived on the street.
There was a shelter
that sometimes had room.
And a couple of kids
who had families who'd
let you sleep on the
floor every once in a while.
And if you were desperate enough,
there was always swiping.
What's that?
You go on ClipTalk,
and just swipe until you
find someone to hook up with.
And if you're lucky,
you might get a warm shower and a meal,
when it's all over.
Okay, if she was still
doing that,
we need a list of the guys
she met up with.
I'll reach out to the tech department,
see if they can get into her account.
No. I bet I can guess her password.
So,
what's the deal with your mom?
That is a long
and boring story.
Which, stakeouts are made for.
Oh, is that what we're doing here?
- Who are we staking out?
- We're just keeping an eye on a friend.
Is it one of those guys?
Stop trying to change the subject.
- You and your mom.
- Look, it's complicated.
You're gonna have to threaten me with a
blue page,
if you want me to say any more.
Alright. Fair enough.
Oh, now it makes sense.
Why didn't you just say we was here
- to watch your boyfriend's back?
- Look, James is looking out
for a neighborhood kid.
He's pushing back
against a local dealer,
so we are here in case
anything goes sideways.
Look, I heard you're still
trying to collect Tyler's debt
from some of his family members.
The kid owes me.
Curtis, he-he's in jail
'cause he tried to get your money.
It's not my fault he can't
stick up a liquor store.
Uh, Harper.
You have got to be kidding me.
I assume we should stop him, yeah?
7-Adam-19,
Code 6 on a 459.
Suspect is a Hispanic male,
blue jeans, grey jacket.
Hey! Stop right there!
Stop! Hey!
Hey. You okay?
You alright?
You okay? You okay?
- Oh, that's deep.
- You're gonna need stitches.
Yeah, and couple's therapy.
I don't follow.
I promised James
I'd mind my own business.
Yeah, you're definitely busted.
7-Adam-19.
I need additional units
to follow our 459 suspect,
last seen at Grant and Lennox.
I also need an RA
for an injured officer.
Alright, Lopez sent a PDF
of Becca's ClipTalk account.
It looks like
she was routinely hooking up
with four different guys.
No DMs indicating that they made plans
to meet up in the past week.
Yeah, well, Lopez should
look into all of them.
ClipTalk might not be
the only way they communicate.
You okay?
Yeah, Tamara knew about the whole
swiping thing, like, right away.
Did you get the impression that maybe
she used to do it herself?
She ever mention it to you?
As close as we are, there's a lot
she won't talk about.
Don't take it personally.
She might just have a hard time
opening up to you.
But I'm sure Tamara will
share when she's ready to.
Who are you?
- I'm Jason's wife.
- Right.
The bitch who won't give him a divorce
'cause she's obsessed, and you're
the crooked cop boyfriend.
- Excuse me?
- Okay.
Ma'am, none of that is true.
- May we come in and talk?
- Hell no.
Ms. Reed, Jason is a dangerous
and manipulative man
who may be involved
in illegal activities.
- Lies.
- Okay, how about this?
Is Jason living here?
Because if he is, he has not reported
this address to his PO,
which means I can report the violation
of his parole in one phone call.
If you've aided in any of the crimes
he's committed in any way,
you can be charged as an accessory.
Or...
How about we just talk?
Jason said that you
might try to get me to
turn on him.
It isn't gonna work, so,
come in and say
whatever you have to say,
and then go.
He told you about his mother, right?
How close they were?
How broken he was when she died?
- May I sit?
- Uh-huh.
That was what first drew me to him.
That depth of feeling.
When we first met,
my father had just died,
and I was a wreck.
Jason was the only person
who understood.
He didn't try to fix me.
He just listened.
He held my hand,
made me his entire world.
So I made him mine.
I had no one else but him.
And he started chipping away at me.
I wasn't smart enough,
thin enough, pretty enough.
But I was lucky to have him...
because who else could ever want me?
I wanted to die.
I was even planning how I would do it.
That was when I finally woke up.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me for asking.
- Is Jason's car in your name?
- Yeah.
Because he's an ex-con, so he said it
would be hard for him to get a loan.
Has he ever asked you to make large
- cash deposits?
- Yes.
And where do you think
that money comes from?
I didn't ask.
Has he ever asked you to buy a gun?
Am I in trouble?
Not if you help us.
So sorry to keep you waiting.
Yeah, uh, I'm all stitched
and ready to go,
so why did I have to hang around?
Your lab work came back,
and I wanted to talk to you about it.
What? Am I...
- Am I sick or something?
- No.
You're six weeks pregnant.
There you go.
- It's all yours.
- Thank you.
- We really appreciate this.
- I'm just...
I'm glad I found out the
truth before it was too late.
Oh, there's one more thing.
Alright,
you think there's something in here
we can use against him?
Well, Jason is good,
but he's far from perfect.
He's gonna mess up at some point.
We just need to be there when he does.
Hey. I'm home
and I'm starving.
What the hell are you doing here?
Th-this is harassment, alright?
Uh, you-you both need to leave.
You okay, babe?
You don't have to listen to
them, you know?
- You have rights.
- I know.
Get out.
What? Oh, come on.
I-I told you,
they're trying to frame me.
Now, you are too smart to fall for
whatever it is that
they're trying to tell you.
Bailey told me everything.
You used all the same lies on
her that you used on me.
Bailey is a very sick woman,
a drug addict, paranoid, delusional...
No, I need you to leave now.
This is my house,
and I want you to leave.
And don't bother coming back.
A restraining order will be
filed before you hit the street.
Well, I look forward
to having your badge
after I win my lawsuit
against the LAPD.
Hey, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- That stays here.
- That's mine.
No, it's mine.
I paid for this.
I paid for all of that.
Fine.
Oh! Want me to light them up?
What?
That green car
just made an illegal turn.
Oh, uh...
No.
Are you okay?
I mean, you've been pretty quiet since
we left the hospital.
Nah, it's just, uh...
Uh, I'm pregnant.
Oh!
Congratulations?
Yeah, I mean, uh, they just
told me at the hospital.
And it was unexpected, huh?
Uh, after Lila,
I had some serious complications,
and I was told that
I couldn't get pregnant.
Clearly, I should have
followed up with a specialist.
Are you worried about how James
is gonna take the news?
James is amazing.
But we've only been together
a few months, and I...
- We never thought that...
- Yeah.
That sounds like a lot to process.
Yeah.
So, what are you gonna do?
Avoid dealing with it
until absolutely necessary.
Yeah.
I use that method a lot.
What the hell
am I doing here?
Martin, are you familiar with
a girl named Becca Price?
Uh, yeah.
- We're friends.
- Friends?
With an 18-year-old?
How about she found you
looking for sex on ClipTalk
a few months ago,
and you've been hooking up
every now and then
in exchange for letting her
sleep in your bed.
Look, what is she saying?
'Cause I don't know if you know,
but that girl is homeless,
unstable.
She's probably on drugs or something.
She's dead.
What?
I didn't...
That wasn't me.
Where were you last night?
At home.
Look, Becca did come over,
but only for a few minutes.
I swear.
- What time?
- Eight-ish.
It was definitely before 9:00.
That's when my girlfriend got home.
Your girlfriend?
Yeah, she travels.
- I get lonely.
- What did Becca want?
A place to sleep, a shower.
I told her my girlfriend
was on her way.
Look, Becca threatened to tell on me
if I didn't give her money.
All I had was a 20.
After she left,
I realized she stole my Cerus watch.
Cost me 10 grand.
And you couldn't file a police report
because you would have to
explain what happened
to your girlfriend.
Okay. Sit tight.
Please, I didn't hurt that girl.
You have to believe me.
There was no watch on Becca's body.
Whoever killed her probably took it.
Or maybe she sold it.
Tamara might know where.
Good news.
They got inside Jason's laptop
and found a very intricate
money-laundering operation.
That's great. Who's he working for?
They can't tell yet.
Jason works a pretty
skilled shell game.
But, Financial Crimes
are monitoring the accounts,
and if he tries to move any money,
- they'll track it.
- He won't.
He knows we have his laptop.
He'll assume you're watching.
Well, he'll have to move
the money eventually.
Whoever he's working for
is gonna expect results.
So, what's his next move?
I don't know.
Yet.
Uh-oh.
Looks like your avoidance plan
just hit a speed bump.
Okay, our first official fight.
So, I'll lay out
the way I handle conflict,
which is to go right at it.
I asked you to let me handle
the Curtis situation
by myself, but you...
- you didn't listen.
- I...
Yeah, you were only there
in case something happened.
I get it, sure.
But that's not the point,
I expressed my desire,
and you ignored it,
and that pisses me off.
I mean, if you don't trust me
when I tell you that I
got something handled,
then that's something that
we gotta work out, because,
- if we can't trust each other
- I'm pregnant.
I-I-I can't tell if you're joking.
I'm not.
I just found out.
Harper. Uh, we need to go.
My mom just sent a 911 text,
and she's not answering her phone.
Alright.
What's up?
I'll call you after my shift.
Becca talked about you all the time.
Really?
She was always wondering
what you were up to.
She was so proud.
It was kind of annoying, actually.
I was like, "Damn, why you
so obsessed with Tamara?
Stop."
But for real.
We're all proud.
I should've stayed in better touch.
I-I'm sorry.
- Look out.
- No. It's okay.
They're cool.
Hey.
How are you holding up?
It's just a lot.
Being back here.
- Did you find out anything?
- Yes, uh...
Lopez interviewed all of the men
that Becca was swiping with.
They all have solid alibis.
We did find out that Becca stole a watch
from one of them,
right before she died,
so if we can trace her back there,
we might be able to find out
what happened to her.
Do you have any idea
what Becca would have done
with a stolen watch?
Tamara, hey.
Uh, it's okay.
There's no judgment here.
Um...
there's a pawn shop we used to go to.
Harvey's.
It's just two blocks.
Okay, yeah. We'll check it out.
- Are you okay here?
- Yeah.
Yeah. I'm good.
Okay.
Alright.
Do you still hear the lambs, Clarice?
Oh, Oscar, you're no Hannibal Lecter.
You're more "Ernest Goes to Jail."
Well, you still need my help so, hit me.
Jason was laundering money.
We shut it down.
The arrest warrant's ready to go.
- We just need to find him.
- Well, okay.
Well, let me think about that.
I'm Jason. Right?
My back is against the wall.
The people that I launder money
for are pissed...
Right?
Probably want me dead.
And the police are moving in.
So...
What do I do?
Honestly?
It's really simple.
I just turn myself in.
Flip on my employers
and cut a sweet deal.
John?
Well, you tell Ye that I want in,
so he should call me back.
Hey.
I tried calling you. What's wrong?
Oh, nothing, I...
I just have somebody
I would love for you to meet.
Aaron.
I'm Morris Mackey.
I'm the reality TV producer here.
It's nice to finally meet you.
You are?
Annoyed.
Right.
Uh, I'll make this quick.
I want to change your image.
You've been the villain before,
you've been the victim,
but you've never been the hero.
Let me make you the
hero of your own story.
- That's it.
- Think about it, baby.
So, all parties here are in agreement
on the terms of the deal...
you, Jason Wyler,
admit to residing in an address
not registered
with your parole officer.
You admit to the crime
of laundering money
for the Southern Front
criminal organization.
And you admit to the
crime of planting cocaine
in a vehicle owned by Bailey Nune.
He does.
And, I regret all of it.
Oh, come on.
In exchange for your cooperation
with an investigation
into Southern Front,
we are prepared to offer you
a reduced sentence of 18 months.
18 months?
He nearly ruined my life,
and that's all he gets?
I know. It sucks.
But putting a dent in an organization
as evil as the Southern Front
is just far too...
compelling for the DA's office.
This isn't gonna stop.
The second he gets out,
he'll find me again.
And we'll be ready for him.
I'm gonna be
very clear, Mr. Wyler,
so there's no confusion.
If you try to pull anything
during the operation,
this deal and any sentiment of leniency
we may be feeling toward you
is off the table.
Do you understand?
I understand, sir.
And I promise you, you won't see
any tricks from me.
Nyla's pregnant?
Yeah.
Congratulations.
You guys didn't waste any time.
Oh.
It wasn't planned.
- Not at all.
- Mm.
But. But i-it's great.
Uh-huh.
You don't sound very convincing.
It's just, she told me
in the middle of a fight.
Oh.
Yeah, an argument bomb.
Angela's dropped a few of those on me.
So, how did you respond?
I didn't.
She told you she was pregnant,
and you didn't say anything?
At all?
Okay, so, w-w-what should I do?
It's big gesture time.
You're gonna have to max your
credit card out on this one.
Man.
If you're just joining us...
Oh, hello, Officers.
Shopping around?
Let me guess. A Rams fan, am I right?
Hey, I've got a signed copy
- of Cooper Kupp's...
- We're looking for a stolen
Ceres watch, worth about 10 grand.
So, you come into my shop, accusing me?
Of purchasing stolen
property from homeless teenagers?
We are accusing you of exactly that.
Oh. So I'm the bad guy?
These kids got nobody
looking out for them.
So what if something falls into their
hands
that whoever owned it won't miss?
They're just trying to survive.
I'm a lifeline to these kids.
Were you a lifeline to her?
Oh, man.
- Is she dead?
- Yes.
And the watch could be the reason why.
It was brought in yesterday.
The serial number matches.
Becca was here.
No.
I bought this off Declan.
Isn't that Tamara's friend?
- Are you okay?
- No.
I miss her, too,
and I'm so sorry I haven't been around.
She showed me the watch.
Said that she was gonna
pawn it in the morning
and use the cash to go back to school.
Be like you, she said.
Believe that?
She was gonna leave me, too.
So, she went to sleep, and...
I tried to sneak the watch out, but,
she woke up, and,
she totally freaked on me,
so I-I pushed her and...
And she hit her head,
and there was so much blood.
It-It was an accident.
I swear that I didn't...
- Declan,
show us your hands right now.
Turn around.
Interlace your fingers
behind your head.
7-Adam-100.
Show us Code 4.
Suspect in custody.
- Hey, are you okay?
- No.
So, we have to check
your mic levels.
Can you speak normally for me?
This must be killing you.
Levels are fine.
You talk to Officer Nolan again,
I'll pull your deal. Understood?
Yes, sir.
Now, shall we go over the plan
one last time, Mr. Wyler?
I get them to turn over the money,
confirm turnaround
to the usual accounts,
and you guys swoop in.
In addition to hearing every word,
we've set up a surveillance camera
at the exchange point.
Anything goes wrong, we'll be in there
quick, fast, and in a hurry.
I have no doubt, Sergeant.
Thank you for this.
You know you don't
have to be here for this.
Yes, sir.
Thank you. But I do.
Friendly moving into position.
7-Adam-19, copy.
Okay, you need to get
your head in the game.
Look at me, I just found out
I am pregnant,
and yet, I am focused
and ready to go.
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
You gonna do the show?
I don't know.
I-I just feel like it would cheapen
everything I went through.
Then why are you still struggling?
Because I feel like
I'm letting my mom down.
And?
Because if the show's done right,
then I can
finally control the way people see me.
Hmm.
Not a good time, Oscar.
Oh, well, then I'll be fast.
Two words... You're welcome.
What am I supposed to be
thanking you for?
Well, after doing a little
digging on your boy Jason,
I found out he has a side hustle
working with the Southern Front.
The same group of fine young folks
that want your pal Oscar dead.
Officer Nolan, the target has arrived.
Sir, we may have a problem.
Oscar, cut to the chase.
What did you do?
Oh, fine. Ruin my story.
Okay, upshot is,
I think I found a solution
to both of our problems.
A few minutes ago,
I had a little talk with a
Southern Front contact.
I told them your boy Jason
was working with the cops
to rat them out, and in exchange,
they lifted the hit on me,
put one out on him.
Two birds,
one shiv, huh?
All units, the friendly's been made.
Move in.
How much we looking at?
About two mil.
Same accounts as last time?
What?
Is there a problem?
Yeah. Apparently, it's you.
- Okay.
- Police!
Drop your weapons! Now!
Cover me.
Put it down!
On the ground! Right now!
Get down!
Get down, right now! On the ground!
Down!
Let's go.
You really don't wanna do this.
Screw that.
If I'm going back,
I want to add "kicking your ass"
to the list of charges.
You were saying?
Hey.
- I was hoping I'd catch you.
- You know what?
It's been a really long day,
and I'm not sure
how much more bad
news I can handle right now.
- What if it's good news?
- Is this a joke?
I convinced my boss
to a cut good deal for Tyler.
Really?
He won't be charged as an adult.
He'll serve six months in juvie,
then probation till he turns 18.
That's a good deal.
I know you think I'm a rookie,
who doesn't
have the experience to do the job,
but you should maybe give me a break.
I actually think we're working
toward the same goal.
Just coming at it
from different angles.
Well, um, I appreciate
you making this happen.
I appreciate you convincing me.
Good night.
So, I've been, uh...
I've been thinking about your offer
to do the show with me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Look, if you can promise me
that I'll have full control
over the pieces of my
life that we expose, then...
Yeah. I'll do it.
Cut.
- What's the problem?
- It sounds fake.
- What does?
- You.
Listen, if you want people
to watch this show,
you gotta sound real.
- You gotta be real.
- Yeah, listen to her, Aaron.
Your mama's the queen of "real."
Can I get a touch-up?!
Let's get a touch-up.
You sure I can't
make you something?
I'm not really hungry.
- Today sucked.
- Yeah.
Big time.
♪ I'm with you by your side ♪
- ♪ By your side ♪
- Thank you.
- For...?
- Everything.
For all your help.
For this bed.
For getting justice for Becca.
You did that.
And thanks for helping me
leave it all behind,
because if it weren't for you,
I probably would have ended
up like Becca eventually.
Well, you don't have to
worry about that anymore.
You're safe.
Do you wanna talk about
what you went through
when you were living on the street?
Um, not now, if that's okay.
Yeah, we don't have
to talk about it now.
You don't have to
talk about it with me.
You know, but at some point,
you might wanna talk to someone...
Before it sneaks up on you.
I will.
I promise.
Okay.
Good night.
Do you want this open or closed?
Closed, please.
- ♪ I'm with you by your side ♪
- Sweet dreams.
You wanted to talk?
Um, actually,
I-I was hoping for
more of a do-over. Um...
I don't like how I handled it
when you told me you were pregnant.
Yeah, you didn't handle it.
You didn't do anything, you just...
- You just stood there.
- I know.
Um, I can only plead
temporary stupidity
and throw myself at your mercy.
Forgive me.
Get up.
- So, am I forgiven?
- Yes.
Yes, get up.
Look, look, um,
I'm here, okay?
I-I'm ready to listen.
I-I'm ready to talk.
I'm ready to do
whatever it is you need.
I need you to understand something.
I made my peace,
with not being able to
get pregnant again, and so,
I never even allowed
myself to fantasize...
I'm gonna have this baby.
Well, then, um...
you and I are going to
make a kick-ass team
because we're gonna fight every day
to make sure that this baby
gets to live in a much better world
than the one that exists right now.
That's a good answer.
There we go.
The sommelier recommended this red.
Sounds fancy.
Yeah. Full disclosure,
it was the guy at the liquor store.
But he just said
everyone's buying this bottle.
Thanks.
A toast.
To finally being able to exhale.
Mm. Can we?
Yes.
Jason is behind bars for eight years,
you have a divorce hearing
set for next month,
and when your future
ex-husband finally gets out,
- we'll get a restraining order.
- Mm.
I really appreciate you
helping me through this mess.
Anytime.
Though, I confess, I,
do find myself
wondering if there isn't yet,
another crazed lunatic of a husband
from your checkered past
lurking around out there.
There isn't.
What a relief. Evil twin?
Triplets. Is that a problem?
Triplets I can work with.