I hate beach calls.
Getting this close
to the water
without being able to dive in
is torture.
Not for me.
It's no surprise
there.
Hating one of nature's
greatest gifts
is totally on-brand
for you.
I don't hate the beach.
I'm just not a fan of the ocean.
You know,
psychologically speaking,
fear of the water equates
to a fear
of not being in complete control
of your environment.
Again, on-brand.
Uh, you know, also,
good luck
dating a lifeguard.
Hey, Ash.
Hey.
Wow. When I called
for the cops,
I didn't expect them
to send their best.
And hottest.
Uh,
so you called about a...
Yeah.
It's right over here.
Did you hear her say
"the hottest"?
Washed up an hour ago.
A couple kids found it.
That's why I don't swim
in the ocean.
It's a dumping ground
for sewage, narcotics,
and human remains.
Still feel like going in?
♪
You offer French
and Mandarin?
Yes,
and you don't have to choose.
If Jack is admitted
to Franklin Crest,
he could study both.
He'd be three
when he starts here.
This all sounds amazing.
My pre-school was
my aunt's apartment,
where she watched me
and seven of my cousins.
That must've been so much fun.
But study after study has shown
that nurturing children's minds
between the ages
of three and five is crucial
to a successful
academic career.
And where better to
nurture your child than here?
I can see why
they call this place
the Harvard
of pre-schools.
We like to think
of Harvard
as the Franklin Crest
of universities.
And what do you do
to keep the kids from becoming
overprivileged monsters?
What are you doing?
I went to schools
like this most of my life.
Most of the kids were awful,
entitled.
And rich and successful.
Be nice.
I'm sorry. We're having trouble
with the audio on our end.
We were talking
about Harvard.
Right. 80% of our students
attend Ivy League schools.
Oh, and that's
a selling point?
The Ivy League is
a breeding ground
for even more entitlement.
I went to Harvard.
Well...
What was --
Sorry --
Frozen --
You know -- call -- back.
What the hell
are you doing?
Look, I know you are dying
to send Jack here,
but we need to make sure
it's a healthy environment.
I have to get to work.
Call them back and reschedule
the rest of the interview.
Sometimes I just can't believe you.
Hey!
Oh, congratulations!
John Nolan,
Union Delegate.
How do you feel?
I feel amazing.
This is incredible.
Guys, you didn't do this
all yourselves, did you?
Oh, my goodness.
No.
Uh, they were just left
at the front desk.
Oh. "To LAPD's
newest union delegate.
From your friends
at the mayor's office."
Wow.
I am so happy for you.
John, you worked
really, really hard to get this,
and I think you are gonna do
just an amazing job.
Thank you. That --
That actually means a lot to me.
- Are you okay?
- Uh, yeah.
Uh, it's -- it's, uh,
the pregnancy hormones.
They -- They make me,
uh, pathologically cheerful.
Oh.
So, um...
Seriously,
it's the worst thing.
Um, I am gonna go
set up the shop,
and I will let you all
deal with this long line.
What long line?
Oh, yes.
So, in honor of your first day
as union delegate,
half the cops
in the station want to, um --
well, they --
they want to talk to you.
That's what I'm gonna talk
to him about.
They haven't restocked
the vending machine
with cheese puffs
in six months.
I need my puffs.
A citizen just filed
a complaint.
I need you
to represent me.
So, what was
the complaint?
I was taking a statement
from a homeowner,
and, well, I needed to use
her bathroom,
and now she's claiming
that I destroyed her toilet.
I want to use a .44 Magnum
as my duty weapon.
When are we getting
air-conditioned body armor?
I'm just looking to get my
emotional support pig deputized.
Seriously?
You had this job
yesterday.
Already cracking
under the stress, Nolan?
No. I'm just wondering
what you were doing
for the last 12 years
as union rep.
It seems like none of these
people's needs were being met.
Yeah, cops always find something
to whine about.
Plus,
I told everybody
how eager you are
to hear their problems.
No matter how small.
You're welcome.
Already hard at work,
I see.
Yes, sir.
Lieutenant Landon Briggs.
I'm the Union --President.
Yes, I know.
Great to finally meet you.
Consider this
a welcome present.
But my small gift
is only the beginning.
You're about to be
wined and dined
across this great city.
I've already received
a-a few gifts,
but I'm just excited
to get started.
I-I'm glad you
stopped by.
What's a good e-mail
for you
so I can send you a list
of my proposals?
- I'm sorry -- proposals?
- Yeah.
I, um, campaigned
on the promise of change.
At the top of the list
is a mental health initiative
that dispatches counselors
on all calls
involving mental illness.
Oh, slow down there, son.
Our fight right now isn't about
the people out there.
It's about making sure
our brothers in blue
get everything they deserve --
uh, paid overtime, benefits.
Eh...
there'll be time
for your list later.
The most important thing now
is to relax.
Enjoy your victory.
Hey. Heard about that hand
that washed up yesterday.
God, I know.
It's super gross, right?
You got any theories?
A couple. I...
At first, I was thinking
maybe human trafficking,
maybe the boat capsized,
took someone's hand off,
but then I realized that
the way the hand was severed
- spoke more
to some type of torture.
- Ah.
Sorry, I
watch a lot of true crime.
Oh, me, too.
I'm actually thinking
it's a "Gone Girl" gone wrong
scenario.
Ooh, I like that.
Yeah, maybe she was, uh,
trying to fake a drowning,
but then got caught
in her boat propeller.
Exactly, yeah.
Nice.
- I'll see you around.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey.
Hi.
What's that look?
N-Nothing.
What?
You wanted to strangle that guy
last week.
Now you're all sweet on him?
"Sweet on him"?
What? Did -- Did we suddenly
just get dropped in the 1950s?
What?
All done.
Who knew a dead hand
would require so much paperwork?
Oh, hey,
do you have plans tonight?
No. Why?
My friend Olive won
four raffle tickets
to this fancy dinner thing,
and she just invited us.
What's a "fancy dinner thing"?
It's called Osia.
It's an exclusive pop-up
on the beach in Malibu --
one night only,
12 fusion courses,
wine pairings
included.
"An experiment
in molecular gastronomy."
I'll have to
think about it.
What's there
to think about?
Uh, the control freak
in him
doesn't like to try
new things, so...
I'm not
a control freak.
I would be happy
to go to your dinner thing.
Sergeant Grey?
Lieutenant...
Caba-relli?
It's Cabarelli.
Ah.
But call me Romeo.
Uh, thank you.
Wade.
- And how was your flight?
- Eh, good, I suppose.
A little tight perhaps.
The Carabinieri does not pay
for business class.
- You're talking to a large man.
Trust me, I understand.
- Yeah.
So, you're hunting a fugitive.
Tell me about him.
Kai Zullo.
Murdered a woman
in a home invasion in Rome.
Made off with 100,000 Euros
worth of diamonds.
Landed in Los Angeles
three days ago.
Does he have any family
or friends here?
No. We believe he wants to hide
in a large city
until he can escape
to South America.
He's fluent
in many languages.
Well, he came
to the right place.
You can hide another city
in this city.
But the LAPD's pretty good
at finding people.
Listen, I don't want to be
a burden.
I'm sure
you're stretched thin.
I simply need an
escorting officer with a pulse.
Not to sing my own praises,
but I'm an expert lawman.
Look, I have no doubt,
and I am stretched very thin,
but it would be my honor
to work this case with you.
I can't possibly ask you
to do that.
I insist.
I'm always looking for a way
to stretch my legs.
Yeah, I do the same.
So here's
your carry permit.
And, you know,
I have a C.I. we can go see.
And you can tell me more
about our suspect on the way.
And when did the break-in
take place, Mr. Swaine?
Around 2:00 a.m.
Okay,
what was taken?
I can't say.
I'm -- I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
Well, if I told you,
I'd be revealing ManMade Labs'
trade secrets.
My company works
at the forefront
of biotechnological
advancement.
You're asking me to reveal
highly confidential information.
Okay. Can you at least tell me
who was working at that time?
I'll have to check with
the lawyers on that one.
How about showing me
where the burglary happened?
That way, we can have TID
dust for prints.
I'm afraid
that's not possible.
We have several
government clients.
You don't have clearance
to go farther than the lobby.
We can't do our job
without access.
Oh, was I --
was I not clear?
I don't expect you to.
I-I just need a case number
for insurance purposes.
Sorry I'm late.
I had to yell at my husband.
Detective Angela Lopez.
Devon Swaine, CEO.
I apologize you had to come
all the way down here.
As I was telling
this officer,
this matter's
extremely sensitive.
We'll be handling it
in-house.
You can send over
that case number
whenever you get
the chance.
Thanks.
How do you want to
handle this?
If they don't want our help,
there's not much we can do.
Just write it up
and send it over.
We heard
you got a body.
Yeah. He'd already lost
a lot of blood
when he got here.
We did everything we could,
but he bled out.
Stabbing?
No.
Someone cut off
his hand.
♪
How clandestine.
I could be in "Dirty Harry."
American police work.
Is it really how
the movies make it look?
Oh, "Dirty Harry" is
pretty outdated.
But, uh...
Alright, here's my guy now.
♪ Perpetrate, strictly real,
never fake♪
♪ Innovate, innovate♪
Flex.
♪ All I do is innovate♪
Who's he?
Romeo is an officer of
the Italian Car-a-binieri.
Carabinieri.
- The what?
- He's a cop.
Just do
what he tells you.
We're looking for a man
named Kai Zullo.
White, six-foot, Italian --
like me.
He's in possession of stolen
jewels from my country --
diamond rings, necklaces,
brooches.
He's an international fugitive
wanted on a murder charge.
Finding him is a big deal.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
No guarantees.
♪ Beg ya pardon like Dolly ♪
Informants.
They're the same
everywhere.
Even the shifty eyes.
So, what now?
Let me guess.
We'll "hit the streets
and see who else is talking."
Not exactly.
How about
"Reach for the sky"?
Do you still say that?
Have you seen
any cop movie
that was made
in the past 40 years?
Why are you wasting
my client's time, Detective?
He is a busy CEO.
I just have
a few questions.
Which he already told you
he can't answer.
Well, your client
might want to reconsider
now that one of his employees
turned up dead.
- Who?
- Mark Kilkea.
Someone cut off his hand to get
past the palm scanners
throughout your offices.
They left him for dead,
but he somehow managed
to get himself up
and stumbled into a hospital
almost 24 hours later.
That's horrible, but my client
has nothing to do with that.
Maybe not,
but given the company's
high-tech
security protocols,
there's no way
your client wasn't aware
that Kilkea palmed his way
into the office
right before
the robbery.
But you didn't share that,
did you?
In fact, according to
Mr. Kilkea's neighbors,
two security officers
from your company
showed up at our victim's door
right after the robbery.
As you are well aware,
my client's business
is highly proprietary.
Yep.
I looked into that.
According to your website,
the company you founded
is "a pioneering force in
biotechnological engineering,
making it possible
for humans to live better lives
in our modern world."
What are you guys making
over there?
Widgets.
Either you answer
my question,
or we will freeze
and hold your company
until we can obtain
a search warrant,
and you won't sell any widgets
until I say so.
Yeah, I'm not gonna
let you do that.
It's a crime scene.
It's my discretion
on how to process it.
Let me help you out.
You created the fastest,
smallest microchip in the world,
and it's about to
go to market.
Does that sound
about right?
Where did you get that
information?
Well, they just don't give
these out to anyone.
What are the chips
used for?
To bridge the gap between
technology and biology,
and that's all
I'm going to say.
And can you think of anyone
who would cut off a guy's hand
to steal this tech?
Chester Frey.
I fired him
about six months ago
for performing experiments
off-site,
doing research
my company never approved.
He called me last week,
insisting he was close
to a breakthrough,
begged me to let him access
our lab again.
I told him
to lose my number.
And how dangerous would you say
Chester Frey is?
He's the worst kind of crazy,
Detective.
He's a zealot.
So, what's next?
Morning sickness,
food cravings?
All of it.
If it is a pregnancy
side effect, I will get it.
But it's just all such
a blessing. Yeah.
Oh.
- John Nolan.
Officer Nolan.
Elena Gutierrez,
district councilwoman.
I wanted to convey
my personal congratulations
on your victory.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
We're a big fan
of the LAPD over here,
so if you ever want to chat,
I'm around.
Well,
are you free tonight?
I do have a couple of ideas
I've been kicking around.
Actually, I have a meeting
down the street from
your station this evening.
I can swing by after,
around 7:30?
That is perfect.
Thank you very much.
I am looking forward.
Me, too.
Wow. Okay.
See, this is why I ran.
A chance to talk
about real issues.
7-Adam-15, this is Lopez.
I have an ID on our hand-thief
murder suspect.
Chester Frey.
His house is five blocks
from your location.
Sending the address
to your box
and additional units
to back you up.
Copy that.
We are on our way.
And thank you so much
for calling.
I know. It's --
It's freaking me out, too.
Police!
God,
it's like a freezer in here.
♪
Chester?
Come on up now.
Show me your hands.
♪
Clear upstairs.
Clear.
This place...
Do you hear that?
Police!
Um, Nolan...
♪
And here we have
a severed arm,
moving all on its own.
Uh...
I can't stop staring.
I think it's amazing.
I mean, the human body --
this truly is a miracle.
Is she okay?
Pregnancy hormones.
Cool. Any sign
of our Dr. Frankenstein?
No. He left plenty
of evidence behind --
notebooks, computers.
Hopefully, we can learn
what scientific breakthrough
he thinks
he's so close to.
Yeah, and where
to look for him next.
- Be right back.
- Yeah.
Any sign of Chester?
No.
So, Chester cut off
Mark Kilkea's hand,
and now there's a severed arm
in his house.
- That's two victims.
- Afraid there's more.
Harper and Nolan found a freezer
with eight more arms inside.
So, is that four more victims,
or eight?
Six, I think.
Four right, two left.
On the initial exam,
the ME thinks
they were removed
post-mortem.
Two of them had clear signs
of decomposition.
So what?
He's a grave robber?
We don't know yet.
Well, tell TID
to get a rush on the prints.
If we can get hits
on his victims,
it might tell us
where he got the limbs from
- and who he targets.
- On it.
Detective Lopez.
What do you want,
Mr. Karga?
Access to
Chester Frey's house.
He stole proprietary property
from my client,
- and I need to retrieve it.
- That would be a no.
This is
an active crime scene --
I don't think
you understand.
If my client's technology
is leaked,
it will destroy
a billion dollars' worth of R&D.
And the LAPD isn't exactly known
for its discretion,
which is why we prefer
to handle everything in-house.
Look, I get it.
But I can't help you.
We're seizing everything
inside this house, Mr. Karga,
and if you even attempt to step
foot inside this perimeter,
you'll spend tonight
inside a jail cell.
Wouldn't want to dirty
that nice suit, would you?
And I would love to get
a look at Chester's computer
after TID is done
processing it --
you know, try to get
into his head.
You think Lopez
would let me?
Doesn't hurt to ask.
It's Ash.
Hey, Ash.
Hey.
Olive just pulled out
of the dinner thing,
so now I have
all four tickets.
I was thinking of asking Byron
and his girlfriend...
Yeah, uh, no.
Y-You know what?
Lucy's been pining after
that place all day.
Maybe we ask her.
Osia? Yes. Oh, my gosh.
Yes, please.
Cool. Does she have
a date to bring?
- Hey, Sanford.
- What?
You got plans tonight?
What are you doing?
Lucy needs a date
to a fancy dinner.
Uh...
It'll be fun.
Okay. Yeah.
I'm in.
Uh, text me the address.
She's good.
Okay.
♪
What?
Don't be
such a control freak.
Hey, we gave it
our best shot.
- Tomorrow's another day.
- It always is.
You know, the architecture
in this city is ghastly.
Do not bad-mouth
my city, Romeo.
Oooh. So sensitive.
- But I will prove it
to you.
- Uh...
Come to Rome.
You walk down the streets,
you'll see thousands of years
of history.
That's what a real city
should look like.
I'm serious.
Bring that wife of yours.
Luna has been on me
about traveling more.
Then it's decided.
You will be my guest.
I will open
my doors for you.
That's very generous.
Thank you.
You know, you remind me
of someone I used to know.
A lieutenant.
His name was Santo.
I was only his cadet
when I joined the Carabinieri,
but he took me
under his wings.
He showed me
my city through new eyes.
Like you are now.
"Used to know."
What happened?
My second year,
he, uh --
he was shot.
I was there.
He died in my arms.
Every day, in here...
I see it.
Yeah, I know a little something
about that.
This is a miserable job
sometimes.
That it is.
And sometimes,
the best.
That is true.
What's this?
Ah.
Flex just got word.
Kai's meeting the diamond broker
tonight --
Gardner and Beverly.
That is wonderful.
But I don't want to keep you
from the end of your shift.
Why don't you drop me off?
I'll go stake it out.
If he's there,
I'll call for backup.
See, I can't
let you do that.
Besides, I already told
the station
that I'm extending my shift
tonight, so...
You've already put in so much
time on my case.
Go home to your wife.
You know... Luna has
book club tonight.
I'm all yours.
I told a foodie friend I was
coming here, and they flipped.
And they said it sold out in,
like, 30 seconds.
How the hell
did you get tickets?
My friend won them
in a raffle.
I'm sorry, but who puts
a restaurant on the beach?
I mean, you're just asking for
sand in your food.
I don't get it.
For your first course,
we have Chef Celine Barris' take
on blinis and caviar --
a savory enoki pancake
with fruit of the forest roe,
and smoked Himalayan salt
espuma.
Enjoy.
- Was any of that English?
- Let me translate.
All you need to know
is that that pancake
is made of mushroom,
which I know is not
your favorite, so I'm just --
Ooh, no, take it.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I didn't know
you don't like mushrooms.
Oh, it's okay.
I'm not the most adventurous
eater, either.
But once on vacation in Jamaica,
I did have curry goat.
Ooh.
Was his name Gerald?
God, shut up.
Don't.
It's nothing.
No, it's something.
Okay, we had
a 2-11 at a petting zoo.
All of the animals
got loose.
So, we --
we nab our suspect,
we him back to the shop,
and that's where we find --
Gerald the goat.
He is so cute.
And he's sitting
in Lucy's seat.
Well, because I forgot
that I had rolled down
the -- the window.
You know,
who knew goats could jump?
Look, she tries to talk
him out of the shop,
but it's a goat, right?
So, she spends five minutes
making goat noises
at this thing.
Yes, he called me
"goat whisperer" for
all of last February.
- It was great.
- The darn thing never moved.
Oh, you know, we finally had
to call animal control.
It's funny.
Thank you so much
for coming, Councilwoman.
Of course.
It is my pleasure.
You know, every time
that I've reached out
to one of my district's
union delegates,
they always brush aside
my invitations to talk.
So imagine my surprise
when you actually seemed excited
to talk to me.
Oh, I am.
No, I-I campaigned
on the promise of change,
and I meant it.
Some of the best people
you could ever meet
are in the LAPD.
I would like the institution
to reflect that.
How can I help?
I'll be honest,
Councilwoman --
- Elena.
Math was never
my strong suit.
My brain bleeds
just looking at my taxes.
But I was going over
our departmental budget,
and even I can see
we're putting a lot of money
in the wrong places.
You won't get an argument
from me.
Now, at least 20%
of our service calls
are for mental health
or substance-use issues.
Now, these people
don't need to be policed.
They need
crisis intervention
and a counselor
dispatched to the scene.
I've been thinking about
a pilot program.
If you could help me get
an audience with the mayor --
I'm so sorry.
This is -- It's my first day.
I'm already overstepping.
No.
Do not apologize.
Your empathy is --
it's genuine. I can tell.
Tell me more
about this program, please.
Alright.
Well, people don't like
the idea of experimenting
on the dead
for emotional reasons,
but it's an important tool
in the medical field.
Yeah,
I'm not arguing that.
All I'm saying is that
turning people into cyborgs
is how the world
is going to end.
So, then, I guess you
haven't volunteered
to be an organ donor
when you die?
Tim? No.
He wants to be cremated
and spread over Dodger Field.
I was joking
when I said that.
My ashes would screw up
the pH level of the grass.
I can't believe you actually
called and asked.
I like the Dodgers.
Yeah.
And for dessert,
we have a spherical
coconut-mango emulsion
with a dusting
of jalapeño essence.
Enjoy.
This is a joke, right?
I mean, people don't actually
enjoy eating this food, do they?
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't mean to --
Excuse me.
I need to use the restroom.
Whoa.
Wade, please.
I feel bad,
making you waste your night
for what's likely
a goose chase.
This is my case.
I'll take the burden
for the both of us.
I'm starting to feel like you're
trying to get rid of me.
No.
I'm loving our time together.
It's just that...it's not good
to work all the time.
You need to
enjoy life more.
That's one thing I've learned
after Santo died.
- There he is.
- I'll call for backup.
Hey!
♪
Preso, bastardo!
7-Adam-100, shots fired.
Officer needs help.
Suspect is white male,
black jacket, black pants.
Hey.
What the hell was that?
He had a gun.
You did not see?
No, I didn't see.
Well, he did.
He's a very dangerous man.
If I'd hesitated,
he would have killed me.
Yeah.
Good morning.
Franklin Crest e-mailed.
Their enrollment is suddenly
full for two years from now.
Okay, I'm sorry,
but if they are that sensitive
to questions about
their students,
then maybe we shouldn't
send Jack there.
We should send him
to public school.
Says the rich boy
who's never been to one.
Well, you went to
public school.
You turned out great.
You're doing it again.
Wait, doing what?
Shoving your privilege
into your back pocket
when you can actually use it
for something good,
like the education
of our child.
- That's not fair.
- But it's accurate.
Look, public school
can be wonderful.
- Then what's the problem?
- You took away our options.
Even if Jack got into
Franklin Crest,
we might not have enrolled him,
but you sabotaged it
and essentially made
a decision without me.
And why did you do it?
Because you have
private school baggage.
Okay. Fine.
Maybe I do have
some...baggage.
Maybe I'm afraid that
our son will become
the same poster boy
for entitlement that I was,
until I realized
I didn't like myself,
and I set out to become
the man that you love.
Mostly.
I'm just disappointed
that you didn't have more faith
in us as parents.
They will record
my name in history.
They will parade me through --
Hey.
You're here early.
Yeah.
I couldn't sleep.
All I could think of
was this disembodied hand
climbing into my bed,
so I've been here,
scrubbing through
Chester's video journals.
You come
to any conclusions?
I try not to use the word
"crazy"...
He cut off a guy's hand and
reanimated a woman's dead arm.
He's crazy.
Yeah.
Okay, so,
he shot this next video
the day before he cut off
Mark Kilkea's hand
and used it
to break into ManMade Labs.
I am here,
trying to officiate a marriage
between science and humanity,
and nothing's working.
I know what I have to do.
I've never wanted
to resort to violence,
but this is not the time
to be faint of heart.
I am so close.
I am so close!
I will show them my miracles,
then my sins will be forgiven
forever.
Okay, so, this next one
is his last video entry,
and it was shot yesterday.
It worked.
Hear that? Hear it?
Hear it?
The wrist is contracting.
The -- The --
The hand is knocking,
pounding on the doors
of immortality!
This changes everything.
Who needs a prosthetic limb
when you can be made whole
with a reanimated one?
I'm creating life.
I am a god.
Whoo--
Anything in these videos
that can lead us
- to where he's hiding?
- Not that I've seen.
Well,
let's keep looking.
- What do you need?
- Close the door.
Come here.
I heard you were involved
in a shooting. You alright?
That was
my Italian counterpart.
He and I tracked down
his fugitive -- Kai Zullo.
But the second
Romeo saw the guy,
he opened fire,
claimed he saw a gun.
- But you didn't.
- Correct.
Did you check
your body cam?
Of course,
but there wasn't a good look.
I phoned Italy
last night.
Spoke to one of
their inspectors.
She told me that Romeo is
currently under investigation
for misconduct.
- So he's a dirty cop?
- Seemingly.
I think it's prudent that
we find Kai before Romeo does.
Okay, so what do we know
about Kai so far?
He's in
a foreign country.
He appears not to have friends
or family here.
He has to stay under
the radar,
so he can't use a credit card
or his ID.
Right, but he is gonna need
a place to stay.
A no-tell motel
that accepts cash.
We will
start canvassing.
Thanks. I'll keep Romeo busy
while you look.
Hey. Implant the size of --
We got hits on prints
on three of the arms
found in Chester's place.
All three were from unclaimed
or indigent people
whose bodies had been in storage
in the County Morgue.
That's a great way to grab
bodies no one would ever miss.
The County holds onto the
remains of unclaimed individuals
for up to three years,
then they're buried
in a pauper's grave.
That's sad.
D-Does Chester have a connection
to the morgue?
Not that we know of,
but it's possible
that he found an
employee who was willing
to sell him body parts.
- We'll check it out.
- Yeah.
Police.
Anyone here?
♪
He's here.
- It's still wet.
- Control, 7-Adam-100.
Can I get backup
for a 415?
Male, unknown weapon.
Standby for further.
♪
He's dead.
7-Adam-100, I have a 187
at the County Morgue.
Suspect is Chester Frey.
Still outstanding
in the building.
Have an RA stand by
until scene is secure.
♪
Everyone, up against the wall.
Go.
Now! Faster!
- You -- Shut up.
No.
Shut up!
Help me!
Stop crying!
Who's the guy in charge?
Raise your hand.
Now!
Okay, no one wants to raise
their hand?
Should I start shooting?
Good.
You, come here.
I need his arm.
That guy there,
on the table.
Stop acting dumb.
You're in charge.
You know how to use
these instruments.
So go ahead.
Pick it up. Start cutting.
Why are you waiting?!
It's either this arm
or your arm!
So pick one!
Anyone moves, I'll blow
their head off. Do you hear me?
It's him.
He's got hostages.
Faster.
- What are our options?
- Faster!
We could wait until
he gets what he wants
and then flank him
on his way out,
but he might kill the hostages
before he leaves.
Which rules that out
as an option.
We could make contact,
bring in a hostage negotiator,
and try to talk him out.
Given the video logs, do you
really think that's an option?
No. Clearly, he thinks
he's on a divine mission.
He'll probably shoot his way out
before he surrenders.
So, what's our game plan?
Now the other one.
♪
7-Adam-100,
show a Code 4.
Suspect in custody.
♪
Okay, I put feelers out
through the union chat group --
a great way to talk to every cop
in L.A., by the way --
and between them all,
they have informants
at 64 of the 71
no-tell motels
in the greater
Los Angeles area.
Of those, one of them has
a possible Kai Zullo sighting.
I say we go get into our civvies
and we stake it out.
God,
I just love this job so much.
- Maybe I should drive.
- Yeah. Okay.
So you mentioned yesterday
that you had
a bit of a history with Kai.
Si, si.
I arrested him
when I first started
with the Polizia Municipale
di Roma,
and many times since.
He's a  --
a repeat offender.
Unh-unh. There's something
about this case
you're not telling me.
I don't know, just...
seems personal.
All my cases are personal.
Are yours not?
Hmm.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
It's Nolan.
We got eyes on Kai.
You want us to move in,
make the arrest?
No, I have a better idea.
He's in room 13.
Harper's in
the manager's office,
having the clerk call
all the rooms around,
making sure
no one comes out.
You wanna wait for SWAT?
Yeah.
Like scared little children?
No. Surely, we're men enough
to go arrest him.
It's not about being "men,"
Romeo.
It's about officer safety.
But I do think
we can handle one armed felon.
Somebody's gonna have to post up
in the alley, though,
make sure
he doesn't rabbit.
Allow me.
Okay.
Get in position.
We'll move in when you call.
♪
♪ La giubba
e la faccia infarina♪
♪ La gente paga♪
♪ E rider♪
♪ Vuole qua♪
♪ E se Arlecchin♪
Drop the gun, Romeo!
♪
Harper and Nolan
arrested Kai 20 minutes ago.
He confessed to working with you
back in Italy,
but then he killed a homeowner
and fled to America.
And you worried he would
flip on you if he got caught,
so you came to kill him.
But what you didn't foresee
is that you would get paired
with the best cop in the city.
A man who believed in me
when I didn't even
believe in myself.
Seriously, how much longer you
gonna be like this?
Let's go.
Romeo on his way to
the Towers?
Yeah, and, um,
Kai is on his way back to Italy
with two U.S. Marshals.
Thanks for everything
you did today.
Of course. You okay?
Yeah. It's just...
I liked the guy.
You liked
who he was pretending to be.
Yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Can't wait.
Hey. Uh,
I wanted to talk to you.
Have to be honest -- I-I wasn't
really feeling last night,
hanging with
Ashley and Tim.
I am so sorry.
Tim and I spend so much time
together on the jobs,
we --
we have a shorthand.
No, no, it's fine.
I just don't think
our first date
should've been
a double date.
So, how about a do-over?
♪ There's never been a war
caused by kindness ♪
I was hoping you'd say that.
Yeah?
Um, but look,
me and my wallet
might not be able to
outdo Osia.
Oh, my gosh.
I don't even care about that.
Uh, what's your favorite
restaurant?
Oh. Pink's Hot Dogs.
I know,
not the most romantic --
No, no, no, no.
I love Pink's.
-  Yeah?
- Yes.
Well, are you --
you hungry now?
Yes. Yes.
Let's go.
♪ Oh, yeah
♪
Hey.
♪ Now we around the world
So, I called Franklin Crest
today
and apologized
to the Dean.
Jack's in.
- For real?
- Yep.
In two years' time,
our child will officially
be enrolled in the Harvard
of pre-schools.
Unless we send him
to the new charter school
that just opened up.
What?
Don't look at me
like that.
I just want every option
available for him
when it comes time
for us to decide.
And just so we can avoid
these sorts of arguments
in the future,
I made up a parenting chart
for us to fill out.
♪ No, we can't conceive
to living ♪
♪ Like the one who calls...
I broke everything down
into categories.
First, let's start
with...discipline.
Do you believe
in grounding?
I'm sorry.
Are you really murder-boarding
our child's future?
♪ You gonna wait for them
to change the tide ♪
I'm -- I'm sorry.
For what?
For last night.
My whole attitude about trying
something new with you.
Look, I'm flexible.
I get every relationship
is a compromise.
But you acted like
you were doing me a favor,
and then you spent
the whole night talking to Lucy.
It didn't feel good.
I know. You're right.
Look, it's just that
the thing is,
every job I've had has been
wall-to-wall unpredictability.
You know, being ready
for anything,
no matter how crazy
or dangerous.
So, when I'm
off the clock --
You like
your creature comforts.
But life can't just be about
watching Rams games on the couch
and talking about the job
with your partner.
She is not my partner, okay?
I'm her sergeant.
And...that is
not the point.
The point is,
you deserve someone who tries,
and I want to be that
for you.
♪ Push us through the night
♪ I just want to live
I want that, too.
Okay.
So, here's what
I'm thinking.
We get on the freeway,
and we go anywhere,
and you take me to do
anything you want, okay?
I'll even call in sick tomorrow
if you want me to.
- Really?
- Yeah.
♪ Oh, yeah
Uh...and we can do
anything?
Hey.
Nolan.
Lieutenant Briggs.
What did I tell you about not
getting ahead of yourself?
I'm sorry. I don't know
what we're talking about.
I am president
of the police union.
I had no idea
about this.
Do you know how foolish
that makes me look?
I-I swear to you, sir,
that's going to be as good
for us as it is
for the public.
The public? That's not
your job to worry about.
You put your brothers
and sisters first.
That's your job!
Um, respectfully, sir,
I disagree.
You know what the best part
about being union president is?
Power.
The power to help the people
I like
and hurt the people
I don't.
So enjoy your free martinis
and dinners, Officer Nolan.
I've got a feeling you're not
gonna be a delegate for long.
Because I did something
to help the city
a-and cops
sent out on calls
they haven't been properly
trained for?
Come on, sir.
You can't honestly be saying
you'd try to push me
out of office for that?
Watch me.
Yikes.
Really? When I need
Detective Happy Pants the most,
I get "yikes"?
Oh, you don't
need me for that.
You are the most positive person
I have ever met.
You certainly are not gonna let
a guy like Briggs
get in your way.
- You know, you're right.
- Mm-hmm.
No matter
what happens next,
I said I was gonna bring change
to the Department,
and I'm doing that.
♪