Previously on "The Rookie"...
Silas is the eyes and the ears
of the neighborhood.
I'm Larry Macer. Everybody
calls me "The Badger" --
Washing out at roll call
on your first day?
That has gotta be
a record.
Being a sergeant's aide
would make me stand out
come promotion time.
What the hell.
Let's do it.
I'm pregnant.
Hey.
You're up early.
Yeah, since 3:00.
Leg cramps, but it gave me
a chance to think,
and I have
made a decision.
We should get married.
Huh?
Yeah,
tomorrow works for me
because I'll be at
the court already.
Wow, um...efficient.
Uh, what
brought this on?
Brett.
At the community center?
What -- What does Brett
have to do with this?
He called me
your baby mama.
Ah, hmm.
I'll talk to him.
No, 'cause he won't
be the only one.
We should just get married.
Problem solved.
What do you think?
I'm in.
Yeah?
Um, let's get married.
Let's get married!
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Okay.
Oh, here we go.
And where are
my keys?
In the key bowl.
I don't have a key bowl.
Oh, you bought me
a key bowl!
So, when do you think
you'll be back tonight?
Uh, I would guess,
but I'd hate to jinx it.
But definitely
in time for dinner?
It's the first time in two weeks
our schedules have aligned.
Yes, if I have to
fake my own death,
I'll be home
in time for dinner.
Mm.
Good, because
I bought a new dress
and new lacy things that
go under the dress,
and I can't wait
to show you.
You can show me now.
Really?
Oh, I gotta go.
Um, you said my keys
were in the key bowl?
Yeah, but now
they're in your hands.
Clearly distracted by
the lacy undergarment talk.
Good.
Well, not good when you're
on the street with a gun,
so think about it
until you get in the truck.
Right. Deal.
See you tonight.
Bye.
Grey wants Thorsen
to ride with me today.
You're with Nolan.
Well, try not to
miss me too much.
Bradford, nice work on
the Stewart case.
I appreciate that, Webb.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Uh, wait,
the Scott Stewart case?
The one where I connected
the Valley Glenn job to him
and that's what helped us
put all the pieces together?
The Scott Stewart
that I put into custody
after he punched me
in the face?
You're jealous.
Is that really
why you do this job,
is for high fives
from Webb?
Okay.
It would be nice to
have some recognition.
Hey, Webb.
Yeah?
I couldn't have closed
the Stewart case without Chen.
You're a legend, Sarge.
A leader who gives credit
to the troops.
Feel better?
No. Now they just think that
you're being selfless.
Sergeant Bradford?
Uh...sir,
I can't tell you how excited
I am to ride with you today.
I'm really looking forward to
soaking up whatever tips and --
Does Harper like
that ass-kissing?
No, sir.
Why do you
think I would?
Set up the shop.
That's not
a good start.
Any advice on riding
with Sergeant Bradford?
Uh, yeah, don't let him take all
the credit for your hard work.
Yeah, well, being a rookie,
I'm not sure
if that really applies to me,
but, uh, thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that's good.
Caradine's thrilled
you're helping him out.
See, between the flu
and hockey injuries,
he's down to
four detectives.
Anything to get out of
that duty belt.
I can only imagine.
Everything okay
with your pregnancy?
Mm-hmm.
I don't want you pushing
yourself too hard.
Don't be afraid
to ask for help.
Please, I have
nothing to prove.
Alright, if you need anything,
let me know.
Alright.
I'm so glad
you're here.
I have a crazy backlog
of cases.
I'm engaged.
What?
Mm-hmm.
Really?!
Yes.
When did he propose?
Tell me everything!
When's the wedding?
You know what?
The backlog can wait.
I say we go
dress shopping.
Wait,
where's the ring?
Uh, we're doing things
a little out of order.
I proposed to him,
and it's, you know,
not really
that kind of wedding.
We're just doing it
at the courthouse.
And James is
cool with that?
Yeah.
Okay.
What if I threw you
the smallest reception?
Tiny. Miniscule.
It's not even about
the recognition, you know?
Every single case file
has Tim's name on the front,
and I'm the one filing
the supplemental reports,
but how am I supposed to take on
more responsibility
if nobody knows
what I'm capable of?
Okay, you make a lot
of good points,
and not to get all factual
and everything,
but wasn't, uh,
riding with Tim your idea?
Yeah, as Sergeant Tim takes on
all the high-profile cases,
which is not nothing.
But now you're
seeing a downside.
Exactly.
Well, then just ask Tim
to reassign you.
I'm sure
he'll understand.
Nolan, this is not
one of those
"help me solve my problem"
situations.
This is one of those
"let's talk about
how Tim is the absolute worst"
situations.
Right. You want to know
who the worst is?
It's Tim.
Sir, I just want to let you know
that I have been
spending my days off
driving the city,
learning every street name,
alleyway,
and cul-de-sac
in our jurisdiction.
Whatever Tim Test
you have for me, I'm ready.
And that's why I won't
be giving you one.
Harper's
a good T.O.,
and you've been on the job
long enough to know
where the nearest
safe bathroom is.
Yeah, Barry's Juice Bar.
It's two blocks east --
So today won't be about
assessing whether or not
you'll pass
the FTO program.
It'll be about
determining
what sort of officer
you'll be once you do.
Okay, and how do
we do that?
By figuring out
your superpower.
Every cop has one.
You know, Harper's a chameleon,
nerves of steel.
Chen's empathy allows her to
adapt to any situation.
And Nolan...
Uh, he talks a lot.
Yeah.
Okay, so what if a cop doesn't
have a superpower?
They grow up
to be Smitty.
Still kind of
feels like a test.
Congratulations.
I knew you guys would
eventually get married.
Yeah,
I-I couldn't be happier.
Why are you lying?
Sorry, that was
inappropriate.
No, no, you know what?
You're right.
Uh
it's just,
I-I panicked when she said
we should get married.
'Cause you didn't
say anything
when she told you
she was pregnant.
Exactly, and I didn't want
to freeze again,
so I just said yes.
And now
you're rethinking it?
I mean, I'm totally
in love with her.
I just don't know if avoiding
being called "baby mama"
is reason enough
to get married.
On top of the fact,
she stole my thunder.
So you want to
marry her?
100%.
It's just, I think we should get
married for the right reasons,
and...I wanted to be the one
to propose.
But enough about my drama.
What's -- What's -- What's next
on the list?
Mrs. Parker,
down the street.
Her court date
moved to next Tuesday.
And what's the case
against her?
She got pulled over last month
for a broken taillight.
Somehow ended up in custody for
obstructing an officer's duty,
so we're helping walk her
through the system,
if you can take her.
Yeah, absolutely.
Cops get
car stop training.
The public's just expected
to figure it out.
Yeah, and with Black drivers,
it's like a minefield
where the wrong move
leads to police escalation.
Hmm.
I can donate some time.
We can hold some classes.
That's a bad idea.
Well, I don't
know about bad.
Well, who's gonna
have time for that?
You want to get the message out,
you got to take it to them.
Make a video.
Then they could watch
whenever they want.
I'm president of
my school's film club.
I could direct it.
Well, okay.
Sounds like a plan.
Great. I got to warn you guys,
though -- I'm an auteur.
What's the move,
Boot?
Well,
car came back clean.
No outstanding warrants
and not reported stolen,
which either means a brand-new
million-dollar car
just broke down
in K-Town...Or?
The real owner's on
his yacht in Saint-Tropez
and this genius doesn't know
how to double clutch.
Let's find out.
You're contact, I'm cover.
Is everything
all right, sir?
Oh, yeah.
Just, uh --
just some engine troubles,
you know.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, you know, you'd think
for the price tag,
this thing could
fix itself, right?
Yeah, well, uh, usually,
she drives like a dream,
but, uh, you know,
these -- these foreign cars
are kind of like
Swiss watches.
You get, like,
a grain of sand in there,
it just gums up
the works.
Yeah, yeah.
I've heard that.
Uh, let me
ask you something.
Um, did you go to Rome
for the full factory tour,
or did you pick up
a floor model from Chuck
down at
Beverly Hills Imports?
Y-Y-You know,
I mean, Chuck's my guy.
But, um, wh-who could pass up
a trip to -- to Rome?
Right?
Right, yeah.
Except...
their factory is in
Sant'Agata Bolognese, not Rome,
and, uh, Beverly Hills Imports
is run by Rita.
She's a family friend.
Sir.
Turn off the car.
This guy has no idea
what he's doing.
Stop the car.
♪ Byeonhan nareulbwa hai?
♪ Naui neomchineun jonjaegam
Get out of the car.
Control, 7-Adam-15,
State Coast Freight PD
is requesting mutual aid on
a 459-train in progress.
Multiple suspects
ransacking train cars.
- Adam-15?
- 7-Adam-15 copies.
We're just about nine-seven
on that. Show us Code 6.
So this is what happened
to that planner I ordered.
How many planners
do you need?
You know, it's not
really about the planner.
It's about the perfect
version of myself
that the planner
represents.
Ah.
Officer Nolan,
Officer Chen.
Badger?
In the flesh.
It's good
to see you guys.
Wait, are -- are you
a sergeant?
Oh, yeah.
I was, uh,
promoted about a month ago.
But, uh, to be fair,
crazy turnover here,
so a lot easier
to move up the ranks here
than it is
for you guys.
Listen, I appreciate
you guys coming out
to my mutual aid call,
but, uh,
I think
we scared 'em off.
Well, good,
'cause I have questions.
Here we go.
Like, uh, how I became a cop
after my firearms mishap?
Well you shot up
the briefing room.
Which could happen
to anyone.
Well, lucky for me,
State Coast Freight Police
decided to give me
another chance,
provided I did
about 40 hours of, uh,
firearms training
and gun handling.
We're just happy
you landed on your feet.
So, what do
we got here?
Yeah, this train looks like
it was hit by a hurricane.
Flash mob, actually.
They wait for the train
to slow down,
and then they jump on
and grab all they can.
They just have you patrolling
the trains by yourself?
Uh, no.
I have a partner.
Uh, Kenny Wilson is his name.
He's a good man.
Actually, you should meet him.
He's right here down the line.
Uh, Wilson? Six-Mary-50.
A to B. Come in.
Kenny?
Kenny!
Where are you?
7-Adam-15, possible shots fired
at our location. Stand by.
♪♪
- Oh! Hey!
- Police. Stop!
♪♪
7-Adam-15, need an RA
for an officer down.
Gunshot wound
to the abdomen.
Stay with him.
40-year-old male.
Kenny, you okay?
♪♪
Control, I see the suspect
heading eastbound
on First Street,
driving a black Buick.
Want on the suspect is
an attempted 187 on an officer.
Start an additional units
Code 3 and an airship.
Shooter slipped away.
They were gone by the time
they made it to the area.
Uh, I-I'm gonna go with him.
Of course.
We'll keep you updated
on what we find.
Okay. Thanks.
Hey, buddy.
He doesn't
look too bad.
Through and through.
He should be okay.
Okay, thank you.
See you later?
Yeah.
Alright, so...
check out the train car
or wait for detectives?
Check out
the train car.
♪♪
It's different
than the other cars.
Not an Amazon box
in sight.
Well, let's see
if we can figure out
what was worth
shooting someone over.
After you.
♪♪
I mean, they were obviously
looking for something specific.
These are all tossed around,
but not opened.
Yeah. They left behind
a lot of things of value.
This antique clock had
to be worth a pretty penny.
Oh, Luce.
Yeah?
This one's empty.
Looks like a vase.
Officers?
Detectives.
Okay, yeah, no, I'm --
I'm -- I'm just gonna wait here.
I got this. You just stay
down there creating life.
The rumor's true?
Is Badger really
a train cop?
He's a sergeant.
The guy whose gun went off
during Roll Call,
he -- he outranks me?
He's a train sergeant.
It doesn't count.
You guys find anything?
Uh, the only thing
that was taken was this vase.
Maybe the guy panicked and just
grabbed the first thing he saw.
Or maybe he got
exactly what he came for.
Someone saw the assailant
toss his gun.
We need you two
to search the area.
On it.
Sir, you know
that water's filthy?
Ah, that's what makes it great
for magnet fishing.
Okay, so what exactly
did you find?
Because your call said something
about a dangerous weapon?
I got it right here.
Hey, wasn't there
a murder nearby
where the victim
was decapitated?
Yeah, and the coroner
thought the weapon
might've been
a machete or a sword.
Uh, I'm gonna have to
ask you to hand that over.
Alright.
At least the day's
not a total waste.
I could probably get a couple
hundred bucks for this.
Grenade!
Clearly, identifying fake
grenades is not your superpower.
♪♪
What?
Nothing.
You know the best thing about
riding with Tim?
Sergeants don't
pick through trash.
Hey, I got an idea.
We solve this, I let you
take all the credit.
I'll just be
a footnote on the report.
Thank you.
Of course, but you have
to search through that.
Are you...
Fine.
Yes.
Ugh.
Okay.
♪♪
Careful.
Oh, oh.
Oh, geez.
Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh!
Ugh, does it smell as bad in
there as it does from out here?
Ugh! Ew!
Sorry, diaper, watch out.
I'm starting
to feel guilty now.
Yeah, well,
you should!
Okay.
Coming in.
Oh, wait, I found it!
Oh, thank God!
Okay, I'll be in the car.
Sorry.
Oh!
Have you ever
been pulled over?
It happens to all of us.
I'm Wesley Evers,
defense attorney.
And in this video,
we'll be talking to you
about your rights
as a driver
and some do's and don'ts
to keep you safe
the next time it happens.
You're off your mark.
To your left.
Oh. Uh, okay.
Before the officer
arrives at the car,
take out your phone
and start a video recording.
That way, if anything happens
during a traffic stop,
you'll have record of it.
Next, do down your window
and place both your hands on
the steering wheel in full view.
What's my line?
"Do you know
why I pulled you over?"
- Do you know --
- N-No, no, no.
It's "Have any idea
why I pulled you over?"
I don't accept
any line changes.
Have any idea
why I pulled you over?
No, I don't, Officer.
Wait, hold on, sorry.
Still rolling.
Sergeant Grey,
let's take a beat.
I need you
to feel this scene.
Be a cop.
I am a cop.
No, I need you
to be a cop.
Make us believe.
You see
the difference?
Not particularly.
From the top.
Sir, in -- in my defense,
I've never actually, like, seen,
like, a-a real grenade
before.
You know, like, how was
I supposed to know
that was
a practice dummy?
It was blue.
Okay, so, uh, I sent
a photo of the sword
to my bladesmith
to see if it's his --
You have a bladesmith?
Well, I mean, like, I had.
In high school, I was, like,
really into manga,
so, like, he made me, like,
a few custom pieces,
and he's, like,
the number-one guy in L.A.
And, uh, he does weapons
for movies, TV shows --
I don't care.
Get to the point.
Okay, so not only
did he make the sword,
but he also gave me the name
of the woman who bought it.
So, I don't know,
maybe closing cases in
record time is my superpower?
Hey, that box car was rented out
by the U.S. government
to ship seized items
to an auction house.
William Bloomfield?
The Ponzi scheme guy?
One and the same.
Okay, so someone
broke into the train
containing belongings of
a disgraced billionaire,
and all they stole
was a random vase?
Was it worth anything?
Starting bid in the catalogue
was $2,000.
This doesn't make
any sense.
Were they able to
pull any prints off
that gun we found?
Speak of the devil.
Brian Cody Shab.
February 14, 1983.
Currently on parole for
possession of stolen property.
No history of violence,
but he's probably our shooter.
You two want to
pick him up?
On it.
Yeah.
♪♪
Brian Shab,
parole check!
Police! We know you're
in there! Open up!
♪♪
That's a lot of trouble
to go through
just to end up
breaking the damn thing.
Brian?
We know you're here.
Just come out
with your hands up!
♪♪
Chen.
House is clear.
He's dead.
7-Adam-15,
show a Code 4.
Notify Homicide.
We have a DB on location.
I'm sure many of you
are wondering,
"What if I'm stopped
by the police
and I don't have
immigration papers?"
When stopped by the police,
you will need to hand over
your license, registration,
and proof of insurance.
But, uh...
Are you
a U.S. citizen?
Stop. Are you a federal
immigration officer?
No, I am not.
Then you do not need to discuss
your immigration status,
where you're from,
or how you got here.
And you always have
the right to remain silent.
Okay, stop.
I just had a great idea
for the next scene.
Shouldn't we just
focus on this, Silas?
That might be something
you’re capable of.
Back to one.
Hey, what's up?
We might have
a break in the case.
Brian Shab -- turns out --
up until five weeks ago,
was William Bloomfield's
cellmate in prison.
Okay, so he broke into a train
and stole a vase
that used to belong
to his cellmate?
Maybe Bloomfield
sent him?
Yeah,
but why that vase?
We should definitely
look into that.
Larry?
Hey.
How's Kenny?
Kenny's great.
Surgery went well.
Uh, no major damage,
and, uh,
he's actually planning
his injury vacation.
Okay, elephant in the room.
Little weird being
in this room again.
At the scene
of the crime?
Uh, it was an accident.
Well, it's okay.
I mean, you're supposed to laugh
at stuff like this anyway.
Is there something
we can help you with?
Well, I'm -- I'm working
this case
on behalf of
the State Coast Freight PD.
I thought maybe
we'd work together.
Of course. We'll CC you
in all our reports.
Okay.
I will, uh --
I guess I'll be
checking my e-mail.
Uh, let me
walk you out, Larry.
Look, um, Harper pokes fun
at everyone.
I just decided to see it
as a sign of endearment.
Sure, b-but...
I guess I saw this
as an opportunity
to show these people
that I'm a pretty good cop.
No one should be judged
on their worst moment.
I'm actually impressed how
you've managed to overcome it.
Thank you.
You two are
a pair of mean girls.
Who are trying
to solve a murder.
So quit worrying about
the choo-choo train cop
and let's get to work.
I just got the forensics report
about the broken vase.
No prints, and when they tried
to put it back together,
they found
it's missing a piece.
So whoever murdered Brian took
a piece from that vase, but why?
What's so significant about
a piece from that vase?
Maybe this
will speak to that.
Bloomfield had
three children.
The oldest went to court
to exclude 10 items
from the auction.
Let me guess.
The vase, or "vahse,"
is one of the items
that he contested?
We need to talk to
the Bloomfield children.
Maybe one of them
can explain
why a shard of pottery
is worth killing for.
Francis Bloomfield,
you're William Bloomfield's
oldest son.
Danielle Bloomfield.
Uh, middle child?
Mm. Does it always
smell like this in here?
Thackeray.
You're the baby in the family.
Yeah,
save the best for last.
Can you tell us about
the list of items
you petitioned the court
to keep out of the auction?
Just a few things
of sentimental value.
Tell us about
this vase.
My mom bought that
in Italy.
It was on our
first holiday as a family.
Such great memories.
Wait, my brother tried to get
the vase back in court?
So you didn't know?
That duplicitous weasel.
Is there some sort of
significance to this vase?
No. It just has great
sentimental value.
Listen,
there must be a reason
your father told his cellmate
about the vase.
I'm sorry, my dad's cellmate
stole the vase?
That conniving
old goat.
I hope he rots
in prison.
You hope your father
rots in prison?
Hell yeah.
Can you think of any reason why
someone would want to steal it?
None at all.
Now may I go?
Do you know why someone
would kill for it?
I'd like to leave now.
Your dad must have told
his cellmate
about the vase,
but why?
What -- What's
so important?
Why don't you ask him?
I'm out of here.
Wow.
What a bunch of
awful people.
Yeah, who are
clearly lying to us.
And to each other,
apparently.
We need to
talk to the dad.
He's at the center
of all of this.
Harper and I have an
appointment at the
prison in the morning.
In the meanwhile,
I'll have midnight shift
start digging into
all their lives.
Hey, so, I think I know
what my superpower is.
It's my powers
of deduction.
Really?
Yeah, I mean,
the -- the car thief,
the sword.
I mean, you gotta admit
I rocked those cases.
You cracked those cases
by being rich.
Your friends are the only
Lamborghini dealer in the city.
You have a swordsmith.
Bladesmith.
He also forges
daggers and knives.
Face it,
your superpower is money.
You're like Batman,
except last I checked,
you weren't trying
to be a superhero.
So, uh, we'll see you tomorrow
at the station?
Hopefully.
Why "hopefully"?
It's gonna take all my skills
to make this footage watchable.
I'm gonna be at it all night.
I'm sure you're
going to make it great.
You headed home, too?
Yeah.
I have to talk to Nyla.
I just don't want her
to feel rejected.
She proposed, you said yes,
and now you're pressing pause.
She might feel rejected.
I love her, and I don't want
to screw this up.
You won't, trust me.
Actually, you might.
It's probably 50-50.
You know, you're really bad
at encouragement.
I know. I'm working on it.
See you tomorrow.
Alright.
Thank you very much.
That dinner was
amazing.
And...?
And it was delicious?
My dress?
Oh, this is
the new dress?
You didn't notice.
It's -- No,
it just looks a little -- little
like some of your other dresses.
Well, I have one in ballet pink,
but this is dusty rose.
Oh, and those are
two very different colors.
Listen, if you don't like it,
I can take it off.
In that case,
I hate it.
I will
take care of that.
Stay right there.
Hey.
Larry,
what are you doing here?
Sorry to just
stop by so late.
Is everything okay?
Kenny okay?
Kenny -- Yes.
Kenny's fine.
Uh, hey, how are you?
We met this morning.
Larry Macer.
I remember, and I'm glad
your partner's okay.
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah.Thank you
for the update.
That's been --
No, no, no.
I-I figured it out.
Why -- Why this vase
is so important.
You sent the files
over on the vase and
I was looking at them,
and I-I noticed that there's
a piece missing, right?
So I pulled up all these
pictures of the vase.
Look at that.
Right on the rim.
Numbers.
Numbers, yeah, but why?
Why numbers on a vase?
There's been talk
that William Bloomfield
tried to hide some of
the money that he stole.
I think these numbers are for
offshore bank accounts.
I'm back here.
Hey.
Long day?
Yeah, the longest.
How is my fiancé?
Can we talk?
Yeah, of course.
I love that you proposed
to me this morning.
And I'd be a fool if I didn't
want to be your husband.
Mm.
But I want you to make sure
it's what you want.
I just don't want to be
your regret --
you know, the guy that
you had to marry.
I want you to be
100% sure.
Well, I mean, what --I need you to really,
really think about this.
I'm gonna spend the night
at my place, and...
we'll talk tomorrow.
I love you.
♪♪
Come on, this so exciting.
It's like we're partners.
You know? I'm like the --
the Starsky to your Hutch,
the Tango to your Cash,
the Ten speed to your Brown Shoe.
My brown what?
Oh, uh, deep cut, sorry.
I'm older.
Hey, Larry's back.
Hey.
Why is Larry back?
Larry
made a breakthrough.
He'll be working
the case with us.
I should've
brought my Kev--
Great.
Uh, what'd you find?
The missing piece to
William Bloomfield's vase,
it had some numbers
and letters etched into it.
And I identified it
as IBAN from my IT days.
IBAN?
International
Bank Account Number.
Yeah, it's a way to
identify bank accounts
across national borders.
So, you see the first two,
uh, letters here?
That's the country code, and
then you got the check digits,
and the rest is basically,
uh, a bank account number.
And the first two letters
were "C" and "H."
Which you can see is
Switzerland.
O-Okay, so Bloomfield knew
the feds were closing in on him
and that they'd seize
all of his assets.
Right. So he squirreled away
a little money offshore
before he got
sent to prison.
And he etched it onto
the top of the vase
so no one could find it.
But Bloomfield knew that
he had to get the vase back
before it was sold,
so he had his cellmate,
Brian Shab,
go steal it.
I'm gonna grab Lopez
and head to the prison.
Whoever killed Shab knew
about the account numbers.
We need Bloomfield to give us
the names of everyone he told.
Alright.
Uh, can I...?
Uh are you
working with Larry now?
Your name will
still be on the report.
It better.
I mean, you know,
as long as justice is served,
who -- who cares
who gets the credit?
Mm-hmm.
So, I thought about it
all night,
and, uh,
you know what?
I have skills
beyond my parents' wealth.
For example,
nothing fazes me.
Your first day,
you almost vomited
at the sight of
a dead body.
Okay, then...
I have a strong
sense of justice.
Congratulations.
So does every cop.
Okay, how about...
I can spot liars?
Okay, you believed your mom
when she said
she wasn't in Paris
on the day of the murder.
Also, one of your best friends
was a killer
and you didn't know.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
♪♪
This video's about
what to do
if you ever find yourself
in custody.
You have the right
not to answer any questions.
Always ask for
a lawyer.
You get one phone call
after you're arrested,
so if you have a lawyer,
call them.
If you don't have a lawyer,
don't worry.
One will be appointed
for you before court.
Great, and cut.
So that's a wrap?
So we're done?
No.
You didn't see
the yellow revisions?
I added two extra scenes.
Come on, man.
I know you're getting married
at the courthouse,
but the place
where I got my dress
is having a trunk sale
this weekend.
Yeah, well, the -- the wedding
might be off.
What? Why?
It's --
I don't get
too many visitors.
Maybe because you're
one of the most...
...hated people
in America?
Direct! I like that.
Great. Then we can pass by the
warm-up and cut to the chase.
Uh, we know that you sent
your former cellmate
to retrieve
the vase that had
your Swiss bank account
number on it.
And now Brian Shab
is dead.
Whoever killed him knew about
the account numbers.
Who did you tell?
And before you answer,
keep in mind
that we can make
your life in here --
My kids.
My kids knew.
One of them
must've killed Brian.
That's amazing.
You didn't
even hesitate
to throw your children
under the bus.
They testified against me.
They sent me here.
They're gonna get that money
over my dead body.
I'm afraid one of them
already has the money.
Not if they only
have the vase.
The passwords are in
an antique music box.
There was no music box
in the shipment.
Huh.
Well...
if you need anybody
to testify against
those ungrateful bastards,
you know where to find me.
Five years?!
And then you just show up
at my doorstep?!
Nah, unh-unh.
- Go, Damien!
- Just go!
I'm not going anywhere,
alright?
This is still my home!
And I want to
see my son.
Hey, Omar!
Hey, it's Pops.
Come on outside.
Ma'am,
everything okay here?
No, it's not okay!
He should be
in prison,
not standing here
in my driveway.
Now, hold up.
Look, I'm gonna reach for
my wallet, okay?
I just got paroled,
so you can look me up.
I will.
Alright, stay calm.
We'll work this out.
Sir, can we talk?
Man, there's nothing to talk
about. I want to see my son.
Please.
Come on,
step over here.
Damien, right?
Yeah.
I'm Aaron.
Look, I know
this is tough, okay?
Five years,
that's a long stretch.
And I'm sure you spent
countless hours
picturing
this very moment.
And I'm guessing it played out
differently than this, right?
Yeah.
But you gotta remember,
I mean, they've been out here
living their lives,
and they might not be ready
right now,
but you
give it some time,
and maybe one day
they will be, okay?
Look.
This is my card,
okay?
You call me
if you need to talk.
I'm also gonna give you
the number
of our local
community center.
Just ask for
James Murray, okay?
He'll have some resources
that can help you
get back
on your feet.
Good?
Alright, thanks.
Yep.
You have a good day.
Nice job.
So, we just got off the phone
with the auction house.
The music box lands with
the 7:00 p.m. shipment tonight.
We need to get those passwords
before our killer does.
Any eyes on
the Bloomfield kids?
I'm sending units to
their houses, workplaces.
Can you three go to the depot
and guard the shipment?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I'll pull
the car around.
Uh, yeah,
I'll meet you there in two.
Uh...hi.
Can I talk to you
for a sec?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah. Thanks.
Okay, so I've been thinking
about what you said, and...
...the truth is,
every morning when I wake up,
I am glad that it is
next to you.
And I want to keep
waking up next to you
until we are
old and gray.
And, yes, yes, this baby
sped things up a little bit,
but we were always
gonna get there.
'Cause I love you.
Well,
I guess it's, um --
it's a good, good, good thing
that I bought this today.
♪♪
Nyla Harper...
will you --
Yes, yes.
Mm-hmm.
But -- But -- But,
for the record,
if anyone asks,
I proposed to you.
That was beautiful.
Smitty.
6:50.
You all right?
Yeah.
Murderous
ex-billionaire.
Just another day
on the train tracks.
They got nothing on us.
Okay, Sarge?
Yeah.
7-Adam-15,
be advised Fire's responding to
a four-five-one on the tracks
at Olympic and Montebello.
Fully engulfed van
on the tracks.
Wait, Olympic and Montebello.
6:50.
That fire is gonna
stop our shipment.
They know we're here.
What happens to a train when
the tracks are blocked?
It gets rerouted.
♪♪
You're sure the train
got diverted here?
Yeah, without a doubt.
That fire was, uh,
west of the 110,
so all southbound trains
through Simi Valley
get diverted to
the Long Beach Station
or the Alameda Corridor.
It's a good thing
you know so much about
the railway system.
Well, I'd better.
I memorized the entire
railway system
for my job interview
so they'd hire me.
You really
wanted this job.
Yeah, well, you only get one
chance at a first impression.
I learned that
the hard way.
What's the number on the car
we're looking for?
1-0-1-9.
1-0-1-9,
there it is.
Give it to me
or I'll kill you!
Give it to me.
Hey!
♪♪
Come on, man.
Give me your hands.
♪♪
- Hey!
- Geez. Hey!
No, it's mine!
Don't move.
What are you doing?!
Hands behind your back.
I was just assaulted!
I'm the victim here!
I got her.
Go get Francis.
Okay.
Uh, I'll meet you there.
You suck,
Thackeray!
Hey, look, I was in the middle
of making a citizen's arrest.
You guys, you have the right
to remain silent.
Please use it.
7-Adam-15,
two suspects in custody.
Third suspect,
officers in pursuit.
♪♪
- Need a lift?
- Whoa! Yes.
Okay.
♪♪
Stop!
You got any weapons?
Tell me now.
I had a gun in my pants, but it
slipped down into my underwear.
You...
Oh.
Ah,
I've come this far.
Ah, there it is.
Oh!
Come on, man.
Okay.
I got it.
Ugh.
Hey, Larry,
uh, it's your arrest.
You make the call.
What?
Uh...
♪♪
Control, Sergeant Larry Macer,
SCFPD.
One in custody.
We're Code 4.
This is what
they were all after.
The password,
right inside.
So, Francis,
did you kill Brian Shab
for the vase
with the account numbers?
I want a lawyer.
He did!
I can prove it!
Yeah, and he used the gun
he had on him.
Mm-hmm.
You guys suck.
♪♪
Thank you.
Hey, Larry.
Great job.
Yeah.
Nice work.
That means a lot,
but, uh...
I'm a hugger.
No, it's true,
come on.
Oh. Okay.
Come on!
- Oh!
- Come on!
Ah!
Ohh.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
♪♪
Are you
drinking tequila?
I'd like
another one of these.
♪♪
♪ When you set my soul alive,
it all comes back ♪
They're pulling up now.
I have to say, babe,
you have truly outdone yourself.
How did you pull this
together so fast?
I had a little help.
Let me guess,
he's, uh, got a rooftop guy?
Woman, actually.
Elisa.
She's my mom's best friend.
She coordinated last year's
Vanity Fair Oscar party,
so Batman
strikes again.
Uh, listen,
in all seriousness...
I think you know
what your superpower is.
You've been through
incarceration.
You know how
it changes a person.
And that compassion
that you bring to the streets,
that is what you
build your career on.
Wow, that's, um --
thank you.
And never talk about what
happened at the park.
Yes, sir.
So, are you ready
to be a big sister?
Yeah. I can't wait till
she's old enough to do stuff.
That might not be
for a few years yet.
But I'm sure your mom
is excited to have your help.
So excited.
They're coming down.
Get ready.
Congratulations!
♪♪
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
We did it!
Yay!
Oh, look at that!
Let's dance, people!
Let's go,
let's go!
♪♪
♪ Come on get up
♪ Just get on down
♪ Just turn it up
♪ Spin around, get on down
You look so pretty,
Mom.
Aww,
thank you, baby.
James is really nice.
I like him.
Oh, me, too.
You're happy
when you're around him.
And I like it
when you're happy.
Well, you made me
happy first.
Don't ever
forget that.
All you've been saying all day
is how excited you were
to wear your
going-out shoes again.
Yeah, and that's why
the shoes are coming off.
That's how you know
it's a good party.
Ah. Mm-hmm.
By the way, you don't have some
secret offshore accounts
I should know about,
right?
If anything happens to me,
just rip open
the seams of
my briefcase.
You're kidding.
Am I?
I'm sorry
about date night.
Don't be.
By our standards,
getting coitus interruptus
by a guy named Badger
is pretty tame.
I'll make it up to you.
You always do.
♪ Dance it up now, baby
♪ So don't complain
or drive me ♪
I was kind of hoping
my new brothers would be here.
Yeah, me, too, but they're
away with their mom.
But we're all having dinner
next week, though.
Alright.
I am thirsty.
I'm gonna go get a drink.
Mnh-mnh. Mnh-mnh-mnh.
My wife does not
lift a finger.
You stay right here.
Lila, how about you?
Um, can I have
a ginger ale, please?
Alright.
Make that two.
Two ginger ales
coming up.
So, tell me.
How's it feel to be
married to Nyla?
Two ginger ales.
Ahh!
I have no words.
Just pure joy.
Hm.
♪ So don't complain
♪ Or drive me,
drive me insane ♪
♪ Come on
♪ Get on down
So, I'd like to propose
a toast to the newlyweds.
I first met Nyla
when she requested a transfer
back to patrol
after having reached
the pinnacle of achievement
as a detective.
I didn't understand
her decision at the time,
but I soon learned that
beneath that tough exterior
is a woman willing
to do anything
for the people she loves.
So, James,
you're a very lucky man
to find yourself now counted
as one of those people.
Hear, hear.
To the happy couple
and their growing family.
Do you know why
I pulled you over --
It's "Have any idea why
I pulled you over?" Come on.
Yeah, you locked the keys
in the car.
The keys
are inside the car?
How did
that even happen?
This is serious.
This is my big line.
- I know. Let me --
- Just go, I'm not gonna --
I have to hold it up
like this the whole time?
Yeah, you see that in
the background -- Is that okay?
Can we cut around it?
You get one phone --
What? No, man, come on.
We're on camera, man! Fail!
One phone call. You get -- You get
one phone call.
Okay, so I've been thinking
about what you said, and...
...the truth is,
every morning when I wake up,
I am glad that it is
next to you.
Nyla Harper...
will you --
Yes, yes.
Now everyone knows
who really proposed.
You are not
supposed --
Mnh-mnh.
♪♪
Silas, that was beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm so glad that we will always
have that to look back on.
That's what I figured.
♪ Give me everything
♪ Oh, we could have it all
You know, technically,
I still owe you a dance.
I mean, there's no
technically about it.
A debt is owed.
♪ And I'd give you all
Oh. Really?
♪ I have to bring
♪ Give you everything
Listen, I know
you think I've been
taking credit
for your work, but --
I know, I know.
You said this would happen.
I did.
But, like, um, that's not
what I was gonna say.
Um... ♪ We could have it all
You're a good cop.
You know, maybe even one of
the top five I've ever trained.
I cracked
the top five, huh?
I-I-I want you to have
a successful career.
I have decided
to list you
as the arresting officer
on all future reports.
But you're
senior officer.
I know.
But you deserve
to be recognized.
You're right, I do.
Thank you.
What is going on?
Look at Bradford's moves.
Yeah.
♪ Could have it all
♪♪