Previously on "The Rookie"... Your dad is
a hell of a guy.
Maybe...you and I could
grab dinner sometime.
That'd be great.
Mm.
I bet your lovely wife
is out there listening, too,
isn't she?
I'm gonna
report your husband
to the California
state bar.
I'm gonna have
his law license revoked
for betraying the trust
of a client.
Lucy: Oh, my God.
Are you going to propose?
I'm in love with you.
Thank God. 'Cause I'm
in love with you, too.
- Bailey.
- Jason.
I'm John Nolan, her boyfriend.
And you are?
Uh, her husband.
[ Chuckles softly ]
Uh, you mean ex-husband.
Uh, I do not.
[ Chuckles ]
Long time, babe. I guess
she didn't mention me, huh?
I mean, I get it. You know,
it's -- it's embarrassing.
A husband in prison.
[ Chuckles ]
Bailey?
You're weren't supposed to
get out for another two years.
Good behavior. I-I can
hardly believe it myself.
Oh. Look. Uh, clearly
I'm interrupting here.
Um, I'm sorry. I didn't realize
you were seeing someone.
Uh, it's nice
to meet you, John.
You, uh,
be good to her, huh?
My wife deserves the best.
It's good to see you.
Sorry.
♪
So you're married.
And you didn't tell me.
[ Voice breaking ]
I-I have to go.
Bailey.
♪
[ Grease sizzling,
utensil scraping ]
Smells great. Salmon?
And eggs.
I'm not really
a breakfast person.
I know. It's for Kojo.
Excuse me.
Salmon and eggs.
For your dog.
Well, not every day.
I have to watch his cholesterol.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Whistles ]
Oh!
There he is!
Who's a good dog?
Who's the best dog?
Tricia will be here at 11:00
to give you a walk.
Ready to go?
[ Dog barking ][ Gasps ]
Whoa! Hey!
Kojo, knock it off.
He's just a little territorial
around his food.
- How long have you had him?
- A year.
He was Lucy's,
but she couldn't keep him.
[ Dog barking and growling ]
[ Monitor beeping,
dog barking ]
Kojo! Unh-unh!
[ Monitor beeps ]
Voice: Armed stay. Exit now.
[ Barking continues ]
Kojo! Hey, hey, hey!
I am -- I'm sorry.
Look, it's your first time
sleeping over,
and he's just not
used to you being here.
Here. Why don't you
just put your hand out?
It's okay.
The alarm is about to set.
We can do it another day.
[ Dog whining ]
Sure.
Hey. Be good.
Alright?
[ Door closes ]
Nolan: Why didn't Bailey
just tell me?
I mean, if it's complicated,
just say so. I'll understand.
Is it because of the ex-con
thing and I'm a cop?
Who doesn't have a criminal
in their family?
It does not get much more
embarrassing than Pete.
Mm.
And I'm -- Oh, I'm spinning out.
I-I'm gonna stop.
Well, of course
you're spinning out.
I mean, she's been lying to you
this whole time.
And technically I didn't ask
if she was married.
Yeah, but she knows
you were serious about her.
Every day that she did not
tell you about her husband
is a day
that she lied to you.
Do you know
why he was in jail?
- No. No clue.
- Alright.
Call my skip tracer,
have him run this Jason guy.
[ Line ringing]
You got a lot of questions.
You need to start
getting answers.
Randy: Skip tracer Randy! That's
me! What can I do you for?
Whoa. Hey, Randy.
It's, uh, John Nolan.
I need you
to run a name for me.
When's Wesley gonna hear back
from the state bar?
Ugh. Any day now. He hasn't
slept the last few nights.
What happened?
They suspended my license.
I can't practice law
for six months.
No. That's insane!
You were under duress.
They have to take that
into account.
Can you appeal it?
Look. It won't make
a difference.
I broke client confidentiality.
The state bar takes that
very seriously.
I-It's not even about
the suspension itself.
I'm on a list now of lawyers
who have embezzled
from their clients,
taken bribes.
For the rest of my career,
whenever somebody looks me up,
they'll see that
I have been censured.
I'm sorry.
[ Softly ] Yeah.
[ Horn honks,
indistinct shouting ]
Alright. Thanks.
I'll be in touch.
What did his
parole officer say?
Same thing --
he got out on good behavior.
Unless he violates parole,
he's a free man.
- And you don't believe it?
- Oh, I believe it.
I'm sure he was charming,
knew all the guards' birthdays,
asked after their kids,
made everyone handcrafted gifts
at Christmas.
Ah, he sounds...awful?
It's all roses
and trips to Paris
until you dare disagree
with him, and then...
This is how it was.
I would try and tell people
who he really was --
they guy they never saw --
and I'd sound insane.
Okay. Well, you know,
it's all behind you now.
You got to focus on the future.
First up, get that divorce.
I tried! For two years!
He would go along with it,
pretending to engage
in the negotiations,
and then he'd cut off contact
for months.
And just when I had given up,
he would come back
with some new demand,
and we would start this process
all over again.
[ Cellphone beeping ][ Sighs ]
Fraud alert?
Someone just charged $2,000
on my credit card.
[ Gasps ] It's Jason.
Or it's more likely
that some rando
cloned your card,
don't you think?
No. No. I-I-I-I-I don't --
I don't know. Maybe --
Hey. Hey!
Do not spin out.
You go into shock inside of
a burning building, people die.
Right now your house
is a little on fire.
So focus up.
What's your plan?
Okay. Uh...call Jason
to the station.
My turf, surrounded
by my friends.
Show him that
I'm not afraid anymore.
Tell him
I want a divorce.
So, how's it going
with Ashley?
Good. Although there was
some weirdness this morning.
I don't think
she likes Kojo.
So you broke up with her?
That's -- That's too bad.
I liked her.
Since when? Last time
we talked about her,
you gave me grief
because she's a lifeguard.
Okay. Look.
I've never really considered
lifeguarding a career.
Okay. You see,
and that is what's called
"Baywatch"-based
implicit bias.
- [ Laughing ] What?!
- Ashley went through
rigorous training at the fire
academy to become a lifeguard.
Okay. My bad. But you know what?
It is a moot point
because she doesn't like Kojo,
first of his name,
king of canines,
destroyer of chew toys.
So, clearly,
Ashley has got to go.
[ Radio chatter ]
Check out
Mister Dollar Sign.
Hand-to-hand transfer.
Classic 11532.
[ Siren chirps ]
Hey.
You are way too young
to be throwing your life away
dealing drugs.
Show me your hands.
Hey. No!
Hey! Stop!
Control, 7-Adam-100.
We got a foot pursuit
southbound, Citrus at Olympic.
Black male. Green pants.
Black hoodie.
Hey! Get back here!
[ Grunts ]
Put your hands
behind your head.
Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
♪
[ Engine sputtering ]
Control --
What the hell?
7-Adam-100. We've got
a possible Code 1000.
Repeat -- Code 1000.
Single-engine fixed wing
in distress, headed --
[ Crash and explosion
in distance ]
♪
Ohh. 7-Adam-15.
A plane is down. 1200 block of
Langston. Send fire and RAs.
[ Engine revs, siren wails ]
♪ Blurry vision, can't see
♪ Heavy breathing, and it's
standing right in front of me ♪
♪ I can't move, I can't stand
♪ I gotta, gotta, gotta, gotta,
gotta, gotta get away ♪
♪ Get away
♪ I gotta get away
[ Gasps ]
You take the car.
Yeah.
♪ Get away
- Hey.
- Get me out of here, please.
- Get me out of here.
- Just relax. Relax.
Right now I just
need you to breathe.
What's your name?
Jade.
Okay, Jade.
Help is on the way, alright?
Bailey, this is Jade.
Bailey's gonna help you out.
- She's one of the best.
- Bailey: Okay.
We're gonna get you out of there
in no time, Jade.
Tell me -- are you
- having trouble breathing?
- No.
Did you hit your head
when you crashed?
- I think so.
- Okay. Come on.
[ Saw buzzing ]
[ Siren wailing,
tires screech ]
♪
What's the situation?
Harper: We're still assessing.
The driver got the worst of it.
The flipped cars were empty.
- And the pilot?
- I don't know.
♪
There's no pilot.
Explains why it crashed.
Man:
Control, this is Air 7.
We're on scene at that
fixed-wing code 1000.
Requesting restricted air space
with half-a-mile perimeter.
Whoever was flying this plane
must've left prints.
I will dust and run them
on my Mobile ID.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
Uh...guys?
There's gold back here.
Like a couple dozen
Fort Knox-size bars.
[ ID device beeps ]
And it gets weirder.
The fingerprints I just pulled
match a Levi Lincoln,
who is currently an inmate
at the California
Correctional Facility.
So an escaped convict
stole a plane
and crashed it in the middle
of Mid-Wilshire?
Don't forget
the 200 pounds of gold.
I'll call the warden.
Levi Lincoln? Why does
that name sound familiar?
[ Gasps ] Oh, wait!
Uh -- Uh, that millionaire
who killed his wife.
Yeah, that narrows it down
less than you'd think.
Nolan: No. Uh, no.
I remember. Yeah.
It was a particularly brutal
murder, but Levi's lawyer
got the charges knocked down
to manslaughter.
Yeah, looks like
he only got 10 years.
This makes no sense.
How does an inmate at
a maximum security prison
break out with a plane
full of gold?
He didn't. The prison says
Levi Lincoln's still there.
Why are his prints
in the plane?
Harper, Nolan,
go to the prison.
Find out what the hell's
going on.
Right.
Uh, give me a minute?
Yeah.
Woman:
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
I know
you're angry with me.
Oh, I haven't really
gotten to angry yet.
I think
I'm still in shock.
I am so sorry.
I -- It was
a nightmare marriage.
I tried to divorce him,
but Jason fought me on it.
Then he got arrested
and went to prison --
Bailey.
I was so tired of fighting him
that I just walked away.
Bailey, stop. I'm not angry
because you're married.
I'm -- I mean, yes, I am.
Of course I am.
I'm just more upset that
you didn't trust me enough
to be honest about
something this important.
Mnh.
And I just don't...
know how to move forward
from this.
♪
I got -- I got to go.
You got to give him time.
I mean, he just found out.
I know.
But I can't lose him over this.
Bailey.
Uh, thanks
for reaching out.
Look, we are not
reconnecting here.
I want a divorce.
I get that you're pissed at me,
alright?
And you -- you deserve to be.
But listen.
Ever since I got out,
I-I've been trying to find you
so that I could apologize
for the man that I was.
And could I --
could I buy you lunch
- and we could talk about it?
- No, Jason.
We're talking here, because
this is where I feel safe.
Of course. Yeah.
Oh. [ Chuckles ] Hi.
[ Chuckles ]
Uh, I'm -- I'm Jason.
Also known as the worst husband
in recorded history.
- I'm Sharon.
- It's nice to meet you.
So, what are you doing
here i-in L.A.?
What do you want?
For you to be happy.
Um...
What's that?
Divorce papers.
I'm sorry.
I was so stubborn.
I-I thought that I could
make you love me again.
But I, uh, ruined
everything, didn't I?
Anyway, uh, legally,
'cause I'm your spouse,
I-I can't hand these
to you directly.
So, uh, Sharon,
if you would be so kind.
Um...
I'll see you around.
Well, he's giving you
everything you want.
Wes.
James. Hey.
What are you doing here?
Ugh. A kid I mentor
just got arrested.
Hey, uh, maybe you
could represent him.
[ Chuckles softly ]
Look, I-I wish I could,
but my license just
got suspended for six months
because of
the Elijah Stone thing.
That's tough, man.
I'm -- I'm -- I'm sorry.
Thanks.
So -- So what are you
gonna do?
Well, right now I'm debating
which bar to get drunk at.
Well, you should not
do that alone.
Text me when you decide, and
I'll come meet you after this.
Hm.
Hey, I-I heard what happened.
I'm so sorry.
I appreciate that.
I'll text you.
So, where's Tyler?
Processing.
I couldn't get ahold of
his mother, so when he said
he knew you, I-I-I thought
it was worth a shot.
Yeah. Tyler's in
a bad situation at home.
His father's incarcerated,
and his mother...
she has problems
of her own.
So you caught him dealing?
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
[ Sighs ] What the hell
was he thinking?
You know, I have a little bit
of leeway here.
I can cite him on a JCR,
which would mean
he would go home today
until his court date.
That would be huge.
I mean, I -- [ Sighs ]
I just started working
with this kid.
He's -- He's veering
close to the edge,
but if we lose him to the system
now, he's lost forever.
Okay. Yeah.
I'll cite him out.
[ Buzzer sounds ]
I hate this prison.
Are there prisons
you don't hate?
All the ones
I haven't almost died in.
At least we're not here
to see Oscar.
Why? Why?
Why do you always jinx us?
I-It's like a compulsion
with you.
[ Buzzer sounds ]
I --
Levi Lincoln.
I am Detective Harper.
This is Officer Nolan.
We have some questions for you.
About what?
Have you ever flown a Cessna,
tail number N97741?
How the hell would I know?
I own a lot of planes.
Okay, well, this particular
plane crashed this morning
with your fingerprints
inside.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Well, that's impossible.
You got that right. You've been
incarcerated for 36 months,
and those fingerprints
are fresh.
So what the hell?
I mean, that sounds
like a "you" problem.
No, no. I think -- I think
something funny is going on.
- I think it's him.
- I agree.
Um, what is your wife's
name?
Linda --
I'm not married.
And I need to see a lawyer.
Sir, you're a federal inmate,
and I have every right
to inspect
your person, so...
♪
Plastic-surgery scars.
How much did Levi Lincoln
pay you to do his time?
$5 million up front
and $5 million upon
the completion of his sentence.
Oh, you -- you should've held
out for more. The guy's loaded.
Prisoners are fingerprinted
upon arrival, so someone here
had to have helped you and Levi
pull this off. Who was it?
If I tell you that,
I'll be dead by sundown.
I'm not saying another thing
till I see a lawyer.
[ Buzzer sounds ]
You think the guards
were in on it?
Or the warden. Or both.
You know who would know...
Oh, absolutely not.
This is his prison.
He's been helpful in the past.
This is because
you jinxed us.
[ Buzzer sounds ]
It's my favorite
law-enforcement officers!
Wait. Don't tell me.
I have a son.
[ Chuckling ]
I always wanted a boy.
This isn't about you.
Oh, you're seeing
other criminals. I'm hurt.
What the hell
happened to you?
Well, it turns out that you
snitch on one lifer too many,
everybody turns on you.
It's like junior high school
all over again.
Oscar, are you familiar with
an inmate named Levi Lincoln?
I am, and I know some
rather shocking things
about Mr. Lincoln,
but it'll cost you.
He's paying a double to serve
his time for him. We know.
What we don't know
is who helped him.
Well, I'll tell you
everything I know...
but you have to get me
out of this prison.
- Forget it.
- Given who I've pissed off,
I'm looking at spending
the rest of my life here,
in protective custody,
alone,
with no one to talk to
but myself.
I am concerned
for my sanity.
So you want
a prison transfer.
A letter of support from a cop
would go a long way.
Fine.
I'll write a letter.
Oh, that is so sweet,
but weren't you arrested
for trying to murder
another police officer?
I was exonerated!
You know that!
I know, but still.
Detective Harper?
Sure.
Where do I send it?
I know you know because --
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Hello?
Randy: Hey!
It's skip tracer Randy!
Randy, I know
you're a skip tracer.
You don't have to tell me
every time.
You never know.
People are forgetful.
Did you get any information
on Jason Wyler?
Yes, sir, I did.
Born in Chicago, 1984.
Married Bailey Nune, 2016.
Convicted of
embezzlement, 2019.
He served two and a half years
of a six-year sentence
at Lompoc and was paroled
last week.
That's it? No other arrests
or complaints against him?
I gave you all I've got.
I'll invoice you
for my services.
Randy out!
[ Click, beeping]
[ Cellphone clicks ]
- Who's Jason Wyler?
- None of your business.
I can help you a lot more
than "skip tracer Randy."
You want the real scoop
on this Jason character...
come holla at your boy.
"Oscar Hutchinson has
provided limited assistance
to the LAPD
on several cases."
Oh, that's sweet.
Now, which
prison personnel
did Levi pay
to pull off this switch?
The warden.
And four guards --
Morrison, Clark,
Hobson, and Lane.
Thank you.
[ Paper rustling ]
Oh, and, uh, I faxed this to
our station, not your lawyer.
[ Buzzer sounds ]
That's just mean!
The guy in jail is a fake.
Levi paid him to do his time.
Well, we got several
911 calls about a man
parachuting near Echo Park,
but he was gone by the time
the police got there.
Any idea where he went?
No. We're pulling footage,
but no hits yet.
I tracked the Cessna's
flight path.
It took off from Sonoma,
home to, among other things,
one of Levi's many estates.
Local police checked it out,
found the back yard dug up.
That's where he got
the gold bars.
So he hires someone
to do his time,
heads south of the border,
finds an out-of-the-way place
where no one will
recognize him.
But he runs out of money,
and he knows he has gold
stashed at the Sonoma house.
And he knows he can't board
a commercial flight, so he flies
the Cessna, has engine trouble,
and here we are.
The rich.
They live just like us.
So you're Levi.
Where to next?
Well, he still needs money.
So if he hid gold bricks
in his vacation home,
what are we gonna find
in his mansion in L.A.?
- Check it out.
- On it.
[ Vehicle doors closing ]
[ Knock on door ]
Tim: Police. Open up.
Can I help you?
We're looking for
the homeowner, Mr. Lincoln.
Mr. Lincoln's in prison.
I'm taking care of his house
while he's away.
Man in distance:
Hurry up! Hurry up!
[ Whispering ]
Is -- Is he here?
[ Whispering ] Back yard.
He's got Alfredo.
[ Guns unholstering ]
Ma'am, come here.
Step outside.
♪
Man: Let's go. Come on.
Dig! Faster!
Let's go, idiot!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Get the damn bag out.
Come on. Faster!
♪
[ Gunshots ]
7-Adam-100. Shots fired
at our location.
Send backup and airship.
♪
[ Dog barking ]
[ Engine starts and revs ]
Control, 7-Adam-100.
Suspect is escaping
on a black motorcycle,
headed east on Acorn.
Levi got away, but we know
he's still desperate for money.
We've compiled a list
of all of his acquaintances
and potential money sources
across L.A. --
anywhere he might
possibly show up.
We should put a unit on
everyone. Squeeze him out.
[ Cellphone buzzing ]
Alright. Send me that list.
I'll use it to brief
the midnight shift.
I'm sorry.
Uh, excuse me.
Hello?
Lucy,
it's Ashley McGrady.
We met at my father's
retirement party.
Is this a good time?
Uh, yeah. Hey.
What's going on?
I have a problem.
I like Tim.
[ Sighs ] A lot.
But his dog makes me
super nervous,
and I-I know
he was yours first.
So...why did you
give him away?
Was he too aggressive?
No! Not at all.
I-I mean, my living situation
just wasn't suited
to having a pet.
Uh, but Kojo
is the sweetest guy.
I mean, do you --
do you not like dogs?
I had a bad experience
when I was a kid.
I-I totally get it.
Listen. Think about it this way.
Kojo is just like --
Well, I-I mean, he's
kind of just like Tim.
He's big, gruff, a whole lot
of bark, but, you know,
underneath all of it,
he's a -- he's a sweetheart.
You know, you should, um, you
should tell Tim how you feel.
No way. Never ask a man
to choose
between his dog
and his girlfriend.
There's a whole genre of country
songs that warn about that.
[ Chuckles ]
- Anyway, I'm sorry to vent.
- No.
I'll let you
go back to your night.
Thank you.
[ Click, beep]
Oh. Oh.
Are you Officer Chen?
Uh, yeah, I am. Hi.
Chris Sanford, DA's office.
Did you cite out a drug dealer
named Tyler Stent earlier today?
Yes. I did.
But Tyler is a juvenile
on his first defense,
so I wouldn't just label him
a "drug dealer."
I know.
Your arrest report
detailed his tale of woe
at length.
Honestly, it's a good thing
this isn't going to trial.
You pretty much just handed
the defense their case.
I handed them the truth.
[ Scoffs ]
You're not really that naive.
No, I'm not.
I'm trying
to protect this city.
And because of you,
a criminal who was selling
dangerous substances
is back on our streets.
Really? So you think putting
a 16-year-old into juvie
for a nonviolent offense
is gonna turn the tide
in the war on drugs?
Now who's being naive?[ Scoffs ]
How long have you been
on the job, Chris?
Four months.
Mm.
But that's not relevant.
Okay. So, tell you what. Let's
give it a year and a half,
and then you can come
and criticize my work.
Alright?
Nice to meet you, Chris.
♪
- Good night. Get some sleep.
- Thanks.
Get home safe.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Engine starts ]
[ Bailey sighs, keys jingling ]
[ Engine sputtering ]
[ Scoffs ] Perfect.
[ Keys thud ]
Just what I need.
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Latch clicks ]
[ Glass bottles
clanking in distance ]
[ Line ringing]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Click ]
Hello?
I'm sorry for reaching out.
I just --
I didn't know
who else to call.
You alright?
Yeah. I'm fine.
It's just been...a day.
I know I'm the last person
you want to hear from right now,
but I feel like
if you and I just sat down,
I could explain.
♪
I really hope that's true,
but, um...
I can't do it tonight.
I just need a little time
to get on top of how I feel.
You, um...
broke my heart a little.
[ Voice breaking ] I know.
I would do anything
to take it back.
♪
I'll call you.
[ Click, beeping]
[ Sobs ]
[ Laughter,
indistinct conversations ]
[ Laughter ]
Hey, guys.[ Door closes ]
Your husband cannot
hold his liquor.
Uh, I am fine.
Don't listen to him.
Is James staying over
for dinner?
Oh!
We're gonna get pizza.
Mm. Ah, and --
and some garlic knots.
Yes.
And garlic knots!
Yep, yep, yep.[ Exhales deeply ]
So, what are you
gonna do with yourself
for the next six months?
I don't know.
S-Spend more time with Jack.
Maybe get rid of the nanny.
Over your dead body.
[ Laughs ] Okay.
Well, I could
always use your help
over at
the community center.
I mean, people come in with
legal questions all the time.
Just yesterday,
a lady came in,
didn't know whether her sister
should take a plea deal.
Oh, man. Do not get me started
on plea deals --
how they
disproportionately affect
people in marginalized
communities.
Yes. Exactly!
I know.
Exactly.
[ Cellphone rings, beeps ]
What's up?
Lopez: Your boyfriend
is at my house.
What?
Yeah. He and Wesley went out
drinking together.
See? That-- That's
what I'm saying!
- I know! A hundred percent!
- That's what I'm saying!
Are they watching
a game?
Mm, no.
Fixing the judicial system.
Luckily,
Jack is at my mom's.
We're ordering some pizzas.
Want to come over?
[ Alarm beeps, door opens ]
On my way.
Lucy: Tim!
Hold up a second.
Hey, did something
come in on Levi?
Uh, no. Uh, you know
that call I took earlier?
It was --
It was Ashley.
Why is my girlfriend
calling you?
She wanted to know
if Kojo was a dangerous dog,
'cause you told her
he used to be mine.
Okay.
That's ridiculous.
I mean, he growled at her
a few times,
but he's just
getting used to her.
I-It's not a big deal.
W-- It is to her.
And you're so concerned
about my love life because?
Because I don't want to drive
around on patrol with you
while you are moping
about screwing this up.
Look, if you like this girl,
you should listen to her.
When have I ever moped?
I don't even know how.
Mm-hmm.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Click ]
- Hello?
- Johnny? It's Oscar.
Calling a cop
on a contraband cellphone
is not the smartest.
Fine.
I could just hang up
rather than tell you what I
found out about your boy Jason.
What did you find out?
First things first.
[ Grunts ]
I need a letter faxed to my
lawyer's office by 8:00 a.m.
supporting my appeal to
change prisons for my safety.
I thought
I wasn't good enough.
Beggars can't be choosers.
Do we have a deal?
Yeah.
Now tell me what you found.
Okay. I talked to a couple
of buddies of mine in Lompoc.
Apparently, Jason Wyler is the
most charming man on the planet,
and he's a cold-blooded
manipulator.
Yeah,
but is he dangerous?
I mean, he's serving time
for embezzlement.
He wasn't violent.
From what I've heard,
he doesn't have to be.
He whispers
in all the right ears,
and whoever is his enemy ends up
on the wrong end of a shank...
with no way
to trace it back to him.
[ Keys clank, switch clicks ]
[ Floorboard creaks ]
♪
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Hinges creak ]
[ Switch clicks ]
♪
[ Hinges creak ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
♪
So, alright.
Here's where we're at.
So, we had eyes on Lincoln's
business associates
and possible money sources
all last night,
but Levi never showed.
Well, maybe he left town without
getting his hands on any money.
That doesn't seem likely.
There's a certain standard
of living he likes to uphold.
So we keep watching his rich
friends and hope for the best.
You know, there is one rich
friend we're not watching.
His double -- Lamar Sheff.
Lincoln paid Sheff $5 million
up front to do the time,
and there's no way
the double's family
could spend it without
throwing up red flags.
Sheff's wife
lives in Whittier.
Harper, Nolan,
go check it out.
First thing we have to do is
take your felony off the table.
A felony conviction can be
a life sentence to poverty.
It'll affect your
future job opportunities,
applying for loans.
Oh, man, so I'm screwed,
aren't I?
Not if we use Prop 47.
Wait. But that's for
personal drug use only.
Yeah, but it's harder
to prove a sales case.
And don't forget -- we have
a friendly arresting officer.
This will get knocked back
to a misdemeanor possession,
which means
no jail time for you.
For real?
So I'm -- I'm good?
Ha! Not even close.
That's the easy part.
Now comes the hard.
From this day on, you are here
every day after school, okay?
We're gonna review
your homework,
and if there's anything
that you want to talk about,
we'll do that, too.[ Door opens ]
And you're getting a job.
[ Door closes ]
Curtis.
[ Clears throat ]
How you doing?
Me? I'm alright.
I'll be a whole lot better
once Lil' Man
hollers at me outside.
Anything you want to say
to Tyler, you can tell us.
And who's "us"?
I'm part of Tyler's
legal team.
Legal team.
[ Chuckles ]
Alright. For real?
Okay.
[ Clears throat ]
So, check this out,
lawyer.
Your client here entered
a verbal commitment with me
over the sale
of certain items.
Those items are now lost.
He owes me restitution.
He's getting a job, but he'll
need some time to pay you back.
With interest.
By tomorrow.
Thirty days.
No interest.
Excuse me?
Curtis, do not
make this a thing.
Aw. Nah. It's too late
for all that, James.
Now, listen.
I came in here alone
out of respect.
In here,
this is your world.
Out there, that's mine.
I'll be seeing you,
Lil' Man.
[ Exhales sharply,
sniffles ]
We got to find a place
for him to lay low
while we work this out.
I can, uh -- I can take him to
his aunt's place in Covina.
Hey. Hey. Relax.
It's gonna be okay.
But you got to go
to ground, okay?
Stay off your phone.
Don't tell anyone where you are.
You got it?
[ Softly ] Yeah.
[ Horn honks ]
You okay?
Yeah.
Well, n-no. Yes. No.
[ Inhales sharply ]
I talked to Oscar last night.
What the hell for?
He got intel on Jason.
The real,
from inside the prison.
And it turns out this guy's
as much of a nightmare
as Bailey hinted at.
Well, it doesn't excuse her
not telling you,
but it does explain it.
She probably still hasn't
dealt with the trauma.
So what do I do?
Do I just...let it slide?
If -- If Jason is
as dangerous as he says,
then he could go
back after Bailey.
Yeah, but Bailey's not exactly
a damsel in distress.
I mean, you remember what
she did to that Russian spy.
If he does make a move,
my money's on Bailey.
[ Lawn mower running ]
[ Lawn mower stops ]
Hey.
What a, uh, nice surprise.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm -- I'm all sweaty. Is --
I know what you're doing.
[ Chuckles ]
Mowing the lawn?
Just stop with the games.
Charming my co-workers,
pretending you want a divorce?
I'm not buying it,
not for one second.
You were in my house!
What? No, I wasn't.
But you're right about one
thing -- I don't want a divorce.
I want things to go back
to the way they were.
Uh, which part?
The part where you shamed me,
belittled me, tried to control
everything in my life?
Okay. Look.
I-I admit that I wasn't perfect.
But you -- you needed help,
guidance, okay?
E-Everything that I did,
I did for you.
You abused me, Jason!
Oh, come on. I never laid
a finger on you!
You didn't have to!
You isolated me from
my family and friends!
You made me think
it was all my fault!
You gaslit me to the point
of a breakdown!
[ Hushed ]
Could we talk about this later?
Hell no!
We are talking about it now!
When I left,
I was in pieces.
And then I moved out here
and I rebuilt my entire life
from scratch.
I am not the same person
anymore.
And neither am I!
Shut up and listen to me.
When I say I am not the same
person anymore, I mean it.
And if you push me,
I will push back harder
than you can imagine.
Do you understand?
Yeah. I understand.
Good.
Stay away from me.
Forever.
♪
[ Exhales deeply ]
- How much farther?
- About five minutes.
Man:
7-Adam-15, be advised --
Whittier police responded
to a 911 call
about your suspect,
Levi Lincoln.
7-Adam-15.
Go ahead.
On-scene detectives confirm
that suspect Levi Lincoln
forced his way into a home
at gunpoint,
forced a female victim,
Linda Sheff,
to wire $4 million
to a Cayman Islands account.
[ Beep, static hisses ]
That's Lamar's wife.
Cayman Islands means
he's fleeing the country.
There's a private airfield
somewhere around here.
Take your next right.
It's about a half-mile east.
Control, notify local PD.
We believe suspect
is headed for Whittier Airstrip.
Have them send backup,
and notify Sgt. Bradford.
[ Engine revving ]
♪
- Harper: Black motorcycle.
- Nolan: Someone's at the plane.
[ Engine revs ]
It's Levi.
[ Siren chirping ]
Gun.
♪
Control, taking handgun fire
from the suspect
at Whittier Airstrip.
We're pursuing on foot.
[ Airplane passing ]
♪
[ Gunshots,
bullets ricocheting ]
♪
What's your plan, Levi?
You're trapped,
and we got backup on the way.
One problem at a time.
All I got to do is get rid
of you two and get in my plane.
I hate to break it
to you,
but law enforcement
has airplanes, too --
and this thing
called radar.
Plus, getting rid of us
is gonna be a tall order.
Yeah.
I've overcome bigger obstacles.
♪
[ Gunfire, bullets ricocheting ]
You do realize
you're gonna spend
twice as much time in prison
as you originally were.
Was three years of freedom worth
the 10 extra?
♪
[ Gunfire, bullets ricocheting ]
[ Radio chirps ]
Tim: 7-Adam-15.
7-Adam-100 arriving on scene.
- What's your status?
- We have the suspect pinned down inside.
We could use backup
at the side entrance.
[ Static hisses ]
[ Gunfire, bullets ricocheting ]
♪
[ Gun clicking ]
Hi.
Drop the gun.
[ Airplane passing ]
Control, suspect in custody.
We're Code 4.
Fun fact --
It's gonna be a lot harder
to buy your way out of this
with no money.
[ Handcuffs clicking ]
Tell me about it.
Being broke sucks.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
[ Buzzer sounds ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Thank you.
Yeah.
That should be everything.
Officer Chen.
[ Exhales sharply ]
You're back.
Has it been a year and a half
already?
Tyler Stent was just arrested
for armed robbery.
He pointed a gun
at an elderly store owner,
who then suffered
a heart attack.
If she dies, I'm charging
your kid with murder.
If you hadn't cited him out,
this wouldn't have happened.
[ Buzzer sounds, door opens ]
♪ Do you remember sounds
of autumn singing? ♪
[ Siren chirping ]
♪ But we have been dropping
like the flies we are ♪
Driver, turn off your car
and place both hands
out of the window.[ Siren chirping ]
What the hell?
[ Music stops,
engine shuts off ]
Driver, open the door
from the outside.
Step out with your hands
above your head.
[ Insects chirping,
dog barking in distance ]
- Step away from the vehicle.
- What is going on?
Ma'am, step away
from the vehicle!
I haven't done anything wrong.
I'm LAFD.
We'll tell you what's going on
in a second.
Step away from the vehicle,
ma'am.
I-I didn't give you permission
to search my car.
What is happening?
Why am I...
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
- Wait. That isn't mine.
- You have a right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you.
It was my husband.
He's framing me.
[ "Jingle Bells" playing ]
Nolan?
[ Buzzer sounds, door opens ]
You got two minutes.
Thank you.
You okay?
No.
I'm pissed.
Jason set me up.
Yes. I know.
I know.
His fragile little ego never
could handle being challenged.
I should have
seen this coming.
This is not your fault.
I confronted him at work.
I embarrassed him.
I knew he'd retaliate,
but I didn't care.
I just wanted to show him
that I wasn't scared.
[ Sighs ]
I was so stupid.
No. You were right
to stand up to him.
There's no winning.
I run.
He tracks me down.
I fight back.
He takes my career.
If I'm convicted
on a drug charge,
they'll throw me off
the job.
And he knows it.
He's taking everything
that matters to me.
It's what he does.
He thinks if I'll get
low enough, I'll go back to him.
Okay.
Well, that's never gonna happen.
How much is my bail?
I can pay you back.
Okay. Well, it's not quite
that simple.
The amount of cocaine
they found in your car --
They're gonna charge you
with a felony.
That means you're gonna
have to wait for a judge
to set your bail.
[ Sighs ]
And how long
will that take?
Hopefully a day,
maybe two.
But don't worry.
While you're in here,
I'm going to fix it.
I can't ask you
to do that.
You don't have to.
I'm doing it because I love you.
Still?
Yes.
Still.
♪
But that doesn't get us
anywhere near to good.
But nobody screws with you
and gets away with it.
♪ I hear the drizzle
of the rain ♪
♪ Like a memory...
Tyler, what happened?
We had a deal.
I had to get Curtis
his money.
No.
We were coming up with a plan.
Why didn't you just listen
to us?
I'm sorry.
I panicked.
I...
Is the lady gonna be alright?
♪
We don't know yet.
Come on.
Move it along.
♪
♪ And from the shelter
of my mind ♪
♪ Through the window
of my eyes ♪
♪ I gaze beyond...
Voice:
Disarm system now.
[ Monitor beeping ]
Hey, buddy.
[ Dog growls ]
♪ ...to England,
where my heart lies ♪
[ Monitor beeps, dog barks ] Disarmed. Ready to arm.
[ Sighs ]
This is a terrible idea.
No.
It's gonna be great, okay?
I want you to feel
as comfortable here
as you do at home.
Look, Carl from the K9 unit said
that dogs respond positively
to people who display control,
okay?
They're pack animals.
They know when they see
a leader.
I know this is scary,
but I'm right here with you.
And I promise you,
you're gonna --
you're gonna love him
if you just give him a chance.
[ Dog whines ]
♪ There but for the grace of you
go I ♪
Sit.
[ Dog whines ]
Too nice.
Just boss him around a little.
♪
Sit.
Down.
[ Exhales sharply, laughs ]
♪
Hey, hey.
[ Laughing ] That's my job.
Okay, Kojo.
[ Laughing ] One step at a time.
♪
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
It's, uh, John, right?
Good to see you again.
No need for the act.
You planted those drugs.
What?
Drugs?
Wh-- Uh, whoa, whoa.
Uh, rewind.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Yeah, you do.
Bailey's sitting in a jail cell
right now because of you.
She is?
Oh, God.
That's, uh, horrible.
No.
It's exactly
what you wanted.
Well, of course
it isn't.
But, you know,
I got to say,
hearing that she's finally
facing some consequences
for her actions, well...
...it does well
for my spirit.
♪
You really can't
let her be happy, can you?
Couldn't stand that she
didn't need you anymore.
Well...
Well, your time is over.
I know who you are now.
And I'm coming for you.
♪