Ahh.
Hey.
Oh.
Come look at this.
Never seen
anything like it.
Um...
No, thanks.
Come on.
I don't know
what the hell it is.
Wow, thanks for waiting.
Hey, hey, hey.
Luther, cool it.
Sorry.
He's usually
such a sweetheart.
Hey, let's go.
Wait, we just got up here.
Ow!
What is going on?
That guy
is serial-killer creepy.
Like, he tried to get me
to go inside with him.
I'm calling 911.
It's Bailey's
Army Reserve week.
How's being
a bachelor going?
Oh, I hate it.
House is too quiet.
Keep making an extra cup of
coffee for her without thinking.
I-I did laundry
last night...
Not a single, weird,
frilly thing
that I don't know how to fold
anyway.
Kinda sounds like
you guys live together.
Whoa! No!
No, we're not ready
for that.
She just stays over
sometimes.
A... A lot of times.
Oh, my God. Did we accidentally
move in together?
7-Adam-15,
we have reports
of suspicious activity
in Griffith Park,
near the DWP relay station.
7-Adam-15,
show us responding.
It's great that you guys
are so happy again.
What is it they say?
If you can survive
a secret marriage,
you can survive
anything?
Whoa.
7-Adam-15 on site.
Signs of forced entry.
We're gonna go in
and check it out.
Lucy.
Move!
Captions by VITAC...
You sure you're okay?
Yes, sir.
Just a little banged up.
That explosion took out power
to most of the Valley.
Gonna take at least 12 hours
to restore it.
Here come the feds.
Matt,
how have you been?
Me? Anxious.
We've been hearing rumors
about a potential terror attack
for weeks,
and now it's happened.
Have you met Agent Fox?
No. Wade Grey.
Casey Fox.
That's Sergeant Bradford,
Officers Nolan and Chen.
Clearly, you're the ones
who found the bomb.
Can you describe it?
Not really.
All I saw was a timer,
some wires, and then I was
running for my life.
Same, but my impression was that
it was fairly rudimentary.
Well, the bomb guys
will get in there.
They'll take a look
once it's safe,
and hopefully
there's something left
that we can trace back
to a source.
Of all the targets in the city,
why hit this place?
I mean, there's no potential
for casualties.
All they can do is knock out
power to the Valley.
I don't know yet,
but there is a possibility
that this attack
is only the beginning,
which is why the FBI
is taking over.
Matt, this guy almost killed
two of my officers.
We're not just gonna stand
on the sidelines.
Okay.
Let's "Super Friends"
the investigation...
Joint task force.
The first thing we need to do
is talk to all the witnesses
who called 911.
Thanks for riding
with me today.
Yeah, of course.
I'm happy to keep filling in
on the detective side.
Because it keeps you out
of uniform.
God, yes.
I feel like I'm already,
like, 90 months pregnant.
What?!
Uh, Professor Meadows,
I am Detective Harper.
This is Detective Lopez.
You called about
an intruder.
Yes. Yes.
Thank you for coming.
I woke up in the middle
of the night,
and there was someone
in my bedroom.
Can you describe him?
I can do better.
I sketched him.
Now, where did I put
that drawing?
Uh, he was an alien.
I can... tell you that much
to start.
You could tell
he was undocumented
just by looking
at him?
No, no, no, no,
not that kind of alien.
No, he was, uh...
Oh.
He was a Heptapod.
With cosmically
awful breath.
Oh, and, um, how do you know
it was a he?
Well, it was more
of a feeling I got.
I-I certainly didn't see
any external genitalia,
or I would have put it
in the sketch.
Mr. Meadows, are you on
any medications?
Why does everyone
always ask me that?
Listen to me.
An alien broke into my house
and stole my manuscript...
Thedefinitive treatise
on Los Angeles traffic patterns.
Why would an alien
travel across the galaxy
for a book on traffic?
Understanding traffic is the key
to human colonization.
Right.
Of course.
You... You think I'm crazy,
but I-I can prove it happened.
The alien attacked me.
I only survived because
I managed to lock myself
in the bathroom.
He's white, dark hair,
30s.
With a scar
under his left eye.
And he had an accent.
Um... couldn't quite
place it.
Well, it was Russian.
Yeah, he sounded just like
Vladislav Ivanov.
Who?
Lelush.
The super-hot model
who was trapped
on that Chinese
reality singing show. I mean...
Can that be right? Oh,
yeah, Lelush is super cute.
No, I mean, the...
We need to pull them out.
TID got a partial on a piece
of the explosive device.
Prints came back
for an Ezekiel Freemont.
That is not
a scar-faced Russian.
So we could be dealing
with a terror cell.
Police!
Clear!
All clear.
He's not here.
Okay, now we go
into manhunt mode.
Let's get a BOLO going,
and I want agents
on the doorstep of everyone
that this guy has ever known
by sundown.
So, small world.
Turns out, our suspect's
high school guidance counselor,
Simone Clark,
is currently a trainee
at the FBI Academy
at Quantico.
So let's get her here
ASAP.
Drifting is not
proper FBI technique!
Hey... Oh. Aah!
What? Hey... Oh.
Whoo!
Trainee, pursuit
is passing you!
Oh, no.
Here we go.
FBI!
Out of the car!
On the ground!
On your stomach! Do it now!
How'd I do?
Pretty good, right?
Where the hell did you learn
to drive like that?
Claybourne High School
in D.C.
I was a guidance counselor there
for 20 years.
Taught Driver's Ed for
eight of 'em, till they realized
I was using the time to teach
myself and my students
advanced
driving techniques.
I also coached
the wrestling team
'cause I wanted to perfect
my hand-to-hand fighting style
so I could pursue my dream
of becoming an FBI Agent.
That's a... fun story.
But the FBI has a very specific
way of doing things,
and a 50-year-old...
48.
48-year-old
former high school teacher
with a "Fast & Furious" fetish
doesn't really fit our model.
Did I make a single mistake
on the driving course?
No.
Did I successfully
pit-maneuver this car
and put the suspect
under arrest?
Yes.
Alright, then I don't understand
what the problem is.
Trainee... you are trying
to succeed at an agency
where J. Edgar Hoover once fired
an agent for having acne.
You're either FBI material
or you're not.
Simone Clark?
Yes, sir.
Do you remember a student named
Ezekiel Freemont?
Zeke. Yes, sir.
He's the main suspect in
a terror attack in Los Angeles.
You're going to L.A. to brief
investigative agents
on Mr. Freemont.
Happy to help, sir.
Have yourself
a very good day... sir.
Let's go, Clark.
Based on his history,
our suspect clearly shares
several personality traits
with Ted Kaczynski,
otherwise known
as the Unabomber.
Whoops.
Don't mind me.
I... I'm just gonna
tuck in over here.
Ooh.
Excuse me, handsome.
No problem.
As I was saying,
Ezekiel Freemont fits
the classic mold of a high-IQ,
low-empathy psychopath.
No,
that's not right.
Did you say something?
No, no, no.
Keep goin'.
Becoming a bomber speaks
to his deep sense of anger
and his impotency.
But social and sexual
tendencies...
Oh, Lord.
Excuse me.
This is... Who are you?
I'm Simone Clark.
I-I just flew in
from the Academy.
I was Zeke's guidance counselor
for three years in D.C.
Right. Step out so everybody
can see you.
You clearly disagree
with Marlin's profile.
I just don't recognize
the kid he's describing.
Zeke grew up
in a violent home.
Had sensory-overload issues
because of it.
But I found him to be
a deeply empathetic person
who isolated himself
from others
as a protection mechanism.
With all due respect,
you're a guidance counselor.
I'm a trained
behavioral scientist
with three decades'
experience.
And I got mad respect for you,
even if you don't appreciate
what a good guidance counselor
brings to the table.
I've worked with literally
thousands of young men and women
at their
most formative age,
from future criminals
to future millionaires
and everything
in between,
and that made me
an expert on people.
Where do you think Zeke
is hiding right now?
Some place dark and quiet.
When the world
got overwhelming,
he just went some place
to hide.
He feels safest
underground.
Thank you for your insight,
Trainee Clark,
but I'm gonna trust our profiler
on this one.
The guy that you knew in D.C.,
he's no longer the same guy.
We think that he's part
of a terrorist cell
intending to strike this city
again.
And we need to catch him
before they set off a bomb...
One that kills innocent people
this time.
So let's get to work.
Um... I just want to say, I am so
sorry for speaking out of turn.
So, w-what can I do now?
I mean, how can I help?
Y-You can't.
You should just go back
to the Academy.
The travel office
is on the fourth floor.
They'll give you a voucher for
a coach seat back to Virginia.
So, no private jet?
Pr...
Je... No.
Excuse me.
That was pretty brave,
the way you spoke up in there.
Thank you, but I don't think
I did myself any favors.
John Nolan.
Simone Clark.
Did you hang back 'cause you
wanted to get my phone number?
No, ma'am.
Just to tell you,
I think they were wrong to
dismiss your insight so quickly.
You're the only one
in that room
who actually knows
our Mr. Freemont.
In my book, that makes you
the only real expert.
Ooh. Keep talkin'.
Well, if you're not in a rush
to get back to Quantico,
how would you like to ride
with me the rest of my shift,
help us find our suspect?
I'd love to.
This way.
How long you been
on the job?
Only a couple years.
I was just the oldest rookie
in the LAPD.
What? That's funny
because I'm the oldest trainee
at the Academy.
So, why'd you change course
and sign up?
Found myself in the middle
of a bank robbery.
What? Helping the
people on the inside
made me want to do
more of it.
What about yourself?
I've always wanted to be
an FBI agent,
but I ended up on an off-ramp
when I found out
I was pregnant
with the twins.
They in college now, so time for
Mama to finish what she started.
It's not easy, though,
trying to keep up
with these 20-somethings.
Sheesh.
Every day, I am determined
to beat them,
and every night, I crawl into
bed feeling beaten.
Can I offer you
some hard-won advice?
Please.
You are never gonna beat them
at being 20-something.
But what you lack
in flexibility
or the ability to run up
a flight of stairs
without getting winded...
you more than make up for
in life experience.
And that puts you way ahead of
the curve, day one on the job.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Anytime.
Alright.
This is the closest tunnel
to Zeke's apartment.
I'll go check it out.
I'mma come with you.
No, it's not safe.
You're not even armed.
I'm telling you,
I know this kid.
He's not
a violent person.
And the bomb that nearly
killed me says differently.
Well...
Stay here.
7-Adam-15, I have eyes
on our bombing suspect.
Heading east
toward King Street.
Zeke. Zeke!
Don't even think
about it.
I got him.
Did you just steal
my police vehicle?
No. I borrowed it
to catch a fleeing suspect.
You're welcome.
Miss Clark, is that you?
Yes, honey.
Please don't let that man
kill me.
What man?
I know that look.
He's overloaded, shuttin' down.
If he wasn't handcuffed to
that table, he'd be under it.
Shouldn't you be on a plane
to Virginia?
Oh, that's my fault.
I asked her to stay.
W-Without Simone, we wouldn't
have our suspect in custody.
Well, I'm glad
that she was of service.
But tell me something, Trainee,
in the Bureau,
what are you taught to do
when given an order?
Follow it, sir,
to the letter.
Matt, considering her
relationship with the suspect,
we were thinking that she should
take point on the interview.
Absolutely not.
She's a NAT, nowhere even close
to being qualified.
Agent Fox is right. We'll
conduct the interview ourselves.
Get yourself back to Quantico
now, while you can.
Mr. Freemont...
we're with the FBI.
You are in a lot of trouble.
I'll, um, walk you out.
If you need any recommendations
on places to eat
before your flight...
Thanks, but I know
all the good spots.
At least, I used to.
I grew up here.
Really? Any family you want
to see before you leave?
None that wants to see me.
Trainee, hold up!
Suspect says
he'll only talk to you.
Can we lose
the shackles?
Yes, of course.
Hey, Zeke.
It's me...
Miss Clark.
Remember to breathe,
okay?
When I first met Zeke, he was
really struggling in school.
Every day, he was either
acting out,
freaking out,
or zoning out.
But then we spent
some time together,
and I realized he just needed
help transitioning
from the chaos at home.
So I told him to come
in my office every morning.
And what did you say?
That I didn't wanna
talk.
Mm-hmm, that's right.
And I told him
he didn't have to.
He could use that time
to get quiet.
And that's what we did.
Every day for two years,
he would come to my office,
sit for 15 minutes,
then go to class.
And who became
an "A" student?
Yeah, after a few weeks,
she bought me an MP3 player
and some headphones so I could
listen to music in the morning.
Mm-hmm.
I'm in real trouble, huh?
I'm afraid you are.
What can you tell us about the
man with the scar on his face?
I don't know who he is,
I swear.
I needed money, so I've been
selling my engineering skills
on the dark web.
He paid you to build a bomb
for him?
No,
just the detonators.
Detonators?
As in, more than one?
I made him six,
along with a regular timer
and five with GPS triggers.
T-Those are special.
I-I-I built them
so they'd go off
when they reach a programmed set
of coordinates.
And what were
the coordinates?
Oh, he didn't tell me.
I-I-I gave him
the instructions
on how to program them in
himself.
You knowingly helped
a terrorist?
He said he was
a research scientist
and that it was for a project
that he was working on.
I-I-I knew
it didn't sound right,
but I was desperate
for money.
And about the time I got
to the exchange,
I realized I made a mistake,
but it was too late.
He grabbed the detonators
and tried to shoot me.
I ran away and hid.
Zeke, is there anything else you
can tell us about this man?
His name,
the kind of car he drives?
I told you everything I know,
man.
I'm sorry I let you down,
Miss Clark.
That is a very troubled
young man.
You really believe he didn't
know he was making detonators
for bombs?
I don't know.
For such a smart kid,
he could sometimes act a fool.
Now he's looking
at a lifetime of incarceration
due to federal
mandatory minimums.
I gotta get
this kid a lawyer.
Uh, do you really think
that's a good idea?
That's not gonna make you
any friends at the Bureau.
I know, but Zeke's
one of my kids.
I told my students
on day one,
"Miss Clark will always have
your back, no matter what."
That's not gonna stop
just 'cause he graduated.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
I appreciate that,
but I know somebody
I can go to
about this.
It was a pleasure
working with you, John.
Wish I could stick around
to help you catch the guy.
Me too.
And, Simone,
don't let them get you down.
You're the real thing.
Professor "Alien"
called again.
He wants an update on
the Heptapod who stole his book.
Well, according
to his colleagues,
he was actually telling
the truth about one thing.
He is the foremost expert
on urban planning.
Unfortunately, he also pioneered
LSD micro-dosing.
And accidentally fried
his brain?
Yeah. He has been having
hallucinations ever since.
Hello?
Professor Meadows, we were just
discussing your case.
Hold on.
Let me put you on speaker.
And I just remembered something
about the break-in.
When the alien fled,
I looked out the window
and saw him jump
into a red flying saucer.
Oh, it was more of an oval
now that I think about it.
Okay, got it. If you remember
anything else, let us know.
So, should I put out a BOLO
for a red spaceship?
No, but if we assume
that the attack is real,
then it's possible
what he saw was a red car.
So we should start pulling
traffic-cam footage.
No problem. There's only about a
million red cars in Los Angeles.
Hey, Grey wants
all hands on deck.
Oh, thank God.
Come on, people, can't rely on
the feds to solve this for us.
Well, Zeke said he made
six detonators for our bomber.
The first one,
a countdown timer that was used
at the relay station,
and the other five GPS-enabled.
If only we had an idea
what the targets are.
Hey, maybe we could
extrapolate them
from the first target,
the power station.
There's got to be a reason
he hit that thing first.
Not because he wanted
to hurt people.
He only knocked out the power
to a big chunk of the Valley.
What if
that was the point?
What if he wanted to, uh,
get something or do something
that he didn't have access to
unless the power was off?
There's at least
a dozen banks.
Jewelry stores,
a check-cashing place.
I mean, there's no
high-value targets here.
Nothing that is
a terrorist's wet dream.
National Guard Armory.
That...
That's gotta be it.
And there are enough weapons
there for an entire platoon.
And enough explosive munitions
to take out a hundred targets.
I'm sorry, but the
armory's in lockdown right now.
I'm the one who called you
earlier...
about your husband.
Is Brady okay?
For now.
And so long as you do
as you promised,
you'll see him tonight.
Now, let's get to work.
Control, 7-Adam-100,
be advised Adam-15,
Adam-4, Adam-22, and us
are Code 3
to the National Guard
Armory
for a possible 459
in progress.
Will advise.
Bailey,
we're three minutes out.
Any sign
of our terror suspect?
Not yet, but the armorer chief
isn't answering his radio.
We're entering the cage.
Got a man down!
John, he's here.
Or he was.
Stay with him.
Everyone, on me.
He's fleeing in one
of our Humvees.
South gate.
There he is.
7-Adam-100, suspect vehicle
heading west on Vernon.
Show us in pursuit.
Whoa, whoa.
Geez.
We need to stop
this guy.
That's not a minivan,
it's a mini-tank.
Bulletproof, bombproof.
Our shops
can't pit-maneuver it.
We have to wait
for the BearCat.
Maybe we can box the Humvee in,
force him off the road.
There's one way
we can find out.
Okay, Nolan, get on his left.
We'll take the right.
You have to ram him in unison,
alright?
Aim for the doors.
Whatever you do,
don't hit the wheels.
What? Why? What happens
if I hit his wheels?
We'll die,
and you'll forever be known
as an LAPD cautionary tale.
Oh, great, proving my mother
right once and for all.
Wait. I'll be
the cautionary tale?
No way.
If this goes bad,
we will both be disgraced
together.
In position.
Alright, on three.
One, two, three!
Show me your hands!
Now!
Hey, Daddy.
What are you doing
in L.A.?
Uh, you'd know if you answered
my calls or my texts or my...
Are you still
in the FBI?
Technically, I'm just a trainee,
but...
He did not just close this door
in my face.
Daddy!
Open the door.
We need to talk.
Are my grandkids okay?
The twins are fine.
Then there's nothing for us
to talk about.
Uh...
Open this damn door!
Da...
Your neighbors are out here
looking at me like I'm crazy.
Hey, Mr. Jenkins.
Your dog is so cute.
This is embarrassing!
Not as embarrassing
as being a leader
in the "Defund The Police"
movement
with a daughter
in the FBI.
Do not close this door,
you stubborn old man.
If you don't want to talk to
your only daughter, fine.
But I'm not here
as your daughter.
I'm here as an advocate.
For who?
Zeke Freemont.
He's one
of my former students.
Now he's being charged
as an accessory
in a domestic terror
plot.
And you're the only person
I trust to get him a lawyer
that'll actually
give a damn.
So, see?
This is not about
you and me.
This is about a kid
who deserves a second chance.
So, will you help me?
My husband was abducted
by this man.
He threatened to kill Brady if I
didn't do exactly what he said.
Okay.
Can you describe him?
Russian... at least, his accent.
Scar on his face.
What did he steal
from my armory?
200 kilos
of C-4 explosives.
Now, nobody asked you
to cook.
Okay, you want me
to throw it out?
Mmm
!Okay?
Mm-hmm. It tastes just like
your mother's.
Miles Davis.
I love this song.
Yeah, me too,
but it's Dizzy Gillespie.
Bup-bup-bup-bup.
Back up.
Don't even come over here
reaching in these pots.
Mama's recipe,
Mama's rules.
We eat at the table.
Oh, I miss everything
about your mother...
except her damn rules.
You would always rope me in
as your accomplice
to break every single
last one of them.
We drove Mama crazy
with our foolishness.
Yeah.
We used to be
so close, Daddy.
Well, that's on you.
Joining the feds,
after everything I went through
at the hands
of law enforcement...
Everything
wewent through.
Really? Because I was
the one incarcerated
for a crime
I didn't commit,
away from you,
your mother.
Which is why I'll find
a lawyer
for your student
who is in trouble.
But, Simone, you are on
the wrong side of this trouble.
It was an FBI investigation
that got you exonerated.
And it was FBI investigations
that tried to compromise Martin,
Malcolm, Angela,
Black Lives Matter.
Daddy, a good agent can make
more positive change
with one case than most people
do in a lifetime.
Oh, what's that?
Quote for the yearbook?
Come on, give me a real reason
why you are doing this.
Because we make up
less than 1%.
Black women make up
less than 1% of the FBI.
Speeches at rallies
only do so much.
If we want real justice,
we need a voice on the inside.
You just don't get it.
Once you're in the FBI,
they'll change you.
Well,
we will never know.
'Cause I am about that close
to being kicked out.
For what?
Well, apparently, there two ways
of doing things...
The FBI way
and the wrong way.
And guess which one
I'm excelling in.
So I'm screwed.
Not according to
Miles Davis.
He said, "When you hit
a wrong note,
it's the next note
that makes it good or bad."
They haven't
kicked you out yet.
So what happens next
is on you.
It's great advice,
Daddy,
but I thought you said you
didn't want me to be in the FBI.
No, I don't.
But nobody tells my baby girl
that she doesn't belong.
Wow. The FBI doesn't really do
moderation, do they?
Seriously, it's like
a spaceship.
Get any sleep? No, but,
uh, Sleeping Beauty here
got an hour
in the back of the shop.
Sergeant's stripes
come with privileges.
Don't be jealous.
Okay, people, listen up.
Garza has an update.
It's a whole new ballgame.
The amount of explosives stolen
sent shock waves
through D.C. overnight.
Homeland Security is now getting
involved, as is ATF,
which means this is no longer
a joint task force.
It's wholly federal now.
All due respect, LAPD has busted
their ass in this case.
Hey, I get it.
I do,
but my hands are tied.
A terrorist got away with
over 200 kilos of C-4,
so that kind of changes
the complexion of things.
Are you blaming my guys for that?
Did I say that, Wade?
Oh, no, uh,
we're all a little tired,
but I think we can remember
we're all on the same team here.
You're not talking
to security guards, Matt.
We've investigators, and we're
not gonna stop hunting this guy
because you tell us to.
Can we talk about this
in private, please?
You're damn straight.
My office.
I got a problem.
Me too.
I've been scrubbing traffic-cam
footage for hours,
hunting for
an extraterrestrial.
No, no, I'm serious.
What is it?
The baby?
No.
TID pulled partial prints
from the professor's rear door.
You know, the one that
the aliens jimmied open?
That's not a problem.
That's great.
It has to belong
to the attacker.
Exactly.
So I ran the prints,
and they came back
as classified.
What?
Yeah, so, I called my friend
over at the DEA
who has top-secret clearance,
and I asked her to run
the prints,
and she was denied
access, too.
Who the hell
is our suspect?
I don't know,
but the classified designation
for our suspect
originated from...
the Air Force base
at Groom Lake.
Okay,
your vocal inflection
leads me to believe
that's a big deal,
but for the life of me,
I don't know why.
How do you not know
about Groom Lake?
Paradise Ranch?
Dreamland?
Also known as Area 51.
Isn't that where the government
supposedly keeps the...
Aliens? Yeah.
You think I'm pissed off because
you hurt our feelings?
We don't care... What the hell
are you still doing here?
Oh, I just need five minutes
with Agent Garza.
You're supposed to be back
at Quantico.
You and I both know that as soon
as I get back to the Academy,
they gonna find
a reason to fire me.
Here is the only place
I can prove I belong.
You're still a trainee.
It's not gonna happen.
Can you honestly say that
all my contributions
haven't earned me a place
on this task force?
Absolutely.
A NAT who can't follow orders
has no place in the FBI.
Okay. Look... my father
was incarcerated
for a crime
he didn't commit.
I know.
I read your file.
Okay, w-well,
here's what's not in it.
My father was
an amazing trumpet player.
He was a jazz prodigy.
After eight years
in prison,
never picked up
his horn again.
He let the system steal
that from him.
He didn't even put up
a fight.
He gave up on his music,
his dreams, all of it.
But let me guess.
It's not gonna be you.
Look at you,
finally starting to get me.
Let me tell you
what I wish someone told me
when I was a blue flamer,
trying to prove myself.
The FBI isn't a safe space
for women's empowerment.
It's a boys' club.
Now, you still have
a chance to make it.
All you have to do is fit in
by hiding who you really are.
Honey, there's
no hiding this.
Simone, I'm trying
to help you.
I know, Casey...
Agent Fox.
A-And I'm sorry for whatever
you had to put up with
to do this job.
But the one thing I learned
in this life
is to be true
to who I am.
So I'm waiting right here
for Agent Garza.
Okay.
Here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna call a professional...
someone you could talk to
about all of this.
But you're working
with the aliens.
No, Professor, we are the ones
who are trying to help you.
We believe that your attacker
is or was in the military.
Yes,
the galactic alien army.
Okay, okay, maybe your attacker
was an alien.
The truth finally prevails
with you conniving WIBs.
WIBs?
Women in Black.
Hi, y'all.
I'm Simone with the FBI.
Can I speak to you two
for a hot sec?
Hey, I'm not trying to tell you
how to do your job,
but that man is having
a clinical delusion.
He's unable to process logic,
so you challenging him
is only pushing him further
towards his beliefs.
And you playing along
is just making him think
his delusions are real.
Are you a psychiatrist
or...
I was
a guidance counselor.
I worked with kids
experiencing everything
from schizoaffective disorder
to severe horniness.
So, you think you can
get through to him
in a way that we can't?
I think I can charm
and disarm him,
and it might bring him back
to reality.
We could definitely use
some more reality.
Give it a try.
Hello, sir.
I am not a Woman in Black.
See?
I'm wearing brown and tan.
It's cute, right?
Mind if we go somewhere
where we could talk?
When I was a little girl,
I used to go out in the yard
and look for UFOs.
And then, one night,
they found me.
Extraterrestrials?
Well, no,
a family of possums
rooting around
in our trash cans.
I thought
they were ETs.
Have you ever seen
one of those things up close?
It's otherworldly.
But I never stopped believing
that it was possible
we're not alone
in the universe.
We're not.
I was attacked by a Heptapod who
smelled of chocolate and blood.
Okay, see, now, Professor,
that makes me wonder
why you're the only person
who saw this bizarre creature.
Because he's a shape-shifter
who can take on many forms.
Okay. Like what?
A white man in his 30s.
Okay, what else can you tell me
about him,
when he was a white man
in his 30s?
He spoke Russian.
Well, at least,
he had an accent.
It's hard to remember.
W-Well, Professor,
did the man have a scar
on the left side of his face?
You've seen him, too.
I'll be right back.
Do you have
a task force BOLO?
I can pull it up
on my phone.
Professor...
is this the man
that attacked you
inside your home?
Yes! That's him.
Okay, everybody, our suspect
is renting a house
in Lincoln Heights under
the name Trevor Gurin.
We tracked him there through
traffic-cam footage
from his origin point
at the professor's house.
That's great work,
detectives.
Actually, Simone deserves
the credit.
She's the one who put it
all together.
Good work.
Thank you, sir.
I just...
Mobilize additional agents
and HRT.
And notify Homeland
and ATF.
So, you two on me.
Get schematics for the house,
send them to my box.
I'll put in for a telephonic
warrant. Alright.
So, you think I should
put you on the task force?
Honestly, only a fool
would keep me off it.
Are you calling me
a fool?
Are you putting me
on the task force?
Yeah.
You're riding with me.
Let's go.
Yes!
Go, go, go!
Secure the perimeter.
We got a body!
Is it our suspect?
No, the abducted husband.
Given how cold he is, I'd say
Gurin killed him last night
when he got back
from stealing the explosives.
House is clear.
For all we know,
this guy's pulling off
his next attacks as we speak.
So let's tear this place apart.
We're looking for anything
that might indicate
our unsub's targets.
All units, be advised
suspect still at large.
Male Caucasian,
armed and dangerous.
Hey,
I-I think this is a map.
It has to have been
of L.A.,
and there were
other pins in it.
If we could
find the publisher,
maybe we could match
the pinholes with locations?
Yeah. On it.
We got a whole department
of eggheads who love solving
these kinds of puzzles.
You got something?
There's no mattress
in there.
This guy was just sleeping
on a hard-ass floor.
Alright, so, what do you think
it means?
He's punishing himself.
Nothing soft, nothing warm,
no creature comforts.
Military man, maybe?
Used to sleeping on the ground?
Finds a bed too soft?
Or maybe too indulgent.
So, what's a better way
to stay focused on the mission
than to take away
every small pleasure?
Sure, that tracks.
What I can't
wrap my mind around
is the connection
to Area 51.
Why would they classify
his fingerprints?
You know, stories about aliens
at Area 51 were only a cover
that they were doing
covert operations there.
So, what are we saying?
Our suspect had ties
to classified U.S. operations?
Geez, what a nightmare
that would be.
Chen found something.
Uh, I figured he would write
on the map,
so I did a wall rubbing.
Uh, I found a word.
It's faint,
but I think it says "Enervo."
What does that mean? It's Latin.
It means "to deprive of power."
Yeah, I worked with a lot of CIA
guys in Afghanistan,
and Enervo is just the type
of pretentious code name
they'd give an op.
"Deprive of power"
is exactly
what he was doing
with the first bombing.
You think he'd go after
more relay stations?
No. In a ground war, what's
the military's first target?
Take out the enemy's
infrastructure.
Power, water...
Roads.
That's why he stole the
professor's book on traffic.
Quickest way to cripple this
city... take out the freeways.
Hello.
I'm Professor Meadows.
I'm so pleased you all agreed
to help me
with my little
research project
on traffic patterns
in Los Angeles.
Inside the envelope,
you'll find your first payment
and your precise driving route
for the day.
It's vital
that you follow the exact
directions in your envelope.
Otherwise, you won't get
your delivery payment.
Excellent.
Then get going.
And remember... drive safe.
Alright,
let's get going.
sync by
jhj@2022