Previously on "The Rookie"...
How serious are you about
becoming a training officer?
Sir, I don't wantto be a T.O.
I'm goingto be a T.O.
This is Sabrina Fowler,
the very talented new actress
on "Hot Suspect."
It's a pleasure.
You know, my character,
is having an affair
with a police sergeant.
And his wife likes to watch.
Lieutenant Landon Briggs.
- I'm the Union -
- President. - Yes, I know.
Nolan. You know what
the best part about
being union president is?
Power.
The power to help the people
I like
and hurt the people I don't.
Hey. What, uh...
What seems to be the problem?
Nothing.
Everyone's overreacting.
Overreacting to what?
Not it.
I'm sorry.
Um, I'm sorry.
I-I meant to get up early and...
and make you breakfast.
And I had this
whole Mother's Day thing
planned with Jack...
Jack's been up for three hours.
I have been up for three hours.
Is that cereal in your hair?
And applesauce.
And, somehow,
banana under my boob.
Mm.
Okay, so...
how can I fix this?
I need a shower.
Mm-hmm.
And a nap.
Uh...
But we have Mother's Day brunch
with your mom later.
Right.
Mm.
New plan.
Mm-hmm?
Shower, blow-out,
mani-pedi, and some mimosas
with Patrice.
Okay, so you're gonna take Jack
to the nail salon.
No.
You'retaking Jack.
Right. I just... I have
that thing with a client
for the restaurant, remember?
Which I'm gonna take Jack to.
I love you.
Happy Mother's Day.
Mm-hmm.
Nolan. Hold up.
I got some bad news.
I'm hearing rumors that
the Union President
is gonna make a move
against you.
Not a surprise,
given how I showed him up
at the City Council.
Any idea what he's planning?
Not yet, but I expect the worst.
There's no hard rule on
the union delegate count.
He can shrink the number by one.
And because I was the last one
in, I'd be the first one out.
What do I do?
You focus on your
T.O. exam next week.
Don't let politics
derail your career.
Oh, no, I've been studying
my ass off. I think I'm ready.
Don't think it.
Be it.
Clearly, you don't have
time to waste.
Are you calling me old?
It was implied.
Hey, you know, why don't
I ride with you today?
I can teach you some things that
are not in the study guide.
One-on-one time with
a supervisor will strengthen
your case for a promotion.
Sir, you don't have
to do that for me.
Nolan, do you
want to be a T.O.?
Absolutely.
Then don't do that small-town
"I hate to be a bother" thing.
You're being offered
an opportunity.
Take it.
Yes, sir.
And thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
And Luna's okay with
you working Mother's Day?
Yeah. It's the first year
Dominique's not at home.
Luna said she's fine
keeping it super low-key.
Oh.
What?
Do you think
she's just saying that?
No.
Mm...
yeah, that's a hard pass.
Look, I'm boycotting
Mother's Day,
but even if I wasn't,
I really don't think this is
the right time to meet
your parents.
I figured you'd say that.
But they've been
hounding me about
meeting you for weeks.
Are you really freezing
your mom out?
I mean, I bought her flowers.
I'm not an anarchist.
I'm thinking we just
lock in the Hyatt.
They have a lazy river.
What else do you need?
Great. You handle that,
I'll book the flights.
On it.
Are you guys planning
a vacation?
Yeah. Hawaii.
Oh, I love Hawaii.
Actually, I've never been,
but I love the idea.
You'd think I'd be sick of
beaches at this point,
but it's gonna be awesome.
I've got to get to work.
Oh, me, too.
I'll walk out with you.
Call me if you change your mind.
I'm not going to.
Stop.
Change your mind about what?
He wants me to meet his parents.
So, uh, whose idea was Hawaii?
Mine, I guess.
Why?
I-I thought you had today off.
I did, but Donovan
has custody this weekend,
and he is punishing me
by taking Lila to see
his mom in Santa Barbara.
So I am spending this
Mother's Day without my baby.
Wow.
That is cruel, even for him.
Yeah, I know.
And James is taking his boys
to see his ex-wife,
because unlike Donovan,
he is an actual
decent human being.
But at least I get paid
time and a half to be here
and plot my revenge.
I can't wait to see
what you come up with.
Somebody should sell tickets.
Mm!
Is it crazy I want to be
a T.O.
with so little time on the job?
No.
Your report writing
is excellent.
You know policy, procedure,
and the law well enough
to teach others.
But your background
could be a drawback.
Every other T.O. knows
what it's like to be a scared,
20-something rookie
because they were one.
And that shared experience
gives them the leg up
in teaching that kid.
Exactly.
But your experiences being a dad
could help bridge the gap.
Only my kid was never
armed and dangerous.
So, you really think
Luna's hoping
that I do something big
for Mother's Day this year?
I think it's always a safe bet
to go the extra mile.
You're right.
We should stop somewhere
so I can get a better gift.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
7-Adam-15.
415 in progress
at Gower Studios.
Right after we take this call.
Yes, sir.
7-Adam-15.
Show us responding.
I don't know how many times
I need to say it.
Please clean it up, okay?
I'm actually triggered by this,
you guys.
I don't think you understand.
They're here. See?
Oh, Sergeant.
Thank God you're here.
Ms. Fowler.
Sabrina Fowler.
She's an actress on
"Hot Suspect."
I'm pretty sure he knows that.
It's nice to meet you.
Congratulations on the baby.
Unless it's just for the show.
Oh, it's both.
They made my character pregnant,
so I got pregnant in real life.
Because she's a method actor.
How else am I gonna
understand the experience?
Wow.
So, what happened here, exactly?
We got a call about an assault?
That's right. The girl from
crafty assaulted me...
with a crouton.
She threw it at you?
No.
She put it in my salad.
Do you know how many carbs
are in a crouton?
Right. Um, well,
what was the name of your,
uh... attacker?
Mm, salad girl?
I don't...
No. Wait. I heard somebody
call her Monica
while she was
destroying everything.
So she made this mess.
That's right.
She completely freaked out
when I told her I was
gonna have her fired.
For putting a crouton
on your salad?
Are you taking her side?
Of course not.
Excuse me.
I have to take this.
The D.A.'s office.
Tell them I'm okay.
I am okay.
I will still make it to court
for the Sanchez trial.
I'm prosecuting
a serial killer later.
Oh. On the show.
Right.
But that was actually
the real...
You know what?
Never mind.
Is there anything else you can
tell me about the incident?
Like six people recorded it
on their phones.
We're trending on Cliptalk.
Right.
They're calling her a folk hero.
Can you believe it?
As if I'mthe bad guy.
We're needed elsewhere.
Ms. Fowler, I'm gonna have
a unit reach out
to studio security to get
your attacker's information.
I want the book thrown at her.
Of course.
And happy Mother's Day.
Oh, thank you.
Nice fake phone call.
It wasn't fake.
The D.A.'s office has
a witness to secure,
and they asked for an advanced
team to assess the site.
So I guess Luna's present will
have to wait a while longer?
Yeah, but don't let me forget.
Are you proposing to Ashley?
What?
Of course not.
We... We've only been
dating a few months.
Okay.
But if you take
a girl to Hawaii,
there's gonna be expectations.
You might not be aware of some
of the signals that you're sending.
What kind of signals?
The kind that makes her get
a manicure because
she's assuming she'll be
sending pictures of her hand
to all her friends.
7-Adam-100.
What's your status?
Uh, 7-Adam-100.
Show us Code 6 on our 415.
- They lost her keys.
- Where are my keys?
Sir, please.
You lost my Bentley.
No, sir, I just... I just don't
know where the keys are.
Okay, everyone, just calm down.
Back up a little bit, please.
Thank you.
What's going on? Jonah went crazy.
He punched that guy in the face,
and he emptied the key cabinet
and then stole a car.
Patrol, we need an R.A. at our
location for an assault victim.
Jonah is a valet?
Yeah, yeah.
He just started last week.
At first, he was amused
by all the rich guests.
You know how petty
and demanding they are.
No offense.
But when that dude told him to
move his ass, he snapped.
Knocked the guy out,
jumped into his Porsche,
and took off with
all the car keys.
And what color is the Porsche?
So all you did was reach
inside of an open car window
and take a bag of chips
from the passenger seat.
Yes.
I was super hungry,
and it was right there.
Are you allowed to bring
a baby in here?
Oh, he's my intern.
So, why is the District Attorney
adding these extra charges?
Burglary and vehicle tampering.
You're looking at the one
who didn'tgo to law school.
I have no idea.
The ADA in charge of your case
is Philip Harmon.
He's notorious for
up-charging defendants.
Is there anything
you can do about it?
Uh... not much.
He does it to force you
to take a plea deal
while he looks tough on crime.
That doesn't seem fair.
It's not.
I'll get right into this.
Hang tight.
Come on, buddy.
Thanks.
If you want, I could watch
the baby while you work.
Not sure how my wife would feel
about that, but thank you.
Come on, buddy.
No breakfast in bed, but Wesley
did get me this bracelet.
That's lovely.
It's no diamond tennis bracelet,
but I don't need him
to show me his love
with extravagant gifts.
Well, no one needs it,
but wouldn't it be nice?
Wesley's running even later.
Oh.
We should order.
It's probably for the best.
Rich-people stuff isn't
as fun when he's around.
No, he does tend
to dampen the mood.
How about you and I spend
the afternoon shopping?
I'll hire a driver,
and we'll do your
first Mother's Day right.
I love you.
Yes.
Cheers to that.
Cheers.
Good morning,
and happy Mother's Day.
Now, I hate to interrupt
your little manufactured
family gathering,
but this is a robbery.
Let's go. Everyone stay calm
and you won't get hurt.
Just put all your belongings
in the bag.
What are you gonna do?
Stay calm.
Do as they say.
We don't want to make
the situation worse.
Come on, cough it up, ladies.
Yeah.
That's beautiful.
Thank you.
Give me the pearls.
Please.
My late husband gave me...
I don't care.
Put it in the bag before
I rip it off your neck.
Patrice, we'll
get it back, okay?
You know, you really shouldn't
lie to your elders.
I'm not lying
when I tell her that.
Or when I tell you
you're under arrest.
You know, I love the confidence.
But, uh... we're the only ones
with guns here.
Oh, I don't mean now.
But soon enough, we'll be putting
a different kind of bracelet on you.
Thank you! Monica: Whoo!
I'll take that.
Thanks, everybody!
We love you!
Hey. You okay?
Yeah.
Did Wesley find you?
He's been frantic.
I know.
Patrice and I had to
scrape him off the ceiling.
I sent him and Jack away
so I could go to work.
Did you get an I.D.
on the stick-up team?
Yep. Jonah Cahill,
Monica Ditmar.
That's our valet.
He beat up a guest this morning
and stole a Porsche.
Oh, and that's the woman
that Nolan and Grey
put out a BOLO for.
She pitched a fit
at one of the stars
on "Hot Suspect" and then quit.
Which suggests the robbery was
a spur-of-the-moment thing.
Yeah. They might have
snapped after a bad morning
at work and decided
that crime paid better.
I'm assuming they
have criminal records?
Yeah. Minor offenses stretching
back into their teens.
They're both living at
a halfway house in Koreatown.
I got uniforms parked outside
in case they come back.
They stole your
Mother's Day's present?
I'm going to get it back.
Damn right you are.
And I am gonna help you.
Nobody messes with Mother's Day
and gets away with it.
Donovan took Lila out of town.
What?
Mm-hmm.
I knew he was an ass, but
I didn't think he was evil.
My abuela taught me the perfect
curse to put on him.
Ooh!
Does it involve boils?
No, but parts of him
will definitely fall off.
Ooh! Okay, we should leave before
we become accessories.Mm-hmm.
Those robbers
don't stand a chance.
Here we are.
The Royal Arms apartments.
D.A.'s office is gonna
secure their witness here
for a week while they get
a more permanent situation
put in place.
That must be tough
going into WITSEC.
I mean, I changed my whole
life to come out here,
but I didn't have to
cut ties with my family.
This poor guy's gonna
have to give up
everything he's ever known.
This "poor guy" is
a runner for a street gang.
He stood by and watched
people get murdered.
He's lucky his testimony
is valuable enough
to get him immunity.
So, what do we have to do
to get the site prepped
for witness protection?
First, the C.I. needs to be
given clear boundaries,
the landmarks that he cannot
cross, to keep him isolated.
Okay, how about Sixth Street
to the north,
that grocery store to the south?
That way, there's lots
of cameras and witnesses
in case anything happens.
That's perfect.
Let's go check out
this apartment.
Looks like nobody's been
here in a while.
Still have to clear it anyway.
Okay. Search for cameras
and listening devices.
Hold the button down,
wave it over anything
that may hide a bug.
Gotcha.
What was your FTO like?
He was one of those guys
who thought he could
motivate me with threats.
One night, he drove me
behind the grocery store,
took off his belt and vest,
and wanted to fight.
What did you do?
I put him in the hospital.
He tread a lot more carefully
after that.
I bet he did.
Check the bedroom.
There's four types of
training officers...
Kings, Coaches,
Teachers, and Slugs.
Well, I already know
the Slug one.
That one's just doing it
for the pay bump.
Kings are the
"my way or the highway" type.
Coaches offer motivation,
and Teachers always want to
explain everything.
Which of the categories
do I fit under?
None.
That's why you got the potential
to make a great T.O.
Take the best qualities of
all the leaders and trainers
who shaped who you are as a cop,
and you'll make
your own category.
Del Monte.
Site's secure.
So, you need us to hang around?
'Cause I got a Mother's Day
present to buy.
Oh, it's a little late
for that, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, actually, I would
appreciate you hanging out.
Uh, my guy is super twitchy.
Having you there play the heavy
will definitely help
him play by the rules, you know?
No problem.
Hey, Sean.
Got a minute?
Uh, yeah, one.
Cute kid.
Oh, hey, you're working
on Lopez's first Mother's Day.
Brave man.
Yeah, in my defense,
she's working, too.
She and my mom were robbed
at brunch.
Yeah, I heard about that.
Everybody okay?
Yeah. Thank God.
I should have been there,
but I was dealing with
yet another case of
prosecutorial overreach.
Well, if that's your way of
buttering me up for a favor,
you might want to rethink it.
Gemma Ramp stole
a bag of potato chips,
you guys are charging her
with a felony?
Oh, yeah, no, that's not mine.
That's Harmon's.
I know.
Hoping you'd talk to him.
Yeah, I mean, I can,
but it's not gonna matter.
That's just his way
of doing business.
Come on, Wes.
None of this is new.
I know.
It just seems like things
are only getting worse.
Look, you're not wrong.
But to be honest,
I'm surrounded by lawyers
who think that being
tough on crime
is gonna get them the top job.
Hell, I've been vetting candidates for
Kelly's open spot,
and each one is
more gung ho than the last.
I get it.
My client is steps away
from the street.
She needs a break,
not the book thrown at her.
I get it. I do.
I just... There's nothing
I can do about it.
My hands are tied.
I'm sorry.
I gotta run.
I already know
what you're gonna say.
My mother's just trying to do
what's best for me.
Oh, no.
Your mom sounds like
a real piece of work.
It's not your job
to make amends.
It's hers.
Thank you so much.
I...
Yeah.
Okay, when did hotels
get so expensive?
Hi.
Hi, Tim.
Oh, that's pretty good. Seriously?
Yeah. I mean,
it's a nice hotel.
If you want to do
better than that,
you're gonna have to take
Ashley to Honolulu Motel 6.
Oh, you're going to Hawaii.
Congratulations
on your engagement.
Ah! Told you.
I'm not getting engaged.
Does your girlfriend know that?
Yes.
It's not an issue.
Is he really this clueless?
Yes, trust me.
It is a daily struggle.
Let's go.
You've reached the cellphone of
Detective Angela Lopez.
Leave a message.
Any luck?
No.
I called half the phones
they stole, including mine.
Straight to voicemail.
I've got plainclothes
officers stationed
at all of the pawnshops
this side of the 405.
If they show up,
we will be waiting.
Tell them I want to be the one
who puts on the cuffs.
I made a promise.
I love it so much.
New phone, who dis?
Detective Lopez.
We met this morning.
It's the cop
from the restaurant.
What's up, Detective?
You, uh, calling to arrest us?
'Cause I don't think you can
do that over the phone.
No, I'm calling to tell you
to turn yourselves in.
You committed armed robbery.
Half the LAPD
is looking for you.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
See, we've got this whole
crime spree planned out.
Isn't that right, baby? That's right.
Listen, I know you two
have gone through a lot.
Please. If you think reading
a file gives you any idea
who we are,
you are a terrible cop.
Trust me, I've read enough
files to understand
that you and Jonah never
caught a single break.
Yet, when you got out of prison,
you tried to go straight,
even got yourselves real jobs.
Yeah. And you know what?
We were still treated like scum.
Not even worth
an ounce of respect.
Angela, they are live-streaming
your conversation.
You can save
the false empathy, Detective.
Today is for every worker
who's ever been mistreated...
Mm.
...for anyone who's ever
wanted to walk off the job.
Yeah, for anybody that
believed the lie
that if you just tried
to work harder,
you could achieve your dreams.
We are done begging for scraps.
Today, we are taking
what's ours.
Let's take it all, baby.
We are taking it.
Let's take it all.
I love you.
Man, I don't like this place.
It's claustrophobic.
Mr. Tran...
Is it just me,
or is it dusty up in here?
I feel like I can't breathe.
Daniel, sit down.
If you want to stay alive,
you need to listen to what
Mr. Del Monte
has to say.
Thank you.
As an informant
in our protection program,
there are a number of rules
that you will follow.
You will not disclose
this location to anybody.
Do you understand?
Good.
This is your new phone.
Do not share this number
with anybody.
Officer Nolan and Sergeant Grey
have established
a strict perimeter in the area.
This is a boundary
that you will not cross
under any circumstances.
Is that clear?
But I can visit my mom, right?
No. Daniel...
you are not to contact
any friends or family, period.
But it's Mother's Day.
We're going
horseback riding later.
Son, you're clearly
not understanding
the severity of the situation.
You will not contact anyone,
family included.
But I have to.
I can't let her down again.
Look, this is for
her safety, too.
Okay, if you really want
to see your mom,
I'm sure we can arrange to
have you both meet
in a secure location.
You can say your goodbyes.
Goodbyes? No.
Daniel, this is
your reality now.
I know it's not pretty,
but it's the only way we can
keep you alive.
Alright, thanks, guys.
We'll take it from here.
Appreciate it.
Present time?
Yeah.
Only I have absolutely
no idea what to get her.
Well, lucky enough,
we got four hours
to figure something out.
I got an update
on Monica and Jonah.
They just robbed a bridal store.
That's an odd choice.
They assaulted the owner
and held her at gunpoint
while Monica tried on dresses.
Oh, well, I guess you won't
be the only one getting married.
What?
Nothing. Ignore her.
We need to catch these two
before they kill somebody.
Well, given the fact that they
made off with a dress and tux,
odds are they're
about to get hitched.
Alright.
We'll alert the local venues
and check out
the obvious locations.
Okay, I'm starting to
panic a little.
Luna and I have been
married 25 years.
At this point, I've given her
every kind of present there is.
So how do I make
this one special?
Well, maybe don't
make it about the present.
Make it about the evening.
What's her favorite restaurant?
Do you think I can
get a reservation
anywhere at this point?
Ooh.
No, not a chance in hell.
Sean, what's up?
No, we're on it.
Daniel Tran took off.
That was fast.
Yeah.
Lucky for us, we know
exactly where he's heading.
Oh! According to this
travel website,
Siberia is the least romantic
place to vacation.
I am not rerouting our trip
to the arctic tundra
because you think Hawaii
sends the wrong message.
No, it is not just me, okay?
TouristPlanet says that
Hawaii is number one
for proposals in 2021.
Ashley can't possibly
think I'm proposing.
Why not?
I mean, you're of
a... certain age.
She's in her prime.
I mean, on paper, it's...
it's like a no-brainer.
Okay, be honest.
Can you see yourself
married to her?
Yeah.
I can.
7-Adam-100.
I have a 415 unknown in progress
at Church of the Chimes.
That's gotta be Jonah
and Monica.
Show us responding.
Send backup, metro,
and alert Detective Lopez.
Hey, hey!
Hey, everyone. Be cool.
You can get back to your wedding
in a few minutes.
We wrote our own vows,
so if anybody ruins them,
they catch a bullet, understand?
H-Hey, hey, hey. And you...
And if you screw up this video,
it'll mean a world
of pain, alright?
Baby, you are
the love of my life.
Before I met you,
I hated the world.
But now...
Now we can hate the world
together forever.
Jonah... you're
my ride or die,
the only person who
has ever really seen me.
No matter what happens next,
you've made me
the happiest girl...
Jonah!
Jonah, we gotta go.
Hey, are we officially married?
Yes!
Ah!
7-Adam-100.
Shots fired at our location.
Pursuing armed suspects on foot.
We need backup at all exits.
Go, go.
Go to the back.
Go. Exit.
Move, move.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
You gotta leave me.
No.
If you leave right now,
you could save yourself.
No.
You could just...
just break me out of jail.
It'll be epic.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Drop the gun.
Show me your hands.
Run!
Suspect Monica Ditmar's
on the loose.
She is armed and dangerous,
wearing a wedding dress
and combat boots.
You go north.
What's the damage?
GSW through-and-through
to the upper back.
They're prepping
the E.R. now.
You should have
turned yourselves in.
I am unrepentant.
I'll be sure to let
the judge know that.
The question is,
are you going to help me
save Monica's life?
Let me guess.
You want me to
tell her to give up?
You're damn right I do.
You think what you're
doing is noble?
You think this has
a happy ending?
Grow up.
You shot at cops.
A thousand police officers
are hunting for your wife
as we speak,
and when they catch her
and she tries to shoot her way
to freedom,
she's not gonna survive.
So you're gonna record a message
telling her to surrender.
Or wake up from surgery to
the news that you're a widower.
Forget it.
Our entire lives,
we've been ordered around.
I'm not just gonna be another
person telling her what to do.
The O.R.'s ready.
Go ahead.
I'm done with him.
Let's move.
I can't tell you how much
your advice means to me.
Thank you.
Of course, Quigley.
And, remember, whenever
you're feeling low,
just tell yourself
those three words.
I'm worth it.
Can I call you "mom"?
I think it's better
if you didn't.
Okay. Thanks again.
I'm worth it.
Okay.
Ready to go?
Yes. Thank you.
You've had quite
a day, haven't you?
Are you gonna be a lawyer
like your daddy, huh?
Jackson, are you gonna help
the less fortunate?
Mm. Not sure how much
I'm helping these days.
Why? What happened?
I'm just tired of
the uphill battle.
Prosecutors have all the power.
Well, if you can't beat them...
Join them?
No. Unh-unh.
Why not?
Are you telling me
that you wouldn't make
a bigger impact
if you had that power?
If Daniel told us about
his Mother's Day plans,
how many others did he tell?
It only takes one
to give him up to his gang.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
You're lucky I'm not putting
you in cuffs right now.
I know. I'm sorry.
Go say goodbye to your mother.
We need to get you back
to the apartment.
Come on. Can't I just spend
the rest of the day with my mom?
No!
You're an informant
in a gang murder trial.
There are people trying
to kill you.
By being here, you're putting
you and your mother in danger.
You're right.
I'll go with you.
But, please, you can't
tell her why you're here.
Excuse me?
My mom doesn't know...
about the gang,
about witness protection,
any of it.
Okay, she's going to find out.
I know, but I just don't
want to ruin her day.
Please.
Fine, fine.
Hi.
What's going on?
Don't worry, Mom.
This is just about, uh... my car.
It got stolen.
Oh, no, Daniel.
That's terrible.
You just bought it. I know.
But I didn't want to
worry you today.
You know who did it?
Uh... yes, ma'am.
That's why we need your son
to come with us...
so he can view the lineup.
I didn't know you
really did that.
Oh, yeah, all the time.
Vital part of police work.
Okay, charade's over.
What's going on?
Who are they?
They're here to kill your son.
What? We need to find cover.
Take mom, watch your backstop.
Daniel. Make sure the horses
don't get hit in the cross fire.
Thank you for the assist.
You're welcome.
On your knees.
Where's Daniel?
He took off.
Sarge, I think we got one more
guy to worry about.
I'll stay with the suspect.
You go find Daniel.
Yes, sir. I'm going with you.
Uh, Mrs. Tran, thank you.
I-I-I've got this.
He got it. He got it.
I know you came in here, Daniel.
The longer you make me
hunt for you...
...the more times
I'm gonna shoot you.
It's a shame. I thought you were
a stand-up guy.
But you flipped the second
you felt the handcuffs go on.
Give me your hands.
Come on.
Get up.
Daniel, it's safe to come out.
Come on.
Hey, hon.
Yeah, I'm on duty
at the hospital.
Come on, baby.
We gotta go.
Don't move.
W-Where's Jonah?
He's in the ICU.
They think he'll pull through.
Now get your hands up.
I promised I'd put
some bracelets on you,
and I keep my promises.
But, first, this is mine.
Turn around.
Come on.
That was a crazy day.Mm.
I can't believe Daniel's mom
is going into
witness protection with him.
She loves him, and he clearly
still needs her.
Thank you for
the one-on-one time today.
I really did learn a lot.
You're welcome.
And for what it's worth,
I think you're a really good
candidate for FTO.
And I'll tell them that
after you pass your exam.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Ooh!
You still didn't get
anything for Luna.
Actually, I did.
You just didn't notice.
Which means it's a good thing
you're not trying
to be a detective.
Well, what'd you get her?
It is time to go home.
I have Indian food on the way.
Where's Jack?
Uh, my mom took him
to Fred Segal.
She's gonna meet us at home.
That kid has a better
wardrobe than I do.
I'm thinking of changing jobs.
To what?
There's an open spot
in the D.A.'s office.
I am literally without words.
You call them the enemy
like four times a week.
I know.
Because they are.
And I love advocating for people
that are caught in the system,
but I lose more battles
than I win.
Do you think the D.A. can
look past your suspension?
Considering I helped
put away a major drug lord
in the process, I think so.
If there is even
a 10% chance that I can
change the system from within,
I have to do it.
Don't I?
I can't answer that for you.
But we can talk about it
over Indian food.
Deal.
Thank you.
I love you. I love you, too.
Hey, I'm about to head out.
You good?
Uh, yeah.
I'm just finishing up.
I'm... I'm right behind you.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Mommy!
Hi, baby girl.
What are you doing here?
Nana brought me.
Maris, w-w-what's going on?
Is Donovan okay?
Oh, he's fine.
Except for this really weird
rash that just showed up.
That and the fact that I clearly
didn't raise him right.
Keeping a mother from
her child on Mother's Day?
I mean, what is wrong with him?
Thank you.
You don't know how much
that means to me.
Yeah, I do.
Listen, I-I know
I haven't done a good job
of keeping in touch.
No, t-that is not a problem.
I know this whole thing
is complicated.
Yeah, maybe so,
but it doesn't matter
what happened between
you and Donovan.
You will always be
the daughter I never had.
Hi.
Hi!
Good day?
Yeah, it was okay.
Lucy was particularly
annoying, but...
I don't believe
that for a second.
Hey, I know we said Hyatt,
but I just found
this super-cute Sharebnb
in Ko Olina.
Cozier, right?
Just the two of us?
That's romantic.
Is... Is that, uh...
Is that a new nail color?
Yeah.
I just had them done.
Oh.
They're... They're pretty.
Yeah?
Uh, I'm sorry.
Ashley, look.
I-I need to...
I need to clear the air
about something here.
The reason Lucy was
so annoying today
is that she is convinced
that you think
I'm taking you
to Hawaii to propose.
But, I mean, you don't...
you don't think that, right?
'C-Cause I'm not.
I mean, I-I think we are
magic together, but I...
Shh!
It's okay.
I am not expecting a proposal.
Okay.
I would say "no" if you asked.
Uh, don't get me wrong.
I think we're magic, too.
But I just have
no interest in ever
being married or having kids.
I'm just not wired that way.
Oh.
Okay.
Uh, great.
It's a vacation.
Look, we're gonna have
a great time.
Yes, we will.
Will you do me a favor?
Hey.
Oh, hi.
So, it's a good thing you
didn't come to meet my mom,
because she drove me
absolutely crazy.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I...
Could you just wait here?
I need to go find Lopez
and figure out
how to put a curse on someone.
Yeah, right.
Oh, you're serious.
Where are you taking me?
Still a surprise.
Alright.
My lady.
I didn't cheat.
I'm not peeking.
Yeah, okay. Alright. I'm here. I'm ready.
I believe you.
Oh, honey.
I know it's been hard
not having Dominique here.
First Mother's Day without her.
So I wanted to do something
special for you.
Oh, really?
'Cause I thought those flowers
you sent earlier
was just gonna be it.
That was all
an elaborate ruse, my dear.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Ready. You ready?
I'm ready, I'm ready, yes.
You ready?
Yes.
Alright, here we go.
And voil.
You bought me a horse.
No.
Riding lessons.
Oh!
Plus, a romantic
Mother's Day night ride
around the property with me.
Sound good?
Yes.
I love it.
Oh, thank you.
Alright, go.
Go play. Go.
Hi.
I'm gonna get you to
buy her for me.
Hey!
What a surprise.
Come in.
Let me get you a drink.
So... how was
horseback riding?
Beautiful.
Wade said that you
helped him find it.
Something like that.
But you guys didn't
come all this way
just to thank me for that.
No.
I just received a formal request
to temporarily assign you
to another station.
My first day in the hole.
Cool.
Not cool?
No. This request
is for the whole week.
That means I'll miss
my T.O. exam.
Exactly.
And before you start
plotting how to sneak back
and take it on your lunch hour,
the station you're going to
is four hours away,
on the border.
This is my punishment
for pissing off
the Union President.
He knows I want
to be a T.O.
Yeah.
Isn't there anything you can do?
I would if I could,
but my hands are tied.
If you try to
reject the assignment,
they will consider it
disobeying a direct order.
So even if you pass the test,
they wouldn't make you a T.O.
if you're facing
disciplinary action.
Well, then you are just gonna
have to take the next test.
When is it?
In two years.