[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Dog barking in distance ]
Control, 7-Adam-15.
We have a structure fire
at 8650 Magnolia.
Please notify LAFD.
You think
anyone's in there?
Well, no one
that's supposed to be.
- Man: Help!
- Was that a scream?
♪
Control, what's the ETA
on LAFD?
Dispatch: Two minutes.
That's -- That's
too long.
Control, be advised,
we're going in
to look for victims.
♪ Pull me into
your coloring books ♪Ready?
♪ Lead me into
your bright adventures ♪
♪
♪ Kiss me under the mistletoe [ Glass shattering ]
♪ Open-mouth
on my brand-new dentures ♪
[ Debris crashing ]
♪
Geez.
Man: Help me![ Coughs ]
♪ Who met in the future
and moved to the past ♪
Man: Help!
Someone help me!
[ Coughing ]♪ All big men
have a gravity ♪
♪ That draws them
to the sun ♪
♪ And gives them
their authority ♪
their control ♪[ Groans ]
Whoa, man.
♪ Gravity that draws them
to the sun ♪[ Groans ]
[ All coughing, panting ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Glass shattering ]
[ All coughing ]
♪
[ Coughing ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
Is there
anyone else inside?
- Not that we saw.
- You shouldn't have
gone in.
Well, it's kind of
our job, saving people.
From crime.
You don't see us
running towards gunfire.
You think that's just wood smoke
you're breathing in?
All the toxic things in a home,
once they catch fire,
they turn to deadly gases --
ammonia, carbon dioxide,
hydrogen cyanide.
So unless you want me
dragging your ass to safety
in the future,
you'll leave the rescues
to the professionals.
[ Sighs ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
How's it going
- with you two?
- Really good.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh Really good.
♪ Oh, oh, whoa, oh, oh
♪ I'm gonna win for you
♪ Like I know
you want me to do ♪[ Sniffs ]
How is it that
I still smell like smoke
after a 30-minute shower?
Welcome to my world.
You always smell
fantastic.
That's because I spend
half my salary on perfumes,
potions, and detergents.
Well, it's working.[ Chuckles ]
Do you think
that fire was arson?
Maybe.
I smelled accelerant.
The arson investigator
will know for sure.
You ever think
about doing that?
Arson investigation?
Yeah.
No.
I like the physical part
of firefighting.
Plus, I wouldn't have time
for all my extracurriculars --
Army Reserve, teaching,
motorcycle racing...
Dating me.
Dating you.
"Motorcycle racing"?[ Cellphone vibrates, chimes ]
What is it?
[ Gasps ]
They found a body.
[ Sirens wailing,
radio chatter ]
- Karl.
- Hey, Bailey.
This is John Nolan,
LAPD.
Hey.
He and his partner
pulled the survivor out
before we got here.
Ah.
Did you give him the lecture
about how stupid it is
to go into a structure fire
without a mask?
It was given --
and understood.
Any, uh, luck
ID'ing the victim yet?
Nah, it's too soon.
There were fifth-
and sixth-degree burns.
But from the size,
I'd say it was a man.
And you might want to start
referring to him
as a suspect
instead of the victim.
You think our DB
started the fire?
That's what
the evidence suggests.
He was right
where it started,
and an accelerant
was definitely used.
No way it could've been
just an addict
falling asleep
next to a lit candle?
No, no, no, no, that fire
got too hot, too fast.
So, what are you thinking?
That the guy
we pulled out of there
might be able
to give us some insight.
Wesley: [ Sighs ]
So, how's the book?
Terrible, but who cares?
It's my third
maternity-leave book.
I've been lucky to average
one a year up till now.[ Baby coos ]
Maybe I should
extend my leave,
spend a little more time
with Jack.
I think
that's a great idea.
Because you don't want me
to go back to work?
Because you want me to quit
being a detective
and focus on
what really matters?
Uh --
Because you think I won't
fulfill my mom potential
if I'm at crime scenes
all day?
Wow.
Where did that
come from?
I don't know.
Clearly, I'm a little conflicted
about going back to work.
I want you to do
whatever makes you happy.
But I do think
that it's time
to leave the baby home
for a night and go on a date.
Who'll watch Jack?
[ Stammers ]
Your mom, my mom,
or some teenager
we pull off the street?
Who cares?
We deserve
some alone time.
- And some fine dining?
- Hell, yes.
- The fancier, the better.
- I'm in.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
♪
Client. Um, I have
a meeting I forgot about.
I'll make, uh, reservations
for 7:00, okay?
Hey.
I love you.
I love you, too.
♪
Hey, how's it going
with Harper?
I mean, I'm still here,
so...good, I guess.
She was my training officer.
You're in great hands.
Look, I'm just trying to do
whatever I can to keep her
from giving me that look.
Oh, the Triple D?
Yeah, I know it well.
Disappointment,
disbelief, and disdain.
I think she developed it
in a lab somewhere
to destroy self-confidence.
Yeah, my mom has
a version of it.
You think I'd be immune given
how often she's used it on me
over the years.
Yeah, well, Harper uses it
on the daily --
I'm still not used to it.
Hang in there.
So, I also need you
to cover C Division today.
Anything else you need?
Paint your house
or clean your car?
[ Chuckles ]
I got two roving sergeants
for six divisions.
Welcome to
your new reality.
That's why you should take on
a sergeant's aide.
[ Scoffs ]
I don't need an aide.
It's not a sign
of weakness.
It's a necessity given
how under-resourced we are.
Yeah, I guess I could use
a go-fer.
Someone to go-fer coffee
or supplies.
Call it whatever you want.
Just pull an officer out
at roll call.
[ Locker door closes ]
Hell, pull Chen.
You two
work together good.
Tim is going to ask you
to be his go-fer.
What? His -- His what?
His aide.
He's stretched a little thin.
Grey suggested
he take you on to assist.
Me specifically?
Yeah.
Uh, is there a problem?
No, ma'am.
I'm just excited to hear
what new nicknames
you came up with for me.
Hm. Uh, I've --
I've narrowed it down
to three.
Um, "Get out
of my face"...
Mm-hmm.
..."sit your ass down"...Okay.
...and "I will tell you
when I am ready."
- I love them all.
- Okay.
Triple D.
What was that?
Nothing.
Just sitting my ass down.
Sgt. Grey: So, all right,
settle down, everyone.
Sergeant Bradford,
you want to start us off?
Yes. Um...
I'm in need of a go-fer.
Now, it won't be glamorous,
but it'll be
a learning experience.
♪
Webb, how about it?
You ready
to get off patrol?
Yes, sir.
Looking forward to it.
You said --
I thought --
Officer Nolan,
so I saw your request
to follow up on the man
you pulled out
- of the fire yesterday.
- Yes, sir.
I checked with the hospital.
He regained consciousness.
Thought it would be important
to get his statement
while his memory was fresh.
I agree.
I'll notify Caradine
for when he assigns
a detective.
Harper:
You're driving today.
Hey, you know
I almost qualified to race
in the British
Grand Prix, right?
I mean,
before my troubles.
And you've never
known real fear
until you've gone airborne
in a Formula 1 car.
Yeah, try being hunted
by a pack of cartel sicarios,
then get back to me.
Okay, that's a story
I want to hear.
Alonzo: Nyla.
Harper: Hi.
[ Chuckles ]
What are you
doing here?
Just stopped by
to ask you to lunch.
It's 9:00 A.M.
Oh, right. Sorry.
When your kid gets up
before the sun,
you lose track of time.
[ Inhales deeply ]
Uh, plus, I was wondering, um,
if you could take care
of this ticket for me.
Unh-unh. No.
Put it away. I can't.
I'm gonna go
- set up the shop.
- Mm-hmm.
Sorry. I knew
I shouldn't have asked.
Yeah, you also shouldn't have
been going 60 in a 30.
What were you thinking?
That my ex was gonna
tear me a new one
if I was late
for my pickup again.
That's no excuse.
Can I take you
to dinner this week?
I'd love that.
I would too.
[ Chuckles ]
Is that your boyfriend?
No, I'm just curious
to know, um,
if I gave off any signals
that would make you
comfortable enough... Uh-huh.
...to ask me
a personal question.
No, the -- um,
there were none.
Mm.
There were
no signals given.
Um, that's what some people
like to call "my bad."
Mm-hmm. Get your ass
in the shop, Boot.
Okay.
Why would you tell me that
Tim was going to pick me
when he didn't?
- Because Grey told him to.
- Then why didn't he?
I don't know, but clearly,
it bothers you.
No, I just --
It would make
a good career opportunity.
As a roving supervisor,
Tim responds to all
the high-profile cases.
And being
right there with him
would make me stand out
when promotion time comes.
So tell him
you want the gig.
Oh, he would
just love that --
being in a position
to decide my fate again.
No...he'll come around.
I just have
to give it time.
Because the one thing
I know for sure
is that Tim is definitely
missing me right now.
I can't believe
the ump made that call --
and in the bottom
of the ninth!
It was clearly foul.
B-- I know --
by like three feet!
What's the point
of instant replay
if you're not gonna
get it right?
Hey, man, you're preaching
to the choir.
Hey, you know
I get season tickets
to the Dodgers
and the Angels,
so if you ever want
to hit up a game,
just let me know.
- I'll hook you up.
- Oh. [ Chuckles ]
Don't say that
if you don't mean it,
'cause I will call.
Hey, that's the least
a go-fer could do.
"Aide."
My man.
- Hi, there.
- Lewis: Hi.
Mr. Hall,
do you remember us?
We pulled you out
of the fire yesterday.
What were you doing
in the house?
Oh, well, uh,
I-I've been squatting there.
Yeah, it's a lot safer
than being on the streets.
Oh, of course.
How long have you been there?
Since I returned.
From...?
Kremulus.
And Kremulus is...?
Oh, it's the planet right next
to Proxima Centauri,
but no one really
knows about it,
so please just keep it
to yourself.
Oh, I-I-I think you can
count on us.
Mm-hmm.
Now, w-were you there alone?
Did anybody come back
with you?
No.
No, those who walk
a celestial path
are destined for solitude.
But I did hear
some voices yesterday.
[ Softly ]
Okay, how do I put this?
Were the voices...
inside your head,
or were they --
- I-I-In the house.
- Ah.
Two guys.
I-I heard them come in
through the back.
I hid so that
they wouldn't see me.
And maybe...
half an hour later,
that's when
the fire started.
Did you hear
what the voices were saying?
Would you recognize them
if you heard them again?
No, they were
pretty muffled.
And you're sure it wasn't
just one man?
Yes...
because one of them
was yelling...
...and the other
was crying.
Mr. Stone insisted
on waiting in your office.
Of course he did.
He's got a couple
shooters with him.
Serious-looking dudes.
Feels like
a "car theft" situation.
That's a good idea.
All right,
give me two minutes.
[ Sighs ]
Hmm.
Hey.
Counselor.
Punctuality is a quality
I expect from all my employees.
Well, having a newborn
kind of throws punctuality
out the window.
Need I remind you why
you still have a son to dote on?
No, I'm aware
of what I owe you.
And yet, you spent
the last month
on paternity leave,
avoiding paying me back,
which makes me think
you're trying to go back
on our deal.
No, not at all.
I just think that
I'm best used
in an un-muddied capacity.
I have been meaning
to speak to you.
I have a sterling reputation
with law enforcement,
but that only benefits you
if I can continue --
Shut up.
You seem confused about
the dynamics at play here.
You work for me now,
which means what I say goes --
So sorry to interrupt,
but someone just tried
to steal my car from out front.
The police will be here
in a minute.
Is that so?
♪
You know, the only thing
worse than stealing...
in my book...
is lying.
[ Chuckles ]
And yet, you lie
and steal for a living.
What can I say?
I'm a walking contradiction.
♪
Just think about
what we just spoke on.
It'd be better
for everybody
if I didn't have
to say it again.
♪
Harper: Where are we
right now, Boot?
Uh, San Vicente and --
If you have to look,
you don't know,
and trouble is not gonna wait
for you to find a street sign.
Got it. Sorry.
I will do better.[ Radio chatter ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
You mind
if I take this?
Whatever you think
is best.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Go for Aaron.
Quinn: Hey, Aaron,
it's Quinn from "TMZ."
I really need
to talk to you.
Disguising your number.
Smart.
Look, man, I told you
I'm not interested.[ Monitor beeps ]
An alert just came in.
You should check the box.
I've been calling you
all week, man.
I can never reach you.
"Hollywood Division
is running a 246."
Look, hear me out
before you say no, okay?
"Drive-by shooting
into a..." I've got a really sweet
deal for you.
I've got my editor
to up the price to 100 grand.
Hey, look, man, I told you
I'm not interested, okay?
Don't call me again.
Uh, did you see the guy
in the trench coat?
He might be
concealing a weapon.
Dispatch: 7-Adam-19,
clear for traffic?
I didn't see a guy
in a trench coat.
- Should I turn around?
- Do you think you should
turn around?
I mean, did you see
a weapon?
Did I say I saw one?
7-Adam-19?
Security check.
What was the drive-by shooting
vehicle Hollywood was working?
I-I didn't s--It came over the radio.
Right. Um, I was --
I was looking for that guy
possibly concealing a weapon,
but I will find him.
Suspect's vehicle is a...
All units,
unable to raise 7-Adam-19.
Last location near Stoner Park.
7-Adam-100,
copy missing officer?
Oh, my God.
An officer's missing?
Two.
Two officers are missing.
Okay, that's even worse!
Should we look for them,
or should we find
this trench-coat guy?
Tim: 7-Adam-100,
I copy the missing officer.
Harper, it's Bradford.
You guys Code 4?
Code 4.
What's our call sign?
7-Adam-19.
Ohhhh.
- We're the missing officers.
- Mm.
[ Clicks tongue ]
That is embarrassing.
Yes, it is -- for you.
I get a free pass
your first week.
All of your many failures
are blamed on the Academy.
So, what have you learned?
That taking the wheel
is demanding enough...
Mm-hmm.
...and I shouldn't be
adding in
personal phone calls
into the mix.
Mm.
There wasn't an armed man
in a trench coat, was there?
Mm, mnh-mnh.
Hello! Didn't I see you guys
on a milk carton?
I don't get it.
'Cause we were
considered missing.
They used to put pictures of
missing kids on milk cartons.
- Yes, in the '80s.
How did I end up
the punch line?[ Laughs ]
- Oh, excuse me.
- Uh, yeah.
Harper: Hey, how come
Bradford didn't choose Lucy
to be his go-fer?
I don't know,
but she's not being
very adult about it.
Oh.
So, how is it
riding with Tim?
Oh, it's been great.
You know, everyone
always talks about
how tough
the Sarge can be,
but we've been
having the best time.
Really?
That's...awesome.
So, you know, when I was
riding with him,
I learned some foolproof ways
to stay on his good side.
You know, if you -- if --
if you want some tips.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Appreciate that.[ Gunfire ]
[ Car horn honks,
tires squealing ]
- Man: Look out!
- Woman: [ Screams ] Hey!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Tires screech ]
Harper:
Let me see your hands!
Show me your hands!
- Guns down!
- Get out of the car!
Harper: Get out of the car!
Let me see your hands!
- Put your guns down!
- Kip: Private security!
We got CCW permits!
Someone just shot our client
through the windshield!
Nolan:
Front seat clear!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
Man: Is everybody okay?!
Sarge?
Tim: Yeah?
I think we got a sniper.
What do you see?
Three shots grouped tight
high on the windshield.
Judging from where the car was,
I'd say our sniper is northeast.
Control, 7-Adam-100.
We got a shooter
with a long gun
at the 16000 block
of Rochester Avenue.
I need eastbound traffic
from Veteran shut down.
Get SWAT en route.
Harper, Thorsen,
secure the scene.
Nolan, Chen, Webb,
you're on me.
- Clear the street!
- Move, move!
Active shooter!
There's a shooter! Move, move!
Get inside! Go!
There's a shooter!
- Get off the street!
- Come on, move!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
♪ Looked the devil in the eye Hey!
Stop right there!
♪ Taking risks is my design
♪ Y'all was born
without a spine ♪
♪ Wicked and twisted
♪ Bars are sicker
than syphilis ♪
♪ Spit and you listen
♪ Only way to stop,
I don't breathe again ♪
♪ You wanna come around [ Gunshots ]
♪ Yeah, see me then
♪
7-Adam-15!
Taking shots inside
16000 Rochester.
Parking garage.
We're going up.
Requesting more units
to cover the exits.
♪
♪ Go for broke
while you go for blows ♪
♪ Jumping on the noose Tim: Get your hands up!
♪
♪ You wanna come around,
yeah, see me then ♪
♪
♪ You wanna come around,
yeah, see me then ♪
♪
[ Sighs ]
I gotta admit, I'm disappointed
you didn't go after him.
Oh, I was halfway
out the window.
Lucy had to pull me back.
Mm-hmm.
Tim: This guy's
a pro, Sarge.
Put three bullets
through tempered glass
into a moving vehicle and still
dead-centering his target --
only a couple dozen people
in the world who could do that.
The secondary escape route
screams elite training.
Someone paid real money
for this guy's services.
You got a name
- on the target?
- Michael Silver.
Some kind of
import-export guy.
Hired a security company
a week ago.
Didn't tell them why --
or, at least,
they're not sharing with us.
Intelligence unit
is running Silver's name
to see if he's in
their database.
Well, clearly, he pissed off
some bad people.
Okay, we got an ID
on our arson victim.
Nelson Crespo.
He's a 35-year-old
restaurant manager,
a couple of
minor drug arrests,
and he has an apartment
in Culver City
with his wife, Celia.
Sir, we could handle
the death notification.
See if Celia might
shed some light
on what our DB was doing
in that house.
All right, go ahead.
I'll have Harper and Thorsen
work the sniper with Bradford.
James: Nyla. Hey.
James.
[ Laughter ]
What are you
doing here?
Oh, just picking up
a few things
for the community center.
I'd ask the same of you,
but I have a good guess.
Yeah, I came for the coffee,
stayed for the sniper.
Uh, this is my new rookie,
Officer Aaron --
Thorsen.
Yeah, I-I remember
your case.
Man, I-I'm so sorry for
everything you went through.
- Thanks.
- I happen to work with
a lot of people who've been
wrongfully incarcerated.
It can help to talk
to a therapist.
I have some names
if you need 'em.
I appreciate that,
but I already go twice a week.
Good, good.
Well, you are very lucky
to have this impressive woman
as your training officer.
Don't let her bite
scare you.
She got a lot of heart.
Uh, now, why would you
go and tell him that?
Just to make your job
that much harder.
Huh.
Uh, we are going out
again soon, right?
You know it.
All right, okay.
Take care of yourself.
[ Chuckles ]
What?
Nothing.
Good.
Triple D's got game.
You n--
[ Clears throat ]
It doesn't make sense.
Nelson went for a jog
to the beach.
What was he doing
near Griffith Park?
H-How'd he even get there?
There's evidence that
the house he was found in
is a place people go
to use drugs.
No.
Nelson was clean --
four years.
Addicts relapse, uh, and --
and they lie about it.
I know. I am one.
If my husband
was using again,
I would've seen the signs.
Something happened
to him.
Promise me you won't
just play "blame the addict."
I promise you -- we will
follow this case where it leads.
If you can think
of anything else,
please call us --
day or night.
And, again, I am truly sorry
for your loss.
[ Breathing shakily ]
You think
she's in denial?
Maybe.
Sure would be nice
to get some clarity.
Well, hopefully,
the autopsy will give us that.
All right,
thanks for checking.
[ Radio chatter ]
Intelligence's saying
that Michael Silver
isn't on their radar.
How's that possible?
No way a guy
who gets popped
by an elite sniper
is squeaky clean.
He's gotta have some
- criminal connection.
- I'm gonna call Records.
Maybe they have some
information, some --
No, it's -- it's
a waste of time.
I'll call LA CLEAR when
we get back to the station.
Right.[ Radio chatter ]
[ Exhales slowly ]
Weird case, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I'm good with weird.
I'm a Manx.
I'm sorry.
You're -- You're a what?
A Manx.
A Manx cat.
That's my feline breed.
My cat personality.
What's your cat
personality, Sarge?
Did Chen put you
up to this?
Put me up to what?
♪
Whoa.[ Saw whirring ]
Oh, what, the smell?
Yeah, it smells like
month-old eggs
and maggot meat.
I mean, you don't --
you don't have to go in,
but this is part
of the job.
No, I'm good.
[ Clears throat ]
Mm.
- Can I just have a sec?
- Oh, yeah, no.
Gather yourself,
because what awaits
smells like a septic tank
filled with tumors.
[ Sniffs ] Okay...
I see what you're doing.
This is payback for me trying
to get too familiar earlier,
but you know what?
It's all good.
I can handle it.
I'm just gonna have
to cancel my reservation
at Eliza and Elektra
tonight,
because there's no way
I'm eating after this.
Whoa, are you crazy?
You have to book that place
like six months in advance.
I dream of eating there.
You want the reservation?
Seriously?
Yeah, it's yours --
if you stop torturing me?
Deal.
Yeah.
I mean,
the only question is,
which boy toy
are you taking?
Is it gonna be
the speed demon
from this morning,
or the upright citizen
from this afternoon?
I mean, unless
there's a third choice.
No, it's James.
It's definitely James.
But he's probably busy.
Well, text him
and find out.
[ Stammers ]
[ Sighs ]
All right, fine.
[ Cellphone buttons tapping ]
[ Cellphone chimes ]
Oh, no.
The vanishing three dots.
That is the worst.
He's probably gonna
respond later.
You kn-- Let's get
back to work.
Right. [ Coughs ]
[ Machine beeps,
tools whirring ]
Detective.
Nice to see you.
Judging by the long sleeves
and queasy demeanor,
I'd say you have
a new rookie.
Yeah. Dr. Lowell,
meet Officer Thorsen.
Of course.
Now I recognize you.
You know, I have to say
that the forensic work
in your case
seemed pretty solid.
You're lucky the Parisians
set you free.
I'm lucky the appeals court
understood that forensic science
can be as corrupt
as the rest of law enforcement.
First autopsy?
Yeah.
Smear this
under your nose.
It'll help
with the smell.
I'm surprised your TO
didn't tell you.
I can't give away
all my secrets
in the first week, Doc.
So, you get anything useful
from the autopsy?
Yeah, I found this
lodged in his T4 vertebra.
Looks like
it's from a .223.
Yeah, possible 77-grain.
Also known as NATO rounds
for their full metal jackets.
Yeah, very heavy
and very lethal
in a skilled marksman's hands.
Yeah, to make a long-distance
shot from a .223 round
would require
a specialized weapon,
which would seem
to confirm
that our shooter
had military training.
Nolan: Oh, hey.
Wait a minute.
She gave you the menthol
on your first visit?
No, the -- the doc did.
Ah, that makes sense.[ Clears throat ]
Harper: All right,
he's all yours.
Let's go get you
a ginger ale.
And you're here for...?
Uh, Nelson Crespo.
Ah, yes.
The burn victim.
You know, you keep running
into conflagrations
without oxygen masks,
and you'll end up
in one of my drawers.
Yeah, we've been told.
So, you got anything
on Crespo?
Well, I'm still writing up
my preliminary findings,
but I did see something
unexpected in his x-rays.
He had a transverse fracture
to his left femur
and compound fractures
to his pelvis.
From when the ceiling
fell in on him?
No. Actually, the fractures
were perimortem.
Likely occurred an hour
before his death.
That doesn't make
any sense.
He would have been
in agony.
Mm. Would explain
why he got caught
in the fire he set.
Oh, he didn't set it.
There was no carbon monoxide
in his blood
or soot in his lungs.
Nelson Crespo was dead
before the fire even started.
Hey, hope you and James
like the restaurant.
Well, actually, he, uh --
he never replied,
so it looks like I will be
going by myself.
How about invite
the other guy, Alonzo?
No.
Trust me.
This -- This place
is romantic,
and you're not gonna want
to eat there alone.
- Ooh, Harper.
- Hey.
Any leads on the sniper?
No.
Uh, detectives are on it.
Okay, when you catch him,
ask him where
he gets his gear.
What are you gonna do
with a zip line?
You know how far it is
to my parking spot.
[ Scoffs ][ Cellphone ringing ]
- Oh -- Angela.
- Ask her about the baby.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey. How's Jack?
You can find out for yourself
if you come over and babysit.
Both our moms bailed.
It's for you.[ Doorbell rings ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
Thank you so much
for doing this.
Of course.
- It's our pleasure.
- Yeah!
Where is that
little rascal?
Wesley's
putting him down.
Mm.
Aw, look at him.
Aw.
[ Sniffs ] Wait,
did you start smoking?
You can't smoke
around the baby.
Uh, n-- Please.
Come on.
I -- No, I-I walked
into a house fire yesterday
instead of waiting
for the fire department...
Mm-hmm....which is what
I should have done.
Mm-hmm.
It's turning into quite an
interesting case, actually.
At first,
we thought the guy
who started the fire
died in it,
but the autopsy shows
he was dead before it started.
Yeah,
with a crushed pelvis.
No one knows
how he got it or where.
Any witnesses?
A transient with
clear mental-health issues
that we pulled out
of the house.
He said he heard voices
before the fire started.
Heard voices
or "heard voices"?
That's what we said,
but given the condition
our victim was in
before he died,
I think our transient
actually heard our killer.
Wesley: Okay,
baby's asleep.
Let's go before
he realizes we're gone.
- Hi.
Bye.
Later.
- Don't call us.
- Uh, of course.
All right.
So...
[ Laughs ]
...what shall we do first?
Order food, or...
...make out?
Order first and make out
while we wait.
See, that's what I like
about you.
You're always thinking.
That's what you like
about me?
Well, there's more,
and I could show you,
but I'm on a schedule
right now.
I have to order dinner.
How dare you play
hard-to-get?
Lopez: Ooh, and the sweet corn
fried rice.
Hell, yeah.
And, uh, meatballs?
Ooh, two orders.
And -- Ooh!
The beet salad.
Thanks.
This is nice.
This is amazing.
Mm.
- Ahh.
- Mmm.
Did you hear Nolan talking
about his murder case?
It sounded challenging,
in an interesting way.
Mm-hmm.
What? It does.
Angela, this is our
first date in months.
I know, but what's more fun
than dinner and a murder?
Fine. No murder.
[ Laughs ]
Is that Nyla?
I guess that's why
she couldn't babysit.
Mm-hmm.
♪
Oh, my God.
Ooh, I think I'm
a little under-dressed.
Nah, man -- it's L.A.
I've seen people
wear flip-flops
to Michelin-star
restaurants.
[ Laughs ]
No one even blinks.
I'm actually
meeting someone.
[ Gasps ] Nyla.
[ Laughs ]
Hey.
You know her?
She's my date.
No, she's my date.
[ Laughs ]
Uh, actually...
y-you are both my dates.
[ Chuckles ]
Eh, funny story -- um...
Oh, no.
She double-booked.
You did not respond
to my text.
Yes, I'm pretty sure
that I did.
No.
O-Oh. No.
Mm-hmm.
Um...[ Clears throat ]
I guess I never hit "send."
Right.
And then
you called me --
your second option.
No, it's okay.
Enough said.
- She's all yours.
- N-- Alonzo, wait, I --
You know, I th--
I think I'm gonna go, too.
Really? We can't just s-stay
and have some wine and --
and -- and talk about it?
No.
I've -- I've acted like
I'm cool with being
one of two guys
you're dating
'cause I like you so much.
Well, that and
I thought one day,
you might actually
pick me.
James, I --
It's just -- It's a little hard
on the ego, so...
[ Clears throat ]
Enjoy the rest
of your night.
By the way...
you look amazing.
♪
Uh, that was brutal.
[ Sighs ] I'm gonna go
invite her to sit with us.
No, wait, wh--
A-Are you crazy?
Let her go.
Pretend it didn't happen.
♪
Counselor.
What a nice surprise.
♪
Yeah. Angela,
this is my client Elijah.
And silent partner
in this fine establishment.
Aren't the meatballs
to die for?
They're great.
Will you excuse me
for a minute?
Of course.
♪
What the hell
are you doing?
It is a crime
how easy it is...
...to hack a baby monitor.
♪
You're making a mistake,
threatening us.
I don't make threats.
I make promises.
And I always follow through --
just like I expect you to.
From this moment on,
whatever line
I need you to cross,
you will cross it.
Whoever I tell you
to represent,
you'll take them on
as a client.
And if I need you to betray
their interests in my benefit,
you'll do it.
I'll get disbarred.
Well,
only if you get caught.
This is what you agreed to trade
for your wife and child.
♪
And you do not want
to default on this debt.
♪
Oh, and you gotta order
the pot de crème.
It's sinful.
♪
[ Indistinct chatter ]
- Chen.
- Hmm?
If you want the job,
all you gotta do is ask.
What?
You sabotaged Webb.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
His cat personality?
Well, that's got you
written all over it.
Look, if you want me
to ride with you,
you don't need
to make up an excuse.
Just ask me.
Sgt. Grey: Good morning.
So, we have
a clearer understanding
of yesterday's
sniper shooting.
According to
the Gang Unit,
the victim had a falling-out
with Elijah Stone.
So, it was
a contract killing?
Looks like it.
Gangs put together
a list of potential shooters
that Elijah might use.
We ran it against
military personnel records
and came up with
a dozen names.
And you guessed it --
detectives want patrol
to do the initial canvass.
So...let's get to work.
Oh, oh.
One more thing.
Sergeant?
Yeah, um, I've decided
to spread the love
and give someone else a chance
to be my go-fer today.
Smitty, you're up.
Seriously?
I'm sorry, you have something
to add, Officer Chen?
[ Chuckles ] No.
Sir.
All right, that's it.
Be safe out there.
[ Indistinct chatter ]
Sarge.
The job doesn't require
any heavy lifting, right?
I've got a tricky back.
No. No lifting required.
Including the
war bags, right?
Yeah, Smitty,
I'll get the bags.
[ Sighs ]
♪
How was the restaurant?
What happened?
They both showed up.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yes.
Yesterday, I was dating
two cute guys,
and today, zero.
Well, it had to end
at some point, right?
I mean, if you cared
about one of them,
you would have made
a decision a while ago.
I liked the freedom.
It was fun being able
to take it slow.
But?
But I just --
I can't get the look
on James' face
out of my head.
And who's
our next contestant?
Aiden Merritt, 32.
One tour in Afghanistan,
followed by six years
as a private contractor.
Any priors?
A couple domestic
complaints in Houston --
an ex-girlfriend --
but nothing since
he moved to L.A.
[ Door opens ]
Hey.
Aiden Merritt?
Yeah, that's me.
What were you doing
yesterday at noon?
[ Chuckles ]
That's an ominous question.
Um, why do you
want to know?
There was a sniper
- shooting yesterday.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, I did see that
on the news.
And because of
my background, uh, yeah,
I get why
you want to see me.
The answer
to your question
actually has some
irony to it, though,
because yesterday afternoon,
I was actually at
the Gun Club downtown.
Well, that's good news.
You got any proof of that?
Um... I might, uh --
I might still have a receipt
for some ammo I bought.
I could go look.
Lucy: Mind if we
step inside?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I do.
But I'll be right back out.
♪
[ Door closes ]
I am getting a vibe.
- You getting a vibe?
- Big-time vibe.
Smart about that
alibi, though.
Gives him a reason
to be in the vicinity.
♪
Lucy, I'm looking
at a rifle.
Then that gives us
probable cause.[ Gun cocks ]
♪
I told you
to wait outside.
Sir, I'm gonna need you
to show us your hands.
Come on, man.
This is a mistake.
I got the receipt
right here.
Lucy: Yes, sir,
and we will get to that,
but right now,
my partner asked you
to show us your hands.
[ Scoffs ]
You really don't want me
to do that.
Yes, we do.
Nice and slow.
Okay.
♪
I already pulled the pin
in the bedroom.
I was planning
to frag your car
when you got back in,
split town before
the smoke cleared.
But...yeah.
[ Sighs ]
Now you've forced the issue.
You didn't survive a tour
just to die like this.
It's better than going
to prison.
Now, put down your guns,
or we can all learn
what shrapnel tastes like.
♪
Okay.
- Fine. You win.
- What are you doing?
You're a better shot
than me.
But I'm a little quicker
on my feet.
Nolan.
You got a better plan?
What the hell are you two
talking about?
The fuse on a grenade
takes approximately
four seconds to detonate.
He thinks if I shoot you
in the medulla,
he'll have enough time
to grab the grenade
after you drop it
and throw it outside
before it explodes.
Nolan --Actually,
I was planning on
kicking it back
into the house.
Where he probably has
more grenades?
♪
You're right.
Change of plan.
♪
[ Electricity whirs ]
[ Taser crackles ]
♪
Spoon's still attached.
We're good.
Thank you.
What? It worked.
7-Adam-15.
Requesting backup
and a supervisor
on our location.
[ Both panting ]
And the bomb squad.
Please, can you take that
outside while we wait?
That's right.
7-Adam-15.
We're also gonna need
a bomb squad.
[ Cellphone ringing, buzzing ]
Hello?
Where the hell
are all the baby monitors?
Um... I threw them out.
What? Why?
There was a --
a safety recall.
Fire hazard.
We can get new ones.
Higher tech.
Okay. Good catch.[ Chuckles ]
[ Door opens ]
♪
Babe, I gotta go.
Secretary wasn't
at her desk,
so I figured
I'd just pop in.
Yeah, sure.
What can I do for you?
I'm loving this
new attitude, Counselor.
It's just the right balance
between confidence
and obsequiousness.
♪
I need you to deliver this
to your new client.
♪
What new client?
[ Sighs ]
♪
I'm Wesley Evers.
- I'll be representing you.
- It's about friggin' time.
Aiden:
Give it to me straight.
How screwed am I?
[ Sighs ]
Well, we'll get to that.
First, I have
something for you.
Ah.
[ Chuckles ]
He hesitates.
You must be new to working
with our friend.
Still in that phase
where you think
you have free will.
Let me guess --
you took an oath
to uphold the law,
not break it,
so now you're torn.
Do you possibly
aid and abet a crime
by giving me whatever's
in that envelope?
I mean, the very act
of passing it to me
is a likely
ethics violation,
which could
get you disbarred.
And yet...
you wouldn't be here
if you had a choice,
would you?
Actually, it's for you.
[ Scoffs ]
You're lucky.
Fail one of Elijah's tests,
you end up as fertilizer.
So, how do you plan
to get me out of this mess?
♪
[ Indistinct chatter ]
How's it going, Sarge?
Fine. [ Sighs ]
How come Smitty's
not doing the paperwork?
♪
He claims to be
allergic to paper.
Hmm. [ Chuckles ]
It's not funny.
You should have
just asked me.
I was doing you a favor.
Yeah? How? By telling
the entire station
that you would rather
ride with Smitty than me,
your old boot?
Look, some would see it
as a demotion for you.
You're back with
your training officer.
Others might read...
[ Inhales deeply ]
...something else into it.
W-Why?
Because I'm a girl
and you're a boy?
A very handsome boy.
Oh, gag.
Look, I really appreciate
the intention,
but screw what
anyone else thinks.
Being a sergeant's aide
would --
Go-fer.
...aide would
make me stand out
come promotion time.
That alone makes it worth
putting up with your Tim tests
and old-school
code of honor again.
So, are you saying
you want the job?
If you're saying
you want me to do it.
♪
What the hell.
Let's do it.
You get here an hour
before roll call tomorrow
and I'll get you up to speed
on all the new protocols.
Will do.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Good luck
with your paperwork.
♪
James. [ Scoffs ]
What are you
doing here?
Well, Aaron asked me
to come by,
said he needed
to talk to me.
That was a lie.
I'm straight-up
playing matchmaker.
Boot, I'm --Hold -- Hold on.
I'm just trying
to do what I can
to fix the mess
that I caused.
You were kind to me
yesterday when we met,
so I feel compelled
to return the favor.
The second that I offered
Detective Harper
my reservation,
she invited you.
And when
you didn't respond,
she was gonna go alone.
But I pushed her
to invite the other guy.
♪
You know how close to the vest
she plays things.
I could still see
how upset she was
when she saw that
she hurt you.
So, maybe...
I don't know,
give her a second chance.
I'll see you tomorrow.
♪
That all true?
Yeah.
♪
I'm sorry
I messed everything up.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay.
[ Clears throat ]
You can take me
to dinner.
I can?
Yes, you can.
Okay.
But if there's anything on
the menu that I need to Google
to figure out what it is,
I'm walking.
No, you're not
- having that.
- I'm -- I'm just --
I'm -- I'm not --
Can't do that.
- Refuse. Refuse.
- Okay, I-I think
I got it.
I've been thinking about
your arson case.
You kill someone,
you set a fire to cover it up.
Pretty standard move.
What's strange
is the broken bones.
So I ran a search and found
two recent unsolved cases
with similar MO's.
Both in Nevada,
both suffered broken legs
before dying in a fire.
Three murders with
the same twisted MO.
We've got a serial killer
on our hands.
♪