Bailey:
Bailey?
Bailey, you okay?
Bailey. Give me your belt.
Your belt. Give me your belt.
Control, this is
Detective Lopez.
I have a fully engulfed
structure fire
at 1600 Quiet Valley Lane
in Newhall.
I need fire rescue and an RA
for a woman with a puncture
wound to her left leg.
Fred's still in there.
Don't move.
We have to help him! Bailey.
No one could have survived that.
Bailey, he's gone.
Hey, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
You're not fine. Come on.
Back in bed. Back in bed.
Watch your legs.
How's the patient?
Did they find Fred?
I'm afraid so.
His body sustained extensive
damage in the explosion,
but the Deputy Fire Chief
made a positive ID.
I'm sorry.
I know you were close.
I thought we were.
Then he turned out to be
a serial killer,
so it would seem that
the guy I liked
was just a disguise
he was wearing.
Lopez: Seems like he knew
we were onto him ‐‐
wanted to go out
on his own terms ‐‐
one last fire.
Hey, you okay?
I heard you got the guy.
Thanks to Nolan and Bailey.
So we need to close out
the case tomorrow.
Do you mind
partnering with Lopez?
Yeah, whatever you need.
Sarge, I was hoping
I could take the day tomorrow,
just to help Bailey
get settled at my place.
I told you I'd be fine
in my apartment.
I'm sure you would be,
but I'm not budging on this.
I don't want to impose.
It's not an imposition.
Okay, here we go.
Watch your step.
You're pretty good on those.
Gymnast all through
high school and college.
If you can sprain it, twist it,
or dislocate it, I have.
All I want is a couch.
You don't want to go
straight to bed?
Not yet.
First, I'm gonna have
a big cry and eat some carbs,
probably cry again,
then I can sleep.
Okay.
I will get the tissues
and ice cream.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So I rolled a stop sign.
What's the big deal?
No, you ran a red light
and a stop sign,
and when we tried to
pull you over,
you flipped us off and led us on
a medium‐speed pursuit.
I was late for an appointment
with Orchid, my life coach.
Well, she's doing
a terrible job.
Go stand over there.
Is there anything we can do
about this lighting?
Hey, so I've been
meaning to talk to you
about our bet
from the treasure hunt.
The bet I won?
No, the bet I won.
I had the gold in my hands.
Because I stopped to arrest
an armed gunman.
Eh, technically, I arrested him.
All you did was stand there
with your arm out.
Which is even more impressive.
Sir, what do you think?
What?
You okay, sir?
Something wrong
with the booking slip?
No. No. What do you need?
An umpire.
Um, who do you think won
our treasure hunt bet?
It was a tie. Oh...
We need a rematch.
Oh, I have an idea.
Why don't we race each other
in an escape room?
Hard pass.
No, we need a neutral party
to decide the terms
of the competition.
And that would be me. Okay.
I'm gonna assign each of you
a penal code violation
at random.
First one to make
their arrest wins.
Officer Chen,
your crime is 266i ‐‐
encourage, influence,
or persuade someone
to become a prostitute.
Sergeant Bradford,
yours is 148.4.
Oh, come on.
Willfully and maliciously
tampers with or breaks
fire protection equipment?
You knew that
off the top of your head?
You didn't?
Hmm. It's unfair.
So is life. Deal with it.
Hmm.
Oh, thank you.
Is there any way
I can get a single?
No. I'm afraid not.
Maybe I can make a donation
to the policemen's fund
or something.
Okay, don't add bribery
to your charge.
It's a whole other
stack of paperwork.
Let's go.
What if I give you
someone worse?
I know about a real crime.
I could cut a deal, right?
Like in the movies.
That depends. What's the crime?
They're alleging you beat a man
to death with a tire iron.
Dude deserved it.
He's banging my ex‐wife.
That's a street violation.
That demands repercussions.
Right. Sadly, street violations
don't hold up in court.
Says here there's a witness.
Yeah, some nosy old man
across the street
saw the whole thing.
Well, that's a problem. Why?
He's the one that's watching us
like some perv.
Be that as it may, we should
start talking plea deal.
A ‐‐ No!
No way, man, okay?
Elijah said you could fix this.
Elijah makes too many promises.
But I'll do what I can.
In the meantime, hey,
you know the drill ‐‐
best behavior.
Don't talk to anyone.
I noticed you got a new client.
Yeah.
Business is good.
Lately, it seems like
all your clients
are on Elijah Stone's payroll.
Well, every criminal defendant
is entitled to a defense,
regardless of who
they associate with.
Yes, and up 'til recently,
you've always chosen
to represent the underdog.
But now, the way
things are going,
you're on your way
to becoming a mob lawyer.
I think that's a bit extreme.
And there's only two ways
I've ever seen that turn out ‐‐
you end up disbarred
and indicted
or you end up dead.
Okay, I think that ‐‐
You know how much I care
for Angela.
If you ever get in
over your head,
you can come see me.
I appreciate that.
But you know
I would never do anything
to jeopardize my family.
I hope not.
I'll let you know if
there's gonna be a service.
Okay, bye.
I made breakfast.
You sure did.
I was feeling
a little powerless,
so this happened.
You're not gonna
hear me complaining.
This smells amazing.
Who was that on the phone?
Fred's old captain.
His family's dealing
with so much,
so I'm contacting some
of his former colleagues.
That's me.
I'll take this real quick.
Hey, what's up?
I just wanted to call
and check in
and see how Bailey's doing.
Uh, she's made four
different kinds of pancakes.
I'm not sure
if that's good or bad.
Yeah, the type A personality's
first stage of grief ‐‐ cooking.
What's next? Uh, cleaning.
Then organization.
She can't fix what happened,
but she can fix
every little thing
that's wrong in her apartment.
Uh, well, she's staying with me.
Yeah, well,
when she changes the drapes,
just roll with it. Right.
Thanks for checking in.
I gotta go.
I am so sorry, David,
but can you repeat that?
When were you at Lake Mead
with Fred?
David: Last Fourth of July.
And you were with him
the whole time? Yep.
It was supposed to be
a week‐long camping trip,
but, uh, a couple days in,
he got a nasty stomach bug.
He got so dehydrated,
I had to take him to Henderson.
He spent the rest of the trip
in the hospital.
Never thought that'd be
the last time I'd ever see him.
And he will be missed.
I will let you know
if there's any details
about the funeral.
Take care, okay? Thanks, Bailey.
You too.
Okay, I know
I'm on pain pills and all,
but you heard
what I just heard, right?
We know Fred was in Nevada
July 8th,
and that lined up
with an unsolved arson‐homicide.
But he was in the hospital.
Fred has an alibi.
That means Fred was set up,
and the real killer
is still out there somewhere.
What about the watch
and all the keepsakes
I found in his house?
Whoever framed Fred
must have planted them there,
counting on us finding them.
I gotta call Lopez,
have her reopen
the investigation.
Don't just call.
You need to go into work.
Find that bastard.
Are you sure?
We have a deal, remember?
I run toward fires.
You run toward bullets.
Time to run toward bullets.
But not literally.
Right.
So, I have a list of locations
we should check out
when we get back out on patrol.
You know, just some places
that I think need
a police presence.
Places you're sure to get
your pandering collar?
Oh. Yeah. Maybe.
Is that really your focus?
Our bet? Come on.
I know that you bribed Nell
to throw any "fire alarm
tampering" cases your way.
Nell and I are friends. Mm.
Sometimes, I give her
Dodgers tickets.
Oh, finally.
What's this all about?
Mrs. Carter, I understand
that you've recently started
your own skincare line.
Yes.
We're a small operation,
but we're growing.
I'm hoping to get
a write‐up in Goop.
I‐I don't know what that is.
I'll explain later.
Uh, a friend of yours
gave us a jar
of your night cream.
She claims that
one of the ingredients
is tiger's blood ‐‐
like, literally,
blood from an endangered animal.
Firms the skin right up.
Participating in
the endangered animal trade
could land you in jail
for up to five years.
You don't understand
the wellness game.
It's cutthroat.
I need to stand out.
How else am I gonna compete
with Sloan
and her vitamin business?
I mean, everybody knows that
her B‐12 rejuvenation pills
are just benzos
in fancy bottles.
Um, she's selling
psychiatric drugs?
Oh, the whole "westside buffet."
What's Sloan's last name?
Hey, any news?
Valley Hospital in Henderson
verified that Fred was a patient
from July 6th to the 10th.
Okay, so there's no way
he committed the murder
and arson in Nevada.
No, we're gonna have to go back
and re‐examine everything
going back to the first
hit and run.
Whoever did this
is covering his tracks,
so we need to separate
the things our killer
wanted us to believe
from the facts of the case.
Hey, uh, Nolan.
Oh, uh, brought this for Bailey.
Hope she's, uh,
f‐feeling better.
Oh, thank you, that's ‐‐
that's very thoughtful.
Yeah, she's doing great.
Oh, uh, I brought that, uh,
doorbell camera footage
you asked for.
Right, thank you very much
for that.
This is Marcus.
He's, uh, Fred's neighbor.
I met him at the barbecue.
Uh, this is Detectives Lopez
and Harper.
Good to meet you.
I mean, bad circumstances.
I ‐‐ I don't know
what I'm trying to say.
Yeah, we're all struggling
with what happened.
Uh, what did happen?
Uh, people were saying
that it was a gas leak,
and one of the firefighters said
it could be arson.
And now I'm standing
in a police station.
I really don't know
what to think.
Uh, well, I'm afraid
there's not much I can tell you.
Of course. Right.
Did you notice anything
out of the ordinary
in the last few days?
Other than a big ball
of fire, no. Sorry.
Well, if you can think
of anything else,
you have Nolan's number.
Absolutely.
Thanks again. Yeah.
What'd he get her?
Uh... chocolates.
That's nice.
Look out.
What do you mean?
Nolan, he was the only civilian
at the firefighter party.
He is buying gifts for Bailey.
Come on. He's a badge bunny.
Just for a different badge.
And your girlfriend's
wearing it.
Oh, no, I don't think so.
No, uh, he knows Bailey.
It's not so weird.
Okay, when was the last time
you bought chocolates
for someone you weren't
sleeping with?
Um...
That guy's after my girlfriend.
Mm. Yeah.
Fun.
Okay, I'm gonna start
combing through
the security footage.
What are you going to do?
Oh, I'm, uh,
headed to the hospital.
The victim you pulled
out of the fire
is finally out of ICU.
I'll go with you. All right.
Thank you. Mm‐hmm.
Elijah needs to see you.
Sure.
Just tell him to come upstairs.
We'll talk in my office.
Nah.
He wants to talk to you in his.
Counselor.
Just heard from Jay.
He expressed
a lack of confidence
in your ability to get him out
of his legal difficulties.
He murdered a man.
Allegedly.
Except for the eyewitness
that clearly saw it happen.
Oh, come on, Counselor.
Eyewitness misidentification
is the leading cause
of wrongful conviction.
That's Defense Attorney 101.
What, I don't got enough
on my plate,
I gotta do your job, too?
Find some dirt on this guy.
Make him seem unreliable.
I'll do my best,
but so far, I ‐‐
Look, Jay got sloppy.
I know, and I'm pissed about it.
But he's my wife's
favorite cousin,
which means
he's my favorite cousin,
so prison's not an option.
Now, either you make
the witness go away,
or Moreno does.
As in "rest in peace"?
I didn't say that.
Unlike my wife's
dumb-ass cousin,
I'm not foolish enough
to commit or confess to crimes
in front of witnesses.
We don't even have to
go there, okay?
I can handle this.
I just need some time.
Get it done today.
Meeting's over.
Get out of my office
and go do your job.
Tim: Take off your sunglasses, ma'am.
Do I have to?
These fluorescent lights
give me vertigo.
Okay, that could be
the least of your worries.
We've been informed that
you're selling psychiatric drugs
as a vitamin.
Who said that?
It doesn't matter.
I'm helping people.
What's the problem?
You can't prescribe
a controlled substance
without a medical license.
My husband is a doctor.
It's the family
prescription pad.
Yeah, that's not a thing.
Look, I don't think
you're hearing me, all right?
This makes you a drug dealer.
And given the circumstances,
a pretty high level one.
You could be looking at
20 years in prison.
What? No. No, no, no, no, no.
This wh‐‐ This whole thing has
gotten horribly out of hand.
Who ratted me out, anyway?
It was Aston, wasn't it?
She's been trying
to take me down
ever since I stole
her portrait painter.
Like she needs to be
hung on a wall.
You want a real crime to chase?
Aston's trying to hire a hitman.
W‐What do you mean?
Her husband's worth more
dead than alive,
so she's been on the dark web
trying to hire someone
to kill him.
Okay. Oh. That's your disguise?
You don't even look
like a hitman.
You just look like you.
This is what real hitmen
look like.
That is not the point.
Come on. Get in.
What I'm wearing is fine. Okay.
Third rule of undercover work ‐‐
know your audience.
You are not trying to fool
another criminal.
You're trying to fool a woman
who gets her ideas about crime
from Lifetime movies.
Put it on.
Fine.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, that's much better.
I look like an idiot.
I'd pull me over in a heartbeat.
Exactly ‐‐ because
you look the part.
Let's get this over with.
It's a little too high.
I know what I'm doing.
Ow.
Sorry.
Mic check, one, two.
Okay, levels are good.
She should be here
in 15 minutes.
What are you doing here?
I have until the end of the day.
I'm just here to get it done
if you can't.
Good luck.
Mr. Andrews, thank you for
meeting me on such short notice.
Long as I ain't gotta
drive nowhere.
So, I just have a few questions
about the crime ‐‐ thank you ‐‐
that you allegedly witnessed.
Uh, first, do you wear glasses?
20/20 vision my whole life.
Great.
Anything to drink
on the night in question?
Been sober 38 years.
How clear was your view
of the events
the night in question?
He killed the man right there.
Huh?
It was getting late ‐‐
8:00 p. m.
It would've been dark.
Not on my block.
Those street lights so much
as flicker, I call the city.
You know why, Mr. Evers?
'Cause I do whatever it takes
to protect my neighborhood.
From criminals.
And their lawyers.
I know why you're here.
Wanna scare me off.
Well, go tell your boss...
I don't scare easy.
I'm not trying
to intimidate you.
I just, um...
I hear you.
Can I use your bathroom
before I go?
Sure.
Thank you.
Operator: 911.
What's your emergency?
My neighbor keeps an illegal
firearm under his bed.
I'm in fear for my life.
Send the police.
70 Oak Place.
Ken: I don't remember his face.
I keep trying, but, uh,
every time I try and focus,
uh, it just skitters away
from me like a silverfish.
Well, that's your mind
protecting you.
It's normal.
Yet I remember him
acting so horrified
that he hit me with his car.
He insisted on taking me
to the hospital, so...
I let him put me
in the back seat.
Just went along with it.
A stranger said
he was gonna help me,
and I trusted him.
Of course you did.
Anyone else
would've done the same.
Did he say anything in the car?
I‐I don't remember.
I‐I blacked out as soon
as I got into the car.
Well, they found Rohypnol
in your system.
That would explain the blackout.
Do you remember anything
from inside
the abandoned building
where he took you?
Unfortunately, um,
when I woke up...
pain was just eating me alive,
and, uh, I remember praying
that I would black out.
And then he started stomping
on my broken legs.
Is there anything else
you remember?
The smallest thing could help.
Uh, his back.
At one point, he leaned over,
and his shirt came up,
and there was something
on his back.
Was it a tattoo? Scar?
Uh, ma‐‐ Uh, maybe a burn?
I don't think it's a tattoo.
Maybe a burn or a scar.
Does that help?
Absolutely.
Um, call us
if you can think
of anything else,
and I will be sure to keep you
up to date on the case.
Okay?
Thank you. Yeah.
Hey, this guy is a predator.
He knew exactly
how to incapacitate you.
What happened
was not your fault.
You made sure you weren't followed?
Yes.
I drove around in circles
for like a half an hour.
So, how does this work?
Well, that's up to you.
Your ad indicated you have
a problem with your husband?
Yes.
I need him to not be
alive anymore.
Mm, that's not gonna be enough.
We need her to spell it out.
Okay.
Do you want it to look like
natural causes?
A suicide? Homicide?
Must be a lonely kind of life ‐‐
being a hitman.
It can be.
So, you're not seeing anyone?
Oh, my God.
She's hitting on you.
No, not at the moment.
Mm. You see, the thing is,
the fee varies
depending on the method.
So I need you to tell me
what you want.
Ooh.
What I want changed a little
when you got in the car.
Wait, is she touching you?
She's touching you, isn't she?
Hey, you know what?
If she offers you money for sex,
I'm gonna win this bet.
Look, I am down to do
whatever you want. Hmm.
Yeah, you are. I just want to get
the business out of the way first.
So, it's $20,000
for a straight murder ‐‐
$25,000 if you want it
to look like suicide.
Sexy.
I'd pay you twice that
to kill the bastard.
And the bastard is?
My husband, obviously.
Yes. Got her.
You know, once he's dead,
I'll be a very wealthy woman.
Hmm.
You're under arrest.
All right. No, I‐I appreciate
the help.
Thank you. Bye.
Hey. Anything?
We struck out
with Fred's gardener.
He has access
to Fred's property,
but he has an alibi
for almost every murder.
He's definitely not our guy.
And the mail carrier
alibied out, too.
So, that leaves us with...
The handyman.
His name's Ricardo Fuentes,
and he has a couple of
assault charges from years ago.
Did you talk with him?
Yeah, and he was less than helpful.
When I asked for his whereabouts
on the dates of the murders,
he refused to answer.
That doesn't make him a suspect.
I mean, maybe he just
doesn't trust the police.
True, but when I asked him
why he went to Fred's house
yesterday morning,
he had an odd answer.
He said he got a call
to go to Fred's house
to strap the water heater down
and that he was told
to enter the property
if no one was home.
And the odd part is?
How he claims he was paid.
With cash, in an envelope
taped to the water heater.
But of course,
he threw away the envelope.
So, maybe he's
telling the truth,
and this is him going
to strap down the water heater.
Or he's setting the bomb
that killed Fred.
Okay, well,
that's easily verifiable.
I can just swing by Fred's house
on the way home,
see if Ricardo did the work.
Thanks.
Let us know what you find.
You got it.
Hey, where's the food?
I forgot.
Sorry. It's been a crazy day.
Which is why I said
we should order in,
but you insisted
that you would be
driving by the restaurant
and would pick something up.
Okay, I forgot.
Okay? Cut me some slack. Slack?
I work just as long as you
but somehow still came home,
tidied up the house, fed Jack,
and put him to bed.
Well, that's because
you're perfect.
The rest of us are just human.
Wow. Where did that come from?
Where are you going?
To get the food.
Hey.
Bailey: When are you
coming home?
You okay? Yeah, I'm just tired.
These painkillers are no joke.
Don't wait up for me.
Go to sleep. How's it going?
We're gonna catch this guy.
I promise.
Oh, don't do that.
I don't need empty promises.
It's bad for relationships.
Trust me. Okay.
Well, we had a suspect,
but his story checks out,
and now we got nothing.
Well, there's three
varieties of pie
waiting for you
when you get home.
You are supposed to be
staying off your feet ‐‐
and what kind of pie?
Cherry, apple,
and chocolate cream.
You're my favorite.
That's good, 'cause you're mine.
Hurry home to me, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Marcus. Marcus: Nolan.
Thanks again for that, uh,
doorbell footage.
It helped. Ah, good, good.
Um, any leads?
Uh, we're checking
all the angles.
Well...
have a good night.
You too.
Ugh!
Hey there.
You were out for quite a while.
You know, mixing Rohypnol
and head trauma
can be a little...
dicey.
Nolan: Where... are you?
Only the coolest
place in Los Angeles.
I found this place
when I was out looking
for a new killing ground.
It's some kind of used factory.
I don't know what the hell
they made here, but it is huge
and super abandoned,
and it got me thinking
on a much larger scale.
Hey, John?
John.
There you go.
Hey.
Do you know what
the adductor longus is, John?
Oh, probably not.
Uh, I'm pretty sure
yours is shredded.
You know, when car hits human,
human always loses.
But who am I to tell you that?
I mean, how many car wrecks
and hit‐and‐runs
have you worked?
They're gonna catch you.
Maybe.
I mean, you ‐‐
you got uncomfortably close ‐‐
closer than anyone ever has.
It's all my fault.
No, I got lazy.
For 10 years, I have had
an ironclad MO ‐‐
travel to hunt.
But I‐I figured, you know,
Los Angeles, it's so big.
I‐I figured if I stayed
far enough away
from where I lived,
it'd be kind of like
a‐a murder staycation.
But then you got lucky
with that hot firefighter,
and I got unlucky.
So, it's time
to leave "Marcus" behind,
get off the grid, go on the run.
But, you know, first, I thought
I'd have a little fun.
Would you stop trying
to break free?
I'm gonna let you go
in a minute.
Bull. No, really.
See, the thing about addicts is,
they're constantly trying
to relive that first high ‐‐
you know, when the effect
was the strongest.
It's just ‐‐ It's never
as good the second time.
Is that why you target
former addicts?
Trying to punish
a version of yourself?
God, no!
I feel no shame for what I do.
The needs I feel.
No, if I could
murder someone every day,
I would be the happiest man
on the planet.
Oh, I don't know ‐‐
maybe I'd lose my taste for it.
You know, like when you eat
too many chips.
Anybody ever tell you
you're crazy?
Sure.
But then I burn them to ash.
Ah.
Ooh, that was close.
Ooh, I should've
seen that coming.
Okay, not a great first step.
We'll call it a useful failing.
A teachable moment.
Now...
here's the deal.
I'm gonna cut you free.
I'm gonna give you
a one‐minute head start,
and then I'm gonna
come kill you.
You gonna give me a weapon?
I said I wanted a challenge,
but I'm not an idiot.
And what if I don't run?
What if I come over there
and I take that knife
and I stick it some place
you don't like?
Aah!
Well, I think we're ready.
Huh?
This is exciting.
I'm ‐‐ I'm actually
a little bit nervous.
Are ‐‐ Are you?
Well, ready, set...
Oops.
I mean, you didn't think
I'd play fair, did you?
All right, well,
a‐one‐a‐Mississippi.
A‐two‐a‐Mississippi.
Tha‐ree‐a‐Mississippi.
Marcus: John?
Well...
This is fun, isn't it?
I gotta say, the silence?
It's kinda nice.
Usually, there's a lot
of whining and begging.
Fair amount of sobbing.
I mean, you'd think
that would be part of my thrill,
but, you know, it really
just works on the nerves.
Whoo‐hoo‐hoo‐hoo!
John.
See, the thing is,
the deck is stacked against you.
You see, I've had weeks
to get this place ready.
Hey, here we go.
What's wrong, John? You stuck?
Run, rabbit! Run!
Agh!
Whoo‐hoo‐hoo! John!
Hey, John.
John, you in there?
Hey, you wanna know
a little secret?
I hate scary movies.
I mean, you'd think
I'd love them 'cause ‐‐
well, duh.
But no, I'm actually a sucker
for a jump‐scare.
You know, the way ‐‐ the way
you get everything real quiet.
And then it gets you
on the edge of your seat.
You know.
And then ‐‐ bam!
Ugh!
Argh.
It's over, Marcus!
Give it up!
We can still call you
an ambulance!
You stabbed me.
What the heck
did you stab me with?
Scissors.
Rusty ones, too.
Now, you give your ass up.
You make this
a fight to the death,
I swear to God,
you'll be the one
they carry out of here!
Aw, come on.
Ah, safety, safety, safety.
Yes.
Agh!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Aw!
Operator: 911.
What's your emergency?
This is Officer John Nolan,
badge number 25253.
I am hurt and under attack
by Marcus Lindsey,
a serial murder suspect
armed with an assault rifle.
Send help!
I win.
And you're under arrest.
Ugh!
Moreno: Whoo.
You need to pay better attention
to your surroundings, man.
What do they call it?
Uh...
Situational awareness.
Elijah's not gonna be
happy about this.
Elijah brought his own bat.
Wait, wait, wait!
Why are you doing this?!
Stop! Stop!
The strangest thing
happened yesterday
after you left
that witness' home.
Cops swooped in
and arrested him.
It was almost like someone
wanted to keep him
out of harm's way.
It's like you were
working against me.
Are you really this stupid?
You told me
to make the witness go away.
That's what I did!
I took him off the board!
I got him arrested for
an illegal weapons violation.
There is no way
he can testify now.
His credibility's shot.
And as an added bonus,
you didn't have
to commit another crime.
Oh.
Well, that changes things.
You need to work on
your communication skills,
'cause this beating's based
on your lack of transparency.
Are we good?
Yeah.
For now.
Great work.
Hey.
Welcome back to the land
of the living.
Doc said you were
pretty banged up,
but lucky you ‐‐
no broken bones.
Really?
It feels like
everything's broken.
They have meds for that.
Great job out there.
We got him.
No, you got him.
Yeah, after he got me.
There she is.
Hi.
Come here.
Ow. Oh, sorry.
No, no. It's okay, it's okay.
It's a good hurt. I can take it.
I can take it.
I can't take it.
Mm.
I'm so relieved you're okay.
Oh, it's nothing.
Just a couple more war wounds
I can flaunt in bed.
Speaking of,
what are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed
to be in bed?
Mm, yeah.
Scoot over.
Done.
Okay.
You got him.
I told you I would.
Oh, no.
"I told you so" is so much worse
than "I promise."
Really? A relationship killer.
100%.
I'm gonna need some kind
of cheat sheet, I think.
Seriously, I can't believe
you bought out
the entire gift shop.
What? You've been
in the hospital before.
You know how boring it can be.
What did you get him? Nothing.
I'll just put my name on yours.
Unbelievable.
Hey, we're going
back out on patrol
after we're done visiting
with Nolan, right?
Lucy.
Mm‐hmm. What?
You know, I have a bet to win.
Okay, can we just call it off?
Police work is too important
to turn into a game.
You're just worried
you're gonna lose.
Sure. If that's what you need to
hear, let's go with that.
Wait, hold on.
Since when did you become
the noble one here?
Does this mean
we're square on our bet?
Fine.
Nobody wins.
But the basket is only from me.
Where you been?
I thought you were gonna
be here for bedtime.
Sorry, I‐I got stuck on a call.
Angela.
What's wrong?
I screwed up.
I need help.
sync & corrections
jhj@2021