Oh, sorry.
Visitors can't park down here.
I-I know.
I'm not.
My dad sent me down
to his car
to get the coffees
he bought for us.
Oh.
Who's your dad?
Steve Miller.
Property Crimes?
Yeah.
T-That's him.
We don't, uh, get to see
each other too often
since the divorce.
Mom got full custody.
So he makes me stop by
the station
for some "father-son"
coffee time before school.
Oh. That's nice.
After you.
Thanks.
♪ Don't care what you say
Four, right?
Huh?
Property Crimes?
Four?
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Divorce is tough.
I have a son a few years older
than you.
I remember when his mom and I
split up,
I wanted to do everything
I could just to show him
that I would still
be there for him.
You know, still be Dad.
I'm sure your father's just
trying to do the same for you.
Yeah.
And this is my stop.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, you, too.
Oh.
Just wanted to say
thank you for the pep talk.
I -- I needed it.
No problem.
♪♪
We need to figure out
how he got access to the roof.
Okay.
Hey.
What's happening?
Someone stole
a police helicopter.
What?
Nolan.
Sir, I just heard about
the airship.
Do you know
who took it?
No.
But you do.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Airship Three,
I repeat, do you copy?
Sir, in Nolan's defense,
a teenager stealing
a police helicopter --
it's highly unexpected behavior.
We're cops.
"Highly unexpected"
is what we do before breakfast.
Hey, kid,
I know you can hear me.
See, right now I have the FBI,
Homeland Security,
and the DOD
blowing up my phone,
and they're all saying
the same thing --
we should launch fighter jets
and blow you out of the sky.
Now, do you copy?
This is Airship Three.
Please identify yourself.
Sergeant Wade Grey, LAPD.
'Sup, Wade?
Listen, I know
they're not gonna blow me
out of the sky
while I'm over
a populated area,
so tell them to just save
the jet fuel, okay?
This is a joy ride,
not DEFCON 1.
I'm just gonna have
a little fun.
I'll return your helicopter
good as new.
Listen here, boy, I --If I may.
Hey. This is John Nolan,
from the elevator.
Hey! Yeah, yeah.
The divorced dad.
Look, you are super good
at bonding, by the way.
I mean, I-I really felt
the emotional connection.
Yes. Thank you.
Listen, we know Steve Miller's
not really your father,
so why don't you tell us
who you really are
and what you want?
Who I really am
is the hero of my own story.
And what I want is to
complete the hero's journey.
Whoa!
What is it?
What happened?
I just saw a cyclist almost get
demolished by a vehicle.
I mean, this city really needs
to add more bike lanes.
But, hey, look, this has been
fun, but I gotta go
because flying a real
helicopter is a lot harder
than the video-game simulation
made it seem.
So, we'll talk soon, okay?
No, no, wait,
wait, wait.
Hero?
Okay, uh,
do we believe him?
I mean, he seemed like
a sweet kid on the elevator.
He's not talking like
he's planning on
doing anything violent.
And he's right.
They won't shoot him down
unless he poses
an imminent threat.
So, how do we get him down
with no casualties?
We got four hours
to figure that out.
That's how much fuel
he's got left.
Nolan, get out there and
shadow him the best you can.
Can I take Lucy with me?
She'll help me get in his head.
Okay. Good idea.
And, Nolan, get him to land
before gravity does it for him.
Yes, sir.
♪♪
Hey. You ready to roll?
Oh. Actually, Grey assigned me
to ride with Nolan
to trail helicopter kid.
Alright. Let me know
if you need anything.
Mm-hmm.
Hey. Guess who's sitting
in a holding cell right now?
Yeah.
I don't do guessing games.
Your old friend,
Dez Robinson.
What'd he do?
Cabot and Lodge
pulled him over
for a traffic violation.
They found a diamond bracelet
in his car that was taken
during a home invasion
that left a family dead.
That triple murder
in Larchmont Village?
Yeah. I'm about to go
question him. You want in?
Bet your ass I do.
I'm surprised you've stayed out
of prison for this long,
given that you're dumb enough
to drive around
with stolen property
when you're still on probation.
The bracelet was stolen?
I had no idea.
I-I bought it
from a pawnshop
to give to my mother
for her -- her birthday.
Yeah, which pawnshop?
Man,
I don't remember that.
I went to like nine of them
you know,
looking for
the perfect gift.
I love my mom.
Do you have the receipt?
No.
I don't believe in them.
Thing is, Dez, that bracelet
wasn't just stolen.
It was taken from
a home invasion two nights ago,
where three people
were killed.
And we believe the same crew
is responsible
for two other home invasion
murders.
Oh, wow.
You guys really
don't like
to leave any witnesses,
do you?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Really. I-I was at work
two nights ago.
Just check with my boss.
Oh, I will.
Look, Dez...
you and I --
we go way back, right?
The joy of recidivism.
And while you've never been
afraid of a little violence,
you're not a killer.
So I don't think you'd shoot
that family in cold blood.
No. I think you hooked up
with this crew
not knowing they were killers,
and now you're tied to them.
If you tell us who they are,
we can make a deal.
If not, we hang the murders
around your neck
with the rest of your crew,
and you'll die in prison.
All we need is a name.
♪♪
Adrienne Mount.
Adrienne Mount
committed the murders?
No.
She's my lawyer.
I'd like to
talk to her, please.
Are you wearing makeup?
What?
No.
Okay, yeah.
Um...I thought that
I got that off.
Hmm.
Yeah. We had
a late-night shoot
at Club Avalon
for my reality show pilot.
How exactly does partying
at a nightclub
reset the world's image
of you?
Well, no.
We were, like, you know,
shooting the reenactments
of, like,
what my life was like
before the murder.
Which, actually,
was pretty cool.
Listen, Hollywood,
I will put up with
this reality show
as long as it helps
to clear your name.
But if it starts to affect
your performance --
It won't, okay?
I swear.
And, look, I couldn't be
any less "Hollywood."
Mr. Thorsen.
Good morning, sir.
I got you
your breakfast.
Who are you?
Kenton Scott,
Mr. Thorsen's assistant.
Uh, no.
I mean, yes, but he's only
supposed to be assisting me
when I'm working on
the show.
And right now,
I'm at my real job.
And I'm still
on probation,
so I need you to go now,
okay?
No.
W-What do you mean, no?
You work for me.
Uh, technically,
I work for your mother.
And she...scares the hell
outta me.
I-In the best way.
She's amazing. I love her.
But if I make a mistake, she'll
catapult me into the sun,
so I'm here for you
24/7.
So should I ride with you,
or just follow in my car?
Probably my car,
so I can run errands if you --
Kenton, Kenton, Kenton,
take a breath.
Okay? Uh, assistants
get lunch, right?
Yes. Absolutely.
Okay. I'm having
this wild pregnancy craving
for some, uh,
bulgogi tacos.
Great, I'm sure I can find that
around here --
Yeah. But not just
any bulgogi tacos.
They have to be from
Apollo Yang's food truck,
which is parked at
a different location every day.
And the only way
to obtain that location
is to text
a secret password
to a specific short code,
which...I don't have.
♪♪
On it.
Yeah.
That'll keep him busy.
I'm so sorry. That --
That won't happen again.
I'mma talk to my mom
about that, okay?
Mm-hmm.
You alright?
Yeah. I think so.
I just got uncomfortable
all of a sudden.
It's the baby?
I don't know.
Um, maybe we should,
um, stop by my OB's office
at the hospital,
just to make sure.
Okay.
Alright.
♪♪
Oh. They ID'd 'copter kid.
Leo Thomas, age 17.
No priors.
Grey's reaching out
to the family.
Clearly,
there's trouble there.
Well-adjusted kids don't steal
police helicopters.
I mean, it could
be classic
teenage attention-seeking
behavior.
You know, trying to stand out,
establish their identity.
The whole thing's gotten
exponentially worse
since social media.
Dying your hair is classic
attention seeking.
Stealing a police helicopter
is extremely dangerous.
Teenagers don't have
fully formed brains.
They don't perceive risk
in the same ways that we do.
You remember that age.
I remember working
two part-time jobs
to save up for college.
You never acted out?
Not in
any substantial way.
Well --
You know, I don't know why
I'm surprised.
Oh, like you were
such a rebel.
I'm --
You have no idea.
Hello?
How's Harper doing?
Still waiting to hear,
sir,
but the doctor
didn't seem worried.
Good.
Keep me updated.
In the meantime, I have
an assignment for you.
Yes, sir.
A riot broke out at
Men's Correctional this morning.
There were dozens injured and
one prisoner airlifted to Shaw
for emergency surgery --
Langston Bryant.
So I need you to relieve
the sheriff's deputy
that accompanied him.
And, Thorsen --
Sir?
Langston's 18 years into
a life sentence
for killing a cop
for a routine
traffic stop.
He did it once, he could
certainly do it again.
Watch yourself.
Yes, sir.
Nurse Howard to 2 West, please.
Hey, I'm here
to relieve you.
Great. I gotta get back
to the prison.
Damn, man,
are you okay?
Not even close.
The prisoner in there --
he's as dangerous as they come,
so be smart.
Yes, sir.
I've been briefed.
♪♪
Good morning, Los Angeles!
This is Airship Three coming to
you live and in the sky.
Looks like there's gonna be
traffic on...
all of the roads.
And I'm actually taking a poll
about where I should go
patrol next.
Um, you know, I-I could take
a trip over to Santa Monica,
maybe see what'll be underwater
when all the glaciers melt.
Hey, there, Leo.
Divorced Dad here.
How's it going up there?
Me? Can't complain.
You know where the bathroom is
in this thing?
Listen, Leo -- what you are
doing is really dangerous.
Your family is worried sick
about you.
Yeah,
that's not gonna work
and I'm disappointed
you thought it would.
So, see ya.
Look. Wait. Hang on.
Hang on. Hang on. Just --
Did you really learn to fly
from video games?
And a few
ClipTalk tutorials.
Ugh.
Wow. That's --
Hats off, man. Wow.
I mean, I --
I love me some video games,
but that's --
You know, uh,
"Breath of the Wild"
consumed my life
for about four months.
I beat Ganon -- twice. Impressive.
I-I bet you're feeling a little
bit like Link and his glider,
flying around up there,
don't you?
A little, yeah.
But even Link couldn't fly
forever, right?
He had to land sometime,
save Zelda, right?
That's right.
The hero always has a purpose.
Great. We're gonna find you
a nice, open place to land.
And he can also use help
from his allies.
Are you an ally,
Mr. Nolan?
Yes, I am.
Great.
So here's the deal.
In order to help me complete
my hero's journey...
I need you to complete
three quests.
If you succeed,
I'll give myself up.
This is not
a video game, Leo.
No.
It's something deeper.
Games, fantasy novels,
they're all built on
the same architecture --
the hero's journey.
A universal story
so central to our identities,
it's as if it's written
in our DNA.
He's been reading
Joseph Campbell.
Ah.
You're the mentor --
an older, wiser figure
like an Obi-Wan
or a Dumbledore.
They usually die towards
the end...
...to signify the hero's true
coming into himself.
Who knows?
Maybe you'll pull through.
Leo, this isn't a myth.
This is real life,
and you are in real danger.
I can't play along with
this quest nonsense.
Why not?
Why not slay dragons
for a kid
I think is
increasingly delusional?
Look, often the best way --
the only way
to deal with people
who are in a crisis situation
is to accept
their reality.
I mean, it's either this
or we drive around all day,
looking up.
Alright.
What are the quests?
I'm not gonna give you
all of them up front.
It doesn't work that way.
What do we have
to lose?
Lives?
A helicopter?
Fine. What is
the first quest?
♪♪
Okay. 9412 Orange.
It's been empty
for over a year.
Persistent 911 calls
about drug activity.
Let's take a look.
♪♪
This is a quest
based in tragedy.
A bunch of kids from my school,
they started hanging out
at this abandoned house.
They party, make a mess --
just the typical rebellion
of youth.
And some hardcore guys saw
a market and they moved in.
They started selling
some hardcore drugs,
and a raven-haired girl
OD'd.
A young princess the hero
liked from afar.
You can't save the princess,
but you can stop the monsters
who hurt her.
♪ Run
Running!
♪♪
♪ Run
♪ I got 'em, I got 'em,
I got 'em, I got 'em ♪
♪ I got 'em, I got 'em
Turn around.
Put your hands on your head,
fingers interlaced.
Don't move.
♪ Can't stop, not yet
You got him?
Yeah.
♪ Never rest
till I'm in the safe zone ♪
♪ I know I can make it home
♪ Can't breathe, next week
♪ Got no time
to think about it ♪
♪ Ain't no other way around it
♪ They can just
forget about it ♪
Control, 7015.
Pull an R.A. unit.
We got a drug-addled victim,
unconscious but breathing.
♪ Run
Hey.
You.
You're that guy.
Yo, man, come here.
Officer, I need some help.
You need something?
That uniform threw me off.
You're that guy
that got railroaded in France
for killing your buddy.
Hold on. Slow down.
Easy. Come on.
I really do
need some help.
I'm dying of thirst.
Cruel and unusual,
know what I'm saying?
Thank you.
Thought I was done
for sure.
What, the riot?
Yeah. Just another day
in paradise.
You a cop now?
Are you done?
Ah. You and me?
We're the same.
No, man,
not even close.
I'm innocent.
You killed a cop.
Right.
And you see me,
chained up, tatted,
you figure
I fit the bill.
This isn't who I was.
It's who I had to become
to stay alive.
Yeah.
Yo, hold on.
You could spare me a few moments
of your time, brother.
I'll be outside.
You're sure
that's my Leo?
Yes, ma'am.
Is he okay?
For now.
We're just trying to make sure
he doesn't hurt himself,
or others.
So he hasn't
contacted you?
No. He wasn't there this morning
when I got home.
I work graveyard.
I called and texted,
but he never responded.
Is that typical
for your son?
Things have been tough for him
ever since...
Go on.
You can say it.
Since his father passed.
Guy was a deadbeat
while he was alive.
Suddenly now,
he's a superhero.
Brian --No, I'm sorry.
I try to do right
by that kid.
We both do,
but he makes it impossible.
He barely talks to us.
He spends all of his time
reading these fantasy books,
playing video games.
Did manage to get himself
kicked out of school.
Leo's not in school?
I teach him at home.
It's -- It's just hard,
uh, with my hours.
♪♪
I'm always tired.
I can't lose him.
And then after my conviction,
I found out
that there were
two eyewitnesses,
both who said the killer
was a short bald guy
who looked
nothing like me.
Okay. So, where was your lawyer
on all this?
Drunk off his ass.
Court appointed,
and he couldn't give a damn.
Now you see
what I'm saying?
Look, you need to file
for a retrial.
I mean,
that's what I did.
I don't have
your kind of money, my brother,
and I can't get a lawyer
to take me on pro bono.
I'm sorry.
I don't need your sorry,
but I could use
your help.
You did two years for
a crime you didn't commit --
I'm going on 18.
Officer,
you have to wait out here.
Surgery should take an hour.
There's no other exits.
Hey.
Is everything okay?
Uh, yeah.
Ultrasound
came back clear.
Doctor thinks that it was
just some heartburn.
So, they're gonna run some
blood tests just to be safe.
He getting his shattered arm
set?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I think
he could be innocent.
Don't even go there.
Look, he talked to me about
his case, and I think --
Who told you to talk to him?
That's not your job.
He is a cop killer, okay?
So just shut up
and guard him, okay?
Bulgogi tacos.
I didn't know what style
you liked, so I got two of each.
Kenton, how did
you find these?
I tapped into
the LA assistant hive mind.
The truck was on location
in Santa Clarita
serving a movie crew.
I drove over,
put on my headset,
and walked right up
like I was part of the crew.
So your tacos are courtesy
of the director
of "Murder Dance Party:
Part Three".
Damn, you are good.Mm-hmm.
No. I'm the best.
Oh.
Ooh!
Hmm. Cocky, too.
Alright. I like that.
But what I have for you now
is -- it's next level.
Are you up for it?
Bring it, Detective.
Alright, um, I have been looking
for this doll
that I had when
I was a little girl,
to give to my daughter.
But I can't remember
what it was called,
and I haven't been able to
find it anywhere.
But she was the first doll
that I ever saw
that had hair and skin tone
that was just like mine.
And she had this, um,
French-sounding name
with a pink parasol --
or was it yellow?
I'm on it.
Watch me do my thing.
What?
♪♪
Here.
I-I can't have these.
♪♪
Hey.
So, Grey talked to Leo's mom.
His home life
sounds like a real mess.
His parents aren't divorced.
His father died two years ago.
That's rough.
Hey. Here's
the weird thing --
he's been homeschooled
for over a year.
So he was making up
that whole story
about the princess classmate
who OD'd?
I don't know.
Okay, Leo.
Quest one complete.
How about we call this a victory
and you land?
The hero's journey never ends
after the first quest.
I was afraid you'd say that.
What's next?
You're a gamer. You know
it's not all easy stuff.
Eventually you get to
a boss battle.
A great beast you will struggle
to defeat.
Leo, how about we cut out
the windup
and you just go straight
for the pitch?
How do you feel about
alligators?
♪♪
Hey.
Thanks for coming in.
Yeah.
I just want to verify
a few things.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, Dez Robinson -- he works
for you, is that correct?
From time to time.
Yeah.
Okay. He said he worked
two nights ago.
Yeah,
sounds about right.
We had a construction job
down in Hawthorne.
Picked up the night shift
for a few extra bucks.
Any chance he checked
in and then maybe ducked
out for a few hours?
Nah, I was there.
I would've seen that.
You sure?
Because, uh, Dez is suspected
in a triple murder
that happened that night,
so anyone who helps him
would be considered
an accessory.
Hey. Hold on.
I had no idea about that.
I want no parts of that,
alright?
I thought he was just out here
cheating on his girlfriend.
I didn't know he was out here
killing people.
Does that mean you want to
amend your statement?
Hell yeah.
I'm gonna amend my statement.
Dez paid me 500 bucks
to clock him in
on the nights
that he needed an alibi.
Okay. So, to be clear,
Dez did not show up to work
two nights ago?
Right.
Oh, and...
he paid me yesterday
to clock him in
for tonight.
♪♪
Hey. Dez's alibi
fell apart.
Nice work.
So when his lawyer lands,
here's the plan --We don't have time
for a plan.
The crew has another target
lined up for tonight.
If we don't figure out
where they're hitting,
they're gonna drop
more bodies.
Let's never
do that again.
You're gonna need
a much bigger leash than that.
And tranquilizers, lot --
lots of tranquilizers.
Cupcake is a sweetheart.
Cupcake ate my Taser.
Thank you.
Okay, Leo.
Quest two is complete.
Funny coincidence --
aside from a reptile
straight out of "Jurassic Park",
we found a bunch of fentanyl
in the house.
Two quests.
Two drug arrests.
We're starting to sense
a pattern here.
Alligator guy had drugs?
It's a good thing
you caught him.
Do you wanna tell us what these
quests are really about?
Not right now.
Leo --
Relax. You'll get
your third quest soon enough.
♪♪
Officer Webb.
Find anything?
The stuff of nightmares.
Man lives like a pig.
So no gun?
Nah.
We need more leverage.
Something
that ties this guy
definitively to the home
invasions.
The only way we stop this crew
in time is if Dez flips.
What have you searched
so far?
We're going full
DEAR system.
You're off
to a good start.
Eliminating things
we don't have to search again.
What's next?
You know
what F.S.T.s are?
Yeah,
Field Sobriety Tests.
and when searching a house,
F.S.T. stands for
something else.
First, you get all the guys
from the outside
to come search inside,
and vice versa.
Fresh set of eyes.
Alright?
L-100, I need all units
from the outside
to come inside
for a sec.
Then you do
a Systematic grid search.
Ah. So Systematic search
is the "S."
What's the "T"?
Alright, everyone,
listen up.
I want everyone
who was searching outside
to swap with people
on the inside.
Then I want
a three-foot search grid.
And there's
a $100 gift card
for the first officer
who finds evidence
linking this guy to
our 2-11.
Got it?
Alright, let's go!
♪♪
The "T" is for
Treat it like a contest.
Cops love to compete,
and they'll push themselves
even harder if they know
there's something to win.
What are you doing here?
Um, why didn't you tell me
you were seeing your OB?
I-I didn't want to worry you
if it was nothing,
and -- and it was.
It was just a little
aggressive heartburn.
I don't care.
If you burp funny,
I wanna know.
He called you here,
didn't he?
And it wasn't about me.
Yes, ma'am. I, um --
I called them about Langston.
Are you trying to get everyone
in the LAPD to hate you?
Because that is
what is gonna happen
if you advocate
for a convicted cop killer.
I told you to drop this.
All due respect, if there is
even a sliver of a chance
that he is innocent,
it needs to be investigated.
Yeah, look.
That hardcore dude in there
is unrecognizable from the guy
that went in 18 years ago.
He's been institutionalized.
I've seen it a thousand times.
A nice haircut and a cute smile
does not mean he is innocent.
Yeah, and a conviction doesn't
mean that he's guilty, either.
I mean, I'm proof of that.
If I'd have stayed
in prison,
that's how
I would've ended up.
And now that I have
a platform
to help people
who are wrongfully accused,
I mean, I have to use it.
I thought you were trying to
"rebrand" yourself.
To -- To reclaim
your identity
separate from
your conviction.
If you tie yourself to Langston,
you will undo all of that.
Alright, look,
there is no reason
to go right to
the worst-case scenario.
Let James and I
talk to him,
just see what kind of
impression we get.
Just to see
if there's any merit.
Alright.
You got 15 minutes.
Okay.
Still waiting on
that third quest, Leo.
Unless you want to just skip it
and land?
You still up there, Leo?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm here,
just enjoying the view.
It's peaceful up here.
You know, we did
a little digging
after our last conversation.
Turns out Murray,
the guy with the alligator,
one of his known associates
is Brian Johst,
your mom's boyfriend.
I'm guessing they have
a little
distribution racket
running?
Yeah, and we'd bet money
that one of the dealers
they sell to
is the guy we arrested
in Quest One.
That's quite an epic tale.
Let's cut out this fantasy crap,
shall we, Leo?
We know you didn't send us
to that house
to avenge a classmate.
There is no classmate.
But I think there is a princess
you need us to save.
Your mom -- she has
a history of drug abuse,
but it seems like
she'd been clean for a while?
She relapsed
after my dad died.
Then she rallied,
got herself clean.
It was good,
like before.
Then she met Brian.
You have to get her
away from him.
He's killing her.
That's your third quest.
Leo out.
We have no evidence
tying Brian to the fentanyl.
We can't arrest him.
And Leo's got 40 minutes
before he runs out of fuel.
Yeah.
Tell me
you found something.
Some old gloves, possible
burglary tools, impact weapons.
Nothing that's gonna help us.
What's going on?
Dez is about to walk out of here
with his lawyer.
Right now,
all I can charge him with
is possession
of stolen property.
Can you stall them?
20 minutes.
Sorry, Sarge.
We've turned this place
upside down.
These tools here
are all we could find.
'Cause you're only human.
Excuse me?
L-100, I need 8706
at my location, Code 3.
Copy that.
8706?
Uh, why the hell
do we need him here?
You'll see.
Okay, taking your statement
into consideration...
And the few online articles that
we read about your case --
Come on, just -- you can just
tell me straight.
Can you get me outta here?
Way too early to tell.
But what I've read has
definitely triggered
some alarms.
I mean, it's clear
there were several
investigative discrepancies,
and clearly,
you were not given
adequate counsel.
So what do I do?
Let me make some calls.
There are a few lawyers I would
trust to take your case.
Pro bono?
Pro bono.
That's great.
But there are
no guarantees here, okay?
There's no promises,
just a little hope.
That's all I can handle.
This will be the hardest fight
of your life.
I'm ready.
I appreciate you both.
You.
♪♪
You listened.
It's been a long time since
anybody's done that.
♪♪
Thank you.
See, bomb sniffing dogs
don't look for bombs,
they look for bomb ingredients,
like gunpowder
from an illegal firearm.
♪♪
Come on, boy, you got this.
Are you kidding me?
Did you really just get
distracted by a squirrel?
Do you realize
how clichéd that is?
♪♪
He found something.
Okay.
Got him.
Oh, hey,
you just missed James.
He and Wesley went down
to the cafeteria
to make some calls.
They're gonna get Langston
an attorney.
I'll text them
and tell them
not to waste their time,
'cause a retrial
isn't gonna matter.
Why?
Sheriff's Department combed
through security footage
from the prison riot.
Your innocent man here
stomped a guard.
Is he okay?
No.
He is paralyzed
from the waist down.
They are charging Langston
with attempted murder
of a peace officer.
That's a 20-to-life
sentence.
Which is why a retrial
is pointless.
He's not getting out
of prison.
Yo, this system is a joke.
I mean, if Langston wasn't
wrongfully convicted
in the first place,
he wouldn't have spent
half his life stuck in prison,
wouldn't have been caught up
in that riot, thinking
the only way to survive
was to stomp a guard.
♪♪
What are you doing?
I'm gonna tell him
that it's over.
♪♪
How's Cupcake?
The alligator?
Yeah.
Fine.
You, on the other hand,
are screwed, my friend.
My officers found a stockpile of
fentanyl in your house.
Where'd you get it?
H-Has she seen a vet yet?
They --
She swallowed a Taser.
Hey, you are in a lot of
trouble, Murray.
You need to focus
on the drugs.
Now, we know you've been selling
to high school kids.
Who are you working with?
No one, man.
Look, this is
important, okay?
Cupcake has
a very specific diet.
I-I can write it down
for you.
Okay, I'll do you
one better.
I'll let you talk to the people
taking care of Cupcake
and make sure
she's all right.
But first, you need to
name your accomplices.
Deal.
Okay.
Murray flipped.
We got a warrant
on Brian Johst.
You want to serve it?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
♪♪
Attention, Airship Three,
I have a quest for you.
What is it?
Can you see your house
from up there?
Hold on.
♪♪
Thank you very much.
Come on, let's go.
♪♪
Hey, Young Hero,
are you seeing this?
Every second.
Great.
The quest is over.
I think it's time
to come down now.
Oh, thank God,
'cause I have been air-sick
for the past three hours,
and I --
Uh-oh.
What? What's wrong?
I'm out of gas.
♪♪
Come on, come on.
Yes.
That was -- Oh, wow.
Hi. Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
That was, uh...
That was intense.
Never do that again.
Yeah, the, um,
hero's journey is over.
Oh.
Not yet.
What?
You stole
a police helicopter, Leo.
You're under arrest.
♪♪
What'd he give us?
Everything.
Every job, every guy
on his crew.
And the location
of tonight's robbery?
Yeah, and they're supposed to
hit the house
within the hour.
♪♪
Give me the keys
and phone.
You know, nobody takes pride
in their work anymore.
Used to be
a getaway driver
was hyper-alert
during a robbery.
I blame social media.
Look, I don't know
what this is about,
but you got
the wrong guy.
No, we don't.
Dez told us
you'd be parked right here,
keeping a look-out.
He also said there's three guys
inside robbing the place.
Is he right?
Is there three men inside?
Answer quick, because if they
start killing people,
those murders are on you.
Yeah.
It's three guys, supposed to be
in and out in 30 minutes,
and they're 28 minutes in.
So, what was
the plan going in?
Where are
we gonna find 'em?
Master bedroom's upstairs.
That's where the safe is.
Don cracks the safe
while Terry loots
the rest of the bedrooms.
Stosh's job is to keep a gun on
the family downstairs.
Get out.
Come on.
Go that way.
♪♪
We can't go in hot
with a guy hovering
over the family
with a weapon.
So we go in
a different way.
♪♪
Alpha team set.
Someone's here.
♪♪
Delivery guy.
I'll get rid of him.
We didn't order anything!
Go away!
- Get down! Get down!
- Get down on the ground!
Don't move.
Man #2: Clear!
- All clear!
- Clear!
Hostages secure.
♪♪
Ugh!
Give me a bang!
♪♪
You okay?
You know it.
Hey.
Sheriff Department's here
to transport Langston
back to prison.
So we're free to go,
if you're ready.
I am.
Bloodwork came back clear.
That's great news.
No way!
Told you
I was no joke.
What?! I have not seen one of
these since I was 10.
Wh-Where did you
find this?
You can get anything
on the dark web.
Wow. Thank you.
You really are
the best assistant ever.
You don't lose him.
Actually, I have to
tender my resignation.
Hulu just bought
my pilot!
What? That's great.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Guess I need
my own assistant now.
Good luck
with the show.
And your baby.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Don't touch it.
Hey.
I'll go pull
the shop around.
So everything is fine.
Best bloodwork
she's ever seen.
I knew it would be.
Listen, I-I am sorry.
I should've
called you earlier.
But to tell you the truth,
I was terrified.
And I needed to pretend
that it was nothing
and if I called you,
I would have to admit
that it could be something.
And I-I get that,
but you shouldn't deal
with these things alone.
Look, trust me,
fear is the worst thing
to have to go through
by yourself.
Uh...
There's, uh, something
I haven't told you.
Um...I was diagnosed
with placenta previa
when I had Lila,
and I started hemorrhaging
late in the pregnancy.
Which is why you freaked out
about a little heartburn.
I should be happy,
you know,
planning her nursery
and buying clothes,
but I'm just terrified
something's gonna happen.
Maybe we can take this
one day at a time.
You know, whatever, we'll --
we'll -- we'll deal with it...
together.
I'm good with that.
So, what is the deal
with the creepy old doll?
She's not creepy.
Oh, no. All dolls
are inherently creepy.
Spoken like the father
of two boys.
Here, hold her.
Oh, I-I really don't want to.
Hold her!
Look at how cute
this is.
Come on.
Got all your stuff?
Yeah.
And your court summons?
But they took my police ID,
though.
The one you stole
to access the roof?
Not surprised.
Where did you get that, anyway?
I lifted it off some cop.
Uh, S-S-Smith? Schmitt?
Smitty?
Yeah.
You know him?
Well, look, thank you.
Not a problem.
Listen, if ever
you have a problem,
before you go stealing
any aircraft, just call me.
Just aircrafts?
Any vessel.
Any wheeled vehicle.
Or animal --
Basically, anything
you could ride in or on.
Deal. What if I have another
epic quest to go on?
Try the bus.
Okay, yeah.
That makes sense.
♪ Stay strong for me
and I'll stay strong for you ♪
♪ Summer is here
but it's slipping away ♪
♪ Why would we want
to waste a good day? ♪
Okay, I got it.
Yeah.
Yeah, look, so, um,
just give me some time,
and I'll get everything you need
over to you.
Yeah. Hey, look, man,
I-I really appreciate this,
and so does Mr. Bryant.
Alright. Bye.
What are you doing?
Wesley gave me a name
of a lawyer
willing to take
Langston's case.
Why? I thought we agreed
that it was over for that guy.
He -- He paralyzed a guard.
Right. And he should
be punished for that.
But he may not have killed
that cop 18 years ago,
and we owe it to that officer's
family to find the truth.
Because if Langston's innocent,
then that means
there's someone out there
right now
who got away with murder.
Who gets to sleep in his bed
every night,
gets to walk out of his front
door a free man every morning.
I can't imagine how hard
it must have been for you.
I was locked in a cell
for 541 days,
in a prison that was built
in the 1800s --
and, trust me, it hadn't
gotten nicer with age.
My best friend was dead.
I thought my life was over.
But you know what?
I got lucky, I got out,
and I got a second chance.
But the person
who murdered Patrick --
he's still out there.
And -- And no one
is looking for him,
because they still think
that I did it.
♪ And I'll stay strong for you
♪♪
You need a little help?
No.
I need lots of help.
I don't -- I don't know
what I'm doing.
Okay.
Show me what you got.
♪ It's one way how to deal
Hey. Ready to go?
Yeah. Can't wait
to get horizontal.
It's been a long day.
I've been doing
some thinking --
I've warned you
about that.
I helped Aaron out today,
just looking at a case.
I heard.
You think he's innocent?
Maybe.
I don't know for sure.
You know, what I do know
is he had a terrible lawyer.
I think when I get my license
back, I might want to --
You want to do even more
pro bono work.
Am I that predictable?
Yes, you are.
I always know you're gonna do
the selfless thing
because that's
the kind of man you are.
And you're okay with that?
Why? Because you're gonna make
even less money?
Why would I have
a problem with that?
Yeah.
♪♪
Hey. You walked Leo out?
Yeah, just left him
with his mom.
What you got there?
It's for
completing your quests.
Hey!
But you completed them
with me.
I know. I made a trophy
for myself, too.
Anyone else
have a crazy day?
You have no idea.
You know what?
Let's get changed,
grab a drink.
Yes.
- On Nolan.
- Whoa.
We're good for one. Then we need
to spring the nanny.
♪♪
Sorry, hold up.
I'm authorizing
all overtime.
There was an accident
at Animal Control,
and they need
all the help they can get.
What's going on?
Cupcake broke free.
Who's Cupcake?
♪♪