[ Rock music plays ]
Alright.
Sumatra Sunrise,
Harissa Honey,
Turmeric Latte.
I like them all.
They're very soothing.
Like the colors
you'd choose for a psych ward.
Do you want to go back
to the browns then?
I really don't.
Just paint it whatever you want.
It's yourapartment.
Yeah,
but this is your room.
You know, you should choose.
It's --
It's not mine, though.
It's...
Yeah.
Uh, what do you think?
Uh, oh, I think
you should hire a decorator.
And I think we really need to
get to the station.
The next 48 hours
are going to be crazy.
Nice to see you again,
Tamara.
Bye.
[ Water runs ]
Hey, do you think,
um, we're being silly --
you know, taking this long
to pick a color.Not at all.
Though I'd argue "we"
is the wrong pronoun to use.
Tamara settled on a color
two weeks ago.
And last week.
And Saturday.
You vetoed them all.
I did not.
I just -- I just really
want to make sure
that she's thinking
this through.
You know, this is her home now.
It's her safe space.
It needs to be perfect.
Mm.
Oh, hey.
Don't forget your bag.
Yeah.What the heck is in here?
Books.
Tim gave me a long list
of books to read
to help me become
a training officer.
According to him,
I have to up my Investigative IQ
if I'm gonna make T.O.
in a year.
[ Sighs ]
Is it weird for you that Tim
is officially no longer a T.O.?
No. I mean, I'm moving on
with my career.
And today so is he.
Plus you secretly love it
that technically
he's a rookie sergeant.
Is he?
I hadn't thought of that.
♪ Oh, whoa,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you like
I know you want me to do ♪
♪ Hey
So, uh, rumor is
I am getting a new rookie today.
Yeah, we need
to talk about him.
Okay.
That doesn't sound good.
[ Knock on glass ]
You wanted to see me,
sir?
Yeah.
I'm afraid I got a complaint
about your uniform.
Yeah. That Department-issued
sergeant's badge --
that won't do.
That is 80% tin.
But this is solid silver
and real gold.
Thank you.
Sgt. Grey:
See, you earned it.
I won't let you down.
Sure you will.
This is a hard transition.
You will fail
as much as you succeed.
And you are
starting your watch
on the craziest weekend
of the year.
I can handle it.
I've been a supervisor before.
Different animal.
T.O.s are drill sergeants.
Supervisors -- coaches.
Orange slices, got it.
Those stripes are Velcro,
Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
You'll do Roll Call today.
I'll go get up to speed.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Oh, uh,
w-what was my bad news?
Your new rookie
is Aaron Thorsen.
[ Laughs ] Poor thing.
If I had the same name
as a tabloid murderer,
I would definitely change it
immediately.
Especially if I was
joining the LAPD.
Yeah.
But he's theAaron Thorsen.
And he was exonerated.
Okay. So the LAPD is just
letting anybody in now?
No. Officer Thorsen had to sue
to get into the Academy.
But he earned solid scores
once there.
And now
he is your new rookie.
So, the question is:
Are you going to condemn him
before you meet him,
or give him five minutes
to prove he deserves to be here?
If he can't hack it,
I will cut him.
Lawsuit or no.
[ Sighs heavily ]
Oh, my God.
Do you know who that guy is?
Um...
Oh, that's the new rookie.
We should introduce ourselves.
Oh, no.
Do you honestly
not recognize him?
Is he not
the new rookie?
That's Aaron Thorsen.
Wha-- Rich kid.
TikTok famous
before he got arrested
for murdering
his roommate in Paris
while he was
studying abroad.
Right. Oh, right. God.
That trial went on forever.
Trialsplural.
The case was a mess.
The dynamics between
two of the investigators
really drove
a lot of the issues.
How do you know all that?
I taught myself French
so I could follow the coverage.
Of course you did.
Officer Thorsen.
Yes, ma'am.
I am Detective Nyla Harper,
your training officer.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.I would hold off
on that sentiment.
I'm gonna make this
very hard on you.
You are getting the equivalent
of five minutes today
to prove to me
why your infamy
doesn't make you a liability
to this Department,
and a threat to my safety.Yes, ma'am.
I will put your past
front and center
because that
is what the public will do
when we are
out on the street.
So you better be squared away,
five minutes.
Or your shift
will be over by lunch.
Yes, ma'am.
Mnh-mnh-mnh.
Rookies sit
in the front row.
Find me after.
[ Officers conversing
indistinctly ]
Sgt. Grey: Alright.
As many of you know --
we have a new sergeant
in the field today.
Everyone,
Sergeant Tim Bradford.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Okay. Okay. Thank you.
First up --
we've got a new rookie --
Officer Thorsen.
Stand up.
Now, there's
a traditional introduction
for probationary officers,
but you are anything
but traditional.
So I'm giving you 20 seconds
to introduce yourself
before the rumor mill ramps up.
Go.
[ Clears throat ]
I know there's nothing
that I can say in 20 seconds
that'll change
the way you all view me.
It's my actions
that will define me.
And I promise to always
have your back,
and I will always strive to tip
the scales towards justice...
...because I know what
it's like when they're
tipped the other way.
And I want to make
something very clear --
Officer Thorsen
was found not guilty.
He survived the Academy.
He earned the right to be here.
Till Harper cuts him.[ Laughter ]
Sit down.
Alright. Down to business.
This weekend's gonna suck.
We got the Dodgers
in the playoffs,
six different concerts,
a fancy art exhibit opening,
and the Getty Gala
tomorrow night.
Now, every A-list celebrity
with a pulse
is gonna be there
in all their blinged out glory.
Paparazzi are out
in full force.
And we're getting requests
for additional security
faster than
we can process them.
Now, I've only seen the
potential for this much chaos
one other time in my life,
and that was at an FOB in Iraq.
So...good luck out there.
Dismissed.
♪♪
Sgt. Grey: Were you trying
to get them to quit?
Just keeping it real.
Not enough orange slices?
Let's go.
Hey. What do you think
of wallpaper?
Love it!
Because I'm not qualified
to hang it,
so you'd have to
hire someone else.
Mean.
Lucy, you are the most
insightful person I know,
you have to see
what's going on here --
Why you can't decide how
to decorate Jackson's room.
Until you make it okay
to move on,
Tamara will never feel
like she belongs there.
[ Engine revving ]
Whoa. Whoa!
She better be in labor.
Control, 7-Adam-15,
we have a reckless driver,
doing 70 down Hope.
[ Siren wailing ]Possible 23-152.
Plate: Three-Ocean-Edward-
Boy-Zero-Five-Eight.
Dispatch:
Plate comes back clear
and valid out of
Torrance to Acme industries.
Oh, u-um...
you mind if I practice T.O.'ing
during this traffic stop?
You wanna
"work on your act" with me?
Like I'm
a no-nothing rookie?
Yeah.
Unless that would bother you?
No. Not at all.
Show me what you got.
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]
Alright.
How do we approach
a vehicle, Boot?
Boot? Really?
Yeah. Sorry.
As soon as it came out --Can we just --
Work with me.
It sounded harsh even
just coming out of my --
I feel terrible.
I'm starting again.
How do we approach a vehicle,
Officer Chen?
[ Chuckles ]
Using "Contact-Cover."
Good work, Officer Chen. You
will take the Cover position.
Copy that.
Hey.
You're doing really great.
Thanks.
[ Chuckles ]
Good morning, Officer.
Morning, ma'am.
You know why we pulled you over?
I was speeding.
70 in a 40 zone.
It would be criminal
to drive this car
at 40 miles an hour.
The rules are the same
for all cars.
No matter
how expensive they are.
Officer Chen,
you're not in position.
Now, may I see your license
and registration, please?
You could run me, but then
it's gonna be this whole thing.
So how about
I just say sorry and go?
License and registration.
Now, please.
[ Bag unzips ]
[ Sighs ]
Promise you won't freak out.
I promise.
Okay, Claire Ivey. Why don't you
step out of the vehicle for me?
So I can be sure
you won't freak out
and drive away
while I run your documents.
Sure thing.
Thank you.
Mmm. I bet he looks
even better out of that uniform.
What's he gonna find
when he runs you?
A white whale.
[ Static hisses ]
Control, patch me
through to 7-Adam-100.
The first lesson of
being a good supervisor --
do not get to
the crime scene first.
Getting to a scene first
can hurt their confidence
and tells them
that you don't trust them.
Yeah --Dispatch:
7-Adam-100, I have 7-Adam-15.
[ Static hisses ]Patch him through.
Uh, sir, I just pulled over
a driver for speeding,
a Claire Ivey.
She has
no outstanding warrants,
but she is suspected
in a dozen
multimillion dollar thefts
stretching back 20 years
from L.A. to Hong Kong.
The Regency diamond heist.
[ Static hisses ]
Nolan, Claire Ivey
has been a target of
this Department
for over 10 years.
Detective Lopez got close
to catching her in 2016,
but a witness disappeared.
Uh, it can't be a coincidence
that she's in town on the
craziest weekend of the year.
What do you want me to do?
Cite her and let her know
she's officially on our radar.
And, Nolan, impress on her
that she should
get her ass out of town ASAP.
Now is the time that
he tells me to leave town ASAP.
Well, if he does,
you should listen.
So?
Suspected in 40 high-end
robberies, arrested for none.
I'm impressed.
What brings you to L.A.?
The weather.
Well, I hear it's going to be
even nicer someplace else.
Maybe you should try there
instead.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
So, does that mean
that I'm free to leave?
You have a nice day.
Thank you.
♪♪
What do you think?
[ Vehicle engine starts,
tires squeal ]
I think that I have
a girl crush.
That's fair.
[ Static hisses ]Control, 7-Adam-19.
Show us on a welfare check
at 3312 Bronson.
So, tell me,
Officer Thorsen,
what are you gonna do if this
welfare check recognizes you?
What I already do:
Nothing.
And if she refuses to deal with
you because you're a murderer?
I'm not a murderer, ma'am.
I was found innocent.
Surely you're not naive to the
reality of false accusations.
Especially against people
who look like us.
How I feel personally about
your case is irrelevant here.
My job is to assess your ability
to become a police officer.
If every single call
is about you,
then [chuckles] this is gonna
make it a lot harder to succeed.
[ Doorbell rings ]
Police!
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Step back.
Radio it in.
[ Clears throat ][ Static hisses ]
7-Adam-uh-19,
we have signs of violence
on scene.
Making entry.
[ Door creaks ]
♪♪
[ Sniffs ]
[ Sniffing ]
Yeah. That's gas.
Holster your weapon.
One spark,
this whole house goes up.
[ Static hisses ]Control,
alert LAFD and SoCal
we got a gas leak
at 3312 Bronson.
Body.
♪♪
[ Coughing,
breathing rapidly ]
[ Soft music plays ]
There's no pulse.
[ Coughs ]
Alright, come on.
Go. Get out of here.
[ Coughing ]
[ Coughs ] Go!
Control, 7-Adam-19,
update this event to a 187,
alert Homicide and a supervisor.
[ Inhales sharply,
coughs ]
A murder on your first call
is a bad sign, five minutes.
♪♪
What do we have?Victim is Michaela Faris,
32 years old.
Celebrity stylist.
Blunt force trauma to the head.
And it looks like
whoever hit her
turned on the gas
to make sure she stayed dead.
Where's your rookie?
Did he puke?
Yeah. But it was more
than just the gore.
You know,
it seems to have
brought back
some uncomfortable memories.
I don't know. It almost feels
like he shouldn't be a cop.
Luckily he has the best
T.O. in the business
to help him through it.
He can say that
now that I've been promoted.
Will you stay focused
on the scene, Sergeant?
[ Siren wailing ]Yes, sir.
What's next?
Well, we should canvass
while LAFD clears it.
"We"?
You're supervisor on scene.
A coach, not a player.
You should stay here,
coordinate response.
Right. Harper, grab your Boot,
go canvass the neighbors.
Yes, sir.
Harper.Hey.
You get anything more
on Ivey?
Car envy.[ Cellphone rings ]
Excuse me. I got --
Bailey, hey.
John.Hey. We have a body inside.
Can you get the gas off
from out here
so we can
preserve the crime scene?
Absolutely.
Mike, will you go take a look?
Uh...how are you?
Good. Uh, you?
No. Good. Yeah.
I'm -- I'm -- I'm really good.
Uh, I'm -- I'm Lucy.
We --
I know. We met at the, um --
the wedding.
Right.
Yeah. Of course.
I should go help the guys.
They're useless without me.
Right. No. Of course.
Uh, uh, great to see you.
You too.
[ Police radio chatter ]
What happened
with you two?
Oh. Nothing.
Uh, this is the first
I've seen her since the wedding.
I mean, we texted a few times
back and forth
after I got back
from Guatemala --
but then
there was the funeral.
And really didn't seem the right
time to start something.
So I -- Once I found my feet,
I just figured she moved on.
Yeah. Well, I'd say
she's still kind of into you.
You should
ask her out again.
Look, I know
I screwed up back there.
It was just
a little overwhelming.
All this time you've been
trying to be a cop,
it never occurred to you
that you might have to
walk into a murder scene?
I thought I was better.
I haven't had an episode
like that in a while.
But this is good.
I found a trigger,
and I'm gonna work through it.
This is not a therapy session,
four minutes.
This is people's lives.
Work through your issues
on your own time.
Narrator: And it was on
that cold Paris night
that Aaron Thorsen's
life changed forever,
accused by French prosecutors
of committing the gruesome
murder of his roommate
and long-time friend
Patrick --
Jack is
finally, finally down.
Who knew rocking him to sleep
in this would actually work?
Of course it works.
It's an unwashed hoodie
reeking of the person
he loves most
in the world.
[ Chuckles ]
You know you're gonna
be wearing that every
day from now on, right?
We should try to
get some sleep while we can.
I just need to finish watching
this episode.
[ Dramatic music plays]
Why are you watching
a docuseries on Aaron Thorsen?
He's Harper's new rookie.
I leave for a month, and they
start letting in French killers.
He's American.
And he was found not guilty.
After he was found guilty.
Yeah.
The defense was a joke.
If I'd have been his lawyer,
wouldn't have gone to trial.
[ Jack crying ]
I got this.
You, get some sleep.
[ Cellphone vibrating ]
Hey.
Hey. It's John and Lucy.
Is this a good time?
Does that
even exist anymore?
How's the baby?
He's great.
A bit of a nightmare.
I haven't slept in two days.
Yikes. Okay.
We'll make this fast.
Uh, you worked a case involving
Claire Ivey a few years ago.
Let me guess,
she's our new captain.
What? No. But she is in town.
We pulled her over this morning.
I've never been so grateful
for maternity leave.
Is she that bad?She's that good.
Claire will pull
some impossible heist
and leave you
looking like fools.
Just like she did to me.
Okay. Any insights?
She doesn't carry a crew.
Always hires locals
for the job.
Getaway driver, hacker,
muscle, demolitions expert.
Back in the day, I put together
a list of people she likes.
Check that file.Will do.
Thank you for your help.
A-And get some sleep.Thank you.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Oh, Bailey.
Hey. Ask her out.
I...
Hey.
Um...
She had to pee.
We all good inside?
Yeah.
We turned the gas off --
the house is venting --
I'd give 10, 15
before you let anyone in.
Okay. Great. Thank you.
Uh, Bailey.
I think you're great,
and I feel like we didn't
really, uh, get a chance
because of just every--
everything that happened.
And I feel like I would l-live
the rest of my life
full of regret
if I didn't take every advantage
of the universe apparently
pushing us back together,
a-and -- and just see
if you wanted to try again.
You know? Just a date. I'm not
gonna ask you to marry me.
Which, you know,
I don't have to say that.
I'm suddenly nervous.
I'm gonna stop talking.
Well, I can't have you living
with regret for all of eternity.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Uh, how's, um --
Tonight?Tonight. Great.
I'll text you.
Tim: Alright. Claire Ivey
doesn't get out of bed
for anything less than
a $5-million payday.
The problem is: There are
a dozen targets in L.A.
this weekend
that meet that criteria.
Including the Rothko exhibit
at LACMA and the Getty Gala.
Well, that Gala is gonna be
crawling with private security.
You know, the chaos of this
weekend could just be a cover
to hit a traditional target
while we're stretched thin.
Or she could be trying
to hit a private home.
I mean, I used to party with
kids in high school
whose parents had millions in
cash and jewelry in their homes.
The challenge is a part
of the thrill for her.
After all these years,
I'd think Claire would want
something worthy of her skill --
not just a payday.
Do we know
where she is now?
Yeah.
Hiding in plain sight.
Booked a suite
at a hotel in Century City.
What about her crew?
Did we run that list of
names Lopez gave us?
No, we don't have to.
Head of security for the hotel
is ex-LAPD.
We managed to I.D. her crew
from the elevator cam.
Sgt. Grey: Jamie Carr.
Evan Rando.
Sadi Ling.
Allan Gibson.
First non-binary person to hack
the New York Stock Exchange.
Explosives expert --
Learned the demolitions trade
from her family business
bringing down
condemned buildings.
Now she blows safes.Gun for hire.
Former British SAS
turned private contractor.
Getaway driver.
Was an up and comer
on the NASCAR circuit
until he failed
a string of drug tests.
What's the game plan,
Sergeant Bradford?
Well, there's no sense
in being covert.
She knows we're onto her.
So I'd put black and whites
on her hotel,
and on every person
in her crew.
Let them see us.
Maybe one of them
will get cold feet,
she'll have to
call it off.
Nolan, Chen,
she's already met you,
so park yourselves
outside her hotel.
Harper,
you want in on this?
Uh, yeah. But Officer Thorsen
isn't ready yet.
I can handle it,
ma'am.
That is my call,
and I say that you can't.
So you will be working the front
desk for the rest of your shift.
I can't prove myself to you
if I'm not with you.
You can't
get me killed either.
Alright.
Let's get back out there.
[ Officers conversing
indistinctly ]
You still looking
for wallpaper?
No. I am trying to figure out
where Claire got the dress
she was wearing
in that surveillance photo.
Found it.
Ugh, it's so expensive.
She's a criminal,
not a role model.
Who says
she can't be both?
She is brilliant,
career-oriented --
Evil.
[ Scoffs ] Listen.
Her drive, my morality, we could
solve the world's problems.
Oh, hey! Where are you
taking Bailey tonight?
Oh, um...Earthing.
Ben recommended it,
so if nothing else,
it'll be expensive.
You're nervous.
I know.
I-I like her.
She's just --Oh, there's Claire.
♪♪
[ Groans ]
You know the spa here
is amazing.
You really should try it.
Oh. So while we get a massage,
you'll, what, steal a Monet?
A Monet?
What am I, a teenage girl from
the '80s decorating my room?
But there is a Jeff Koons
at the Broad that would look
phenomenal at my house in Vail,
so [clicks tongue]
I bet.
But you've hit museums before.
You're looking
for something new.
Someone has been
doing their homework.
Yes, I have.
Thank you.
So, if you're not into Monets,
what is it?
You can't honestly think
you're going to stop me.
I mean, I've gone up against
the best law enforcement
agencies in the world.
Well,
if you're so confident,
why don't you just
give us a hint?
I know you love
a challenge.
Okay. Here's your hint:
By the end of the day
tomorrow,
I will be buying
a private island
and you'll be doing paperwork
and feeling sad.
So the heist is tomorrow?
Sure.
Or I'm just messing with you.
Have a lovely evening.
♪♪
Oh, hey.
How was the, uh, front desk?
Great. How was the stakeout?
Do you need something from me?
Yeah. I heard the front desk
was anything but great.
How many people asked
if you were a murderer?
Nine.
Uh-huh.
And TMZ showed up?
Briefly.
That's a problem,
don't you think?
No. Not for me, ma'am.
I can handle it.
Unless you're gonna cut me
from the program.
No.
I'm not gonna fire you.
No. I don't have to.
'Cause you are
gonna go home tonight,
and you are not
gonna sleep.
'Cause you are gonna keep
thinking about that woman's body
and the panic that you felt
when we found her.
And you will realize that you
are going to feel that panic
every day at this job.
And then you'll come in
early tomorrow -- and quit.
And if you don't quit,
thatis when
I will fire you.
[ Soft music plays ]
That's not fair --
I am doing you a favor.
There is honor
in resigning.
In realizing that
you are not up for this.
But if you get fired
from this job,
what comes next, hmm?
The embarrassment,
the shame, the ridicule.
And, Officer Thorsen,
haven't you been through enough
ridicule for one lifetime?
[ Breathes deeply ]
Right.
We're getting off track.
These are the facts we know.
Aaron and Patrick
were roommates,
studying abroad in Paris.
Yeah,
but not just roommates.
Friends who had known each other
since childhood.
Right.
But then Patrick brings home
a girl from the club
one night.
Mm-hmm.
After a few hours,
she leaves.
We know she leaves
because of the security footage
from across the street.
And the next morning,
Aaron wakes up,
goes to the bathroom,
finds Patrick's body
on the tile floor
with his throat cut open.
Or Aaron was the one
who slit Patrick's throat,
after she left.W-- And then waited till
the next day to call the cops?
No, no, no.
She did it.
Or her jealous boyfriend,
whose whereabouts
were never established.
And Aaron
somehow heard nothing?
He was knocked out
on painkillers.
You saw the texts.
By the end,
Aaron hated Patrick.
No, look.
Texts mean nothing.
They were roommates,
they argued.
The media
was trying to paint Aaron
as some spoiled kid
who committed murder
because he didn't want to
do his share of the chores.
Or because he did them
so badly.
Okay. Loading the dishwasher
can be complicated.
[ Jack crying ]
We are so stupid.
We could've showered.
We could've changed clothes.
We could've slept.
What is wrong with us?
Am I interrupting?
[ Exhales sharply ]
Please, interrupt.
College is so hard.
Um...
I'm -- I'm sorry.
I've been so picky
about the paint color.
It's stupid.
Whatever, it's cool.
No. It's not.
I think I've just been having,
like, a really hard time,
because...
[ Soft music plays ]
You know,
it makes it real, that...
[ Inhales shakily ]
...that he's never coming home
and...
I'm sorry.
I know.
[ Breathes deeply ]
Every time
I change something,
it just feels like
I'm erasing him.
I want to be happy
that I'm living here...
...but I can't stop feeling
guilty that he's not.
He would want you here.
He would want something good
to come out of this.
This is good.
And he would mock us,
endlessly.
I mean, look at this place.
[ Laughs ]
It's kinda growing on me.
Yeah, like a fungus.
Please. Do whatever you want
in this room.
Whatever I want?
Yes?
[ Laughs ]
[ Sighs ]
I mean, yes. Yes.
Let's think about it.
[ Doorbell rings ]
Hi.
Come in.
Thanks.
You look beautiful.
I'd better. My entire closet
is on my bedroom floor.
I spent two hours looking
for the perfect outfit --
which said interested
but not desperate.
Hot but not too hot.
Mission accomplished.
You look very handsome.
Thank you.
Um, first thing I put on.
God, it must be nice
to be a man.
So where are we going?
A new restaurant
in Silver Lake.
Apparently all their entrées
are made from mung beans.
Cool.
Um...what's a mung bean?
I believe
it's a legume of a sort.
I think -- Honestly,
I-I picked it
just so
I would appear hip.
Mm. I've dated hip guys.
It's exhausting.
Oh.
But I'm sure
the place'll be great.
Okay, um...
How about
I give you the option?
Uh, we can go
eat mung beans --
So delicious.
Or -- how would you feel
about going on a stakeout?
Oh, hell yeah.
[ "Irresistible" plays ]Okay. Let's do this.
Yes.
♪ Help myself
♪ Can't take my eyes off you
Oh, finally.
Here we go.
Thank you.You're allowed to drink
on a stakeout?
Cops have all the fun.Oh. I'm not on duty.
There's cars waiting
at every exit
to follow her
the second she leaves.
She?
Mm.
Okay.
Over my left shoulder.
Mm-hmm.Tall blonde, great dress.
I don't know how
to tell you this.
But that's my sister.
[ Spits ]
I'm --
[ Laughing ] I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
[ Coughs ]
Oh, my God, your face.
That was convincing.
Or maybe
you are just too trusting.
♪ Till we hanging at the top
Fancy seeing you here,
Officer Nolan --
or can I call you John?
What kind of
alleged master thief would I be
if I didn't do my homework?
[ Chuckles ]
He's divorced. One kid.
Moved here two years ago
from Foxburg, Pennsylvania,
to become a cop,
and you have been
in the headlines ever since.
But, you, I-I don't know.
And you won't.
Who's your friend
in the silky shirt?
He's not one of your crew --
we've I.D.'d them already.
Unless you need someone even
more specialized for this job.
Perhaps a pilot?
Expert spelunker?
He's a dentist.
Well, it's getting late.
I should get to bed.
It is a busy day tomorrow.
Enjoy those drinks.
See you in the morning.
Probably not.
Really nice to meet you.
♪ Can't help myself
Well, I guess
that stakeout's over.
Yes. The stakeout's
definitely over.
But that doesn't mean
that the date has to be.
No. It doesn't.
♪ You got that irresistible
♪ Ooh
Is this a sneaking out
full of regret thing,
or a letting me sleep
thing?
Letting you sleep thing.Oh, well.
In that case, I'm awake.
I know it's early, I have
a capoeira class to teach.
I'd ask to join you, but I don't
think you should see me
fall on my ass
till our second date.
Second?
Technically,
this is date number three.
Oh. Is it too early
to ask for date number four?
Let me get some coffee
in me first.
I'll call you later.Okay.
Bye.
[ Knock on door ]You got a minute, sir?
Sure.
Where's your rookie?Oh. In a perfect world,
he is about to walk in here
and resign.
I want you
to not stop him.
I heard that you asked
for him to be assigned here.
I did. A wise captain
once taught me that
there's value in having rookies
with unique perspectives.
With all due respect, sir,
there is unique,
and then
there's Aaron Thorsen.
Look, you need to --
Who clearly isn't
walking in here to resign.
Man: Hey, Aaron.
Good morning.
Why are you dressed?
Didn't I tell you
what would happen to you
if you didn't
turn in your papers?
Then cut me.
I know you think I'm just
some privileged train wreck
who sued his way into the
Department to play dress up,
but I'm not.
I'm here
because I have to do this.
Because what happened to me
was so awful,
I need to make sure it
doesn't happen to anyone else.
And if you block my path here,
then I'll go to Long Beach.
And if they bounce me,
then I'll try San Diego.
Then Modesto or Stockton
and Fresno, Bakersfield --
until someone
gives me a chance.
♪♪
Because I'll do whatever
it takes to be a cop.
[ Groans ]
♪♪
Alright, five minutes.
Go set up our shop.
If you are this committed,
I might as well make sure
that you are well-trained
before you end up
at a lesser department.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
♪♪
The night shift said you
were at the hotel last night.
Yeah. Bailey and I
had dinner at the bar.
Oh.
Two birds. One stone.
How'd it go?With Claire? Or Bailey?
Either? Both?
Claire is definitely planning
on robbing something today.
Yeah.
And Bailey is...
[ Laughs ] Nice.
Yeah. No. I know.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
Ah. Speaking of.
"Thank you again
for a fantastic night.
I had a lovely time, but I don't
think this is gonna work.
Sorry."
I don't understand.
Listen.
As someone who has
been broken up with by text,
I feel your pain.
Yeah. Seriously, though,
I mean, we had an amazing night.
I d-- I d--
What the hell?
This is...
I'm gonna call her.
Should I call her?
Tim: 7-Adam-15, go to Channel
Nine for a status report.
[ Static hisses ][ Sighs ]
No sign of Claire yet.
Um, what about
the rest of her team?
They're having brunch
together.
Brunch? You think
they're messing with us?
100%.
And that makes me nervous.
Here she comes.
Oh,
that is so unfortunate.
You know, as a practice,
you should really pay
those tickets promptly.
On the bright side,
it does match.
Cute.
But you don't actually think
that's gonna stop me, right?
Well. It doesn't matter...
who did what.
My backup plans
have backup plans.
[ Engine starts ]
See ya.
[ Engine revving ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
Sergeant Bradford,
Claire just left the hotel
on a black motorcycle, heading
south down Avenue of the Stars.
I think they're
making their move.
Surveillance teams,
get ready.
[ Brakes hiss ]I've lost eyes on --
Somebody get in there.
All units, move in.
[ Tires screech ]
[ Siren wailing ]
Where'd they go?In the bus.
[ Tires screech ]
♪♪
[ Horn honks in distance ]
[ Water dripping ]
♪♪
Control, show us
Code 6 at 3312 Bronson.
A neighbor reports someone
entering our crime scene.
Who are we gonna find
inside?
It's either a burglar
knowing the homeowner is dead,
or the killer came back
to see what the police took
or left behind.
At my scene, there was a
paparazzi climbing the skylight
to get pictures while
the police were still there.
♪♪
[ Door creaking ]
[ Clattering in distance ]
♪♪
Police!
Show me your hands.
Oh, my God!
Hands up.
Turn around.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm Leilani. I'm Michaela's
assistant. I need her laptop.
We are T-minus six hours
to red carpet.
And I have a dozen clients
to dress before the Gala.
A laptop wasn't found
at the house.
I reviewed
the evidence logs last night
while I was working
the front desk.
No.
It has to be here.
She didn't go
anywhere without it.
And if I can't track down
Emma's choker,
I might as well change my name
and go into witness protection.
Wait.
Michaela was coordinating the
jewelry deliveries for the Gala.
Yeah.[ Chuckles ]
I know what the heist is.
[ Wolf Alice's "Smile" plays ]
Whenever there's
an awards show or gala,
celebrities borrow tens of
millions of dollars worth
of bracelets, earrings,
and necklaces
to bling out their gowns.
They're delivered by
an armored car before the event,
and then picked up again
right afterwards.
Claire must've killed Michaela
to get the delivery schedule.
And if she wants
to maximize the score,
she'll hit the armored car
right at the beginning.
♪ I scope it out,
then I throw myself into it ♪
♪ I ain't ashamed in the fact
that I'm sensitive ♪
♪ I believe that it is
the perfect adjective ♪
♪ I wear my feelings
on my sleeve, I suggested it ♪
♪ It serves me better
than to swallow in a sedative ♪
♪ I am what I am,
and I'm good at it ♪
♪ And you [ Tires screech ]
♪♪
[ Taser fires,
electricity zaps ]
♪♪
[ Shotgun cocks ]Put it down on the ground.
[ Tires screeching ]
♪♪
[ Gun cocks ]
Claire! Stop!
[ Gunshots ]
Ugh!
[ Groaning ]
♪♪
It's over, Claire.
Throw your gun out
and come on out.
I don't see myself
doing that.
Oh, now,
I never took you for a quitter.
I'm not a quitter.
I'm just not interested
in prison.
See, now, I thought
you would look at that
like your next challenge.
Escaping from prison?
That can't be as hard as
breaking into the Vatican.
You pulled that off
well enough.
Allegedly.
Allegedly. Right.
So, what's it gonna be?
You coming out?
Alright. Okay.
I'm giving up.
♪♪
[ Groaning ]
Keep your hands
where I can see them.
Turn around.
Put them behind your back.
Guess I underestimated you,
huh?
Oh, don't feel too bad.
Everyone does.[ Handcuffs click ]
Ow!
Sorry.
Okay. Let's go.
What happened today can't
happen again if you expect
to keep those stripes.
I stepped up.
I took charge.
You put yourself
in the center of the action.
It was the best use
of my skills.
It wasn't a tactical move,
Tim.
When push came to shove,
you just didn't trust
anyone else to do it.
Control freaks
don't make good sergeants.
Look, I know you've got
decades more experience --
Whoa. Hey. Wh--
A decade.
Okay.
But I got my own.
And directing the action
from a distance works for you.
I don't know
if it'll ever work for me.
I need to find my own way
of being a sergeant.
Fair enough.
Anything else?
Yeah.
It's important to give praise.
An attaboy from the boss
goes a long way.
[ Groans ]
It's against my nature...
but I will give it
a shot.
Make sure you
check the shop thoroughly
after you turn in
your war bags.
Yes, ma'am.
Detective Harper --
Can I ask you a favor?
Do you think you can
give me another nickname
rather than five minutes?Why?
'Cause that's about
how long Patrick was alive
after his throat was cut.
He crawled
out of the shower.
Looking for help.
Looking for me.
If I had just woken up,
he might still be alive.
I'm sorry.
I didn't -- I didn't know.
Yeah.
Look. I'm not looking
for any special treatment.
I just --Hey, don't worry about it.
After your solve today,
you get a little more leash.
And besides, coming up
with nicknames is fun for me.
[ Chuckles ]
Yes, ma'am.
I look forward to hearing
what you come up with.
♪ I was afraid of me
♪ I was afraid to see
what I'd become ♪
[ Door closes ]
♪ Well, now there's no you
to run to ♪
♪ What have I done?
What are you doing?
Uh, I am...
paying you back.
By going
with booties again?
I am disappointed.
I thought
you were more original.
It has been
a busy couple of days.
Plus I -- I accidentally
ordered twice, so...
You're welcome.
♪ Ready to overload
Okay. I'm gonna go,
leave you to it.
Hey, um...
[ Chuckles ] Yeah?
♪ Even when you tell lies,
tell lies ♪
You and Nolan --
you did good work today.
♪ You tell lies, tell lies
I've been told
that it's important
for a supervisor
to give praise.
Oh.
Well, thank you.
What else do you appreciate
about me?
That you know
when not to push your luck.
Yes. Okay. Good night.
Good night.
[ Chuckles ]
♪ I'll be here for you,
for years to come ♪
[ Cellphone chiming ]
Why isn't it on vibrate?
Go! Go! Go! Go!
It's gonna wake him up.
Don't wake up, don't wake up,
don't wake up.
♪ I'll be here for you,
for years to come ♪
[ Both sigh heavily ]
Thank God.
Yes!
They caught Claire Ivey!
[ Jack crying ]
♪ For years to come [ Sighs ]
♪ You-ou-ou
♪ You-ou-ou-ou-ou
You still love me, right?
♪♪
♪ No matter the distance,
wherever you are ♪
[ Furniture scraping ]
Tamara? Do you need help?
Tamara: Nope.[ Chuckling ] Okay.
[ Scraping continues ]
♪♪
♪ And I'll be here for you
Are you sure?
Okay, I'm done.
Promise me
you won't be mad.
Of course. I-I promise.
Okay. Uh...
♪ I'll be here for you,
for years to come ♪
♪ You-ou-ou
♪ You-ou-ou-ou-ou
♪ I'll be here for you...
Do you like it?
Uh...
[ Exhales sharply ]
No. I...
I love it.
♪ Even in death,
I hope you always know ♪
♪ That I was here for you
♪♪
♪ And I'll be here for you,
for years to come ♪
I know breaking up over text
isn't super mature.
No. It's -- It's fine.
I-I just wanted to make sure
it wasn't something I did.
It's not you.
I-I know that's a cliché,
but I-I really mean it.
You're -- You're great.
You're funny and handsome.
Warm. Smart.
Confused.
It's just --
I'm good at a lotta things.
But I am terrible
at relationships.
And they all go
the same way.
We'll start dating.
You'll open up.
I'll distract you
with jokes
so you don't notice
that I'm keeping you away,
until you get tired
of my bull
and you tell me
this one-sided relationship
isn't working
and I'll tell you,
"Well, this is who I am,
take it or leave it."
And you'll leave it.
So, you know,
I thought I'd skip to the end.
Wow.
That sounds like a lot.
Well, that's me.
I'm a lot.
Yeah, thing is,
I-I'm not believing it.
I mean, that you're bad
at relationships --
totally believable.
By your own admission,
you've never --
never actually been in one.
Which is fine.
But I am standing here as living
proof that people can change.
Who you were
up until this very moment
is not who you have to be
moving forward.
So, really,
the question here is:
Do I make you want to show up
differently?
And...so that you know,
if you say that I do...
I'm all in.
Well...
when you put it that way.
♪ I'll be here for you,
for years to come ♪
♪ You-ou-ou
[ Applause ]
♪ You-ou-ou-ou-ou
♪♪