♪ How I was going to part?
I'm not bitter, bitter ♪
♪ No, no, I swear
♪ I'm better, better now
♪ You're gone
Come on.
We gotta get to work.
She'll be here.
Seriously.
We gotta go.
She'll be here.
[ Chuckles ]
♪ How I was going to part?
[ Horn honks ]
Hey!
Watch it!
Oh.[ Tires squealing ]
[ Music stops ]
[ Laughs ]
[ Sighs ]
Isn't she pretty?
My first car.
Uh...my car
was your first car.
I mean, if we're including cars
I've stolen,
this is probably,
like, my fifth.
What?
Joke.
The seized car auction was
definitely the way to go.
I got such a good deal.
You are gonna take it
to the mechanic, though, right?
You never know what these cars
have been through.
Yeah. Tim set me up
with this guy.
- What? He did?
- Yeah.
Oh, you have a heart
after all.
Oh, relax, okay?
It was purely self-interest.
You would be a total drag
to ride with
if she died in a fireball
of mangled metal on the 405.
[ Scoffs ]
Joke.[ Dog barking, panting ]
What's going on?
[ Barking continues ]
♪
I am not getting
my new car back, am I?
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
[ Mondo Cozmo's "Come On"
plays ]
♪
♪ I was the silence
in the desert ♪
Why exactly do they call it
"Day in the Hole"?
Because any day on the job,
there are "holes" in staffing --
but typically,
it's only for a day,
and it's always within
the county of Los Angeles.
But you pissed off
your union president so badly,
he catapulted you
all the way to the border.
What can I say?
I'm a bit
of an overachiever.
But we are making
a vacation out of it
with Ellroy and Nell,
because we're "roll with it"
kind of people.
Damn right we are.
♪ There's a fire
in the sunrise ♪
♪ Hello, hello
♪ I'm the rider of the storm
♪ Come on, come on
♪ They'll be staring
at the skyline ♪
♪ Hello, hello
♪ And we'll watch
this city burn ♪
Hey!
[ Engine shuts off,
music stops ]
[ Chuckling ] Hey.
Welcome to
this little oasis.
Uh, where,
I might add, uh...
[ Chuckles ]
...it seems like no one
is minding the store.
Oh, I think they get like
three visitors a year.
So check-in's
on the honor system,
and housekeeping will be by
in the morning to tidy up.
Oh, that's a shame.
I was really looking forward
to ringing
that little bell.
Oh, yay, you're here!
Hi!
- Hi!
- So good to see you again! Hello.
Hello.
Well, you said
this place was quaint,
but I think it feels more
in the "abandoned" category.
And haunted.
Kidding.
Or am I?
Do not tease me
like that.
Nell would kill to stay
in a haunted motel.
I mean, my listeners
would love it.
I've got
that murder podcast.
What? How do I
not know about that?
I've mentioned it, like,
a bunch of times.
- Sorry.
- You really should listen.
It's super fun.
Ellroy does
all the forensic analysis.
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
I bet -- Which --
Uh, which ones are we?
Oh, you're
in the corner suite --
"suite" is...
Uh, I don't know.
Y-You'll see.
Oh.
Well, this isn't
too bad.
It's surprisingly clean.
I wouldn't be
too sure about that.
You want me to grab
the black light
from my trunk --
check for fluids?
Uh, no. We're good.
We're good. We're --
Thank you, yeah.[ Vehicle approaching ]
Oh.
[ Engine shuts off ]
Hey.
Officer Nolan.
Yes. John.
And, uh, this is Bailey.
- That's Nell.
- Hey.
And over there
is Ellroy.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm Gabrielle.
Uh, I know you've had
a long ride,
but I was told you were
gonna be working with me
while my boss
is on vacation.
Uh, great.
Let me just change my clothes,
and, uh,
we can hit the road.
You can give me
the lay of the land.
Um -- [ Chuckles ] --
this motel wouldn't happen
to be haunted, would it?
Uh...no, ma'am.
That's too bad.
Any murders take place here?
Big or small.
Ooh!
How about, like,
just a hostage situation?
Really giving me
hostage vibes.
Uh, no.
How about aliens?
No.
Tamara:
I don't understand.
Somebody packed the car
with half a million in heroin,
and then lost it?
How does that happen?
You don't just forget
where you parked your drug car.
You might if you're high
on the drugs
that you're transporting.
Okay, here we go.
Previous owner of your car
is Jake Butler.
Multiple arrests
for drugs and violence.
Let's take a look
at his mugshot.
What?
[ Scoffs ]
- What?
- Um...
Oh.
What the what?
♪
What's going on?
♪ You can play rough
if you wanna get rough ♪
♪ If you wanna get
♪ I got my war paint on
♪ Just the way I was born
♪ When my lions eat out,
get me foamin' at the mouth ♪
[ Siren chirps ]
♪ If you wanna play tough,
get it ♪
♪ We can play rough
It's even more uncanny
in real life.
♪
What the hell?
[ Chuckling ]
Yo.
Why you
looking like me?
Cuff him.
[ Handcuffs click ]
♪ Come on, now,
let's go ♪
So, how long
have you been on the job?
Two months.
I joined after getting
my degree in criminology
from UC Riverside.
So far, I haven't really had
a chance to use
what I've learned.
Quiet town?
[ Chuckles ]
Imagine the vacuum of space,
and then make it 10% quieter.
You know,
I looked you up.
You've been involved
in some really cool cases.
"Cool" is not the term
I would use.
How would you
describe them?
Intense.
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
I thought you were
taking me to the police station.
Oh, this is
the station --
offices and holding cells
are in back.
Oh, is it
a diner/police station?
Or is it
a police station/diner?
Depends on whether
you're here to file a report
or get some pie.
[ Door hinges creak ]
♪
Hey, Gabby.
Is this him?
Yes, John Nolan.
I'm Martina Sanchez.
Gabby says you're
a big-deal LA cop.
She's really hoping
you'll teach her some things.
Ay. Martina.
What?
We both know you're too shy
to ask him yourself.
Well, I'm happy to impart
any knowledge I can.
Thank you.
Anything going on?
Mrs. Gonzales
stopped by again.
Her cactus is growing weird.
Weird, you say?
Wrong angle.
- We'll get right on that.
- Please do.
[ Telephone rings ]
Ooh, this is exciting.
Phone only rings about
twice a week here.
Frontera Police Department.
We'll be right there.
Trouble?
Bar fight.
Well, big cities
and small towns --
you can always count on someone
to be drunk by 9:00 a.m.
Your first hour on the job,
and you're already getting
all the exciting stuff.
You must be good luck.
Or bad.
Maybe you were separated
at birth.
He's a year older than me.
And he was born in Florida.
Plus, ah, he really doesn't
look that much like me.
Mm. The hell he doesn't.
Not the brightest
bulb, though.
Oh. Oh, my God.
[ Laughs ]
It's -- It's Tim...
and Dim.
[ Laughter ]
Okay. Come on.
Let's get this over with.
That's good.
[ Chuckling ]
Yo, this is blowing my mind!
It's like we're looking in
a fun-house mirror of handsome.
Sit down, Dim -- Jake.
You need to focus.
Okay.
Have we met before?
No.
That, I'd remember.
Oh, you would.
We found your car.
Dude, you found it?
[ Chuckling ] Yo, thank you,
thank you, man.
I mean, some asshat
stole it from me last week.
Your car wasn't stolen --
it was towed.
You parked in front
of a hydrant.
Oops.
My bad.
So, where's the car now?
In evidence.
We found four kilos of black tar
heroin inside of it.
What? Yo, that's crazy.
I mean [chuckles]
it ain't mine.
Your fingerprints are
all over the bags.
Which means this is decision
time for you, Jake.
You help us,
we help you.
Otherwise, it's
back to prison.
Bruh, I thought that
we had a bond.
Where are the drugs from?
[ Sighs ]
Mexico.
I was hired to drive them
across the border,
but, you know, I hit up
my girl's place when I got back
in town -- you know
what I'm saying?
Anyway, I went back out,
the car wasn't there.
I've been freaking out
ever since.
Alright. Who are you supposed
to deliver the drugs to?
Roy Hajek.
Got the job through
a slinger we both know.
Have you ever met Hajek
or any of his crew?
No. Why?
You know,
they've never met.
So Tim could
go undercover as Dim,
and -- and -- and we would
arrest a major trafficker.
- Forget it.
- What?
Come on, you totally pulled
off playing the hitman.
I agree.
It's too good of
an opportunity to pass up.
You just want to see me
pretend to be Dim.
Duh.
Fine.
I'll do it.
Yes! Oh, okay, okay.
So, uh, we got
to dirty you up, and then --
and then we have to
slick back your hair, 'cause,
you know, that guy was,
like, kind of greasy.
You are enjoying this
way too much.
Ooh! And tattoos --
we got to get tattoos.
When we get to the bar,
don't park right out front.
Oh, but it's just
the Benedict brothers.
They fight
every other day.
Doesn't matter.
Always do things the right way.
That way,
when the danger is real,
the moves are automatic.
Got it.
[ Grunting ]
♪
You got this?
Yes, sir.
Doug, Will, come on,
knock it off.
[ Grunts ]
I said
knock it off -- now!
[ Grunts ]
Doug!
Okay, okay, okay.
Doug, are you okay?
Doug: Yeah.
Uh, but my neck kinda hurts.
No, no,
don't touch that.
Ugh.
I'm so sorry, man.
Oh, please don't die.
Hey, you know what?
Shouldn't we just pull
this thing out?
No, don't touch it.
Thank you for coming.
Nearest hospital is
an hour away.
Of course.
Good morning.
Two margaritas, if you are able.
What?
We're on vacation.
- Yeah, you want anything?
- No.
I'm gonna need some tape
to secure the glass
so we can take him
to the hospital.
I've got some
in the shop.
But you don't
have to take him.
Yes, I do.
He's my patient now.
I got you, dude.
How much have
you had to drink?
Not a drop.
We just got here.
Okay. You're gonna
take your brother and Bailey
to the hospital.
And then you're gonna pay
Walt for all the damages
- you've done here.
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay. Come on.
Got you.
Cheers.
Mm.
This is a dump.
Uh, Bailey made it
to the hospital.
Doug is in surgery.
[ Sighs ]
Thank God.
Those two are
idiots, but...
they're not bad guys.
Tourists.
They never plan for the heat.
Pete?
Whoa!
It's gonna blow!
Pete, get back here.
It's just overheating.
Save yourself!
God.
Hey.
John? Oh, my gosh,
the answer to my prayers.
Um...the car
broke down.
Yeah. I can see that.
He's still running.
Pete! Stop! Come back!
Pete: Is it safe?!
Yes! I promise!
- Really?!
- Yeah, you're safe!
You sure?!
I told him this
was gonna happen,
but he isn't happy unless
the AC is blasting at 60.
Ah.
Yeah.
Hi. I'm Chastity.
Sorry. Where are my manners?
This is Officer Navar.
Officer Navar,
this is Chastity.
She's dating
my brother Pete.
[ Panting ]
Half-brother.
Right,
my half-brother Pete.
Whew!
I see this all the time.
I got some coolant in the back,
should get you going shortly.
Thank you.
Why do people run, dude?
It sucks.
What are you doing here?
[ Coughs ] What do you mean?
You invited me.
I absolutely did not.
Well, it was
certainly implied.
I mean, why do you think
I got this Airstream, dude?
It's so we didn't have
to pay for a room.
I didn't even know you
owned an Airstream.
I don't.
Oh, my --
I feel like I'm gonna die.
Did you bring
my inhaler?
Yeah, of course I did.
Do you need it right now?
- Yeah, I do.
- You need it right now.
I do.
[ Door creaks lightly ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
♪
[ Beeps ]
Friendly is on site.
♪
[ Guns cock ]
[ Tires screech ]
♪
I got a piece on my left.
I want it back.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Trunk lid closes ]
Let's go see the boss.
♪
Trojan horse is away,
and we are on the move.
Lopez: Copy that.
All vehicles, stand by.
Rescue one, status?
Lucy: Rescue one,
we're ready in 60 seconds.
[ Elevator whirring ]
[ Elevator bell dings ]
♪ Now don't you know,
one of us gotta go up, yeah ♪
♪ Why you, wanna, see me down
♪ Praise to the man,
I'm blessed, yeah ♪
♪ I just pray,
don't stress, yeah ♪
♪ He say he wanna
build with me ♪
♪ When he see the way
that I flex, yeah ♪
♪ Praise to the man,
I'm blessed, yeah ♪
♪ I just pray
don't stress, yeah ♪
♪ He keep hittin' my line,
but, I ain't got time to text ♪
♪
Here we go.
UC in sight.
Rescue one, stand by.
Boss, he's here.
You're a brave man.
Disappearing with my dope,
then showing up here
like nothing happened.
I was worried
I caught a tail.
I went to ground till
I knew it was safe.
Didn't want to jam you up.
Hear that, Wisco?
He's looking out for me.
Come here.
What do you think
of my view?
It's dope.
So, when do
I get paid?
Once you convince me
not to have Wisco
throw you over
the balcony.
Get ready to breach.
Anyone lays a hand on our UC,
you put them down.
Yo, you trying to scare me,
it ain't working.
We both know you're too smart
to murder me where you live.
Plus, I gots people
who wouldn't take it too well.
Safer for you to keep me
on the payroll.
Smarter, too.
You know...
...I heard you were
a bit of a dumbass.
[ Chuckling ] Yeah.
Well, helps people
underestimate me.
Wisco will give you
your cash on the way out.
Word.
Or...
...you could do another job
for me and triple it.
What kind of job?
Can't tell you that yet.
But it's heavy.
And wet.
And tomorrow.
Oh, and we'll need
a driver, so...
bring your old lady.
I hear she's fast.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, sometimes, too fast.
No such thing.
We'll be in touch.
♪
Arrest team, stand down.
We need to see how
this new job plays out.
Thorsen, what's
the status of the package?
Still on the move.
Want us to intercept them?
Negative.
Keep eyes on until
the Drug Unit
takes over surveillance.
Copy that.
[ Siren wails ]
Nice felony stop.
Good distance, nice angle.
Thanks.
A wise man told me to do things
the right way, every time.
So when the danger's real,
the moves are automatic.
Good evening, sir.
Do you know why we
pulled you over?
[ British accent ]
Well, I'm assuming it's because
I was driving like
a bat out of hell.
I do apologize.
License and registration, please.
Yeah. Um, unfortunately,
I don't have any of that.
I was mugged a few hours ago,
and, well, my car keys
are the only thing that
I got away with.
Where did this happen?
It was at
a gas station about...
40 miles back?
Yeah, I'm -- I'm -- Look.
I'm still shaking.
[ Chuckles ]
Did you file
a police report?
No, no. I was --
I was too scared.
Gun! Back out!
Back out! Back out!
Drop your gun!
Drop it.
Alright.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey! Hey!
Look, I think there's just been
a misunderstanding, alright?
I thought you were
connected with the guys
that just robbed me.
What were you thinking?
Me?
Yes.
You nearly
got yourself killed.
You didn't do
a proper threat assessment,
and then you put yourself
in the line of fire.
Mine and his.
I'm really, really sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
It's not about thinking --
it's just about training.
And, clearly,
you haven't had enough.
Well, you can't blame her,
can you?
Look at this place.
Run those prints.
I want to know who he is
and whether he's got
any outstanding warrants.
I can't.
It's past 7:00.
The station only allows
us access to the CJIS database
during business hours.
Budget cuts.
Looks like you're
spending the night.
Oh, come on.
Like I was telling you --
I was afraid for my life.
Yeah. You also told me
your name was John Smith.
So save it for the judge.
Do you want me to take
first shift?
No. You've got friends here.
I can handle it.
And I owe you
for the screw-up.
Alright.
Call me if you need anything.
And don't let him out of there
for any reason.
What if I need to pee?
Hold it.
So, I had Dim's
girlfriend picked up.
Okay.
Wait.
Why are you being weird?
It's easier to show you.
Oh, um...
That is disturbing.
Guess we know who's going
undercover with Dim.
Yeah -- Juicy.
No.
Mm-hmm.
It's Juicy.
I don't like that.
Hello!
Hey! There he is!
- Hey.
- Come join us!
Uh...
maybe in a minute.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah. Fine.
Just a bit of a scary moment
during a traffic stop.
Gabrielle has some definite
holes in her training.
Well, then, it's a good thing
you came to town.
♪ Can't dance in
the corner by yourself ♪
It's fate, bro.
The universe is putting you
exactly where you need to be.
Yeah, I don't know that
I believe in all that stuff.
Oh, I do.
If fate hadn't put us together,
then I never would've had
the courage to ask
Nell out.
Aww. And I never would've met
the love of my life.
And I would've
never met Pete.
You're like
the Hook-up Whisperer.
I don't know that
that analogy tracks...
Yeah, dude.
You're like Tinder, dude.
Oh!
Something
to be proud of.
Embrace your
special gift.
You bring people
sexual gratification.
That's awesome.
Amen to that.
Thank you.
Is it weird to suggest
that we all go into our rooms
and maybe do
a little making out?
Yep.
Alright. Figured.
But I am feeling
a little bit tired.
Oh, me too.
Come on,
let's go, baby.
Oh.
[ Laughs ]
Good night.
- Good night.
Oh, there's a cat in there now,
but i-it's fine.
He's our friend.
Shall we?
It's either that or watch
the Airstream start a-rockin'.
Here you go.
Alright.
Carry me.
Oh, thought you'd never ask.
Come here. [ Laughs ]
♪ This is my conquering song
Tim: If we're gonna
make this work,
our back story's
got to be air-tight.
Agreed.
Okay, so, um, how did
Dim and Juicy meet?
At a barbecue.
Mm-hmm.
That's lame.
Really?
You think you can do better?
Watch me.
[ Clears throat ]
Okay, so, um...
you were on the run
from the cops --
a bank robbery
gone wrong.
You ended up in
my building -- frantic,
looking for a place to hide,
and [breathes deeply] --
and I opened
the door for you.
I lied to the cops
for you.
And -- Ooh.
And it got me so hot
that we hooked up
while they were still
searching the building.
Okay.
♪ For the spirit of
the eternal drum ♪
That -- That -- That's
pretty good, actually.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
♪ Where only my love survive
So, look -- we --
we should -- we should
probably, you know, talk about
the elephant in the room.
Mm.
You know, 'cause,
i-if we're gonna sell
that we are, you know,
actually boyfriend
and girlfriend,
then we might have to, uh...
You know.
Have to --
Have to what?
We might have to...
♪ Where only my love survive ♪
Do you...
♪ The long crawl to the tide
Okay, okay.
We might have to...
PDA?
[ Sighs ]
You know what?
Forget it.
No. No. Okay.
You're right.
You -- Yeah, you're right.
I mean,
if we're gonna --
[laughs] if we're
gonna have to kiss,
it probably shouldn't be
for the first time, right?
- That's what I'm saying.
- Right. Yeah.
Should we maybe --
uh, should we stand?
Yeah, I think
we should stand.
Yeah, that's good.
[ Clears throat ]
This is... Good.
Um...sure.
[ Laughs ] No.
Oh, you know what?
We're professionals.
Let's just get this done with.
Whoa!
Well, that's romantic.
I'm not trying
to be romantic.
Well, you're succeeding.
Sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Okay, okay. Okay. Yeah.
Hold on. Just -- Yes.
Good.
- Take your time.
- Yep. I'm g-- I'm -- Mm-hmm.
Yep.
I -- Yes, I'm ready.
♪ Where only my love survive
Okay.
♪ Love survive
♪ Where only my love survive
I'm s-- I'm sorry.
Is that it?
You know what? If -- If you're
gonna criticize me --
[ Stammers ]
♪ Where only my love survive
♪ Love survive
♪ Ooh-ooh
♪ Where only my love survive
- Oh.
- Tamara: Oh. Ah.
I...I should probably go.
No. This is work.
This is work.
Yeah, yeah. W-We're --
We're going undercover,
and it's --
Yeah, it's --
I mean, hey, hey.
It's cool.
I mean, you don't have to
explain yourself.
[ Chuckles ]
I should probably go.
No. No, no.
I was just about to leave.
You know what?
I don't have anything.
Um, I'll see you tomorrow.
G-Good work tonight.
Bye.
Great work, as well.
Mm-hmm.
Bye.
- Mm.
- I'm gonna go to my room.
Yeah, me too. Good.
[ Animal howling ]
♪
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just gonna go
relieve my rookie.
Go back to sleep.
Mm.
[ Breathing sharply ]
[ Grunting ]
You're getting good.
Thanks.
[ Sighs ]
Almost dying is a real
motivator for learning how
to defend yourself.
Where are you going?
Ah, just down to the office
to check on Gabrielle.
Can I come?
Sure.
Alright, let me
finish real quick.
[ Wheezes ]
That was it.
Let's go.
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Chuckles ]
Hey.
Uh...any contact
from Hajek?
No. Not yet.
Listen, about --We should prob--
Oh, the... Sorry.
Sorry, no.
Go ahead.
You go first.
- You s-- You sure?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I-I just wanted to say...
♪
...we need more work
on our back story.
Give it more depth.
Key moments, you know?
Yeah, we, uh, we could
take the morning --
you know, while we're
waiting for Hajek to call.
That's great.
Great.
Okay.
Yeah. [ Chuckles ]
[ Knock on door ]
Uh, you got a minute?
Sure.
Everything okay?
Yes, yes.
But, um, my doctor
wants me to start
my maternity leave
this week, so...
You know, get off my feet,
take it easy for the baby.
Of course.
Whatever you need.
[ Sighs ] Thank you.
Is there something else?
No, uh...
[ Sighs ]
Yes.
I need to talk to you
about what comes after.
That sounds ominous.
No, it - it's not at all.
I just -- I-I-I've been thinking,
and once this baby is born,
I would like to stay
with the detectives.
I figured as much.
Nyla, you're
an exemplary T.O.,
but at heart,
you're a hunter.
I assume you'd like
to stay paired with Lopez?
Yes, we work
great together.
Okay.
I'll tell Caradine and find
a new T.O. for Thorsen.
Thank you...
for everything.
I'm gonna make some coffee.
You want some?
Yes, please.
Morning.
Hey, I was just about
to call you.
I ran our suspect's prints
the minute the system
came online.
He's seriously a bad guy.
Blair Darvill.
Great name.
I see why you'd want to
keep it secret, though.
Number one on the ATF's
most wanted list.
Weapons trafficking,
attempted murder.
They're gonna be
pretty psyched when I call
and tell them you're here.
Yeah.
Here's the thing.
When I didn't
show up last night,
my guys started
looking for me.
You should really let me go
before they get here.
Nice try.
Ellroy: Hey, John, could
you come out here,
uh, for a minute?
Too late.
Keep an eye on him.
Mnh.
Man: LAPD.
You're a long way
from home.
How can I help you?
Let's just say
we can help each other.
You have a friend
of mine in custody.
I am here
to pay his bail.
- Oh, score.
- Ellroy.
Sorry.
That's not how bail works.
He has to go in front
of a judge first.
But you already know that.
I do.
But sometimes cops play hard
to get before they take a bribe.
Right. Well, I don't
take bribes.
Your friend's going away
for a long time.
And I'd bet that much money
that there's
an outstanding warrant
or two for your arrest,
so why don't you
show me some ID?
Are you sure you really want to
play it like that?
♪
And there's more on the way --
arrival, imminent.
Maybe -- and I'm just
talking here --
we take the money.
Or just forget
the money.
Or we just let him
have the guy.
They're not the only
ones with guns.
I do not have a gun.
Last chance.
Right back at you.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Cellphone dialing ]
[ Line ringing]
[ Sighs ]
We're going to war.
Take it down.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Chain saw revving ]
♪
[ Cellphone rings ]
Hey. Nell and Chastity
are going antiquing,
so I'm coming to have
breakfast with you.
No.
Don't come here.
Where's Pete?
Sleeping. Why?
What's wrong?
Ah, lots of guys,
lots of guns.
I need you to grab Pete, and I
need you to get out of town.
John, they're cutting
down the cell tower.
[ Chain saw revving ]
John, are you there?
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Bailey?
What happened?
We're cut off.
♪
What the hell is happening?
You need to open
that gun safe.
I-I can't.
The sheriff has the key.
That would've been
good to know before you decided
to take a stand.
Okay, okay. New plan.
Go get the prisoner.
Yes.
Okay.
- You're giving him up.
- No.
We're gonna
use him as a shield.
I like my idea better.
[ Weapons cocking ]
Get down!
[ Gunfire ]
Oh!
♪
Oh, oh!
Pete!
Pete, wake up!
[ Rock music playing ]
Pete!
♪
[ Engine shuts off ]
Oh! Oh!
[ Gunfire stops ]
He's a feisty one.
Come on.
You know, you should probably
just let me go.
If you do it now,
I can probably talk them into
letting you live.
Forgive me
if I don't trust you.
Hey!
You shoot at us again,
you kill your boss!
You think
that's gonna stop us?
We'll just come in
and get him.
And we'll make it hurt.
You come in here,
you won't walk back out.
All they have are handguns
and limited ammo.
Okay, come on, come on.
Enough talking.
Alright.
Stick him in the kitchen.
Hold him in there.
And you plant yourself
right next to him.
It's the safest spot
for you and Ellroy.
I'll cover left.
You cover right.
Ellroy, you're spotter --
you call out trouble
when you see it.
Sounds like a -- a --
a lot of pressure.
♪
Right!
Left, left, left!
[ Gunshot ]
It's so loud!
Right!
The left!
Get to the right!
Left!
[ Grunting ]
[ Groans ]
♪
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
♪
♪ When you take out
the figures ♪
♪ And you pull all
the triggers, well ♪
♪ You're taking me back
♪ When you listen to mystics
as you lay at your picnics ♪
♪ You're taking me back
[ Grunts ]
[ Clangs ]
♪ I'll bet you do,
but not for long ♪
[ Gunfire ]
♪ I'm alone
♪ But not for long
[ Grunting ]
♪
Okay.
[ Breathing sharply ]
Let's do this, big boy.
Aw, come on!
[ Rock music playing ]
[ Grunting ]
♪
Ah!
[ Music playing ]
[ Grunting ]
♪
Ah!
[ Exhales deeply ]
Oh.
[ Laughs ]
[ Chuckles ] Nice.
[ Laughing ]
Holy...
What?
Nothing.[ Gun cocks ]
[ Thud ]
[ Grunting ]
♪
[ Rock music playing ]
[ Yawns ]
♪
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts ]
♪
[ Panting ]
What's going on?
[ Yawning ] Is there, uh --
Is there any coffee?
[ Chuckles ] This trip is gonna
make one hell of a podcast.
Oh, my God. Baby.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're okay?
- I'm okay.
- Oh, okay.
What happened to you guys?
[ Sighs ]
[ Handcuffs click ]
Wait. Where's
Captain Money Bag?
[ Thud ]
Thanks.
Now we're even.
[ Elliott BROOD's "Stay Out"
plays ]
♪ I do believe
that I've had enough ♪
♪ But I don't wanna go home
You should've seen me --
I kicked his ass.
I was a little preoccupied
saving Nolan.
Uh, well, I think
we all saved each other.
It's not a contest.
Oh, it is a little bit
of a contest,
and I'm clearly the winner.
♪ And I don't wanna go home
Alright, Bailey is clearly
the winner,
but I-I'm a close
runner-up.
♪ Or this is gone in
the blink of an eye ♪
Looks like a war zone
in here.
You should see
the other guys.
Where are
the other guys?
♪ I wanna stay out
a little while ♪
♪