Previously on "The Rookie"...
I would like to formally give
my endorsement for union rep.
John Nolan.
- Dad was a monster.
- Dad's dying.
I'm really sorry
about today.
I'm still not going to
see him.
La Fiera took Angela.
I need to know where
she's holding her.
- Elijah: No problem.
- I'll do whatever
it takes to get her back.
You work for me now.
Making a deal
with Elijah
was the only way that I could
get you home safe.
Well, you're not
becoming a C.I.
I will do everything humanly
possible to keep him safe.
We can't screw this up.
We won't.
♪
[ Handcuffs click ]
[ Car alarm blares ]
Ugh.
7-Adam-15, Code 4.
Suspect is in custody.
♪ 'Tis the season to be jolly,
fa-la-la-la-la ♪
Are you looking at
engagement rings?
Maybe. What do you think
of this one?
Oh, for Bailey?
Oh, my God.
Are you going to propose?
Uh, maybe.
I mean, I'm thinking about it.
I-I know we haven't been dating
very long --
No, what matters
is how you feel,
and -- and I've never
seen you happier.
Me and my lady got hitched
after three weeks,
and we're still
going strong.
- When you know, you know.
- Exactly.
The only thing
I don't know
is what kind of ring
she would like.
But that's -- that's
pretty, right?
No one wears emerald cut
anymore.
There's a reason
I left that behind.
Was Henry excited
when you told him?
Henry.
They haven't even met.
I can't think about proposing
until I get his blessing.
Invite them both over
for dinner.
He's in Japan
through Christmas.
Oh. You know what?
This is good.
It'll give you time
to plan the proposal,
and I know of a photographer
that's not too expensive.
A photographer...
for a proposal?
I could hook you up
with the choreographer
- that designed mine.
- Choreographer?
Okay. Um, see,
I was just thinking about
going to a nice restaurant
and, you know, asking.
Yeah. Let's workshop it
back at the station.
Come on.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
[ Coffee pouring ]
Oh, I see
what you're doing there.
You asked me
to help decorate your tree.
Yes, that was to trick you into
staying for a few more days.
No trickery required.
Mm. [ Smooches ]
You know, in spite of myself,
I have really enjoyed
this whole being taken care of
thing the last few weeks.
And now that my leg
is feeling better,
I want to start
making it up to you.
Well, while I like
the sound of that,
it's really --
really not necessary.
I mean, that's one of
the many built-in perks
of being in
a healthy relationship.
Which, by the way,
do you still feel
you're terrible
at intimacy?
I may have graduated
to mediocre.
Oh, I'd say
you're at least intermediate,
if not proficient.
Oh.
[ Smooches ]
By the way,
Henry's supposed
to call this morning.
I was hoping the two of you
could talk
and finally get a chance
to know one another.
I would love that,
but it's my first day back
from medical,
and I can't be late.
Speaking of...
[ Gasps ]
Is he free tonight?
Uh, well, he might be in
meetings.
Tonight is tomorrow for him,
I think?
I don't know. I keep forgetting
how the time change works.
Okay, another day,
then.
I'm so sorry,
I have to go,
and tell Henry
I said hi, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
See ya.[ FaceTime ringing ]
♪ Home for the holidays
Oh. Um, there's, uh --
Hey.[ Cellphone clicks ]
Henry: Hey, Dad.
[ Chuckles ]
Sorry I'm late.
Dinner ran a little long.
Uh, no.
No -- No problem.
How's Japan?
Well, Nolan says
an open concept sells better,
so I'm thinking
we take out this wall
and then move on
to the kitchen.
Do you remember how Mom used to
make us pose by the window
for every formal dance?
Oh, my gosh.
My mom did that, too.
And I always had to have
a wrist corsage.
Yes.
Why was that ever a thing?
No.
No more reminiscing.
This is about fixing up
the house and selling it.
- That's it.
- What? Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
I mean, you guys are ending
a huge chapter in your lives.
You guys need closure.
[ Saw buzzing ]
What?
I said you need closure!
You're an idiot.
♪
Did you vote yet?
The polls just opened
20 minutes ago.
We have all week.
I know.
Vote for change.
I just know
that low voter turnout
is an epidemic
in this country,
and I don't want to
lose to apathy.
Can I ask you something?
Do you think
marriage proposals
have to be a big spectacle
nowadays?
No. No.
All those viral
flash mobs are tacky.
It should be
an intimate moment,
not some desperate grab
for likes.
Okay.
That's what I thought,
but Lucy seems to think
I need to plan
something extravagant.
Is Lucy the one
you're proposing to?
No.
Am I the one
you're proposing to?
No.
So why are you talking to either
of us about this?
Right.
The only person's opinion
who matters is Bailey's.
Yeah, I-I'm not even sure
myself yet.
I'm just testing
the waters.
Mm-hmm.
Well, whenever you do,
make sure
that you let her
help you pick out a ring.
Donovan got me this massive
diamond that cost a fortune
and was not
my style at all.
Really?
One of the best things
about the divorce
was finally getting to
sell that thing.
Huh.
Tamara, hey.
Oh.
Hey, John.
Do you know where
Sergeant Grey's office is?
I sure do.
The big glass one right there.
Oh. Thank you.
See ya.
Hey.
Ready for our interview?
I am so sorry.
I -- Something came up.
Is there any way we can
reschedule to next week?
Uh, my criminal sociology
paper's due on Friday.
But it's fine.
I'm sure whatever you're doing
is way more important.
Remind me what this paper's
about again.
Um, how aging affects
perspectives of cops
throughout their career.
And Lucy told me you'd be
the perfect candidate
because you're an old --
I'm sorry.
Uh, I mean veteran officer.
Right.
♪
Follow me.
Smitty, this is Tamara.
She'll be shadowing you.
You mean like a ride-along?
No. Not --
You are not to step foot outside
this station with her.
Just show her around,
answer her questions.
Sure thing, boss.
♪
There's nothing I don't know
about policing.
Ask me anything.
You spelled
"magnet" wrong.
♪
Our target
is Elijah Stone.
He's smart
and ruthless.
Multiple agencies have tried
to get listening devices
in his base of operation.
Every attempt has failed.
But other agencies didn't have
our ace in the hole --
Wesley Evers.
As Elijah's lawyer,
Wesley is ideally situated
to place a listening device
in Elijah's main office.
Please familiarize yourself
with the briefing materials
and be ready to roll out
in an hour.
That's it.
You don't have to do this,
you know.
Yes, I do.
This is the bug
you'll be planting.
Did you read the list
of suggested locations
I put together?
I did, but I doubt
I'm gonna time
to unscrew
an electrical socket.
With limited time,
I would focus on someplace high
or someplace low.
The most important thing
is doing it safely.
Agreed. If you do not have
the opportunity today,
that's fine.
We can try again
when you meet with him
next time.
Wesley, Metro wants to go over
a few things.
♪
I know cops aren't supposed to
make promises,
but promise me
you'll keep him safe.
♪
We promise.
So, you've been on the force for
30 years.
What's been
the biggest challenge
as you've gotten older?
The change in technology?
Procedure?
Yes.
Hey, you ever heard of
ClipTalk?
I'm trying
to upload a meme.
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Tamara:
You can't be serious.
This is how you want to
beat your opponent?
Hell yeah.
Help me go viral
and I'll buy you
a candy bar.
[ Computer beeps ]
Surveillance is in position.
Copy.
Rescue Vehicle One in position.
Wesley should arrive for
his meeting with Elijah
in about 10 minutes.
[ Cellphone buzzes, chimes ]
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Oh, my skip tracer
just sent his report.
Your skip tracer?
Well, yeah, I can't use
police resources
to run personal
background checks,
so I got a guy
on retainer.
You should have one, too.
What do you got him
looking for?
Leverage.
I'm trying to find anything
I can use
to keep Donovan
from getting custody
and moving Lila
to San Francisco.
And?
Did he find anything?
Uh, no.
Quote, "Your ex is so boring,
I am charging you double."
You guys are so lucky.
I begged my mom and dad
to have a sibling.
They got me a turtle.
Um, it was cute,
but a little smelly.
Cute and smelly pretty much
sums up Tim's teenage years.
You didn't miss much.
Wow. And to think
I was actually excited
when they brought you home
from the hospital.
Little did I know.
♪ It's been too long
♪ And get back home
♪
♪ It's been too long
What is it?
There's -- There's something
in the wall.
Ooh, is it my Malibu Barbie?
She's worth a lot now.
No. It's --
It's metal.
♪ You been out on the road
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪
What the hell is a gun doing
in our wall?
How long has that
been back there?
It's hard to say.
Look. The serial number's
been filed off.
That's what criminals do,
right?
We need to run ballistics.
Wait, you don't actually think
it was used in a crime?
Well, it's our job
to find out.
We'll be back
as soon as we can.
But it's your day off.
You said you'd help.
It won't take long.
C'mon, Chen.
I knew you'd find
some excuse to leave.
Genny,
this is serious.
It's fine.
Go.
Uh...
Hey, she's got a point.
I mean, you could've called
someone to handle this.
You still can.
No, a good sergeant doesn't
create work for his officers.
Even on his day off.
And it's not at all about
the emotions
this house is stirring up?
It's just a house.
Holy crap.
What?
My skip tracer looked into
Penelope, Donovan's fiancée.
[ Scoffs ]
She used to be an escort.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
She's -- She's been lying to him
this whole time.
Well, you don't know that.
She may have already told
Donovan.
Or, heck, that could be
how they met.
Oh, no. No.
Donovan is such a prude.
If he found out,
he would lose it.
And if the court found out,
you'd win your case.
It just doesn't feel right,
bringing her into our fight.
And the fact that
she was a sex worker
has no bearing on her
as a stepmom.
Neither does you doing
undercover,
but he's using that
against you.
Sure, but using her past
against her
makes me just as bad
as Donovan.
I can't. I-I got to figure out
something else
to change his mind.
Okay.
Any ideas how?
No. [ Sighs ]
Heads up.
Wesley's going in.
♪
[ Rapping ] ♪ Rambo rap
Elijah's expecting me.
Cellphone.
♪ I just move on 'em,
advance on 'em ♪
♪ Groove on 'em, then dance on
'em, put a trance on 'em ♪
♪ With this tool on 'em
♪ Tell all my young MCs,
bust a move on 'em ♪
♪ Mass track the D's
when I grant groove on 'em ♪
♪ Put in long hours
over strong flowers ♪
Come in.
Sit down.
So, how are we getting Reyes
out of trouble?
I can get the witness testimony
thrown out, but the, uh,
surveillance video's
a whole other problem.
Looking for something?
You guys paint
since I was last here?
Elijah: No.
Room looks different.
Must be the Christmas
decorations.
As I was saying,
the video is a problem,
but your bigger issue
is your guys
don't know how to
- get arrested.
- He's doing great.
They can't keep assaulting
police officers.
Yeah.
He'll be fine.
Resisting arrest is making
my life harder.
You hear that, Moreno?
Our friend thinks I'm making
life too hard for him.
No, it's just --It's what, Counselor?
What part
of our arrangement
is about making
your life easier?
Hmm. Nothing.
Piece of
unsolicited advice --
fire Reyes
as soon as possible.
So? He punched
the arresting officer.
- Reyes is good people.
- Reyes is a moron.
He bragged about the assault
to an inmate in lockup,
ended up being
an informant.
- Where is he?
- Making a run
to the food bank.
Alright, when he's done,
get him in here.
Someone needs a refresher course
on keeping his damn mouth shut.
Now, I'm hearing whispers about
a threat on the horizon,
but I can't
get traction on it.
- That's news to me.
- Well, what about
your wife?
Has she heard anything?
Uh... I don't know.
You guys are
lucky to have me.
That's the signal.
Point to all units.
Friendly has given the signal.
Go ahead and initiate
"Blind Eye."
I can't make any promises,
but...
[ Sirens wailing ]
What's going on?
We may have a problem.
[ Sirens chirping ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Vehicle door opens ]
Police Officer:
Get your hands up!
- Get your hands up!
- Hands up!
- Don't move!
- Hands behind your head.
Get down
on your knees.
Well, that's not ours.
Moreno: No.
Never seen him before.
Wesley:
Everything okay, guys?
Yeah, it's nothing.
Just, uh...
That's the second signal.
He's planted the bug.
Music has been deployed.
Stop units can clear.
He did it.
Now get out of there.
Wesley:
Well, that's it.
That's all I got for you.
He's walking out now.
Okay, good work,
Counselor.
Keep me updated on Reyes.
Will do.
But seriously,
fire him or teach him
to keep his mouth shut.
[ Walkie-talkie chirps ]
Boaz.
Come walk out the lawyer.
He's ready to go.
[ Static crackling ]
Boaz: Go again.
♪
Moreno:
Boaz, do you copy?
Come get the lawyer.
[ Static crackles,
Boaz speaks indistinctly ]
That's static.
The bug Wesley planted
could create interference
with a two-way radio.
We didn't know they use
walkie-talkies in there?
- Harper, come in.
- Already on it.
All units, stand by.
Be ready to breach on my go.
Boaz:
I can't hear you.
Come again? [ Speaks indistinctly ]
Can I just walk
myself out?
I mean, seriously,
I have a meeting across town
in 30 minutes.
Oh, no, no.
Slow up, Counselor.
It can wait.
♪
This is very interesting.
[ Static continues ]
You know, from what I recall,
when the sirens went off,
you didn't even jump.
Didn't even bother
to look.
It's almost like you knew
they were coming.
What the hell
are you talking about?
[ Static crackling ]
♪
Mm.
We may need
a new exterminator.
We have to go now.
No. Elijah's too smart
to hurt Wesley
while we're listening.
All units hold.
What is that?
[ Softly ] No, no, no, no.
Don't even play.
Testing, testing.
Can you hear me?
Whoever you are.
Is it the FBI?
The DEA?
Oh, wait.
No. Of course.
What am I thinking?
It's the LAPD.
I bet your lovely wife is out
there listening, too, isn't she?
Angie, you out there,
sweetheart?
You're smart.
You know I don't say
anything incriminating
in front of your husband,
so you turned him into
a Trojan Horse
to leave a bug behind.
And your little game
almost worked, too.
Speaking of games,
you know what my favorite is?
"I Spy."
I spy with my little eye
a pest control van.
No. No.
No, you wouldn't be in there.
That's too "Miami Vice."
Oh.
There's a mail truck.
No, no, no.
That has to stay on the move,
lest someone
get suspicious.
Oh. The minivan.
Roomy enough for equipment,
yet nondescript.
So, tell me, Angie,
did I win the game?
Of course I did.
I always win.
You know why?
Because I play by
the rules.
Which means I'm gonna report
your husband
to the California State Bar.
That's right.
I'm gonna have
his law license revoked
for betraying the trust
of a client.
This is not over.
For you, it is.
[ Door opens ]
Wesley, come on, man.
He's all yours.
I just fired him.
- Listen to me closely.
- Uh-huh.
You lay a hand on him
or his family,
it'll be the last thing you do
as a free man.
I don't need to
touch him.
He just screwed himself.
Let's go.
Walk away.
Until we meet again,
Counselor.
♪
Hey, ballistics came back on
the gun we found in the wall.
That was fast.
Yeah, I mean, I had to buy
a case of Girl Scout cookies
from Derek's kid.
You're welcome.
Okay, so, the striations
from the gun match up
with a bullet from
a homicide from 25 years ago.
The murder victim's name
was Frank Ochoa.
He lived down the street.
I was 14
when he was murdered.
According to the case file,
Frank's murder
was the result of a suspected
botched home invasion.
Well, I think we can
rule that out
now that we found the gun
in our wall.
Do you remember anything
from that night?
Yeah,
I had a football game.
Uh, my mom took me and Genny,
and when we got back,
there were
cops everywhere.
My dad hated that guy.
Your dad had an alibi.
Um, Frank's wife, Monica.
She was at the house.
He was helping her
with her taxes.
Monica is not
a solid alibi.
They were having
an affair.
My mom didn't know,
but I did.
Uh, if -- if Frank discovered
the affair --
My dad would have had motive
to kill him.
That's how the gun ended up
in the wall.
Okay, but why hide it
in there?
I mean, why not just dump it
in a storm drain or an ocean?
I don't know.
- You did good today.
- Not good enough.
The radio interference
wasn't your fault.
Doesn't make me
any less scared.
What's next?
We regroup and hit this
in the morning.
You two go home,
cuddle Jack.
Install the VARDA system.
And get to know
your security detail.
- VARDA?
- Don't worry.
It's only the most intrusive
and creepy security system
ever invented.
Thank you
for everything.
I wish I could do more.
Hey. Why are you letting Smitty
walk all over you?
I'm not letting Smitty --Yes, you are.
I've been here watching Smitty
talk smack about you
to the other officers.
I-It's obscene.
Please tell me you're planning
on hitting back.
Okay, I agree
it's not great,
but Smitty has chosen
his path,
and I'm not gonna get anywhere
if I resort to
the same tricks he does.
But you're still not
gonna get anywhere
if you let this happen,
either.
You could lose.
I think negativity
turns off voters.
I'm gonna run
a clean campaign --
and apologies, I do have a call
scheduled with my son.
Can we pick this up later?
Sure.
Thank you.
Don't tell me you have
more interview questions?
Just one.
You want to go viral?
I'll help you
make the video.
What's your
ClipTalk password?
Hey, where you going?
Monica Ochoa's
in Interrogation.
I'm gonna get to
the bottom of this.
Whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're going to question
your father's mistress?
She's his alibi.
If anyone knows whether
or not my dad killed
her husband, it's her.
Yes, but you can't be
the one to question her.
Look, we need to
do this right.
You do it.
Thank you for coming in,
Mrs. Ochoa.
Of course.
So, what is this all about?
Your husband's murder.
We recently had a break
in the case,
and we just wanted to go over
a few details with you.
What do you mean,
a break in the case?
It's been 25 years.
I'm afraid I'm not at liberty
to discuss
the details at this time.
What do you remember
about that night?
I have been over this
so many times.
Don't you have the report?
It's all in there.
I'm sorry.
I realize this is
a painful subject.
I wouldn't ask
if it wasn't important.
[ Sighs ]
I was across the street
at the neighbors'.
The Bradfords. [ Scribbling ]
Right. Tom was helping me
with our taxes.
Um, [chuckles] I had made
a mess with them,
and he was a CPA.
When I got back home,
the door was open,
and, um...
the place was a mess.
I-I'm sorry.
Um, it's been a very long time
since I've had
to talk about this.
Uh, just
take your time.
I found, uh,
my husband, Frank.
He was -- His body
was in the kitchen.
Um, there was blood
everywhere.
I guess he surprised
whoever broke in,
and, um, they shot him.
You were close with
the Bradford family?
We socialized,
like neighbors used to.
So, the night of the murder,
you were at their house,
working on your taxes,
and, uh,
the rest of the Bradford family
was there?
Uh, no, Mrs. Bradford
and the kids
were at, um, a basketball game
or something.
Okay, so you were alone
with the husband.
Was this
a regular occurrence?
What are you getting at?
I-I'm just trying to understand
what happened.
Uh, did -- did Mr. Bradford, um,
leave at any point?
Uh, I-I'm sorry. Could we maybe
do this another time?
It would be easier
if we got it done now.
I don't know.
Uh, you just sprung this on me,
and, um,
you're asking a lot.
Yeah. You know what?
If we just get
a few more questions,
we'll -- we'll be done
and get you
right out of here.
No, I-I want to go now.
♪
Tim?
Mrs. Ochoa.
Did my father leave
at any point that night?
Of course not. You think that
I lied to the police?
Look, I know you were
having an affair --
Excuse me?
It's fine.
It was a long time ago.
But if you're protecting him --
Okay. That's it.
I'm done.
♪
She's covering for him.
Maybe,
but we can't prove that.
Thanks so much.
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Door closes ]
So, we have two officers
standing guard on rotation
for the next 72 hours,
motion sensors
in the front yard,
and an alarm system
that will bypass 911
and send a red alert
to every cop in the area
if anything happens.
No way Elijah makes it
through that door.
How long do we have
to live like this?
Hey, the only thing
that matters
is that
our family is safe.
It's gonna be okay.
Totally. And I'm probably
gonna lose my law license,
but on the bright side,
more time with Jack.
[ Exhales sharply ]
- Where you going?
- Back to work.
I'm not letting
that criminal beat us.
[ Sighs ][ Door opens, closes ]
Hi.
Thanks for coming all the way
down here at the last minute.
What am I doing here,
Nyla?
Okay. Well, uh,
I know that we're back to
talking through lawyers,
but I thought we could have
an actual conversation
and avoid dragging Lila
through another
painful custody fight.
Okay.
What are you proposing?
Since Lila has her school
and her friends here,
I am proposing that she spend
the school year with me,
and the entire summer,
she can be with you.
And obviously,
you can visit any time.
What are you thinking?
I think
there's more to consider
than just school
and friends.
Okay, like what?
Like the fact that you've been
an absentee parent
until recently.
Look, I will admit
that my old job
took up a lot of my time,
but that is why
I switched to patrol.
I'm sorry, why are we meeting
in front of your station
instead of the restaurant
you suggested this morning?
Because I am working overtime
on a case.
Right.
So you want me to give you
full custody
so a nanny
can raise our child?
That is not fair.
Come on, Donovan,
what is this really about?
[ Stammers ]
Let me guess --
- what happened at Halloween?
- No. No.
Yes, it is. You feel guilty that
we slept together.
- It was an accident.
- That we both made,
so stop punishing me
over it.
I'm -- I'm not.
For two years,
I have been the only parent
helping her with her school
work, going on field trips,
taking her to every single
doctor's appointment.
Where were you?
[ Siren wailing ]
Okay.
I think the court would agree
that I am the parent
that is the most --Please do not do this.
Not just to me,
but to our daughter.
She's adaptable.
She'll make friends at school,
and when she gets home,
she'll have two parents
there waiting for her.
Nyla, Penelope and I
can give her stability.
Oh, right. Penelope.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing.
I will see you in court.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Door closes ]
Oh, man.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Never thought
I'd see your face again.
Genny tell you to visit?
Wow, liver really did
a number on you, old man.
I don't have it so bad.
Nurses here all love me.
It's just...
no one will bring me that shot
of Patrón I keep asking for.
Ah.
Apple juice.
It's a joke.
You always seem to have
someone looking after you,
even when
you don't deserve it.
Something on your mind,
son?
Remember Frank Ochoa?
Lived down the street.
Shot to death
25 years ago.
Well, I-I'm sure you remember
his wife, Monica.
Can't say that I do.
Come on.
You were sleeping with her
behind Mom's back.
[Laughing]
Where'd you get that from?
Because I saw you two together
when I was 13.
Oh. Crap.
For some reason that I still
don't understand,
I lied for you,
lied to Mom.
Poor little Tim-Tim.
What are you bitching about?
You kept your mouth shut.
You did good.
Now get over it.
You know, I found the gun that
you hid in the wall.
I know you killed Frank.
But why'd you do it?
You wanted Monica
all to yourself?
Ruining one family just wasn't
enough for you, was it?
♪
And so what if I did?
What are you gonna do
about it?
Get back in bed.
♪
Make me.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
[ Slaps hand ]
You're right.
I killed Frank.
But he had it coming.
So, screw him,
and screw you.
Put the cuffs on me.
Drag me away from my death bed
like a big man.
This isn't over.
Get the hell
out of here.
♪
[ Door opens, closes ]
Okay, one second.
[ FaceTime ringing ]
Here comes Bailey.
Everyone on?
Hi, Henry. Hey, Bailey.
It's nice to finally --
Buddy,
you're breaking up.
Now -- Now you're frozen.
[ FaceTime bloops ]
Now he's gone.
Hang on a second.
I'll ring him up.[ FaceTime ringing ]
Oh, there he is.
Hang on. I'll answer.
There you are, Henry.
Can you hear me?
Hey, sorry, service is
a little spotty over here.
I'm just happy
my two favorite people
finally get
a chance to meet.
Henry, your dad tells me
you're in Japan for work.
Yeah. Some first
[speaking distorted]
Ben is
Buddy, you're breaking up.
[ Fire alarm ringing ]
Sorry. I gotta go.
We got a call.
Right, you go.
You go, Bailey.
So, was that
[speaking distorted]
Wait, what
Now you're frozen again,
and you're still breaking up.
Henry, can you hear me?
[ FaceTime disconnects ]
There you are.
Grey and Lopez have something.
Great.
- What's going on?
- Lopez figured out
how Elijah smuggles drugs
into the country.
We were replaying the tapes from
Elijah's office,
and something stuck out.
Elijah said that one of his
guys, Reyes,
was making a run
to the food bank.
He doesn't seem like
the selfless type.
Exactly.
So we dug into his finances
and found that he's been
making large donations
of canned goods from a factory
in Mexico every month.
Cans are sealed.
Dogs can't smell the drugs.
So Elijah has his food bank
import the cans,
and then his crew
distributes them
throughout the Southland.
- So, that's it.
- No.
It's our theory.
Enough to get a warrant.
And Elijah's
no one's fool.
He knows we heard him
reference the food bank.
He's probably clearing
the place out as we speak.
Look, I know we're going deep
into overtime territory --
Screw that.
You're family. We're in.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♪
♪ Oh!
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♪ Driving the new foreign
♪ Swervin' through the lane,
lanes ♪
♪ Headed to the money, yeah,
ain't nothing change ♪
♪ Bust the brains out the AP,
make it dumb out ♪
♪ Oh, God, I drop the top,
you see ya son out ♪
♪ See ya son out, yeah
♪ Son out, yeah
♪ Driving in the foreign
♪ Girl, my life ain't boring
♪ Haters always hatin'
♪ Tell 'em get insurance
♪ Driving in the foreign
♪ Girl, my life ain't boring
♪ Haters always hatin'
♪ Tell 'em get insurance,
oh, Lord ♪
♪ Oh, Lord
♪ The way that I drive
the glide ♪
♪ It look like I rented it
♪ I dive inside lil ma,
she think I invented it ♪
♪ I got two bulldogs,
beware in my premises ♪
♪ Don't make me snap
like free benefits ♪
♪ I gotta get lettuce,
I gotta go, let us ♪
Police!
Search warrant!
[ Gunshots ]
♪ I wake up, skip eggs
♪ I am that...
I know that she watch ♪
♪ I'm out in Erie, P.A.
♪ I'm in the Boscov store,
I'm sipping Henny ♪
♪ The city is
treating me great ♪
♪ My women are stingy
♪ They always say they want me
to the face ♪
Drop it!
It's over!
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
driving a new foreign ♪
♪ Swerving through the lanes,
lanes ♪
♪ Headed to the money, yeah,
ain't nothing change ♪
♪ Bust the brains out the AP,
make it dumb out ♪
I ain't saying nothing.
♪ Oh, God, I drop the top,
you see ya son out ♪
You don't have to.
We have enough to put you and
Elijah away for a long time.
♪ Haters always hatin'
♪ Tell 'em get insurance
Hey.
My dad confessed
to Frank Ochoa's murder.
- I'm typing up the report.
- Tim --
Do me a favor
and call the DA.
But, Tim, stop.
Look, while you were gone,
I brought
Monica Ochoa back in.
Why?
Because I knew there was
more to her story.
You -- You couldn't see past
the version
that you wanted to see.
What'd she say?
[ Light snoring ]
You brought me a present?
Think of it
more as a push.
[ Sniffs ]
[ Shot glass clinks ]
You didn't kill Frank.
[ Glass clatters ]
Sure I did.
Now, come on.
Cuff me.
Let's just
get this over with.
Monica confessed.
Leave her out of this.
Frank was beating her.
She fought back.
She shot him.
She was terrified,
so she ran to you.
You came up with
the burglary story,
helped her stage the house,
then you hid the gun
in case the cops got too close
and you needed to
frame someone else.
He was a brutal,
abusive bastard.
She deserves a medal
for what she did.
He was an abusive bastard?
What?
You think I'm like him?
I was nothing like Frank.
I taught you
what you needed to know, son.
You're a man now
because of me.
No. I'm who I am
in spite of you.
Oh.
Goodbye, Dad.
I hope it hurts.
You okay?
No.
He was protecting her.
He never did anything
to protect us,
but his mistress -- broke half
a dozen laws for her.
They picked her up.
She's being processed right now.
I don't think the DA
is gonna prosecute your dad
on his death bed.
Doesn't matter.
He'll get judged
soon enough.
The Tim Tests --
those don't make me
like him.
I know.
You're nothing like him.
I...
♪
Come here.
You're nothing like him.
♪
Hey.
How'd it go
with Donovan earlier?
Mm. Don't ask.
I didn't tell him.
I couldn't.
That's really very sweet
of you,
but he's not playing fair,
and unless you want to
lose your kid,
you have to
start playing hardball.
Use Penelope's history
to get him to back off.
[ Sighs ]
There's no other way for me to
win this, is there?
No.
Penelope's a grown woman.
She can take care of
herself.
You take care of Lila.
Alright.
I'll call my lawyer
and tell her to use it.
Hey.
Judge signed off
on the warrant for Elijah.
Let's go get him.
[ Sirens wailing ]
♪
Three blocks away.
Kill lights
at the next intersection.
♪ Take off,
lemme see you take off ♪
Dispatch: Sergeant,
we just got a 911 call.
Multiple shots fired
at your warrant address.
Did SWAT move in early?
No, sir.
They're still two minutes out.
I don't know who's shooting.
♪ Take off,
lemme see you take off ♪
♪
Control, we don't hear gunfire,
but there's evidence of it.
Tell SWAT we're going in.
♪ We outta here
Police!
♪
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
What the hell
happened here?
♪
[ Banging ]
LAPD!
Come out with your hands up!
♪
Give me your hands.
[ Handcuffs clicking ]
Who did this?
Abril.
She is not yours anymore.
No!
Abril's in Guatemala.
La Fiera's cartel
fractured when she died.
No, she took control
and then came for revenge,
'cause I'm the one who told
Wesley where to find you.
♪
Lopez:
Her name is Abril Rodas.
The late La Fiera's
top sicaria.
Abril came to get revenge
on Elijah
for giving us the intel
that led to my rescue
and La Fiera's death.
But she wasn't only here
for retribution.
Her sicarios hit
three competing gangs
at the same time she cut down
Elijah's crew.
They took back
all their lost territory.
BOLOs are out for Abril,
and the DEA and FBI
are launching
a joint task force.
We will keep heightened
security precautions in place
for Detective Lopez and her
- family until Abril is caught.
- Lucky me.
What are
you doing here?
Making things right.
So, alright.
Good work today, everyone.
For those of you 20 hours into
a 12 hour shift, go home.
You've earned the rest.
[ Up-tempo music plays ]
Tamara:
So, what do you want
this video to be?
Something embarrassing
for Nolan.
I can't beat the guy
on the issues.
He actually has a platform.
I didn't know we needed one.
I gotta play dirty to beat him.
I can't beat the guy
on the issues.
I gotta play dirty to beat him.
That's not me.
I can't beat the guy on
the issues.
I gotta play dirty to beat him.
I can't beat the guy
on the issues.
I gotta play dirty to beat him.
She said
she wasn't recording.
There's no expectations
of privacy here.
A good cop should know that.
I gotta play dirty to beat him.
I can't beat the guy
on the issues.
♪
♪ The screaming noises
came across the radio ♪
Here, let me --
let me help.
I got it.
I'm good at cleaning things up
on my own.
I know you are.
♪ I remember what you told me
I'm -- I'm sorry I haven't been
here to help more.
Sorry I haven't been
a better big brother.
You're not that bad.
When you're around.
♪ I parked my car outside
the supermarkets ♪
Well,
all that changes now.
I'm coming to visit you
every holiday.
I'm gonna be calling you
at least twice a week.
And I will handle fixing up
this place and selling it.
You should go home.
Be with your family.
You're my family, too.
♪ And I do
♪ Yes, I do
How about this?
We fix and sell this place
together,
and then we'll both
be done with it.
♪ It's all high, low
All of it.
♪ High, low
Yeah.
♪ It's all high, low
♪ High, low
What ever happened
with that gun?
♪ Oh
♪
[ Clicks tongue ]
[ Yawns ]
Hey.
I'm talking to Henry.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Outstanding.
Hey there, buddy.
How long you guys
been talking?
Oh, about an hour.
Has it been that long?
I have to go
get in the shower.
Really nice finally
talking to you, Henry.
I'm going to need you to
describe that Jiro dinner
in excruciating detail
when you get home.
Deal.
Oh, thank you.
Mm. Thank you.
Bye, Henry.
So, you guys finally
got a chance to talk.
What do you think?
I think that there's a reason
you've been trying to
get us to FaceTime
for the last two days.
Are you proposing?
[ Door closes ]
Um, not -- not yet.
I just wanted to make sure
you liked her,
'cause...
things are getting serious.
Well, I'm happy for you.
And when you decide to ask,
there are some really beautiful
venues out here in Japan.
Destination weddings
are all the rage right now.
♪ High, low
Thank you, buddy.
Arigato.
♪ High, low
Donovan: I had no idea
you would stoop this low.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
I-I tried to have
a conversation with you,
but you left me
no choice.
I did what I thought
was best for Lila.
Congratulations.
Penelope and I broke up
and Lila is devastated.
You broke up?
That's not what I was --
Oh, please.
It's exactly
what you wanted.
The move is off.
You won.
Okay, look, I'm sorry,
but I did what I had to do
to stay in
my daughter's life.
You were doing the same thing,
digging into my past.
Because your past has actually
harmed our daughter.
Penelope's had nothing to do
with anything.
Then why'd you break up
with her?
Because she didn't tell me.
And I can't be with
another woman who lies to me.
[ Exhales sharply ]
I guess there's no telling
when we'll be rid of
the alarm system.
No, but if Abril
wants me dead,
I doubt that thing's
gonna stop her.
She killed eight armed men
by herself.
[ Cellphone buzzing, ringing ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Hello?
Buenos días.
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Abril, where are you?
I just crossed the border.
In 20 minutes,
I'll be on a plane back home.
How's the baby?
None of your business.
What? You don't think
I would hurt him? Or you?
I spent my day wading through
dead bodies.
There's nothing
I'd put past you.
Oh, no, that was just business,
you know?
Unlike La Fiera,
I kill only when it's
strategically advantageous.
But killing a police detective
and her family --
No, that is bad business,
and it will stay that way,
unless you come after me
in Guatemala.
I'm good here.
Bueno.
Then this is goodbye.
[ Cellphone beeps, clicks ]
♪
So, do you see
anything you like?
[ Sighs ]
Um, everything.
I'm warning you right now,
I will be photographing
all of our food.
Go for it.
So...
I've been thinking a lot
about us lately.
♪
Me too.
- You're a pretty decent roommate.
- Thanks.
And you are
a super good kisser.
And the fact
of the matter is,
I'm in love with you.
Thank God.
'Cause I'm in love
with you, too.
♪
[ Horn honks ]
Bailey.
Jason.
I --
When did they
let you out?
Uh, last week.
Uh, who are you?
I'm John Nolan,
her boyfriend.
And you are?
Uh, her husband.
♪