Previously on "The Rookie"...Sandra:
"Querida Angela, in my country,
we tie a red ribbon
around the baby's wrist
"to ward off evil."
I'll be out of here
before you know it. No, you won't.
You can lie to yourself
about it if you want...
Just like you lied
to yourself about Diego.
Diego!
You look amazing.
All right. And something new.
It's like Mary Poppins in there.
[ Laughing ]
Uh, the wedding's in 10.
[ Knock on door ]I'm coming!
Angela?
Breach team is in position.
Copy that...
No sentries on roof.
But drone infrared is not able
to penetrate the structure,
so I don't know what's
waiting for you inside.
Well, let's go find out.
Just say the word.
I repeat, we're green and go.
Nolan: Guys,
Angela's gone. Lucy: I can't find Jackson.
Harper: Malos Dorados just
hit the prison transport.
They freed La Fiera. Tim: She must've
taken them.
Lucy: We got surveillance video
of Lopez and Jackson
being taken.
It's being uploaded now.
Tim: Sir, the breach team
is ready.
We're ready to breach.
Sarge, are you there?
Stand by.
Drone's finishing its pass.
Sarge, you should wait
for my guys to breach.
We can be ready in 20.It's been three hours
since Officer West was killed
and Lopez taken.
We traced the kidnap
vehicle here.
We're going in now.
Breach team, take the warehouse.
Clear.Clear.
Harper: Clear.
Guys, it's Lopez's dress.
Stop!
There's a trip wire running
from the dress under the SUV.
C4... couple pounds of it.
All right, we're outta here...
Same way we came in.
Everyone move slowly
and keep your eyes peeled
for any more booby-traps.
Tim: Sir, the warehouse
is empty,
but they left an IED behind.
We're gonna need the bomb squad.
[ Sighs ] Understood.
Any sign of Lopez? Just an empty
wedding dress.
Most likely, they had
a switch vehicle in place.
Given the timeline, I'd say
they've been on the road
at least 40 minutes. It's too much time.
They could be halfway
to anywhere by now.
Sir, we need that
bomb squad ASAP
so we can process this scene.
Our only hope of finding Lopez
is to ID the switch vehicle.
Nolan: Guys?
They didn't have
a switch car waiting.
They used this old road
as a makeshift runway.
They had a plane.
[ Airplane engine whirring ]
I told you I'd be out
before you know it.
Where are you taking me?
Home
where I am the strongest.
You're wondering why
you're still alive.
It's not hard to guess.
Killing me quickly
wouldn't be satisfying
after I called you out
for Diego's death.
So you're taking me with you
where she can break out
the toolbox and make it hurt.
[ Chuckles ] No.
Abril isn't here
to hurt you, hermana.
She is here to protect you.
Or rather, to protect el niño.
You see, I'm not
going to kill you.
Not yet, anyway.
Not until
mybaby is born.
That's not good enough. Taggart:
With all due respect,
you wouldn't be in this
meeting unless a U.S. Senator
didn't owe your family a favor.
My fiancée was just abducted
by a cartel queenpin
who is running circles
around the DEA,
so don't give me that... Okay! Okay, okay.
This is getting us nowhere.
So
What are you doing to get
my detective back alive?
The DEA is using
all available resources
to track down any intel
on La Fiera's recent actions.
But here's the hard truth...
You have no proof
that Detective Lopez
was even on that plane.
If they were going to kill her,
they would have done it
at the same time
as Officer West.
She's still alive,
and I'm not gonna lose
another cop.
Do you understand me? If we get proof that
Angela was on that plane,
you'll go get her?[ Sighs ]
Look, believe it or not,
I am not a bad guy.
But when you are this high up
the federal food chain,
there is a layer of politics
that needs to be navigated.
Now, the reality is,
you could bring me that proof.
I can't act on it...
Not right away.
If we don't move heaven
and earth to protect our own,
it'll be open season on cops!
Even a suit like you
should understand that.
Sergeant, I share
your frustration...
My frustration?!
I lost a kid who was like
a son to me!
What I'm feeling... is biblical!
So, if you are done
wasting my time,
I have a killer to catch
and a friend to save.
[ Door opens, closes ]
Do you at least know where
La Fiera would take Angela?
Ascertaining that information
is our number-one priority.
Mine, too.
Welcome to your new home.
It's beautiful, no?
I had it built with
the look of the old world
with the comforts of the new.
And the security.
This place is defensible
against everything
short of an air strike.
Para hacerta fácil.
I'll save you the trouble.
We have six guard teams,
two with dogs.
But we rotate them daily so
they don't fall into a routine.
But you'll never get
to test that,
because for
the next three months,
I will not be leaving your side.
Lucky me. Come.
Let me show you to your room.
Bienvenida.
You didn't tell me
que es tan bonita.
This is Dr. Morales.
She brought my angel Diego
into this world.
And she'll be living
here with you,
solely focused
on you and the baby.
Let's get you settled so I can
check your vitals...
Make sure the baby's fine
after all your recent stress.
Don't touch me.
Hermana, you seem
to misunderstand.
You have no choice here.
No free will.
You are here as a surrogate
for my child.
As long as you play nice,
you will want for nothing.
A life full of pure luxury.
But if you resist
if you cause trouble...
Dr. Morales will put you
into a twilight sleep,
and you will spend
the next three months
as an incubator...
Not even conscious
when your baby comes
and your life ends.
Lucy: I almost
got us all killed.
That trip wire
was nearly invisible.
I only saw it because
I had the right angle.
That's not the point.
I should've known to look.
Well, that sounds like
a failure in training.
Perhaps you should
bring it up with Tim.
[ Scoffs ] Can you imagine?
[ Voice breaking ] I ca... I
can't believe Jackson's gone.
I know.
Do you really think that
Lopez is still alive?
Yes, I do.
Why?
'Cause they took her.
If they wanted to kill her,
it would've been easier
just to do it on site.
Yeah, but maybe less satisfying.
Maybe La Fiera wanted
to kill her personally.
Look, we can't think like that.
Tim: No, Harper's right.
We have to look at this
with cop eyes.
Now, give me a reason why La
Fiera would go through the trouble
of taking Lopez
to Guatemala with her.
The baby.
The two women bonded
over motherhood.
Diego's death would have
devastated La Fiera.
Psychologically,
she'd need a scapegoat
for her anger and grief. That was Cesar,
and she killed him.
Yeah, but that didn't
bring her son back.
And then we caught her.
Could that turn her rage on us?
Specifically, on Lopez,
who she felt
betrayed the bond
that they shared.
If La Fiera truly wants
to hurt Lopez,
taking her baby
is the ultimate revenge.
Yeah... that, I buy.Mm-hmm.
What happened?
We're on our own. Lucy: What?
How can the DEA
not help us? Politics.
Harper: W-We can't just do
nothing.Sgt. Grey: We're not going to.
Job one... track down the man
who killed Officer West.
I reviewed the security footage.
Our killer clearly reacted
to something physical
right before he shot
Officer West.
He yanked his arm back.
Nolan: Jackson scratched him.
He knew he was gonna die.
His last act was helping us
find his killer.
Caradine: Coroner found skin
under Officer West's nails.
We're rushing the DNA.
Hopefully, we'll have
results in the morning.
And hopefully, they match
someone in our system.
What about Angela?
I don't know yet.
It's just, um...
Look, we're all racking
our brains, sir.
We'll come up with a plan.
It's not all on you.
All right, um,
today was a hard day...
The worst day.
Go home, try to get some rest
while Caradine's team
takes the baton.
Tomorrow won't be any easier.
I can't go back
to the apartment...
His empty room...
You don't have to.
You can stay with me.
I don't want to impose.
No, Lucy, you shouldn't be
alone right now.
Thanks.
Yeah.
How do you think
Wesley's holding up?
[ Loud rock music plays ]
I need to talk to Elijah.
[ Sirens wailing ]
Hold on! Elijah:
You gotta watch this part.
This is my favorite.
Look, look, look, look.
♪ I've been described as good
♪ Some would even say great
♪ But what have I done
♪ To deserve such a fate?
Mr. Lawyer Man.
Word on the street is,
you got trouble.
Yeah. And you
came to me for help.
Look, I don't have many options.
La Fiera took Angela.
I need to know
where she's holding her.
No problem. In Guatemala.
Oh. Mm.
Well, that adds
a level of difficulty.
You saying you...
You can't find that out?
No, I can get that.
But you know what
it's gonna cost you.
I do. You need to say it.
I become a crooked lawyer
for you.
I use my access and my privilege
to break my oath,
deliver orders
to guys in prison...
Money to people that
you can't get close to.
And you're okay with that?
Because the first time I asked,
you got a little
high and mighty.
I'll do whatever it takes
to get her back.
A desperate man.
That's my favorite kind.
I'll make some inquiries.
Wait for my call.
[ Snarls, growls ]
[ Sighs ] That's not
creepy at all.
You know you're gonna
have to sleep sometime.
I never sleep.
Everybody sleeps.
You'd go crazy if you didn't.
When I was, um, a niña chiquita,
these soldiers came
and they took my father.
Ripped me from his arms.
Just threw me away like nothing.
The doctors told my mother
that the fall damaged
the part of the brain
that controls sleep...
And arousal.
Ironically, although
I can never fall asleep,
I am turned on all of the time.
Sounds exhausting.
[ Laughs ]
Abril, Sandra has lost control.
Even you have to see that.
She's not thinking
rationally anymore,
and that's gonna
get her killed...
And you with her.
Then I die.
And I will finally rest.
[ Sighs ]
Tim: I'll take the couch.
Wait, I thought you were
setting that up for me.
I'm not gonna have a guest
sleep on the couch.
And I'm not gonna kick you
out of your own bed.
Come on. Get up.
Okay.
Um...
Do you need... anything?
The last 24 hours back.
I'm afraid I don't
have that power.
A hug. [ Stammers ]
Yeah. Come here.
[ Sniffles ]
It's okay. Thanks.
Um...
Good night. 'Night.
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
[ Door opens ]Tim: Yeah, okay.
We'll be right there.
Wesley knows where
they're hiding Lopez.
What?
La Fiera is holding Angela
at a compound outside
Guatemala City.
I'm going to get her back,
but I could use help.
I'm in. Me, too.
We all are. Hold on.
The only people
qualified to even think
of doing this craziness
is Bradford and Harper.
Are you saying we don't even try
and save her? Sgt. Grey: Of course not.
But we can't just go running
into hostile territory
without a good damn plan.
La Fiera is gonna have sicarios
and half the police force
protecting her.
She'll know the second
we step off a plane.
So, then, we don't
fly commercial.
Last I checked, LAPD
doesn't have an air force.
And the DEA isn't gonna
lend us theirs.
What about Max?
Who the hell's Max?
I'm listening.
Um, you remember
that counterfeiting case
a while back
that started with the murder
of a transient?
You mean the case
where the killer
came wandering up to you
at the docks in Long Beach?
Yeah, I remember it.
Yeah, well, you weren't
fully "in the loop"
for some aspects of that arrest.
Tim: Max works in the shadows
at the Defense Department.
His unit runs covert operations
around the globe.
They printed that counterfeit
money to fund them.
And we let him walk with it
in exchange for our killer.
He would have the resources
to fly us in under the radar.
Maybe even provide tactical
support on the ground.
And why would he do that? Because
he doesn't want his sins put on blast.
You have a way
to contact this guy? Not exactly.
Well, last time, he found us
when we ran the name of
a colonel through the system.
I would bet that
if we ran that name again,
he'd find us again.
Okay, do it.
Nolan, you fold in
with Bradford and Harper.
Start a mission plan.
Chen, you're with me
at the station
to work the murder case. Yes, sir.
Nolan, come here.
Given everything that happened,
it's easy to lose sight
of what today signifies for you.
The end of your time
as a rookie.
You accepted your punishment
with grace and humility,
and I'm proud to say
you are officially a P2.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.[ Cellphone ringing ]
You're welcome.
Sgt. Grey: Hello?
Congrats.
We're gonna find her. I know.
Well done. Thank you, sir.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
The DNA came back.
We have an ID
on Jackson's killer.
Sgt. Caradine: His name
is Armando De Leon.
17 years old.
Gang unit says he was jumped
into Malos Dorados
six months ago.
Murder weapon is outstanding,
and he's considered
armed and dangerous.
SWAT hit his house
20 minutes ago,
but he's in the wind.
That means we are following up
with everyone he knows.
Let's flush him out.
Shooting policy
is the following...
Even if he's fleeing,
deadly force is authorized.
He's already killed
one of us. Hold up, Sergeant.
We're not in the
retribution business.
This kid comes in in handcuffs
unless there's no other choice.
Is that understood?
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Good.
And no solo riders today.
Everyone doubles up.
Be safe out there.
Look at him. He's just a child.
No, he's a killer.
Now, let's go find him.
Nolan: No, these satellite
images are garbage.
I can't even see the place.
I-If I'm gonna find
a crack in the system,
I need high-res photos.
Blueprints would be even better.
Yeah, we're not gonna get those.
This is not the kind of place
that's ever been listed
on Zillow.
No, but whoever
designed the place
would have the plans.
We just need to figure out
who that is and "borrow" them.
[ Knock on door ]
You were told to leave us alone.
Where's Max? We're all Max.
Why am I here? We need help.
One of our own is being
held in Guatemala...
Angela Lopez. The girl with
the .50 cal.
The woman.
And you're gonna help us
get her back.
No can do. We don't
do private parties.
Cool. I'll be sure to make
that distinction on CNN.
We had a deal.
Circumstances changed.
We're making a new deal.
I can get you in and out,
provide basic supplies
on the ground,
but no personnel.
And if you get caught,
you're on your own.
Next stop, Guatemala.
Two untraceable vehicles,
full gas tanks.
Three ARs, five mags each.
Tim: We won't need them.
This turns into a shooting war,
we lose ten times out of ten.
Harper: Sure,
but I'm still gonna take mine.
In the bags, there's pistols,
an RC ground drone,
scrambled radios, flashlights,
food, and water.
You have ten hours
to get your woman
and get her back here for exfil.
We won't wait,
and we will not make
more than one pickup.
Is that clear? Yeah.
Happy hunting.
All right, we're gonna
set up an overlook,
recon the compound while you go
steal the blueprints
from the architect,
find us a way in.
Right. Wesley's plane
should be landing right now.
He needs to play his part
perfectly, or they're gonna
kill him the second
they're clear of the airport.
[ Plane engine roaring ]
Hola, Señor. Hey, hola.
This way.
Spread your legs. Take it easy.
I'm here to talk to
Sandra de la Cruz.
Man, guess what, gringo?
She doesn't want to talk to you.
So it looks like you flew
a long way...
[ Speaking Spanish ]
Let's go.
No, I didn't.
I have an offer for La Fiera
that she would kill you to hear.
So we're gonna go see her.
Right now.
We can introduce you
to la muertalater.
I'm here. So are we. Good luck.
Okay.
[ Cellphone ringing,
indistinct chatter ]
SeñorMitchell? Yes. Sí.
Yes, and thank you again
for seeing me
on such short notice.
Por supuesto.
Your call was intriguing. Oh, thank you.
As I was telling you
on the phone,
I am the project manager
for the 17th-richest man
in the U.S., and he fell
in love with your country
after vacationing here
last Christmas.
There is much to love.
Por favor.
There sure is.
Now, he's about to close
on a hundred acres
just outside Puerto Barrios,
and he wants to build
something truly unique.
Now, typically, we would go
with Munson Jennings
out of New York,
but I convinced him
we need to look more locally.
I appreciate that.
What kind of property
is he looking to build?
If I may be frank,
something massive.
A compound... uh, main house,
guest house, stables.
The kind of cutting-edge
securities that celebrities
and dictators have
come to love. [ Laughs ]
Have you designed anything
along those lines? Of course.
We have several
unique options in here.
Oh, these are exquisite!
Yes. Very nice.
Now, he will be putting
the main house
right on a mountaintop.
Have you designed anything
specifically like that?
We have.
Maybe you can show me
some of the properties
you've built for him
so I can get a better sense
of his style...
And your capabilities.
Yes, of course.
That'd be a great idea.
Uh, before we get started,
may I use your restroom?
Por supuesto.
Back past the elevators.
Thank you. Uh, gracias.
[ Laughs ] De nada.
[ Fire alarm blaring ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Blaring stops ]Man: [ Speaking Spanish ]
[ Elevator bell dings ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Gears whirring ]
Tim: On the bright side,
they don't have a tank.
Yeah, but they got
everything else.
I mean, this place
is crawling with guards.
Cop car... he's coming up
to the house.
Well, they didn't kill him.
Mr. Evers.
You surprise me.
I didn't think you were
the type to die for love.
I'm here to negotiate. Your office is next
to an aquarium supply store.
What could you possibly
have to offer me?
If you know about my office,
then you know that
my family has money.
A lot of money. I have more.
No doubt, but what
you don't have
is a U.S. senator
in your pocket...
One who is standing ready
to insert language
into the trade deal
that's currently being
negotiated with your country.
Trade deals don't apply
to what I sell.
No, but they do apply
to the export companies
you use to launder money
in the U.S.
Tariffs are killing you
right now.
I could cut them in half
with one phone call.
If I let you walk away
with Angela.
And my baby.
Let me make a few phone calls.
Ensure that you can deliver
on what you promise.
And then we'd
have a deal? Maybe.
Or, maybe I don't care
about the money,
and I feed you to my dogs.
[ Sighs ]
Sgt. Grey: Control, 7-Adam-100.
Show us Code 6 at 1305 Dozier.
Armando's cousin lives in 3C.
You ready?
Yeah.
Look, I know it hurts.
But you're a professional.
It's your job, and everyone
is depending on you to do it,
especially Jackson's family.
And you don't want to
let them down, do you? No, sir.
Good. Let's go.
7-Adam-100.
Send backup to our location!
Code 3!
[ Rattling ]
Armando!
Freeze!
Armando, show me your hands!
All right, all right.
You got me. Lucy: [ Over radio ]
7-Adam-100.
B to A, what's your 20?
Sergeant Grey, where are you?
What's your t...
I ain't scared.
Yeah, you are.
I bet you were even scared
when you pulled that trigger
and killed my officer.
A young man so full of life.
It hurts my soul to think of him
lying on a cold table
in a dark drawer.
You're here to get revenge?
Revenge
it's a fantasy.
I got a devil on my shoulder
telling me he's holy,
and it would be
so easy to listen.
So easy to give in
and pull this trigger...
Just like you pulled
that trigger.
But I won't.
[ Handcuffs clicking ]
You're under arrest for the
murder of Jackson West.
If there's any justice
in the world,
you'll realize
the grief you caused
and the life you threw away.
Control, 7-Adam-100.
I can't raise my partner.
We may have an officer down.
I need help and an ambulance.
Code 3.
[ Sighs ]
Thank God. Ugh.
Control, cancel
that distress call.
7-Adam-100 is Code 4.
Hey. Are you okay?
What the hell are you
doing here?
Negotiating for your release.
[ Whispers ] Hey.
We have a plan.
Buying time until Tim and Harper
can get us out of here.
Hey! Hey!
Back it up! Back it up!
She's not yours anymore!
No, she's mine!
Okay? And you don't touch her
unless I say you can.
Do you understand me?
He's got it.
We're all good.
Right, baby?
Yeah, I'm good.
Nolan: I got bad news.
According to the blueprints,
this place is a fortress...
Redundant security systems,
pressure-sensitive alarms.
But there's good news,
too, right?
Yes. There should be
a covert way in.
It's an access tunnel
that leads to the wine cellar.
Pan left. Tim: Okay.
Right at the base of the house.
And, there. Now zoom in.
And it... Damn it!
What? Well,
they realized it was a weakness.
They put a gate on it.
That was not in the plans.
Maybe we can break the lock,
or, uh, bump it, or...
No. No, we'd be
exposed too long.
A roving patrol would spot us.
Plus, there's no guarantee
that other, new security
measures aren't inside.
[ Sighs ]
We have to go to Plan B.
I don't like Plan B.
There are too many unknowns.
Would you rather stage
a frontal assault
on an elevated position?
No!
[ Cellphone rings ]
Did you get her? No.
We're going to Plan B.I don't like Plan B.
Join the club. It's what we got.
Are you ready? Uh, just...
Just let me get set up, okay?
Call me when you're in position.
Max, come in. Go for Max.
We're going to Plan B.Ooh. Really?
Yeah, we don't have a choice.
The pickup's at
a new extraction point.
Copy that. We'll be there in 60.
But if you're not there
on time, we're not waiting.
All right,
we got to go get set up.
I'll stay here, keep eyes-on,
let you know
when they're on the move.
Then I'll fall in behind,
meet you at the exfil.
Wait.
We got to alert Wesley.
[ Fireworks exploding
in distance ]
That means there's a problem.
We have to go
to Plan B.What's Plan B?
Means they can't
get in to rescue us.
We have to get La Fiera
to get us out of here.
How? She's not letting me leave
until I have the baby.
Hey! Go get a doctor!
Hey, go! She's feeling
really lightheaded.
Oh.She's had blood pressure
issues during the pregnancy.
Uh, lay her on the bed. Go! Hurry up!
Okay. It's okay.
[ Velcro rips ]What the hell is that?
Pitocin. Enough
to start contractions.
No, no. It's too early.
We will lose the baby. Angela, Angela.
We need to get them to
take us to the hospital, okay?
Harper will be there with a drug
to counteract the effects.
I know you're scared.
Listen, I'm scared, too.
But this is the only way
outta here.
Trust me, okay?
[ Speaking Spanish ]
Come on, let's go!
Let's hurry up!
[ Groaning ]You okay?
It's fine. You'll be all right.
Let's go! What did you do?
Nothing. Hey!
Lopez: Wait!
What are you doing?!
[ Speaking Spanish ]
Lopez: What are you doing?!
No! [ Groaning ]
No! No!
No!
We got a problem. Harper: What is it?
They're taking Wesley
somewhere to kill him.
I'm going after them. There's no time.
The chopper will be here
in 30 minutes.
He'll never make it back.
John, you can't.
We have... I have to.
I'd never be able to look
Angela in the eyes again
if I didn't.
John, listen to me...
There's nothing we can do
to help him now.
Damn it![ Cellphone rings ]
Hey. Hey. You got them?
Not yet.
Uh, wait.
Yes. A black SUV,
yellow stripes.
They have a Guatemalan
police car escorting them.
How far out? Um, five minutes?
All right, thanks.
We got it from here.
T-Tim?
Please be careful.
I always am.[ Cellphone beeps ]
You ready? I told you I hated this plan,
right?
Twice. But it's gonna work.
Element of surprise.
Little shock and awe.
A controlled retreat. Yeah, we'll see how
"controlled" it is.
I'll see you on the other side.
[ Engines shut off ]
Lopez: [ Groaning ]
Okay. [ Speaks Spanish ]
[ Buzzer buzzes ]
[ Siren wails ]
[ Engine revs ]
All: [ Screaming ]
[ Air hisses ]
[ Both coughing ]
♪ The walls are closing in
♪ My skin feels paper thin
♪ My mind is trapped again
[ Groaning ]
Okay. All right.
How do you feel about running?
I'm in labor. Not for long.
Give me the shot!
That should stop it
pretty quick, okay?
We gotta go. We gotta go.
♪ Living the lie
♪ Are you gonna live?
♪ Are you gonna die? [ Speaks Spanish ]
♪ I cease to exist
♪ No right to exist
Tim: Max, we need
immediate evac.
We are three minutes out.
Okay.[ Gunshots ]
We're gonna be dead
in three minutes.
Get here faster! We need to save Wesley.
They took him! Nolan's got him.
[ Door alarm dinging ]
[ Groans ]
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
[ Groaning ]
Let's go, let's go!
[ Screams ]
You okay?
The bullet just grazed me.
What about Wesley? And Nolan?
We need to make another stop.
No other stops. I told you that.
Okay, we're gonna
make another stop.
Oh, this is very dramatic.
Life is sacred, no?
We should honor it
when we take it.
Plus, they'll use your body
as fertilizer.
Makes the oranges extra sweet.
Bueno.
This is far enough.[ Gun cocks ]
Where do you want it...
In the face or
the back of the head?
Neither.[ Tractor engine starts ]
Ohh!
[ All grunting ]
[ Both grunting ]
[ Hollers ]
Aagh!
[ Grunting continues ]
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
Come on. That's our ride.
Lopez:
Go, go, go! Let's go! Let's go!
Go, go! Go, go!
Tim: Go, go, go, go, go!
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
Lopez: I miss the nurses.
Why did we have
to leave the hospital?
Well, they kicked us out.
Welcome home! Welcome home! Welcome home!
Oh, no. Did we just
wake the baby?
No, it's okay.
Watch.
7-Adam-20, shots fired
at Pico and Arlington!
He sleeps through everything.
He's the best baby ever,
which means I'm
the best mom ever.
She doesn't know
they all sleep like that
for the first few days? Nope, and we won't
tell her.
Hey, I'll get him settled.
Thanks, babe. No problem.
You guys didn't
have to do all this.
We wanted to.
You got a year's
worth of diapers,
and both freezers
are stocked with meals.
"Both"?
We ran out of room,
so we bought you
a second freezer.
Nolan: What are you
in the mood for?
We have mac and cheese,
lasagne, enchilada,
mac and cheese... All of it.
I like your style.
Enjoy.
So, Nyla and I
put this together.
There's fenugreek,
Shatavari, goat's rue tea...
Great for breast feeding...
Raspberry leaf... excellent
for uterine health...
And, of course, an assortment
of lactation cookies
filled with brewer's yeast
and moringa.
These are homemade.
Thank you so much.Mm-hmm.
Uh, I'll... I'll go
put the rest of this away.
All I'm saying
is that, personally,
I would not eat any of it.
Not even the cookies?
Especiallythe cookies.
But it made her happy
to focus on
something positive, so...
I'm gonna go hide these.
♪ Oh, oh
♪ So, go ahead and burn bright
♪ Try to be your
♪ Shelter from the rain
I thought they'd be mostly
pulling each other's hair out
by now,
but Mom and Patrice,
they just play with the baby
and gossip about "The Bachelor."
I live in fear
that they'll start watching.
"Real Housewives" next.
What else?
Kind of miss the station.
Not the smells but...
the rest of it.
I know I'm lucky right now.
Can't imagine going in and
not seeing your smile
or hearing your voice.
[ Sniffles ]
By the time my leave's over
maybe I'll be able to face it.
Anyway, [Sighs]...
that's my update.
♪ Go ahead and bright
Come on, Jackson. [ Sniffles ]
Let's go home and see Daddy.
[ Sniffles ]