Previously on "The Rookie"...
Someone should really run against him.
Lopez: You could.
Lucy: It's Aaron Thorsen.
TikTok famous
before he got arrested
for murdering his roommate.
Sgt. Grey: Officer Thorsen
was found not guilty.
I've been thinking about
your arson case.
I ran a search and found
two unsolved cases.
Both in Nevada,
both suffered broken legs
before dying in a fire.
We've got a serial killer
on our hands.
Woman: Go!
I can't wait to hear this story.
This isn't what it looks like.
It looks like you're creating
a falling hazard
in the middle of a public park.
Yeah, that's part's exactly
what it looks like.
The question is, why?
Uh, I lost my keys?
Sir, is this yours?
Yeah, actually, uh...
Can I get that back?
"If gold's your goal,
then take a stroll,
let angles point you here."
Sir, are you digging
for buried treasure?
If I say yes,
are you gonna arrest me?
No. Since you haven't done
any real damage
to city property,
we will cite you and let you go,
but you need to
fill this hole back in.
Okay. Yes.
Yes, it's a treasure hunt.
But I'm starting to think
there's no treasure down here.
You know that says "Angel's,"
not "angles," right?
Man.
I've been digging all day!
Whoa!
Does that count as...?
Real damage? Yeah,
I'm afraid it does.
Well, I-I'll fix it.
I'll fix it!
He was wrong about the location.
That doesn't mean
the treasure map is a hoax.
No, common sense
means the map is a hoax.
Plus, it's not even a map.
It's a poem.
Okay, you scoff,
but the Internet
is taking this very seriously.
Mm-hmm. You want me to list
other things
the Internet takes seriously?
Point taken. I'm just saying,
it's worthy of an investigation.
What?!
Smitty... I didn't think
he could stoop so low.
You need a new slogan anyway.
I do? Yeah, definitely.
And a new poster,
while you're at it.
I mean, this kind of feels
a little middle school.
No offense, sir, but, I mean,
you need a cooler picture,
better graphics,
maybe a QR code to link
to your campaign website?
You do have
a campaign website, right?
I will as soon as you become
my new campaign manager.
Are you sure?
I mean, this is
a lot of responsibility,
and you've only known me
a few weeks.
And I'm already impressed.
Plus, you want to
tip the scales of justice,
make a difference.
I plan on shaking things up
around here.
You should be a part of that.
And you know publicity.
Yeah, badpublicity.
That's the spirit.
Alright, I want to see
three new design ideas
by tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Jerry McGrady. Hm.
Tim: Guy's been a cop since
E.T. phoned home.
Yeah.
I'm out of options on
how to assign him.
Now, I put him behind
the front desk,
he spends an hour with each
and every person that comes in.
Well, he's not any better
in the kit room.
Every time he lifts a war bag,
I worry he's gonna stroke out.
He needs to retire.
Yes, he does.
And that's what I want you
to talk to him about.
Is that part of
my sergeant's training,
or are you trying to avoid
being a bad guy?
A little bit of both. Mm.
But, hey,
it's a difficult conversation.
No. No, it's not.
Look, Jerry's seen it all.
He's done it all.
Best thing to do
is to show him respect
and be straight up.
And if he pushes back,
his injury will make it easy
to retire him
with an involuntary disability.
Young Mr. Thorsen.
How's the training going?
Great. Or terrible.
I mean, only Detective Harper
knows for sure.
Well, next time I see her,
I'll ask,
and report back what she says
on the DL.
I'd appreciate that.
Look, I know the program
is stressful,
but I hope you're making time
for your personal life.
Netflix and I
are closer than ever.
Seriously,
learn from this old man.Mm-hmm.
It's easy to let the job
become your whole life.
Let me help you with that.
Thanks.
Here you go. Alright.
Hope you don't need 'em today.
Yeah, me too.
Tim: Jerry.
Sergeant Bradford! How ya doing?
I'm good, Jerry.
Do you have a second to talk?
Of course.
I always knew I'd be
working for you one day.
What you went through
in your early career
could've taken down
a lesser man.
But you handled everything
with grace,
like a true lawman,
and this old man's proud of you.
Thanks, Jerry.
So what can I get you, Sarge?
Name it.
Well, it's actually
what youneed, Jerry.
Are you sure you're okay
working kit room duty?
I mean, you're... you're
carrying a lot of injuries,
and I just want to make sure
you're up for
the daily aggravation.
I'm fine.
I get to see everyone.
I get to hear stories.
Makes me feel like
I'm still part of it, you know?
Yeah. Yeah.
Alright, look, Jerry, I'm just
gonna be straight with you.
What do you say
you ride with me today?
Seriously?
Uh... It would be an honor.
Great. Uh, you get your vest on,
and I will see you at the shop.
How'd it go?
You're gonna want to
assign someone else
to cover the kit room.
Jerry's riding with me.
What happened to
the cold, hard truth?
I got this.
By the end of the day,
he'll be buying a boat,
I promise.
Hey.Hey.
Any update on
that serial killer?
The lab isolated the acetone
he used as an accelerant
in both fires.
It's called Instant Strip.
But the manufacturer
discontinued it last year.
Why? Why what?
Why... Why did they
discontinue it?
I used to use it all the time
when I was contracting.
I just want to make sure
I'm not gonna get cancer
or anything crazy, because...
I'm... I'll just Google that.
What about that victim
that Harper rescued?
Last thing he remembers is
getting hit by the killer's car,
then waking up in the hospital.
Hey.
I thought I was
coming to see you.
We were in the neighborhood.
John, Angela, this is
Lieutenant Fred Mitchell.
Nice to finally meet you.
I'm looking forward to
your barbecue tonight.
Yeah, it should be fun.
Bailey tells me you have intel
you want passed around
to the fire crews.
Yes.
So far we know that our guy
is targeting ex-addicts
and he's killing them
in abandoned buildings.
Our operating theory
is that he scopes
the buildings out first,
but we don't know
how he targets them.
So far, he's picked
a house in foreclosure
and a condemned warehouse
across the city.
What's the deal with
the gold watch?
Uh, that belonged
to our first victim.
It's possible the killer
took it as a trophy.
Maybe he'll leave it behind
at another fire.
It's a long shot,
but if your people see anything,
just let us know.
That's all you have?
No, but it's all we're
releasing right now.
Well, if I lose a firefighter
because you withheld
something important,
I'm gonna be pissed.
We'll keep you in the loop
on everything you need to know.
Okay. Mm.
Fred's a good guy.
He's just a little direct
sometimes.
No problem. Hopefully the flyer
will get us a break in the case.
See you later. Thank you.
Okay, quick, before you go,
uh, what can I bring tonight?
Nothing.
Fred puts out quite a spread.
Thank you for saying yes, again.
I know it must feel like
you're meeting
my 10 older brothers
who will do nothing
but judge you all night long.
But? There's no but.
Oh, okay.
Uh, I do have to bring
something, though.
I can't arrive empty-handed.
Fine. Bring... flowers.
Perfect. Thank you.
Flowers, I can do.
Bye.
Hey.
Assignment change.
Tim is riding
with Jerry McGrady,
so I'm with you.
Kit Room McGrady? Why?
I'm past the point of asking.
Okay, well, no. That's good.
That's great, actually.
I can tell you all about
the treasure map we found...
Treasure poem
that we found... puzzle?
First thing we do,
we decide what to call it.
That used to be a Woolworth's.
And right there,
that's the first place
I ever got stabbed.
How many times were you wounded
in the line of duty?
21.
Nine stabbings, two gunshots,
four broken bones,
three teeth knocked out,
and two torn hamstrings.
That's, uh... That's 20.
Right.
Food poisoning, 2007.
Last time I let Smitty
pick a restaurant.
You know,
all that wear and tear...
Gotta make it hard to put
the duty belt on in the morning.
It's a righteous pain.
Dispatch: Control, 7-Adam-47.
We are Code 4
on the barking dogs.
That guy sounds like
Junior Gamez. You remember him?
Junior. Yeah.
You, uh... You still
in touch with him?
Ah, not since he died.
What about, uh...
What is it... Buddy Kepler?
Yeah, I remember Buddy.
He was just, uh...
Oh, he was nuts.
What about his...
Buddy's brother Frank?
He was even worse.
Yeah.
Buddy passed in '09.
Frank, 2014.
Oh, man.
It's great being out
on the streets again.
Hey, I gotta wait for
my client in lockup to sober up
before they can question her.
Wanna grab lunch? I can't.
I inherited a case from Burns
that goes to trial next week,
and I need to start prepping.
Hmm.
I've never been to court
for a case that wasn't mine.
And Burns can't fly in
from New Mexico for the trial?
I called.
She yelled, "I'm retired,"
and hung up.
But if you're free later,
it would be great
if you could walk me through
a cross-examination.
Sure. I'll go easy on you.
Hell no. Put me on the stand.
Give me your worst.
Oh, you can't handle my worst.
Bring it, pretty boy.
What do you think of roses?
They're a little predictable,
but a timeless symbol
of love and romance.
Wait, is it Bailey's birthday
or something?
No, they're not for her.
Uh, her boss is having
a barbecue tonight.
Okay.
I should bring something else?
I mean,
to a firefighter's house?
Yeah. Beer.
Ahh.
And someone put a lot
of effort into this,
although the rhyme scheme
is a little loose.
"If gold's your goal,
then take a stroll,
let angles point you here."
The guy we arrested thought it
said "angels," not "angles."
He won't be the last one
to make that mistake,
although "angle" isn't
necessarily a noun.
Oh. Uh. Uh, uh, uh!
The Santa Monica Pier.
That's our first stop.
How do you know that?
Just trust me!
We gotta head over there.
Okay, but if we find
the money, I get half.
Of the zero dollars
we'll be allowed to keep?
Yeah, deal. Ooh!
I think this line refers to
one of those coin-operated
viewfinders.
You might want to intervene.
They've tapped into
their inner Neanderthals.
Woman: Out of my way!
Man: I was here first!
Whoa! Hey, police!
Woman: No!
Hands on the rails.
Control, 7-Adam-15,
send an RA to our location.
Victim's a woman, 30s,
impalement to her chest.
She's not conscious,
not breathing.
This poem was posted on Reddit
two days ago,
and it's the reason why
a young mother
is laying
in the morgue right now.
Uh, people are only gonna
get crazier
hunting for the treasure.
So Nolan was right.
I'm sorry, if you say that
again, I can record it.
People actually think that
this will lead them
to buried treasure?
Yes, because Stuart Packer
claims to be the author.
Why does that name
sound familiar?
He pulled the Joseph & Wells
robbery back in '03.
Ronnie Wick was
the lead detective.
I was there when they brought
Stuart in, the little snot.
He wouldn't tell us where
he hid the gold coins.
Gold coins?
Yeah. Nearly $2 mil worth.
Sgt. Grey:
We never recovered the coins.
The city's losing its mind.
I mean, w-we're getting
flooded with calls
of people climbing
the Hollywood sign,
diving into Echo Park Lake.
Alright, we need
to find this gold
and to end the chaos
as quickly as possible.
Now, Chen, you deciphered
the first clue.
How'd you do it?
Well, i-it... it first clicked
when I realized that
"angle" could mean "fishhook."
The pier is
a favorite fishing point,
and fisherman are also
called anglers.
Nerd. What?
Don't let him shame you.
That was a great catch.
Thank you, Jerry.Okay.
What about the rest
of the stanza?
Uh, "Next find the lens
thru which you'll spy"
the West Coast's greatest view."
I mean, the lens is obviously
the viewfinder at the pier.
Yes, and, uh, um,
this next line,
"The fee you pay," refers to
the fee of the viewfinder,
which is 75 cents,
so we just need to change 75
into a-a year.
But what century?
That could be 1775...
It's 1975.
It's the Year of the Rabbit.
Call me a nerd. I dare you.
Well, uh, the poem states,
"The fee you pay becomes
the year of Rabbit minus two,"
so 1975 minus 2 is 1973.
Okay, okay, okay.
What does it mean?
1973 could be
the combination of a safe,
uh, the number of
a storage locker.
Uh, it's not gonna make sense
until we solve
the second stanza.
The third stanza says that,
once we put
those two clues together,
we will find the gold.
Harper and Chen, I'm putting you
in charge of solving this.
Uh, sir. I have been known to
solve a Timescrossword, uh,
once or twice in my day.
Well, I'm sure
they'll let you tag along
if you ask nicely, Nolan.
Thorsen, you're riding with me
the rest of the shift.
Everyone, be vigilant out there.
Hey, uh, you guys want in
on this task force?
'Cause I can make that happen.
Cute. But Jerry and I,
we're gonna solve this
with good, old-fashioned
police work,
not literary analysis.
Damn straight.
I'd love another shot at Stuart,
smug little bastard.
Care for a friendly wager...
Who finds the treasure first?
You're on.
If we find it first,
you have to stay quiet in
the shop for an entire shift.
Okay, uh, and if we win,
you have to do something
completely out of
your comfort zone... my choice.
Enjoy your little poetry club.
Enjoy reviewing 18-year-old
evidence from a cold case.
I hear those
are super easy to crack.
Do you honestly think that
my client murdered his wife
and then stuck around
waiting to get caught?
It's not about what I believe.
The facts are that he was
holding the murder weapon
in his hand
when officers arrived.
Cops have a saying, don't they?
"The husband always did it."
Everyone has that saying.
Right, so you and all
the officers working on the case
went in assuming
my client's guilt.
That's not fair.
I agree.
Police bias is never fair.
Did you even bother
looking for another suspect?
I mean, the victim's
estranged business partner
didn't have an alibi.
The business partner
wasn't found at the scene
holding the gun. Well, according
to my client,
in his panic,
seeing his dead wife,
he picked up the murder weapon.
Did you even bother checking
the second layer of prints?
Of course. Came back no match.
And did you run the prints
both orientations?
No, Detective Burns did not.
I need to go run those prints.
Thanks for helping.
I wasn't too hard on you, was I?
Part of me wanted to slap you...
The other wanted
to jump your bones.
Oh, me too. God, I love us.
Who knew people would go
so mental over buried treasure?
Clearly, you did, Stuart.
And the question is,
why start a treasure hunt?
Are you really looking
to give away your stash,
or you just trying to
get on the news?
They've been talking about me
all morning.
It's pretty cool.
Wish they'd use
a better picture, though.
Did you see that a woman was
killed because of your poem?
But that wasn't part
of the plan.
That was just a fun bonus.
Yeah, you pretend to be a tough
guy, Stuart... Mm.
But Ronnie Wick told me
you wept like a baby
when he put the cuffs on you.
Yeah, your buddy's full of crap.
Drove him nuts I never gave up
where the gold was,
didn't it?
Oh, I heard he kicked it
a few years back.
That sucks he never got
that closure.
Look, Stuart, you got
your thrills, alright?
Now I can get you upgraded
to the nicest cell in here.
Maybe even get the DA to knock
a few years off your sentence.
Just tell us where the gold is.
Sure.
Give me something to write on.
Here's where I hid it.
The DA can always
add a few years, too.
Oh, you don't know, do you?
I'm terminal. Pancreatic cancer.
Mm. Karma's a cruel mistress.
When they denied my request
for a compassionate release,
I realized I'd never get to
spend my hidden fortune,
so I decided to
let chaos rain down
on the City of Angels.
Guard. All done here.
Jerry.
You weren't just around
when Stuart got arrested...
You were friends with
the lead detective.
Look, I want to take you down
to the scene of the robbery.
I want you to walk me through
everything you remember
about the crime, even what
the city looked like back then.
Jerry: This is it...
Joseph & Wells Rare Coins.
At least, it used to be.
Alright, so Stuart pulls up
in a stolen getaway car,
parks there, goes in,
grabs the gold,
comes out,
jumps back in his car.
It doesn't start,
so he flees on foot.
We apprehended him 12 hours
later near Western and Melrose.
Even if Stuart was on foot
the whole time,
he could have covered
quite a bit of ground.
Now, the original search grid
has him going west.
Because 90% of suspects turn
right when exiting a building.
Oh, man.
I think Ronnie messed up
back then.
Today, when Stuart wrote
"up your ass,"
he used his left hand.
Meaning it was more likely
Stuart went left
after the robbery.Yeah.
The original search grid
was way off. Let's go.
Lucy: Oh, dammit.
Tim just texted me.
Him and Jerry just had
a big breakthrough.
Oh, he's just trying to
get in your head.
Ignore him. I agree. Focus.
"Watch the Stars of Hollywood
influence from their spheres."
Stars of Hollywood.
What... What are we thinking?
Can't be movie stars.
That's too obvious.
"A monument to Rebels gone."
Are they dead? Is it a cemetery?
The Forest Lawn Cemetery?
They do mention "lawn."
Okay, well, we have "monuments,"
"dead Rebels,"
and "darkness' edge."
That... That could be
a cemetery.
Yeah, but what about
these spheres?
Uh, where are they
influencing from?
The... The heavens? The stars?
Oh, wait, that's it.
Stars, spheres,
celestial objects, heavens.
Griffith Observatory. Griffith Observatory.
Yes, and the Observatory
was in the movie
"Rebel Without a Cause."
They even have a bust
of James Dean's head up there.
Alright, the rest,
we can decipher later.
Wait, wait. Hold on.
I gotta text Tim and tell him
we are about to kick his ass.
Huh. Ah.
James Dean's bust
is just up this way.
Officers.
Looks like we need
to up our game.
Seriously.
Gotta be in it to win it.
Woman:
He's got a bomb!
Hey!
Hey, stop!
Stop right there!
I know this looks bad,
but if you'll just let me
blow up that wall,
I can finally prove to my wife
that I was right about
something.
Sir, you need to drop
the bomb right now!
Guys, chill!
I know what I'm doing.
Ohh!
These damn treasure hunters
are packing dynamite now?
The deceased is
a special case, sir!
Why are you yelling?
I'm sorry. Uh, uh, my ears.
The explosion was loud.
Uh, the deceased had access
to demolitions
because of his job
at a quarry in Oregon.
They're coming all the way
from Oregon?
That's it. We need to
lock down this location,
cut off access
to any more gold seekers.
Now, how close are you guys
to figuring out the poem?
We're at a bit of
an impasse, sir.
The second stanza states
that the next clue
is only visible in
early morning light.
The longer this goes on,
the more dangerous it becomes.
Look, I need the gold found.
Aaron: So, I need y'all to
stand back, okay?
Stay back. Stay back.
Thank you for your service.
Sorry. I know
that's usually for the military.
I just, uh... It's just,
I appreciate you guys.
And I know you don't usually
get to hear it.
No, uh, thank you.
That... That means a lot.
I'm Cleo, uh, Officer Thorsen.
Aaron.
Nice to meet you.
Can I buy you dinner?
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
I should not be bothering you.
That just slipped out.
No, no, no, no. No, no. Uh...
D-Dinner sounds good.
Um, but it's on me.
Actually...
can I get your number?
Yeah.
Text me later. Yeah, for sure.
Well, congratulations.
You just had your first contact
with a "badge bunny." A what?
A woman who is attracted to
the uniform,
only dates cops.
So, I recognize her.
She dumped Officer Haspel
a month ago,
Sergeant Daffern in May,
and Officer Williams,
I believe, a year ago.
That's a relief.
I thought maybe she had, like,
a podcast or something
and was only interested in me
'cause of my past.
Thanks.
Jerry: What's the plan
for tomorrow?
Yeah, look, about that, uh...
We need to have
a conversation, Jer...
Hey, Dad.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Your car's in the shop,
remember?
You asked me to pick you up.
Right. Sorry.
It's been a busy day.
This is my daughter... Ashley.
Tim Bradford. Nice to meet you.
He's been texting me
all day about you.
It really meant a lot to him
to be back out on the street.
Would you like to join us
for dinner,
as a "thank you" for today?
I couldn't.
Yeah, you can.
My daughter makes
a mean take-out,
just like her old man.
Sure. Yeah, sounds nice.
I told you to bring flowers.
Yeah, I know.
How'd you know I was here?
I went to get napkins.
I saw you pull up.
Hey, John.
Glad you could make it.
Thanks. I brought beer.
Actually,
this is a sober gathering.
A couple of the guys
are in recovery,
and we decided as a family
to honor their struggle.
That is very thoughtful
and probably why Bailey
suggested I bring flowers.
Well, I do love flowers.
I'm just gonna put this
in the truck.
Appreciate it.
Okay, we have until
dawn tomorrow
to figure out this next passage,
but no pressure.
Okay, look.
"A monument to Rebels."
That's plural, so it can't
just mean James Dean.
What other statues are nearby?
Okay, there's one
on the front lawn
of six prominent astronomers.
I mean,
scientists ahead of their time
could be see as rebels.
Is one of them Sir Isaac Newton?
Yeah. What...
What are you thinking?
Uh, "Follow in
a great man's path",
his First Law as your guide."
So we start at Newton's statue.
And follow his path
in a straight line.
"Until darkness' edge you find."
What... So we walk
until we hit darkness?
A shadow.
That's why we have to start
at early morning light...
Otherwise the shadow
won't be in the right place.
Ooh! There it is.
You know, riding with you today
was the highlight of Dad's year.
Hell, his last five years.
Yeah, I don't get it.
Most cops who stay on the job
this long,
they don't have anything else
waiting for them,
but I'm sure you'd love to
be able to
spend more time with him.
Mm, because I've got nothing
going on in my own life?
No, no. That's...
That's not what I meant.
Relax. It's a joke.
No one ever gets my jokes.
I guess I'm just used to
jokes being funny.
I-I guess that's why
I got confused.
Honestly, I think my dad regrets
not retiring 15 years ago
when he was still on the street.
Like all his buddies did.
Comin' in hot.
Thank you.Yeah.
Oh. Hey, Bailey.
Good to see you.
Hey, Marcus.
This is my boyfriend, John.
Hey, nice to meet you.
And you. Hey.
John's a cop.
Oh. Oh. That is impressive.
He's very impressive, isn't he?
Thank you for that.Mm-hmm.
And how to you fit in here?
Oh, I just, uh, live
across the street.
Marcus is the best neighbor.
Whenever I'm at the station
for a stretch,
he keeps an eye on my place...
Waters my plants,
eats all my ice cream.
Okay, that happened one time
and I will never
hear the end of it.
He ran off to Nevada
over the summer
for, like, two weeks.
He left his fridge full
of chocolate mint fudge.
What am I supposed to do?
That sounds like
extenuating circumstances.
I'm sorry. I don't think
a jury would convict.
Hey, you're low on ice.
Uh, there's more in
the garage fridge.
I'll go grab it.
Thanks.
Hey.
The re-orientated print
came back as a match
to the business partner.
Burns arrested the wrong man.
Yes!
See, I knew that guy was fishy.
Wait. Did I just exonerate...
We.
Did we just exonerate a man
who wasn't even my client?
I knew I was good, but damn.
Nolan, what's up?
I'm at
Bailey's lieutenant's house
and I just stumbled upon
a case of acetone
just like the kind
our arsonist uses.
Lots of people use it. Yeah, I know.
But I just found out
that Fred here
was in Nevada over the summer.
Do you know what month?
'Cause if we can put him there
at the time of
the second Nevada murder...
He didn't say.
I can try and find out.
Would that be enough
to get a warrant?
No. We're gonna need more.
We'll need to do a deep dive
on this guy,
find something beyond
circumstantial evidence.
Okay. And what should I do?
Do about what?
Uh... I'll call you back.
Hey, there.
I was, uh...
Just grabbing the ice.
Do about what?
Oh, nothing.
John, why are you lying to me?
Alright, so here is
the "great man,"
Sir Isaac Newton.
Lucy: And his path along
the shadow.
And then what?
The Ancho family.
Who are they?
Cover it.
So much for no one
having the next clue besides us.
I know Fred. He's not a killer.
He spent all yesterday
handing out those flyers,
talking to other lieutenants
at other houses,
asking them to spread the word.
Does that sound like
the actions of a guilty man?
It doesn't, but there's enough
circumstantial evidence
to warrant an investigation.
Because he was in Nevada
this summer or owns acetone?
Which he uses for woodworking,
by the way.
I know this is hard.
If he's innocent, then we can
eliminate him as a suspect,
and then we'll just be
that much closer to the truth.
I know you're doing your jobs.
I get it.
Just do it fast, okay?
I gotta get to work.
You can't breathe a word of this
to Fred or anyone else.
I won't.
Okay. Tell me what you think.
For some variety, I went in
two completely different
directions.
Those are amazing!
I love them both!
Huge improvement.
Yours were terrible.
That's fair. This is...
Can I have a copy
of each of those,
one to send to my son?
Yeah. You give me the go-ahead
and I'll print up 100.
Absolutely. Go ahead.
Sergeant Grey said you had
an assignment for me?
This is my suspect,
Fred Mitchell.
Get a good look. You're
gonna hunt for him online.
Easy. Don't get cocky.
Fred has
no social media footprint.
But most of his friends
and coworkers do,
so use them to document
everywhere he's been,
especially last summer.
Well, where the hell
did he stash the gold?!
Uh, we'll figure it out,
alright? Our plan is solid.
We'll cross-reference
our new search grid
with every location in that file
until we find it.
I don't know.
It's gonna take
a lot of days, Sarge.
A cop like me doesn't have
many of those left.
Yeah, about that...
We need to have
a frank conversation.
Get the hell out of here.
Excuse me?
I know where the gold is.
Wait, for real? You sure?
Absolutely.
Oho! We are gonna win this bet.
So, the Ancho family...
Who are they?
Harper: Not sure,
but the next step
is to put the first clue
with the second, so these...
Sorry, guys.
I have to take this.
Hey. I checked
Fred's work schedule.
Bailey.
I know, but it was easy to do
and no risk.
And what did you find out?
He was on vacation when
the murder in Nevada occurred,
but that doesn't mean anything.
I will tell Lopez.
Then what?
Then about a thousand
other steps.
Investigations take time
and paperwork and patience.
What kind of evidence
do you need
to get a warrant for his house?
Something that would give us
his exact location...
Receipts, uh,
credit card statements.
Okay, I gotta go.
I'll talk to you later.
Alright. Thank you.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I hope so. Where are we?
No one in the Ancho family died
or was born in 1973.
Okay, then what if
it's not a year?
What if it's an address?
1973 Ancho Street.
Well, wait.
It says in the poem,
the two clues "translate."
Ancho means "width" in Spanish,
so wide, deep, broad.
Uh, 1973 Broad Street.
That's, uh... That's right here.
That's downtown.
It's a dress shop.
"If you seek true happiness,
you must look within."
Does the dress shop
have a basement?
Um...
Oh, uh... The Red Car.
It's the original subway
in Los Angeles,
built in the 1920s.
It's right underneath that shop.
Nolan: Wow.
I never even knew
this place existed.
It's been shut down
since the '50s.
Harper: It's a perfect place
to stash gold.
Mm.
Man: I got here first.
That gold is mine.
Man #2: Do you think solving
the poem is the only way
to find the gold?
You... I saw you.
You were at the Observatory...
Behind me.
All the better to find you.
You thought you could just
follow me here
and steal my treasure?
All's fair in
love and gold, my man.
Now tell me where
the treasure is
or you're dying in this tunnel.
Dude, you brought a shovel
to a gun fight.
Nolan! Stay with him!
Hey.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
He's running. Get him.
7-Adam-15.
Foot pursuit
in an old subway tunnel.
Heading South.
Control, Adam-100.
Go ahead and cancel
that backup call.
We're Code 4.
How did you guys
get here so fast?
We were already here.
Did you...? Find the gold?
Let's see.
My gold. I was so close.
Yeah, not really.
What... How did you guys
even end up down here?
Jerry found it with the file.
It said in there that
Stuart's sister worked at
the Bonaventure Hotel
up the street.
And their parking garage
has access to
all these abandoned
subway tunnels.
Yeah, so Jerry thought Stuart
might have known about it
from his sister
and stashed the gold down here.
The entrance was sealed
a few years back,
but I sweet-talked
the maintenance guys
so they opened up, let us in.
Me and Jerry win.
No, we would have
been here first,
but we had some police matters
to deal with.
Great. Good job. We still won.
Nope, we're gonna call it a tie.
What? No way it was a tie!
- 100% a tie.
- Ohh!
I wish Ronnie was here
to see this.
I bet he'd have been proud
you were the one who closed it.
Yeah, not too bad
for an old-timer, huh?
You did great.
Look, Jerry...
Just...
It's my time.
It's my last day on the job.
Thank you, Sergeant Bradford.
For what? I feel awful.
No, no, no, no.
You could've pushed me out
on an involuntary disability,
but no.
You let me go out
the way I came in...
Working the streets...
on my last patrol.
Thanks. Yeah.
Damn it.
John, I was
searching Fred's house...
You what?! Yell at me later.
He's here now, and I'm trapped.
Sit tight. I'm nearby.
John. What are you doing here?
Uh, well, I was on patrol,
and I realized I was
in your neighborhood.
And you stopped by to say hi?
Yeah, and... say thank you
for the party last night.
I had a great time.
Sure. You're welcome.
Uh, Fred, I, um...
I also wanted to ask you
about Bailey.
What about her?
Well, I'm an old-school guy,
and, uh, both of
Bailey's parents being gone,
you are about the closest thing
she has to a father...
Stop.
If you are about to ask for
my blessing to marry Bailey,
don't say another word.
You may be old-school,
but Bailey is as modern
as they come,
and she would not appreciate
you talking to me
before talking to her.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
You really helped me
dodge a bullet there.
I've taken enough of your time.
Thank you very much.
Sure.
John...
Good luck.
Thanks.
That was so stupid! Tell me about it.
I mean, you want to marry me
after only dating a month?
I had to say something
to distract him,
and now I amgonna yell at you.
Do you... Fred has the victim's watch
in his office,
and a whole lot of other things
that look like trophies.
You can use that to get
a warrant, right?
Yes, I can.
I thought I was gonna
prove him innocent.
So, how was the date
with the badge bunny?
Well, with all due respect, sir,
her name is Cleo, okay? Mm.
Let's not label her.
Last night, actually,
she was open and honest
about only dating cops,
so we shouldn't judge her
just 'cause she has a type.
You know, you're right.
I apologize.
Yeah.
How was your date with Cleo?
It was fantastic.
She's... She's great.
She thinks I'm great,
and, uh, we're actually
going out again tonight.
I'm glad you found someone
who's not put off by your past.
Actually, I don't think
she knows who I am.
You didn't tell her?
And you think that's fair?
I mean, she told you about
her thing,
but you want to keep her
in the dark about your thing?
It's just...
It's been a long time
since someone's liked me for me.
I understand, son.
But she's gonna find out
about it sooner or later,
so who do you want her
to hear it from?
Yeah.
I'll, uh...
I'll tell her tonight.
Good man.
Can you imagine what that stuff
is worth now?
Phew. Yeah.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Tim called.
I'm so proud of you.
Alright, folks,
attention, please.
Turn your hand packs
to the district channel.
I need to borrow your dad
for a second.
Hey, Jerry.Yeah.
Control, 7-Adam-100.
I am privileged to announce
the retirement
of Officer Jerry McGrady,
badge number 9944.
After 43 years and 9 months
of service,
this concludes his final shift.
Officer McGrady, you, sir,
are End of Watch.
Congratulations.
Uh...
It's been an honor
serving this great city
all these years.
S-So...
take care of her
now that I'm gone.
- Whoo!
- Jerry!
Congrats.
That was really beautiful.
Dad won't forget it.
Neither will I.
It was my honor.
Your dad is a hell of a guy.
You know, maybe I could
stop by the house sometime,
see how he's handling
retirement.
That'd be great.And...
maybe... you and I
could grab dinner sometime?
Even better.
Judge signed off on the warrant.
I really don't think
you should be here for this.
Tough. Hey.
Remember, you said you don't
run towards bullets,
so I shouldn't run
towards fire? Mm-hmm.
Well, there could be bullets,
so I need you to stay...
sync & corrections
jhj@2021