-Here we go.
-We're rolling.
Spring 2021.
The group's walking a new path.
For the past 27 years, they've existed
as the idol group TOKIO.
And today, all three are in suits.
Let him take one picture
sitting like a president.
-Okay.
-On the chair?
-That's unexpected...
-Yeah.
This is unexpectedly fitting.
-Yeah...
-I agree.
This trio is walking a new path.
And it is TOKIO Inc.
TOKIO originally consisted
of three members when formed in 1990.
They debuted their first CD
four years later.
They had an unusual rock band style.
The wild idol group
would sometimes remove clothing on stage.
Having gotten older,
they've chosen another wild path
of creating their own company this year.
TOKIO INC. STARTED
There was some change. That's why
we decided to establish our own company.
If we don't enjoy those changes,
time will pass us by
and things will end on a vague note.
Landscapes I haven't seen.
Yeah, that's something I want to see.
I had my title sewed on.
It's a secret.
PRESIDENT
I went to a local tailor myself
and got it done.
I made the reservation,
and the shopkeeper said,
"he's actually here!"
and was all surprised.
APRIL 1, 2021
The three members started their company,
announcing it in the Nikkei.
Sweat.
Work.
Experience.
This is the company's motto.
I'm TOKIO Inc.'s president, Joshima.
Thank you for your card.
My name is Matsuoka.
Pleased to meet you.
If you get cold, you can burn my card.
It's not a piece of firewood...
What kind of company will this be?
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
TOKIO INC. BEGINS NOW.
It's two months
before they establish their company.
FEBRUARY
The three are in talks at the moment.
TAICHI, SHIGERU, MASAHIRO
The main agenda for today is
to see if Matsuoka can use Zoom.
Yes, I heard.
Yeah, I don't know
so I'll leave it up to you.
But you can't just ask a manager.
Do it yourself.
I don't know how to approach this.
-Including that.
-Exactly.
The Zoom application.
Zoom app?
Is that app on this thing?
I just gotta search for it, right?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Zoom.
-Wow.
-Here it is.
You okay?
The password...
What's the password?
Just a moment.
Open.
I'll take a picture now.
Here we go.
This is my first time doing a video call.
You're so Showa.
-It's amazing that you can do this.
-It is amazing.
-Sorry, please look here.
-Yeah, go ahead.
MARCH
Pictures for the homepage.
The members take pictures themselves.
-We can relax doing it.
-Yeah.
-I think these are really good.
-That's too close.
Oh, it is good...
-See? I told you so.
-Yeah, yeah...
It's good. I like it.
-Right?
-Yeah.
It's good.
The president is the leader of the group,
Shigeru Joshima.
He's quiet and receptive to others,
with a gentle personality.
Taichi Kokubun.
Vice president in charge of planning.
Full of ideas,
he proposes various projects.
Hold on. Move back a bit.
And the youngest, Masahiro Matsuoka.
Vice president in charge of PR.
Known for his mischievousness,
he's actually sensitive.
He's an indispensable member that
aligns the group on the same wavelength.
For this shoot, I wanted to take pictures
without exerting ourselves.
The promotional photos
we've taken before were too perfect.
I'm tired of those.
We don't need to overedit these.
This is just fine.
-Is it blinking?
-It is.
Is it? I can't see it.
They all remain particular with their work
all the way through to completion.
-Did it take?
-There it goes.
TAICHI KOKUBUN
These business cards
are an example of that work.
TOKIO INC. PRESIDENT
SHIGERU JOSHIMA
TOKIO INC. VICE PRESIDENT
MASAHIRO MATSUOKA
MARCH
They've set out to create business cards
in Fukushima, a place they've grown close
to through years of television filming.
The group cuts down the trees themselves.
That's great.
-Come on!
-Hey!
How was that?
Hey!
It's not falling.
-Fall over!
-It's not.
Trees are alive too, you know?
It's like, "It'll take more than that."
Guys, running a company is the same thing.
It's not that easy.
Come on down!
Go!
-It fell over!
-You did it!
It's amazing. Trees are amazing.
-It was very resilient.
-What an amazing tree.
It's a good tree.
The back of the business card
has an engraving of TOKIO Inc.'s logo.
Kokubun designed it himself.
By doing things with our own hands,
I believe it has given us confidence.
A sense of completion and pride.
By having more of these feelings,
I strongly believe
we've given ourselves more confidence.
I hope that people out there
appreciate and acknowledge
our originality,
the things that are unique to us.
It's a kind of warmth.
It's a kind of memory.
A sign that the tree was alive.
I wonder what we'll leave behind,
what we'll make.
There's a level of anticipation.
In the end, I'm not satisfied
unless I do it by myself.
If you do or make something yourself,
you can complain.
But if you have someone
do it for you, you can't.
I think a sense of responsibility
arises there.
It's better if we make ourselves do it.
Their homepage has been completed.
Hello. This is President Joshima.
TOKIO Inc. will partner up with businesses
to spread the concept of creating things
to all the people of Japan.
We are looking for partners
who will help us realize our vision.
From the planning
until the fruition of the project,
they're not just speakers
on the sidelines.
They're involved as part of the team.
PLANNING THE CREATION OF THE COMPANY
APRIL
THREE WEEKS AFTER THE START OF THE COMPANY
Good morning.
I'm Joshima, the president.
Wow...
TORIDOLL HOLDINGS
Their company is collaborating
with a large group
that has udon stores nationwide.
The three have been asked to think
about a summer promotional campaign.
I'm Matsuoka.
Hello. I'm Awata.
Thank you for your card.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
This isn't just a company project.
This isn't simply
a request to do something.
We'd love to have discussions
about ideas that
we can't come up with ourselves...
For the longest time, they've danced
and entertained on television.
Now they must come up with ideas.
Please send us a video
that shows the texture of the udon.
The texture of
Marugame Seimen udon versus...
the texture of a baseball.
This isn't a meeting for a TV program.
-It was just an idea.
-Yeah, I know.
So you want the Marugame Seimen food truck
to go all around the country?
-That's great.
-Yeah.
People will come take a look
at the food truck.
Being able to actually visit
the food trucks
will energize people.
In addition, they'll come up with
new menu ideas.
This is our first meeting and here we are...
Focusing on what will make mothers happy
might be the most interesting.
It's very difficult though,
to create a balanced lunch meal.
A kid's meal may be good.
Yeah, something like that...
That's interesting.
Japanese people often eat udon when
they aren't feeling well or have a cold.
-Yeah.
-Right.
When my kids have fevers,
they'll eat udon.
Happily.
The ideas they come up with
also require results.
Kokubun went back to the office that night
to brainstorm more ideas.
You've been writing ideas
in there all day.
-Ah, yeah...
-Your notebook.
It's like,
I have to take notes when the client
becomes enthusiastic about something.
I've gotten a lot of use
out of this notebook.
-I've taken a lot of notes.
-Wow.
Yeah.
It would be nice if we could create
some merchandise like this.
Here's some ideas for stickers.
This design is
on the back of the notebook.
You already have it created.
This is pretty interesting.
There's fun in seeing an idea
become a tangible item.
What changes
when something becomes a tangible item?
As a company,
we have to do everything ourselves, right?
Yeah.
In many cases we won't get any work
if we're not proactive.
Artists and entertainers
are often a part of a large company.
For TOKIO Inc., I'm the point of contact.
This means I have to work myself.
I'm not young anymore.
I can't just rely on others.
The president's in his fifties now.
He's fifty-one years old.
MAY
Good morning.
Today Kokubun's visiting a test kitchen
to try out some new menu items.
-Thank you for coming.
-Oh no, it's my pleasure.
He'll be testing an idea
he thought of during the meeting,
the udon lunch meal for children.
He'll be selecting
each ingredient himself.
It has to be something nutritious
for the parents to consider,
while making the children happy.
From a food education perspective,
if the meal's contents are well-balanced,
there's your answer.
In the future, it could also be part
of the household menu.
You're right.
We'll need a meal
that could be used as a sample.
Kokubun himself is a father
taking care of his children.
You could say they're moody...
-Let's try a piece of fried chicken.
-That's the top recommendation.
-This is?
-Yes.
-Is it?
I can't imagine udon with fried chicken.
Right?
I'm sure a fried wiener
will make them happy.
A little bit of this...
As a parent, I'd want to put something
with more color in their meal.
A long time ago,
we used to put corn with the udon.
Children loved it with the corn.
Even just with corn.
This is good.
This is good. It fits perfectly.
The fried shumai works really well.
Let me take this piece of broccoli
and put it in here.
-How about mayonnaise on the broccoli?
-Do we have any mayonnaise?
Maybe it's because I'm an old man...
I feel relieved when there's boiled food
to go along with the fried stuff.
Is it because I'm an old man?
Experiencing the meal directly
leads to even more ideas.
Parents will usually open up
the packet of broth for their children.
If the children
could do this by themselves,
that would save time and effort
for the parents.
Opening the broth packet
isn't easy for kids
and will cause a huge mess.
Yeah.
Would it be possible, um...
before we present something,
to have a group of mothers
try out the meal ahead of time?
I want to be loved by everyone.
So if somebody said that
this is completely awful,
it'd be a bit...
I've become pretty scared of that.
What kind of meal will he create?
-Hello. Good morning.
-Good morning.
Thank you for having me today.
Your arm.
The children's udon lunch meal that
TOKIO Inc. created
will be tasted
by their client company's president.
TORIDOLL HOLDINGS
They paid most the attention to
the ingredients' nutritional balance.
They improved the broth container,
making it easy to open for children.
Excuse me. This is the kid's udon meal,
in regular and large sizes.
I'm really nervous.
It looks nice.
-It's colorful.
-Yes, very.
Thank you for the meal.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, yeah.
Yes, this is delicious.
I feel like I'm a child.
-Pretty good.
-Is it okay?
Yes.
Mr. Joshima also had some.
He said the corn is sweet and delicious.
He complimented the colors too.
Really? That makes me happy.
-The president approved?
-Yes, he did.
That makes me happy.
There's one more idea.
TOKIO Inc. developed
this product from scratch.
Curry udon with tomato and egg.
Matsuoka is in charge of this.
Making these meals is a hobby for me.
I really do enjoy making them.
Matsuoka is known for his love of cooking.
Using a recipe he's developed
over many years,
he's made an original dish.
Good morning.
-Thank you for having me.
-Thank you for coming.
JUNE
UDON TASTE TEST
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Oh, it looks good.
I like the tomato.
-It's the tomato.
-Yeah.
The tomatoes are wonderful, yeah.
It's nice and spicy.
Yeah, it's nice and spicy.
This is the menu for summer this year.
I'm so happy to hear that.
In the end, both items were discontinued
in the midst of their popularity.
Thank you very much.
-Thank you for today.
-Thank you for coming.
TOKIO INC.
As pop idols get older,
they are faced with decisions to make.
Why did these three choose
to establish a company?
We were fixated
on using the TOKIO name for our company.
With all the experiences we've had,
we didn't want to lose
the core essence of the name TOKIO.
That's why it felt right to create
another set of experiences.
It felt appropriate.
As for the three of us working together,
people were opposed to it.
It was not like...
we were encouraging ourselves.
When you get to this age,
you've experienced
a lot of different things.
And using your own filter,
you think about new ways
to express yourself.
What's a road
that can only be paved by TOKIO?
We have to create a new path.
At my age and being part of this company...
it fills me with excitement to be able to
try approaching new things.
"That's intriguing."
"I've never established a company before."
Somehow...
Those kinds of things motivate me.
AUGUST
-Thank you for having me.
-Thank you for coming.
Today, another campaign idea
from the meeting has come to fruition.
Creating a food truck.
The truck has been decorated
with wooden panels, as per TOKIO's style.
Each little idea is brought to fruition
one at a time.
It all starts there.
That's good.
-Is it good?
-I did it.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-I did it.
This is really good.
You've done a great job.
On the next RIDE ON TIME...
I just want to clean it up.
TOKIO Inc. has hit the ground running.
They sweat and work every day.
Now that there's only three of us,
so I have no choice.
And Kokubun's back on the music stage.
I do like to create things.
I'm showing proof
I'm participating in something.
Realizing those passions.
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin