2021 SPRING
7 COLORS OF LIGHT EMITTED BY A GROUP OF 7
I don't know how many tours we have left,
but let's go out there and have fun!
Can we do that?!
We can do it!
Okay, let's go.
Yeah!
Yay!
It's been seven years since their debut.
JOHNNY'S WEST.
This year's tour will be the first to
feature a live audience in two years.
However...
As of right now, Osaka's been canceled.
JOHNNY'S WEST
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA (28)
Due to the spread of
the novel coronavirus,
the concert that was planned to be held
in their hometown, Osaka, was canceled.
And the rock festival they were hoping
to perform in, has also been canceled.
The group steadily loses
venues to perform.
The group of seven
on their seventh anniversary.
What will they be able to do
in this tough situation?
Definitely this year.
It's RIDE ON TIME!
A blue horizon
Run through...
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
"Eejanaika!"
Yokohama, you're the last show!
Let's hit it out of the ballpark!
Let's go! Yeah!
In April 2014,
JOHNNY'S WEST made their debut.
Their debut song "Eejanaika"
reached first place on the Oricon Chart.
DAIKI SHIGEOKA (29)
In the center of the group
is Daiki Shigeoka.
Can you keep up with us?
Akito Kiriyama hosts many variety shows
and drives the group
with his broad perspective.
JOHNNY'S WEST
AKITO KIRIYAMA (32)
I'm Junta Nakama!
The oldest, Junta Nakama, shows
his knowledge on informational programs.
Everyone can rely on him.
Are you having fun?!
JOHNNY'S WEST
JUNTA NAKAMA (34)
Tomohiro works on live choreography,
lyrics and song composition.
Tomohiro Kamiyama's talents
are in his creativity.
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA (28)
Known for his energetic performances,
Ryusei Fujii is loved by audiences
as being an airhead on TV.
RYUSEI FUJII (28)
JOHNNY'S WEST
TAKAHIRO HAMADA (32)
Loved by all for his character,
he's the life of the party
and a comforting friend.
Takahiro Hamada.
NOZOMU KOTAKI (25)
An actor and a model.
With his excellent style,
he's the youngest member.
Nozomu Kotaki.
We're going to heat things up!
Can you keep up with us?
Today's the first zodiac reunion
in 100 years.
I can't watch this!
They've been searching for their own path.
No, I can't hold this.
Hey, you're holding it in your hand!
The first five years after we debuted...
It felt like we were calm at sea.
No tailwinds or headwinds.
The public didn't really know
about JOHNNY'S WEST.
TOKYO AND KYOCERA DOME TOURS 2020
But they finally got their chance
to hold two large dome tours last year.
But with the pandemic,
that dream did not come true.
We haven't really gone ahead of ourselves.
We've taken it one step at a time.
In fact, we've had times
where we stopped progressing.
That's why...
We want to perform at the Dome.
The winds started blowing
in their favor this year.
Both Shigeoka and Hamada are starring
as main characters in their own dramas.
And this fall, the group's namesake
program will air on national television.
NAMESAKE PROGRAM
TO AIR ON NATIONAL TELEVISION
So viewers, now's the time
to invest in us.
They'll be like, "We should have
cheered for JOHNNY'S WEST more back then."
Everything started in February.
Starting in April, the group will have
a seven-stop tour around the country
called rainboW.
CONCERT MEETING
The meeting to finalize the first concert
with a live audience in two years.
"Big Dipper" hasn't changed.
Let's go with the full.
And this is from the headset.
-Headset.
-Headset?
With a mic, I thought that
it might look like a different dance.
It's been three years
since Fujii started directing.
There have been some big changes.
Kotaki, the youngest says...
NOZOMU KOTAKI (25)
We had less meetings before.
We only went over the important parts
and found that
we often weren't ready in time.
With Ryusei at the center,
We're not sure what to do
about the live performances over the year.
Fujii's been thinking
about it all this time.
Good morning.
MARCH
CONCERT FOOTAGE FILMING
Today they're filming footage
to open their concerts.
You can see my face at the last moment.
It's like, bam...
Fujii pays great attention
to detail here as well.
Ready, action!
JOHNNY'S WEST's live performances
are generally like "Bam! Ryusei Fujii!"
Then it's like, "Wow!"
The way I see it is
all about the timing of the "Wow."
But this time we can't say anything.
So I'd like the footage
to be a bit more natural.
We won't put anything like "Bam!"
or any names this time.
Okay, cut.
Cut.
Cut!
Okay, thank you!
Okay!
Thank you!
They're doing what they can
during the pandemic.
Fujii joined Johnny&Associates,Inc.
in 2006.
He was 13 years old at the time.
He was a tough boy that played soccer.
It was his mother
who suggested Johnny&Associates, Inc.
But he turned 18 before he could debut.
I was just constantly in a daze.
I thought it'd be better if I quit.
But there were two choices.
Quit or join the Nissay Theatre.
I called Mr. Johnny and said I want to
join Nissay Theatre's Shonentachi.
And he said, "But I officially
announced the members already."
"You can't join now."
I thought about giving up,
but two days later...
"Nissay Rehearsal."
The sign said, "People going to Nissay."
And I saw my name and Nozomu's.
I was like, "Whoa!"
I thought to myself, "I'm going!"
This sort of helped
continue my life at Johnny's.
I laid this town to waste.
They called me Johnny at the time.
18 YEARS OLD
It's better to do something and regret it,
than regret not doing something.
Kamiyama, who spent his junior days
with Fujii says...
RYUSEI FUJII
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA
These days, Ryusei's been studying
how to direct concerts a lot lately.
He goes to see other artists perform.
He even went to Las Vegas to study.
He's proactive and always on the move.
He's taking it all in
and using it to help the group.
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA (28)
So I really trust him with this stuff.
I need a "zun!" here.
Can we do it again?
-Can we do it again?
-One more time?
With Fujii at the center, the group
will try something new in their concerts.
This time, all seven members
will have their own solos.
This is the first time
we'll be doing this.
It's an average of five minutes
for each member.
That's a total of 35 minutes.
Right.
Thirty-five minutes of solos
in a two hour concert?
I think that's pretty amazing.
And this will be a challenge for us.
But if every member can really shine
for their five minutes,
it'll be an amazing feat
as a seven-member group.
Our seventh anniversary
with seven individual solos.
There's a member in the group
that pays great attention
to their solo performance.
MARCH
Good morning.
Good morning, morning!
I've brought the equipment I usually use
and the guitar I'll need today.
Kamiyama who works
on the composition and lyrics
is filled with passion for the music.
KAMIYAMA IS SERIALIZED
IN MUSIC MAGAZINE, MG.
On this day, a scoop for a music magazine
where his works have been serialized.
Good morning.
Good morning. Let's get started.
-Let's get started.
-Thank you.
It's a session with the band he admires
that has arranged his solo song.
I'm really nervous!
No, no. We're the ones nervous here.
That's some insane equipment.
Yeah, it's amazing.
It's hardcore.
Isn't that crazy?
Kamiyama started the guitar
when he was in middle school.
These are all Kamiyama's own equipment.
I often play with these at home.
The reason why he's focused on
the guitar now is because of this song.
He's always wanted
to create a song like this.
As for Hamada...
JOHNNY'S WEST
TAKAHIRO HAMADA (32)
I was actually better at the guitar
than Kamiyama at first.
I started learning before him.
But he started learning
and before I realized it,
he was teaching me how to play.
Seriously.
Seeing him get better made me realize
just how important it is to keep doing
your best even when no one is watching.
Kamiyama's thinking of doing
a creative solo arrangement this time.
MARCH 13TH
SOLO PRACTICE
I want to film all instruments.
The guitar, bass, and drums.
I want to create a video where
it looks like I'm a five-man band.
That's why I'm practicing.
If I do something simple,
it won't be interesting.
I want to show the audience what I can do.
He's playing all the instruments himself.
What kind of solo will he show us?
Kamiyama joined the agency in 2004.
He admired V6,
being only 10 years old at the time.
His personality took a 180-degree turn
from when he was younger.
According to Kotaki...
He's calmed down a lot.
He used to be so edgy
like a kadokeshi eraser.
He'd say, "Hey, Umeda group!"
When we went home,
we had the Umeda and Nanba groups.
Like, "Umeda group! Let's go already!"
I tried to stay away back then
because I don't like scary people.
Yeah, I was really uptight back then.
It was because I was young.
When I first debuted, I still had
a little bit of that personality.
I thought, "I gotta do something
about this. I'm his senior."
Finding people I can depend on and trust.
Learning how to depend on
and trust someone.
That's how I calmed down.
Rather than doing everything myself,
I would leave some parts for the others.
Then I take charge of my own part.
Everything starts in Sapporo.
The tour of this
seven-member group started here.
-Ah!
-Good morning.
Good morning.
APRIL 28
This is the third stop in the tour.
Backstage in Nagoya...
JOHNNY'S WEST
Hey! Shigeoka!
It's RIDE ON TIME!
Hey!
FILMING: TAKAHIRO HAMADA
Ow.
You're just here to bother me.
Go over there.
This is how Kiriyama dries his hair.
Doing it like this...
gets me some nice curls!
They're beautiful curls!
Sexy, sexy, whoa! Sexy, Ryusei, sexy.
We don't really show
the behind-the-scenes.
Ah, yeah.
"Ah, yeah."
Lady bug make up.
Yeah, it's spring.
-Spring.
-Because it's spring.
-Spring style.
-Yep.
Pat, pat, pat, pat.
Kamiyama's putting on make up in the air.
Look at that powder fall down.
It's RIDE ON TIME!
A blue horizon
Run through...
Ah...
What will this concert be like?
Horizon...
Whoa.
There's so many people. Let's do this.
Thank you, let's go.
Are you excited about our show tonight?
Piece of cake.
Are they really there?
There's a live audience, right?
Wow, it's so quiet.
It really is. Are they not there?
No audience today?
Unlike before, live audiences in concerts...
are not allowed to cheer,
shout or make any noise.
We got a live audience today too.
Every single time is important for us.
Let's have some fun, get everyone excited,
and make it good!
Yay!
I don't know how many tours we have left,
but let's go out there and have fun!
Can we do that?!
We can do it!
Okay, let's go.
Yeah!
Yay!
They're finally going to be
in front of their fans.
For the opening song,
they purposely chose a quiet one.
It's a narrow hallway,
so please be careful.
It's a narrow, so please be careful.
We can only do this because of
how well-mannered the audience is.
I can feel
the audience's blessings for us.
Then they had their solos.
JUNTA NAKAMA'S SOLO
TAKAHIRO HAMADA'S SOLO
"YASASHII HITO"
AKITO KIRIYAMA'S SOLO
"KANASANDO"
DAIKI SHIGEOKA'S SOLO
"SARARIIMAN NO TOUSAN"
RYUSEI FUJII'S SOLO
NOZOMU KOTAKI'S SOLO
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA'S SOLO
Nagoya, this is the last one!
Take my message with you!
LET THEM LAUGH AT YOU,
STICK OUT LIKE A SORE THUMB, LAUGH IT OFF
THEY'RE ALL NOTHING BUT SCRATCHES
LOSE YOURSELF IN IT ALL NOW
There's a lot going on right now.
If you're ever feeling down,
just remember this.
You're also part of JOHNNY'S WEST.
Everything will be all right!
THANK YOU
The members' emotions got through
to the audience.
LET'S CHASE THE DREAM!
Good work everyone.
Yay!
Hey there.
We did it!
But here in Nagoya,
they were told some bad news.
As of right now, Osaka's been canceled.
Due to the spread
of the novel coronavirus,
the concert that was planned
to be held a week later
in their hometown, Osaka, was canceled.
Furthermore...
This really sucks.
I was looking forward
to Osaka and the METROCK.
The festival they wanted to perform in,
the outdoor rock festival,
METROCK, was also canceled.
APRIL
OSAKA METROCK 2021 REHEARSAL
It's a rock festival for famous
domestic bands and artists to perform in.
JOHNNY'S WEST
was scheduled to perform too.
I think guys would like the songs too.
It would be nice if people
acknowledged our music at this festival.
"JOHNNY'S WEST's got a cool sound."
"They got some good songs.
Let's listen to them some more."
"MACHIGACCHANAI"
There was one song they wanted to perform.
WHO KNOWS WHAT WILL HAPPEN TOMORROW
NOBODY KNOWS
MEETING YOU, BELIEVING IN OUR DREAMS
BARING OUR FANGS AT THE ANSWER
IT'S NOT WRONG
This song represents them.
"A song that would cheer anybody up."
We're making more and more preparations.
We're adding more things
we can do to our list
so we can cram everything
into our performances.
It's like having a new dream or purpose.
On the next RIDE ON TIME...
This group of seven are in high spirits
and have reached a new stage.
We're confident
we can show ourselves to anybody.
There was some unforeseen trouble too.
Thank you.
But people who laugh when they're sad
are so much stronger.
Wow...
They're all testing themselves
in their own areas.
"Should I be here?"
That's what I'm wondering.
I'm going to do my best to perform so
people can say that I was the best.
Where do they get this energy from?
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin