SEPTEMBER TOKIO INC. OFFICE
TOKIO Inc.
The company's long-desired project
gets off to a start.
I'm the vice president of TOKIO Inc.
I'm Taichi Kokubun of TOKIO.
Thank you for applying for
the cooperative project
Make with TOKIO, with our company.
We truly appreciate your application.
Thank you.
They're challenging themselves
by partnering with different organizations
to create something new.
To choose their partner,
they have been interviewing
a wide variety of candidates.
The influence we received was huge...
I have a question.
So am I correct in assuming that your firm
can support all farmers nationwide?
As for imperfect produce...
Do you have any plans
to put these on the market?
Our president will be 70 years old
in 20 years, is that okay?
It's okay.
-That's good.
-It's all good...
Is there anything you decided you won't do
as a company at the present time?
You won't do...
Let's see... I don't think so.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
For 27 years, they lived as TOKIO,
this is their new challenge.
Oh!
This is TOKIO Inc.
APRIL 1, 2021 NIKKEI
The three members hold something
dear to their hearts.
Sweat.
Work.
Experience.
They did everything themselves, right from
the meetings before the company formed.
FEBRUARY
KOKUBUN, JOSHIMA, MATSUOKA
The main agenda for today is
to see if Matsuoka can use Zoom.
Yes, I heard.
Yeah, I don't know
so I'll leave it up to you.
But you can't just ask a manager.
Do it yourself.
I don't know how to approach this.
-Including that.
-Exactly.
I'll take a picture now.
Here we go.
This is my first time doing a video call.
You're so Showa.
They've started to create something.
What's a road
that can only be paved by TOKIO?
We have to create a new path.
"That's intriguing."
"I've never established a company before."
Those kinds of things motivate me.
Into an unseen world.
Action!
Energize Japan with udon!
-Say it.
-Okay.
-It was our president.
JUNE FILMING FOR DRAMA SAMURAI KASAN
He's here.
Joshima challenges himself
to something new.
Eat the katsudon.
You watch too many cheap detective dramas.
Two chukadon and two gyoza.
Now 50 years old, this is his first time
as the main character in a drama series.
Show me.
Stop it.
He plays a mother raising
an adolescent son.
Papa, he's hiding something.
I just know it!
-Oh, oh, oh!
-What? What are you doing?
-Ohhh!
-Ouch...
Let me go already.
Have you been properly resting?
Of course, I want to.
But I need time to read the lines.
I have to remember them.
Our group is in charge of composing
the main theme song for this drama.
My kid is asleep at night so I needed to
figure out where I could play instruments.
But I found some time
and composed up to the chorus for now.
But since then, I haven't had
much time to play any instruments.
What time do we start again?
There's one thing
that supports him during these busy days.
Those are the memories of his mother
raising him with all her heart.
During a drama promotion interview...
My mother is very old-fashioned,
very Showa period.
She's the stereotypical mother from Osaka.
My mother would always say,
"That's such a waste."
There's a river called Yamato River.
I caught two carp one time
when I was in elementary school.
I told her, "I got two of them!"
"That's wonderful," she would reply.
I put them in the water tank
in the back somewhere.
That night, we had grilled fish.
When I said, "My fish!"
She replied, "I grilled them."
"Just eat them," she said.
The next day, I came home
and I said, "I'm hungry."
I look over and she says,
"I boiled them in soy sauce today."
Can you please place your legs
in the pink area? Thank you.
Here I go.
Joshima did not have
an easy time as a young boy,
but he decided to become a pop idol.
Okay.
FULL OF LOVE
In 1990, when the three formed TOKIO,
Joshima was already 19 years old.
He was oldest and the leader of the group.
UNDERSTAND THE EFFORT WE MAKE!
Joshima wanted to change his life.
I saw Shonentai on TV,
they were in the spotlight,
singing and dancing.
"I can't believe
there's a world like this."
If I jump into that spotlight,
my life will change.
I wanted to free myself
from everyday life.
I wanted to change.
I didn't belong anywhere,
so I wanted to jump into that spotlight.
I have memories
of feeling like that back then.
However, 19 years old
is a slow start for a pop idol.
He had one weapon though.
That was the guitar.
Makes me want to drink tea from a teacup.
Back home in high school,
I was already playing the guitar
and forming bands.
I thought I'd go for what I'm good at.
I used to play at the dorms.
Mr. Johnny saw me and said,
"If you like instruments so much,
why don't you form a band?"
And that's how TOKIO started.
They were a rare type of an idol group.
TOKIO was born as a rock band.
Sometimes they would wear
T-shirts or nothing at all.
They've always done things their own way.
COMPOSING THE THEME SONG
FOR DRAMA SAMURAI KASAN
This is really tall.
Like it's for Nagase.
No, no.
It's been seven years
since Joshima composed a song.
"KOKORO NI HANA"
SHIGERU JOSHIMA
This will be sung by KanJani8.
KANJANI8 / GUIDE VOCALS
Joshima is recording
the guide vocals himself.
Testing, testing.
-Something surprised me now.
-Yeah?
I was looking at my headphones
and couldn't see the "L" or "R" on it.
I know what you mean.
I know exactly what you mean.
It made me scared.
I know how you feel.
IT'S OKAY IF TODAY DOESN'T WORK OUT
JUST TRY AGAIN TOMORROW
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT HEADWINDS OR WALLS ARE THERE
THEY ARE THERE FOR YOU TO OVERCOME
TODAY'S FAILURE IS
TOMORROW'S SECRET INGREDIENT
THERE'S A FLOWER IN YOUR HEART
BATHE IN THE SUNLIGHT
OPEN AND CARVE YOUR PATH
NO MATTER WHERE YOU GO
The lyrics of the song come from
his memories that have supported
this journey he has been on.
This is tough.
-The beginning...
-Yes?
It doesn't really sound like KanJani8.
I see.
How should I put this? They're more...
-A little unrefined.
-Yeah.
-I strained myself too much.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, I see.
For over an hour and a half...
he continued to sing.
AUGUST HIROO, TOKYO
Good morning.
Today, he's in a photoshoot
for the police department's
scam awareness poster.
Good morning.
My name is Joshima. It's nice to meet you.
RYOTARO SUGI
Joining Joshima is Ryotaro Sugi.
He is a famous actor known for
Toyama no Kin-san.
Thank you for coming today.
You're the best. Thank you.
One picture.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, Mr. Sugi.
Just one more picture.
-Aren't you hot in this?
-How is this?
Your outfit looks a lot hotter, Mr. Sugi.
On this day,
they had actually invited someone
who's a big fan of Mr. Sugi to the set.
Thank you so much. Excuse me.
Thank you.
We're done.
I got here early so I was waiting here.
-I didn't want to be in the picture.
-Come with me.
Joshima's mother.
You look so young.
Not at all.
-No, you do.
-You're too kind.
I'm 77 years old.
I know.
I watched you in Toyama no Kin-san,
among others.
That was a long time ago.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for your time.
Thank you again so much.
-I'm so happy.
-I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
I'll call you later.
I have no regrets now.
I can die anytime now.
Thank you. Good luck!
Thank you.
They're about to start recording.
KANJANI8 RECORDING FOR "KOKORO NI HANA"
Give it your best!
Huh?
Good to see you.
Good morning.
KANJANI8
YOU YOKOYAMA
You can do things at your own pace.
I'm always like this.
-Always?
-Yes.
-That's amazing.
-What is?
Energetic from the get-go?
It's not really that,
I think of this as a job to do.
-Well, thank you for coming.
-Thank you for having me.
-That's amazing.
-No, not really...
Joshima silently looks on.
Excuse me, can I hear
the first part one more time?
There, Joshima had his own thoughts
after being TOKIO's leader for many years.
Everyone has their own way
of singing, acting, and living.
Their habits show
in their personality too.
Even if something feels missing,
there are times
when that's completely okay.
And there are times
when something's missing a tiny piece
and if we had it,
we would complete the puzzle.
But it's just that
one piece that's missing.
Like if it were a building,
even without that piece,
it won't fall down when it shakes.
I don't like things to be too perfect.
And I don't think any of us
in TOKIO are perfect.
But because of
the imperfections, the gaps,
we've been able to do well
and succeed in our endeavors.
And this would make me question
if there is a right way to do things.
They don't try to fit
into a certain shape.
I think the Johnny's Shop
was established in 1988.
JOHNNY'S SHOP HARAJUKU
This is his first visit to Johnny's Shop
in 20 some years.
This brings back memories.
Ah...
There's TOKIO.
Wow.
Matsuoka was so cute.
When I think of Matsuoka,
this is the image I think of.
His cheeks were a little chubby.
We were all rascals back then.
Look at how unruly we were.
Here too.
And here too.
Johnny's groups usually wear
colorful clothing on stage.
People got mad and scolded us back then.
Yeah.
We relied on our seniors a lot too.
They paid for our meals
and doted on us as junior members.
The music that we played...
had a lot of that mixed into it.
It gave us the power to create something.
Only the three of us could do that...
It was our way of expression.
How should I put this?
It would be nice if we could find
a new way to express ourselves.
Sorry for making you stay so late.
Don't worry about it.
I'd like a Matsuoka set, please.
-Matsuoka's set?
-Yeah, the old one.
-Would you like just his picture?
-Yes, of course.
I'll hang it up somewhere in the company.
This is nice.
I'll be going now.
Thank you so much.
-See you later.
-Okay.
-See you next time.
-Okay, goodnight.
Half a year has passed
since the company's activies began.
They've been having many discussions
about the next project.
The first year of a company
is all about creating a foundation.
What can we challenge ourselves to?
All sorts of foundations.
Foundations as a company.
Foundations as an entertainer.
Foundations as an individual.
I'd love it if we could
expand each one of them.
The member have been clearing out
the different fields unique to them.
Mr. Kokubun, thank you for your time.
Thank you for your call. This is Kokubun.
Kokubun is joining in
a TV station's broadcast program council.
He has been asked his opinions
as an authority on creating TV programs.
The issue for discussion today
is about a certain variety program.
...I believe I was able to
see a lot of that.
If I'm to speak from
a presenter's point of view,
I wouldn't want to be given
a specific format.
I believe all the presenters
will want to create something on the spot.
So I really liked how it was edited
to emphasize that this was happening.
Here's the host, Mr. Shigeru Joshima.
Joshima will appear on a business program
as TOKIO Inc.'s president.
Even if that's the case,
will we be able to reach that point?
In addition...
"KOKORO NI HANA" MIXING
Yay!
Thank you.
Now you have to sing it in front of
the fans, share it, and then it's done.
Or maybe songs don't end just like that.
Maybe songs don't have an ending.
Since songs are passed down
to the people that listen to it.
Matsugoka goes onto
a new stage as an actor.
DRAMA PRESS RELEASE
It was an acting experience
that I have never had before.
I have acted
in all sorts of things before,
but I believe this one
has left an impression on my heart.
He talks to the director backstage.
He's getting used to using smartphones.
Toyama no Kin-san.
-I'll see you later.
-Thank you. See you later.
Okay.
-Thank you.
-Good work.
Launching TOKIO Inc.
was the first step in our journey.
And we're all middle aged men now.
The president will be 60 in nine years.
We don't want anyone
to be responsible for us
and we don't want to be a big burden.
How can I put this?
If Shigeru Joshima can wear a red vest
and we can all laugh, it'll be okay.
If we keep that atmosphere,
I think we'll be able to do
something interesting.
I faintly feel that way.
Our group has made it this far
after experiencing so many failures.
"This time wasn't perfect,
so let's make the next one a success."
TOKIO is just that kind of group
that repeats that cycle all the time.
Having the quality to see people
for who and what they are
is probably the biggest factor
to enjoy us as a group.
I just love TOKIO as a group.
It's difficult to continually
work hard on something...
but it's important.
No matter how much we change,
I don't want to lose my home,
the place I belong.
I love TOKIO.
I'm objectively a fan.
Here we go.
Masahiro Matsuoka, age 44.
Shigeru Joshima, age 51.
Taichi Kokubun, age 47.
No way, no thanks!
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to put our backs together.
We're too old to be
doing something like that.
Ninety-seven years old.
Their story has just gotten started.
Next time...
In 2021, there's a group of seven
that was able to debut.
Naniwa Danshi.
One month before their debut announcement...
BEFORE THEIR DEBUT
I don't know how we'll be,
but how do you want to be?
Naniwa Danshi in the future.
They talk about
what they should aim for as idols.
Like the pioneer of boy idols groups.
I want to be a hero to everyone.
To be acknowledged as an idol group.
I think everything ends
once we realize our possibilities.
We're here because of our fans.
I want to do things
nobody has done before.
Backstage of Naniwa Danshi's debut.
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin