To them, a New Year's holiday
that can never be forgotten had begun.
NANIWA DANSHI
Good morning!
Tokyo Dome!
Yeah!
DECEMBER 30, 2021
TOKYO DOME
November of last year,
Naniwa Danshi made their CD debut.
DECEMBER 30, 2021
TOKYO DOME
They matched up to their seniors
and stood on Tokyo Dome's stage.
After aiming to become an idol
for a decade,
Daigo Nishihata made it here at last.
DAIGO NISHIHATA (25)
I seriously didn't think
that my efforts would ever pay off.
Yeah.
But what I've been doing wasn't
a mistake all this time.
That's what I strongly think now.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
FORMED OCTOBER 2018
Naniwa Danshi was formed in 2018.
Good morning!
DECEMBER 25, 2021
The atmosphere surrounding them
had changed drastically.
-Oh, it's chicken!
-Wow, it's chicken!
How many Christmases
have you spent with us?
Three out of four years.
Nice job!
You really like us!
NANIFAM GATHER!
NANIWA LIVE XMAS 2021
On this day was their first
Christmas live stream.
The scale of the set on site
had been their largest ever.
Ever since Naniwa Danshi
was formed, it's been like this.
That's honestly scaring me.
You know...
If you go up,
there's gonna be a time you go down.
When we fall, we'll need to work together.
Right? And overcome it.
If we can get a nice wave going,
that'd be great.
The time to put their abilities
to the test was drawing near.
Last year, the Johnny's Festival was held
for the very first time.
DECEMBER 27, 2021
NANIWA DANSHI INTRODUCTION
"UBU LOVE"
So big!
Wow!
Oh, so that means there's three stages.
A band stage, dance stage, and main stage.
There's a moving stage too.
Jun Matsumoto of Arashi directed it,
and 13 debuting groups all attended.
Naniwa Danshi was scheduled
to perform their debut song
before the audience for their first time.
Wow, it's super pink.
The costumes were renewed
by Matsumoto's orders.
Wow, this will stand out.
Looks like we'll stand out, huh?
The costumes most of all.
RYUSEI ONISHI (20)
Matsumoto only notified the reason
behind the costume change
to Kento Nagao, the one in charge
of Naniwa Danshi's costumes.
Oh, thank you.
KENTO NAGAO (19)
You know how the current costumes
for "Ubu LOVE" are a little weak?
When we're on stage
and it doesn't stand out...
You know, since it's big...
I think our image gets thinned out.
That's why if we use bright pink,
people's eyes will focus on us.
There aren't many occasions
we can have Jun make our costumes.
So we're really thankful
and happy about it.
I told Jun we'll leave it to him.
The choreography was also rearranged
for the dome concert.
So, um...
I'm the choreographer, Take.
We're Naniwa Danshi! Nice to meet you!
Thank you. Nice meeting you.
The choreographer
who directs Arashi's dances.
You'll be memorizing
"Ubu LOVE" a bit today.
So, you boys don't know the moves
of "Maemuki Scream!"
For this Johnny's Festival,
Jun wants you to focus on the performance,
so he wants you to memorize
the numbers yourselves.
And in that case,
you'll have to decide yourselves.
It's a number hell,
but try hard to memorize them.
-Yes.
-Okay.
The formation changes according
to the stage.
And don't come forward too much
because they'll come in front of you.
The first one...
If I'm around one, is that okay?
I can't go in too much.
That's right, yeah.
Michieda, you aim for where Jo was at.
Okay.
I was in front quite a bit.
-Oh, everyone, there...
-Here, yes.
For the song's position, stay at the same
place from Ohashi's last chorus.
Did it change?
It changed a lot. The moves are
programmed into our bodies.
JOICHIRO FUJIWARA
So even if it's our usual dance,
we'll panic if we have
to shift our dance timings midway.
I see.
Yeah, so our brains are mixed up there.
Even the normally skillful
Kyohei Takahashi, seemed confused.
KYOHEI TAKAHASHI (21)
-And you walk.
-I walk.
Then go to the lower step.
Lower step?
The stairs here. This is the lower step.
Wait, next? What?
Um, that's gonna spread more?
That's right.
The directions were
the most detailed ever.
They learn the reason behind that
at theTokyo Dome rehearsal.
It hasn't felt this tight in a while.
Well, time. It's been a while
since we had no time like this.
And Michieda and Ohashi
had another big role waiting for them.
SHUNSUKE MICHIEDA
KAZUYA OHASHI
"AI NO KATAMARI"
They were assigned as backup dancers
for their seniors, KinKi Kids.
All right, looks good.
No, no, it's bad!
-It's bad? Really?
-A bit.
Should we recheck?
The music once more...
Let's do it again with sound.
Once more please.
With only a day of practice,
the Tokyo Dome rehearsal arrived.
DECEMBER 29, 2021
There were monitors
at every corner of the stage.
A performance mixed
with video was key to the concert.
MIC BASE
What are they gonna start with?
Scary.
Good morning, everyone. Let's do our best.
The rehearsal.
Everyone, good morning!
Good morning!
Let's do our best today!
Let's do our best!
Come down slowly there.
Um, when your body sways,
we can't capture you.
Yes, okay.
-Michieda.
-Yes.
This is what we're doing.
When you move sideways...
Oh, face forward. Forward.
Forward, B side.
Yes, okay.
This is what we're doing,
so you'll get cut off if you sway.
So try not to sway.
Okay.
Why their positions
were directed in detail
were due to these features.
Clean positions please.
Yes.
NANIWA DANSHI
Uh, two points.
Um, what Onishi said earlier
about passing in front...
Yes.
For that, the leader's better in front.
Is behind him okay?
I'll pass behind him.
-Okay.
-Yes.
And was it Takahashi
when Onishi was singing on top?
-Yes.
-In the lower front?
For there, can you slightly shift half
your body weight over to the left please?
Uh, okay.
Um, because when we're taking
Onishi's shot,
you overlap him slightly.
-Yes, okay.
-Yeah.
-Just those two points.
-Yes.
No matter how detailed the moves are,
they are never half-hearted.
We should at least
confirm the traffic line.
That's true, but even if you suggest
this and that, I'm on the very outside.
-Yeah.
-Right? The most.
I can't get in.
-Um, Kento...
-If I go in at 0,5, I won't reach in 0,5.
And I'll be shown.
For the oldest member, Fujiwara,
there was a phrase he cherished.
I saw Mr. Nakai on TV saying,
"The time to bloom depends
on that person," to Snow Man.
I thought, "That's amazing. Wow."
He said that the time to bloom
is different for each person,
so don't rush and keep working.
That really touched my heart.
I see.
And now, Ohashi and Michieda's turn came.
"Just like our seniors,
continuing to stand on this stage."
That is Michieda's dream.
I was tense the whole time.
I want to do my best at tomorrow's
concert, so that I have no regrets.
Meanwhile, Nishihata was
notified of some news.
I was just told earlier.
Yeah, just earlier, Matsumoto told me.
Really.
He's like, "I'm gonna
have you say it last."
What?!
So, I still have time to mentally prepare.
It's here.
He was assigned
the role to introduce the last song
of the concert, "smile."
No pressure. Though it's a vital part.
Hey, hey, what are you saying?
You trying to put pressure on me?
Dai, if you mess up, "smile" won't begin.
Gosh, this is a big responsibility.
Suddenly. It came suddenly.
It's a vital...
I'm super happy though.
I'm ultra happy though.
DECEMBER 30, 2021
And the day of the concert came.
An audience of 40,000 people.
The collaboration
with their seniors began.
"KOIFURU TSUKIYONI KIMIOMOU"
REN NAGASE
KANSAI JOHNNY'S JR. UNTIL 2015
SHO HIRANO
They're amazing.
They'll finally stand
on the same stage as their friends
who once worked together toward debuting.
It must be a view we've never seen.
Onishi was watching the seniors
who inspired him to become an idol.
"MUSEKININ HERO"
KANJANI8
Naniwa Danshi's turn was approaching.
Finally, it was Naniwa Danshi's turn.
Good, good...
Let's have fun!
Now, everyone, gather.
We're last, there's lots of our seniors,
but let's send
Naniwa Danshi's "Ubu LOVE" out.
-Yes!
-Here we go!
All right!
A special feature had been
prepared just for them.
Now, continuing on, I'd like to introduce
our juniors who've newly joined in 2021.
Please take a look.
Each of the seven members' names and faces
were unveiled at Tokyo Dome's grand stage.
NANIWA DANSHI
"UBU LOVE"
NANIWA DANSHI FORMED IN 2018
WHILE WORKING TOWARDS THEIR DEBUT,
THEY CLASHED AT TIMES
We're a group.
So I hope the message gets across.
2020, THE PANDEMIC
THE GROUP FACED DANGER...
I get frustrated
when I think it's the pandemic's fault.
THEY POLISH THEMSELVES,
BELIEVING THERE'S A PATH BEYOND IT
I'll always travel.
Ready, get set...
2021, THE DAY HAD FINALLY ARRIVED
JULY 28
"DIAMOND SMILE"
Now, this is the last song.
I pray that everyone's lives
will continue to be filled with smiles.
Five...
And the following day, New Year's Eve.
Two, one...
Happy New Year! 2022!
JANUARY 1, 2022
The year 2022,
as they head toward a future path
that no one has walked before,
the seven of them set out.
It was brilliant.
I was able to feel that we moved
onto the next stage.
Joichiro Fujiwara.
He aims to be both an idol and comedian.
The leader, Kazuya Ohashi.
He leads the group higher
with his singing and dancing.
Um, for our next goal
we probably want to do it here.
We want to do it at Kyocera too.
The Dome Tour...
Kento Nagao.
He'll absorb everything he can
to open up a new world.
Oh, they let us use half.
Possibilities?
Well, aren't they limitless?
I mean, you know...
People have the power to think.
I'd like us to create things
others haven't yet.
We were able to dance "Ubu LOVE"
in front of our fans for the first time,
so I was glad for that.
It was very fun, and it
became great experience too.
Kyohei Takahashi.
He wishes for their song
to reach everyone.
Ryusei Onishi.
He shifted from an admirer to the admired.
Having this excitement
of what we'll do next
as we work is a real joy.
I hope that this excitement
always continues,
imagining what kind of work we'll do.
Shunsuke Michieda.
An idol and actor,
he walks down both paths.
I was able to walk the ideal path
that I imagined.
So I'd like to continue that
without wavering.
Every person who is precious to me.
Like my friends and family.
People I'm indebted to.
They're all watching me.
So I can show them the good,
cool parts of me,
I would like to work hard.
Continuing on to an unseen world,
Daigo Nishihata.
Do you enjoy life?
I do enjoy my life.
Whatever people may say,
my life is my own life.
They say you only live once.
Tokyo Dome, good job!
Good job!
Good job, everyone!
Thank you very much!
See you again!
Excuse us!
Please excuse us!
And camera.
The next episode is on SixTONES.
Nearly two years since their debut,
the six of them each spill their thoughts.
After a year passes,
just spirit doesn't cut it.
Like, is there a need to lie to you guys?
Then why do you lie?
No, I'm not lying.
Baby! Baby!
We have to take good care of our fans.
We think it's just a bluff
that those people created.
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi