Kis-My-Ft2 is celebrating the
tenth anniversary of its CD debut.
Their first show in three years
with a crowd was approaching.
-Does it seem okay?
-Seems okay.
When they think we disappeared,
we just kind of slink in.
So once the video is off,
we shouldn't stand?
Small adjustments are made past midnight.
You should go home.
None of this is going to be interesting.
We raised the bottom by a meter.
I want to make it 800.
-A bit lower?
-Yeah.
Can you drop
the smaller chandelier by 200?
This is documentary series Ride on Time.
Ten days before the concert, the costumes
arrived at the rehearsal room.
Wow, this is super cool.
Really awesome.
This is exciting.
Stuff like this makes me happy.
Good morning.
Yuta Tamamori was in charge of costumes.
These look great!
However...
You know, I want more black.
-It's not finished, right?
-No.
I wonder if it will get darker.
It's a bit faded, don't you think?
Um, we just put the fringe in to test it.
We might not need it.
This one looks a bit white.
Maybe it depends on the person.
Without this, it'll end up too simple,
so I'm thinking of adding enough
to achieve about this sort of balance.
There was a certain message
instilled in these costumes.
It's an F.
Oh look at that. It's an F.
-Look.
-Wow.
Where's my Y?
It's here, right?
Amazing.
Each of their initials
were embroidered on.
And on their back was an X to commemorate
their tenth anniversary.
The next costume...
-I put one on?
-Yes.
-What should I do with this here?
-Isn't it cuter open?
Like this? Yeah, I think
I might like it open too.
Then we'll take this part in a bit more.
How many times now?
I think this is about my fifth
or sixth time doing costumes.
But I'm still making new discoveries
of what looks good on everyone.
I like clothes,
so I want everyone to wear
something cool that motivates them.
That's how I'm operating.
Please turn around.
Thank you.
Your jackets will also have
the little chandelier thing on Senga's.
What did the members think
of their three newly made costumes?
Up until now we were in track suits.
So I think the mood will change.
True.
You get that feeling of a live show.
We'll be doing a dress rehearsal later.
Do you find yourself trying not to dirty
the costume at rehearsal?
I totally get that.
If we get it dirty here,
it'll be dirty for our first show.
It's over if you trip.
The costume team will lose it.
"It's rehearsal so don't dance so much."
But if we don't, Nika will yell at us.
We're in a pickle.
That's where we always are.
Yeah.
Boom. You were slow.
No, it's this posture.
They were set to have
a dress rehearsal on this day.
But then...
Can I put my arm through?
Yeah, sure. It's up to you.
I'm the only one
like this during "A10TION."
I don't put my arms through...
Tamamori was also concerned about
this overcoat worn over the shoulders.
If I ever have to put it over my shoulders
or need to take it off...
What would be the best for you?
Having it on your shoulders
is going to be hard.
When I have to dance.
-It's hard to dance in, huh?
-Yeah.
Which means...
Do they prioritize the design
or the dancing?
Yeah, that's cool.
The seven of us are at our best
and our coolest when we're on stage.
It'd make me happy if people saw us
and thought we were cool.
It would really make my day
if people felt that way.
All decorations go up...
Taisuke Fujigaya posed a question
to himself ten years after their debut.
I don't even know myself.
I wondered what I'd think
after ten years had passed.
Like, I've learned how to do this or that.
But I haven't learned
to do anything at all.
What's going to happen?
There was someone Fujigaya
couldn't wait to see.
Third floor?
It's his kindergarten teacher,
who he loved as a child.
It was 30 years ago.
I wonder if she remembers me.
Excuse me.
They're dancing.
What?
Ms. Ishida?
-Oh, long time no see.
-Taichan?
What? Taichan?
It's Taisuke Fujigaya. Is that really you?
Yes.
It's been a long time.
Such a long time.
Hold on.
How are you?
I'm doing well.
Really? Thank you for meeting me.
Of course.
Ms. Ishida left kindergarten teaching
and now provides mobility assistance
to people with disabilities.
Oh, right, sorry.
-Here you go.
-It's me!
Yes.
Oh no.
My drawing ability
hasn't improved since then.
I haven't improved at all.
My drawings still look like this today.
Looking at this makes me feel
so many emotions.
It makes me laugh.
-A field trip?
-Digging up potatoes.
Stone-faced.
I haven't changed.
Everyone's smiling,
yet I'm standing there stone-faced.
You would do this with your hands.
I loved the hero shows.
So many hero poses of you.
Is that so?
I was looking forward to what I would
be thinking after ten years.
After ten years, like...
Would I think that I've learned
some skill, or I've gained confidence?
I was looking forward to that
going into the tenth year.
You never know.
-No?
-Not at all.
It goes for work, too.
The ten-year mark is just the beginning.
When I got to my tenth year,
I was just starting to enjoy it.
Things were just getting fun.
Is that so?
I mean, over the last ten years
you've been learning to sing and dance.
It was a long process, wasn't it?
So you've reached a certain level by now.
Now you just entered a different stage,
figuring out what to do next.
I see.
These last ten years
have been mainly input for me.
So from this point,
I'll be thinking and acting on my own.
If you earnestly live true to yourself,
it will all work out one day.
You need to believe in yourself.
Yes.
Even now, I often think of you.
-Really?
-Really.
Fujigaya had this to say
after meeting his teacher.
That takes me back.
It's not impatience,
but I figured I should be able
to do something after ten years.
I probably need to be proud of myself.
I asked myself what I've learned to do.
And I haven't learned
to do anything at all.
I'm just blessed with my fans
and the people around me.
And I have a means
to take on these challenges.
And I realized that
this is a new start for me.
I want to be something to someone.
Something like that.
Though it's conceited to say so.
If people can find a moment of happiness
after discovering Kisumai, then great.
I guess I want to focus on
the fans and staff
and make them feel glad
they supported Kisumai all this time.
The middle of January.
ECOPA ARENA
The seven members arrived in Shizuoka
for the first day of the arena tour.
Good morning.
It's the day before the arena tour.
On set,
there's a flower
that Yokoo has likened to Kisumai.
Called the dogtooth violet,
it takes six years to bloom.
Nikaido, in charge of direction, had this
to say after looking at the stage.
I mean, the set is...
TAKASHI NIKAIDO
...incredibly beautiful.
It's been three years since we were
in front of an audience.
I'm uh...
I'm excited.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Let's smash this Shizuoka rehearsal.
We'll do our best!
The rehearsal began.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
That's going back, right?
No, somewhere the camera can get it.
Maybe further back.
Please give it a check.
It's okay.
Please raise the A-dash click a bit more.
The final full rehearsal.
Nikaido separated from the group
and headed into the audience seats.
-It's hard to see over there.
-Okay.
You can hear Nika's voice.
He checks the show
from the fan's perspective.
Key is the fifth step.
So it's five, six, seven.
At the point they'll think we disappeared,
we just kind of glided in.
If we crouch down too much,
it seemed as though
they'd just be able to see us.
So when the video turns off,
we shouldn't stand yet?
Does "One Kiss" need to be that early?
Not a lot goes on in the middle.
I guess that's for the best.
Nikaido has his final meeting
with the staff.
The square light up above.
The white one?
Sync that up with the clapping.
I want the lighting timed to the clapping
instead of keeping that tempo.
We have it set to red at the end of
"NAKED", and there's something after.
-You want it to end on red.
-Yes, on just red.
Okay.
You should go home.
None of this is going to be interesting.
-That's its original position?
-Yes.
So...
Either way, you want to raise
the lowest one a bit?
He wasn't happy with
the chandelier on the main stage.
Okay.
We raised the bottom by a meter.
I want to make it 800.
-A bit lower?
-Yeah.
Can you drop
the smaller chandelier by 200?
Twenty centimeters. They continue
making small adjustments.
I like this.
The light hits the truss, too.
Yeah.
Like this?
It's beautiful.
How's the V motion?
It's lowered at that slow speed.
Spot checks continued past midnight.
JANUARY 15, 2022
It's the first day of the arena tour.
Good morning.
The seven members get ready
for the concert upon arrival at the venue.
Good morning.
Attention to all those whose
venue entry time has arrived.
Their last show with a crowd
was three years ago.
...please notify the nearest staff member.
Off we go!
It's been three years
since our last show with fans.
Let's make it a good one.
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
Let's do it.
OPENING VIDEO
THE SHAPE OF LOVE
THAT CANNOT BE EXPRESSED IN WORDS
It's been ten years since Kis-My-Ft2,
with its seven distinct members, debuted.
A new journey begins.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto