On this day,
they witnessed the love
of an audience who had to remain silent.
Their name is SixTONES.
It used to be a given.
Hearing the cheers from an audience.
I guess it was trying to get
as many people to think it was cool.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Music was at the center of their career.
They were busy creating
a new album for a concert tour.
There are a total of
19 tracks we need to record.
I might die.
They broke the typical idol mold
to search for a way to express themselves.
This is really hard.
I hate my voice.
I love my voice.
I can't change my voice.
Maybe I've embraced it.
There are idols who love music
and want to express that
from the bottom of their hearts.
When the six of us sing,
I'd feel lucky if we have an audience.
There are nine months before the concert.
I want to be acknowledged even more.
We followed them
as they threw themselves into the music.
This is documentary series Ride on Time.
-Where should I be?
-You're over there.
-And me?
-Here.
-Then I'm center.
-Yeah.
Is here okay?
Which way? Here? Here?
The six members get along so well
they give the staff a hard time.
This is the reason you're pushing.
I'm like your kid brother.
The humorous Jesse,
and the beloved oldest member Yugo Kochi.
And the laidback Taiga Kyomoto
as well as Hokuto Matsumura,
the brainy one in the group.
The youngest, Shintaro Morimoto,
is the life of the party.
and Juri Tanaka's role is
to bring the group together.
SHINTARO MORIMOTO (24)
JURI TANAKA (26)
JANUARY 2020 DEBUT
The thing they have put
the most work into is their music.
In just two years since their debut,
they've released 50 songs.
It's like a dream.
Being able to do so much music
in this environment
is an ideal situation.
And it's exceeded it.
Their strength is singing.
This January, they received
a lot of attention for their performance
on the one shot recording series,
THE FIRST TAKE.
"IMITATION RAIN" FROM "THE FIRST TAKE"
Meetings for production of
the second album have begun.
They ask the members
what they want from the tracks.
I liked this song, so I want to do it.
It might go faster if we fit them into
morning, noon, or night first.
They repeatedly listen to the songs
to pick each one carefully.
On this day, they were
discussing a particular song.
If we choose a song like "RAM-PAM-PAM"
people might find it lame.
So we need to break away from
something like "RAM-PAM-PAM",
and hook them with a melody or chorus.
Yeah, something more like a song.
And one more...
If we're factoring a concert,
rather than relying on dance for intensity
the intensity is individual so
having a more aggressive song is better.
I agree with Hokuto, in terms of approach.
A sense of unity?
There wasn't anything better than
"RAM-PAM-PAM" or "Special Order" for me.
Yeah.
"RAM-PAM-PAM" is a killer track that
never fails to pump up the crowd.
The song symbolizes SixTONES' brand,
which is not your typical idol fare.
How will they evolve
from their existing discography?
It's something they are
always thinking about.
What's a deciding factor?
If it's a song I want to do or not.
Since we want to do music properly,
we do the songs we want.
Cool songs.
That's the best.
Or else it's not fun.
I want to enjoy my work
such that it doesn't feel like work.
HOKUTO MATSUMURA (26)
Their solo careers have also
taken off since their debut.
Hokuto Matsumura has
a regular spot on an art magazine.
Recently, he's known
for his excellent acting career.
Not that direction.
TV DRAMA COME, COME, EVERYBODY
In 2021, he gained attention
for his role in an NHK morning drama,
as Minoru Kijima, a character who had
a big impact on the protagonist's life.
DRAMA WHO NEEDS TRUE LOVE?
And from April, he had
a new TV drama in the works.
He played a chef-in-training who
captured the hearts of the female patrons.
He had many names of dishes
to remember for his lines.
Copy that.
-Rolling.
-We're rolling.
Ready! Action!
Excuse me.
Every lunch comes with
salad, bread, and coffee.
Today's fish is flounder from Miyagi.
The meat is... a pork roast.
I'll come back for your order.
Cut! Let's try that again.
So close.
You tried.
That's rare.
It happens all the time.
I drew a blank.
I stumbled on the flounder
from Miyagi for a split second.
And as I was thinking,
the meat didn't come to me.
I only had the flounder.
Here's what I want.
Lightly graze her body,
so you're pretty close to her.
How will he manifest
the director's orders?
I'll be touching you a little bit.
Okay.
Roll rehearsal. Action!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Here's your salad.
-Thank you.
Can I take a picture?
-No problem, just one moment.
-Okay.
Here is your chicken ratatouille.
Are eggplants okay?
-Yes.
-Good.
-Sorry for the wait.
-Can I?
I'm sorry, we're cooking the meat now.
Could you wait a little longer? I'm sorry.
We'll make it extra good.
Thank you very much.
You touched them a lot.
You went like this then this.
I did touch them a lot.
That was funny.
You were really handsy.
We'll use it.
Thank you.
I think it was great.
Do you have a vision for yourself?
A vision?
If I had to choose,
I want to be...
someone who is like a threat.
There are a lot of our seniors like that.
Ninomiya is definitely
a clear example of this.
People his age who play similar roles,
they must see him as a threat.
Ninomiya has something
that nobody else does.
He has this presence in his roles
that is really enchanting.
Hectic days acting and singing.
However, it's something he's wished for.
Production for SixTONES'
second album began.
Was it over there?
You're pretty busy all day, right?
-Yeah, with this and that.
-This and that.
Good luck.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
"With the Flow" is a duo track for
Taiga Kyomoto and Juri Tanaka.
A special song
Tanaka wrote the rap lyrics for.
Kyomoto is also a star in musicals.
In the top Japanese musical Elisabeth,
he worked with iconic stars
and worked on his expressiveness.
And in 2021, Shuichiro Koike,
the master behind Elisabeth
cast Kyomoto as the main role
in his next production.
Okay, got it.
He has strong feelings
when it comes to music.
I think I messed up the second one.
I think I goofed it up.
Sorry.
For the line that goes "trivial worries,"
I think at the end I'll...
bring my voice down to a natural tone.
Like that.
Can we record a take like that?
Mixing it my natural voice
might make it easier to follow the rhythm.
Thank you.
Here we go.
-Good work today.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Can you give us a sec?
No problem.
The chorus is coming along.
-Yeah?
-It sounded nice.
I'm getting the hang of it.
I Might be able to
figure out the right melody.
I'm still working on it.
It feels like...
You're firing us up too.
That's really helpful.
It's nice to hear.
For this track,
he will be recording
his guitar playing for the first time.
This being our second album,
I want to up my game to the next level.
We all do.
Like how Juri wrote
some of the rap lyrics himself this time.
A lot of us are trying things
for the first time for this.
I'm sure the other four are
taking up their own challenges too.
Okay.
Sounds good. Just one thing.
When you're strumming up.
Yeah, put an accent there.
Got it.
Let's give it a listen.
Wow.
Sounds good!
Was that me playing?
It was.
-That was me, right?
-Yeah.
-What?
-Nice job.
I've debuted. Man.
I guess you can debut multiple times.
That's amazing.
Honestly, I thought I was done for
when I got the sheet music.
It looked so hard.
But you said you wanted to play it.
-Yeah.
-That's what I heard.
You know.
I was in performance mode.
Like right before a show.
-You know.
-So honest.
Like, "Are you ready for my guitar?!"
I was overconfident enough
to say that without thinking.
-When the sheet music came...
-Yeah.
Okay, let's do it.
-Let's do it.
-Yeah.
Juri Tanaka is the group's rapper.
He's performed his own lyrics before.
I woke up 40 minutes ago.
Really?
Yeah.
Ready for your verse?
So right now, it ends with
T-shirts and jeans, in our style
That's the flow right now.
-Yeah.
-According to the guide.
The one I first came up with was
T-shirts and jeans, in our style
Which feels better?
I mean...
You're fine either way?
I'll give it a few tries.
That's one version.
Well, with that version you went
T-shirts and jeans, in our style
Oh, "T-shirts and jeans, in our..."
-We'll do a few.
-Okay.
I'll go with this.
-Thank you.
-Yeah!
Okay, I'm ready.
Can I go?
Nobody's stopping you.
People seem hesitant.
Oh, yeah?
July.
Tanaka received an exciting job.
JULY 2021
FNS SUMMER SONG FESTIVAL
I don't have time to talk today.
No free time?
I've got better things to do.
Look at this set.
Look at this wonderful set.
This isn't the time to be filming.
Do you admire them?
Yeah.
You must be happy.
I am, but I'm more nervous.
I'm nervous.
A collaboration he dreamed about.
He's working with one of
Japan's greatest rappers,
and a world champion DJ.
R-SHITEI, DJ MATSUNAGA
What you have for the chorus works fine.
Even just hitting certain words is fine.
You can sing up until then.
Okay.
-Okay, got it.
-Something like that.
Checking in with everyone!
REHEARSAL
"KATSUTE TENSAI DATTA ORETACHI E"
Things they never dreamed of
before their debut
are happening one by one.
They are only beginning to grow.
Could we swap numbers?
Sure.
I was wondering when you'd ask.
That was nerve-racking.
Next time, they start work
on the concert tour.
We want people to come.
That's our real job.
Something cool.
Something flashy.
Let me do that again.
We get worked.
My body feels worked.
It'd be better if Juri did this himself.
A duet didn't make sense to me.
Better to do the better one.
What kind of concert are they envisioning?
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto