August 10th, 2021.
Tokyo Sky Tree.
Say cheese.
Kis-My-Ft2 was there.
Kis-My for short.
Ten years ago this day,
they made their CD debut.
I'll take a pic of the Earth.
Ever since, the seven members
have continued running.
You can't dance here.
I tried to be the most excited person
in Japan at 9 a.m.
Look, you're a little funny.
Ready?
How do they feel about
these last ten years?
It's a miracle we've been together
these last ten years.
There was a chance that
the seven of us wouldn't have made it.
There were highs and lows.
One day we think we could see the light,
and the next day it would be pitch black.
With everything happening
with the anniversary,
it makes me wonder what being and idol is.
These 10 years didn't go as planned.
That's why...
things won't go as planned
in the future either.
Ten years of struggling
and miraculous dreams.
"As long as evil exists in this world,
so shall the flame of justice."
And they will have their first
concert with an audience in three years.
Let's do it.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Kis-My debuted in 2011
using roller skates as their weapons.
They conducted a tour
of the five big domes in 2019
attracting nearly 600,000 people.
Additionally that year, they performed
their first overseas show in Taiwan.
TAIPEI
ARENA
Let's all get fired up!
Summer of 2021,
they began doing press for
their 10th anniversary of their debut.
"KIS-MY-FT2 KIS-MY RADIO"
They all appeared on radio.
It's true.
Did you know that Miyata
loves cucumbers an abnormal amount?
I didn't know that.
They also filmed videos for fans
they weren't able to meet.
Wow!
As this was happening,
the youngest member of the group
Kento Senga expressed his frustrations.
KENTO SENGA
We don't know when Covid is going to end.
It takes a lot of stamina and
it's hard to care about someone for years.
Yeah.
So having lost concerts...
It was one of the types of entertainments
that could move you emotionally.
Losing something like that worries me.
Will things be okay?
-Good morning.
They started putting together
an arena tour,
their first concert in three years
with an audience.
Good morning.
'Morning.
It's RIDE ON TIME.
Don't mind me.
I know it's early, but let's get started.
Great.
The arena tour will start
January 15th of next year.
As of now, November is...
Takashi Nikaido is in charge
of the concert's production.
TAKASHI NIKAIDO
APRIL 2021 METLIFE DOME
The fountain piece featured
during their 2021 livestream concert
was a big hit with fans.
I never imagined a situation
where we couldn't do a concert
in front of an audience.
Even if we let in an audience now,
fans aren't able make any noise.
Cheers are part of the show.
And that's one thing gone.
Which is why our level of
enthusiasm and performance
including our songs
need to be enough
to entertain our audience.
The show's theme
is ten years of gratitude
expressed by decorating the stage
with various flowers.
Yokoo makes a suggestion.
Can you add another flower?
There's a flower called
the dogtooth violet
that takes six or seven years to bloom.
That seemed just like Kis-My-Ft2.
DOGTOOTH VIOLET
The dogtooth violet takes
six or seven years to bloom.
He explains that they're similar
as they took six years
from their formation to debut.
I think that's really nice.
That's really nice.
-That's really nice.
You know how gratitude is our theme?
I thought singing "Re:"
as our first song could be touching.
-I see.
-Just an idea.
Their song "Re:"
is a song whose lyrics reflect
their feelings for their fans.
WHEN WE GOT LOST
YOU KEPT ON LOVING US
THANK YOU
I WANT TO SEND TO YOU
A LOVE THAT CANNOT BE EXPRESSED IN WORDS
I know it's not the kind of song
we start with usually,
but that could make it perfect.
Like the face will pop up
with a super close-up.
Maybe the eyes would be different.
There won't be a big dance number
around the medium block.
First day of rehearsals,
Nikaido who is in charge of production
arrives earlier than anyone.
-You more excited?
-I'm more excited.
Before the members gather,
he checks the things that worry him.
Just count at the start.
One, two, three, four.
Not there, the top of the song.
Right, right, there.
The set list is written
on the white board.
"Re:" is set to be the opening number
as Tamamori suggested.
Since the seven of us are building this,
I wouldn't have imagined
starting the show off with "Re:."
It's a song with a lot
of emotion behind it,
so I think it's perfect
in regards to gratitude.
Rehearsals began.
They start with a song
with newly changed choreography.
On the first day of rehearsals,
their dancing was rusty.
My body feels so heavy.
Over here too.
They danced for nearly three hours.
On this day, they were filming
the music video for a new song.
From the top.
The first on set
is the oldest, Hiromitsu Kitayama.
Let's do good work.
Seems like the sound will work.
Their new song "Fear" was the theme song
for a TV drama starring Kitayama.
He proposes ideas for
the music video as well.
Thank you.
They film each member one by one
and composite the footage.
Slowly turn this way.
There is no dancing or big movements.
They only use facial expressions
to depict the song's world.
A performance they've never done before.
Just at the threshold
before it gets uncool.
That's true.
You could look a bit higher.
Right, a bit.
If you looked further back.
Wasn't something supposed to come out
at that last part?
Kitayama had a strong conviction.
It gets interesting
when you've never done it before.
Whatever we can imagine
doesn't surpass the limits
of our imaginations,
which is why we want to try things.
That's just more interesting.
I mean, doing interesting stuff,
we need to betray expectations
in a good way.
You know?
It requires courage though.
We don't want the people watching
to get bored.
That's always on our mind.
Since their debut,
Kis-My has released
around 300 songs in ten years.
What they've strived for
was a new form of idol.
When you think of Kis-My-Ft2...
...you think of the roller skates
they've worn since their debut.
Even their first concert
in three years with an audience
cannot do without
a roller-skate performance.
It's a weapon I really cherish.
It all began when Mr. Johnny asked us
if we could wear roller skates.
Just a different way to present
ourselves or something.
It's like the type of excitement
when the theme park mascot comes out.
Personally, I want to wear them.
Even when I'm an old man.
Good work.
9 p.m.
One member stayed late after rehearsals.
That's a good transition.
It's Nikaido.
-Like Chrome Hearts.
-Yes!
The meeting for the concert video began.
You know...
Actually,
what if the choreography
and video were connected?
-You know how the song goes like...
-Right.
And then a video that relates to
"SHE! HER! HER!" pops up.
If the sound can...
He had a commitment to the production.
I feel that there's nothing better for
an audience than to see us live.
So we should never make a video
that draws the attention away from us.
If the video distracts from the group,
then I would question
what we are trying to show.
Whatever way we can showcase the group
the most is the best in my opinion.
This is a radio program
Nikaido is a part of.
This is RIDE ON TIME.
I'm so nervous having a camera here!
-They won't use this.
-Why not?
-It's not that type of show.
-It's not?
-That was a nice one.
-Sorry.
That one had some snap.
RADIO RECORDING
Nikaido calls himself Kis-My's
variety specialist.
He polishes his talking and
comedy skills with jobs such as these.
I love Atsuko Maeda,
so I put a neck pillow she used
in a Ziplock bag.
That makes you a pervert.
I'm not a pervert. This was 15 years ago.
It's not that old.
What the heck?
We don't need a boy scout, Takashi.
You seem off your game today.
I'm not.
So they let me have fun like this.
Having Mr. Kuro-chan...
Don't say it like Ms. Agnes Chan.
It's like he has disease that makes you
constantly interrupt people with a joke.
The leader will get mad.
Enough, Shiro-chan.
That's the wrong color!
Good grief.
There was a shoot going on this day.
So the Tokyo version...
It was the opening video
they would use for the arena tour.
Ready, action.
The theme this time
would be to thank their fans
for all their support
these past ten years since their debut.
Each member would compose
a letter to the fans.
That's nice.
There was a special sentiment behind it.
Looking good.
The concerts we're privileged enough
to do every year
are our way to show
our appreciation to the fans.
We each do it in our own style,
but that sentiment
is even bigger this year
from not being able to see them.
We're celebrating
our ten year anniversary,
because of our fans and their support.
They give us energy.
Often fans would tell us,
"Your concerts lifted our spirits."
And other comments,
but I feel like we're given even more.
We get a burst of adrenaline, too.
I feel like we're the ones
getting saved a lot instead.
So this tour really is...
something that will become very special.
Ready, go.
Kis-My's center, Yuta Tamamori.
YUTA TAMAMORI
He was undertaking a certain challenge.
He's been learning Chinese
the last three years.
Ready?
I'm really happy.
Yes, there was another grammar point here.
It all started in 2019.
Their first overseas performance
they did in Taiwan.
TAIPEI
ARENA
Please introduce yourselves.
We are Kis-My-Ft2.
Ever since, he's been continuing
Chinese lessons with Miyata.
TOSHIYA MIYATA
I'm really happy.
Well done.
Have you been busy?
A bit busy lately.
What are you doing?
I play games all day.
That's good.
He also began a YouTube channel
in December of 2021.
He plays games with friends like
Daiki Arioka from Hey! Say! JUMP
and Miyata who also like games.
Okay, let's go.
That's fast.
-Whoops.
-Hey!
-Sorry.
-Tamamori?
Yes!
It's a new challenge for Tamamori.
Being Kis-My's center,
I've always been the one to
do something new.
A lot of things I've never done before.
I was told to just challenge myself.
You know...
that's something I want to continue doing.
There's a feeling that pushes me through,
but I'm not the type to say it out loud.
He pushes himself his own way.
Next time, Kitayama takes up
a new challenge as well.
We're always evolving.
When that stops, we stop.
Th ever-evolving Kis-My-Ft2.
A world we've never build before.
A view we've never seen.
I'd love to be able to grow
by focusing on things like that.
But Taisuke Fujigaya had certain
apprehensions as he grew as a performer.
It makes me wonder what being and idol is.
I wonder what it is.
Subtitle translation by:
Zensho Yamamoto