Shintaro Morimoto, age 24.
He's one of the six members
of Johnny's SixTONES.
Music was at the center of their career.
Each musically talented member
pumps up the crowd with their free spirit.
It's one of their charms.
And even amongst the members,
the youngest member, Shintaro Morimoto,
is the most free-spirited.
Ouch! You hit me!
I'm singing!
Yeah!
Okay, we're rolling.
Even during a TV drama shoot,
he doesn't forget to have fun.
Action!
I'm great at putting the chair in.
Do it.
-Who?
-Me.
-Do it.
-Okay.
-Without looking.
-You're good.
-See?
-Wow!
Impressive, yeah?
Ready, action!
Aisaka's shunga still exists
in the present day.
But the museum said...
Yeah.
He's doing some dubbing
for scenes that were already shot.
Ready, action!
So heavy.
I live my life trying to be
the happiest I can be.
So...
I don't want to hide.
I mean, usually when you do interviews,
you don't sit like this on a chair.
I know it's wrong.
You do?
Of course, I know I shouldn't.
But I do it because I want to.
It's huge.
This is Toriike!
-Yay!
-We're here!
He doesn't lie to himself.
His straightforward personality
draws in like-minded friends.
Wow.
This is probably another world.
Somewhere I've never been before.
Let's take a look.
He's taken to an underwater cave.
His natural self
was hungry for a moment of excitement
from the bottom of his heart.
Wow.
Amazing.
So amazing!
This is documentary series Ride on Time.
Preparation began for their
New Year's concert tour.
Let's start.
Okay, let's start our first meeting.
Let's do it.
You have some ideas?
Something cool.
Something flashy.
We used lots of lights for our last one.
So let's do something else.
All of their concerts
began with their idea proposals.
What they seek is unpredictability,
to surprise the audience.
2021 COUNTRYWIDE ARENA TOUR
You know like how
we had the slide for on eST.
Something to put
the center stage in new light.
Could we get cars to
transport us from each stage?
Something surprising.
Like the monitor becoming a stage.
And then it moves.
The main stage splits in two.
Wouldn't they see backstage?
They'd see backstage.
What will our crew do?
What if it splits
and another stage appears?
We'll make it a medium-sized
main stage to start,
then it splits, and another appears.
-Making it big.
-A big main stage!
They might question the main stage.
Until the main stage.
I haven't written any of this down.
I thought about it, but haven't.
Jesse, age 25.
This is cool too.
Beautiful.
Fans would send us letters every month.
Mentioning which pictures they liked.
That was me.
He has a unique presence,
even amongst the other Johnny's members.
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2021 TO 2022
The countdown concert where
Johnny's idols all perform at once.
SixTONES!
We're going to give this year our all.
Cross, cross, circle, circle.
Maru, Maru, Maru.
-Jesse!
-Maru!
That's enough.
Okay, cut it out.
He's not timid around his seniors.
However, he is particular
about the way he presents himself.
I like that Safari doesn't
list who they feature on the cover,
unlike the other magazines.
They're not promoting the models.
Like so and so.
When readers thumb through it,
they realize that I'm in it.
That's what I like.
I'm doing this in secret.
This is like my secret spot
nobody knows about.
What about secretly doing radio?
Yeah, without using my name.
"Welcome to another Friday."
"Another day of fun radio."
"That sounds like Jesse."
But I never say my name.
I want to do that.
Without being found out.
What's important is that
they see him for who he is.
The most important thing
is to have as many people
think that I'm cool.
People I know
always tell me how cool I am,
and that makes me happy.
It makes me want to show more of myself.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We want people to come.
That's our real job.
I need people to know that
that's the real me.
Make them realize what I do.
Yeah.
Passion for concert shows.
And another new song has been completed.
Choreography for Jesse
and Shintaro Morimoto's song
is being handled
by world champion dancers.
So the steps for the chorus...
They must have the steps
perfectly memorized
for the music video shoot in a week.
Then.
It's a bit fast.
-And this...
-Wow, Jesse.
Don't put pressure on me.
I'm just doing it now.
I forget as fast as I learn.
They cherish their unity
with the crowd above all else.
More than precise choreography,
they each push
to showcase their individualism.
The dance that incorporates
the new jack swing from the '80s
is intense and also has a rhythm
that is difficult to grasp.
Let's go from the top.
I haven't moved this much in a while.
It's intense.
Then up we go.
Switch!
Then to the back.
I can't do that.
My body can't keep up.
Put the music on.
Yeah.
This is so hard.
I'm impressed by how they
learn the steps and express themselves.
They're really professional
when it comes to looking cool.
They've got the feel.
It's not just their movements.
I feel that from SixTONES as a group.
If they're able to
turn it into entertainment,
things will become very interesting.
Roll sound!
"LOUDER" MUSIC VIDEO FILMING
SixTONES' All Night Nippon
Saturday Special!
We have a message from Mr. Dine.
-Mr. Kochi.
-Yes.
"Where did you get the picture
of a hairdresser wearing a gang jacket?"
That's a good one.
They cosplay at work.
The lovable one that gets
messed with by listeners
is the group's oldest member
Yugo Kochi, age 27.
Okay, let's put on a song here.
Our seniors V6 will close
the curtain after 26 years
and disband in two days, on November 1st.
So we'd like to give them
a nice send-off with this big hit.
V6's "Take me Higher."
They played a popular hit by their seniors
who finished their final show.
V6 LAST CONCERT 2021
Did you go to their show?
What? V? Yeah.
Want to talk about it?
Honestly, I cried looking at the stage.
You just figure they'd be around forever.
I get it.
You know...
you can't imagine this group being gone.
I totally get it.
The people above are disappearing.
There were tons of people
who admired them.
How long will SixTONES be around?
Hm... Maybe until we reach the age
that government workers retire.
That's hilarious.
Until retirement.
I'll probably retire first.
-Since I'm the oldest.
-I see.
As time passes, what view awaits them
in the future they arrive at?
Man.
It feels good.
He spends his days off away from
the competitive entertainment business.
Thanks so much.
Oof.
YUGO KOCHI
Looking good.
Before SixTONES was formed,
Kochi was planning
to leave the idol world.
So hot.
How should I put this?
As I've said before,
I wasn't a someone who was
aggressive about being in entertainment.
I just had seniors doing it.
People like V6.
People who I thought
would always be there.
Then they suddenly left.
It makes me sad,
but when I saw their last show,
I thought it was
a really cool way to disband.
How much they cared about the fans.
They took a stand and made it through.
I understood that
they lived their idol life to the end.
They're great role-models
on how I want to be.
So,
I'm sure that there's still room
to grow at that age,
so I felt that I have to work harder.
-You're reading off that?
-Yeah.
He chose to go on with SixTONES.
He's working hard
to polish his skills for the group.
That's so hi-tech.
Really? You can't delete
what you've written?
-No, you can.
-Really?
"MAKKA NA USO"
Yeah, that's much better.
-So...
-Too much emphasis?
So, it sounds like you're going lower.
Oh.
"Why" should be... How do I put this?
Try not to throw too hard.
Yeah, don't do that.
Try that melody.
Like this.
That's low.
-Something like that.
-That's low.
Yeah.
Yeah, good.
Let me do that again.
-You did it.
-Good, good.
Let's hear it.
Do you go for lessons?
Yeah, although I'm not sure
I'd call it lessons.
We get worked.
My body feels worked.
-With a whip?
-Yeah.
I see.
I have to do it.
They follow me around.
But it really helps me.
It's fine.
The six members
live and think differently.
They've pit their individuality
against one another,
to create their own style.
-I'll do the neck.
-That'd hurt.
That's a compromise they're
not willing to make creatively.
Let's go again.
He had an issue with
a part the staff gave him.
Shouldn't you give this all
to Juri instead?
-It'd be better if Juri did this himself.
-I see.
That will really cut your part down.
That's fine with me.
It's not about who gets more.
It's better to do what's better.
Juri is the better rapper.
You think?
What about going back and forth?
Like having two MCs to hype each other.
It's exciting to hear as a listener.
So it could be really effective.
Let's record it for now.
-We'll do some combinations.
-Yeah, that works.
-That's the gist.
-Got it.
-Bye.
-Thanks.
Good work, everyone. Thanks.
Good work.
I can't hide my emotions.
If I don't think it's fun,
it shows on my face.
If I don't like it,
I'm really bad when that happens.
I don't care as long as I'm having fun.
What I tend to think is fun...
the other five are good at utilizing.
That's why I think
I have so much fun being
a member of SixTONES.
Because I have a place to return to,
I'm able to live so freely.
That's why I can do so much.
That's something I don't want to forget.
I think that's why it's fun,
and why we really trust each other.
Next time, recording
for the album ramps up.
I'm envious of Taiga.
I can't hit high notes.
But from my perspective,
Jesse can do things I can't
like sing in English and hit low notes.
What are the emotions
behind their singing?
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto