JULY 28, 2021
DEBUT CD SET FOR RELEASE!
Last summer, it was decided that
Naniwa Danshi would release a debut CD.
A new chapter of their journey just began.
Yes!
Hooray!
The next day.
106 DAYS UNTIL DEBUT
The excitement lingers
in the seven members.
We just worked all day!
We took a bath.
We had nothing until 11 p.m.
Isn't it busier after announcing a debut?
I don't know.
But we've got this here.
-But...
-Good morning!
-Morning.
-I took a bath.
Same here.
Whoa, cool! Awesome!
-There's flowers.
-And plushies.
Wow!
How are they?
-Awesome.
-Thank you.
Each one of them received
flowers matching his member's color.
When I see these kind of things,
the reality sets in.
-That you're debuting.
-Yeah!
When I see these things, it does set in.
However, a different feeling
was setting in at the same time.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
OCTOBER 2018
Seven young boys from Kansai
formed Naniwa Danshi in the year 2018.
-Let's liven this up!
-Okay.
Long before this group was even formed,
these boys were chasing
their dreams of debuting as idols.
Being on this radio show
was another dream.
You're on.
Naniwa Danshi's All Night Nippon!
The day after we announce our debut,
we get to host this special show called
Naniwa Danshi's All Night Nippon
as radio personalities...
The group's organizer, Daigo Nishihata,
worked 10 years to make his debut.
JOINED 2011
You know how they ask
for your favorite foods?
I've said motsunabe and gizzard up to now
and edamame recently, but...
Those are all old men's favorites!
Ryusei Onishi took 9 years, working
diligently from a young age to be an idol.
JOINED JULY 2012
But a walking human alarm? I like that.
The innocent Kento Nagao.
JOINED NOVEMBER 2014
I can tell jokes, like comedy.
The scatterbrained Kyohei Takahashi.
JOINED 2014
Well, being 19, you know...
The ever-earnest Shunsuke Michieda.
The 3 of them took 7 years
to make their debuts.
JOINED 2014
We're looking forward to
lots of m-messages.
The laid-back leader,
Kazuya Ohashi, waited 12 years.
JOINED APRIL 2009
Having joined the agency at age 8
and waited 17 years to debut,
Joichiro Fujiwara is the oldest.
This week's All Night Nippon's
host for Thursday
was Naniwa Danshi!
Bye-bye!
Isn't this crazy? We're working at 3 a.m.
-Crazy!
-We're popular idols!
That's crazy. It's after 12 a.m.
But I'm not sleepy at all.
-Right?
-What?
Today, everything looked different
than yesterday.
Everyone was indulging themselves
in happiness.
Meanwhile, along with happiness,
another feeling had surfaced in Nishihata.
I've seen everybody go through
their debuts all this time,
so I understand that feeling too.
That's why,
I can't exactly say this aloud.
About this.
What was on Nishihata's mind
at this moment
was his friends from Kansai Johnny's Jr.
that worked together toward debuting.
Because they were friends who supported
one another when times were tough,
he was hesitant to indulge
in happiness by himself.
We won't be returning
as a Johnny's Jr. group.
That's why in these
three and a half months
I'd like to do whatever we can
to repay Kansai Johnny's Jr.
I personally wish to do one more concert...
as a Kansai Johnny's Jr. group.
Yeah...
Yeah.
And we talked about
how we'll concentrate on future work.
Thank you very much.
I hope we work together again.
As the arena tour
and debut preparations continued...
We'll practice it.
That desire never came true.
Alright, see you.
And this day too,
there was a member who spoke of
a surprising thought before his debut.
AUGUST 21, 2021
83 DAYS UNTIL DEBUT
AICHI PERFORMANCE
These are the lyrics.
Oh. Are the parts...
No. There's two songs.
The moment arrived to listen
to their long-awaited debut song's demo.
It's called "Ubu LOVE."
"Ubu LOVE"? Nice!
Oh, I'm super nervous!
I see.
Oh my god, oh my god
OMG, OMG
"OMG, OMG" means "oh my god, oh my god."
Oh, awesome!
Thank you.
We can't wait.
The one who gave a surprising comment
was Fujiwara.
Umm, I'm more worried now.
Like cloudy.
Hmm.
Of course it's important to move on
to the next step, but...
Hmm. Right? It's contradictory.
I wanted to debut, so I worked for it,
but I get scared once it's final.
That's why, in order to distract myself
from that pressure,
I play catch, with a baseball.
The more that's expected of you,
the more pressure's that on you.
Daigo probably feels the same.
And I'm the oldest,
so there's more weight on me.
Hmm.
I'm sure there are a ton of things
that might crush us from the pressure.
While holding onto those feelings,
they took on this recording.
"UBU LOVE" RECORDING
Good, it's getting better.
Let's go once more.
Fujiwara decided to do several retakes of
his vital part leading up to the chorus.
One last try?
I'm sorry, can we?
-Just once more.
-I'm sorry.
-Dinner's on me.
-Last one!
Let's hear it!
How was that?
Yeah, good! Let's listen!
I suddenly did this while singing.
A hard-won victory.
Okay, we're finished!
-Thank you so much.
-Okay, good work!
Yes!
Probably before,
I would've said okay sooner.
But something inside me was saying that
I gotta do much better.
Right now, if I decided my own limit,
the perfect score so to speak,
I feel like I wouldn't grow any further.
Like I mentioned briefly before,
I'm afraid of debuting.
You know, confidence...
How much effort you put into it leads
to your confidence.
I did a bit of that today.
It really was a luxury
to be able to do so.
But I did feel that I needed
to aim much higher.
Overcoming fear
and fulfilling expectations.
Going forward, that will continue.
"UBU LOVE" FILMING
Look!
It's a Ford Thunderbird.
It's parked over there.
Their first music video shoot
took place on a large set.
In this music video, we want to show
your feelings toward the fans.
...toward the camera.
All takes toward the camera.
What was asked of them
was the exact world created by the lyrics.
To convey puppy love.
Kyohei, you're a bit stiff. Be more...
I don't have to sing or anything?
-No, you're good.
-So...
Well, if you'll make some expressions,
we'll use it.
-But mainly...
-Just during the singing.
They must produce results
within the limited time they have.
For example, even in situations like this.
When did that happen?
At the start.
Crap!
I noticed the sole was flopping around,
and thought, "Ah, it peeled off."
-It's done.
-I'm sorry.
-Were you okay?
-I was totally fine.
There was one problem
while filming the dance part.
Is it okay that I'm at one?
Zero.
Then I'd be here.
Huh?
Next to the rail and...
Their positions weren't working
due to a problem with the markers.
Can you place a tape marker?
To mark zero.
The rail... Yeah, because it's off.
Is something sticking out?
From the center?
The one who came up with an alternate plan
was the leader, Ohashi.
Isn't this the center? This white one?
This center tag is off.
So the center...
Match the center to the rail.
This line, if we just put this
over here more...
And this side line...
Like, if we just have the center line,
we'll be fine.
Oh, okay.
So, these kind of things
are going to continue going forward.
It's a joyful experience to be able
to interact with different people.
To be able to create one work together
with different people.
I'm thrilled.
It's really nice weather today.
Ohashi in particular has a strong
determination to survive in this world.
He learned the basics of singing
and dancing as a child,
and joined the agency
when the time was right at 11 years old.
However, he was never chosen for any units
and was a presence
who never got the spotlight.
-One, two.
-One...
In the meantime, he earnestly continued
refining his singing and dancing.
-One...
-Six, seven, eight!
-Two.
-From there probably...
-Thanks.
He is respected by the other members.
Kyohei.
He's still continuing his vocal training
while staying updated on new dance styles.
"Just sing and dance
in the Johnny's style."
"No need to take dance lessons."
"We just have to dance
whenever there's a concert."
I really hate that kind of mindset.
If that's the case,
I want to excel at dance within Johnny's.
After we make our debut,
we'll probably get more work, right?
If we're a group that never changes,
the audience will definitely...
They won't be pleased.
Plus, as a group we should challenge
ourselves at everything.
Or we won't be able to tell
what's good from bad.
Well, debuting isn't the goal,
it's the start.
Plus, thinking further...
Just making our debut
probably won't make
me feel like saying, "Yay!"
So pretty!
This completely different look
from daytime, it's kind of nice.
Once you debut, what do you think
will happen with Naniwa Danshi?
-I wonder.
-Yeah.
Well, I seriously don't know.
I have completely no idea...
I think Michieda, Takahashi, and Nagao
are probably more prepared for it.
I suddenly joined out of nowhere.
So I feel a bit like, "Oh, this is scary."
I wonder how things will turn out.
I can't tell until we actually do it.
I really do wonder.
Well, I'm sure there will be
ups and downs, of course.
We probably can't stay as a group
by just being friendly.
All of us having respect for each other
and consideration for one another is going
to continue for years from here on.
I hope we can strengthen
this aspect of our group.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Vroom... Ka-vroom!
Oh, I might be good at motorcycles.
A motorcycle waiting at a light.
Oh, that's good.
This is our group.
My bike at a light's good, eh?
That lingering feeling Nishihata
felt before their debut.
It wasn't until the last day of the tour
that it took shape.
NIIGATA PERFORMANCE
It happened on the last day
of the National Arena Tour in Niigata.
Good morning!
The seven members were trying to decide
what they'd been discussing for a week.
The last song we sing
as a Kansai Johnny's Jr. group,
we don't know
what we want it to be right now.
We have the most memories
with "My Dreams."
What song will they end their last concert
as a Johnny's Jr. group with?
But shouldn't it be a song
we want to sing?
Since it's the end.
The fans have their own ideas, but...
Keeping that in mind of course,
what do we want to sing last?
How many minutes is
the full version of "Kansai Island"?
-Including the second verse.
-From "arienkuraini," right?
Think of it this way...
"Kansai Island" is a song solely
for Kansai Johnny's Jr.
It is a song embedded with the memories
of hard work with friends.
We'll have everyone come out.
Let's do it with everyone,
not just the seven of us.
This. Since it's the end.
You really mean the full version?
Seriously... Then how's this?
How about this too?
We can't sing this. We'll cry.
They appear for their second encore.
Yeah! Okay!
We're gonna blast this!
This is our last song
as a Kansai Johnny's Jr. group.
Here we go. Please listen.
"KANSAI ISLAND"
Okay, last, with everyone!
Thank you!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
They put their whole heart into the song.
Naniwa Danshi First Arena Tour 2021
#NaniwaDanshishikakatan
has finished!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Thank you! It's finished successfully!
This is Naniwa Danshi
and Lil Kansai and Kansai Johnny's Jr.,
who've been with us for 26 shows.
Thank you!
I'm a fan of Kansai Johnny's Jr.
I love Kansai Johnny's Jr.
We gotta work harder and harder
to pass onto the next Kansai kids,
to the people of Kansai, a new baton.
We'll just keep doing our best.
Everyone, over here please!
On this day, Naniwa Danshi entered
the TV station at 2 a.m.
Three, two, one, bam!
NOVEMBER 22, 2021
LIVE TV
Thank you! Now you'll perform live!
Please get ready!
Okay, we will!
Time has passed rapidly since their debut.
"UBU LOVE"
The world after debuting
is something none of us have seen yet.
Next episode,
Naniwa Dashi takes off
into an unseen world.
This is really like a dream.
And it's a moment
where our debut really sinks in.
I'll blast some dynamite.
I'll throw some dynamite.
How does the world look to the seven
who chased their dreams together?
Yeah!
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi