The pop idol group SixTONES.
They started a concert tour this January
to push their second album.
I remember this.
ONE MONTH EARLIER
The group has different
personalities and preferences,
but they come together when
they put on a concert.
I see.
Seems doable.
Let's give it a try.
A cheering crowd
used to be a given, so I hate...
not being able to hear them.
I want things back to normal so we can
do simple interactions with the crowd.
They spent over 10 years in Johnny's Jr.
before they were able to achieve
their CD debut.
They nearly lost heart many times.
The one thing that kept them going
was their audience's cheers.
Back during that time,
there was this invisible persuasiveness
that was our main drive.
And passion.
There was an emphasis on
that which can't be quantified.
The heart they put into the shows.
It was one of the fundamental blocks
of their formation as a group.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Where is your origin?
This is me.
It was definitely here.
The atmosphere is similar.
It's like what Frieza rode
in his first form.
Taiga Kyomoto visited an area
where he lived during childhood.
I played with Yamada from Hey! Say! JUMP
in this sandbox as a kid.
-Yeah.
-Are you kidding me?
I have a lot of surprising stories.
His first encounter with his mentor
in the agency
was too long ago to remember.
He's had a strange connection to Johnny's
since then.
I was an only child
and I probably didn't come here
with my kindergarten friends.
I'd come here alone
and kind, calm kids
like Yamada would approach me.
And we'd become friends.
I wouldn't join in with kids
playing rowdily with balls.
Kyomoto may be starring in musicals now,
but he wasn't interested in singing
before he joined the agency.
Do you sometimes imagine a different
version of yourself?
Well, you know,
I don't have a sense of adventure at all.
If I fall in love with something,
I stick with it forever.
I love singing right now.
But that's probably only because
I joined Johnny's.
Above everything else, Mr. Johnny was...
He's the one that led me
to singing and everything else.
Mr. Johnny told me to sing on my own.
Mr. Johnny pushed me
to be in musicals too.
I'm so grateful to have
been taught about this world.
Each member's origin.
SHIMADA, SHIZUOKA
Hokuto Matsumura visits his hometown,
where he lived up through junior high.
I'm a little nervous.
Aki!
-Long time no see.
-Yeah.
-It's been three years.
-Has it?
Before you left.
Long time no see.
-How've you been?
-Good.
That's good. Are you off today?
I just went in this morning. Then I left.
What should we do?
First, I'd love to see
the junior high school.
We never were in the same class, were we?
-You're right.
-Right?
Weren't you scared of me?
How'd we get close?
Right? But I never said
I was scared of you.
I just thought you were a noisy guy.
Like, there's this noisy guy
making a ruckus.
He entered Johnny's at age 13.
In the beginning, he commuted
to Tokyo from his hometown.
-Hello.
-Thanks for having us.
-This was the student entrance.
-Yes, I'd come through here on my bike.
-That's right.
-I'd come on my bike.
-This brings back memories.
-It does.
It looks cleaner.
My classroom was over here,
and yours was over there.
Right.
Our classrooms.
I was over here.
We hated being apart, so sometimes
one of us would sit in the other's class.
-Then we'd get sent back.
-We'd sit in until we got caught.
For some reason on this floor
it was popular to sing
and dance to KinKi Kids and KAT-TUN.
-You know what I mean?
-Like this.
On and on like this.
And we'd check each other out.
-That brings back memories.
-You still remember.
One time we got so into it
that we broke the ceiling.
-I didn't think I'd make it this far.
-Totally.
Don't agree!
You know, from my point of view,
I wanted you to work hard and make it.
But I couldn't tell you to
work hard and do your best.
Yeah?
Because I knew how tough it was for you.
Yeah.
Matsumura was selected
to join a promising unit.
He took the plunge and moved to Tokyo
after junior high school.
However, not long after,
the unit disbanded.
This forced him and Yugo Kochi,
who would go on to join SixTONES,
to search for a different path to follow.
-I remember graduation.
-Right?
After graduation, we made plans
for me to spend the night at your house.
-Right.
-Yeah.
So I asked when I should spend the night.
When I should go over.
Then you said, "Sorry."
"We're all leaving for Tokyo today."
I wasn't prepared for that emotionally.
So I was like, "I see."
Yeah, I didn't tell anyone
I was moving to Tokyo.
I said I'd work hard at baseball,
so you work hard at being an idol.
We said we'd hang out together.
And I cried.
-Right.
-Yeah.
You know...
I remember we talked about the Tokyo Dome
because they play baseball there too.
So we were like,
let's both reach the Tokyo Dome
following our own paths.
We talked about working that hard.
Setbacks and a promise with a friend.
Both have made Matsumura
into what he is today.
Let's go then.
This brings back memories.
When Juri Tanaka wants to reflect
on himself, he comes to this place alone.
He also experienced a slow period
after joining the agency.
-Do you sometimes come here alone?
-Yes, I do come here alone.
I don't often open up to other people.
Like, about my problems
or about my dreams for the future.
It's like...
I wonder why I don't.
But when I was 18,
I did open up just once to my mom.
When I was about 17 or 18, I told her
I wanted to quit.
I've only said that once.
Quit Johnny's?
Just that once.
My mom didn't say anything at the time,
but three days later
she told me I could quit
whenever I wanted.
So I thought I'd try harder,
and became even more closed off.
His turning point was when he was
selected to be in a school drama.
There he would find five friends with
similar apprehensions about the future.
JOHNNY'S GINZA 2015
They hit it off and went into direct talks
about creating their own group.
The name is...
Yes, the name...
Six people...
Six Tones.
Tones.
Their group would later be born
under the new name of "SixTONES."
We each bring our own uniqueness.
All six of us were thinking of quitting.
We placed a final bet on SixTONES.
So we're continuing to bet on SixTONES.
We'll keep going until we lose the bet.
And when we feel like we've lost...
we'll walk away.
2019 SINGLE GROUP CONCERT
Before their CD debut, concerts were
important for gauging fan reactions.
SixTONES created its style
of enjoying the show with the audience.
Then finally...
DEBUT CD SET FOR RELEASE!
SIXTONES CD DEBUT ANNOUNCEMENT
Congratulations.
DECEMBER 2021
FEEL DA CITY ARENA TOUR REHEARSAL
Rehearsals for their New Year's concert
have entered the final stage.
That's a wrap.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
Well...
-It's a bit loose.
-Well, it's tepid.
To be honest, during the rehearsal
I only had fun with "Louder."
I just wasn't feeling it.
I just never overall felt
that we'd captured
the feeling of a SixTONES concert.
They lacked that SixTONES fervor.
They needed major revisions.
We want something strong.
-Yeah, totally.
-There aren't many strong songs.
Wanna "Special Order" into "Rosy"?
I like it.
That felt pretty good to me.
Totally fine.
Do you guys think you have the stamina?
I think our first lineup was made
considering our physical stamina.
-We can do it if we try.
-Okay.
They will take up the challenge of a more
rigorous show that pushes their limits.
JANUARY 2022
YOKOHAMA ARENA
-Let's do our best.
-Yes.
Off we go then.
This was the day
their second album was released.
How will the fans react
to the six months of work
they put into the album?
All right.
And to close the first half of the concert
they will play their new song
designed for audience participation.
We do love concerts.
We didn't care if we couldn't debut
as long as we still got to do concerts.
We're most at ease with concerts.
Whatever we do, the fans
will come see us because they want to.
This is their home.
We have the name SixTONES.
SixTONES is our house.
The way we think, the way we feel...,
The way we act, the thoughts we have...
SixTONES is all over the place.
But somewhere we're connected.
The group called SixTONES is
connected by music.
Some want to do well on variety shows,
and some on TV and movies.
We all see where we want to be the best.
However, when it comes to music, we feel
that it's definitely the six of us.
There's one thing I'm certain about,
and it's not quitting the group.
But if someone left,
I wonder if we'd go on.
If someone said they're leaving...
If SixTONES disbands,
I'll have no reason to try hard.
The only thing I'll have left
in my life is eating.
If SixTONES disbands, that'll
be the end of my idol career.
That's how set I am
on working hard with everyone.
Nobody can be added or subtracted.
This number is everything to them.
And most likely, this sentiment
will continue from here on out.
On the next RIDE ON TIME, it's Kis-My-Ft2,
ushering in their tenth anniversary.
They speak candidly about their conflicts
and dreams over the decade.
"I'll burn you up!"
One day we'd think we could see the light,
and the next day it would be pitch black.
We need to make it big.
Or there's no point.
What is being an idol?
It's nothing I've experienced before.
A thirty-year reunion.
Ms. Ishida?
Taichan?
And...
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
They walk down a new path
to hone each member's individuality.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto