Okay, here we go! Rolling!
The idol group SixTONES.
MUSIC VIDEO FILMING
Production for a new song was ramped up
for the release of their new album.
I was thinking that you could all
give this dance a go
maybe five or six times.
Copy that.
Although, we'll see
if we have the stamina.
But if you guys want to
make some cuts, that's fine.
No, we're fine. Whichever is easiest.
Okay, copy that.
We'll do the opposite.
We do things the hard way.
They took on many different genres
in their first album for a wide range
of music fans.
"UYAMUYA"
People said how great our first album was.
And I loved hearing that.
However, it raises the bar
for the second one.
We have to take inspiration
from all sorts of places
and put in the second album
to surpass our first.
That's what I think.
They want to make this second album
better than the first.
What is the music
the six of them are striving for?
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
-That syllable is low.
-Yeah.
I can't get that low.
I bet.
HOKUTO MATSUMURA (26)
That's low.
Yeah.
That's a C to an G.
That's it.
-That's hard.
-That was good.
"MAKKANA USO"
The song Matsumura and Kochi
sing is an ambitious one
meant to highlight their
different voices and personalities.
YUGO KOCHI (27)
You hit the smoothness right.
It wasn't quite it.
Yeah, the feeling. It was low.
I want to get it right.
Okay, let's go again.
Whoa.
Was that good?
Good work.
Good job today.
Do you think I can listen to a rough cut?
Yeah, sure.
Kochi has such a kind voice.
-You know?
-For sure.
He seems really sunny.
More kind than sunny, actually.
A good person.
He sounds like a good person.
My voice is a nag.
-You think so?
-No way.
A nag?
It seems sensitive.
Oh.
Any retakes needed?
I'm up for it if there are.
Let's go from the top then!
How to best showcase his own voice?
He's searched for a way
every time he takes on a new song.
Take it from the top?
Okay.
You think you could be more aggressive?
-Yeah.
-Something more wild.
-Okay.
Great. Let's listen to that.
Perfect!
It's like it was hammered into your body,
so it's going really fast.
I did do a lot yesterday.
You did? You did a lot?
I did so much yesterday.
-I guess you did choreography. Right.
-Yeah, choreography.
Since we debuted,
we've had the privilege of
showcasing our singles on music programs.
I guess the bar is set really high.
Like we're part of something big.
You know?
So sometimes I'd think
I didn't do enough to prepare.
I'm 27 now, and I wonder
how many skills I can learn by 30.
What do you think
your strengths are with singing?
With singing?
Well, among the SixTONES members,
I feel like
I have the best sense of rhythm.
That goes for everything, like jump rope.
I just really hate my own voice.
I only listen to the guide track.
I keep my voice volume low.
There's a cue box that lets you
hear your own voice,
I just listen to
the guide voice track at full volume.
But I was told
when I started going to lessons,
that it's important to accept my voice.
That made sense.
So I started accepting it.
I can tolerate my speaking, but I'm still
not comfortable with my singing.
Not yet.
Shinataro has a killer voice.
Yes, it's really sexy.
Thank you.
But I hate it.
I see.
Okay, here we go!
FILMING SPECIAL VIDEO
FOR SECOND ALBUM "CITY"
We going with rangers?
When's your play 'til, Kyo?
-October?
-Twenty-eight.
-Thirty? Then next month.
-We can't then.
TAIGA KYOMOTO (27)
Taiga Kyomoto was also starring
in a musical at this time.
He kept talking to a minimum
in order to save his voice for the stage.
Being cautious, they did the recording
before the show opened.
Hello.
You look tired.
You look well.
You seem really well.
Sorry, I meant the opposite.
So energetic!
So dumb.
How's your throat?
Or is it more your body?
My throat is...
I'm up for it.
Yeah.
But we'll be running full dress
rehearsals until the show,
so if I mess up my throat,
I won't have time to rest it.
I see.
It's just gonna be full on.
I'm not in great condition,
but I can still get on stage.
If I think about doing the play
for the next month,
I have to be conservative.
Being able to hit high notes,
Kyomoto had an important part
to play in this song.
Will I hit it?
The top note is B, as in A, B.
I can do that.
If you're on form.
-It's feeling super high.
-True.
It's magic.
Yeah, B shows up twice.
-I can do it.
-Yeah.
-Let's give it a shot.
-Okay.
Hm?
Should we do it?
Can you do the Buddha pose?
-Wanna do it?
-Oh, this pose?
I'll give this a go.
Nope.
-Let me go again.
-Okay.
I'll put it under my heels.
Go for it.
-I'm ready.
-Let's go.
-Cool.
-Felt good.
Listen to it.
Can I try that again?
-Sure, of course.
-Awesome.
So cool! Let's hear it.
This is bad, I end up going all out.
Right?
Please stop me.
Okay, we will.
You'll never be able to air this.
No?
You can't air me abusing
rolls of tape like this.
But it helped create a beautiful song.
That makes it an effective use.
It's not the right way.
-I'm sorry about the tape.
-Oh, right.
-Sorry.
-Look at that.
-Wow.
-Sorry.
It can still be used.
It's still adhesive.
Taiga-san, do you like your own voice?
I wonder.
I don't especially like my voice,
but there's a voice of mine that I like.
I don't really like my talking voice.
And my singing voice
there's some frustration that it sometimes
doesn't match the songs I like.
Jesse always tells me he's envious of
my voice because of how high I can go.
But from my perspective,
I think Jesse is so cool
because he can do things I can't
like sing in English and hit low notes.
We both have different strengths.
I guess the grass
is always greener with voices.
JESSIE (25)
Some people might think you're good
because you can hit low notes,
while others think hitting high notes
make you good.
Or some may value
being able to convey a feeling.
I'd be happy if any of those fit me.
Which would you like?
I can't hit high notes.
I'm envious of Taiga.
I wish I could do that.
-Because he can hit high notes?
-Yeah.
For him, singing was something
that gave him joy.
Hello.
Goodbye then.
Let us in.
He chose a famous song
by someone he loves and respects.
MELODY KOJI TAMAKI
Why do you know Koji Tamaki so well?
Because I love him.
It started when I saw him on music
programs my grandpa and grandma watched.
I'd see clips when I was little.
I started looking him up myself,
and finally got to see him live last year.
I cried before he even got on stage.
I couldn't see him at all
through my tears.
You know? Like...
For the last hook,
just play around with it and adlib stuff.
Okay.
Just wing it.
-I'll start two lines earlier.
-Okay.
That was great.
Perfect.
Thanks, we got it.
There's no right answer.
That was great.
Well, I wonder what Mr. Tamaki would do.
I want to see him.
I bet you could.
I wonder where he is.
Where could he be?
JURI TANAKA (26)
Jesse's so cool.
Juri Tanaka is in charge of rapping.
He talked to us about their voices.
I like my own voice.
That's why I listen to the song.
It's a voice that sounds unsettling
when you hear it as a sound.
Or rather, my voice is
really good at lingering.
I want to give meaning
for the six of us to sing.
If our voices were all uniform and
came together in one big, pretty voice,
then only the one
with the best voice needs to sing.
But since there's six of us,
there's meaning if we're all different.
JANUARY 2022
YOKOHAMA ARENA
So the other five members can
cover for me to make the sounds I can't.
Bring it in.
Alright, bring it in.
Yo.
Even Juri's rapping,
or Shintaro's sweet voice.
We all have our own
unique character in our voices.
I can't imagine not singing together.
Next time, it's the big concert.
If SixTONES disbands,
I'll have no reason to try hard.
I'm so grateful to have been taught
about this world.
We're most at ease during concerts.
Whatever we do, the fans will come see us
because they want to.
I'll give it a spin.
Subtitle translation by:
Zensho Yamamoto