DECEMBER 31, 2021
New Year's Eve, 2021.
An event returned after a two year hiatus.
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2021 TO 2022
Johnny's countdown concert.
Kis-My-Ft2, or Kis-My for short.
YUTA TAMAMORI
Yuta Tamamori is the center member.
What does 2022 mean to him?
The 10th anniversary of our debut,
be it our fans,
or the people who helped support Kis-My.
Of course I feel grateful
and want to give back to all of them,
but I also want us
to be even more popular.
I've always felt that.
We need to make it big.
Or there's no point.
What is his motivation?
This is documentary series Ride on Time.
Good morning.
Their first concert in three years
with an audience was closing in.
Yuta Tamamori is in charge
of Kis-My's costumes.
On this day, the costume design sketches
were brought out.
SENGA
This patchwork makes it more elegant.
This may be a little more pop,
but I want something more elegant.
There's a chance we need to
rethink the shape for Gaya's.
We may need to do something.
MAY 2019 TOKYO DOME
Tamamori has been in charge of costumes
for many of their concerts.
He's currently thinking
about Fujigaya's costume.
Only one of them would be wearing
a long coat over their jacket.
FUJIGAYA
With this kind of style,
you really need to... make the line right.
I don't want it looking too baggy.
What are Tamamori's feelings
towards the costumes?
I try to make them look cool.
I want the seven of us
to be a fashion statement.
Johnny's costumes leave
a strong impression.
They have a distinct brand.
Being sparkly or frilly.
That's of course mainstream and wonderful,
but I want to go in
a more fashionable direction.
Something that makes
Kis-My look more sophisticated.
Something that looks cool
and motivates us.
I strive to make costumes
that will make people think,
"Wow, that costume is so cool."
That's the kind of costumes I try to make.
Everyone gets in position at the intro.
Rehearsals that go into
the tiniest details.
The one joshing around
with Fujigaya during a break is...
Kis-My's life of the party,
Toshiya Miyata.
TOSHIYA MIYATA
I'm forgetting what I memorized.
What's wrong with me?
-I'll get it done by the 8th.
-By the 8th?
Like doing your homework
the last day of vacation?
Is that bad?
He always lightens the mood like so.
Because I'm a detective.
He cut his hair short
for his role in a TV drama.
That's right. It starts in January.
They said my bangs shouldn't
reach my eyebrows so I cut it.
I guess it'll be short
for the concert too.
-Really?
-Is it weird?
It suits you.
That's nice to hear.
I've got a pretty face
so it's only natural.
Miyata is making headway
into new territory in his solo career.
I'm so pretty.
He made his voice acting debut
in an anime movie in 2020.
In 2021, he took on musical theater.
MUSICAL GREAT PRETENDER
I'm a black belt in karate!
Take this!
Wait, you're...
Abby's a friend.
I feel like I've desperately...
held on these last ten years.
I had no confidence, and was so timid.
Of course I'd get messed with.
I've totally changed.
He heads out after work.
Good evening!
Long time!
Good to see you again.
The voice actor Daisuke Namikawa.
Miyata's been receiving
private lessons from Mr. Namikawa
ever since his role
in the anime movie BEM,
looking up to him as a teacher.
I'm going to have you read
as a hero, a main character
in a romance, and a mascot character.
-Which one first?
-Let me think.
I'd like to do the romantic lead.
You really love those parts.
I do.
There's pattern A and B.
Which do you want?
I like B.
I see.
Okay.
-We'll do pattern B.
-Okay.
So punctuation marks.
Like periods, and commas.
I always wonder about
how much I should be adhering to them.
As you're talking to me now,
are you thinking about punctuation?
No.
-You aren't imagining punctuation, right?
-That's true.
So don't think about punctuation marks.
You can just forget about them
as a concept altogether.
Why don't you go ahead.
Picture it in your mind.
Okay.
"I love you.
I can't stop this feeling.
No matter what view lies ahead of us,
as long as I'm with you,
I'll be able to admire it with a smile.
Now, take my hand.
Let's go take in this view together."
Okay, thank you.
First off, what kind of character is he?
What I imagined was someone 21 years old,
who I'm sure wanted to
take her to a bridge
to admire the night skyline
together or something.
First, I want to say
that you're not in that scene.
From that performance.
You have to become this character,
so you can't be looking
into the scene from the outside.
-Right.
-I think you're not sure.
About whether you're looking at
the mountain, river, or the heroine.
You haven't settled on
what you're viewing.
It's about a guy who is
not able to stop his own feelings.
Right.
"I love you.
I can't stop this feeling."
"I love you."
You say "I love you" to her.
He repeated this line for 40 minutes.
"I love you.
I can't stop this feeling.
No matter what view lies ahead of us,
as long as I'm with you,
I'll be able to admire it with a smile.
Now, take my hand.
Let's go take in this view together."
Yes, nice!
I can picture the scene.
-I'm happy.
-That's great.
"As long as evil exists..."
As a fan of anime,
Miyata developed a new skill
in voice acting.
But when he first debuted...
"I'll burn you all!"
Society just associated anime culture
with being gross and creepy.
But I thought it was worse
to say I didn't like it because of that.
Miyata was struggling having to
hide himself, until...
When we were doing a Kis-My concert,
I said I wanted to do otagei.
Otagei is that cheer dance
done by geeky fans.
I think everyone knows what it is now
but back then people were like,
"Is that cool? Is that even fun?"
Some people didn't view it positively.
But the other members were on board.
Their attitude was,
"Sounds cool, let's do it."
AUGUST 2016 TOKYO DOME
The whole group performed
the otagei at their show.
Miyata's love for anime became known.
Present day, ten years after their debut...
I feel that working hard
to achieve my dream
is something that will eventually
connect back to the group.
Like an anime created by
Kis-My's Toshiya Miyata.
Doesn't that sound good?
And the title song would be by Kis-My-Ft2.
That'd be great.
Welcome.
Nikaido is in charge
of the tour's production.
He shares his thoughts on Kis-My.
TAKASHI NIKAIDO
Well, I love... I love it, I guess.
I love it very much, but...
It might not look like
we get along from the outside.
It's not that we don't get along.
I think we just don't want to
act like we get along for appearances.
When Nikaido works on production,
there's something he keeps in mind.
When I'm coming up with ideas,
I'm not in Kis-My anymore.
I become a fan.
I think about what fans want to see
and what would make them happy.
Something that will make them feel great.
I become a different person.
That's why I probably lose my spotlight.
With such thoughts
going into the concerts...
MAY 2021 METLIFE DOME
LIVE TOUR 2021 HOME (LIVESTREAM)
The waterworks they showed off
during their 2021 live stream
became a big talking point among fans.
Also, there is always someone on his mind.
Every year when we do a show,
I always wonder what Mr. Johnny would do.
I wonder if we're
meeting his expectations.
"Are you guys giving
the audience a good time?"
That's what I imagine him asking us.
This could be the time
when I think about him the most.
The Kis-My-Ft2 member
with a unique character.
Wataru Yokoo.
He's a first-class tuna butcher
while also an idol.
TUNA BUTCHER
He has many other qualifications,
such as that of a pet carer.
PET CARER
One day during rehearsal...
The timing.
Yeah, we can do that.
-Can we change it, Nika?
-What?
Kitayama will hang back talking,
but if he wants more time
between songs, I can stay back.
-Sure, that's fine.
-Okay?
-Totally.
-Thanks.
Even during a break...
Nika, for "FIRE BEAT"...
Right now, Mr. Kitayama is in the center.
What if we move him over there,
and everyone else gathers around him?
-No problem.
-That might be better.
Shall we do that?
He is always looking
at the bigger picture.
The root of this trait
can be found at the book store.
If this were for business,
I would try to imagine how
Kis-My should position itself,
or how we should conduct ourselves.
Tamamori handles our costumes.
Miyata is on merchandising,
and Nika's handling production.
And Mr. Senga works on choreography.
There are four divisions.
What can we do to keep that flow going?
That's something great businesses
have figured out already.
You can learn a lot from their examples.
Their 10-year anniversary
is giving Yokoo certain misgivings.
Until how old are you an idol?
How long can you do it?
We're all in our 30s now.
Can we carry on until our 50s
like some of our predecessors?
So 20 more years.
Or...
it could be 10 if we stumble.
Every member of Kis-My-Ft2
is in their 30s now.
What's something Yokoo keeps in mind
for them to continue their idol careers?
It's important to think
and act for yourself.
You can't just be told
what to do, being a puppet.
When that person disappears,
you won't be able to do anything anymore.
We need to...
be able move on our own
to a certain degree.
Yokoo recently started
MORE VEGETABLES IN PASTA AND SOUP
writing for a cooking magazine.
The food-loving Yokoo
found a new path for himself.
Think and act for yourself.
That's Kis-My.
KIS-MY-FT2 WATARU YOKOO'S
WATARU MEAL FOR YOU
DECEMBER 31, 2021
The tumultuous year
that was 2021 was ending.
DECEMBER 31, 2021
Three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
-It's 2022!
-Happy New Year!
The Johnny's Countdown Concert.
It returned to Tokyo Dome
after a two year hiatus.
Three, two, one, go! Come on!
Of course, Kis-My was there too.
After the Countdown concert ended,
Tamamori shared his current feelings.
Having fans who've...
been supporting us continuously
without changing for ten years
is really significant.
After all, normally...
concerts are the only opportunities
we have to meet our fans.
We haven't had that in about two years.
So we've been wanting to
show them our cheerful selves,
that's what we've been thinking.
What time is it? Almost 2:00 a.m.?
There's only 12 months left.
Only 12 months left, it's too soon.
It'll be over in a flash.
I don't know what it is,
but I'm in a rush to live.
I'm always in a hurry.
Really?
Of course, I feel pressured since
so many talented kids are coming up.
Right?
If you take it easy, they'll pass you by.
And...
We need to make it big.
Or there's no point.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure if I should be saying this,
but I mean, what's the point then?
We're doing this to be popular.
And for the fans.
I mean, it's for ourselves and Kis-My too.
But since we're doing it,
we should be make it big.
I feel strongly about that.
As long as we're in this game,
we need to be striving for the top.
we need to be an even stronger group.
That's how I see it.
And so began 2022,
the year of resolutions.
Next time, the arena tour is closing in.
Fujigaya continues to struggle.
I wondered what I'd think
after ten years had passed.
Like, I've learned how to do this or that.
But I haven't learned
to do anything at all.
And he visits a special someone.
What?
Ms. Ishida?
Taichan?
The final rehearsal for the arena tour.
Three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
When they think we disappeared,
we just kind of slink in.
So when the video turns off,
we shouldn't stand?
Off we go!
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
Let's do it.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto