There is a song
that describes their journey.
LYRICS
"How long have I dreamed for."
"Time View ~Hatenaku Tsuzuku Michi~."
The days when they dreamed
about making their debut as idols.
The emotions built up
inside directly became a song.
NANIWA DANSHI
SHUNSUKE MICHIEDA (19)
Like, "Days that were hard to swallow."
I'm sure there were many days
the seven of us weren't satisfied.
I wondered, "Do we have no choice
but to continue in show business?"
I'm a not a great talker...
but this is how we show
what we're thinking.
How do I put this? Something like that.
I did think,
"Oh, I'm glad I wrote something."
When I felt worried,
there were always my members beside me.
"Even if I'm about to break,
when I look over, you're with me."
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
NANIWA DANSHI
In November 2021,
Naniwa Danshi from Kansai Johnny's Jr.
successfully made their CD debut.
The group was formed in October, 2018.
While repeatedly tasting defeat,
the seven of them diligently continued
to chase their debut.
THREE YEARS OF WORKING TOWARD THEIR DEBUT
Well, I'm not that young either,
so if I lose this, to be honest,
I have nothing...
Yeah, nothing left.
That moment had arrived
last summer.
Naniwa Danshi's first
solo national arena tour.
JULY 3, 2021
DAY BEFORE MIYAGI CONCERT
Let's go!
-Wow.
-Let's go!
-Good morning!
Good morning!
Wow, it's big!
Cool, it's a diamond!
At this moment,
the seven of them had not been notified
of their debut yet.
Now, the members will scatter
to their spots.
The big stage where Naniwa Danshi's
abilities will be put to the test.
The one in charge of stage directions
was the group's center role,
Daigo Nishihata.
It's very big.
Huh?
This place is big, yes.
It's different when you come to the site.
It's spacious too.
And you get really amped up too.
How many will fit in here?
One of the youngest members with
an innocent character is Kento Nagao.
You haven't heard?
Oh, Jo, how many fit in here?
-Fit what?
-People.
Four can fit the bath.
Four?
Oh, that's tight.
They say four can fit the bath.
Their other youngest member
who performs in dramas and film,
Shunsuke Michieda, rechecks his moves.
SHUNSUKE MICHIEDA
I know I can't eat all of this.
I'm an athlete.
Like...
The one working to become an idol
since he was ten,
Ryusei Onishi.
NANIWA DANSHI
RYUSEI ONISHI (20)
The baseball lover always
in uniform is the oldest,
Joichiro Fujiwara.
To the outer path and "Seven Stars."
Let's get the audience excited
all the way up to the top.
It's a big slope, so try to look upward.
Okay.
And the arena too.
From eight years old, he has been working
toward his debut for 17 years.
The one who's been taking
voice training to aim for debut,
Kyohei Takahashi.
NANIWA DANSHI
KYOHEI TAKAHASHI (21)
The pillar to uphold Naniwa Danshi,
the leader, Kazuya Ohashi.
KAZUYA OHASHI (24)
Is your throat okay?
Yeah.
It's completely fine.
Practice like you perform,
perform like you practice.
I think we'll do the best we can
and have fun.
And so, their tour began.
Hey, come with us!
Now please listen to
"Time View, ~Hatenaku Tsuzuku Michi~."
The song that Michieda wrote
on Naniwa Danshi's journey up to now.
The hearts of all the members
were intertwined within this song.
The moment they discussed that
was that one day.
JUNE 27, 2021
DISCUSSION
So, probably everything...
The lyrics of "Time View"
is speaking for us.
Yeah.
-Yeah!
-Everything.
When you listen to that alone,
doesn't it make you tear up?
Yeah, definitely!
I do get tears slightly.
Well, it's our own song
and it's a song written by our member.
Right, it's a special song.
So, you know, it speaks for us.
That's our feelings.
Even though Michieda wrote it.
Yeah.
Wait a second.
His smug face is kind of really...
I'm just glad to hear that.
Well, it is a good song.
I wrote it and did think that maybe
it was a little too direct and all...
No, it's okay. That's good.
That's what's good.
I wasn't really confident
about it actually,
but if everyone says that's
how you guys feel, I'm glad I wrote it.
Because they had a mutual goal
of making their debut,
the seven were able to unite their hearts.
When a certain phrase is sung,
there was something Ohashi
always kept in mind to do.
EVEN IF I'M ABOUT TO BREAK
WHEN I LOOK OVER, YOU'RE WITH ME
In "Time View,"
that line that says,
"When I look over, you're with me."
I do look over, yes.
I'm singing, "When I look over,"
so when I look, I'm like,
"Who's there? Oh, it's my members."
They won't look at me.
No one looks at me though.
You noticed that?
I know they definitely notice!
They notice, but they won't look this way.
I don't want them to glare at me,
but I want them to glance this way.
If they do, I'll probably get goosebumps.
I'm gonna state it here,
everyone's review.
I want them to tell me how they feel, so...
JULY 27-28, 2021
YOKOHAMA ARENA
The moment finally arrived.
Good morning!
The Yokohama Arena,
including their seniors,
is a stage where many
famous artists have performed.
Anyone interesting there?
Well, everyone is amazing.
Incredible.
Nishihata was moved in a different way.
Exactly two years ago,
we've always, um...
We've been talking about how we wanted
to do a concert on the day of 728.
It's already the day of 728
before we even knew it!
Oh, it is the day of 728.
It is!
Even at this point,
they had not been notified of anything.
The waiting room was just like normal.
Mr. Ohashi, what's that? Your feet.
These are one-tooth geta sandals.
When I was dancing before,
I felt that I wobbled a bit.
I thought I needed more strength,
so I felt I should wear these.
It gave me a ton of muscle here!
There were problems
with the reception and connectivity,
so this time, we had them modify
the ones we've been using.
The difference between this and that
is that it's rubber here,
so it acts as slip resistance...
The modified headset.
It's a little arched.
Oh, this is really nice!
It's perfect. Look!
-Was there a dance like that?
-Yes, there is.
-But we'll do this.
-Definitely like this.
The distance here
will be quite spaced out.
It fits perfect!
The Yokohama Arena is large,
so its outer path is stretched out.
Yes.
The length of the path from the main stage
to center stage is twice that of Sendai.
-Yes.
-So the travel time will be longer.
Um, so please run on your own
at those moments.
Jeez, that's tough.
Our legs will be in pain.
Let's try it.
Okay, let's do it.
Because the C Stage side's
outer path is very wide.
Oh, I'm sorry,
the main stage side is wide.
To the audience filled
to the corners of this large hall,
the seven of them must deliver
their hearts to everybody.
The second day of Yokohama,
that moment finally arrived.
Kansai Johnny's Jr., KanJani8, WEST were
with us before, but we're solo this time.
The day of 728,
let's keep this day in our hearts.
Today, Naniwa Danshi,
let's make lots of our fans happy!
-Let's go!
-Hey!
They've worked frantically
and reached July 28th at last.
My body's very flexible,
so I'd like to show you right now!
The kanji for "ground"!
And now, "stop"!
-Yay!
-For real!
It happened midway through the concert
during the talking segment.
-That scared me.
-Huh? What?
An EKG.
DEBUT CD SET FOR RELEASE!
A CD debut from Kansai Johnny's Jr.
hasn't been decided
since JOHNNY'S WEST's seven years ago.
All right!
I'm glad. Seriously, I'm so glad!
Seriously!
Honestly, thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
Did you imagine this at all?
I did have a slight expectation,
of course.
But that's every performance.
I'm at my limit.
My eyes will be puffy by next performance.
It's okay.
The seven who knew nothing about
each other when they were first grouped
shed tears together.
All right.
Thank you.
It was so long,
seventeen and a half years.
"Time View" is gonna be hard.
Plus, the lyrics are,
"How long have I dreamed for."
"Those days when I thought
it would never come true."
"I'd remember
and pretend not to think about it."
But now, that's a reality.
I have to thank Micchi.
"TIME VIEW ~HATENAKU TSUZUKU MICHI~"
Thank you, it was good.
I'm so glad.
Oh, don't cry.
I'm so happy.
I'm really happy myself.
Thank you.
But it'll be even harder from here.
That's true.
Well, we'll work hard.
Good work!
To celebrate the members,
a good friend had rushed over.
Good work.
Yeah!
A member of Snow Man,
Koji Mukai.
Can you wait here?
They spent their days together
at Kansai Johnny's Jr.,
a friend who aimed for the same goal.
Hey!
Yeah!
-Muka-chan!
-Good work!
I came for the encore.
Oh, seriously?
Good work!
Anyhow, I'm just happy for them.
I teared up during Daigo's speech too.
To me right now, like...
How do you say this?
They're a presence that inspires me.
How do I put this?
What I kind of imagined
or what was built up here inside me
feels like it all disappeared.
So I'm now really empty in a good way.
I think I'll restart from scratch
and work hard.
Thank you.
To be honest,
when I wrote "Time View"...
Of course it holds the feelings
of us seven too.
But I wrote this
so we can cry while singing it.
Really.
"Time View" was very nice.
I'm glad we were able to sing it
as we cried.
The lyrics didn't sink
into the crowd though.
They probably couldn't make out the words.
Since we were all bawling while singing.
But even still,
the fans were intently watching us
while they cried.
So I thought,
"I'm glad I joined Johnny's."
Next time,
the surprising feelings flooding
the debuting Naniwa Danshi.
I'm more worried now.
It's contradictory.
I wanted to debut, so I worked
for it, but I get scared once it's final.
What is demanded
of them grows bigger by the day.
The picture seen after debuting
will become different, definitely.
How does the picture look from their eyes?
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi