Riatotsu WEST for national television.
This is the first recording.
Let's do this guys!
SEPTEMBER
RIATOTSU WEST FILMING LAUNCH
It's been seven years since their debut.
Their namesake program will launch
nationwide in October.
Haru, what's that over there?
Whether in dramas or plays,
the members are continually performing.
That energy for performing is unstoppable
for JOHNNY'S WEST.
Ouch!
We stayed with the seven of them
for seven months.
-What are you doing?
-You made me do it.
I've always thought that
this group got along the best in Johnny's.
I think the other groups find it
a bit weird how well we get along.
But seeing them
after a long time was fun.
That's when I'll realize for
the first time, "This is what I wanted."
The spotlight has begun
shining on all of them.
What are they thinking?
What are their goals?
Stop fooling around!
Stop...
Don't fight during class.
Guys, let's do this right, okay?
-Let's do it.
-Yeah.
Did you get that?
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
In April 2014,
JOHNNY'S WEST made their debut.
Their debut song "Eejanaika"
reached first place on the Oricon Chart.
Today's the first zodiac reunion
in 100 years.
I can't watch this!
They've been searching for their own path.
No, I can't hold this.
Hey, you're holding it in your hand!
It's not like we reached
a million sales right away.
We've taken it one step at a time.
In fact, we've had times
where we stopped progressing.
But they finally got their chance
to hold two large dome tours last year.
But with the pandemic,
that dream did not come true.
OSAKA CONCERT CANCELED
In addition, there was a seven-city tour
they were supposed to have.
But the concert in their hometown
Osaka was canceled.
MAY 30
SAITAMA SUPER ARENA
Nevertheless, they're looking forward
to a six-city tour with a live audience.
We can only do this because of
how well-mannered the audience is.
Thank you!
Everyone is helping us.
It feels like everyone
is helping create this.
They've safely finished
performing in five cities.
The last one is in Kumamoto.
-Good work.
-Thanks.
Good work, guys.
There's a new wind
blowing in for these seven.
JUNE
-Mr. Hamada is now on location.
-Thank you.
-Please come in.
-Hello.
BUSHI-STANT AISAKAKUN! FILMING LAUNCH
Playing the role of Sojiro Aisaka,
this is Takahiro Hamada.
Thank you.
JOHNNY'S WEST
TAKAHIRO HAMADA (32)
This is the opening for
BUSHI-STANT AISAKAKUN!
We're starting to film now. Thank you.
Thank you.
This is Hamada's first main role drama
without his group.
The original story is
a popular manga series.
He plays a shunga painter who has
time warped into present day Japan.
All right, let's start filming.
Okay.
Here's the octopus.
When somebody's doing well,
it has that good effect on the group.
-Synergistic effect?
-Yeah, that's it!
When somebody improves themselves,
there's a strong feeling
we have to do better too.
I believe everyone in the group
thinks this way.
Everyone gets fired up.
That was... my first octopus.
I got scared during the filming.
In 2002, when he was
in his second year of middle school.
Hamada came knocking
on Johnny&Associates,Inc.
The adorable character he has
all started from this point.
The younger members remember
what he was like back then.
I also happened to be
in the same Junior unit
with Hamada when he was young.
Hamada said something to me...
Even though he's older,
he told me, "Just call me Hama-chan."
That's how it happened.
Since I've joined,
I've only called him, "Hama-chan."
I've never used polite language
since we've debuted.
We always used "kun"
with Akito and Junta.
But Hama-chan has always been "Hama-chan."
That's what makes him amazing.
He's got talent.
If I needed to talk to someone,
it would probably be Hama-chan.
He's easy to talk to
and easy to get advice from.
He's a great listener.
An adorable character
and the life of the party.
This was taken during their break.
Let's start already.
This is right before
their concert started.
Running away
from the behind-the-scenes people.
Even during the concert...
Ferrari.
There was also this side of him.
Our live tour rainboW starts now!
Let me introduce one of our buddies!
Thank you!
June.
This is the last day of their tour.
The Kumamoto concert.
JUNE 20
GRANDMESSE KUMAMOTO
"OMOI, FUWARI"
However, performing in both
concerts and a drama
took a toll on Hamada's body.
-Is it bad?
-Yeah.
You should tell them
you strained your back.
If you're going to say it, say so now.
"I'm sorry for worrying you. I'm okay."
You should tell them yourself.
They must have realized,
so you should tell them.
-Go out there and tell them.
-Yeah, I agree.
Hamada strained his back
in the middle of the concert.
He's not here, is he?
He somehow managed
to pull his part off.
I'm so embarassed.
But the next day,
he was back to his drama.
JUNE 21ST
BUSHI-STANT AISAKAKUN! FILMING
I wanted to see happy faces of people...
Okay.
-That's good.
-Okay.
We're changing up the setting
so please vacate for now.
Okay.
Thank you for helping me up.
One, two.
There you go.
Thank you.
I strained my back yesterday.
Yeah, it was fun.
But I'm like, "Why now?"
It was a witch's shot.
Everyone's been helping me out.
I'm so grateful.
I'm sorry, I strained my back...
Oh really?
So just lift it up slowly...
-I didn't know that.
-Yep.
Okay, everyone,
please stop what you're doing.
Staff members, please come here.
I strained my back,
so I think they're discussing
whether or not to film tomorrow.
I can't believe this is happening now.
Seriously.
Right before Hamada arrived
on location, he was with Shigeoka.
JOHNNY'S WEST
DAIKI SHIGEOKA (29)
I was on the same plane
going back with Hama-chan.
I remember it vividly.
He got in the manager's car.
I told him,
"Good luck with the drama."
Then the window of the car rolled down
and he said to me,
"I shall be back!" and left.
Things like that.
I couldn't say something like that.
I'd probably be a little sad.
Filming a drama with a bad back
on a very tough schedule.
I'd probably sulk a little
and be moody because I'd feel restricted.
I'd definitely feel nervous.
Despite all that, Hama-chan said,
"I shall be back!"
as if nothing was wrong.
I've gotten to know
such an awesome guy.
That's what I seriously thought to myself.
I have no problems
introducing Hama-chan to other people.
Of course,
I could introduce the others too.
But Hamada is special.
It's like reading through sayings
and famous quotes.
What's the one I like?
"People who laugh during tough times
are the strongest."
It's this quote.
It's like...
People who laugh
even though they're mad
are stronger
than those who just get mad.
It's okay to cry when you're sad,
but I read that people who laugh when
they're sad are so much stronger.
I think that's how
I developed my own habits.
And there's also this man who
takes care of and fights for the group.
JULY
PHOTO STUDIO IN TOKYO
A photo studio in Tokyo in July.
There's one man here who
takes care of and fights for the group.
Aren't you cold?
JOHNNY'S WEST
NOZOMU KOTAKI (25)
PHOTOSHOOT FOR MAGAZINE FINEBOYS
This is a photo shoot for a magazine
for which Kotaki has been
an exclusive model for five years.
Yes, thank you.
To make it onto the green
in one shot in Kawagoe,
I'll need an eight or a nine...
Let's go with eight. An 8-iron, please!
Should I uncross my legs?
The other way...
Like this?
You want to see the sneakers, huh?
-It's not in frame.
-It's not?!
I really don't like doing things in a rush
or workplaces that are tense.
Everyone's having fun
chatting and working.
Having fun is what matters the most.
What matters most to Kotaki are
good relations with the staff.
This applies to other workplaces too.
Is that a tour T-shirt?
Yeah. A staff T-shirt?
We're working hard
together as a team.
And that includes the staff.
That's why...
I want to wear the same T-shirt
as everybody else during rehearsals.
I want to have fun during rehearsals too.
Behind the scenes during rehearsals,
he wears hoodies and T-shirts
meant for the staff.
In 2008, inspired by Hey! Say! JUMP's
Ryosuke Yamada,
Kotaki joined Johnny&Associates,Inc.
at the age of 12.
He was the youngest member in the group,
the only one to debut in his teens.
I'm always grateful
to the staff that supports us
and the all the fans
who cheer us on.
I'd like to repay everyone back.
Please continue to support us.
The way he thinks
is like a 35-year-old.
His thought process.
It's amazing.
TAKAHIRO HAMADA (32)
I think he's very mature.
Very sincere.
That level of sincerity
is pretty rare to see.
And he continues to grow.
Kotaki absorbs everything.
This power to absorb everything
has made him very successful as an actor.
Last year in October, he starred
in the play The Elephant Man.
SETAGAYA PUBLIC THEATRE
For this play, Kotaki...
BEST ACTOR & HARUKO SUGIMURA AWARD
I'm grateful to have had
the opportunity to play as Joseph Merrick.
And I'm thankful that
I was a part of this play.
Hello there.
Wow...
"Should I be here?"
That's what I'm wondering.
These people are
the cream of the crop.
They're really the people at the top
of the theater community.
And here I am. It felt quite strange.
And this year, Kotaki will be part of
Agatha Christie's original play,
The Witness for the Prosecution.
I will be part of this play.
Then...
I'm going to do my best to perform
so people compliment me
and can say that I was the best.
That's how I feel.
What does JOHNNY'S WEST mean to him?
I didn't feel helpless then
nor did I feel lonely.
But seeing them
after a long time was fun.
That's when I'll realize for
the first time, "This is what I wanted."
And the group begins
to move in a new direction.
Yay!
Hamada's back is now
thoroughly healed in July.
JULY
BUSHI-STANT AISAKAKUN! FILMING
Cut!
That's the end of this scene.
Okay.
-Oh?
-That means...
What does it mean?
-What does it mean?
-Sojiro Aisaka.
Mr. Takahiro Hamada.
Hey, hey!
You're done filming!
Good work.
Thank you very much.
Yeah!
The filming for the drama is now finished.
This was my first drama by myself.
We wouldn't have been able to film
such a good drama
without everyone's help.
I truly believe this.
I'm going to do my best to promote it!
There is one more piece
of good news about Hamada.
We're in charge of the theme songs
for the dramas we starred in.
It doesn't usually happen.
In the past, I would often ask,
"Can we have a tie-in with a song?"
They'd be like, "no, no tie-ins."
That's how it would be.
I'd always ask just in case.
I'm grateful.
Oh, that's great.
Hamada's not the only one.
Shigeoka is also starring in a drama.
JOHNNY'S WEST is in charge of
the theme songs for both dramas.
BUSHI-STANT AISAKAKUN! THEME SONG
"KIDOAIRAKU" MUSIC VIDEO
The theme song for Hamada's drama
is a high-energy track
that works well with comedy.
"Kidoairaku."
"KIDOAIRAKU"
On the other hand, in filming "Dekkai Ai,"
the theme song for Shigeoka's drama,
the group takes on
a certain new challenge.
"DEKKAI AI" MUSIC VIDEO
The whole thing will be
a bit mother-like.
You'll be doing the chores.
It's our first time doing this,
a music video where we don't sing.
It's the first time for our group.
We're all excited
and nervous while filming.
I have a question.
This is the setting, right?
The doors connect here
but they're different places.
-Yeah, it's all one house.
-Right?
Can we talk here?
Or is that not allowed?
Specifically speaking, it'd be interesting
if there was this kind of conversation.
Just sweep normally like this.
I got it.
Cut!
Sorry, that was an actual take.
-Was that an actual take?
-Yes.
-Sorry, I thought it was practice.
-Wow.
-Can we do it again?
Sorry, I should have been clearer.
No, it was our fault!
No, no, it's seven to three.
Who's seven? Which is seven?
I was looking elsewhere, wasn't I?
Shigeoka and I were looking
somewhere else.
Shigeoka stands out.
I wasn't looking at the right place.
-Shall we do this?
-Let's do it.
-Somebody should decide.
-Who?
The group's working hard
for this acting music video.
Then...
"DEKKAI AI"
I was a lot of different dramas.
Yeah, it was a lot of work.
But I think this song is
truly perfect for it.
I feel like this song somehow,
gives me courage in my life.
I hope that we'll be able to
grow with this song.
The seven lights
will continue to shine more brightly.
On the next RIDE ON TIME...
You surprised me.
I'll go in now.
Nakama takes on the challenge
of being on the news.
Also...
There's no Japanese translation for that.
Don't you know that?
Kiriyama challenges himself
in the theater as a chairman.
Here's what we discovered...
If things continue like this...
I honestly might think of
doing other work.
If Mr. Johnny said "No," I'd have quit.
Junta told me he would too.
We both said the same thing.
"If you're not here,
then I don't need to do this."
The strong emotions they don't show.
Smile!
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin