Hello. This is President Joshima.
TOKIO Inc. will partner up with businesses
to spread the concept of creating things
to all the people of Japan.
We are looking for partners
who will help us realize our vision.
They were serious
about starting a company.
FEBRUARY
As a promotion,
we're planning on releasing
this advertisement on April 1st.
I'm thinking that having an ad
in the Nikkei would be fun.
I think we should enjoy
the fun that the Nikkei has to offer.
We should have a one-page ad
because we're a company.
People will know us by releasing that ad.
We'll establish our company by
putting out a business card in the Nikkei.
Sweat.
Work.
Experience.
Days of realizing those passions
has now begun.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
TOKIO Inc.'s first project
began to turn its gears in April.
Good morning.
I'm Joshima, the president.
Nice to meet you.
Wow...
Creating things is
one of the company's philosophies.
Their first job is
teaming up with a national udon chain
to create new menu items.
You can put some sashimi on it too.
Thank you.
TOKIO Inc. developed ideas such as this.
As a parent, I'd want to put something
with more color in their meal.
It's an udon meal for children.
After much trial and error at home,
Matsuoka makes a new menu item,
curry udon that has tomatoes and eggs.
This is the menu for summer this year.
I'm so happy to hear that.
They're part of the whole process,
from beginning to end.
Yeah.
This is how TOKIO Inc. gets things done.
JUNE
YOKOHAMA
Thank you for the meal!
They're filming a commercial
for the children's udon meal.
That looks good.
How is it? Do you like it?
Tamagoyaki.
Yay! Cool...
You look cool, awesome.
One, two...
The wooden table in the commercial
was also built by the group.
So, how is it?
One week earlier.
Good morning. Nice to meet you.
KAWASAKI
Good morning. I look forward to today.
Good morning. Let's do some work today.
Was building this table
your idea, Mr. Kokubun?
Yes, it was.
For some reason, I just said...
"Let's try building a table."
When I said that,
the others were like,
"That's a good idea!"
After all, our company motto is
"Sweat, work, and experience."
That's why I decided to sweat and work.
Kokubun will build the tabletop.
It feels like I'm actually working.
I'm actually working.
The tree has curves here too.
Have there ever been any entertainers
that have built their own sets?
I feel a sense of attachment to it though.
I might get mad if the filming crew
accidentally bumped into this.
Like, "Cut that out!"
-Good morning.
Morning.
Any without cracks?
All of them have cracks...
Joshima works on the legs of the table.
I just want to clean it up.
This really shows your personality.
This is something you do quietly
but since we're on TV,
I have to say something.
That looks good. Thank you.
How about this part...
Very meticulous.
Matsuoka works on putting it together.
-All right.
-Okay.
I'm the one
that shouldn't be able to do this.
Yeah.
When it was the five of us,
I was the worst at this.
Now that there's only three of us,
so I have no choice.
Okay.
Okay. All right.
This is cute.
Wow. If you had more time...
It looks handmade. It looks good.
Yeah, this is cute.
Matsuoka sands the table,
so the children won't hurt themselves.
This is nice.
It's nice and round.
Where should we stamp the table?
The members
put their finishing touches on it.
Oh I see.
-Here I go.
-Right in the middle?
Good.
It's a bit diagonal.
That could look good.
I want to take a picture.
-Done.
-It worked!
-Cool.
-I did it. It worked.
This is a new TOKIO Inc. logo
they designed.
Please be ready to clap for me.
Here we go.
Congratulations.
Take a picture of me.
What are you taking pictures of?
You should be taking pictures of me.
I think it's ready.
Really?
Here!
It's barely on there!
Hey!
This is really bad.
Everything was going well
until now. Sorry.
Well, it actually has
its own flavor, so it's okay.
You can try another spot.
Yeah, I'll do it again.
I have no problem showing my mistakes.
This is a mistake.
This one has a lot more smoke coming out.
-I think it's ready.
-No, no, no...
Here!
See? It's perfect.
There it is!
I'm relieved.
This looks very cool.
Good.
A table of success born from a mistake.
During this time,
Kokubun was working at TOKIO Inc.,
while writing new songs.
In charge of his own group,
he works on a big
music TV program's opening theme song.
When I feel the creative juices flowing,
I'll bring a MIDI keyboard with me.
I'll do this when I have some time.
I do like to create things.
No matter how I look at it.
No matter how I look at it,
I love creating things.
It just pops in my mind.
Those sorts of ideas
that make things interesting.
That's why I do things
I'm not even asked to do.
It's like...
I'm showing proof
I'm participating in something.
Yeah.
I guess I feel strongly about that.
Rehearsal Day.
JUNE
TOKYO, TENNOZU
Good morning. I look forward to today.
Good morning.
Thanks for coming.
Thank you.
It's been a long time
since I've done something like this.
Due to COVID-19,
Kokubun hasn't been able to meet
his band members until today.
It's been a while. Thank you for coming.
Have you been busy?
No, I'm completely free.
-Really?
-Yeah, it's really bad.
It can't be that bad...
What about concert tours?
-Those dried up.
-Really? That's too bad.
That's why I focus on
composing music right now.
I compose just a few songs as a hobby.
Sometimes I'm able to complete them.
Then that's a good thing.
I teach music too.
I see.
I never thought it'd turn out like this.
-I know what you mean.
-Yeah.
Kokubun understands the lives of
his band members as if they were family.
I was so happy too.
Excuse me.
I look forward to working with you.
Hello, may I introduce myself?
I'm Taichi Kokubun. We established
TOKIO Inc. in April of this year.
Nice to meet you.
I've been thinking about the band name.
It's a bit long,
but it means
"make use of an opportunity immediately."
That's what it means if you rephrase it.
My interpretation of it is
"create something out of your passions."
And that's why I created this band.
Thank you.
That's nice.
So cool.
Awesome.
Could the people in the brass section...
dance or anything like that?
Can the guitars do like...
"I thought the guitars would be rock-like,
but it unexpectedly sounds like..."
That's the way I'd like it to be.
Just really that kind of mood.
That looks cool.
It's really cool.
He also designed the logo for the band.
I won't fit a medium...
That looks good on you.
Thank you.
That looks cool. You look like a DJ.
Totally a DJ.
Six minutes left!
Are there any staff members
without anything to do?
Please raise the roof.
Yay!
If you do, it'll energize the people here.
Okay!
Thank you.
TOKIO was formed back in 1990.
At the time, the group consisted of
Kokubun, Joshima and Matsuoka only.
Strangely enough,
the exact same members now.
HELLO, THIS IS TOKIO!
Living together at a boardinghouse,
they focused on their CD debut.
Their dream came true four years later.
But it wasn't smooth sailing
from the beginning.
We wanted to get first place
right after we debuted.
When you debut in Johnny's,
you usually get first place.
Most artists will usually get first place.
That's how I thought it would be for us.
There were younger artists that
debuted after us, like Kinki Kids and V6.
And they all got first place
like it was nothing.
The group decided to stick to
their own way of doing things.
They didn't wear
colorful clothing meant for pop idols,
but wore T-shirts
or nothing at all at times.
They've always shown
their true selves this whole time.
We were almost naked.
I always thought
we should cover up a little more.
When we were younger...
We wore the colorful clothing
young idols wear now.
But along the way,
we stopped wearing that kind of clothing.
The opening starts
with something like this...
LEVECHI NA HITO, MITSUKETA FILMING
After his idol days,
he worked as a presenter on TV.
No matter what genre.
He carved out his own career path.
DANSHI GOHAN FILMING
That's good.
KOKUBUN TAICHI NO OKIRAKU SANPO
~HAPPY GO LUCK~ FILMING
Kokubun has a record
number of TV appearances,
topping first place six years in a row.
TOKIO TERRACE FILMING
Nothing comes to mind using this.
I can't imagine coming up
with ideas while using this.
August.
Can I get in the car?
Yes, please.
Am I riding in this one?
Excuse me.
Kokubun was put in charge of
a cheerleading team for the Tokyo Olympics
by a certain television station.
While gathering information
on the athletes,
he also learned a few things
he could apply to his own work.
The beauty of sports
isn't just about the medals.
It's the process.
The beauty of the process
of getting to this point.
That's what moves me.
I believe the process
is extremely important.
That's what makes it easy for me
to give it my best at whatever I do.
I believe it's important
to be inspired by other people.
Good work.
I look forward to it.
Yes, thank you.
JUNE WANGAN STUDIO
On this day,
a meeting that would predict
the future of TOKIO Inc. took place.
We'll do everything here.
Here?
Yes. We'll take it here first.
Thank you.
TOKIO Inc. is starting a project to create
things by partnering with organizations.
There were many applications.
Wow. Look at all these applications.
There's so many of them, I'm so grateful.
They had more applications
than anticipated.
Start with number one.
Oh, from the bottom.
We'd like you to narrow it down
to 10 to 15 companies.
Please start choosing ones
that interest you.
I'll take a close look on my own.
Yeah, I agree.
I'd like to take my time to look at these.
If you see something...
Something we like...
And you need more information,
please tell me what number
and I'll send you their information.
So please let me know.
Even while working on other projects,
they take their time
looking at each proposal.
With all these people joining us
and working together to create something...
I feel like there's a vision.
I feel closer to them.
It's the idea of pursuing one thing
and creating something from scratch.
It feels like
there's a deep meaning to it all.
There's a memory
that Joshima will never forget.
It happened 29 years ago.
It was before TOKIO debuted
with their first CD.
AUGUST 28
HARAJUKU
When was the last time
I walked down this road?
It's the same.
It was their first handshake event
which took place in this
Johnny's Shop in Harajuku.
It's exactly the same as before.
Wow.
Before we debuted as TOKIO,
we had a handshaking event here.
We wanted to raise our recognition
and see if there were any fans.
"How many people could we attract?"
All of us were so excited.
Our boardinghouse wasn't too far
from here.
We were curious.
"It would be amazing
if there was a line here."
We peeked outside the window
and saw there was a little bit of a line.
"What is that?"
"What do we do if it's for us?"
When we came, it was for us.
The fans were lining up.
They saw us and were like, "Wow!"
It's one memory I have
seeing them through the window.
It was very touching.
That brings back memories.
Wow...
In that way...
They're emotions I can't let go of
in the history of TOKIO...
This place is a holy ground for us.
Yeah.
I'm so grateful to all the fans.
That made me really happy.
The joy of creating something
with someone left a mark in his heart.
They're now working on a photoshoot
to promote the udon chain restaurant.
Don't pan the camera.
Yes, thank you.
I don't...
I don't usually get embarassed.
But these make me so embarassed.
-Sorry.
-Seriously...
Yeah, that looks good.
During this photoshoot,
there was one member
who did exactly what the cameraman said.
It was Matsuoka.
After that...
Okay, I got it.
Smile like you're sending
a message to the children.
That's great. Perfect.
"Let's do our best!" "Be healthy!"
That's wonderful.
What memories
have left an impression on Matsuoka?
Nice.
-It's okay, you can sit there.
-Thank you.
Next time, the one side of Matsuoka
that we don't know.
"If I can hold my breath
until I get out of this tunnel,
I'll make it into Johnny's."
I did that a lot.
Of course. Very much a coward.
I'm like a Pomeranian.
Well... If left alone, I would die.
He's strict yet nice.
If I brought your family here,
your dad points would go up.
What am I saying on this program?
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin