2021.
JOHNNY'S WEST has completed
a three-month tour.
What's that, Haru? Let's check it out.
What? Where?
This fall, the seven members
are busy with personal projects.
They're walking toward their future.
Everything's good experience.
Let's sing.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
2022 CONCERTS MEETING
September.
The group is having a meeting about
their important concerts.
This might be the case
and I'm not sure about it yet,
but the new sets they're making
may be built so that
we can get closer to the audience.
No one has used sets like these before.
Being close to us while we're performing
is one of the audience's real thrills.
If we can develop our own style for this,
it would be a big draw for us.
If all seven of us could do that on stage.
That's something I'd like to do.
Something like that.
There's still a lot to look forward to.
The end of this year is full of
things to think about for 2022.
Gotta push a bit further.
So viewers, now's the time
to invest in us.
Now is the time. Right now.
We're heading on up.
They'll be like, "We should have
cheered for JOHNNY'S WEST more back then."
Don't say that.
So says the center of the group, Shigeoka.
It was a year filled with big challenges.
During the performance Shigeoka...
March of this year.
I'll do my best.
I'll really try.
This rehearsal is for a concert
starting in April
which celebrates
their seventh anniversary.
Let's do it again.
At this concert, all seven members
will perform solo songs.
It went down as I sang.
Shigeoka wrote a song
in gratitude of his now-retired father.
"SARARIIMAN NO TOUSAN"
He was transferred to Tokyo this April
and was working there alone.
Since he's coming back to Hyogo,
I thought the timing was right.
Shigeoka joined the agency in 2006.
At the time everyone was happy
for him, except his father.
My father wasn't really interested
in the entertainment business.
He's only been to one of my concerts.
My father's the silent type.
He basically lives to work.
When it came to family, my mother
was the one who tried hard.
Yeah, but my father really did work hard
at his job for us.
I'm afraid to get into a fight with him.
I see.
How should I put this?
I can't disobey him.
I wanted to invite him
to a concert in Osaka.
I don't think he knows
what I'm planning for him.
I'm already 28 years old and
being a good son seems easy
but it's actually quite hard.
That's why I wanted to try this.
-Shall we try it?
-What?
-Let's do it.
CONCERT REHEARSAL
Shigeoka's a passionate man.
For a dummy like him
to have created that song,
I couldn't believe it.
I told him he'd need a ghostwriter.
HE'S NOT NUMBER ONE IN THE WORLD
NOR IS HE RICH
SUPERMAN CAN'T BEAT HIM
MY SALARYMAN FATHER
HE HELD ME IN HIS ARMS WHEN I WAS A BABY
I THINK OF YOU FROM THEN
He's the only one who can be
the center of the group.
I think he's a center that rocks.
Shigeoka often plays around
with me, Junta or Akito.
He only treats Kamiyama differently.
It seems he's still afraid of him.
Maybe he still has memories
of Kamiyama's scary side.
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA
Right now, Shigeoka and I are creating
a lot of songs.
The way we create songs
is completely different.
I do enjoy the music
that Shigeoka creates.
Yeah, I think they're great songs...
"MACHIGACCHAINAI"
LYRICS AND COMPOSITION: DAIKI SHIGEOKA
OSAKA-JO HALL
The concert Shigeoka invited his father to
was to be held in Osaka,
the fourth venue of the tour.
However, the Osaka performance
had to be canceled.
MAY 2-5 PERFORMANCE
I'm feeling a little bit gloomy about it.
I mean...
I can't just say,
"Watch me from the living room.
I'm going to sing now."
It has to be done on stage.
He's never been interested in my work.
He's only cared about his own.
And then he retires.
I think he feels things
differently than me.
"Oh, my son's doing this kind of work."
Every opportunity is important.
Today's gonna be fun too.
He wants to show his father
that he's grown.
And this summer, while facing
his feelings about his father,
things take a mysterious turn.
Good morning.
Morning. Good morning.
Shigeoka is selected to play the lead role
in a drama on Friday nights at 10 p.m.
Congrats.
You're a fully-fledged illustrator now.
Not yet.
The fact that it's here
means it's not selling.
I'll sell them for you. Leave it to me.
It so happens that Shigeoka plays
a father raising his son.
Too bad there aren't any grasshoppers.
Do you like them?
No?
-I've never seen one.
-You haven't?
No way.
-I'm not lying.
-Yes you are.
You lie!
You're lying.
This is his first role as a father.
Touch it.
Don't worry. Pill bugs are harmless.
In both his drama and concerts,
he faces the idea of fatherhood.
I try to talk with him
even when the cameras aren't rolling.
I'm not doing it for the role though.
Haru is just so cute.
-You're really like a father.
-Yay! Alright!
Haru is really cute.
We catch grasshoppers and take pictures.
Your aura's different when you're alone
versus when you're with the group.
I'm doing well, right?
This is probably how I usually act.
He's definitely lying.
Why's he lying like that?
That's scary.
He says of himself,
"I'm a lion at home and a mouse abroad."
No one reacts to him
so he usually doesn't play stupid.
He says he's afraid to.
So he behaves wildly in dramas,
especially toward the group.
He'll pretend he's stupid
and then fall asleep.
I'm sure he's very tired.
We just watch over him.
JUNE
"KIDOAIRAKU" MUSIC VIDEO FILMING
Hello I'm Junta Nakama's mother.
I'm his father.
We started a YouTube channel.
Please subscribe!
I'm really sorry.
-Oh well.
-Yeah, oh well.
Don't be too sad.
Don't touch me.
Seriously.
FRIDAY DRAMA
There will be a time
when Shigeoka's wishes come true.
June 20th. The Kumamoto performance.
GRANDMESSE KUMAMOTO
The last day of the tour.
Mr. Shigeoka's arriving.
-Fist bump me.
-Ah...
Thank you.
Let's do this.
He was able to invite his father.
It's finally happening.
Finally.
I'm so happy that he's here today
and I'm able to do this.
It's Father's Day.
The curtain has been raised.
It's almost time for his solo.
I'm going on.
-Break a leg!
-Yeah.
Why don't you just tell
your father you're grateful?
I'll be back, you rascal.
All right.
Here I go.
Shigeoka shows
how much he's grown to his father.
"Dear father,
thank you for
your long, hard work as a salaryman."
"You are the backbone of the family
and have kept us all happy."
"You worked hard as a salaryman,
right up to the very end."
"I'm so proud of you for that."
"Back in the day, you didn't like singing
but I practiced at home anyways."
"It must have been noisy."
"Thank you for not complaining
and letting me sing."
"Thanks to you, singing has become
my purpose in life."
"Sarariiman No Tousan."
LYRICS AND COMPOSITION: DAIKI SHIGEOKA
SMILES AND SIGHS
INTERMINGLE AT A RECENT BIRTHDAY
EVEN A DENTED CAN OF COFFEE
HAS TO KEEP ITS SHAPE
WHEN IT'S EMPTY
Isn't it great?
It makes me want to cry.
It's a good song.
A TATTERED OLD CELL PHONE
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING
A GENIUS AT MAKING MOM MAD, MY FATHER
FROM BIRTH TILL DEATH
I AM ALWAYS YOUR SON
YOU MADE ME WEAR A RED JAPANESE VEST
EMBARRASSED, I LAUGHED
I WAS ALWAYS CHASING AFTER YOU
FOR YEARS AND DECADES,
YOU WENT TO WORK AT THE OFFICE
YOU MADE SURE WE WERE ALL HAPPY
MY SALARYMAN FATHER
MY FATHER I LOOK UP TO
I LOVE YOU FATHER
Yeah!
Nice!
I did it.
I somehow did it without crying.
-Fifteen seconds left.
-Huh?
Fifteen seconds.
All right.
Thank you mom and dad. Thank you!
-Thank you everyone!
-See you later!
The curtains have closed on the tour.
I think my family
won't forget about today either.
I think he'll always be able to say,
"That was a great performance you gave
on Father's Day of 2021."
Yeah, I think I was a good son today.
Their personal projects result in
good things for the whole group this fall.
Osaka.
There's a job
that supports Shigeoka right now.
This is Hyodo.
Don't call me Hyodo.
He's my friend.
Shigeoka. He's my friend.
FILMING
In 2013, when Shigeoka was still a junior,
he took over a program
from KanJani8's Murakami as a regular.
Right at the time I was set to take over
I was feeling very discouraged.
This job saved me
and so I feel truly grateful for it.
And I've always felt that way.
Their personal projects result in
good things for the whole group this fall.
Welcome to JOHNNY'S WEST's show!
Yay!
SEPTEMBER
RIATOTSU WEST
Their namesake program went
from local to national television.
That's too much explaining!
I never thought this show
we put so much effort into
would go national so quickly...
Yeah, I know...
It appears on the schedule.
Things like, "You'll get dirty,"
or, "You'll get wet."
Isn't this the worst?
"Please bring spare underwear."
-Ah.
-Yeah.
That was always the case.
So one time on the schedule it said,
"You won't get dirty or wet."
Then don't write it.
Do other TV programs do that?
"Eejanaika!"
Yokohama, you're the last show!
Let's hit it out of the ballpark!
Let's go! Yeah!
2014.
These seven debuted from Kansai.
All right!
ALL SEVEN MEMBERS HAVE FULFILLING
PROJECTS ON THEIR SEVENTH ANNIVERSARY
The winds that have started blowing,
will get stronger over time.
I do wonder what it is that we can do?
It is a work of art
that allows us to raise this question.
The important lines
and the stimulating lines too.
I hope that my acting will be easy
to digest for the audience.
That would be great.
RYUSEI FUJII
FIRST-TIME STAGE READING
Without actually reading the script,
I was acting in some scenes.
That's why it was difficult.
I think I'll be able to grow one step
at a time. Like self-expression.
Thank you, thank you!
SEPTEMBER, FILMING ENDS
FOR DRAMA #KAZOKU BOSHU SHIMASU
Haru, give me a hug. Come closer.
We'll meet again. I'll do my best.
I love you Haru. Thank you.
MEETING
And here they are,
preparing for the 2022 concerts.
Hitting the ground running.
My favorite part is when we're having
concerts together as JOHNNY'S WEST.
It's our reason for living.
It's where we started.
It's what we should be doing.
Without our audience,
it's like we don't exist.
We want to hit the ground running,
once there's a green light.
It's a lively place.
It's lively but for us,
it's also somewhere we live.
That liveliness lets us
express our talents.
It's a place that gives us life
and lets us survive.
It's not usually the case that something
would fit so well like these concerts.
I look at everyone during them.
It's because of us
and this place that we're able to show
our talents and charms.
I strongly feel this way.
At first, I didn't understand
what Shigeoka would say sometimes.
He'd say, "Whaa!"
Then I would just laugh
because he was hilarious.
Then everybody in the group
would start laughing,
and the fans would laugh with us too.
We're doing all this
in such a happy atmosphere.
I think I know the things that only
JOHNNY'S WEST can do or show.
It's just a matter of doing more of it.
I'd love to show that to our audience.
I hope they can see it.
"JOHNNY'S WEST is awesome."
I want them to say that.
Hey! Let's have some fun
starting from noon!
On the next RIDE ON TIME...
It's better to do it and regret
than regret not doing it.
It's their 27th-year challenge
since their debut.
TOKIO Inc.
Overcoming some rough waves,
these three challenge themselves
to the group's new format.
It's one or the other.
We do or we don't.
We've made it this far
with all these failures.
In the end, I hope people enjoy it though.
It's like we're going in circles.
TOKIO's now going for it.
97 years old.
TOKIO INC. BEGINS NOW
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin