It's been seven years since their debut.
JOHNNY'S WEST.
They haven't lost to the pandemic,
looking only towards their future...
Okay!
Midori, Haru, look over here.
DAIKI SHIGEOKA (29)
JOHNNY'S WEST
TAKAHIRO HAMADA (32)
DRAMA BUSHI-STANT AISAKA-KUN!
Acting in dramas.
You gotta be kidding me!
How can we let someone like that in?
JOHNNY'S WEST
TOMOHIRO KAMIYAMA (28)
PLAY LUNGS PAMPHLET PHOTOSHOOT
And theater.
JOHNNY'S WEST
RYUSEI FUJII (28)
NOZOMU KOTAKI (25)
PLAY THE ELEPHANT MAN
And quiz shows.
Everyone's busy with their own work.
It's an active year.
JOHNNY'S WEST
JUNTA NAKAMA (34)
We stayed with them for seven months.
All right, yeah!
I thought about a lot of things.
"If things continue like this...
I honestly might think of
doing other work."
If Mr. Johnny said "No," I'd have quit.
Junta told me he would too.
We both said the same thing.
"If Junta's not here,
then I don't need to do this."
Smile!
Smile
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
July.
The leaders of the group
are challenging themselves
with personal projects.
I did it! I won.
I was wiped out in the first round.
Junta Nakama.
-Junta Nakama!
-Oh yeah! Yay!
He's the oldest member in the group.
And since April this year,
Nakama's received many offers
to be on quiz shows.
The results depend on
how much I study every day.
When I first participated on Toudaiou,
I didn't know anything.
After I started joining these shows,
I've started watching the news.
Then I thought,
"Oh, I might be able to do this."
I am able to see different view points.
That sometimes happens
when I'm on the shows.
We had Nakama show us his study notes.
The miscellaneous trivia he looked up...
These famous historical figures
have interesting stories.
It's quite fun to look them up.
I'm studying more now
than when I was a student.
I made a promise about university
with my mom.
"If you're entering Johnny's,
go to university first."
She made me promise I'd graduate first.
I didn't like studying back then.
All right!
For Nakama to join quiz shows,
he had to think a little differently.
I think quiz shows are
what makes me unique in the group.
The other members,
they're all interested in acting.
If we all did that,
it would be pretty crowded.
So I decided that I would challenge myself
and do something unique to me.
I've set myself apart completely.
NOZOMU KOTAKI (25)
He's got a lot to compute in his mind
since he's the leader too.
And...
He's usually in control too.
It's not like he can do
whatever he wants though.
I think that's why
he's in these quiz shows.
When he does well on them,
he looks very satisfied.
I'm sure he has a lot of fun then.
JUNTA NAKAMA (12 YEARS OLD)
Nakama was first interested in Johnny's
when he was 12 years old.
When I was in fourth grade,
I went to Taiwan because of my dad's job.
It was around the time
I was in sixth grade,
that KinKi Kids had
their first concert in Taiwan.
Johnny's was having auditions
for Taiwan Jr.
Back then the only thing I did was play.
I wasn't good at school or sports
and I had no hobbies.
My parents were really worried.
They wanted to do something for me.
That's when my mom
found the audition notice.
So I went.
I got into Taiwan Jr.
and stood up on stage for the first time.
It was so fun and that was the start.
When I first met Junta
I thought to myself,
"Who is this dude? He's so cool."
He was a bit clumsy though.
He's smart but
since he was raised overseas,
it seemed like he wasn't used to Japan.
It was very curious.
His intuition's foreign
but he's speaking Japanese.
Junta's got a creative power
that I think none of us,
including me, have.
It's amazing.
SEPTEMBER
OSAKA
The beginning of September, Osaka.
Using his individual charm,
Nakama was working on something.
Good morning.
You surprised me.
I'll go in now.
Mainly broadcasted in Kansai, this is
a live morning news information program.
Five seconds before start, four, three...
Okay Nakama...
Nakama acts as a commentator
on various news topics.
He talks about his own opinions here.
I've been wondering why
America withdrew its troops so suddenly.
How should I put this?
Being allowed to do a job where I can
express myself makes me really happy.
It includes this program
and the quiz shows.
I think it's mainly because
I was raised overseas.
I'm pretty straightfoward.
Being polite is important but at times
it makes it hard to see the truth.
I'm the type of person
who's pretty straightforward.
That's why I prepare,
research, and then comment.
If I say something unnecessary,
it'll cause problems for the group.
But it's only recently that Nakama has
been feeling positive about the group.
For the first five years after I debuted
It felt like we were calm at sea.
No tailwinds or headwinds.
The public didn't really know
about JOHNNY'S WEST.
I thought about a lot of things.
"If things continue like this...
I honestly might think of
doing other work."
Yeah.
Like retiring from the entertainment
industry, and do what I love.
I like fashion,
so something related to fashion.
A friend of mine has a shop.
I'd love to help out at that shop.
That's why I'm glad
that the group gets along.
Because we do it's always
fun to see them and I can carry on.
In September, one member of the group
had his first day on stage in theater.
SEPTEMBER
TOKYO TATEMONO BRILLIA HALL
Columbus is Columbus.
There's no Japanese translation for that.
Don't you know that?
What did he do?
Akito Kiriyama.
PLAY AKA SHIRT
Sorry to keep ya waiting.
-No problem.
-Welcome home.
Yeah.
Kiriyama is acting as the main character
of the comedy, who wears a red shirt
originallyfrom
Natsume Soseki's novel Botchan.
He's also the chairman of the play.
The audience followed the infection
prevention rules while enjoying the play.
This allowed us to perform the play.
Their applause really hit me hard.
Especially this time,
I'm the chairman for this play,
so I have more responsibilities.
This time in particular,
Sexy Zone's So Matsushima's here too.
It was his first time doing theater.
So I want him to enjoy his time here
and find theater fun.
You made Madonna your wife
and now you want to make her a concubine?
That's just like you.
You're just like our dead father!
You idiot!
JOINED IN 2002
Kiriyama knocked on Johnny's door
when he was 12 years old.
I was already dancing in my hometown.
There was a guy two years older.
He went for an audition
three years before I joined.
That's when I discovered
the entertainment industry.
I wanted to dance and do similar things.
I wanted to work
in the entertainment industry.
That's what I wrote in the resume I sent.
But I was in my first year
of middle school at the time.
I had a mohawk and shaved my eyebrows.
I was a silly kid.
I guess that's exactly
what left an impression on Mr. Johnny.
He was touching my mohawk constantly.
It was spiky too.
"What's this hair of yours?"
"Nobody has a hairstyle
like this nowadays."
I don't know if he liked it or not.
I can never forget.
I thought it was scary. It was a mohawk.
TAKAHIRO HAMADA (32)
He didn't talk to me though.
But when I tried to talk to him,
he was surprisingly humble.
He said, "Nice to meet you!"
He's now that cheerful character
we all know.
"Nice to meet you! I'm Kiriyama! Yes!"
"Call me what you like! Please!"
He's like an older brother.
That's how I felt.
How should I put this?
He treated me like a younger brother.
Having older members like him around
made it easier for younger me
to go to the training hall alone.
I'm grateful for that.
For Kiriyama, the one who's been with him
the longest is Junta Nakama.
I think a year passed by then.
Junta joined Kansai Jr. and at a concert,
we were part of KanJani8's concerts.
We were in the elevator,
getting off the stage.
"You guys are B.A.D."
That means we're not good, right?
I had a mohawk then too...
I just let it go saying, "Oh yeah..."
"I guess you're right."
"Why are you telling me this in English?"
After that, Murakami the host
told us something.
"Will B.A.D. come over?"
"B.A.D. come over?"
"Oh didn't somebody
call us that in the elevator?"
Then's when I first knew.
"I guess we're a group now."
Just like this, in 2004
Kiriyama and Nakama formed the unit B.A.D.
Journeying together.
"AMEFURI → RAINBOW"
Since then for 17 years,
the two have been chasing
the same dream in JOHNNY'S WEST.
This is rare. Things usually change.
Junta's been with me this whole time.
When I was going to debut at Johnny's,
I went for direct talks.
I was talking to Junta
and said, "Let's go talk to Mr. Johnny."
If Mr. Johnny said "No," I'd have quit.
Junta told me he would too.
We said the same thing.
"If Junta's not here,
then I don't need to do this."
And Junta said, "If Akito's not here,
It would be nice to debut,
but if we couldn't,
we decided we would walk a different path.
That's what we told Mr. Johnny.
That's how close I am with Junta.
There's not many friends
who would do that for you.
We were so scared
when we told Mr. Johnny that.
Honestly speaking.
We had our reasons as to
why we wanted to debut.
So we explained everything
to Mr. Johnny from the start.
He told us no then.
But it wasn't really no.
He said, "You don't need to.
It's like you've already debuted."
"Two of you will fill up
Nissay Theatre for a month."
"You'll fill up Shochiku
for a month with an audience."
"You're already starring in dramas."
We realized then we were already working.
"Mr. Johnny's right..." We couldn't respond.
We told him we're grateful
and thankful for our situation.
And then the talks just ended
on that note.
The next day at 6 a.m.,
Mr. Johnny woke us up.
He said, "Wake up, wake up!"
"What's going on?"
"We got the recording company."
"Isn't it too early?
You told us we'd know at noon."
We got so many calls since morning.
The phone wouldn't stop ringing.
I guess it's because we
went to have direct talks with Mr. Johnny.
That's why we couldn't afford to fail.
This is why Kiriyama
continues to hold conviction.
This applies even for non-Johnny's work.
CONVICTION
Everything I do is for the group.
I'm seeing many people for the first time.
By seeing my performance,
I want them to think well of me.
If they do, they might look me up
and see that I'm from JOHNNY'S WEST.
Then they can try listening to our songs
or try going to our concerts.
This is my hope when I'm working solo.
Nakama feels the same way.
Seeing us in different places
will give us exposure to new audiences.
People will recognize us more.
People will get excited
when we're all together.
There are two members
playing the lead part in dramas.
In the same season too.
Three to four people
starring in theater plays.
And me, starring in quiz shows.
When we're on music shows,
people will realize we're a group.
"This guy and this guy
are in the same group."
That's the ideal.
It's like we're all Avengers.
That's the group we strive to be.
In all this, there's one member
who's been observing them all...
Is that what it is?
JOHNNY'S WEST members
have their own personal projects.
But this man misunderstood something.
No, I haven't gone to see it yet.
But of course I will go to watch it.
RYUSEI FUJII (28)
The group's most airheaded character.
Ryusei Fujii.
VS TAMASHI FILMING
We discovered something during a shoot
for a program Fujii's a regular in.
Kiriyama's play Aka Shirt.
Before Fujii goes to watch it,
there's something he's curious about.
I thought it looks interesting.
Kiriyama plays the Aka Shirt, right?
I see.
It's like the Aka Shirt has come to life.
It seems like Fujii thinks
Kiriyama is not playing a human,
but rather a red shirt.
Wait a moment!
When we tell him the truth...
Is that what it is?
The explanation was
"The Aka Shirt's point of view."
I was wondering what that was about.
I don't know anything about Botchan.
"The Aka Shirt's point of view."
Wouldn't you think it's a shirt?
How did the members
react to Fujii's misunderstanding?
I'm what? I'm playing a shirt?
I mean Akito you...
Botchan from the eyes of a shirt.
That's a new way to think about it.
I'm what? I'm playing a shirt?
I mean Akito you could be
hanging like this from a clothes hanger.
To be honest,
I'm not familiar with Botchan.
That's why I thought you were a shirt.
Simply genius.
A fight breaks out while you're talking.
Then the spotlight comes on.
This is a comedy skit.
"Oh, I should have done this back then."
What kind of play is this?
Hey...
ONE WEEK LATER
Fujii's really hilarious.
He's a genius.
He'll definitely stay
in the entertainment industry.
Seriously.
Today's Kiriyama is the host
for the recording of a variety show.
Thank you.
Laugh! Turn Table.
It's a two-hour special!
The show is mainly about
comedians performing songs.
Comedian Shinichi usually ends the show,
but this is a special collaboration
with JOHNNY'S WEST's Tomohiro Kamiyama.
I went to India for only a week
But my values have changed
A fellow group member Kamiyama
joins the show.
In addition...
Tonight we have Kogaken and JOHNNY'S
WEST's Junta Nakama for a special version!
Nakama joins too.
Glued to the television during work
The security officer
Doesn't notice the intruder
It was very fun.
There were quite a few
important guests there.
It's reassuring to know one of our members
can handle and do a good job
at entertaining them.
If people laugh,
that makes me the happiest.
Seeing Akito laugh makes me really happy.
Akito is in charge
of this show as a presenter.
I know he wants
the whole program to be lively.
Showing that JOHNNY'S WEST is
doing stuff like this too.
You can feel the love.
It feels reassuring.
I don't feel like I'm by myself.
This group is special.
They're like family, like brothers.
Like friends.
Like rivals.
These kinds of connections
just all seem to come up everywhere.
It's because they're
a part of JOHNNY'S WEST.
No matter where...
I think we'll be fine
as long as all seven of us are together.
"SILHOUETTE"
It finally feels like
the winds are blowing in our favor.
If we keep this up,
it looks like it'll be a fun life.
But we still have a long way to go.
It's still a long way.
On the next RIDE ON TIME,
You haven't?
This is the first time
Shigeoka's playing a father in a drama.
What does he think about his own father?
I wanted to invite him
to a concert in Osaka.
Being a good son seems easy
but it's actually quite hard.
Why don't you just
tell your father you're grateful?
I'll be back, you rascal.
And aiming for 2022,
JOHNNY'S WEST is not slowing down.
Welcome to JOHNNY'S WEST's show!
Yay!
Their futures...
Hey Kumamoto!
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin