Thank you.
I'm TOKIO Inc.'s president, Joshima.
Thank you for your card.
My name is Matsuoka.
Pleased to meet you.
If you get cold, you can burn my card.
TAICHI KOKUBUN
It's not a piece of firewood...
TOKIO, INC. VICE PRESIDENT
TAICHI KOKUBUN
TOKIO challenges themselves
to a new endeavor.
TOKIO, INC. PRESIDENT
SHIGERU JOSHIMA
TOKIO, INC. VICE PRESIDENT
MASAHIRO MATSUOKA
TOKIO Inc.
This is their motto.
Sweat and create things.
SWEAT, WORK, AND EXPERIENCE
We're making everything.
But isn't it amazing?
Business cards, signs, tables.
Oh yeah, we also made tables.
It looks like it will be beautiful.
It does.
New days of challenges have started.
This is documentary series, RIDE ON TIME.
Today they're in Fukushima Prefecture.
We're filming now.
How did you get here?
Due to a past segment on the TV program,
TOKIO has been involved
with Fukushima for over 20 years.
Could you please stand
and face the camera first?
Action!
Let's go.
-Okay!
-Yeah.
Okay.
Ever since the
Great East Japan Earthquake,
the group has supported
those working toward recovery.
The prefectural office even has
a division like this.
TOKIO DIVISION
Let's write our names later.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
I waved to somebody in that apartment
and they waved back to me.
It's looks really nice.
It might be the fanciest one here.
Yeah.
Matsuoka never forgets
to pay attention to his surroundings...
even during little moments like these.
It's an easy character to write
yet I can never write it nicely.
Here you go.
And today's the day
that really touched his heart.
GUNMA
TAKASAKI CITY THEATRE
Matsuoka is a big fan of this anime,
Tokyo Godfathers.
He plays the protagonist
in the theatrical version.
CREATED BY KON SATOSHI
Pardon the intrusion.
-Good morning.
-We look forward to filming today.
The character he plays is a
homeless person that was a drag queen.
Make up is everything.
It's everything for acting,
be it a period piece or cross-dressing.
Yeah, that surprised me.
-Oh really?
-Yes.
I do it all by myself.
-Seems like it.
-Yeah.
Period dramas have their own style.
Women have their own unique style too.
I see.
I learned that it's very tough
if you have somebody else do it for you.
Yeah.
The Kyoto staff as well as
the older actors taught me that.
When you're performing concerts as TOKIO,
do you do your own make up?
We're bare-faced for our concerts.
Yeah.
No one wears make up?
That's right, no one in TOKIO wears any.
At a concert?
-I didn't know that.
-Nope, not at all.
Nope.
-We don't have make up artists around.
-I've always wondered about that.
For programs on location
like THE TETSUWAN DASH
there may be some around
but they're for the other groups.
-I see.
-TOKIO doesn't have any.
I've always thought
idol groups would have them.
That's one thing that makes us different.
It's off because I was talking.
-Sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
I was the one talking.
-It's okay, you can sit there.
-Thank you.
Just then, Matsuoka...
North.
North is this way.
It's 15 to 20 minutes before the start.
The original creator of this work...
Mr. Kon.
Yes, Director Kon Satoshi.
He was originally from Hokkaido, like me.
I was originally a big fan of this work.
He was like a god to me.
That's why I prayed to him today.
I do it every time,
facing north.
Do you remember
the first time you made a prayer?
-A Prayer?
-Yes.
It was before I entered the industry.
Yeah.
Have you ever held your breath
while driving through a tunnel?
Maybe not anymore.
In the past we used to hold our breath.
"If I can hold my breath
until I get out of this tunnel,
I'll make it into Johnny's."
I did that a lot.
I did that for a good two years.
-Okay, I'll get going.
-Okay.
JULY
WANGAN STUDIO
The three members get together
to have another meeting.
Once I'm done here,
should I brush my teeth?
-Ah...
-Do you have any?
Yes.
Look at all these applications.
THE PREVIOUS MEETING
Applications with ideas for the
TOKIO Inc. collaboration project
have come flooding in.
Now they must find a partner
among those applications.
Take a look at this one again.
It's important to first read
everything thoroughly.
Yes.
The platform will be
chosen after this, correct?
These are the original plans, right?
Yes, they're all here.
It was then...
I have something I want to say
but I can't with the camera in our faces.
-May I?
-I'm sorry.
SHIGERU JOSHIMA
It's only been a short while
since they started their company.
They are discussing whether or not
they're rushing to make this decision.
-Sorry about that.
-No, I'm sorry.
Sorry for all this.
I apologize.
Yeah, it's no problem.
Mr. Yasuda was calling for you...
Oh did he? Is he here today?
What time will you be back?
1990.
When they formed TOKIO back then,
Matsuoka was only 13 years old.
It was a year after his wish
of joining the agency came true.
Is here okay? It's backlit.
-Wherever you'd like.
-Really?
To survive among the many would-be idols,
Matsuoka was desperate.
What should I do
to leave a strong impression?
Yeah.
What should I do so that
people remember me as TOKIO's Matsuoka?
I tried and did many things.
This is what happened.
Even though it was Johnny&Associates,Inc.
I wore sunglasses and spiked my hair.
People were thinking,
"Who the hell is that?"
But when that happened,
they actually remembered me.
It's a win for us if they remember us.
Have you ever been scared
you would be pressured to conform?
I'm the type to think,
"If you don't act, nothing will happen."
So I'll just have to be stronger then.
This is really embarrassing to say
but I'm a coward, so it hurts my feelings
when people look down on me.
That's the only reason.
I don't look down on anybody.
But I'm stupid and a coward.
It's just bad if somebody
looks down on me.
That's how I've dealt with it
this whole time.
Yeah.
Do you think yourself a coward?
Of course. Very much a coward.
I'm like a Pomeranian.
I'll bark, bark and bark.
I crave attention
so people know that I'm here.
Yeah.
Well... If left alone I would die.
TOKYO GODFATHERS
Matsuoka paved his own way
as an actor after that.
He has rules he set himself
when comes to acting on stage.
This is very brazen of me,
but I told myself I wouldn't do theater
until I became famous.
If they don't know who I am,
I don't want people coming.
I wouldn't like that.
Coming to see the play knowing who I am,
versus coming to see the play
without knowing me.
I won't go on stage
if I haven't made a name for myself.
I didn't want to become
an actor or a pop idol.
I wasn't the type of person
who wanted to succeed in music.
I wanted to become famous.
That's who I am.
Thank you so much. Sorry to bother you.
Thank you very much. Goodbye.
-I watched your drama.
-Thank you.
The one with the maid.
Ah, Mitazono. Thank you for watching.
You haven't changed at all.
Please wait a moment.
I have one Mitazono T-shirt left.
So here you go.
-We'll pay for it.
-No please don't.
Here you go.
I just ask that you don't sell it.
Please take it.
Thank you so much.
-Thank you again.
-Thank you for coming.
Goodbye.
JULY
SAITAMA
-Good morning.
-Hello.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Hello.
They're filming a commercial today.
Good morning.
COMMERCIAL FILMING FOR
TOMATO EGG CURRY UDON
The commercial is filmed on location.
The close-up camera doesn't capture
Matsuoka's expression well.
Action!
The director wants to talk to Matsuoka.
Take a look at this motorhome
since you're here.
Impressive ones like these are rare.
I only get to use this
because I'm filming.
-Excuse me.
-Come on in.
You can see the television over there.
There are lunch boxes here.
And in the back...
I believe this is
supposed to be the bedroom.
I think it was remodeled
and now it's a dressing room.
It'd be nice if you could
open these and see the sea.
I mean now it's just a highway in Saitama.
Matsuoka was kind to let the crew
film for the documentary.
I bet this motor home
uses up a lot of gas.
Would it be good to rent one?
There's a shower and also a toilet.
If you include this,
they'll think I'm always
looking in the mirror.
Yeah...
I mean this is the only place
where you can film me.
-Yes.
-Right.
Where would you choose to debut? Arashi?
I mean age-wise.
KanJani8 is definitely younger.
But close in age I think.
Yeah, Yoko is...
-A year younger.
-A year.
-Murakami too.
-I see.
Kohara was once
on the same path as Matsuoka
but is now working
at an advertising agency.
Coincidentally, he was
in charge of this commercial.
Why did you decide
to work for an advertising firm?
-Why an advertising firm?
-Wow...
This is like an interview.
It's good to see it from the outside.
Ah.
People who quit the industry
Be it actors or musicians
they're able to understand
how it feels to step away.
They can objectively see
what's not enough.
It's great if they come back.
If I tried to re-examine myself
there wouldn't be a place for me anymore.
I'll come running back.
Just a little.
For three days I'll be immersed in myself,
and by the fourth day
I'll contact the staff.
"So about the next drama..."
You'll say, "Can I come back?"
It's just a holiday.
Yeah.
What am I saying on this program?
Yeah, it's very important.
Don't take this for granted.
Who is this for?
Myself.
Are you ready?
-Yes.
-Okay, let's start.
Walking straight ahead
on the path he chose.
Taichi Kokubun's Radio Box.
"When I hit the accelerator,
my mouth goes, 'vroooom.'"
I haven't done this in a long time.
The vice president of TOKIO Inc.,
Kokubun, keeps getting busier by the day.
I might just do it now too.
Your bag looks heavy today too.
Yeah, this is today's load.
I have a lot of stuff in here.
There's documents for
the company and the Olympics.
Yeah.
-Good work.
Good work everyone.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Kokubun arrives at an event
held by an IT company.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
I'll take you to the waiting room.
Ever since they started the company,
there's two things Kokubun always carries.
Hello, excuse me.
-Thank you for the other day.
-Thank you. We met on the remote call.
The first thing is his business card.
The other is...
May I have this?
Which size would you like?
-This please.
-That one? Sure.
-I'll put it on my PC.
-Please do.
-Can I have one?
-Sure.
-May I have one?
-Of course.
-Can I have one more?
-Pardon me for being faddist.
Please excuse me.
What's important is that
people remember the TOKIO Inc. name.
I just made these stickers on my own.
Kokubun has plans with a friend tonight.
-Pardon the intrusion.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Hey there.
Sorry about this.
His best friend since his younger years,
Yoshihiko Inohara.
Inohara was the first person Kokubun told
about his idea of starting a company.
Yeah, my line of vision was like this.
Right? I knew you would remember.
Cheers.
-Long time no see.
-Same here.
They reminisce about their earlier years.
That tastes good.
Remember the baseball tournament?
All the main players
were trying to take a group photo.
The PR people were like,
"Please stand here."
"The center's so and so."
And every single time,
we were in the back just hanging out.
They took the picture
and I was laughing with this guy.
"We're the goldfish poop
of Johnny&Associates,Inc.
Always just clinging on."
We always laughed about it.
-That was the beginning.
-Yeah.
Taichi once told me something.
He said he found a way
to stay in the industry for a long time.
I asked him, "What? What's that?"
"Just cling on to somebody."
I said, "Oh, I see!"
That's what he said.
Thirty years have passed since then.
-From rehearsal...
-Yeah.
Inohara was worried about
the new first steps Kokubun took.
What did the other members say?
Not a lot of opportunities
come at the right time.
Let's go back and stand at the start line.
Show people our sweat,
blood and tears at our age.
It might...
be something that adds to our lives.
When I told them that,
they said, "That sounds interesting."
They understood what I was saying.
Yeah, I see...
You're always happy for me
when I'm on specials.
The three members realized something big
when they were in talks with each other.
I always thought I knew
what they wanted to say instinctively.
But if they hadn't told me,
I wouldn't have known.
I realized I didn't know
what they don't like,
or what they're thinking.
I won't know if they don't say it.
There's lots we don't know.
Yeah, exactly.
Even though you've
been with the group for 20 years...
Exactly. You'd think you knew.
That's why I thought I knew.
Right, right.
I realized we should vocalize some things.
I see.
Matsuoka said something very wise to me.
"Staying in the company
and trying to do something new.
That's what we should work on."
It's because of what he said
that I started to think deeper.
Staying in your comfort zone
while trying something new.
I think that's a valid way of life too.
I think it's a catalyst
to start thinking about things.
-Yeah, you're right.
-Yeah.
I don't think Mr. Johnny
would have ever imagined
you would actually
start a company named TOKIO Inc.
Yeah...
I believe he would have
left it in your hands,
and happily cheer you on as you
did something that he didn't envision.
I think he would say, "TOKIO is amazing."
-I hope so.
-I'm sure of it.
He would say, "I didn't think of that."
We're moving ahead but
we don't know if what we're doing is right
-It's fine if the outcome's good.
-Yeah.
Can I go pee? May I?
Shall I go too?
Let's go together.
Don't pee at the same time as me.
TWO MONTHS SINCE THE START OF THE COMPANY
During this time, President Joshima...
Two gyoza, please.
And can you replace
the white rice with red rice?
Now 50 years old, this is his first time
playing the protagonist in a drama.
He plays a mother
raising her adolescent son.
I brought your side dishes!
Don't come here for that.
Side dishes are an important part
of a lunch box.
To make the character come alive,
he recalls someone important to him.
On the next RIDE ON TIME,
the company president, Shigeru Joshima.
A 30 year journey that was supported
by memories not known to many.
I wanted to free myself
from everyday life.
If I jump into that spotlight,
my life will change.
Subtitle translation by:
Benj Soonthornwacharin