Now open your eyes wide.
Ready?
Okay, look straight into the camera.
They are filming footage
for a concert show.
Now dart your eyes around.
Miyacchi, you can move your mouth,
but keep your neck still
as much as possible.
Okay.
We're going to composite the footage
using different parts.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Kis-My-Ft2, Kis-My for short.
What are they striving for
as they enter their 10th anniversary?
What is something people aren't doing?
There's this mainstream line at Johnny's.
That's totally great.
But something outside that,
something that nobody has really done.
That might be something
we're looking into.
This is documentary series RIDE ON TIME.
Kis-My members have
rich solo careers as well.
Give them a nice pose there and...
TAISUKE FUJIGAYA
Taisuke Fujigaya is reprising
his role in the musical Don Juan
after a two year break.
REHEARSAL FOR DON JUAN
-Don Juan! Don Juan!
-Hey!
I'm not your friend.
Who do you think I am?
They were running through the final
dress rehearsal before their opening day.
Fujigaya was playing Don Juan,
the legendary playboy.
What were his thoughts on this play?
It's hard work.
I get pushed to the limit daily.
The way you project your voice
is totally different.
It's hard, I still can't do it.
I'm super popular
when it becomes break time.
The producers would come
and give me notes
on my singing and dancing.
They all just surround me.
And I'm just like, "Oh no..."
Really?
You know where you charge Rafael?
Your shoulder drops in this motion.
You want to keep the shoulder parallel.
Keep it...
He receives sword fighting direction.
The producer too.
PRODUCER
HIROKAZU IKUTA
This is the popularity Fujigaya
was referring to.
Rehearsal ran for 12 hours.
Excuse me.
My body's exhausted before opening day.
Feels more like mid-production exhaustion.
Fujigaya mostly keeps to himself.
When asked about their 10th anniversary,
he gave an unexpected answer.
With everything happening
with the anniversary,
it makes me wonder what being and idol is.
What kind of idol can I be?
You know, I'm searching for it.
I wonder what it is.
I've never had this before.
There's this new feeling
I've never had before.
What is it?
What is an idol?
Fujigaya took this musical as a challenge.
Let's go!
Yeah!
The curtains open.
You've gone too far this time.
Did you call me here just to tell me that?
MUSICAL DON JUAN
Including Tokyo and Osaka,
there were 32 performances
over a period of a month.
What did it feel like when you killed him?
Nothing.
FINAL SHOW
He had this to say at the end.
Some of you may be seeing me
for the first time.
I'm normally being an idol in Kis-My-Ft2.
So please come see us
if there's a show nearby.
We are a group of six charismatic guys.
If Don Juan leads to other
exciting experiences, then great.
I hope that as entertainment progresses,
it's able to bring you more happiness.
Sorry for the rambling.
It's what I believe.
I'm blessed. Thank you.
Yay!
Thanks!
Fujiyama continued forward
as he kept up his search.
Another member searching for something...
is Kento Senga, the member
in charge of choreography.
He's one of the highly skilled
dancers in Kis-My.
One and two and...
He is coming up with new choreography
for the song "Girl is mine"
for the upcoming arena tour.
I think the count is off.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, and three.
Four and five and six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
Thank you.
Senga doesn't compromise his dancing.
There is a reason behind his commitment.
We're all middle-aged,
with the youngest being 30.
We're gradually drifting away
from dancing.
You know,
people think it's because of our age
and that's kind of annoying.
So we want to show the fans
our continued evolution
and make them realize
that Kis-My is still cool.
So I tried to come up
with a new dance number
that is going to get them excited.
He's having trouble with the choreography.
I tried incorporating steps
which we haven't used very much,
into this new choreography.
It's pretty simple right now,
so it'll need more revisions.
Senga had another talent
the group acknowledged.
That talent is...
He started focusing on his artwork
a few years ago,
and continues to this day.
ARTIST: KENTO SENGA
He tells us how he started his artwork.
It was a way to relieve stress. You know?
It was basically my toilet.
It feels good to go to the bathroom.
When I create my art,
I empty my mind, and just draw freely.
I take my accumulated stress
and put it in my art.
So all my works are negative.
During their debut period,
Tamamori, Fujigaya, and Kitayama
were the main members of the group.
However, Yokoo, Senga, Miyata, and Nikaido
weren't in the same spotlight
as the three of them.
There was a distinct difference
within the group in terms of
the amount and type of work we got.
It was completely different.
And it wasn't divided equally.
"Why don't they give me
more parts to sing?"
"Why am I dancing in the corner,
when I'm good at it?"
I thought it was important
to find a place to vent.
That, for me, was art.
This isn't dark at all.
But to me...
After earning recognition
within the group,
he was put in charge
of Kis-My's concert logos,
giving him a strong, new weapon.
In these last ten years,
we spent so much time together,
and the more we spend together,
the group will only get more interesting,
and we'll become
even more complete as a unit.
The future of Kis-My
is something that looks very bright to me.
He finally found choreography
he's happy with.
So the hand and shoulder
should be the same direction.
And the opposite shoulder too.
Front, then step to the side.
Then...
-Back here?
-Yes.
Between rehearsals,
Hiromitsu Kitayama begins a meeting
with the staff.
Kitayama is directing the concert video
for their new song "Fear."
In the music video,
they did something new,
only using their facial expressions.
These are the storyboards of his idea.
However, Kitayama...
A meeting for the concert video.
When Kitayama looked at the storyboard...
Let's start here.
So my thoughts are,
instead of fading in from these trees,
it'd be more impactful
to just cut to the eyeballs.
-Impactful?
-Yes.
And maybe the trees
are reflected in the eyes,
or a butterfly, letting you know
that's the scene.
During the meeting,
Kitayama repeated himself.
So what I'm going for here
is something creepy.
I think it's creepier to be facing it.
I thought the mix would be creepy.
You mean...?
The actual measurements are a bit larger,
but having a big one mixed in
could be creepier.
"Creepy."
An image not often associated with idols.
The worst is if you don't leave
any impression either way.
But you know,
if there aren't any artistic qualities,
you just have to be cool
inside this neat and tight package.
So, it's about how artistic and cool
you can do it.
It's the day of the shoot.
Ready?
Okay, look straight into the camera.
Now open your eyes wide.
Nice and big.
They are cutting sections
from the member's faces,
to create a visual
they've never seen before.
Now dart your eyes around.
That won't move.
How does Kitayama feel about
their 10 year anniversary?
Personally, it's only been 10 years.
Although, it makes me think about
what we need to do
in order for us to continue
another 15 or 20 years.
I'd want to have the courage
to be able to change with the times,
to stay interesting.
But also we're originally...
a group created by Mr. Johnny.
So we need that passion
to never forget our roots.
Kis-My-Ft2 was formed in 2005.
It took six years
until they were able to debut.
Kitayama looks back at that time.
I never got an explanation
of why Mr. Johnny created this group,
or what he wanted us to be.
He never gave us a real explanation.
I was never told,
"You're here because of this!"
It all started with being told
to come over.
But there has to be some reason.
That's where we'll find some clues of
how we can reach the next level
as a group.
Kitayama had something he wanted to do.
It's open.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Excuse me. Hello.
I'm Kitayama. Nice to meet you.
Please come in.
He experiences a tea ceremony
for the first time.
First to prepare, go to the tokonoma.
He reads the hanging scroll
as he learns the proper etiquette.
TEA MASTER
MUNEKAZU AKIYAMA
Excuse us.
The first thing served wasn't tea,
but a traditional kaiseki meal.
Yes, then return the top one after.
-Like this?
-Then hand it to her.
So I do this first.
-Here you go.
-Wow.
Then rice wine.
This is called chaji,
the proper way to treat guests.
So you put it on top of the bigger bowl.
Put it on top.
Exactly.
Kaiseki meals
are meals served to complement the tea.
The sauce is very good.
Yes, delicious.
The mustard stings.
You have to mix it in!
I'm supposed to mix it?
Did you see the yellow stuff?
You have to mix that in.
I didn't know that.
Mix it in with the miso.
I thought I was supposed to eat it as is.
It's been two hours.
It's time for tea.
How is it?
You don't have to finish it all.
Wow.
He went into the tea ceremony searching
for something missing from himself.
What did he feel?
I thought that
this could be entertainment.
It wasn't like "Drink the tea!"
There are different varieties to enjoy,
and different preparations,
and different pots and cups.
I'm sure a lot goes into thinking
about making it entertaining.
My legs were dying, but they told me
I could sit comfortably.
I'm sure that's not actually okay.
Next time, Toshiya Miyata
works on his passion.
I love you.
I can't stop this feeling.
That's such a waste.
_I messed it up.
You forced it.
Yeah.
-I know you did.
-You got me.
Tamamori creates
the costumes for the tour.
However...
There's a chance we need to
rethink the shape for Gaya's.
We may need to do something.
Tamamori shares his true feelings.
We need to make it big.
Or there's no point.
What is his motivation?
Subtitle translation by:
Zensho Yamamoto