THE FUTURE OF NANIWA DANSHI
Today, they discussed their future.
Once the concert tour ends...
I don't know how we'll be,
but how do you wanna be?
Naniwa Danshi in the future.
I would like to create
a Johnny's boom again.
Ah...
I feel that
I want to be a hero to everyone.
A group to make people smile is nice.
Even after we make our debut,
I want to do things
nobody has done before.
Do things that surprise people.
Yeah.
Let's keep them surprised.
And so, their true feelings
began to flow out.
That's just it. Same with
Arashi's last live concert...
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
The group finally made their takeoff.
NOVEMBER 12, 2021
DEBUT
Let's try to line up closely on stage.
Yes, thank you.
You're going on. Now, please!
Wow, awesome!
The sea of media had been waiting for
the idols born from Kansai, Naniwa Danshi.
"UBU LOVE"
The group was formed in October, 2018.
Their debut.
The seven of them continued to chase
that dream beyond dreams.
THREE YEARS OF WORKING TOWARD THEIR DEBUT
How we grasp the chance,
how we win that over,
will be up to us.
But we've been doing this
believing that this day would come.
DEBUT CD SET FOR RELEASE!
There was even a member who had been
waiting 17 years for this moment.
Yes!
Hooray!
This is the path to their debut,
the time until they get on their feet.
March of last year,
the group was notified of some news.
MARCH 2021
Hi!
We're Naniwa Danshi!
Let's go!
Unbelievably, our nationwide tour
has been decided!
-Let's go!
-Thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
We'll visit Hokkaido up north
all the way to Fukuoka down south.
When they hadn't even heard
of any news on debuting yet,
their nationwide arena tour was decided.
Behind the scenes, one of their senior's
presence was always there.
He has been watching over them
since the group was formed.
Tadayoshi Ohkura of KanJani8.
He knew that this was an important time
for Naniwa Danshi
who was working toward their debut.
Oh, it's okay.
To be honest,
I already knew their debut was underway
when they decided on the concert.
I want them to be a Johnny's group
that will represent their generation.
It's not like they'll have
a producer forever.
So I wanted to give them a big test
and see how they do with it.
To shape up their qualities more
and to train them internally.
That was probably the test.
Yeah.
The stage direction was assigned for
the first time to the group's center role,
Daigo Nishihata.
NANIWA DANSHI
DAIGO NISHIHATA (24)
From that segment, the flow from the intro
will all be Naniwa's songs.
Okay.
And "Yobaiboshi"
will be the dance version this time.
Okay.
The dance just goes with it,
but the sound...
The sound doesn't change.
I'm super worried about this... layout.
If this layout with this set list was okay
is tormenting me now.
I'm like, "What do I do?"
Nishihata used to belong to
a different unit with Ren Nagase,
who is currently in King & Prince,
but that slowly came to an end.
DAIGO NISHIHATA
He was betting everything
on Naniwa Danshi as his last chance.
And there was another member
who held the same feelings
in his heart as Nishihata.
Ryusei Onishi, who was working
to become an idol since he was ten.
RYUSEI ONISHI (20)
For this tour, he is in charge
of the concert merchandise.
No, I just happened to be here.
This is a face mask charm.
Not many people wear charms,
so we can have everyone use them
for concerts or special occasions.
And days when they're not used,
I thought it might be cute
to put them on these small plushies.
So I'm testing them now.
I don't want to mess up.
Which one's cute?
The one who has performed
in many films and dramas,
Shunsuke Michieda.
NANIWA DANSHI
SHUNSUKE MICHIEDA (19)
Mr. Michieda,
that was so good to the point
where a snake and a mongoose
could probably become friends.
Your analogy. Your analogy is...
Despite his dreamy looks,
he has a very earnest character.
He always arrives first at the studio
for rehearsals, sweating away.
Thank you very much!
The one who supports the group
with his singing is Kyohei Takahashi.
NANIWA DANSHI
KYOHEI TAKAHASHI (21)
Let's stretch the end.
-Right, right. Let's go!
-Yes.
Right, right! That pitch!
After that pitch, continue naturally.
Was your voice that strong before?
Hasn't it become louder?
My volume?
Well, I do voice training after all.
Yes, so I was better
at those lower keys before,
but higher keys are easier now.
Really.
The costumes essential
to excite the concerts.
The one who was racking his brain
over those designs was Kento Nagao.
NANIWA DANSHI
KENTO NAGAO (19)
I thought we could wear a baseball shirt
with a baseball jacket over it.
When I told this to Jo.
He said,
"Anyone over No. 100 is a trainee."
"We're working towards our debut,
so we're the same,"
he says with his back toward me.
-How funny.
-Right?
He has an innocent and lovable character.
A big fan of baseball
and always wearing a baseball uniform
is the oldest member, Joichiro Fujiwara.
JOICHIRO FUJIWARA (25)
He joined the agency at eight years old,
but his peers outpassed him repeatedly.
He worked on making his debut
without giving up for 17 years.
If we do this at Miyagi
and at Yokohama Arena again...
During that time,
he has been polishing his comedy skills.
He writes the script
of the concert host's part too.
Do scissors...
Rock-paper-scissors!
If you win, bang. If you lose, no.
-Rock-paper-scissors!
-Bang!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Chuki.
-Wait, wait...
-What is that?
And the leader who loves to eat,
Kazuya Ohashi.
Yum!
Yum-yum!
Thank you!
He looks like a clown at first glance,
but in fact, he is the pillar that upholds
the Naniwa Danshi's music and dances.
That was great. Here we go. Um...
The firm determination
to survive in this world
has always encouraged the members.
Feels like I haven't been here in a while.
You can't try to have
a taste of normal life.
Not in this occupation.
So, I want to be a person who thinks,
"I hope everyone works hard,"
or "Let's work hard today."
It's not tough at all.
JUNE 27, 2021
The final rehearsal of the tour.
It is the day that determines
if their efforts pay off
for what they've built up
from March up to this day.
Eh, this is that thing!
Oh, that's awesome! So cool!
-Wow!
-I want this!
I want this! Just this!
-Everyone will get one.
-"Naniwa Danshi."
Uh, how's it look?
Oh, I'm sorry.
We win.
The sound of the drumsticks
will enter a bit...
The concert's main staff
have all gathered.
The timings of the actions
will be told through the mic.
Let's give it our best.
Let's give it our best!
All members exit the stage.
For this tour, including the encores,
they will sing over thirty songs.
The key to doing this is dressing quickly.
Ten sets of costumes were prepared.
This is where it comes out.
Okay, good work!
Good work everyone!
Timing-wise, it's perfectly two hours.
The problem seems to be the dressing time.
They will have to layer two costumes.
Their limit to dress here is two minutes.
You did it, a minute and fifty seconds.
No, I didn't.
Two minutes, two minutes passed.
I messed up the order.
Yeah, the shoes first was better.
-Right.
-Yeah.
And I spread the hakama too much.
We need to start thinking
that we may not make it in time.
Since we probably won't have time
to practice on site.
Most of these costumes weren't seen live,
so I want to show these new costumes...
As much as possible.
I do want to show them
as much as possible.
But there's no point if we can't make it.
That would be the worst-case scenario...
True.
What's important is trial and error while
compromising between ideals and reality.
We won't have time if we return here...
-At all?
-Not at all!
Near here, there's a stairway
to go under stage...
In the end, it was solved by shifting
the dressing area closer to the stage.
Except, these types of routes are showing.
And here...
It's the result of all seven's discussion.
Just when we were formed,
I don't think we were able
to freely speak our minds.
We blindly listened to the grown-ups
or to whatever the elders told us maybe.
But lately, even the younger members
give lots of feedback too.
It's very you know...
I can sense that they're talking honestly.
But I'm worried about that there.
Like how we're going to turn out.
Yeah.
What kind of...
group Naniwa Danshi wants to be.
They began to speak their minds.
I don't know how we'll be,
but how do you wanna be?
What kind of figure do you want to be?
What kind... of idol do you want to be?
It could be personally too.
If there's a personal future image
of Naniwa Danshi, I'd like to hear it.
The future of Naniwa Danshi.
Nishihata was the one to begin speaking
about his admirable seniors.
I grew up watching Arashi, so...
The image Arashi painted in my head
was really intense.
-Yeah.
-Like the image I had of them.
So that's why I want us
to become like that.
To become someone's help
and someone's support.
To become a figure
that could cheer people up like that.
So...
By Naniwa Danshi existing,
if more people could feel that way,
that would be nice.
A dome concert doesn't equal
a national idol.
-That's true.
-Right?
Not just because we reached a milestone...
Well...
In the entire Japanese audience,
I want us to be...
To be acknowledged as an idol group.
That's difficult.
-So our seniors are incredible.
-I don't understand!
What's the standard of a national idol?
I don't know what the standard is...
A group to make people smile is nice.
When Arashi goes to the country,
even grandmas would say,
"Oh, you're Arashi, aren't you?"
and comes up to them.
Like, they're smiling
just from meeting them.
A figure that everybody
recognizes in person,
who can make everyone smile,
is probably what a national idol is.
In my opinion, being able
to give everyone hope for tomorrow
or give energy to survive,
to motivate people,
to make people positive, are also factors.
To make people feel happy too.
If we can make each
and every person happy,
that's what a national idol
would be in my opinion.
Plus, in Naniwa Danshi's future,
I feel that
I want to be a hero to everyone.
So, although the place may be different,
or even if the occupation
may be different,
we want to become the hero of idols.
Mm.
In the future.
I would like to create
a Johnny's boom again.
Ah...
Currently, there's all kinds of idols
besides Johnny's,
so I wanna prove Johnny's great.
Because Johnny's is like
the pioneer of boy idol groups.
Johnny's is...
So we wanna become a group
that will live up to that.
Right.
And you, Takahashi?
I just wanna make people happy.
Well, that's vague, but important.
That's most important!
I want to be part of people's lives.
Oh!
Having people just see
our good side is you know...
Well, I understand. I get it.
That's what I value.
You grow thanks to
these people who scold you.
They help you notice things.
Some say, "Naniwa Danshi again?"
These words may hurt a bit, but...
That just depends.
If you think
that's how much they watch us...
That's a compliment.
You know, since our Johnny's Jr. days,
we've been doing a lot
of unexplored things.
The Koshien tournament
and commercials too.
Even after we make our debut,
I want to do things
nobody has done before.
From here on too.
Do things that surprise people.
Yeah.
Arashi and SMAP probably
went through a stormy path.
We shouldn't just trace that path,
we need to make a Naniwa Danshi path.
And like, live every moment
of our own lives.
Well, this...
Not knowing the future yet
means that we really don't know
our potential, right?
So if we can enhance
our potential further...
I think everything ends
once we realize our possibilities.
I want to continue being in a state
of not knowing our potential.
It's scary, but it's more fun that way.
I don't know how we'll be...
But I really want Naniwa Danshi
to become an idol
that could represent Japan.
We've never had any time
for these kinds of chats before.
When these talks begin,
everything's nearly done cleaning up.
If we can have these kinds of discussions
going forward too,
without being embarrassed.
Well, we'll be more embarrassed as we age.
But I hope we can stay like that.
Like, this suddenly came to me,
but I want to take a group photo now.
Seriously?
-I don't know!
-Like this? Now?
Yeah! We could look back on
how we did this with the seven of us.
I want to take a photo of this.
I want to make this one photo precious.
-Then let's take it.
-Yeah.
Me too, I'm a little...
Oh no, I think I'm tearing up!
Wait a minute,
my eyes are seriously watery right now!
Of course we'll have footage,
but I want to save a photo.
A photo after rehearsal feels like,
"Oh..." but I don't know.
We've never taken one before!
I don't know.
Here it goes.
The summer of 2021,
they discussed their future.
JULY 3, 2021
MIYAGI
The group's arena tour began.
Let's go!
-Wow.
-Let's go!
-Good morning!
Good morning!
Awesome!
The stadium was their biggest ever.
How cool!
Wow!
This is awesome.
Seriously cool.
Cool, it's a diamond!
Let's do our best.
Will they be able
to touch the hearts of their fans
who will fill up this large stadium?
Good morning!
The time to test those abilities
was drawing near.
Good morning!
Morning, we're Naniwa Danshi.
Nice to meet everybody!
We'll do our best!
Let's do our best!
Yes, let's do our best.
Please.
Let's meet next when we've made our debut.
You can cover us once we debut.
Next time,
the day they carried through the promise
they made three years ago.
There is a secret hidden
behind that touching moment.
I have to thank Micchi.
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi