(graphics tinkling)
(cheerful music)
- (gasps) Mailbox.
(Stacy trilling)
(graphics pops)
(letters whooshing)
(gasps) It's Teddy's birthday.
(bubbles popping)
(gasps) Princess party.
(princesses popping)
- Oh.
I will go.
(letters tinkling)
(gasps) It's Mia's birthday.
(graphic dings)
I need to go.
And all in the same day.
(fanfare music)
How to do everything?
Oh!
(light bulb dings)
One and two.
(graphics tinkling)
- [Crowd] Wow.
(Stacy trilling)
- I'm going to the princess party.
And I'm going to Teddy.
(Stacy boings)
So I'm going to Mia.
(Stacy trilling)
I'm the first.
I'm the second.
I'm the third.
- [Crowd] Oh.
- Ooh, this honey is for Teddy.
(audio whistling)
- Ooh, it's for Mia.
Ooh.
(object whistles)
(box whooshes)
Let's have a tea party.
(Stacy trilling)
(birds chirping)
(engine revving)
(hooves clopping)
(fanfare music)
Oh, my present.
(cauldron whooshes)
(Stacy trilling)
(engine revving)
(cauldron boings)
(playful music)
(engine revving)
(cauldron boings)
(Stacy grunts)
(Stacy trilling)
(cauldron whooshes)
(kids cheering)
(bubbles popping)
(upbeat music)
(engine revving)
(kids cheering)
(honey squelches)
(Pooh burps)
- Ew.
(cauldron whistles)
(cauldron boings)
(Pooh yawns)
(Pooh snores)
- Hey, why are you sleeping?
What about party? (grunts)
(screen whooshes)
(engine revving)
(Minnie cries)
(Stacy gasps)
(gasps) What's going on?
- [Minnie] It's my birthday,
but there is no presents.
- Look, I have a present for you.
(kids cheering)
Happy birthday!
- Oh.
(toys whistling)
- Wow.
(screen whooshes)
(hooves clopping)
(horse neighing)
(kids laughing)
- [Stacy] Hi, guys.
- [Playmate 1] Hi, Stacy.
- Let's drink a tea, girls.
(graphics tinkling)
- Oh.
- Who wants banana tea, girls?
- I want.
(graphics tinkle)
- With lemon.
- Thank you.
(lemon pops)
(group laughing)
(door creaks)
- Stacy, time to go home.
Stacy, time to come inside.
- (gasps) Wait, wait. Bye-bye.
- [Dad] Stacy, come home.
- (gasps) Dad calls me.
Bye. I must go.
Hi, Dad.
- Hello, Stacy.
(audio boings)
- Dad, hi!
- Hello.
(audio boings)
- Hi.
- Hello.
(birds chirping)
(upbeat music)
(Stacy snoring)
(phone ringing)
(Stacy yawns)
- Hello?
- Hey, Stacy. Let's go hang out.
- (gasps) Hi. Let's go.
- Okay, I'll pick you up at 6:00.
- Okay.
(phone chimes)
Yay! I have a date.
La, la, la, la.
(audio scratches)
(Stacy gasps)
Oh no! Acne!
(Stacy trilling)
(cat meows)
(Stacy cries)
(hand knocking)
- Stacey, what happened?
- I'm unpretty.
- How are you not beautiful?
Come out and show me.
- Look.
- Whoa.
- Ew.
- Well, there you go. (cries)
- Oh, I think I know what to do.
Here. Now it will disappear.
- What's that?
(brush popping)
- [Dad] Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Like this, like this.
Right now!
(kid chuckling)
Oh, it didn't help.
(fanfare music)
Let me think of something else.
- (whimpers) What about my date?
- Here, you can wear a mask.
(masks booming)
- [Stacy] Give me this one.
(audio chimes)
(fanfare music)
- Try on another one.
(playful music)
(mask chimes)
Well, let's try this one on.
(audio trilling)
Something just isn't right.
Hold on. This one will look good.
Well?
- Ew.
(person laughing)
(Stacy singing indistinctly)
(Dad clapping)
- (whimpers) I'm not
going to the carnival.
(mask clangs)
(Stacy grunts)
(Stacy cries)
(graphics rattling)
- We need some medicine.
Wait, right there.
(playful music)
- Whoo-hoo!
(mask whistles)
(hood whooshes)
(audio trilling)
(Dad sniffs)
(fanfare music)
- Hmm. Something interesting.
(mixture gurgling)
(graphics chiming)
Hmm. (coughs)
(mixture gurgling)
- All right, it's ready. Close your eyes.
(graphics zapping)
(spray thumping)
- Eh.
(person laughing)
(Dad gasps)
(Stacy grunts)
(upbeat music)
(graphics zapping)
(spray thumping)
(Dad babbling)
(intense music)
(door knocking)
- (gasps) Dad, my prince is here.
Figure something out, please. (cries)
Please, please, please, Dad.
- (gasps) Look.
- New, very effective cream for pimples.
Order Now.
(eye tinkles)
(key pad beeping)
- Hurry up. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
- Hello?
We want to order the cream for
pimples as soon as possible.
(phone crashes)
(cream whooshes)
(upbeat music)
- (gasps) Ointment.
(graphic tinkles)
(door knocking)
- Dad! Dad!
Hurry up.
(pimples zapping)
(kids cheering)
- Yay!
Open the door.
(playful music)
- Yes.
(Stacy trilling)
(gasps) He's gone.
- [Kids] Ah.
(Stacy cries)
(fanfare music)
- Let's go do some experiments.
- (gasps) Let's go!
- Let's go.
Let's make volcano!
- Let's make a volcano!
(upbeat music)
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- [Dad] Put on your goggles.
(upbeat music)
(liquid sloshing)
- Wow.
(upbeat music)
(liquid sloshing)
Wow.
Hold on.
(upbeat music)
(liquid sloshing)
Wow.
(upbeat music)
- Hit the like button.
- Please like.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
- Shhh.
(playful music)
(footsteps thumping)
I think it's Stacy's house.
(gift tinkling)
(cat 1 trilling)
- [Dad] Whoa!
Ha! Whee! (laughs)
(graphics chiming)
(doorbell chiming)
(Dad gasps)
(Stacy gasps)
- Who's there?
- [Dad] Ooh, what's that?
- Oh.
(gift trills)
- There's something inside.
- Let's open it.
(gasps) Wow.
- [Cat 2] Oh, where am I?
- (gasps) My sweetie.
- [Crowd] Oh.
(audio whistles)
(Dad sneezes)
- Dad, let's keep it here.
- (sneezes) No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Please.
(graphics trilling)
- Oh, okay.
- Yay.
(fanfare music)
Take and hold it.
Look how cute it is.
(playful music)
(graphic zapping)
- Oh!
(cat 2 meows)
Look what this cat did.
It scratched me.
(blows) We need to take
this cat to the groomer.
- [Cat 2] Where am I being taken?
- [Stacy] We are going to the shop.
(kids laughing)
(cheerful music)
(cat 2 purring)
(playful music)
(door handle tinkles)
- [Dog 1] Hello.
(dog 2 barking)
- [Cat 3] Hey, don't
touch me. Let me sleep.
Go. Go on.
- [Cat 2] Wow, I'll get a
manicure and pedicure. I like it.
- (gasps) Let's take it.
- Whoa, look how big this cat is.
- [Cat 3] Hey, hey. Be careful.
- This cat is even bigger than me.
- [Cat 2] Oh, he cleans
my ears. It's very nice.
- (gasps) Dad, let's take the dog.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- [Dog 3] Take me, please.
- Wow.
(playful music)
- [Cat 3] Oh, what a pretty
cat. Come visit us again.
- Hey, let's go on.
- Let's go. Let's go.
Shall we go home?
- Why? No.
We need food and toys.
- Ah, okay.
Ah, who knew having a cat
would be so much work.
- (gasps) Dad, look. Let's buy a collar.
- Okay.
(graphics tinkling)
- (gasps) This is a good one.
Dad, let's get this dress.
(cash register dings)
- (gasps) How much?
(money trilling)
- Please.
(cash register dinging)
- Uh-oh.
- Oh.
- (chuckles) Yes.
Toys. Oh, we'll take it.
(cat 2 purrs)
(cash register dings)
- Hmm.
(person laughing)
(Stacy chuckling)
(cat 2 purring)
(upbeat music)
(plates whooshing)
(calculator clacking)
Oh geez.
(cash register dings)
This stuff is so expensive.
- [Stacy] This house too.
(cat house whooshes)
(cat 2 purring)
- Okay. This is the last
thing we're getting today.
- Yay. Baby socks?
- No, I said enough.
(buzzer buzzes)
- Okay.
(gasps) Dad, look. Look at this.
- Yes, they're very nice houses for cats.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
(Dad gasps)
(fanfare music)
- Let's buy.
- (sighs) No, no. My heart
can't take it anymore, Stacy.
(fanfare music)
- Maybe a snake?
(snake hisses)
- Ugh. What a disgusting thing.
- [Stacy] Dad, look, birds.
- Oh, parrots. I love parrots.
- [Parrot] Uh-huh, dad's stupid.
- Uh-oh.
(Stacy laughs)
(cash register dings)
- Oh no.
- Yay.
Finally, we are at home.
(cat 2 zapping)
Now, we are going to eat.
- [Cat 2] Mm, yummy and tasty. I like it.
How beautiful I am.
I've never been so beautiful.
- Now, let's play.
(bright music)
(toy chirping)
- [Cat 2] I like this place.
Yes, I will stay in this house forever.
(toy chirping)
(Stacy smacks)
- It's so boring.
(insect buzzing)
- (yawns) Uh-huh.
(upbeat music)
- Whoo-hoo!
- (gasps) Disco.
(upbeat music)
(fanfare music)
(party organizer scoffs)
(kids laughing)
- This is a disco.
(graphic scratches)
A barbie.
- Okay. Be right back.
Now, we'll get dressed up.
(objects whooshing)
- Put it.
(graphic tinkles)
- Wow.
- [Stacy] (gasps) This is a good one.
- [Crowd] Wow.
- Hmm.
(fingers tinkling)
(stickers tinkling)
(hand popping)
(playful music)
(stickers tinkling)
- [Dad] Nice.
(upbeat music)
(bag tinkling)
- Wow.
(upbeat music)
(sunglasses tinkling)
(hands clapping)
(hands popping)
(both trilling)
(screen whooshes)
- Stop. How old are you?
- I'm five.
- You're too young to pass.
(Stacy grunts)
(person laughing)
And how old are you?
- 40.
- You're too old.
Go home.
(audio rattling)
(fanfare music)
(cheerful music)
- A ball.
- Hello. The dress code is formal.
- We have to go change.
- [Stacy] Yes.
- Let's go.
(both trilling)
(cheerful music)
Stacy. I'm ready.
(graphic tinkling)
- (gasps) Well, what's
it? Change your cloth?
(graphics tinkling)
(magical music)
Do you like?
- (gasps) You look stunning.
- Dad, it's for you.
- Covered in silver.
(suit tinkling)
Wow!
- Yay!
- Something is missing.
- [Stacy] Hmm.
(upbeat music)
(net whistles)
(person laughing)
- Aw.
(upbeat music)
(person chuckles)
I caught some butterflies for you.
(Stacy gasps)
(butterflies trilling)
(dress boings)
- That's so cool.
- And you need something.
(hair tinkles)
(Dad chuckles)
And the crown.
(kids laughing)
Oh, no. You need another one.
(buzzer buzzes)
(crown whistles)
(crown whooshes)
(people laughing)
Oh, not this one. (chuckles)
Well done.
(graphic tinkles)
- I invite you to the ball.
- Yay!
(upbeat music)
(magical music)
(graphic tinkles)
- So, may we get in?
- Go check your height, please.
(drum rumbling)
No, you can't pass.
- Oh.
- Uh-oh.
(fanfare music)
(dramatic music)
(buzzer buzzes)
- You're too tall to pass.
(audio trilling)
- Oh, no.
(audio tinkling)
(upbeat music)
- Check that out.
- [LOL Mascot] Hi.
- May we get in?
- [LOL Mascot] No, only LOL, please.
(audio rattling)
- Dad, hurry up.
(both trilling)
(upbeat music)
(object boings)
(shirt whistles)
(box zapping)
(object trilling)
La, la, la, la, la.
- I'm ready too.
(graphics tinkling)
- Try this one.
- Ew.
(headband whistles)
- No, something's not right.
- (laughs) Or maybe this one.
(headband whooshes)
(Stacy laughs)
- No, this is for girls.
(headband whistles)
(Dad meows)
- Try this cap.
- And this is what I need.
- Yes.
- Wow.
- [Stacy] Perfectly.
- Let's go to the party.
- Go!
(upbeat music)
So, may we get in?
(fanfare music)
- [LOL Mascot] Okay. Come in.
- Yahoo!
- Yay!
(upbeat music)
- Do you remember this?
- Ew.
(cat 2 trilling)
(kids cheering)
(cat 2 purring)
(balls boinging)
(ticks trilling)
(ticks laughing)
(fingers scratching)
- Something is biting me.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
- Dad, look.
(audio boings)
(fanfare music)
- Let's get out of here quickly.
(Stacy whooshes)
(Dad trilling)
(thunder rumbling)
It's raining.
- It's raining.
(gasps) Dad, look.
Look at this, and this,
(snails and worm laughing)
and this.
- [Dad] Oh, worms.
(footsteps boinging)
(playful music)
(Stacy whooshes)
- Uh-oh.
(Dad trilling)
(playful music)
- (gasps) There is no one.
(door thuds)
(bees buzzing)
- (laughs) Run away.
- Whew, they're gone.
(bees buzzing)
(audio boings)
(Stacy gasps)
(Dad babbling)
- Hey, get out. Get out.
(Dad screams)
(bees buzzing)
(bite pops)
(bees whooshes)
(fanfare music)
(person laughing)
- [Dad] Ow.
- Oh no. (gasps)
(bees buzzing)
(person laughing)
(gasps) Run.
- Let's run away!
Run!
(siren blaring)
Let's go.
(playful music)
(Dad coughing)
(spiders whistling)
(spider whistles)
- Oh.
(spider boings)
(kids cheering)
- So, where was it?
- Look.
(box tinkles)
- Oh, let's take it.
(ticks boinging)
(footsteps thumping)
(ticks popping)
(both trilling)
(drum rumbling)
- Whoo-hoo
(kids cheering)
(upbeat music)
(tires rattling)
(engine revving)
(Stacy laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Turn it on. Faster, faster.
(blower buzzing)
(kids cheering)
Wow. Such a cool house.
(fanfare music)
- [Stacy] Yes.
(playful music)
(zipper zapping)
Wow.
- Wow.
(Stacy laughing)
(cheerful music)
(playhouse whistling)
(bees buzzing)
(Stacy laughing)
(person laughing)
(light bulb dings)
(zipper zapping)
(playful music)
- Hmm.
(kids cheering)
(chuckles) Wow.
(playful music)
(chair whooshes)
What about me?
- Wow.
(Stacy grunts)
- Aha!
(light bulb dings)
(Stacy trilling)
Aha!
(foam whooshes)
(kids cheering)
(thunder buzzing)
(water pattering)
(lightning booms)
- What happened?
(air hisses)
The house is deflating, Stacy.
- Uh-oh.
(air hisses)
(kid laughing)
- Let's get away from here.
- [Stacy] Run.
(footsteps thumping)
(playful music)
- (sniffs) Nice.
- Fantastic.
- Stacy, come and eat.
(dramatic music)
(footsteps thumping)
- I'm not Stacy. I'm the princess.
- Okay, princess, sit down and eat.
(playful music)
(wand chiming)
- Feed me.
(audio popping)
- (chuckles) Yeah, right. Eat by yourself.
You're not a baby.
(Stacy gasps)
(Stacy grunts)
(wand tinkles)
- Well, I'll turn you to the frog.
- (Dad laughs) Show me.
(wand whistling)
(playful music)
(Dad grunts)
(Stacy laughs)
(frog croacking)
(Stacy blows raspberry)
All right. All right.
I'll feed you. Just transform me back.
- Well, okay.
(wand tinkling)
- (croaks) Oy, oy, oy. Let me feed you.
(upbeat music)
(kids cheering)
- Well, now I want a tablet.
- (gasps) No, that's too much.
- Well, I'll turn you into the frog.
(wand chiming)
(Dad gasps)
I will get it myself.
(frog croacking)
(upbeat music)
(drawer whooshing)
(person laughing)
- [Dad] Sweetie, transform me back.
- Okay.
(wand zapping)
- Yo.
- And now I'm gonna sleep.
Silence.
(Stacy snoring)
- Wow.
(wand tinkling)
- Aha.
(wand zapping)
(graphic pops)
(donkey grunting)
- [Speaker] Yeehaw!
(wand chiming)
(playful music)
- What?
(wand chiming)
(cat 2 trilling)
(fire crackling)
(Dad laughing)
- Hey, wake up.
(intense music)
- Hmm. Well, hold on.
(graphics popping)
(audio scratches)
(Stacy gasps)
- And now, put all your toys away.
- What? Me?
No way.
- Take this then.
(wand chiming)
(person laughing)
- [Stacy] Dad, please change me back.
- Well, all right.
(wand tinkling)
(Stacy gasps)
(toys whooshing)
- Whoo-hoo!
- Whew.
- And now go and clean the car.
(wand tinkling)
- Well, okay.
- Yeah.
(eye tinkles)
(rug squeaks)
I shouldn't behave like that.
- And now, go clean the
cat's litter box. (laughs)
(audio chimes)
- Ew.
- (gasps) Dad, sorry. I'll
never behave like that anymore.
- [Crowd] Oh.
- All right, sweetie. I forgive you.
Do you behave well?