(gentle music)
(Nastya snoring)
(knocking on door)
- Come here, come here.
(bright music)
- I lost my puppy. (cries)
- [Children] Aww.
(woman cries)
- Don't cry.
Don't worry.
Wait here.
(dramatic music)
(siren wailing)
(Nastya imitates siren)
(shaker chimes)
Puppy.
(siren wailing)
(Nastya imitates siren)
- [Children] Aww.
(dramatic music)
(Nastya gasps)
- [Children] Ew.
(bright music)
- Huh?
- Excuse me, is this your puppy?
(woman gasps)
- Oh, my puppy.
(children laughing)
This is for you.
(chime dings)
- [Children] Yay.
- Oh, thank you.
- Goodbye, bye.
- Bye.
(bright music)
(baby crying)
- Baby cry.
(children gasping)
(bright music)
(siren wailing)
(Nastya imitates siren)
(baby crying)
(siren wailing)
(gentle music)
Oh.
(bright music)
(knocking on door)
(children screaming)
- Hello, my little pretty. (laughs)
- Is this your baby?
(baby crying)
(witch laughing)
- Oh no.
Come back here.
- No.
(bright music)
(witch laughing)
(baby crying)
(bright music)
(knocking on door)
(gorilla grunts)
Hi, is this your baby?
- This is my baby.
(gorilla grunts)
- [Children] Aww.
- Bye.
(gorilla grunts)
(baby crying)
Look.
(sped up audio playing)
(children laughing)
(bright music)
(baby crying)
Is this your baby?
(chime dings)
- I'll check.
One baby.
(chime dings)
Two.
Three.
(chime dings)
(children laughing)
(slide whistle blowing)
Four.
(chime dings)
five.
And six.
(bright music)
(children screaming)
Where is my baby?
- This is your baby?
- Yes, yes, it's my baby.
- [Children] Yay.
- Hmm, and clean up here.
(bright music)
- [Children] Ew.
- Okay, sorry.
This is surprise for you.
- Yay.
- Okay, thank you.
(children cheering)
(bright music)
- [Children] Hooray.
(bright music continues)
- Help me.
Help.
Help me.
- Somebody needs help.
(sirens wail)
- Help me.
Help.
Help me.
- [Children] Oh no.
- I will help you.
(gasps) Gorilla.
(children gasp)
(bright music)
(fighting sounds)
(birds chirping)
(Children cheering)
(bright music)
(indistinct) gorilla.
(gorilla grunts)
(birds chirp)
- Thank you very much.
This is for you.
- Thank you.
Bye-bye.
(bright music)
(top pops)
(bright music continues)
(slide whistle blows)
(children cheering)
So cute.
What a hard day.
(Nastya snoring)
(bright music)
I'm going to my friend's.
- [Children] Hooray.
(dramatic music)
(Nastya gasps)
(germs laugh)
(slide whistle blows)
(dad gasps)
- Stay home.
- [Children] Aww.
(bright music continues)
(door creaks)
- Boring. (cries)
- No, no, no.
Do you want a challenge?
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's go.
Choose.
- [Children] Yummy.
Ew.
(bright music)
(straw slurps)
- Mm, apple juice.
- [Children] Yay.
(straw slurps)
Ew.
(bright music)
- Ew, eggs.
(children laugh)
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- [Children] Ooh.
Ew.
- Now my turn.
- Okay.
(bright music)
(chime dings)
- Green.
(bright music)
(straw slurps)
(Children laughing)
Broccoli.
- [Children] Ew.
- My turn.
- Okay.
(straw slurps)
- Mm, Coke.
(bright music)
Wee.
- [Children] Yay.
- Hmm, next one.
(chime dings)
(bright music continues)
- My turn.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Yes.
(bright music continues)
(straw slurps)
Mm, milk.
- [Children] Hooray.
(bright music continues)
(straw slurps)
- Tomato juice.
(children laughing)
oh.
(dad screaming)
Hot.
(alarm blaring)
- I want my friends. (cries)
(upbeat music)
- Do you wanna dance?
(children laughing)
- Okay.
- [Children] Yay.
(upbeat music)
(record scratches)
♪ Baby shark doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Baby shark doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Baby shark ♪
- Bleh.
♪ Mommy shark ♪
(record scratches)
(upbeat music)
- Nuh-uh.
♪ Old McDonald had a farm, E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And on that farm he had a cow ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ With a moo, moo ♪
(record scratches)
(upbeat music)
- Hmm, boring.
(upbeat music continues)
(gentle music)
I miss my friends.
- [Children] Aww.
(upbeat music)
- Do you wanna paint?
- Hmm, okay.
(bright music)
(brush strokes)
(indistinct)
- [Children] Yay.
(chime dings)
Hooray.
(bright music)
- Green.
- Orange.
(bright music continues)
- [Children] Yay.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Let's play.
- [Children] Yay.
(bright music)
- Mm-hmm.
My turn.
(upbeat music)
(children laughing)
- No.
(bright music continues)
(dad screams)
A-ha.
(children yell)
(bright music continues)
(paint sack boings)
- [Children] Yay.
(bright music continues)
(paint sack boings)
(paint sac boings)
(bright music continues)
- [Children] Yay.
- Daddy.
- What?
- You're best friend forever.
(bright music)
la, la.
Oh.
- [Children] Wow.
- Oh.
(bright music)
Ta-da.
(bright music continues)
Mm-hmm.
- [Children] Cool.
(bright music continues)
(suitcase pops)
(sped up audio plays)
(bright music continues)
- Hmm.
Wow.
(bright music continues)
(finger taps)
Hmm, mm-mm.
(shaker chimes)
Hmm.
(dad gasps)
Mm, no.
- Let's try this.
- Hmm, okay.
(bright music)
(children laughing)
- Uh-huh.
(bright music continues)
- Hmm.
- Okay.
(bright music continues)
(slide whistle blows)
Music.
(gentle music)
(person gasps)
(water drips)
(gentle music continues)
(dad screams)
(alarm buzzes)
(hands flapping)
Woo.
- It's okay.
It'll get back to normal soon.
It's time to take the mask off.
- Okay.
Ow, ow, ah.
- Ew.
(flies buzz)
- Ow.
Ah.
- [Child] Uh-oh.
- Is this normal?
- Hmm, I'll fix it.
(bright music)
(flies buzzing)
Another mask?
(flies buzz)
- No, no more masks for me.
- Let's try this then.
- Okay.
(upbeat music)
Hmm.
(bright music)
- Fantastic.
(dad sneezes)
(stones clack)
(Nastya hums)
(bright music continues)
(spring boings)
(dad groans)
- Stop, stop.
- Sorry.
- Enough, enough.
I don't want anymore treatments.
- Have a seat please.
(bright music continues)
- Mm.
Ah.
(slide whistle blows)
(electricity buzzes)
(bright music)
(dad screams)
(bright music continues)
(smoke puffs)
- Oops.
(bright music continues)
(dad groans)
- Sweetheart, you should play safe games.
(horn blows)
- Yay, hooray.
(upbeat music)
(chime dings)
Wow.
(slide whistle blows)
(bright music)
(water runs)
(bright music continues)
A mask.
Bye guys.
Ah.
(bright music)
Let's count to 10.
(upbeat music)
- Count.
One.
- [Nastya And Dad] One, two, three.
- I win.
(children cheering)
(bright music)
(Nastya gasps)
- [Children] Ew.
- I need to eat it?
Mm, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Mm.
(bright music)
(children giggling)
Mm.
- My turn.
Two.
Oof.
(children laughing)
(bright music)
One cake,
(bright music continues)
(slide whistle blows)
Two cakes.
- [Children] Yay.
- You need eat it.
(upbeat music)
(children laughing)
(person chomping)
(bright music)
One more, Daddy.
(children laughing)
(bright music continues)
My turn.
Three, three, three.
(gentle music)
(chime dings)
Balloons.
- Let's pop it.
- Yay.
- Ah.
(balloon pops)
(bright music)
- [Children] Yay.
(balloon pops)
Yay.
- Four.
(bright music)
- One, two,
three, four.
You need drink all of them. (laughs)
(children laughing)
(slide whistle blows)
(upbeat music)
- Ah.
(upbeat music continues)
(children laughing)
- Drink, drink, drink, drink.
Drink.
(dad gulps)
(water flows)
(children laughing)
- Good job.
- [Children] Yay.
(bright music)
(water pours)
- Number five.
I need do this?
(indistinct)
(children laughing)
One,
(slide whistle blows)
two,
three,
(slide whistle blows)
four,
and five.
T-da.
(horn blows)
- Six.
(bright music)
(chime dings)
(bright music continues)
Uh-oh.
(children laughing)
(bright music continues)
(slide whistle blows)
- One.
Two.
(slide whistle blows)
Three.
Four.
(dad yells)
(Nastya gasps)
(bright music continues)
(slide whistle blows)
Five.
(bright music continues)
- Six.
- [Children] Hooray.
- Seven, seven, seven, seven, seven.
(bright music)
(baby cries)
- [Children] Ooh.
- Oh no, no, no.
I'm not a baby.
- Yeah.
(bright music)
- Mm.
(chime dings)
Second.
(bright music continues)
Mm.
Mm, bananas.
(bright music continues)
Yuck.
- [Children] Ew.
(bright music continues)
- Yuck.
(slide whistle blows)
- Mm.
Ugh.
Eight.
- Guess animals.
Meow.
- [Children] Yay.
- Okay.
(dad imitates a monkey)
- I know, this is monkey.
(Nastya imitates a monkey)
(dad imitates a rooster)
I know, this is rooster.
(chime dings)
(dad imitates a pig)
I know, this is pig.
(horse neighs)
(dad imitates galloping)
This is horse.
- [Children] Yay.
(dad imitates an owl)
- Maybe owl?
(chime dings)
(dad imitates sheep)
- Ah, this is sheep.
(dad imitates tiger)
Maybe a tiger.
- Yeah.
(dad imitates dog)
- Dog.
(chime dings)
- [Children] Yay.
- My turn, nine.
(upbeat music)
Don't blink.
(children laughing)
- One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine.
(eyes blink)
Bravo.
- 10.
- [Children] Yay.
(bright music)
- You will be ballerina, ballerina.
(children laughing)
(bright music)
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, 10.
(bright music continues)
(drum bangs)
(symbol tings)