(sharp playful knocking)
(toy dog barking)
(rapid scuttering)
(door swinging open)
- Hi!
Stacy, come with me to the dance.
(Stacey cheering gleefully)
- Yes.
(magic sparkling)
- Nice dress.
Oh my gosh.
Ooh!
(light bouncing music)
(horn bellowing)
(grunting in despair)
Oh, Daddy.
(bell chiming)
(light quirky music)
Daddy, daddy.
- What?
- I need a dress, I'm going to the dance.
- Ah, of course.
(light music)
Take this.
- Thank you.
I found a dress.
- Well done.
(clothing whooshing)
(cheerful trumpet)
Ready?
(traditional marriage melody)
- Are you getting married?
(record player rewinding)
Change your dress.
(quirky music)
Dad.
- What?
- Look, you gave me the wrong dress.
(horn bellowing)
(Dad grunting in confusion)
(magic chiming)
- Take another one.
(Stacey gasping gleefully)
- Thank you.
(light magical music)
(shoes popping)
(playful quirky music)
(dress whooshing)
(children laughing)
(sister grunting playfully)
(bright music)
(sister laughing)
- [Audience] Wow.
(bright music)
(horn bellowing)
- Dad!
(newspaper whooshing)
(Dad gasping in surprise)
- What?
- What did you give me again?
(dress whooshing)
- Here, try this one on.
- Okay.
(light pensive music)
(magic chiming)
Boo!
(Halloween objects whooshing)
(bright Halloween music)
(evil witch laughing)
(ghost bellowing)
(sister gasping)
- Is it Halloween?
- No, that's how I dress for the dance.
- No, it's not good.
- Oh, dad!
Hey daddy, this dress isn't for the dance.
(Dad humming pensively)
(dress whooshing)
- Take this one.
(quirky music)
(upbeat music)
- [Audience] Wow.
(magic whooshing)
(sister yawning)
- No.
(audience exclaiming)
- Stacey, look at this
dress I found for you.
- [Audience] Cool!
(Stacey cheering ecstatically)
- Yeah!
Hey, look at my dress.
(light music)
(magic whooshing)
(Stacey gasping)
She's sleeping.
(Stacey yawning)
I'm tired too.
(clock ticking)
(sisters gasping)
- We overslept the dance.
(sisters crying)
- Girls, what's wrong?
- We overslept the dance.
- All right, girls, let's go and play.
(audience cheering)
(bright music)
- Look!
(children laughing gleefully)
(light bright music)
(bubbles whooshing)
(audience cheering)
(quirky whistling music)
(sisters screaming)
(girls laughing gleefully)
(horn bellowing)
(Stacey giggling)
(Dad laughing cheerfully)
- Come on!
(upbeat music)
(Dad thudding against slide)
♪ Na na-na boo-boo ♪
(upbeat music)
(slide squeaking)
(quirky music)
(Dad shaking cheeks)
(upbeat music)
(hand whooshing)
(plastic ball squeaking)
(Dad thudding on water)
(quirky music)
- [Audience] Ew!
- Ooh, freedom!
Catch this!
(upbeat playful music)
(water toys whooshing)
(Dad chuckling)
This one too.
(water dinosaur whooshing)
- Bye!
(upbeat playful music)
(quirky Halloween music)
- Halloween!
(Dad laughing evilly)
(pumpkins thudding)
(Stacey gasping)
(light pensive music)
(box magically whooshing)
- Is it real?
(Spider ghost bellowing)
(Dad and Stacey shouting)
Let's get rid of it.
(quirky music)
(Stacey gasping)
(spider ghost thudding on chair)
(thrilling dark music)
(quirky thrilling music)
(bats flapping wings)
- Wow!
(quirky playful music)
(ghost whooshing)
- What's it?
(Stacey yelping)
- It's a walking hand.
(Stacey giggling)
(Stacey screaming)
(walking hand thudding)
(light bright playful music)
- Take a photo.
(camera shutter snapping)
(ominous music)
(Stacey gasping)
Uh-oh.
(mysterious ball squeaking)
(ghosts bellowing)
(Stacey gasping)
Look!
- Awesome.
(quirky bubbling music)
(toy whooshing)
(quirky music)
Turn it off, Stacey.
(Dad sighing)
(Stacey giggling)
Get away.
(robot toy thudding)
(blender whooshing)
(button popping)
(Dad gasping)
(Dad shouting)
(Stacey laughing hysterically)
(blender thudding)
- Oh, it's video camera.
- Wow.
(quirky bubbling whirling music)
(quirky Halloween music)
(camera reel whirling)
- [Audience] Wow!
(quirky Halloween music)
(camera reel whirling)
- Cool.
- Yes!
(quirky playful Halloween music)
(audience laughing)
- Oh, wow.
- They're Halloween Costumes.
- Yes.
(ominous music)
(skeleton laughing)
(audience giggling)
- No, I don't like this one.
- Let's try on another one.
- Dad, do you like this one?
(monster roaring)
(thrilling spooky music)
(Stacey giggling)
- No, it's not so good but check out mine.
- What are you doing?
(toy duck quacking)
(Stacey giggling)
(rapid scuttering)
- Hey, try this one and this one's for me.
(bells chiming)
(Dad humming pensively)
Ooh!
I'm the witch.
(bats flapping wings)
- Cool costume, check out mine.
(extravagant upbeat music)
(audience laughing)
(Stacey gasping)
(extravagant upbeat music)
- No, no, no.
It's too much.
(bells chiming)
- And how about this one?
- Ah, what a scary costume.
(Stacey gasping)
(depressed trumpet)
(audience exclaiming)
Dad look.
Maybe this one.
- Hey there, folks.
(cheerful chiming music)
- Hmm, not bad but it'll
be better without this one.
(quirky music)
(thrilling music)
(Stacey gasping)
Fume.
- We've gotta put it out.
Let's go quick.
(light upbeat music)
- Hurry up, hurry up.
(quirky music)
(contents rattling)
(Dad gasping)
(Stacey gasping)
(light thrilling quirky music)
(Stacey laughing)
(tap running)
(quirky magical music)
(fumes whooshing)
(Dad grunting and laughing)
(Stacey giggling)
(quirky playful music)
(Stacey gasping)
- A puddle!
(water splashing)
- [Audience] Oh, no!
(birds chirping)
(Dad gasping in shock)
(quirky music)
Hi, Dad.
- [Audience] Ew!
(Stacey giggling)
- What is this?
You should be a princess.
(crown thudding)
(Stacey whooshing)
Here put this on and you'll
look like a princess.
- Hmm, well, okay.
(Stacey giggling)
(cheerful music)
(crown whooshing)
- My princess.
- [Audience] Aw!
(Stacey gasping)
- Wow.
- [Audience] Wow!
(Dad sighing)
(quirky playful music)
- Ooh, wow.
Wow.
(Stacey gasping and giggling)
(audience exclaiming)
(sand rustling)
(playful cheerful music)
(Stacey giggling)
- Stacey, where are you?
(Dad gasping)
(quirky music)
What have you done?
- It's just sand.
- Oh my goodness.
(quirky music)
Get out of there.
(Stacey whooshing)
(audience laughing)
You're a princess.
You can't play in the sand with a dress.
- Okay, daddy.
(light bright music)
- Put this on.
- [Audience] Wow!
(audience exclaiming)
(audience cheering)
Hmm, I wanna eat.
(Stacey's stomach rumbling)
- Hey.
- Hmm, watermelon.
Yummy.
(Stacey munching loudly)
- [Audience] Ew!
(depressed trumpet)
- Sweetie, princesses don't eat like that.
(audience gasping)
(dress whooshing)
(Dad grunting)
(magic whooshing)
(audience exclaiming and cheering)
(Dad grunting)
(serious pensive music)
(Stacey gasping)
(cheerful music)
(bike bell ringing)
(Stacey giggling)
(dress ripping)
(dress tearing)
(Stacey gasping)
- Oops.
(Door lock clicking)
- What again?
(horn bellowing)
- Oops.
(Dad weeping)
(Dad grunting)
(audience laughing)
(quirky music)
(dress whooshing)
- Here.
(audience cheering and exclaiming)
(bright music)
(Dad grunting)
(heels clacking)
(hose splashing water)
(cheerful music)
- Dad, look how beauty I am.
(audience gasping)
- Hey, Daddy, hey.
(Stacey giggling)
(heel tapping)
(Stacey grunting angrily)
(Dad gasping)
(quirky music)
- My bad.
- Well, hold on.
- No, no!
(playful music)
(audience laughing)
(water splashing)
(playful music)
(light spooky music)
(Stacey grunting evilly)
- Halloween.
(spooky music)
(pumpkin basket whooshing)
(witch laughing)
(skeleton grunting)
- [Audience] Ew!
(bones shaking)
(bones cracking)
(Stacey gasping)
(thrilling spooky music)
(spider thudding)
(audience laughing)
(birds chirping)
(audience cheering)
(victorious trumpet)
(ghost bellowing)
(spooky music)
(skeleton grunting)
- Hello?
(roof thudding)
(Stacey gasping)
(ghost laughing evilly)
(roof thudding)
(ominous music)
(creative laughing evilly)
(Stacey gasping)
- What do you want?
- Trick or treat.
- Ah-huh.
(candy whooshing)
(audience cheering)
(Stacey gasping)
- [Audience] Yummy!
(quirky spooky music)
(creature laughing evilly)
(bright playful music)
(candies tumbling)
- [Audience] Wow!
(Stacey gasping)
(Stacey grunting)
(thrilling spooky music)
(Stacey gasping)
- My nails!
(audience exclaiming)
(creature laughing)
(Stacey screaming)
(magic whooshing)
(Stacey sighing in relief)
That's disgusting.
(candies thudding)
(quirky spooky music)
(Stacey grunting angrily)
(pumpkin basket whooshing)
(Stacey giggling)
(spooky chiming music)
(skeleton bones clacking)
(door creaking)
(creatures laughing evilly)
(dark spooky music)
(doorbell ringing)
(thunder roaring)
(thrilling music)
(clown laughing evilly)
(Stacey gasping)
(playful circus music)
- But what about the candy?
(clown laughing evilly)
(Stacey grunting)
(clown singing foolishly)
- Thank you.
- Bye.
(clown laughing evilly)
(light music)
(basket thudding)
(Stacey sighing)
(candies thudding)
- [Audience] Cool!
- Hmm, yummy.
(bright music)
(clown laughing evilly)
(spooky music)
- [Audience] Ew!
(Stacey whelping)
(magic whooshing)
(Stacey sighing)
(Stacey grunting angrily)
(bats' wings flapping)
(Stacey gasping)
(woof howling)
- Trick or treat.
- Welcome.
(creative laughing evilly)
- Give me candy.
(quirky music)
(bell chiming)
(drum roll)
(victorious trumpet)
- Yes!
(audience cheering)
Thank you.
(Stacey blowing kiss)
(quirky music)
(creative laughing evilly)
(bright music)
(Stacey sighing in exhaustion)
(candies thudding)
(audience exclaiming)
- Hmm, it's chocolate.
(bright music)
(Stacey gasping)
(magic chiming and whooshing)
(audience laughing)
(Stacey gasping)
(quirky music)
(magic whooshing)
(thrilling music)
I don't want this candy anymore.
(Stacey grunting angrily)
(thrilling music)
(ghost bellowing)
(Stacey gasping)
(spooky music)
- Ouch.
(ghost bellowing)
Oh, that's disgusting.
(Stacey gasping)
Hi, hi, there, boo.
(rapping on door)
(spooky music)
(Stacey screaming)
(eerie spooky music)
- [Audience] Oh no!
- Trick or treat.
- Yes.
(basket whooshing)
(candies chiming)
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
(bright music)
(Stacey sniffing loudly)
(magic whooshing)
(candies thudding)
(candy whooshing)
(Stacey sniffing loudly)
(Stacey grunting)
(light quirky music)
(hand whooshing)
- Wow.
(record player rewinding)
(Stacey screaming)
(thrilling music)
- [Audience] Ew!
- Ew!
(Stacey screaming)
(audience cheering)
(Stacey sighing)
(Stacey grunting angrily)
(quirky music)
- Stacey, where are you?
Oh, sweet.
(bright music)
(candies rustling)
(Dad humming in delight)
(Dad chugging liquid)
(Stacey gasping)
- Daddy, don't eat it, no.
- Huh?
(magic whooshing)
(audience laughing hysterically)
(Dad yelping)
(audience laughing)
(Stacey and Dad shaking cheeks)
(audience cheering)
(victorious trumpet)
Hooray, all of these go in the trash.
Let's go cook our own sweets.
- Yay.
(audience cheering)
(bright music)
(Stacey cheering)
(plate thudding)
(microwave chiming)
(Stacey gasping)
Wow.
(bright music)
- [Audience] Yummy!
(Stacey and Dad munching loudly)
(Stacey weeping)
(audience exclaiming)
- Why are you crying, sunshine?
(Stacey weeping)
(Dad gasping)
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
(quirky fun music)
You wanna a dress, right?
(Stacey weeping)
(depressed trumpet)
(bell chiming)
Wait, wait.
(quirky chiming music)
Here, I know you wanted makeup.
(Stacey weeping)
(light sad music)
Let's go hang out.
(quirky music)
(Stacey weeping)
Fun music.
(upbeat music)
(audience exclaiming)
(depressed trumpet)
What is going on?
Let's go.
(audience exclaiming)
(bright music)
(Dad roaring)
(Stacey weeping)
(baby babbling)
(baby crying)
(quirky music)
(monster roaring)
(Dad chuckling)
(eerie spooky music)
(spider rattling)
(clown screeching)
(Dad grunting in despair)
(bell chiming)
(quirky music)
(bright music)
(light sad yelping)
(toys whooshing)
- [Audience] Aw!
(bright music)
(light sad yelping)
(Dad giggling)
- [Audience] Wow!
(depressed trumpet)
(bell chiming)
(tropical upbeat music)
(light sad yelping)
(food whooshing)
(quirky sad music)
(Stacey sniffing)
- Ew.
(Dad munching loudly)
(bell chiming)
- I have one more idea.
(Stacey sighing)
(bright music)
(candy whooshing)
- No.
(depressed trumpet)
(quirky music)
(Stacey weeping)
- That's it, I'm calling the doctor.
(phone whooshing)
(dial pad chiming)
(Stacey weeping)
Hello, please come urgently.
- On my way.
(urgent rapping on door)
(quirky music)
(ambulance siren)
(heart beating)
(bell chiming)
(light bright music)
Show me your hands.
(doctor gasping)
A splinter.
(audience exclaiming)
(Stacey yelping)
(splinter straining and popping)
Whoa!
(Dad gasping)
- Thank you, doctor!
Thank you!
- Hooray!
(audience cheering)
And now surprises.
Oh, surprises.
The biggest first.
(audience exclaiming)
Knock and knock, who lives in the house?
Flamingo with wings.
(indistinct)
I'll make juice.
- [Audience] Wow!
(quirky music)
(Stacey slurping juice)
- [Audience] Ew!
(bright music)
Aw!
(toy giggling)
(audience cheering)
(ball bouncing)
- Oops.
You see?
(indistinct)
- [Audience] Wow!
(bright music)
And what is this black?
Kitty.
(kitty meowing)
Bye.
(audience laughing)
(cat meowing)