- Hurray!
- [Child Audience] Wow!
Cool!
Oh, whoa!
Wow!
- [Adult Audience] Aww.
- I'm gonna call my
friend and show off a bit.
Hello, Nastya, come visit me.
- All right, on my way!
(door knocks)
- Yeah!
- Hello!
Wow, what a dress!
- Uh-oh.
This is my dress!
This is my dress.
- Hmm.
(Nastya gasps)
Wow, what a bag.
And a perfume.
(perfume puffing)
- Oh, no!
Give it back.
It is mine.
- Humph.
- Hmm.
(Nastya gasps)
- [Child Audience] Yay!
- I've already told you, they're mine!
Don't touch it!
Humph!
- Humph, all right, then.
I'm leaving.
Humph.
(door creaks)
- Humph, whatever!
Who cares?
Look at this.
(child audience laughs)
I don't even need that friend.
I have a new friend.
An idea!
(child audience laughs)
Ta-da!
- [Child Audience] Oh, whoa!
So, buddy, let's dance!
♪ La la la la ♪
(child audience laughs)
(audience exclaim in surprise)
(Stacey gasps)
(Stacey cries)
- Why are you crying now, Stacey?
- I'm bored, I don't have friends! (cries)
- (gasps) Let me find someone for you.
Hmm.
Oh!
(ball boinging)
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Artyom, come with me.
Come on, come on.
Look, I brought you a friend.
- Hello.
- Yay, hello!
Come on in!
- [Child Audience] Yeah!
- Sit down, please.
(Stacey giggles)
We're going to play now.
(child audience laughs)
(Stacey giggles)
- No way, come with me.
Let's go play.
Please sit down.
Take these.
(punches thudding)
(Chun-Li yelping)
- This is for boys.
Hey, hey.
It's time for you to go home.
(Artyom groans)
Bye-bye!
Bye!
Goodbye!
(Stacey sighs)
I shouldn't have argued with my friend.
- Dad.
- What is it?
- (groans) I'm bored.
- (sighs) Let me figure
something out for you.
Hmm.
Oh!
Hello, hey!
- Hello!
- Come on in!
Come on, come on!
- Of course.
Let's go.
- Here.
I brought you some friends.
Look!
(baby giggling)
- What?
A baby?
Uh-oh.
(baby giggling)
No, no, no!
- Wow.
(baby giggling)
- (gasps) Oh, no!
Thank you for coming,
but now you should go.
Thank you, thank you.
(door creaks)
Bye!
Ugh.
I think it's time to
make up with my friend.
- Hello?
- Nastya, I'm sorry.
Please come visit me again soon.
- All right, I'll come.
- [Child Audience] Oh, whoa!
- Come in, come in!
(door creaks)
- Hello!
- [Child Audience] Yay!
- Here, these are for you.
- Thank you.
- And please take this perfume.
- Thank you!
What?
Is it me?
- (gasps) Oop.
No, no, it's nothing.
- Hmm.
("Everybody" by Elijah N playing)
(Stacey giggling)
(Cymbals crashing)
(Stacey's father roars)
(Stacey gasps)
(balloons boom)
(Stacey's father laughs)
- [Child Audience] Oh, whoa!
Wow!
(Stacey giggles)
- [Adult Audience] Aww.
- [Child Audience] Yay!
(bee buzzing)
(bee snickers)
- Shoo, shoo!
(bee buzzing)
- Shoo!
(slime cries)
(Stacey and Stacey's father gasp)
- [Both] The slime!
- Oh, no!
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Ah, let's go.
- [Child Audience] Wow!
(child audience laughs)
(balloon boinging)
(Stacey giggling)
(Stacey's father snoring)
(balloon boinging)
(child audience laughs)
(bee buzzing)
- Shoo!
(Stacey's father puffing)
(bee buzzing)
- Whoa!
(bee snickers)
- (gasps) Pop!
- Whoa!
(balloon pops)
(child audience gasps)
(child laughs)
- Whoa.
Uh-oh.
(Stacey's father groans)
- Yay!
(Stacey giggling)
(child audience laughing)
(water sploshing)
(Stacey giggling)
(child audience laughing)
(water splashes)
(child audience laughs)
- [Adult Audience] Aww.
- It's okay.
We're gonna go do something else.
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- Dance, dance, dance.
- [Child Audience] Oh, whoa!
- Dance time.
Yay!
(Stacey boinging)
Where's daddy?
(Stacey gasps)
(child laughing)
(Stacey's father groaning)
(Stacey's father pops)
- Whew! (chuckles)
(bee buzzes)
(bee snickers)
(inflatable castle boinging)
(hole blowing)
- Oh!
- Oh no!
- Be careful!
- It's falling down!
- It's gonna trap us!
Oh!
(Stacey grunts)
- Daddy?
Daddy, where are you?
- I'm here.
What happened?
And how do we get outta here?
Oh, finally.
- Phew.
- I am so annoyed with this bee!
- [Both] You better fly away fast!
(bee buzzing)
(child audience laughing)
(audience laughing)
(bee buzzing)
(bee snickers)
- Oh!
- [Both] It flew away!
(bee buzzing)
(cat meows)
(cat munching)
- Aww.
- [Both] "Frozen".
(coins clink)
- Daddy!
- What?
- Can you buy us something?
- Hmm.
I got it!
- [Both] Hmm?
What is this?
- I don't know.
That's what I had enough money for.
- [Both] Oh, no.
What is it?
("All Is Found" by Evan
Rachel Wood playing)
(Stacey gasps)
- Let's get inside!
- [Adult Audience] Wow!
- That's so beautiful!
(Stacey singing)
My turn!
- [Child Audience] Wow!
("All Is Found" by Evan
Rachel Wood playing)
- Now it's your turn.
- [Audience] Fantastic.
- Wow!
Reindeer!
- Hmm.
My turn!
Hmm.
Wow!
(Stacey groans)
- Hmm, now I'll go inside.
(Stacey mocking)
- Humph.
- [Child Audience] Wow!
(Olaf singing)
- Bye-bye.
- Here.
- (gasps) Is it for me?
- Yes.
- [Adult Audience] Wow!
(Stacey gasps)
- Margarita, your hair is white.
- Yes.
(Margarita groans)
(Stacey gasps)
- Hmm, interesting.
Where did you get so many toys?
Hmm.
(both gasp)
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- Ah, just like I wanted.
(everyone cheers)
(train chugging)
(both gasp)
(train blows horn)
(train chugging)
- Sweet shoes are on sale.
Come and get some.
Sweet mirrors.
(Stacey munches)
(drums rolling)
- Hmm.
- Hello.
- What a shoe.
Hmm, so beautiful!
- No, no, no.
- Huh?
- Gimme something a mermaid would like.
- Hmm, just a moment.
Here.
- Wow, a mermaid!
Okay, here you go.
- Thank you!
♪ Under the sea ♪
(Margarita gasps)
- Hello.
- (gasps) What amazing shoes you have!
Where did you buy them?
- Right there.
- (gasps) Thank you!
- You're welcome.
- Hello.
(gasps) What a beautiful mirror.
Hmm.
Wow!
I need these!
Here's the money.
- Money?
Uh-uh.
Give me something a mermaid would like.
- Hmm, okay.
Here, take this.
(gasps) Thank you!
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- [Child Audience] Yay!
- Look what I have.
- (gasps) They are so beautiful!
(bubbles popping)
(Stacey giggling)
- So beautiful!
- And mine are so bright!
- Yeah, really cool.
- Hmm.
Where did you get these?
- [Both] There!
- Hmm.
- Oh, hi!
- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm!
It's my size.
Here you go.
- No, no, no.
- What would you like then?
- Something for the mermaid.
See?
- Okay.
- So have you bought it?
- No, I don't get it.
Mermaids?
- [Both] Hmm.
Bring her these.
- Thank you!
- [Both] Bye-bye.
(Stacey humming)
- Hey, will these things do?
- Yes!
Thank you.
Here, take them.
- Thank you!
- [Adult Audience] Wow!
(rain pattering)
(Stacey giggling)
- Great.
- Mm, tasty.
- A sweet hat.
Different sweets.
Come and get it.
- [Everyone] (gasps) A hat?
- Give the hat to me!
- Give it to me!
Me, give me the hat.
Please!
- The hat, please!
- I want the hat.
- Well, what can you offer?
A mermaid lady?
- Look, I have the toy from the cartoon.
- Hmm, nu-uh.
- Look what I have.
Do you want it?
(Ursula snickers)
- (gasps) No!
- Look what a poster I have.
- Hmm, nu-uh.
(Magarita and Nastya gasp)
- [Everyone] Hmm.
(Magarita and Nastya whisper)
- We're gonna buy something.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
- [Adult Audience] Wow!
- For you.
- (gasps) Yay!
Whoa!
- And this is also for you!
- Hmm.
- Humph, give it to me.
(Margarita gasps)
- Humph.
- Hmm!
- Humph, mine!
Hmm.
- Bye-bye, guys.
(Stacey humming)
(bed boinging)
- Uh-oh!
(bed crashes)
- (gasps) Uh-oh!
Daddy!
- What is it? What happened?
What- (gasps)
- The bed broke.
- Well, let's fix it.
(drill buzzing)
(hammer thudding)
It's ready!
(gasps) Thank you!
- All right, sleep tight.
Sweet dreams.
(Stacey snoring)
- What's under there?
(Stacey screams)
- Sweetie?
What happened?
- Daddy, there's something
under the blanket!
I'm scared!
- Look, there's nothing here.
- I guess it was a dream.
- Probably.
Sleep tight.
I won't turn the light off.
(Stacey groaning)
(Stacey thuds)
Daddy!
I fell outta bed!
- (gasps) Sweetie, what happened?
- I fell.
- Oh, my poor Stacey.
Get up, come on.
Lie down.
(Stacey snores)
- Shh.
(Stacey groans)
(springs boinging)
- Ouch!
Daddy!
- What is it now?
- Daddy, I need a new bed!
This one is really old!
- You're right.
I'm gonna order a new one.
Hello?
I'd like to order a new bed, please.
- A cute, beautiful bed!
A very beautiful one, okay?
(door knocking)
- (gasps) It's here!
- It's here!
What?
What did you order?
- Huh?
Here, lie down.
Sleep.
- Okay, all right.
(Stacey grunting)
(Stacey groans)
No, it's too small.
Could you order a new one, please?
- Hello, I'd like to order
a new bed for my daughter.
- [Child Audience] Wow!
(both gasp)
- Look at these wheels!
- It's really firm!
(yawns) I am so tired.
I wanna sleep.
- I better sleep next to you tonight.
(Stacey's father snores)
- What's this?
(gasps) What is it?
Oh.
(gasps) It is such a cute gift!
(dog barks)
(gasps) Again?
(gasps) One more gift!
Daddy, Daddy, wake up!
My bed is magic!
- (gasps) Really?
- Look.
- [Audience] Fantastic.
- (gasps) Wow!
- (gasps) Yes!
Let's try again.
- It's glowing again!
- Yes, yes!
(Stacey's father gasps)
- Let's try again.
More, more!
(wheel cracking)
- Uh-oh!
(bed crashes)
- [Both] It broke again.
Yes.
- Oh, oh.
- Uh-oh.
- Bye-bye.
- Mm.
It's made of candy!
- Yeah!
- It's also made of candy.
Even the nose.
Wow!
(Stacey giggling)
(Stacey's father gasps)
- Wow!
- [Adult Audience] Ah.
- Welcome to Candy Land!
(Stacey giggles)
- [Adult Audience] Wow!
(Stacey giggling)
- Wow!
(children giggling)
- Have some!
(playful music)
(Stacey's father sighs)
(air blowing)
(chipmunk snickering)
- Pick them up!
You can do it!
- Wow, look!
(Stacey giggling)
(audience gasps)
(Stacey's father grunts)
(Stacey giggling)
- Phew.
Ow!
Ah, bye-bye!
Hello!
Where are you?
Where-
Stacy?
Stacey, where are you?
Stacey?
- I'm here.
- Oh, here you are.
Where have you been?
Phew, we made it.
- Yeah!
- Hello!
(bubbles popping)
(Stacey munching)
- Whoa!
- Wow!
(upbeat disco music)
(children giggling)
- [Adult Audience] Aww.
- [Both] Welcome!
- Hmm.
(guitar riffs)
(Stacey's father humming)
- Wow!
(Stacey humming)
Candies!
(Stacey's father snickers)
(Stacey's father roars)
- Be careful, lizard!
Is it tasty?
Hmm.
(Stacey's father babbling)
(Stacey giggling)
- Look, candies.
Nice!
(children laughing)
- [Both] Bye-bye!