(lamp squeaking)
- Get out!
Hey, get out!
(Stacy growls)
Dad!
(door squeaks)
- Yes, sweetie? What happened?
- Okay, now you're gonna be the Genie.
- Genie?
- Yeah, of course. Put it on.
- [Children] Wow!
Aww.
- Hmm... You need something.
(Stacy giggles)
♪ A whole new world ♪
Now I'm gonna wanna paint you.
- Maybe not.
- Come on, dad.
(makeup brush squeaks)
- Uh-oh!
(fanfare sound effect)
(children laughing)
- Now I want a magic carpet.
- I'll try.
(victorious electronic music)
- [Children] Wow!
Yay!
(air whooshes)
- Help!
(Stacy sighs)
(laughter sound effect)
(Stacy growls)
(rubber stretching sound effect)
Let's fly!
Hmm!
- Yes?
- Ahhh!
(children laughing)
Okay, that's enough!
(dad laughs)
- Hmm...
Do magic, do magic, do magic!
- Okay.
(mysterious chiming sound effect)
(Stacy laughing)
- [Children] Wow!
(Stacy yells)
(birds chirping)
(Stacy sighs)
- Well, hold on!
- Look!
(air whooshes)
- Go!
(children cheering)
Ah-ha! Go!
(water rushes)
(thunder cracks)
(gasps) Uh-oh!
Ahhh!
(monkey chirps)
Help! Help!
(water splashes)
(Stacy sighs)
Hmm!
- Now, now, we'll fix everything.
(sparkling sound effect)
(children cheering)
- (gasps) I like it!
Hmm! Why are you doing this?
Get in, hurry!
- In the lamp? No.
- Come on! Get in, hurry!
- Well, all right.
- Yay!
(victorious fanfare)
- Get me out of here!
(Stacy giggles)
Well, I'm done with all this.
(sparkling sound effect)
Oh! I know how to get out of here.
(tissue squeaks)
(Stacy gasps)
(smoke whooshes)
- (gasps) Uh-oh!
- [Children] Wow!
- Finally.
- Dad?
- Hello!
- (gasps) Let's play again.
- No, sweetie. Enough for today.
- Hmm. I'm tired of being alone.
I'm tired of you. Hmm.
I should go to my father.
(children laughing)
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
Let's play, please?
- [Children] Aww.
- Play alone or find
yourself some friends.
- Hmm!
(mischievous music plays)
(baby sucks on pacifier)
- (gasps) Oh no!
Hmm. Ah!
(gasps) Oh no, it's
raining and I have no home.
Oh, the rain is gone.
- [Children] Yay!
(cardboard rustles)
- Ah!
(children laughing)
(Stacy gasps)
- Stop!
Hey, stop!
(squeaking sound effect)
It's mine!
Hey, get out!
(baby cries)
(gasps) What's up, beauty?
- [Children] Wow!
(Stacy pounds on plastic)
(mysterious music plays)
Get out!
- Let's be friends!
- Okay!
Yay!
(Stacy gasps)
Hmm. Odd one.
(door squeaks)
(baby laughs)
(gasps) I wanna jump.
Hey, let me jump!
- No, it's my trampoline!
- Hmm!
But I know what to do.
- Hmm?
- [Children] Wow!
- Do you know what's on my mind? Ah-ha!
- [Children] Yay!
- 1, 2, 3!
(boinging sound effect)
Yay!
(gasps) Uh-oh!
(children laughing)
Hmm! It was my house!
- Na na na na na!
- Well, we are not friends.
Hmm. I'll watch TV.
(laser buzzes)
Na na na boo boo!
(Stacy laughs)
(TV clicks off)
Get out! It's mine!
(drum roll sound effect)
Get out!
(baby cries)
- Na na na na na!
(whines) I have no friends.
- [Crowd] Aww.
- I have to make up with her.
(baby crying)
Let's be friends and never quarrel.
- [Children] Yay!
- The friendship is wonderful. Bye!
(crying) Where is my cat? It got lost.
My cat got lost.
(dad snores)
(Stacy cries)
(Stacy bangs on door)
- (gasps) Hello? Hello?
I'm listening. Hello?
Hello?
(phone beeps)
- Hi, I'm here.
- (gasps) Hi!
- I got lost my cat.
- (gasps) We'll find it now! Don't worry!
(whimsical music plays)
Ah!
(bike squeaks)
(engine revs then explodes)
(fire roars)
(gasps) Uh-oh!
Nice!
(engine revs)
(bike squeaks)
- Oh, no!
- (gasps) Ah!
(dog barks)
- (laughs) Yippee! I found it, I found it!
(Stacy gasps)
Here, take it!
- Hmm. It's a dog.
(dog barks)
- (gasps) I'll continue searching.
Here, here, here, here, here! (vocalizes)
Oh!
(horse whinnies)
Oh, no!
- [Children] Wow!
- Yeehaw!
Uh-oh.
(structure snaps)
Uh-oh!
- [Children] Aww...
(dad imitates siren)
Kitty, kitty!
Oh!
(dog purrs)
- (cries) Where is my cat? (gasps)
- Here! I found it!
- Yay!
Hmm. It's a dog.
I had a cat! Cat, cat!
- Okay, okay.
- Go and get it.
(dad whistles)
- [Dog] I love you!
- Oh, donuts!
(relaxing piano music plays)
(dad laughs)
(dad chomps donut)
(dad burps then exhales)
(dad snores)
- (gasps) He's sleeping!
Hmm! Hey, get up!
- Yes, yes?!
(sped up speech)
(cat meows)
(Stacy gasps)
- Look! It's my cat!
(cat meows)
- Here, take it.
(fanfare plays)
- Thank you!
- Ahh...
Mmm.
(phone rings)
Hello? Police speaking.
- Hello, police? My cat got lost again.
- (gasps) Oh...
(dad cries)
Hi!
- Hello!
(triumphant music plays)
(audience claps)
(discordant violin music plays)
Ew!
- Boo!
(triumphant music plays)
Boo!
- Next one.
(sad trumpet note plays)
- Oof!
(Stacy cries)
Oh! Idea!
- [Children] Yay!
- (gasps) Yes!
(dad beats on drums)
(funky drum music plays)
- [Children] Cool!
Wow!
(crowd whistles)
- Now, no.
(Stacy gasps and whines)
- [Children] Aww...
(sad trumpet note plays)
(Dad growls)
- Uh-huh!
- [Child] Woo-hoo!
- Great!
(electric guitar music plays)
(upbeat rock music plays)
- Oh, it's really cool!
(dad laughs)
(crowd whistles)
- [Child] Yeehaw!
- So, do you like?
Yes!
- Eh...
No. No, no, no.
- Hmm!
(guitar slams on ground)
(dad gasps)
- [Child] Uh-oh!
- Next one!
(dad growls)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
(guitar snaps)
(gasps) Oh, let's do it together!
- Let's!
(Stacy laughs)
(dad growls)
(funky rock music plays)
- [Child] Yahoo!
(cat meows)
- [Child] Whoa! (laughs)
(fire roars)
(car honking sound effect)
(dad exhales)
- [Children] Yay!
- Whoa, that was so awesome.
- Yes!
- [Both] Hooray!
(dad laughs)
- Bravo.
- [Children] Yay!
- [Child] Fantastic.
- Bravo!
(Stacy vocalizes)
(dad laughs)
(Stacy gasps)
- Oh, it's the treasure map.
(children laughing)
Ah-ha!
My friends, wait for me! Go!
(upbeat rock music)
Wow!
(Captain growls)
Come on!
- I am Captain Jack Urave!
(crowd laughs)
(lion roars)
Now we will go catch the
pirate. Faster, faster!
Take ye weapons faster.
- [Stacy] Well, hold on.
(steam sprays)
(Captain laughs)
(children cheering)
- So if you cannot hear us...
- [Children] If you cannot hear us...
- We scream a little louder!
- [Children] We scream a little louder!
- [Stacy] Look!
(Captain laughs)
(children laugh)
- [Skeleton] What are you doing here?
- [Stacy] Oh, look! What's it?
(light whimsical music)
(buzzer sounds)
Hmm... Look there!
Hmm...
(fanfare plays)
- [Captain] Great job!
- [Children] Wow.
- It's too heavy. What a huge box.
We are pirates! (laughs)
- [Children] Yay!
(skeleton laughs)
- [Captain] Come on, get
'em out! Look how many keys.
Come on, come on, come on!
- [Child] Whoa!
- [Captain] Whoa!
It be the treasure!
- [Crowd] Wow!
- Yo ho ho!
- [Children] Yo ho ho!
- Good job.
- [Children] Na na na na boo boo!
(skeleton laughs)
- Give it back, give it back!
(skeleton pops)
- [All] Hurray!
(children laughing)
- [Stacy] Come on, girls!
Let's beat the boys!
- [Children] Rah!
Hey, stop, stop! Help me, help me!
- Hold on!
(children laughing)
- So, my friends, I'll
see you at the next party!
- [Crowd] Wow!
- I like it!
Hmm. Ah!
(Stacy gasps)
(crowd gasps)
(sad trumpet note plays)
Hmm!
(Stacy gasps then whines)
I can't, I'm tired of this!
Dad!
- Yes, sweetie? What happened?
- Look!
(dad gasps)
- Uh-oh!
(Stacy growls)
I have an idea.
- [Children] Yay!
- Wow! (gasps)
- I'll go now.
- Uh-huh, okay. Thank you!
Oh, it's empty.
(buzzer sounds)
(gasps) It's empty!
(Stacy cries)
- Daughter, what happened again?
- I have nothing to do makeup.
- We gotta go to the store.
(Stacy gasps)
Let's go!
- Go!
- Let's go, let's go!
(children laughing)
- (gasps) I want this one.
Wow!
- Yeah, yeah.
- Hmm. And this one.
And this one.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- (gasps) Wow!
I want this one and this one!
And buy me this and this
one. And lipstick, of course.
- Maybe that's enough.
- And this one is exactly
what I really need.
Yes!
- We had a lot of fun.
- Yes!
(gasps) Wow, thank you!
Let's start!
(upbeat whimsical music)
Daddy, come on!
- Wow!
- Hello!
- Oy, oy, oy.
- So do you like?
- I think you're a bit
too young to wear makeup.
(sad trumpet note plays)
(Stacy whines)
I know what can help you.
- Huh?
- Here, Stacy. Practice on this.
(fanfare plays)
- Thank you, dad!
(upbeat rock music)
- And have some candy.
(Stacy gasps)
(both sucking on candy)
Mm, tasty!
(upbeat whimsical music)
(rag squeaks)
(bricks crumble)
Oh, my God!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
(alarm sounds)
(lava bubbles)
Uh-oh! (gasps) I'll call Stacy!
(cat sniffs then meows)
(Stacy slurps drink)
Hello? Stacy, help me, please!
Get here quickly, help me, please!
- (gasps) Dad!
- I need your help!
- (gasps) I will save you.
Hmm...
Oh, Marshall!
I'm here. Let's go!
Go! (yells)
Wait for me, I'm going.
(exciting whimsical music)
(horn honks)
(tires squeal)
- (gasps) Come here, come here!
(water drips)
(Stacy groans)
- Hmm!
- Oh, no!
- Hmm, Batman.
(bats squeaking)
(dad munches on snacks)
(dad gasps)
(fire roars)
Ooh!
(dad grumbles)
Hmm.
Ah!
(wall crumbles)
(birds tweeting)
(gasps) Uh-oh!
Ah!
(squeaking sound effect)
(Hulk growls)
(dad exhales)
(fire crackles)
(dad cries)
Once again, nothing had happened.
I know what to do.
(gasps) This one!
- [Children] Wow!
(ice crackles)
- Who? A princess?
(crowd laughs)
(ice crackles)
(gasps) Yay, it worked!
- Oh, easy.
(children cheer)
- Thank you so much!
- What? Superman?
Princess, of course.