- Today is a play date.
(horn blowing)
Whoo-hoo!
(Dad gasps)
- Play date?
- Hello? Yes, come.
I'm excited for our play date. Bye!
Yay!
(dad grumbles)
Blow it up.
And this one.
Done.
Ready?
Great.
(chime dings)
Bring the see-saw.
(bright music)
(silly music)
Let's go.
(chime rings)
Pour the sand here.
(bright music)
Wow.
Let's go, let's go.
(chime rings)
(bright music)
Mm.
- Tasty?
(bright music continues)
(cookies pop)
Mm.
- No, no, no, Daddy.
They're for my friends.
Let's go, let's go.
- Let's.
- Come on, come on.
(bright music)
(shaker chimes)
Whoo-hoo!
(Nastya laughs)
My guests will like it for sure.
(bright music)
(ball bounces)
(knocking on door)
(Nastya gasps)
- The guests are here.
(bright music)
(knocking on door)
(children laughing)
(bright music)
(bright music continues)
(children laughing)
- Wait, wait for me.
(Nastya gasps)
Oh my gosh.
(bright music continues)
(children laughing)
- [Older Kids] Cool.
(whimsical music)
- Oh.
Oh, I need to gather them.
(bright music)
(children yelling)
- Wah.
- Woo hoo.
(bounce house boings)
(girl laughs)
(bright music continues)
- Come on.
- Stacy-
- come play with us.
- Come join us.
- Just a second.
I'll tidy here,
and go to you right away.
(slide whistle blows)
(bright music)
- Yay.
(bounce house boings)
- On my way.
I'm here.
Here.
I'm...
(record scratches)
Wait, my bouncy castles.
(gentle music)
- I'm bored.
- Let's go to the sandbox.
- Yeah.
(Nastya gasps)
(silly music)
- Yay.
(bright music)
(children laughing)
(girl laughing)
(boy laughing)
(children stomping)
- Ew.
Oh, no, they're misbehaving again.
Alright, let's get out of here.
They forgot to pick it up again.
(chime)
(sweeping)
Phew. (groaning)
- Yay.
(silly music)
(scampering music)
(sinister music)
- Stacy. Come play with us.
(groaning)
Stacy.
- Come here.
- Stacy. Stacy.
- Stacy, come here.
- Just a second. Phew.
(boing)
(silly music)
- Sit down.
(giggling)
Look! Iguana!
- Cool!
(silly music)
- What about me?
(girl yelling)
Woohoo!
(Nastya gasps)
I'm all dirty!
(frustrated groaning)
- Mmmm.
- Ardo, look!
- Mm!
- [Crowd Of children] Wow!
- No forks. Oh, whatever.
Mm.
(upbeat music)
- Hmm.
(upbeat music continues)
I'm here, I'm here guys.
- [Older Kids] Oh, Stacy. Hey.
(Stacy gasps)
(Stacy crying)
- Hmm?
- I've had enough of this play date today!
It's time to go home!
There's the door.
- Okay then. Bye.
- Please leave.
- Oh, you're already leaving?
- Yeah.
- Bye-Bye.
- [Older Kids] Bye-bye.
(Nastya huffs)
- Next time the play date's at your house.
Bye.
- Okay, bye.
- Dad! Let's play together!
- Of course. Let's go.
- Wahoo!
Ah!
- Go on.
(silly music)
Ouch.
- My turn! Wah!
So much fun!
- Tsk, tsk, tsk.
- Dad, you're my best friend.
(low chime)
Love your parents.
(crowd awhing)
(rooster crowing)
Good morning.
I'm gonna make my bed.
(happy chime)
(playful music)
You should brush your hair in the morning.
(happy chime)
Mwah.
(cabinet opening)
(playful music continues)
I dress myself.
(happy chime)
La la la, la la la.
Oh, hey guys!
(mischievous giggling)
(popping)
Hey there, hey there.
(boy chuckles)
May I play with you guys?
- [Older Kids] Hmm.
No.
- Why not?
- You're too small. Go on.
(defeated trumpet)
(dark music)
(Nastya groans)
- Oh, I have an idea.
(silly music)
Look!
(silly music continues)
- [Crowd of children] Cool!
- Mhm!
(paper towel ripping)
Now I am ready.
I'm so tall.
I need some gum.
(chewing)
(inhaling and inflating)
(bubble pops)
(popping)
(high pitch chime)
- I'm gonna win.
- Nah, you're gonna lose.
- Hey guys.
- Hmm.
(bubble inflates and pops)
- [Crowd of children] Wow!
- [Older Kids] Hmm.
- Let's play together.
- Hm?
(whimsical chime)
(tense music)
- Nah.
- [Older Kids] You're a baby.
- A baby?
(silly kalimba beat)
- The cool kids won't play with me.
- Hmm, come with me.
I'll talk to them.
(silly music)
- Yay.
- Hey!
- Huh?
- You should all play together or I'll...
Mm!
- Fine.
- Take it.
- Yay!
- Ouch.
- Oops.
So fun.
- Ouch.
- Sorry.
- [Older Kids] Hmm.
(ball whistles)
Ah!
- We're done here baby.
(older kids groan angrily)
(Nastya gasps)
- Go on. Go on. Go, go, go.
- Go on. Bye-bye.
(older kids sigh in relief)
- I am not a baby.
I can use my phone.
(phone dialing)
Hello.
Animals? Today?
And kittens?
Yes! Okay, please.
Bye!
(phone beeps)
(happy music)
(truck honks)
Yes, they're here!
(puppy barking)
Wow!
(chicks chirping)
(puppy barking)
(pig oinking)
A rabbit!
Puppies!
Pigs!
Chickens!
Rabbits!
Chicks!
And kittens!
Look at them.
(kitten meows)
(girl gasps)
- We want to play too.
- Yeah.
- [Older Kids] Can we play with you?
- Mm-mm.
Go there.
Let's measure your height.
(both gasp)
- [Older Kids] We're too tall.
- We can't play?
- Bye-bye guys!
- Hmm. Oh!
(puppy drinking)
(chicken crowing)
(puppy barking)
- Here. Can we play with you now?
- Come on in.
- [Older Kids] Yay.
(playful music)
(crowd laughs)
- A hare.
(silly music)
- Uh-oh.
(goats bleating)
(goat suckling)
- It's a piglet.
- Awh.
- A chick.
(pig snoring)
He's sleeping just like a baby.
- His eyes are red.
- [Crowd of children] Wow.
(kitten suckling)
- Such a cutie.
(chicks chirping)
- [All Three] Hey kids!
Did you like the video?
Press like! Bye-bye!
- Look at this kitten.
(Nastya mimics meowing)
- Bye-bye.
(balloon inflating)
(girls giggling)
(sneaky music)
(cymbals crashing)
(Dad gasps)
(girls giggling)
- Girls!
(silly music)
(girls giggling)
(bubble inflating)
(splatting)
(defeated trumpet)
(girls giggling)
Oh girls.
(peeling and popping)
- [Girls] Sorry.
- Hmm-hmm.
I'll teach them a lesson
about popping balloons.
Girls, come here.
- [Girls] Balloons.
- Balloons with surprises.
- [Girls] Hurray! Balloons!
- Here are the sticks to
pop them, but be careful.
- [Girls] Okay.
- One, two, three.
(splashing)
(silly music)
(dad laughing)
- [Girls] Water?
(water sloshing)
- Now pop the green one.
One, two, three.
(silly music)
- Yay.
- Whoa.
- [Crowd of children] Cool
(cybernetic music)
- [Girls] No, no, no.
- One, two, three.
(cymbals crashing)
(mischievous laughter)
- [Girls and Dad] Whoa.
- And what's this?
What color's this?
- [Girls] White.
- Pop it.
Whoa.
- [Crowd of children] Wow.
(glittering sound)
- [Girls] Diamonds.
- Let's pop the yellow one. Come on.
(silly popping)
(girls yelling)
(girls laughing)
- Woo-hoo.
- I didn't expect that.
(girls laughing)
- [Girls] Let's pop another one.
(water beads sloshing)
- Whoa.
- So cool.
- [Girls] Orbeez.
- Here's the last one.
Pop it.
(balloon yelling fearfully)
- [Girls] One, two, three.
(bubbles popping)
- [Girls] Ew. Slime.
- And what's this?
- We're gonna make slime out of this.
I'll add an activator.
(low boinging)
(giggling)
Press like.
(silly music)
(slime stretching)
- Wow.
(girl struggling)
- Catch it.
- Oh.
- Here.
(girls giggling)
- Like a long sausage.
(girls yelling)
- Hold it.
(spacey music)
(slime stretching)
- Uh-oh.
- I think I'm prettier.
- No, I am.
- No.
- [Older girls] Me.
- Everyone come here.
I'll paint your face.
I'll make your lips beautiful.
And here, you can choose crystals.
(girls gasping)
Come, come.
- Wow, how beautiful.
I want this one.
- Okay.
(silly music)
- Yes. Yes.
(sponge squishing)
(video game coin chime)
(bell dinging)
(sponge popping)
(whimsical chime)
- Hmm.
(sponge swiping)
(video game coin chiming)
- Hmm.
Unbelievable beauty.
All done.
(girl gasping)
- What have you done? It's horrible.
- It just happened.
(girl groans angrily)
- Look at that.
My turn. Mine!
- May I have this one?
- Okay.
Here, sit down, sit down.
- Thank you.
This one and this one.
- Uh-huh.
(whimsical synth)
- Hmm.
- All done.
(girl gasping)
- What's this? It looks horrible.
- Sorry. I did my best.
(girl giggling)
(silly music)
(whimsical chime)
- Let me try again.
I'd like this.
- Great choice.
- Be more careful this time.
(brush swiping)
- Wow.
(whimsical synth)
- All done.
- Wow, so beautiful. Thank you.
(hip-hop music)
Look, now I'm prettier.
- Hmm. My turn.
How about this one?
- It's easy.
(silly giggling)
(silly music)
(woohooing)
(silly music continues)
- Beauty contest,
I'm announcing a beauty contest.
- Me, me, I'll participate.
- And me and I'll participate.
- [Older girls] I'll
participate. Me, me, me.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey hey.
Hey, hey!
- [Older girls] No, I'll be prettier.
I'll be prettier. I will.
- I'll participate too.
(futuristic music)
- [Older girls] Hmm.
(silly music)
(whimsical synth)
- I'll just use a little bit of makeup.
(playful music)
(bell dinging)
Girls, look what I have.
(girls gasping)
- [Older girls] And I want this dress.
I want this one.
- All beautiful girls are invited.
(crowd booing)
(crowd wowing)
(meter sliding)
- [Crowd of children] Ew.
(girl giggling)
(upset trumpeting)
- Contestant number one.
(children booing)
Contestant number two.
(defeated trumpeting)
And contestant number three.
(children wowing)
The winner is contestant number three.
(older girls sigh)
- Natural beauty.
- Let's go wash our faces girls.
(Successful video game chime)
- Let's go.
(scurrying)
(silly music)
- A.
(cow mooing and pig oinking)
(horse neighing)
- Animals.
- [Dad and Nastya] Run!
(silly music)
(farm animal noises)
- Here.
(jazzy music)
- B.
(jazzy music continues)
(Nastya giggling)
- Black.
C.
(Nastya gasping)
- Confetti.
(tube popping)
- Woo.
(silly rhythm)
(Nastya giggling)
(silly music)
- D.
- Whoa! It's a dog!
- Dog!
(dog barking)
(barking continues with silly music)
- Catch me!
- E.
(Dad getting electrocuted)
(Nastya giggling)
- Yes, electricity.
F.
(video game coin chime)
(silly music)
(fire scorching)
(Dad yelling)
Fire!
(Nastya inhaling and blowing)
(successful chime)
- G.
(both gasping)
(ghost moaning)
- Ghost.
(silly music continues)
Bye!
(Nastya giggles)
- H. Bring it here!
- H!
(medieval chime)
(game chime)
(Nastya yelling)
Hand.
(sinister laughing)
Hi.
- Ew.
- High five.
(slapping)
- Ouch!
- I.
Ice cream!
- Wow!
- Yum yum.
- Mmm.
- [Dad and Nastya] J.
- What is this?
- This is jelly.
It's slippery.
(silly music)
It's so slippery.
Jelly candy.
K!
Woohoo!
- Key.
(Nastya gasps)
- Chocolate key.
Click click.
(Nastya chomping and chewing)
- Hey hey, kids shouldn't
eat so much chocolate.
Enough, enough.
(Dad chomping and chewing)
- L.
(adventurous music)
(Dad and Nastya yelling)
(Nastya screaming)
(video game chime)
(lion roars)
(silly music)
- [Dad and Nastya] M.
- What is it?
(Nastya gasps)
Music.
(Party music)
- Let me listen.
(party music continues)
(wind blowing)
(boxes falling)
(Nasty and Dad gasping)
- [Dad and Nastya] Oh!
- Hurray!
- You found it.
- N.
(silly music)
(horn honking)
(Nastya laughing)
Nose.
O.
(crowd wowing)
(Nastya crying)
- Ugh.
(Dad and Nastya crying)
(Drum rolling)
- Onion.
(Nastya crying)
- [Dad and Nastya] P.
Playhouse.
(playhouse skittering and bouncing)
(Dad and Nastya gasping)
- Queen.
(children laughing)
(Dad snoring)
R.
- Huh?
(playful music)
(Nastya gasps)
Rain.
- Rain.
Rainbow.
- Rainbow.
- S.
(whimsical chime)
- Shots.
- No, no, no. No shots!
- Pew, pew, pew.
- No, no, no.
- They're jelly shots.
(silly music)
- [Dad and Nastya] T.
(silly music continues)
(crowd laughing)
(Dad laughing)
(Dad and Nastya laughing)
- Teeth.
U.
Daddy, where are you?
(Nastya gasps)
(whirring)
(silly music)
Unicorn.
V.
Vampire.
W.
Walnuts.
Mm, chocolate.
- Mm, chocolate.
(Dad groans painfully)
It's a real one.
This one's real, this one's chocolate.
- [Dad and Nastya] X.
- X-Ray.
- [Dad and Nastya] Y.
- Mm.
- Yummy.
Yogurt.
(both sipping)
- [Dad and Nastya] Mm.
- [Dad and Nastya] Z.
- Hmm.
It's empty.
(patting on box)
(zombies groaning)
(Dad and Nastya gasping)
- [Dad and Nastya] Zombies!
- Bye-bye!
(zombies groaning)