(rooster crows)
(bright music)
- Today I'm a good girl.
Uh-hmm.
(bright music continues)
(Nastya gasps)
Chocolate.
(bright music continues)
Mm.
- Hello.
(toothbrush scrubbing)
Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
(Nastya gasps)
- I'll do more good deeds.
(bright music)
(upbeat music)
(Nastya hums)
Shh!
- [Woman] Chinese.
- Um-hmm.
(Nastya speaking in Chinese)
(Nastya gasps)
Yay!
(bright music)
Ooh!
(bright music continues)
(candy crunches)
Ooh!
Next lesson.
Spanish.
(Nastya speaking in Spanish)
(Nastya gasps)
(bright music)
Candy flowers.
(candy crunching)
Mm!
(bright music continues)
I'm gonna show my dad.
(dad sniffs)
- Oh wow.
(flower crunches)
Candy, I want some.
(Nastya gasps)
- No, my candy.
Hm!
(Nastya gasps)
Where is my candy?
- Hmm?
(Nastya gasps)
- No.
Open your mouth.
No.
Hmm, okay.
(Nastya gasps)
My candy.
(bright music)
(chocolate crunches)
(dad hums)
(dad gasps)
- I love chocolate.
Can I have some?
- No, no, no.
(buzzer buzzes)
It's mine.
- Hmm.
(Nastya gasps)
- Where is my chocolate?
(bright music)
Hmm.
- No!
- Mm, mm, mm.
- Uh-oh.
- Hmm!
(feet stomping)
(bright music)
It's my candy.
Not for you!
(drum roll beating)
(Nastya gasps)
(horn blows)
Where is my candy?
(bright music)
Hmm!
No.
(suspenseful music)
(horn blows)
(Nastya whimpering)
Hmm.
Huh?
Daddy?
(bright music)
- Mm, num, num, num, num.
Yummy.
Mm!
- (gasps) My candy!
- No, no, no.
(buzzer buzzes)
- Why?
- You have to share.
These are only for good kids.
- Okay, daddy, I will share.
- Okay, this is for you.
- (gasps) Yay!
(upbeat music)
(both grunting)
(cat meows)
(upbeat music continues)
- We need a suitcase.
Go get a new one, please.
- Okay.
Good.
(bright music continues)
Good, right?
- Mm-mm, it's not gonna work.
Get a different one.
- Okay.
(bright music continues)
Here.
- What is this?
(Nastya gasps)
- Hmm?
- Uh-uh, go buy the right one.
- Okay.
(upbeat music)
Bye-bye.
Here.
(upbeat music)
- Ugh, I'll do it myself.
This is a good suitcase.
- Hmm.
(upbeat music continues)
(dad hums)
- And mine too.
- Ow!
(upbeat music)
(Nastya laughs)
(record scratches)
(ominous music)
- [Crowd] Oh no!
(Nastya gasps)
- Hmm.
Mm, thank you.
(bright music)
- Uh-hmm, go!
(car system beeping)
- What?
Oh.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Oh, hello?
Oh, no!
Ow!
Please!
(dad whimpering)
- Don't worry, Dad, I have a tool set.
(enchanted music)
(dad gasps)
- Mm!
(whimsical music)
Ow!
Nice.
- Good job!
(dad humming)
Daddy, I'm hungry.
- Me too.
(cheerful music)
(crickets chirping)
Hmm?
Hmm.
- Don't worry, Daddy, I will cook!
(pots bubbling)
(eggs sizzling)
- Mmm, yum, yum, yum.
- Stop!
(dad gasps)
You need to wash your hands.
- Eh, nah.
(upbeat music)
Oh my. Daddy, Daddy.
Clean.
- Hmm?
(tummy growling)
Please call the doctor.
- Okay.
(phone beeping)
No answer.
(dad whimpering)
Don't worry, daddy.
Doctor, I can be the doctor.
(children chuckling)
Okay, you need this one.
(upbeat music continues)
(dad gasps)
(dad grunts)
(all applauding)
(whimsical music)
- I don't like this anymore.
- [Both] Bye-bye.
(upbeat music)
- Nastya, Nastya!
Oh, oh
- (Gasp) Daddy!
(whimsical music)
(Nastya gasps)
(dad grunts)
(Nastya chuckles)
(sneeze)
(dad grunting)
(Nastya chuckles)
(dad grunts)
(dad sneezes)
(cheerful music continues)
(hand rubbing)
(whimsical music)
- (gasps) Wow!
Hmm! Hmm!
(uplifting music)
- Ooh. Uh-huh.
- Daddy, open it please.
(dad grunting)
(dad grunts)
(uplifting music)
Again?
(upbeat music)
- Hmm?
- Thank you.
- Ow!
(dad sneezes)
(upbeat music)
(ominous music)
- It's sour.
I know!
Chips!
(Nastya grunting)
I know!
Uh-hmm.
Daddy!
(dad humming)
(upbeat music)
(dad gulping)
La la la, la la la.
Daddy, open it please.
- Okay, it's easy.
(dad grunting)
(whimsical music)
- Try to open it like this.
- Uh-huh.
(dad gasps)
Want one?
- No, no.
Huh? Dad, Daddy!
- Hmm.
(upbeat music)
- Hmm!
Mm, it's all mine.
Wow!
(Nastya gasps)
Mm, yummy.
Come on, open up.
(Nastya grunting)
(upbeat music)
(Nastya sighs)
Phew.
Daddy!
(dad snoring)
Daddy, open it, please.
Hey, daddy!
Open it, please.
Be careful this time.
(upbeat music)
- Okay, I will.
(dad grunting)
- Come on, come on!
Open it like this.
- Okay, let's try.
(sighs) Everything's fine.
(Nastya laughing)
(children chuckling)
(Nastya chuckling)
Hmm, not bad.
I like it.
- Oh, my.
(cheerful music)
- Nastya! Wake up, wake up, wake up.
- What happened?
- We hit 50 million subscribers.
(horn blows)
- Yay!
(gasps) We need a big party today.
(upbeat music)
(doorbell chimes)
- Mm?
Oh!
(Nastya chuckles)
- Huh?
(man gasps)
(upbeat music)
- (gasp) Uh-huh!
(Nastya panting)
- I need to dress up.
- [Audience] Wow!
Cool!
(Nastya gasps)
(upbeat music)
Cool!
- (gasps) It's for me?
- Yes, yes.
(calm music)
- Yeah.
(doorbell chimes)
(all gasp)
- Candy!
- Yay!
(door knocking)
(Nastya gasps)
- Ice cream!
Ice cream, who wants ice cream?
(upbeat music)
- Me, me!
- Me, me, me!
- Okay.
For you.
For you, and for you.
- Thank you.
- Guys!
(cheerful music)
- Me, me!
- Me, me, me!
(suspenseful music)
(all gasp)
(Nastya gasps)
(enchanted music)
(upbeat music)
- Ta da!
- Me, me!
- Me me me.
- Pick me!
(Nastya gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(cheerful music)
- Wow!
- [Onlooker] Oh my God!
(upbeat music)
- Ta da!
(audience applauding)
- Wow!
(Magician laughs)
- No, no, no, no.
- No, no, no, no!
- You!
- Huh!
Oh, no.
Uh-oh!
(Magician laughs)
(guest grunts)
(all gasping)
- [All] More, more, more, more!
(upbeat music)
- [Audience] Wow!
(all clapping)
- Wow, Bravo!
- Kids, time to eat.
(kids cheering)
- [All] Food, food, food, food!
Food, food, food, food!
Food, food, food!
Huh?
No, not today.
Food, food, food, food!
Food, food, food, food, food!
No!
- No, we want cake!
- [All] Cake, cake, cake, cake!
Cake, cake, cake, cake!
Hooray!
(upbeat music)
(Nastya gasps)
- [Dad] Rainbow.
- [Audience] Wow!
(all applauding)
- Yay!
- Bravo!
- [All] Bye-bye.
(Nastya gasps)
(cheerful music)
- This is for me.
- No, it's for me.
- Mine! Mine!
- Mine!
- No, no, no.
Do you want to have a challenge?
- Yeah!
- Find all of these shapes.
(upbeat music)
(water bubbling)
One, two, three,
go!
(upbeat music)
- Huh?
This way.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Wow!
(cheerful music)
(Nastya gasps)
- Oval!
Yay!
- Next, go!
Woo!
(girls laughing)
- Oh!
(upbeat music)
(gasps) I found it.
Diamond!
(calm music)
- [Audience] Cool!
Ew!
(snakes hissing)
(both screaming)
- Blah!
- Ew!
(upbeat music)
(Stacy gasps)
Triangle!
- Circle!
Yay!
- Yay!
- Next.
(upbeat music)
- [Audience] Wow!
- Ready? Set? Go!
- Uh-mm!
- Uh-m!
(calm music)
- No.
- (gasps) Square!
- (gasps) Ooh!
Heart!
Wow.
- Finished!
(playful music)
- [Audience] Wow!
- Just one?
- At least you had fun.
(ominous music)
- Let's share!
(girls giggling)
(ominous music)
(Nastya chuckles)
- Yeah!
(upbeat music)
Yay!
(cheerful music)
- Wow!
(bunny chuckling)
(girls gasping)
- [Audience] Wow!
- (gasps) A Barbie dress.
- Ooh, a Princess dress.
(upbeat music)
(Nastya gasps)
Hmm.
- Hmm.
(ominous music)
(girls chuckling)
- My princesses.
- Hmm!
(upbeat music)
Ooh!
I need hot water.
(upbeat music)
Ta Da!
(Nastya gasps)
Hot water!
(water bubbling)
Hair.
I love Barbies.
- Hmm, my turn.
(Nastya gasps)
- Wow!
(upbeat music)
(Princess mimicking bubbles)
(Nastya gasps)
- [Audience] Wow!
(car honks)
Hmm, Barbie is better.
(Nastya mimicking bubbles)
- Hmm?
No, princesses are better, uh-hmm.
(cheerful music)
(horse neighing)
- Hmm.
Ta da!
(upbeat music)
(Nastya gasps)
- Uh-hmm.
Here.
Nails and lipsticks.
(upbeat music)
- Pets.
(dog barking)
(water bubbling)
(dog barks)
(Nastya gasps)
- Uh-hmm.
(horse neighing)
(Nastya gasps)
- Hmm!
(gasps) No more!
That's not fair.
You have big toys, and I have small toys.
- Hmm.
- Give it to me!
- No, it's mine!
- Please!
- No!
- Give it to me!
- No, it's mine!
Mine!
- [Stacy] Mine!
(Nastya gasps)
(Stacy gasps)
- [Both] They disappeared.
- Okay, let's play together.
- Yeah!
Yeah, let's share!
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Do you guys share toys?
- You need to share.