(playful music)
(Stacy hums)
- Ready.
(playful music)
They're chocolate.
Daddy.
Daddy, let's have an
edible/inedible challenge.
- [Dad] Okay, I'd love to.
(rock music)
(mouse clicks)
- [Stacy] Potatoes.
- [Dad] Potatoes.
(rock music)
- [Stacy] Well, let's try it.
- [Both] Uh-huh.
(teeth crunch)
- Ew.
- Mm.
- I have a cake.
- Hmm?
- Do you want it?
- Yeah. Do you want mine?
- [Stacy] No.
- [Dad] No.
(teeth crunch)
- [Both] Mm.
(suspenseful music)
- This is mine.
(whimsical music)
- Lemon? They're so sour.
I don't like them.
(teeth crunch)
(upbeat music)
It's cake, mm.
- A lemon.
(Dad laughs)
(sad music)
- Ugh, so sour.
Ugh, you're so lucky.
(mouth slurps)
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
(upbeat music)
- [Stacy] An egg.
- Egg?
- It's a real one.
- Mine must be chocolate then.
Mm-hmm.
(teeth crunch)
(egg yolk plops)
Ew. (spits)
- Ew.
Then mine is a cake.
(upbeat music)
(teeth crunch)
Mm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Hmm.
- [Both] One, two, three.
- [Dad] Let's do it.
(upbeat music)
Onion.
- [Both] One, two, three.
(teeth crunch)
(whimsical music)
(Dad cries)
- Yeah.
(teeth crunch)
(magical music)
Chocolate.
(Stacy laughs)
(Dad cries)
- [Both] Mm-hmm.
(both gasp)
(suspenseful music)
- Uh-oh.
- This is gonna be hot.
(teeth crunch)
(Dad moans)
(upbeat music)
(teeth crunch)
- Mm, chocolate.
(fire sizzles)
Ah!
(extinguisher sprays)
Whew.
- Hey, I want a piece of chocolate.
(teeth crunch)
(mouth slurps)
Mm, phew, ooh.
- Come on. Come on.
- Mm.
- Come on.
- Oh, corn.
- Corn.
(upbeat music)
- Ah!
(teeth crunch)
It's okay.
It's a real one.
(teeth crunch)
- Mm? (sniffs)
(mouth slurps)
Mm, it's cake.
(whimsical music)
- Oh.
- It's parsley.
- [Dad] Parsley.
(mouths smack)
- Hmm, it's so-so.
- Mm, candy.
- A candy?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
(whimsical music)
(mouth smacks)
Daddy, choose a newspaper.
- Hmm, mm?
This one.
- Okay, Daddy. Uh-huh.
Mm, sweet.
(Dad gasps)
(teeth crunch)
(Dad coughs and spits)
- It's real.
Oh, my stomach.
(Dad groans)
(whimsical music)
- Oh. I know.
(techno music)
(Stacy hums)
(bell jingles)
(door creaks)
- Stacy, hello.
- I brought you some cakes.
- [Both] (gasp) Mm.
(rock music)
- Uh-huh.
(kids gasp)
Sweet potato.
(mouth slurps)
Mm.
- Ah.
(teeth crunch)
(Stacy laughs)
(kids spit)
- Ew.
- Ew, Stacy.
(potatoes thump)
- It's a joke.
- [Both] Hmm.
- Take these chocolate lemons.
- Wow.
(teeth crunch)
- Mm.
- [Friend In Pink] Mm.
(teeth squeak)
Stacy.
- Stacy.
- Ew. It's sour.
- Ugh.
(Stacy laughs)
- Choose one.
- I'll take this one.
(teeth crunch)
- Mm. Chocolate.
- Mm? (cries)
(both laugh)
- Who wants some pepper?
- [Both] Hmm.
- Hmm?
(teeth crunch)
(upbeat music)
Mm, it's chocolate.
- Mm.
(teeth crunch)
Ouch, it's hot.
(both laugh)
Hmm.
Ouch, my stomach.
(friend in orange groans)
- Not anymore.
- No more.
- Hm?
Ah.
(hands clap and rub)
(whimsical music)
- Ah! Mm.
Yummy.
(whimsical music)
Ah!
(mouth slurps)
Ah.
- No, no, no, no.
Did you clean your room?
- Just a second.
(upbeat music)
Done.
Done. May I try it?
(classical music)
- [Kids] Wow.
- Here.
- Oh, well. Thank you.
(fork squeaks)
Mm.
- Mm.
(lid pops)
(playful music)
(gumballs rattle)
- Ah! Mm, yum, yum. yum.
- Mm.
(magical music)
(gumball rattles)
(Stacy gasps)
Have you done anything productive?
- I'll do it now.
(upbeat music)
Uh-oh.
(suspenseful music)
(Stacy grunts)
Hmm.
I know.
(upbeat music)
Yay.
(Stacy giggles)
(suspenseful music)
Uh-oh.
(upbeat music)
(magical music)
Nice.
(whimsical music)
I did everything, Daddy.
- Good job. Go ahead.
(whistling music)
(Stacy gasps)
- No, no, no.
- Mm.
- One's enough.
- Oh, well, thank you.
(playful music)
- [Kids] Cool!
(door creaks)
(Stacy gasps)
- Chocolate. Mm.
- [Dad] Tasty.
- Ah.
(buzzer buzzes)
- Hey! Hm.
(sad music)
Mm-mm.
- Just a second, please.
Don't eat it without me.
(upbeat music)
(duster wooshes)
(water splashes)
(vacuum whirs)
(objects thump)
(bubbles pop)
(upbeat music)
(cat purrs)
(tired music)
I've done everything.
- [Dad] Hmm, good job.
Come here, come here.
(stomach growls)
- I'm hungry.
- Here you go.
- Ah!
(teeth crunch)
- Mm.
- Want one?
(teeth crunch)
(head thumps)
(lullaby music)
(Stacy snores)
- Tricks.
(upbeat music)
(Stacy gasps)
Hocus pocus.
Here I go. Whoops.
(whimsical music)
- Oh, oops.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauds)
Bravo. (claps)
- Bippity, bobbity, boo.
- [Kids] Wow.
- Ooh, wow. (claps)
- Bippity, bobbity.
(cat meows)
(audience applauds)
- Oh! Mm, mm-hmm.
Mm, mm-hmm.
(sad music)
(hand taps)
- Bippity, bobbity, boo.
- [Kids] Wow.
- Bippity, bobbity.
Boom!
- Oh!
- Hmm.
(sad music)
- Ow!
- A hole.
La, la, la, la.
(kids laugh)
Hello, kids.
(sad music)
(kid laughs)
- Why would you do that?
Put it back to normal.
Come on, I want my body back.
Why did you do this to me?
- Hocus pocus.
- [Dad] Uh!
- Yay!
- Phew.
- Woo-hoo!
Bippity, bobbity, boo.
Higher, higher.
- Wow.
Ah!
- More, more.
Boom.
(Dad laughs)
(audience applauds)
Come on, come here.
(Dad claps)
Put your hand here.
(arm squeaks)
(fingers tinkle)
(lock squeaks)
(fingers tickle)
Uh-huh.
Ah-hah.
- (gasps) No, no, no, no, no.
(dad screams)
Aw.
(sad music)
Uh-oh.
- Yee-haw.
(magical music)
- Phew.
(oven mitt flutters)
(confetti plops)
- Bippity, bobbity, boo.
- [Kids] Wow.
(whimsical music)
(fast upbeat music)
(Dad groans)
(kids laugh)
(playful music)
- Hocus pocus.
- Hey there, kids.
(kid laughs)
- [Kids] Oh, no.
- Nice.
(playful music)
(head pops)
Oh, bravo. (claps)
- Come here.
(magical music)
You try it.
- Oh, okay.
Bippity, boppity, boo.
(gasps) Where are you?
- [Stacy] Cuckoo.
- Wow. Amazing.
- Bye. Fantastic.
(Dad claps)
- [Clown] Hey, what's this?
- (gasps) What is it?
(clown laughs)
- (gasps) So interesting.
What's inside?
(foot thuds)
- No, no, no.
(Stacy gasps)
Hey, money first.
(coins jingle)
- Okay.
Here you are.
(upbeat music)
(coins jingle)
(clown laughs)
He's so weird.
What's inside?
Ah!
Ah, wow.
Mm.
- [Clown] Uh-oh.
(water drips)
(Stacy gasps)
- The roof is leaking.
Oh.
(phone beeps)
(phone rings)
The roof is leaking here.
- [Clown] On my way.
- Ah. Oh, no.
(clown laughs)
Look.
The roof is leaking.
- (laughs) I can fix it
for a price.
(coins jingle)
- Hmm. All right.
(upbeat music)
(tools rustle)
- (laughs) All done.
- Mm. (laughs)
(birds tweet)
(poop plops)
Huh? (sniffs)
Ew.
(phone beeps)
(phone rings)
- Hello.
- Come here. Faster.
- On my way.
(magical music)
- Yes, yes, yes, please.
(clown laughs)
(coins jingle)
- Mm. All right.
- (laughs) Ew.
(upbeat music)
(clock ticks)
All done.
- Ah! Mm-hmm.
(clown laughs)
Ah! A spider.
(Stacy screams)
- [Kids] Oh, no.
(clown laughs)
- (gasps) Spider.
- Uh-huh.
♪ Do, do, do, do, do, do ♪
(laughs) What happened?
- A spider.
(clown laughs)
(coins jingle)
- [Stacy] Mm?
(sad music)
(coins jingle)
There.
- Hey, spider.
Come here. Where are you?
Mwah, mwah, mwah. My cute spider.
- Ew.
(clown laughs)
Phew.
(sad music)
(rain patters)
Ah, ah!
Oh, no.
Hey, wait. Come back.
- Huh?
(whimsical music)
- [Both] Hooray.
- Oh.
- Oh, no.
(whimsical music)
- [Both] Hooray.
- [Stacy] Aw.
- [Clown] Aw.
- (cries) My house.
- Hmm. It must be the evil witches spell.
- What should I do?
- I can help you.
(coins jingle)
- Oh.
The last one.
Mm.
(clown laughs)
(coins jingle)
Woo-hoo.
(magical music)
- Ah! My house.
(sad music)
Hmm.
- Oops.
- Hmm. Gimme my money back.
(clown laughs)
(radio static buzzes)
(upbeat music)
♪ Girls and boys ♪
♪ Let's take your toys ♪
- Hm.
♪ Take them to the bath ♪
- Here.
♪ Where we'll wash your toys ♪
- Hm.
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
♪ Just take a bath ♪
(Stacy giggles)
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
- Ah!
(water gurgles)
♪ Just take a bath ♪
- Woo!
♪ We've just begun ♪
♪ Dum, dum, dum ♪
♪ So let's go mum ♪
(bath bombs plop)
♪ Let's make lots of bubbles ♪
(water gurgles)
♪ And have more fun ♪
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
- Stop.
♪ Just take a bath ♪
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
- [Kids] Yay!
(Stacy laughs)
♪ Just take a bath ♪
♪ Blue, green, and red ♪
♪ Just take that paint ♪
♪ There are so many colors ♪
♪ It looks so great ♪
- Wow!
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
♪ Just take a bath ♪
- Mm.
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
♪ Just take a bath ♪
♪ Now, my friends ♪
♪ Let's wash your hands ♪
♪ Let's take a soap and careful ♪
♪ Wash your hands ♪
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
- Ta-da.
♪ Just take a bath ♪
♪ Let's take a bath ♪
♪ Let's ♪
(dramatic music)
(Dad thumps)
- Oh, no.
- Ow.
- [Kids] Ew.
- (gasps) You need to take a bath.
Music.
(upbeat music)
♪ Taking my bath ♪
♪ I'm taking my bath ♪
- Hm.
♪ Bubbles and boats ♪
- Wow!
♪ I'm taking my bath ♪
♪ Divers and ducks ♪
♪ I am taking my bath ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Kids] Cool.
♪ Splashing my hands ♪
♪ I'm splashing my hands ♪
- Aw!
♪ Bubbles and boats ♪
(Stacy laughs)
♪ I'm splashing my hands ♪
♪ Divers and ducks ♪
♪ I am splashing my hands ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Singing my song ♪
♪ I am singing my song ♪
♪ Bubbles and boats ♪
♪ Divers and ducks ♪
♪ I am singing my song ♪
- Bye, bye.
(techno music)
- Ah, oh!
Hello.
- [Kid] Hello.
- Can I have one?
- I'm sorry, but no, it's mine.
- Mm. I know.
(upbeat music)
(spoon taps)
(Stacy laughs)
(upbeat music)
(flour plops)
Some milk.
(milk pours)
Hm, it's a bit watery.
(upbeat music)
They're gonna be tasty donuts.
Mm-hmm.
(clock ticks)
- [Kids] Wow!
(upbeat music)
(Stacy hums)
- Ah, mm.
Can I have some?
- Let's change.
- [Kid] Let's.
- Here.
(upbeat music)
Ah! Hooray.
Thank you, bye.
- Bye.
Mm.
(teeth crunch)
Ah!
(dramatic music)
Mm.
Ew.
(whimsical music)
- Wow.
Ah! It's golden.
Wow.
I love slime.
(kid hums)
- Wow.
- Wow,
Can I try it?
- Mm-hm.
No, no. Give it back.
I have only one.
- Mm.
I know, wait here.
I'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
(straw gurgles)
It's a good bag.
Ah, milk.
(gulps) Ah.
Ah, Chanel.
Oh, here it is. Just what I need.
Hmm.
(techno music)
Look.
- Yes, yes.
- Mm. Thank you, bye.
- Mm, thank you.
(kid gasps)
- [Kids] Ew!
Ah!
- Wow. (gasps)
Look.
(Stacy gasps)
(kid giggles)
Aw.
Wow, eye shadow.
(whimsical music)
(upbeat music)
(Stacy gasps)
Ah! Mm-mm.
Not happening.
(whimsical music)
Mm.
(magical music)
Mm-hm.
(techno music)
(kid sniffs)
- Hello.
- (gasps) Hmm.
(feet stomp)
(dramatic music)
Nobody has this one.
Mm.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
(audience cheers)
(cameras snap)
- Ah!
Wow. Can we also have this?
- Of course, let's go.
Here.
And, the T-shirts.
- Ah, wow.
So cool.
- [Stacy] Here, and this one.
- Yes. Thank you.
- [Both] Mm.
- There's one more.
(upbeat music)
- [Kids] Wow.
(audience applauds)
- [Both] Bye, bye.