(cheery music)
- Let's go camping!
- Yes.
The main thing is not to forget anything.
(zippers zip)
(cheery music continues)
- Awesome!
(elephant trumpets)
(Stacey's dad humming)
(monkeys chattering)
- Dad, I'm tired.
- Uh-huh, me too.
Let's take a break.
- Dad, I wanna eat.
- (gasps) We forgot!
(Stacey cries)
There!
(upbeat music)
(Stacey's dad thuds)
(Stacey's dad groans)
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no!
(Stacey gasps)
- Dad!
This is for you, sweetie.
(birds chirping)
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- [Chipmunk] Nice.
- Eat this.
(Stacey and Stacey's dad munching)
- Look, it's almost night.
(children cheer)
(cicadas chirping)
- Welcome!
- I found marshmallows!
(fire roaring)
- [Chipmunk] Yummy.
(Stacey's dad screams)
(Stacey gasps)
(Stacey's dad whining)
(Stacey munching)
- Mm.
Oh, it's mine!
(Stacey's dad whines)
Oh!
(Stacey dad sniffles)
- [Chipmunk] Woo-hoo!
- (gasps) It's time to get some sleep.
- Yeah.
(happy whistling music)
(cheery night music)
(Stacey's dad snoring)
(ants munching)
(Stacey's dad screams)
- What happens, Dad?
(Stacey's dad grunting)
- Whoa!
(Stacey's dad sniffling)
- (sighs) Daddy, Daddy.
(wolf growling)
- Boy.
- Oh.
Hey, get in the tent.
- Oh my God.
(wolves howling)
(zipper zips)
- So, let's go home.
- Let's go.
(broom rustling)
- Whew. (gasps)
- Wanna be a princess?
Call and visit us now.
(Stacey gasps)
(broom and dust pan slam)
- Hello?
I wanna be the princess.
- [Person on Telephone] Just come.
- Go.
(Stacey gasps)
Wow!
- [Child Audience] Wow!
Wow.
(gasps) Dresses.
- (gasps) What a beauty!
(hand slaps)
- Mm-mm, mm-mm.
Come in.
(Stacey humming)
- [Child Audience] Ew.
- Pew.
What do you want?
This?
- Uh-uh.
- This?
- Mm-mm.
- (gasps) Yes, yes, yes!
- Sit down, honey.
(Stacey gasps)
(Stacey humming)
(spider snickers)
(stylist gasps)
- Ew!
Ew!
- [Child Audience] Ew!
- Ugh.
(cheery music)
(Stacey gasps)
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- Uh-oh.
(Stacey gasps)
- [Child Audience] Aww.
- What have you done?
It's over.
You can't be a princess.
- [Child Audience] Aww.
Cool!
- I want this one.
- Put on this dress!
(gasps) Wow!
- [Child Audience] Yay!
(Stacey gasps)
Wow!
(intense suspicious music)
(Stacey gasps)
(cuckoo chirps)
(stylist gasps)
(stylist groans)
- Get up.
I said, get up!
Hey.
Get up!
Let's try Belle's dress.
(Stacey gasps)
- Hi, I'm Belle.
- [Child Audience] Wow!
(the Beast roaring)
- (gasps) It's the Beast!
(the Beast roars)
(Stacey screams)
(Stacey screaming)
(the Beast roaring)
(the Beast growling)
- Phew, he's gone.
(gasps) I wanna be the Snow White!
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- Finally, you've become a princess.
(child audience cheering)
Oh.
(stomach grumbling)
- I wanna eat.
- Okay.
(Stacey munches)
- Uh-oh.
(glass shatters)
Uh-oh.
(Stacey giggles)
- You can't be a princess!
Get out of my salon!
("Baby Shark" playing)
(Stacey giggling)
(bubbles popping)
(Stacey and Stacey's father gasp)
- Breaking news.
Children's YouTube is being shut down!
(Stacey and Stacey's father gasp)
Children are crying all over the world.
(baby crying)
They're not eating, they're
not studying colors or numbers.
(news caster sobs)
(baby crying)
- [Both] Oh, no!
- (gasps) What will happen?
(glass shatters)
- Eat, sweetie.
- Fasten your seatbelt.
- There isn't a Stacey channel anymore.
- (gasps) I won't eat anymore.
- Stacey, what letter is this?
- (sighs) I don't know.
- And what number is this?
- I don't remember.
(balloon blowing)
- Name these colors, Stacey.
- I don't remember.
- [Chipmunk] Uh-oh.
(balloon pops)
(Stacey gasps)
(children crying)
(Stacey crying)
- Breaking news!
(Stacey gasps)
(Stacey's dad gasps)
Kids' YouTube is back!
Hurray, friends!
- Yay!
- Hurray!
(alarm rings)
(Stacey's dad gasps)
(Stacey's dad screams)
(children laughing)
- Stacey, what letter is this?
- W!
- Correct!
And this one!
- S!
Stacey, name these colors.
- Pink, yellow, (gasps)
red, purple, green.
- Correct!
(child giggling)
- A gift for you.
(Stacey gasps)
- Thank you!
(gasps) Cinderella's dress.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hi, I'm Cinderella.
(magical tune)
(mud spattering)
- [Bert] Uh oh.
(Stacey gasps)
(mud spattering)
(cat meows)
(Stacey gasps)
- Huh?
(gasps) I must clean a job.
(cloth squeaking)
Whew.
- [Chipmunk] Woo-hoo!
- Whew, I'm tired.
I don't want Cinderella's dress anymore.
- Yeah, I agree.
(Stacey groans)
- Here.
- (gaps) Ariel.
(cheery music)
- Beautiful!
What's happening?
(Stacey gasps)
(children laughing)
(gasps) Stacey's a fish!
- Not fish, but mermaid.
(gasps) Water, water!
I can't breathe!
- What do I do?
What do I do?
Come on, Stacey.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
(tail boinging)
Hurry up!
Come on, come on, come on!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
(victorious tune)
(water hisses)
(water plopping)
- [Child Audience] Hurray!
- Whew, I don't wanna be mermaid anymore.
- Let's go, fish.
Look what else I have.
- (gasps) A wig.
Wow.
(magical tune)
- (gasps) Beautiful!
Thank you.
- [Audience] Aww!
(ice creaking)
- (gasps) Oh!
(hair dryer blowing)
(Stacey's dad shuddering)
- This one doesn't suit us either.
(Stacey giggling)
Look what I found.
Who's it?
- This is Mary Poppins.
- Well, okay.
Hello.
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- Great!
(magical tune)
- Oh!
(drums rolling)
(Stacey slams)
- Ooh.
(Stacey groans)
(hat thuds)
(umbrella slams)
- Would you stop with the presents?
- Okay, let's play then.
(Stacey's dad babbling)
- You come back.
(Stacey giggling)
(Stacey's dad munching)
- Mm, carrots.
- [Both] Smash like!
- Bye!
- Bye-bye!
(Stacey gasps)
- I'm a big girl.
(telephone rings)
(Stacey gasps)
Hello, tell me.
- [Person on Telephone]
Stacey, we need your help.
Quickly, to the base!
- (gasps) Okay!
Duty calls.
Go!
(dog barks)
("Bingo" plays)
(tires screech)
Let's find out who needed help.
- Help me, help me!
(fire roaring)
(children screaming)
(Stacey gasps)
- Let's go!
Hold on, I'm coming.
(tires screech)
(fire extinguisher blows)
(fire roaring)
Yay!
- Phew, it's time to eat.
Mm.
- Let's go back!
(telephone rings)
- Hello, who's this?
- [Person on Telephone]
Stacy, can you help again?
- Yes.
Well, who's in trouble?
(house rumbling)
(house crashes)
- [Child Audience] Aww.
- Help me, help me.
- (gasps) Wait!
I will save you!
Wait me!
Whew, just sit here for a while.
- Done!
(victorious music)
Whew, it's time to eat.
Mm. (giggles)
Wow!
- [Marshall] Help me, help me!
- (gasps) I will save you.
Hmm.
- [Child Audience] Ew!
(Stacey gasps)
(police sirens wailing)
- [Chipmunk] Uh-huh.
(Stacey shushes)
(criminal snoring)
- Give up!
(criminal gasps)
It's police!
You are under arrest!
(criminal gasps)
Go to jail!
- Well, all right, all right.
- Come on!
Get in, hurry.
Hmm, well done.
- Ow!
- Hey, you are free to go.
- Good job, Stacey.
- [Child Audience] Yay.
♪ Nanny nanny boo boo ♪
- (gasps) Presents.
(coins clinking)
I found it!
Yay!
(bubbles popping)
Don't forget to put like.
Bye.
(Stacey snickers)
(car engine revs)
(car horn honks)
(engine revving)
(child giggling)
(car horn honks)
(gasps) Oh!
- [Chipmunk] Oh.
(car thuds)
(walls cracking)
(Stacey gasps)
(footsteps stomping)
(Stacey's dad groaning)
(gasps) Sorry!
- You can't drive in the house.
(Stacey whines)
Let's go play outside!
- [Child Audience] Yay!
- Yes!
(hammer slamming)
(Stacey dad groaning)
(Stacey groaning)
(water splashes)
- Ow.
(Stacey laughs)
(Stacey dad groaning)
(water splashes)
(Stacey giggling)
(water splashing)
- Stop!
I'll catch you!
Stop, stop!
♪ Nanny nanny boo boo ♪
(victorious tune)
Uh-huh.
(water sprinkles)
(Stacey gasps)
(water splashes)
(Stacey dad laughs)
- Humph.
Hold on.
(Stacey dad laughs)
(child laughing)
(Stacey snickers)
- (laughs) You crazy!
(Stacey giggling)
(metal clanking)
- Cuckoo!
(children laughing)
(metal clanking)
Cuckoo!
- Come on.
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
(children laughing)
Now it's your turn.
Let's.
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
(children laughing)
(bubbles popping)
One, two, three!
(chipmunk snickers)
- Wow!
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- Rock, paper, scissors!
(buzzer buzzes)
Rock, paper, scissors!
You go first!
- [Chipmunk] Woo-hoo!
- Yay!
- Ha-ha!
- Ha-ha, foo!
- Oh, no!
Hmm.
Right now.
(Stacey's dad groaning)
(bowling pins slam)
(Stacey's dad spitting)
(Stacey laughing)
- How terrible.
- You go!
- Yay!
- Yeah, clear.
Yu-bee!
- Look how it's done.
- [Chipmunk] Woo-hoo!
- Nastya wins!
Only play outdoors.
- It's good for your body.
Bye!
- I'm the best.
- No, I am.
- No, I'm the best.
(Stacey groans)
(Lava groans)
(footsteps stomping)
- Stop, stop.
Enough.
Stop, that's enough.
(Stacey and Lava groaning)
Oh, I announce a competition.
(Stacey and Lava gasp)
- Aha.
- Hmm.
- Ha.
- One egg.
- Hmm.
(Stacey snickers)
Extra sugar.
- [Child Audience] Wow!
- Aha!
(waffle maker hisses)
- [Chipmunk] Fantastic.
(Stacey and Lava humming)
- Done!
Ew.
Look!
- Done!
- Mm.
Mm.
Tasty!
(chipmunk laughing)
Mm.
- [Chipmunk] Woo-hoo!
- What is this?
Ew!
- [Chipmunk] Ew.
Good.
Now, the drawing competition.
- [Both] Mm-hmm.
(cheery guitar music)
- Ah, easy.
(cheery guitar music continues)
(Stacey snickers)
- [Both] Done!
♪ Ta ta ra ra ♪
- Here's mine.
- It looks wonderful.
- [Chipmunk] Woo-hoo!
- And it's mine.
- (gasps) Mm-mm.
- Yay!
Yes!
- And now, a beauty contest!
- [Child Audience] Wow!
(Stacey and Lava gasp)
- It's mine!
- No, its mine!
- No!
- Oh, exactly.
I have this one.
(cheery whistling music)
(gasps) Now I'll do makeup.
- [Child Audience] Ew!
(Lava snickering)
- So girls, are you ready?
- [Both] Yes!
- Nice job!
(Stacey's dad gasps)
(Chipmunk laughs)
No, no, no, no, no!
- [Chipmunk] Good.
- The last contest.
- [Stacey] Contest of magic!
- Do some magic, Stacey.
(whimsical tune)
(tiger roars)
(gasps) Wow!
Amazing!
Do magic, Lava.
(whimsical tune)
(frog croaking)
- (gasps) Oh!
(whimsical tune)
(Stacey's dad gasps)
- Wha-
Huh?
No, no, no, no, no.
And the results.
(victorious tune)
And the prize is, friendship!
Yeah!
(children cheer)
- Let's be friends and never quarrel.
- Okay.
- [Both] Bye!