- [Nastya] Mm.
- (blender noise)
- Mm.
- (mumbling on the phone)
- [Nastya] (humming)
- (gasps)
- Mm.
(lighthearted music playing)
- [Nastya] (humming)
(drumming)
(gasps)
- Mm. You've got candies here.
- Give me this one.
- Hmm.
- Oh,
- (Nastya humming)
- Surprise.
- [Nastya] (gasps)
- Mm mm. let's trade.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- It's empty.
- Dad.
- [Nastya] (grunting)
- Blue color. Blue color.
Where are you? Here I am.
- Mm.
- It's empty.
- (gasps) he ate the candies too.
- Hmm.
(playful music)
- Mm.
- [Nastya] (giggles)
- He he he.
- [Dad] (groaning in pain)
- [Nastya] (gasps)
- You must go to the hospital.
(ambulance noises)
(knocks on the door)
- Sit down.
- What is the problem?
- My stomach.
- Oh. Oh,
- (gasps)
- You need an injection.
- Uh oh.
- [Dad] (groaning in pain)
(cheering)
- Don't eat too many sweets again.
- Uh huh, got it.
- (laughs) Bye.
(bell ringing)
- Hi.
(sigh noises)
(playful music)
- Okay.
- [Nastya] (evil laughing)
- (wow)
- [Nastya] (eating noises)
- (grunting)
- He he he.
(laughing)
(happy cheering)
- [Nastya] (eating noises)
(sniffing)
- Ah huh.
(laughing)
(cheering)
(grunting)
(wow)
- [Nastya] (eating noises)
- Ah huh
(whistling)
- What?
- Ah huh
- (grunting)
(laughing)
- (oooh)
- (kids laughing)
(hooray!)
- [Nastya] Uh oh.
(writing noises)
(cool cheering)
- [Nastya] (eating noises)
(sniffing)
- Hm, chocolate?
- Hm.
(laughing)
(grunting)
- Huh?
(evil laughing)
(blows up bubble)
(POP!)
- [Teacher] (gasps)
(lightening strikes)
- Hmm.
- [Nastya] (sighs)
(bag drops on floor)
- [Teacher] (gasps)
- Uh oh.
- Time out.
- Sorry.
- Ahh.
- Bye bye guys.
(playful music)
(laughing)
- (mirror laughing)
- Ew.
- [Mirror] Uh oh
- (crying)
- I am not pretty.
- (door squeaks open)
- (gasps)
- Nastya, what happened?
- (Crying)
- (mirror laughing)
- All right, I'll call a beauty salon.
- (phone ringing)
- I will call a hairdresser.
(phone ringing)
- They didn't answer.
(crying)
- Okay. We'll do it on our own.
- [Audience] Oh, no.
- Hmm. Brush your hair now.
- I'll go get the nail polish.
(horse walking sounds)
- Dad, oops.
- (gasps)
- Phew.
- Sweetie, you should
brush your hair carefully.
- Hmm.
- This one.
- And now makeup.
- Hmm?
- [Nastasya] (crying)
- Now paint your nails using this makeup.
(happy music)
- This one.
(kittens meow)
- Ahh. Kittens.
(kittens purring)
- You're my pretty little things.
(kissing sounds)
- So, have you done your nails?
- Uh Oh.
- (gasps)
- (mirror laughs)
- You should be more careful, sweetheart.
- Now I'll help you.
- (yawns)
- (snoring)
- Hmm.
- That's it. It's ready.
- Where are the dresses?
- Hmm?
- You do makeup. I'll go get the dresses.
(playful music)
- Here, pick a dress.
- (gasps)
- [Audience] (gasps)
- Who does makeup like this?
- You shouldn't apply too much makeup.
- Mm hm.
(chimes and music)
- (blows kiss)
- Choose one.
- Hmm, mm mm.
- How about these?
- Next?
- (gasps)
- What about shoes?
- Okay, put the dress on
and I'll get the shoes.
- (struggling noises)
- Nastya.
- [Audience] (laughs)
- (happy music)
- [Audience] Cool.
- Hmm?
- These ones.
- [Audience] Wow.
- I'm so beautiful. I must go to a ball.
- Do we have a coach?
- We do.
(happy music)
- Get in.
(dramatic loud music)
- The coach won't move.
- (big sigh)
- (humming)
- Yeah.
- Holidays. Woohoo.
- Holidays.
(piano playful music)
- Ahhh.
- Let's go.
- (playful laughing and music)
- Daddy
- Huh?
- Did we forget anything?
- No, we forgot nothing.
- (laughs)
- Wow.
- Let's go Nastya.
- Come on.
- (gasps)
- Hey, wow.
- Hey
(laughs)
- Ooh.
- Oh.
- Wow.
(ghost noises)
- (Gasps and slams door)
- Mm.
- Look. Look.
- Wow.
- Cool.
- (water splashing sounds)
- (gasps together)
- [Audience] Wow.
(playful whistling and music)
- Look.
- (humming)
- Ouch!
- A surprise.
- Wow. Mm.
- Mm.
- (gasps)
- A surprise.
- (munch munch munch)
- Hmm? Ice cream.
- No. No. No.
- What's this?
- (gulp sounds)
- (raining sounds)
- [Nastya] (screaming)
- (yawns)
- La la la la.
- What's in this room?
- (gasps) Cats.
- A cat.
- and another
- (gasps)
- [Nastya] And one more
- 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
- (snoring)
- Wow.
- (meow)
- (gasp)
- (meowing cats)
- Huh?
- A cat.
- (meow)
- Cat.
- Another cat.
- (cats meowing)
- (screams)
- Cats.
- (gasps) Cats.
- I remember we forgot the cats at home.
- (gasps)
- (cats meowing)
(dramatic music)
- Let's go. Let's go.
- (cats meow)
- Well now that's all.
- Let's go.