(upbeat instrumental music)
(girls laughing)
(monster roaring)
- [Group] Ah!
- Shh.
- [Kids] Wow!
- Yeah!
(girls snoring)
- Uh oh!
(spider squeaking)
(girls screaming)
- [Group] You come here right
now, we'll teach you a lesson.
- [Narrator] Oh, no.
(door creaking)
- [Group] Aha.
(girls whispering)
(girls laughing)
- Huh?
- I'm a mermaid.
- [Group] Arden, don't
be upset, take this.
- Thanks.
- [Kids] Wow.
(girls laughing)
- Oops.
- Who did this?
- Oh, it was her, she did it.
(cat mewing)
- How could you?
- Phew.
- [Narrator] Uh-oh.
- Yummy, yummy.
- Phew.
Nastya, Nastya?
- Aha.
♪ Do do do ♪
♪ Do do ♪
- Did you eat the last ice-cream?
- It's the cat, it's all her.
- My goodness, you're such a naughty cat.
- [Kids] Oh, no.
Ooh!
- I won't clean it.
- Oof, ow, ow,
oh, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ooh!
- [Kid] No!
- Oh no, no, no, no.
- Nastya, who did this, huh?
- It wasn't me.
- [Narrator] Oh, no.
- My nose, my fingers.
Daddy, help me.
Daddy, it's me.
Wait for me, wait.
- Uh-oh.
- Daddy, where are you?
- Shh.
- Daddy, dad, where are you, daddy?
- [Dad] Oof.
(knocking on door)
- Daddy, come out here, shh.
(door creaking)
- Ah, monster, ah!
- Daddy, it's me, I'm
your daughter, Nastya.
- Huh, Nastya?
(Nastya crying)
You lied to me, didn't you?
You shouldn't lie.
- I'm sorry, I won't do it again.
I'm so sorry.
- [Kids] Yay!
- Yeah, kids, never tell lies.
Let's play, let's go, come on.
Daddy, please.
- Nastya, I'm busy.
Here, take this.
- A gift, let's go, come on.
- Here you go.
- Chocolate, daddy, let's go.
- Oh, we need a nanny.
Hello, do you have nannies?
Send one right away.
(knocking on door)
(door creaking)
- Hello.
- Come on in.
Okay, I'm gonna go back to work, bye.
- Oh, what a sweet little girl, bye, bye.
- Let's play.
- Oh, ooh, hey.
- Let's go play.
- Darn it.
- [Kids] Oh, no.
- Clean it up.
- I won't do it, it wasn't me.
- Okay, daddy?
- Clean it.
- Ew, uh-huh.
- Come with me.
- What are you doing, what are you doing?
Please stop.
- Woo, daddy?
- So what happened now?
- Daddy, daddy, it was her.
She was like, she threw
the toys around like.
- Are you evil?
- [Kids] Ah.
- Alright, now clean this up quickly.
- Bye, bye.
(dog barking)
- [Narrator] Oh, no.
- Ew!
She's sleeping, I'm going
to record everything.
- Such a bad girl, I'm gonna
teach you a lesson, stay there.
- I've recorded everything.
Daddy, daddy, watch this.
- Huh?
- Stay there.
- I'm so sorry, honey, let's go.
Hey, get up.
- What happened?
- You're fired, get out.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
It was all her.
- No, it was all you, leave.
- It must be a mistake.
- Bye, bye.
- Yeah, it's a simple mistake,
guys, it's a mistake.
- Bye, bye.
- Good riddance.
- Let's go play, honey.
- Let's.
- Let's go.
(upbeat instrumental music)
(Nastya sneezing)
- Bless you.
(girls screaming)
- I got you.
- [Group] Stop.
- Who are you?
- I'm a virus.
- Are we sick?
- [Group] No, we're healthy.
- No, you're not.
- [Kids] Oh, no.
(monster laughing)
- And now, you.
- [Group] Oh, hello.
- It's itching.
- [Group] Oh no, I'm so scared.
- And now it's time
for the scariest thing.
- Can I have some?
I'm thirsty too.
- You're mine now.
- I know, we need sanitizer.
- And a mask.
- We're not scared anymore.
- [Group] Yay!
- Hello.
- [Group] Stop.
- Give your hands.
- [Narrator] Yeehaw.
(upbeat instrumental music)
- [Kids] Hooray!
- Good job.
- I want ice-cream.
- [Kids] Yay!
- Okay, we don't have ice cream.
Let's buy ice-cream.
- [Kids] Ah.
- Closed.
- I want an ice-cream.
- [Kids] Ah.
(kids laughing)
- [Kids] Yay.
- We will make ice-cream.
(blender whizzing)
- [Kids] Yay.
(timer ringing)
- Not tasty.
- Ow!
(kids laughing)
Okay, ow!
- Uh-oh, I want an ice-cream.
- [Kid] Ah.
Hooray, yay!
(blender whizzing)
Yay!
(timer ringing)
- [Kids] Hooray.
- Not tasty.
- Okay.
(upbeat instrumental music)
- [Kids] Ew.
(blender whizzing)
- [Kids] Hooray.
- Broccoli ice-cream?
- [Kid] Ew!
(blender whizzing)
Ew!
(clock ticking)
(timer ringing)
- [Kids] Yay!
- Is it tasty?
- No.
- No, no?
- [Kids] Ah.
- Don't worry, daddy.
I'll do it myself.
- [Kids] Yay.
- I like chocolate ice-cream.
- Nailed it.
- [Kids] Yay.
(blender whizzing)
(timer ringing)
- [Kids] Yay.
(clock ticking)
(timer ringing)
- It's over.
- [Kids] Yay.
- Delicious.
- Yummy.
- The best ice cream.
- No, the best of the best ice cream.
- [Kids] Hooray, ew!
- Let's play a joke on dad.
Daddy, come here.
- Yes?
- [Group] Tasty.
- You wanna try?
- Yes, ooh.
(girls laughing)
This is a bad joke, guys.
- [Group] Sorry.
- [Kids] Ah.
- I have an idea.
(kids laughing)
- [Kids] Ah.
- Daddy.
(kids laughing)
- Oh, no, oh, no,
oh, no, I loved this.
- [Kids] Ah.
- Daddy.
- [Kids] It's a joke.
- [Kids] Yay.
- Joke, it's a bad joke, guys.
- [Group] Sorry, daddy.
- [Kids] Ah.
(girls whispering)
- [Kids] Cool.
(kids laughing)
- Yummy, daddy, come here.
- What?
- It's yummy.
(kids laughing)
- You wanna try?
- Yes.
(kids laughing)
- Okay, oh!
- Is it good joke?
- No, it's not good joke.
- [Kids] Oh.
- We're gonna make slime.
- Yeah.
- [Kids] Yay.
Hooray!
- Slime.
(kids laughing)
- [Kids] Oh, ew!
Oh, no, ah.
- [Group] Yummy, uh-oh.
- Don't move, stop.
- [Group] Don't worry, daddy.
- Why are you eating slime?
- Haha, it's edible slime.
- [Kids] Yay.
- Yes, it's yummy slime.
Good joke.
- Now it's my turn to do joke, girls.
- [Group] Huh?
- [Kids] Ooh.
- How did you do it?
- This is a good joke, you understand?
- [Group] Yes, okay.
(girls whispering)
- Daddy, come here.
- Are you doing jokes again?
- Yes, look.
- [Kids] Ah.
- [Group] Let's try.
(kids laughing)
- How did you do it?
- It's so easy.
(kids laughing)
- Wow, it's a great joke.
Great joke.
- [Kids] Hooray, yay.