(Santa Claus gasps)
(Messenger notification tune)
(mailbox pops)
- I see.
Okay.
(back cracking)
(Santa Claus groaning)
Oh, what should I do?
(elves snickering)
Oh, the elves!
(orb whirring)
(whimsical tune)
- [Both] Wow!
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
All right, enough fooling around.
Deliver the gifts.
- [Both] Uh-huh, uh-huh.
- Oops.
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
(gift bonks)
- How about we open it?
- [Both] Uh-huh, uh-huh.
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
- Wow!
- [Child Audience] Cool!
(bubbles popping)
- Hurray!
- [Child Audience] Yay!
- [Both] Hurray!
(child audience cheering)
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
- Ooh.
(box pops)
- A bed.
(Stacey and Lava humming)
(cheery music)
(tires screech)
(box bonks)
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
(tires screech)
- [Both] Everything's done!
- Everything's done!
- [Both] Done.
- Well done!
Here, have some candy.
- Thank you!
(Stacey and Lava humming)
(girl humming)
(girl gasps)
- Yay!
(child audience cheers)
- [Child Audience] Aww.
(girl cries)
(telephone rings)
(Santa Claus gasps)
Oh.
Hello?
- Hello?
Santa, I've just received the
gift, and it was empty. (sobs)
- (gasps) What?
I'm so sorry.
Just a moment.
Of course.
Hey, you.
Come here.
(Stacey and Lava gasp)
What have you done?
Give me the candies back.
- Hmm.
- Deliver the gift, and quickly.
Hmm!
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
- Oops.
(gift bonks)
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
(tires screech)
Turn it on.
- [Both] Hmm, we can't go on.
- Ah, it's okay.
- Let's open this one, too.
- Yes.
(Stacey gasps)
- [Child Audience] Cool!
- Wow, what a bus.
(bus horn honking)
- [Both] Aha.
- It's a swimming pool!
(water splashing)
- Yahoo!
(water splashes)
- [Both] Wow!
Move it.
(Stacey and Lava giggling)
Everything's done!
- Well done.
Here are your candies.
- [Child Audience] Yay!
- Wow!
Yay!
(girl groans)
(girl cries)
(telephone rings)
- Hello?
- Hello, Santa.
The box is empty again.
What is this about? (sobs)
- (gasps) What?
Again?
Hmm.
How could you!
(Stacey and Lava gasp)
Deliver this gift, quickly!
(Santa Claus grumbles)
(yawns) Oh, I'm so tired.
(Santa Claus snores)
- (gasps) He's asleep.
- Let's open it right here.
(Stacey giggles)
(gift wrapping rasps)
(Stacey and Lava shush)
Wow!
(gift wrapping rasps)
(Santa Claus snoring)
- [Both] Wow!
(children giggling)
- [Audience] Wow!
- Hmm?
(gasps) Uh-oh.
(Stacey and Lava humming)
(Santa Claus growling)
(Stacey and Lava gasp)
(Santa Claus gasps)
(Santa Claus groans)
- Uh-oh.
- [Both] Uh-oh.
- All these elves.
- No, no!
Oh, no!
No!
(Santa Claus grunts)
I have to do everything myself.
("Jingle Bells" by James Pierpont plays)
Ho ho ho ho ho ho!
- [Child Audience] Yay!
(twinkling tune)
- Hey, girls.
What's up? (gasps)
(Evelyn and Stacy gasp)
(Evelyn and Stacy cry)
Oh my gosh.
Sorry, sorry.
(Evelyn and Stacy crying)
Don't be upset.
Here are some toys for you!
- [Both] Mm-mm!
(Evelyn and Stacy cry)
- I also have these!
- [Both] Humph!
- Oh!
Mm-hmm.
(Evelyn and Stacy gasp)
- Hmm?
(Stacey chomps)
Mm!
Would you like some?
- Mm-hmm.
(Evelyn chomps)
Mm.
(Stacey groans)
- I can't open it.
Hmm.
Mm!
(Stacey chomps)
Mm-mm!
- Give it to me, please.
- Here.
(Evelyn chomps)
- Mm.
(Stacey chomps)
- Hmm.
- [Both] More!
- More!
- More, please!
- Okay.
(Evelyn and Stacy gasp)
- Shoes!
- So beautiful!
(Stacey gasps)
(Stacey groans)
Hmm.
Is it chocolate?
(Stacey chomps)
Mm!
- [Both] It's made of chocolate!
- Mm.
- [Both] Yay!
(Evelyn and Stacy gasp)
- Crayons!
Hmm, they're real.
I'll draw a kitten.
- Hmm.
Hmm.
(Evelyn chomps)
(drum beats)
(cymbals clash)
Hmm?
- Mua, mua.
- [Both] One, two, three. (gasps)
Hmm.
- A teapot.
(Stacey chomps)
Ew.
Mm, tea.
- Hmm.
(Stacy sniffs)
(Stacey chomps)
Mm!
(Evelyn chomps)
(Evelyn and Stacy gasp)
- [Both] Lipstick!
- A pen!
(Evelyn gasps)
- It doesn't work.
(gasps) It's a lollipop!
Mm.
(Stacey gasps)
- [Both] Tasty!
Hmm, interesting!
- You called?
- Would you like to try it?
- It's a tasty fork.
(Stacey chomps)
- Hmm, yes.
- [Both] Have a try!
(Artyom groans)
(Evelyn and Stacy laugh)
All right, here's some for you, too.
(Artyom chomps)
- Mm.
- [Both] Let's build a tower!
- Let's build a tower.
- Hey, everyone!
(everyone gasps)
(everyone groans)
- [Child Audience] Aww.
- Oops!
(Stacey's dad and Stacey laughing)
(bee buzzing)
- [Chipmunk] Oh, no.
(flies buzzing)
Oops.
(Stacey's dad and Stacey gasp)
- Ew!
- Ew, gross!
Disgusting!
- Ew!
- Ew, ew!
- [Chipmunk] Yahoo!
(spray fizzes)
- Get out of the house!
- [Cockroach] Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
- It's cleaning time!
- Hurray, cleaning!
(cat meows)
(vacuum cleaner whirring)
(Stacey humming)
(cloth squeaking)
- [Both] Whew.
- Oh.
(spider squeaking)
(Stacey's dad and Stacey gasp)
- [Both] Spiders?
- (gasps) Oh, no!
(spiders squeaking)
Oh, no, no, no.
- Oh, no, no.
It's gone too far.
- Cleaning time!
(water spattering)
(spiders squeaking)
- [Spider] Uh oh.
(water spattering)
- [Both] Yay!
(victorious tune)
(Stacey groans)
(stomachs grumbling)
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm, yummy.
(person groans)
(mouse squeaking)
- Hello.
- Ew!
(Stacey's dad exclaims in disgust)
It's time to clean!
(avocado thuds)
(flies buzzing)
Ew!
(cloth squeaking)
(Stacey humming)
Shoo, shoo!
(flies buzzing)
- What are these?
(Stacey's dad and Stacey gasp)
(door creaks)
(wings flapping)
(Stacey gasp)
- [Chipmunk] Uh-oh!
(spider chomping)
- What?
- It's time to clean!
(Stacey humming)
Hey!
(Stacey's dad gasps)
- Cool!
- (sighs) I'm so tired.
- Phew!
(Stacey's father sighs)
- [Both] Ants!
(Stacey screams)
- So many!
- Ants!
- Lift it up.
(Stacey's dad gasps)
- [Chipmunk] Wow.
- And what's this?
- Oops, cleaning time!
(Stacey groans)
(foot stomps)
Daddy.
Daddy!
(foot stomps)
- I'm here, I'm here!
What's wrong?
- Today, I'm a princess!
- (gasps) What kind of princess?
- A stolen one.
(Stacey's dad gasps)
- Bring me a dress.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Huh.
Here, I brought some dresses.
- Pink?
I can't stand pink!
Black!
- (gasps) All right, all right.
- Hurry up, Dad.
(cat meows)
- Here, here you are.
(magical tune)
- Ha ha ha.
It will do.
- Your crown, your majesty.
- And now, dance!
(Stacey's dad gasps)
(upbeat disco music)
(person laughing)
Mm-hmm.
(upbeat disco music)
(Stacey's dad panting)
(Stacey snoring)
(Stacey's dad gasps)
(Stacey's dad shushes)
(Stacey gasps)
(staff stomps)
Stop!
(Stacey's dad yelps)
I'm hungry!
- Hm, got it, got it.
Here you are, princess!
- Ew, bleh!
- Maybe you'd like chicken with eggs?
- Hm, no!
- How about a tuna sandwich?
- Ew, bleh!
- Maybe a pizza?
(Stacey sniffs)
- Very well.
- Phew.
- Oh, I'm full.
Hey!
Bring me a prince!
(Stacey's dad grumbles)
- Oh!
Get down here, get down here!
I'll make you a prince.
- Hmm, okay.
Ooh, let's go, let's go!
- Look, I brought you a prince.
- Hello.
Come here!
- (gasps) No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
Take it back.
Bye-bye.
(Stacey's dad cries)
- What's wrong?
(Stacey's dad sighs)
- I can make her laugh.
This is what girls like.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm!
Phew.
- Hello!
Look what I brought!
- Hmm.
Have you brought them for me?
Humph.
Humph!
- (gasps) Oh!
(Evelyn screams)
(Stacey's dad chomping)
- (gasps) No, I can't let that happen.
- So, are you bringing me a dress or what?
- Listen, princess, have
you done your homework?
(Stacey gasps)
- Then you'd better get started.
- Mm-hmm.
- (scoffs) If you're the princess,
I'm a king!
(staff stomps)
(Stacey's dad groans)
- (gasps) Oops.
(Stacey grumbles)
- And here's the snow!
- [Audience] Aww.
(feet stomping)
- This snow isn't real.
(Stacey groans)
- And here's a snowman!
(chipmunk laughs)
- Beep beep.
He also isn't real.
(Stacey grumbles)
- Ah!
- (gasps) Snowballs!
(groans) These aren't real either.
- [Audience] Aww.
(sad piano music)
(cheery music)
- Mm-mm!
- I have an idea.
Stacey, let's go look for snow!
- (gasps) Hurray!
(airplane roaring)
(gasps) Where's the snow?
- There, there.
Ready?
Look!
- Wow!
- [Audience] Wow!
- Faster, Daddy!
Put it on!
- It's your hat.
Here.
(Stacey giggles)
- Yeah!
(gasps) Snow!
- It's real!
Woo-hoo!
(Stacey giggles)
Wow, real snowballs!
- Hurray!
(upbeat snowy music)
Daddy, you're leaving me behind!
- (gasps) Oh.
(Stacey yelps)
(Stacey screams)
- [Stacey's Dad] Woo!
- Cool!
(upbeat guitar music)
- [Chipmunk] Ooh!
(audience cheering)
- Let's go swimming!
- Let's go!
(Stacey inhales)
(Stacey giggles)
- Hello!
(upbeat violin music)
Whoa!
(Stacey yelping)
Ice!
- No, no, no, no, no, Stacey.
It's not a lollipop or a candy.
No, no, no, Stacey.
- Oh, shh.
(Stacey shushes)
- (gasps) No!
What are you doing?
- I love snow.
- Oh, what now?
- Shh, bye-bye!
(pen scribbling)
All right, it's ready.
- Mine too.
(Stacey gasps)
- Ho ho ho ho ho ho ho!
Merry Christmas, everybody!
Ho ho ho!
(items rumbling)
(Santa Claus yelping)
Ooh.
(birds chirping)
(Stacey's dad gasps)
(Stacey gasps)
- Presents!
Which present is whose?
- Yeah.
- Oh ho.
(Stacey gasps)
- I didn't ask for this.
(child audience laugh)
(Stacey giggles)
- Wow!
- Hmm?
- Ooh!
- (gasps) I wanna try it too, Daddy!
- Woo!
- I wanna try it too, Daddy!
(gasps) May I try it, please?
Give it to me, please.
Please.
- It's for adults only.
(Stacey cries)
(gasps) Hey, hey, don't be sad!
You can play with these!
(Stacey gasps)
Whoa.
Whoa!
- Ooh.
Ooh!
(Stacey sighs)
There are more gifts.
And another one.
(Stacey gasps)
(cat meows)
(toy bonks)
- Hmm.
(Stacey gasps)
- [Audience] Wow!
- Wow!
- What do you think of my costume?
(children laughing)
- Daddy.
One, two, three!
Let's light the tree!
(upbeat festive music)
- [Chipmunk] Woo-hoo!
(children laughing)
- (gasps) Let's keep opening the presents!
I'll open this one.
(gasps) Chocolate!
Oh, it's broke.
(Stacey chomps)
Mm.
- Hmm.
Look!
(gasps) Yummy!
- Yum, yum!
(Stacey munching)
- Mm, wow!
That's great!
You asked for a good gift.
- Mm-hmm.
- For the toilet?
Ew!
I didn't ask for this.
- (gasps) That's mine!
Give it here, please.
Here you go.
Just like I wanted!
- [Audience] Aww.
(Stacey's dad humming)
- (giggles) Oh, daddy.
(Santa Claus snoring)
- Huh?
(Santa Claus gasps)
(Santa Claus shushes)
- Oh, it was probably nothing.
- Probably.
What else do we have?
- What?
You asked for sushi for the new year?
- Not at all.
They're socks for the new year!
- Let me try the sushi.
They're such cool socks!
(Stacey gasps)
- Wow!
Yeah, pull it!
Oh.
(dinosaur boinging)
Ooh!
(stomach grumbling)
- Oh, I'm so hungry.
(Santa Claus gasps)
(Santa Claus munching)
(stomach grumbles)
(Santa Claus gasps)
My stomach, it hurts!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
- There are no more presents!
- (yawns) Let's go to bed.
- Yes, and the dog, too.
- Let's go.
- (gasps) They're gone.
Oh, oh.
(Santa Claus gasps)
Phew.
Oh, okay, children.
Wait for me patiently and
I'll bring your gifts.
(Stacey giggling)
- [Camera Person] Oh!
(Stacey clapping)