- Hmm.
(bright musical notes)
(girl gasps)
(chimes ding)
(horn blows)
(worrying music)
(slide whistle blows)
Dad.
(bright musical notes)
(sound effects)
(bonk noises)
- [Children] No.
- Okay, I'll change it now.
(bright musical notes)
(drumming musical notes)
This?
(bright musical notes)
- Nuh-uh, mm-mm.
(music notes continue)
- This?
- Mm-mm.
(buzzer sound)
(bright music)
This?
(phone ringing)
- No, no, no.
(whomp sound effect)
- Hmm.
Oh, idea.
(bright musical notes)
- Hmm.
(whistling music)
- Here.
- Hmm.
(boing sound)
(pillows laugh)
(laughter continues)
No, no, no.
Hmm.
(musical notes)
(bright music)
- Ow.
(ding sound)
- It's uncomfortable.
(jolly music)
(dad grumbles)
(chime sound)
(upbeat music)
(sewing machine whirring)
(victory horn blows)
- [Children] Wow.
(dad snores)
- Fantastic.
(chime sound)
(bright musical notes)
Here.
- Mm, thank you.
(bonk sound)
(twinkling musical notes)
(downcast musical notes)
(horn sound)
(deeper and longer horn sound)
Really, it's uncomfortable.
(drumming sounds)
(sad horn sound)
(musical notes)
(bright music)
(dad gasps)
- Oh
(chimes)
(snores)
(clap sounds)
(snores continue)
(sneaky music)
- Shh
(snores continue)
(musical notes)
(bear grumbles)
(dad screams)
(bonk sound)
(boing sound)
(bear grumbles)
(dad sighs)
- Here take it.
(girl sneezes)
- hmm umh
(musical notes)
(trumpet sound)
(bright music)
- Oh no.
(dad exclaims)
(cherry music)
(laughs)
Gimme.
(whomp, whomp, whomp notes)
Gimme, gimme, gimme,
Gimme, gimme.
(ominous music)
(buzzer sound)
(ominous music continues)
(musical notes)
Run.
(doll cries)
- Say hi.
(as toy) Hello.
- Here. Look.
- Ah.
- Here, take it.
- But I don't like red pillow.
- Hmm.
Here, take it.
- Yes.
(happy music tones)
(small ding sounds)
Well, how to sleep on this?
(drumming sounds)
- Ow.
- Well bring some more.
(instrumental Itsy Bitsy
Spider begins to play)
Hmm.
(dad sighs & hums)
(upbeat music)
- Aha.
(buzzer sound)
(girl gasps)
Stay where you are.
(police sirens)
Listen, you have committed a crime.
- Hmm.
(bright music)
- Ah.
You are under arrest.
(whomping sound effect)
(background menacing laugh)
(musical tones)
- Uh oh.
- Okay. You are free to go.
Get out.
(winding sound effect)
No, no, no.
(musical notes)
(dad breathes)
(girl gasps)
- Lie down. Lie down, daddy.
(bonk sound)
Sorry. Dad. Have a rest.
I realized that I was misbehaving.
I shouldn't behave like that.
Wow.
(chime sound)
(chiming sounds)
(piano sounds)
- Whohoo
(squeaking sound)
- [Children] Wow
(girl laughs)
(bonking sounds)
(upbeat music)
- Fantastic
- Yow
(girl laughs)
(music continues)
- Hello to you. And you. And you.
- Hi.
Bears.
(she gasps) Pigs
(pig snorts)
(both snort as pigs)
(she gasps) It's a pig.
- [Children] Wow
(bonk sound)
(upbeat music)
(girl sneezes) Uh choo
(dad sneezes)
(dad sniffs and sneezes)
(girl sniffs & sneezes) Uh choo
(girl laughs)
(upbeat music)
Wow.
(music continues)
(girl laughs)
Help.
(upbeat music)
(woohoo in background)
(bright whistling music)
(kissing sounds)
(bell dings)
(warbling sound)
(bird twitters)
(musical notes)
- Ow.
- Dad, come on.
(squeezing sound)
(ding)
- [children] Yay
- Thank you.
(girl laughs)
- Who's there?
(chicken clucking)
(laughing)
(makes monkey noises)
(gulping noise)
- Hmm.
(angelic harps)
- [children] Wow
(upbeat music)
(computer sound effect)
Hmm.
(horse neighs)
(horse clucking)
(chime sound)
(music continues)
(buzzer sound)
- Ugh.
- Ugh. It's a turd.
(flies buzzing)
(upbeat music)
(groovy music plays)
(chimes)
(girl laughs)
(dad laughs)
(instrumental Head,
Shoulders, Knees & Toes plays)
(swing squeaks)
(girl laughs)
(music continues)
(piano notes)
(boing sound)
- Yeehaw
(bonk sound)
(long bonk sounds)
(music continues)
(video game sound effect)
- I love you.
(different groovy music plays)
(dad laughs)
Oh how many Stacy's are there?
(drumming sounds)
(chime)
- [Children] Wow
(swipe sound)
(girl laughs)
(instrumental Itsy, Bitsy Spider ending)
- Uh oh
(boing sounds)
(long boing sound)
(slurping sound)
(eating sound)
(decreasing musical notes)
(children laughing)
(eating and slurping sounds)
(instrumental Old MacDonald plays)
- Ehyah
- Bye bye.
- Bye.
(music continues and slowly fades)
(upbeat music)
- Hmm
(twirling sounds)
(gasps) (whistles)
(chimes & cheers)
- [Children] yay
- Take it all out.
- Okay.
(upbeat music)
Come on. Come on, come on. This way.
Quicker. Quicker.
(music continues)
(chime)
(squeak sound)
(music continues)
- Uh oh.
(laughter)
What are you doing? Put me back.
(music continues)
(ripping sounds)
(cheers & chimes)
(chime) Wow
[All] Goodbye
(swoosh sound)
- Hmm. Daddy.
(snoring)
(whistles)
(poof sound)
(upbeat music)
(spray sound)
(music continues)
(celebratory chimes)
And now...
Bed.
(jaunty music plays)
(girl laughs)
- It's me here.
(swipe sound)
(gasps)
(children laugh)
(wooble sound)
(boing sound)
(bonk sound)
[Children] Yay
(music continues)
(bonk sound)
(struggling moans)
(music continues)
(dad laughs)
(girl laughs)
(music changing)
(dad sneezes)
(children laugh)
- And a special mirror for makeup.
(squeak sound)
- This one? No, no, no, no.
Daddy. I need a larger mirror.
- Right now.
Be careful.
- [Children] Wow.
- It's so beautiful.
(music continues)
(girl gasps)
(plink sound)
(revelry horns)
- Where to? Where to?
It's here, please.
(upbeat music)
That's right.
- [Children] Wow
- Muah (kissing sound)
♪ Do you wanna build a snowman? ♪
♪ I never see you anymore. ♪
- Where is dad?
- Cuckoo.
(both laugh)
(cherry music & chimes)
(children laughter)
(kissing sounds)
(swoop sound)
(music fades)
(new upbeat music plays)
(bonk)
(bonk) (bonk)
(children laugh)
(bonk)
(girl laughs)
(bonk) (bonk)
I need a wardrobe.
(music crescendo)
- Oh, I am tired.
(girl gasps)
- Idea.
(bell dings)
(upbeat music)
(glass crashes)
(blending whirring)
(music continues)
(machine whirs)
(girl laughs)
(triumphant music)
(slurping sound)
(springy bong sound)
- Hmmm
(chiming pop)
(powering up magical sound)
- [Children] Yay
- Hmm
(fast paced upbeat music)
(slow magical music)
(music continues)
(magical chimes)
(girl gasps)
- [Children] Wow
(cat meows)
(music continues)
- There is Elsa.
But there is no Anna.
(buzzer sound)
(wondering ding)
- You will be Anna.
- Me? No, no, no, no, no.
- Yes, yes.
- No. Noooo
(jaunty musical notes)
(swoosh & children laugh)
(record scratch)
- Stacy. (angry grunt)
- I like this.
(bell chimes)
(cat meows)
(robotic whirls)
(ball boings)
- Hello Stacey. Let's
go play in the street.
- Cartoons.
(robotic whirls)
(hand swipes)
(bell chimes)
- Buenos noches, senora.
(party music)
(maracas shake)
(music and clapping)
(swirling bonk)
(music continues)
- Cartoons.
(sad whooping)
(babies cry)
- Stacey help me. They're crying.
- All right.
(instrumental nursery rhyme plays)
- She's sick, Stacy.
- She just needs to be turned off.
(baby cries)
(plunk sizzle)
Let's see.
(baby plonks)
(baby cries)
Just
(fabric tears)
turn off.
Let's see it.
(stroller plonks)
(musical notes)
(twinkling notes)
(various bonking)
Cartoons.
(robotic whirling)
(twinkling notes)
- Brush my hair.
Brush me.
- Dad. Don't be a baby.
(bonk)
- Please?
- Well, okay. Just fast.
(dad grunts & grumbles)
(dad yells)
(whirling sounds)
- Is it all?
(negative notes)
(boing)
(robotic whirling)
(twinkling notes)
(paper rustling)
(dad plops)
(girl laughs)
(crunching sound)
- Mmm mmm.
What a tasty ice cream.
(crunching sound)
Mmm.
I have to end it.
(robotic whirring)
Now, I'll cut off the internet.
(machine crackles)
(robotic whirring)
(girl gasps)
- Daddy.
Daddy.
It's not funny.
Dad, where are you?
- [Children] Yes
(wrapping crackles)
(girl laughs)
- Yes.
- Let me help you.
- Yes. Let's.
(bell chimes)
- Wow.
- Now it will be slime.
Oh, it's green.
(children laughter)
- You did it.
Wow. What a beautiful color.
(children laughter)
- It's slimy.
Oh, slimy slime.
(robotic whirls)
(magical music)
(phone rings)
- Hello.
I'm busy.
I'm playing with my daughter.
- What is it?
How do I look?
- Beautiful.
- [Children] Wow
- Now, I go to bed.
Guys don't watch cartoons too much.
It is better to play with your parents.
Do you agree, Dad?
- Huh? Yes. Yeah.
Goodbye.
- Bye bye.
(magical chimes)
(pig oinks)
(car honks)
(upbeat music)
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
(toy honks)
(girl gasps)
- Oh, it isn't broken.
Hmm. I'm starting the experiment.
(twinkling chimes)
(light chimes)
(bell chimes)
(twinkling chimes)
(upbeat music)
(toy plonks)
Let's, what happens?
(button chimes)
(toys swish)
Hey, the, toys aren't broken.
And the next experiment.
(music continues)
(musical chimes)
Hmmm.
(toy crackles)
(toys squish)
(toys squeak)
(toys laugh)
(toys yell)
Uh oh.
(twinkling chimes)
(laughter)
(birds twittering)
(toys yell)
Wow.
(toys plop)
(girl laughs)
(toys creak)
It isn't broken.
(toys skit erring laughter)
Go.
(toys yell)
(toys quack)
(toys plop)
(toys pop)
(plop) (plop) (plop)
Hmm.
(toy wobbles)
- It's empty. I'm going to dad.
(twinkling sound)
(upbeat music)
(slurping sounds)
- Ooh.
(creaky footsteps)
(hand bonks)
- Where are you taking those?
- It's for my experiment.
- Hmm. Let's go take a look.
Let's go.
(swoosh)
- Hey, look.
(upbeat music)
(candies pop)
- Wow. So cool.
Let's try this one.
- Okay, put it down.
(music continues)
Let's.
- Un hunh.
(items squash)
- Cool. Let's smash this one too.
(item whines)
- Yoo-hoo.
(car revs)
(item crunches)
- Awesome experiment.
- That's right guys.
- Bye-Bye.
- Bye.
(game sounds)
- Dad, today I'll be your
mother and you'll be my baby.
(children laugh)
Stay here.
And banana turned into the eggplant.
And my soup is ready.
Baby, come eat.
(game sounds)
Go eat quickly.
(gasps) Un huh.
(upbeat music)
Eww.
- I forgot bread.
(twinkling steps)
Mmm. Bread.
(gasps)
He's gone.
Daddy?
Hmm?
Bad.
Daddy.
(chime)
Hey.
(ghosts moan)
Ew.
Daddy.
Oy!
Daddy. Daddy.
Hmm? Who's in the car?
(children exclaim)
No, no, no. Go with soup quickly.
- Hmm.
(disappointed music)
Come on.
Open wide.
Here comes the train.
Good job. Open wide.
- Oh no.
- Well done. You ate it all.
You got dirty. Change your clothes.
(clothes honk)
- Here. I changed my clothes.
- No, no, no.
Look.
(bell chimes)
(children laugh)
What a beauty.
Go play.
- Where to?
- You need some balls.
- La la la.
La la la.
- And Pacier, of course.
- Maybe we should.
(grunts)
- Wait for me.
- Hmm? I don't wanna play anymore.
(upbeat music)
(warbling sounds)
(dad plonks)
(TV whirls)
(girl laughs)
- TV. No, no, no, no.
It's time to get some sleep.
- Ah, well, okay.
- Nice.
Here.
Sweet dreams my baby.
- Ah.
- I'll read you a story.
Well listen.
Once upon a time.
(baby yawns)
(girl snores)
- Nice.
(twinkling steps)
(baby yawns)
- Oh, he is gone.
(foot stomps)
- Ah, ah, ah.
(baby cries)
- What's going on here?
- Ah, the baby is crying.
He needs his mommy.
- Let, lemme take them.
Ah. And you go away not to disturb me.
- Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
(dad cheers)
- Ah, ah, ah.