[eerie music]
(male presenter, off)
There is a fifth dimension
beyond that
which is known to man.
It is a dimension
As vast as space
And as timeless as infinity.
It is the middle ground
between light and shadow
between science
and superstition
and it lies between
the pit of man's fears
And the summit
Of his knowledge.
This is the dimension
of imagination
It is an area which we
call The twilight zone.
[music intensifies
Dramatically]
[cheerful music]
Right here,
Ladi es and gentlemen,
Special july clean up sale!
Lovely things,
Calamine lotion,
Good for sun-burns!
How about binoculars?
(male presenter, off)
Street scene
Summer, the present.
Man on the sidewalk
Named Lou Bookman.
Age, sixtyish.
Occupation, pitchman.
Lou bookman,
A fixture of the summer.
A rather minor component
To a hot july.
A nondescript
Commonplace little man,
Whose life is a treadmill
Built out of sidewalks.
In just a moment,
Lou bookman
Will have to concern
himself with survival.
Because as of 3 o'clock
This hot july afternoon
He'll be stalked
by mr. Death.
[ominous music]
[cheerful music]
[lou iaughs]
(chiidren) Hi, Lou!
(lou) Hello, darling!
Oh, here, here.
Oh, my goodness,
It is hot today!
Yeah.
Let's sit down.
What are you
selling today, lou?
Toys, lou?
Are you selling toys?
I'll show you What I
was selling. [chuckies]
There's one for you.
Thanks, lou!
That's alright, maggie.
Here, ricky.
Thanks, lou!
Now the lou bookman
Social and ice cream hour
Takes place
Right after supper.
The regular
Turn now!
Don't forget!
Good bye.
(chiidren)
Bye, lou.
(lou) Don't forget
The ice cream, huh?
[humming]
[intense ominous music]
You're, you're the man I saw
on the sidewalk today.
You were writing
In a book.
You are lou bookman,
aren't you?
That's right.
Louis J. Bookman,
Is there something
I can show you?
Maybe something In collar
stays? I'll get that.
No, mr. Bookman.
I'm not here to buy anything.
Now let's get
To business, shall we?
Louis J. Bookman,
Aged 69, right?
I'll be 70
In september.
Hm. Occupation,
Pitch man, right?
Yeah, that's right.
[chuckies]
Are you
A census taker?
Born in new york
City in 1890.
That's right, 1890.
Father jacob bookman,
Mother flora bookman.
Father's place of birth,
Detroit, michigan,
Mother's place of birth
Syracuse, new york, right?
That's right. My
goodness, [chuckies]
You got it all down
In that book there.
Yes, we have to keep
these things efficient.
Now today
Is the 19th of july.
And your departure's
At midnight tonight.
My departure?
[knocking at door]
Oh, excuse me.
Hi, maggie!
The key's bad, lou.
Can you fix it?
Oh, sure,
Come on right in!
Come on in.
(chuckies)
Let me see it.
Well, there's your
trouble right there.
See that little cogwheel?
Well, you've been pushing in that key
when you were winding it. You see?
See? Now
It's all right.
See?
I'd introduce you two, only I
don't know your name.
No need.
I think I got it
Now, lou.
This gentleman came here to
ask me a lot of qu estions.
What gentleman?
[ominous music]
That gentleman!
What gentleman?
(mr. Death) Mr. Bookman,
she can't See me or hear me.
Why not?
Why not what, lou?
Why can't you
see him or hear him?
See who, lou?
It works great now, lou.
Thanks an awful lot.
See you after supper, huh?
Now wait a minute. You
haven't forgot your manners.
Aren't you gon na
Say goodbye?
Oh, yeah. Good bye,
lou. Thanks a lot!
No, no, I mean
To the gentleman there.
Oh, it's a gam e.
The invisible man.
Goodbye, invisible man.
See you
After supper, lou.
[suspense music]
I can see you,
yet she can't.
(mr. Death) Only those who are
To accompany me can see me.
Understand, Mr. Bookman?
Uh, mr. Bookman,
Only those who are
To accompany me can see me.
Now don't you think you ought to
start making your arrangements?
Arrangements?
For what?
For your departure.
My departure where?
[sighs]
You just don't get it.
I just will never
understand you people.
You get the idiotic notion
That life goes on forever.
Of course, it doesn't.
Everyone has
To go sometime.
Go? You mean--
That's right. And what I
further don't understand
How little you appreciate
The nature of your departure.
Think of all the poor souls who
go in violent accidents.
The non precognition victims.
We're not permitted
To forewarn them.
You, mr. Bookman,
fall into the category
Of "natural causes."
"natural causes?"
Number one, I find you
A very devious sort,
Number two,
I think that
you're dishonest.
Number three, Why don't
you say what you mean!
Mr. Bookman, I've done everything
but phone your own undertaker.
How much clearer
Do you want it?
If you still
don't know who I am
Then you're the dumbest
man I've come up against.
[intense ominous music]
You are--
You're death?
Exactly, mr. Bookman.
Now, shall we get
down to business?
Time of departure
Is midnight tonight.
I trust that
will suit you.
Preordination is
for death during sleep.
I assume this too will
meet with your approval.
You'll find this a relatively
Simple and painless--
No, just a minute.
I don't wanna go!
No, they never do.
But there's no reason to go.
I'm a very healthy man!
Outside of a slight cold
I had last winter,
And a sliver that festered
In that finger there,
I don't think i've had
A sick day in 20 years!
That may be,
But departure time
Is set for midnight.
And departure
Will be midnight.
Don't I have anything
To say about that?
We do listen to appeals
But frankly, mr. Bookman,
There's very little here
In the way of an
Extenuating circumstance.
There are three major
Categories of appeals.
One, is hardship cases.
Now do you
Have a wife or family
Who might su ffer beyond a
reasonable point Your dem ise?
[softiy]
No, no family. No.
The second category
Is priority cases
Statesmen, scientists, Men
on the verge Of discoveri es.
I take it you're not working On any major
scientif ic Pursuit at the moment.
[softiy]
No [chuckies] no.
[firmiy]
What's the third category?
I don't think you're
Qualified here either.
Unfinish ed business
Of a major nature.
You don't have Any unfinished
Business, do you?
Ah, but i do!
Indeed i do!
That's it,
You see. I-- yeah.
I have some
Unfinished business.
Unfinished business, yes.
I've never flown
In a helicopter. That's it.
I've never flown--
(death)
Insufficient, mr. Bookman.
Anything else?
Now you look here. I've lived
in this Room for 2 1 years.
And you keep popping up in corners of
the room I've never even seen before.
Will you please
Stay in one place?
Is there anything
Else, mr. Bookman?
Yes, yes.
I have never seen
A zulu war dance.
Now that's
The answer right there.
So you'll have to give Me a couple of
months to go Over to that zulu cou ntry
No?
No. Unfinished business
Of a major nature
Is something a man
Had yearned for
And something He m ight
accomplish Given an extension.
Well, there is one thing.
What is it, mr. Bookman?
Well, between you and me,
I never made
A truly big pitch.
I mean, i mean
A big pitch.
A pitch big enough
For the skies to open up.
You know,
A pitch for the angels.
Of course, It wouldn't
mean Very much to you,
But it would mean
A great deal to me.
It would mean
That for one moment
In my whole life I would have
done Something successful.
It would mean That maybe the children
Would be very proud of me.
The children?
Yes, yes, i've always Had quite a
fondness For children, you know.
Yes, that's all
Here in the record.
The problem here, Mr. Bookman, is
that You'd require delay until--
Until I make a pitch!
The kind of pitch
I was talking to you about.
The one for the angels?
That's right.
One for the angels.
I'm terribly sorry,
Mr. Bookman,
But, no.
You see, these categories
Are very specific
And when reference is made to unfinished
business Of a major nature,
The only interpretation
To be made here
Is simply that--
What-- what i mean
Is that, uh,
Unfortunately, mr. Bookman,
An ability to, to succeed
In a given
Profess ional venture
Is really hardly
Of a major--
Mean a great
Deal to you, does it?
A great deal.
All right,
Mr. Bookman.
Under the circumstances I
believe i can grant You a delay.
Unti l--
What do you mean 'until?'
Until you've made this pitch.
I can live til then?
That's the agreement.
Oh, well i think
That's a f in e bargain.
I didn't get your name.
Now, about
This pitch, mr. Bookman,
When might
We expect it?
When?
Oh, soon.
You know.
Maybe not this year, maybe Not for a
couple of years, [chuckies] but soon.
I have the very odd feeling That
you're taking advantage of me.
Oh, you have?
Well, that's a pity,
Because I am!
You'll never catch me
Making a pitch anymore.
You think you can
Fool me, eh? [chuckies]
I'll hardly open
My mouth from now on.
[mischievous music]
Really, mr. Bookman?
This is much more
Serious than you imagin e.
It's much more complex Than
yourealize, what you've just done.
Here I've gon e
Out of my way to help you
And this is the way
Yourepay me?
Mr. Bookman.
It won't just end here,
You understand?
There will be
Consequences, you see?
FYI, that means
For your information
You made your bed And you
shall have to sleep in it.
We made a bargain that I don't
have to go until I make a pitch.
And you'll have to wait
unti l i make that p itch.
I can say this without the
least Fear of contradiction.
Have you got A long
wait! [chuckies]
That may well be,
Mr. Bookman,
But since you won't
Come with me,
I've been forced
To select an alternative.
[brakes screeching
And woman yelling]
[people shouting]
Maggie!
I swear
I didn't see her.
She jumped right Off the
curb and I had no chance to stop.
I swear to you I never had
no Chance to stop at all.
Well, then someone
Send for a doctor!
Get an ambulance.
I'll call one.
(lou) You're gonna
be all right, darling.
You're gonna
Be just fin e.
Hi, lou.
Hello, sweetheart.
[intense ominous music]
Lou?
Yes?
Who's that man?
[ominous music]
Do you see him?
Yes, lou.
Hey, wait a minute.
You can't take her.
No, siree,
Now listen, I'll go.
Never mind the pitch.
I don't even want to wait,
I'll go right now.
You can't take her.
I'll go with you, i'll--
[ominous music]
(man)
How's maggie, doctor?
(doctor) I can't
tell. I can't tell.
Doctor?
It's hard to tell. She's
a very sick Little girl,
But we'll know Soon, she should
have a crisis by midnight.
By midnight?
I think by then.
He won't come here.
I won't let him come here.
[suspense music]
[intense ominous music]
Good evening,
Mr. Bookman.
You've got
Business in there?
I most certainly do.
It's quarter to 1 2 :00.
In 15 minutes, midnight.
That's my appointment.
Mr. Death, that little
Girl's only 8 years old.
I'm ready now.
I'm sorry, mr. Bookman, But i
had to make Other arrang em ents.
It's impossible
To change them now.
She's to come
With me at midnight,
So I must be
In there at midnight.
And if you're
Not in there?
It would be pretty
much unheard of.
You see, If i didn't get in
there at precisely midnight,
Then the whole Timetable
would Be upset.
It's unheard of.
It's unheard of?
What are you
Doing, mr. Bookman?
I'm just setting up
A pitch, that's all.
At this time
Of night?
Oh, I very often Have a
late sale. Very often!
Not many customers.
Oh, they'll be here.
They'll come round--
You're here, anyway.
Oh, yes, i'm here.
But i'm afraid
I'm not much of a custom er.
How do you know?
Have you seen my stock?
Take this lovely tie
Here, for instance.
Oh, oh, excuse me.
What does that
Look like to you?
It looks like a tie.
Feel it.
So--
Ladi es and gentlemen,
If you wi ll
Feast your eyes
On probably the most
Exciting invention
Since atomic energy.
A s imulated silk
So fabulously conceived
As to mystify even the ancient
Chinese silk manufacturers.
An almost unbelievable
Attention to detail!
It has a wonderful
Work of weaving.
[suspense music]
(lou) Witness, if you Will, a
demonstration Of tensile strength.
Feel that if you wi ll, sir.
Unbelievable, isn't it?
As strong as steel.
Yet as fragile and
delicate As shantu ng silk.
(lou) Picture if
you will 300 years
Of backbreaking
Research and labor,
To develop this.
The absolute
Ultimate in strength.
And what would
You expect to pay
For this fabulous,
I say fabulous, incredible,
Amazing developm ent
Of the tailor's art?
Would you pay
30 dollars a spool?
25? 20? 1 0?
Well, very well
You might, sir,
If you were trying To
purchase this At stores.
But this fantastic thread
Is not available in stores.
It is smuggled in
By oriental birds
Especially trained
For ocean travel.
Each carrying a bit
Quantity in a small satchel
Underneath their
Ruby throats.
It takes 832 crossings
To supply enough thread
To go around one spool.
And tonight,
At my special
Get acquainted, introductory,
Mid july hot Summer sale
I offer you this
Fabu lous th read
Not at 20
Dollars a spool,
Not at 1 0, not at 5,
But at the ridiculously Low
price of 25 Cents a spool.
I'll take all you have.
(lou)
Sewing needles, yarn,
Marvelous plastic shoelaces,
Genuine static eradicator
Will fit
Any standard radio,
Suntan oil,
Eczema powder,
Razors, athlete's
Feet destroyer,
How about some nice
Simulated kashmir socks--
All right, all right.
I'll take it all.
All of it.
Right there.
(lou) And now for The
piece de resistance.
An item never before Offered
in this or any Other cou ntry.
One guaranteed
Live human man saver.
How's that?
For what i ask
You sir, receive
A willing, capable,
Worldly, highly sophisticated,
Won derfully loyal
Right hand man
To use in any
Capacity you see fit.
How's that?
Me!
Louis j. Bookman,
The first model
Of his kind,
He comes to you
With an absolute guarantee
All parts interchang eable.
With a certificate of 4 years
Serviceability
He eats little,
He sleeps little,
He rests only occasionally,
And there he is
At your elbow
At you beck and call
Whenever you need him.
Mr. Bookman, you are
A persuas ive man.
I challeng e
Any other store
Wholesale house
Or in dustry
To even come close to
matching What I offer you here.
Because my dear man,
I offer you, i offer you--
[beiis toii]
It's midnight!
It's midnight and i've
Missed my appointment!
Give her the sedatives Every
three hours, Mrs. Polansky.
She'll be all right. She
just needs a lot Of rest now.
[bells continue to toll]
She's all right.
One minute past
1 2 :00, mr. Bookman.
And you made me
Miss my appointment.
Thank god.
A most persuasive
Pitch, mr. Bookman.
An excellent pitch.
Yes, it's quite a pitch,
Very effective.
It's the best
I've ever done.
It's the kind of a pitch
I've always wanted to make.
A big one.
A pitch so big,
So big that the sky
Would open up.
A pitch for the angels.
That's right,
[soft melancholy music]
Well, I guess it's
Time for me now.
As per our agreement.
Well, I'm ready.
After you, mr. Bookman.
Oh, excuse me,
I forgot something
I'll be back in a minute.
You never know who might
need something up there.
Up there?
Up there, mr. Bookman.
You made it.
(male presenter, off)
Louis j. Bookman,
Age, sixtyish,
Occupation, pitchman.
Formally, a fixture
Of the summer,
Formally, a rather minor
Component to a hot july.
But throughout his life
A man beloved by the children
And therefore,
A most important man.
It couldn't happen, you say?
Probably not
In most places,
But it did happen
In the twilight zone.
(male presenter, off) Rod serling,
The creator Of twilight zone,
Will tell you
About next week's story
After this word
From our alternate sponsor.
And now, mr. Serling.
Next week, we invite
You to take a walk
Down a western
Frontier street
At the elbow
Of a doomed gun man.
Whose salvations lies In
nothing less than A magic potion,
And a colt 45.
Mr. Dan duryea stars
On mr. Denton on doomsday.
Next week
On the twilight zone.
We hope you'll be able to be
with us. Thank you and good night.
(male presenter, off) Kimberly clark
invites you To watch steve mcqueen
In wanted dead or alive,
Saturday night over
Most of these same stations.