(yells)
(school bell ringing)
(belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
(alarm ringing)
* Every day she takes
a morning bath *
* She wets her hair *
* Wraps a towel around her
as she's heading *
* For the bedroom chair *
* It's just another day *
* Slipping into stockings,
stepping into shoes *
(gargling)
This will be a good day.
And five, and six... oh, yeah!
* At the office
where the papers grow... *
Your man is going to love
those sexy new abs.
* Drinks another coffee
and she finds it hard *
* To stay awake *
(groans)
* It's just another day *
* Do-do-do-do do-do-do *
* Do-do-do-do do-do *
(singing along):
* It's just another day. *
(laughs)
Check it out.
That crazy lady's singing
a million-year-old song.
(school bell ringing)
(sighs)
Okay, Edna, remember:
if you can teach one kid
one thing,
then today will be a success.
(electronic beeps and blips)
Now, class...
class.
Class, please pay attention!
Text "Uncle".
(ring tones and electronic noise
grow louder)
(cacophonous noise)
You're children.
Why do you all need cell phones?
Safety.
Emergencies.
Educational.
(sighs) Could you at least
set them to vibrate?
(loud vibrating)
(vibrating grows louder)
That's it:
everything in the box.
No more gizmos in this class.
They're all going in the drawer
with the biology frogs.
(croaking)
(lock clicking)
(students groaning)
Okay. We'll call your bluff.
Teach us-- using only
the knowledge in your own head.
Hey, don't worry.
We still have the good old
classroom computer.
Who wants to play Word Jammers?
(loudly booting up)
My stroked-out grandfather
has more memory than that thing.
How is he doing?
Better. Thanks.
(muttering angrily)
How could Krabappel
take my cell phone?
I'm only on month one
of a 60-month plan.
You know, Krabappel
just needs to chill out
and realize life is cool--
but how?
(Homer giggling)
(drunkenly):
Okay. Now I'll be the dog,
and you be the daddy.
(barks)
(Santa's Little Helper barking)
Hmm. You know,
my dad is a lot more fun
after a few beers.
Maybe Mrs. K would be nicer
if we "Irish up" her coffee.
Put blood in it?
No, booze.
First the easy part.
Kids, get some liquor.
(Tchaikovsky's "Dance of the
Sugar Plum Fairy" plays)
Hurry! She's almost
done flirting
with the vending
machine guy.
(laughing)
What if she
tastes the booze?
Relax.
Hazelnut creamer
covers all sins.
(slurping)
Ah.
And that's why I found
Good Night, Gorilla
to be the perfect
summer beach read.
Two stars for you.
And an extra,
'cause you're going
to have a hard life.
* This old man, he played one *
* He played knickknack
on my (hiccups) thumb. *
You look tired.
Maybe you need some more coffee.
Ah.
(giggling drunkenly)
Dizzy.
(students giggling)
* You'll be going
back to Denmark *
* Spain and Uruguay *
* And we promise
that we'll write you *
* But you know
that that's a lie *
Hey! You know why
they call it a choir.
Because "choir" we
listening to this crap?
(grunts) These pantyhose
are all twisted up.
Edna, please! Even the union
can't protect you from this.
Give me one
night, Dewey.
I'll get you
off Broadway.
Never!
Edna, let's go.
Uh-oh.
Do you think
we went too far?
Nah.
Booze only makes you do things
you already wanted to do.
I'm queen of the world!
Oh!
(crashing)
(Krabappel groans)
I'm so sorry.
I really don't know
what happened.
You made quite a nanny goat
of yourself yesterday.
I know I did,
but I don't know why.
(sighs) This is the hardest
thing I've ever had to do,
but I'm letting you go.
Seymour...
I'm going to cry.
Here. Take my hanky.
I'm working on my magic act
for the Faculty Follies.
But right now,
I don't feel much like follying.
Could I have a moment alone?
Of course.
There's a form to extend your
health insurance on my desk.
I never wanted
her to get fired.
I bet it was that hamster
medicine we added
that put her
over the edge.
Maybe I should tell Skinner
that it was our...
Needle scratch!
My name is Zachary Vaughn.
I just got my masters
in education
from Tufts University,
and you are my first class ever.
An M.E.D. from Tufts?
Nice.
But why talk when I could text?
Our cell phones!
Our Blueteeth!
My tip calculator!
(electronic tones sounding)
STUDENTS:
Whoa!
That text was totally worth
the 15 cents it cost
to receive it.
BART:
Then, Zach Skyped us,
live-blogged our
spelling bee
and friended us
on Facebook.
I thought you were studying
the Lincoln-Douglas debates.
You mean the L Man/D Dog
flame wars.
(groans)
I'm glad you've got
such a stimulating substitute,
but I'm worried
about Mrs. Krabappel.
Oh, no worries.
I heard on the four-square
court she's doing great.
No one even plays
four-square anymore.
They just gossip.
Ah...
All right.
Who can tell me
what the Monroe Doctrine was?
Oh, oh!
The policy of President Monroe
that America
has the right as a nation to...
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you telling me
you memorized that fact
when anyone with a cell phone
can find it out in 30 seconds?
I-I...
I've crammed my head
full of garbage!
Yes, you have.
What are these?
Those are smiley stickers.
Mrs. Krabappel used to put them
on our papers
as a reward for good work.
I run a paperless classroom.
Check this out.
But this is just
nonsense punctuation.
Oh, my God!
Anybody want to return
these caveman kudos
to Mrs. Krabappel?
Uh, sure.
It's sort of on my way home.
I can check up on the old girl.
She probably landed a job at
some fancy-schmancy prep school.
Make way for the new freshman.
Where do I find the books,
the booze and the broads?
Hey, Dean, how about
a little privacy?
I've got to matriculate.
(laughs halfheartedly)
(doorbell rings)
Door's broken.
Mrs. K, is everything
all right?
Sure. (coughs)
Never better.
(hacking)
I know, Bart.
It's pretty sad to see
your teacher fallen so low.
(laughing)
It's the movie.
It's so funny.
Sir, this is a benefit to
increase our endowment.
Honey, if we increase
your endowment any more,
we'll all be in the shade.
Hey, you're all right.
Hey, everyone,
dessert's on me.
(chuckles)
(laughing)
Sorry, sorry.
Thanks for bringing over
the smiley stickers, Bart.
They really liven
the place the up
Mrs. K, you've got
to get out of here.
When was the last time
you washed your hair?
Hmm. Two weeks ago?
Well, that's better than me,
but still,
you've got to get out.
What's the point?
Out of work, I'm out of money.
No man wants me,
except Disco Stu.
Stu is about more
than just disco.
I'm also-- ha! --
super Christian!
Okay, look, there's a big
football game on tonight,
so we can get this thing
over real quick.
Show me some of Bart's artwork,
give me a little false hope,
and here's a little something
to help with his grades.
I'm not asking for A's,
just incompletes.
Mr. Simpson, I don't
need your money.
Bart can definitely be
a challenge,
but, yeah, I like challenges,
and he...
(laughing):
...he's got a wild sense
of humor.
Look at this picture he drew.
(laughs)
It will be his last birthday
if he keeps drawing pictures
like this.
What?
I said,
are there any areas
that we, his parents,
can improve upon?
Yes. Just one: relax.
You're clearly
a caring father.
(crying)
You're the first teacher
that ever got me.
(crying)
Let it out. Let it out.
(sobbing)
(loud sobbing)
(very loud sobbing)
Keep it in. Keep it in.
Two hot chocolates
with hot fudge boost.
Milhouse... (sighs)
...we ruined Edna's life.
Maybe we can get her job back.
But we can't lose Zack.
Look at the awesome video
he just e-mailed me.
Check out the multiples
of seven, y'all.
* *
There's got to be
some other way to help Mrs. K.
Maybe we can find an
answer in this bookstore.
Bookstores don't have answers.
They just have creepy guys
sitting in easy chairs
at the end of aisle ways.
I ain't paid for Doris
Kearns Goodwin in my life,
and I ain't gonna start now.
Oh, that's some good
Doris there.
You're right.
I guess no one's
ever written a book
to help a middle-aged
woman turn her life around.
Excuse me. I believe you boys
are looking for... The Answer.
What's The Answer?
Only the best-selling book,
slash, DVD since the bible.
WOMAN (with Australian accent):
My life was over.
I'd lost my job,
my husband left me.
I had to sleep
in a kangaroo's pouch.
And then I found...
The Answer.
("O Fortuna" from Carmina Burana
plays)
The Answer was discovered
by the philosophers
of ancient Greece, who hid it
under a rock where it was
discovered by the knights
of King Arthur,
who placed it in a bottle
and set it in the ocean,
where it was found
by Pat Sajak.
These great men
knew The Answer.
The Answer is the secret to
achieving your heart's desire.
Learn The Answer,
and change your life.
ANNOUNCER:
Available wherever dubious,
quasi-scientific
self-help books are sold.
So, um, you're wearing
the same bathrobe
you were the last
time I was here, huh?
That's cool.
Bart, you're a good kid.
You're the only one
who came to see me.
Well, Mrs. K,
I have just the book, slash, DVD
for you-- The Answer.
"This book uses
the ancient power of wanting."
That makes absolutely no sense.
Hey. "Just because
we don't understand electricity,
doesn't mean we can't enjoy
its benefits."
But we do
understand electricity.
Every positively charged
nucleus is...
Cut it out.
You're not a teacher anymore.
Way to cheer me up, kid.
(coughing)
Look, Mrs. K, I'm a Simpson,
and a Simpson
never gives up
until he's tried at
least one easy thing.
Let me help you.
Aw.
So, did you write
your dream on the...
"index card of fate"?
Yes, but it still seems...
stupid.
reading:
Great idea!
Now, let's see.
"Break your dream down
into smaller wishes,
then break those down
into wish-able actions."
Bart, this is starting to sound
like one of those loony
self-help books.
Loony? Would a loony self-help
book come with a magic
question mark inside?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
All thanks to The Answer!
Well, opening this store
was a lot of work,
but your faith in me
got me through it.
And it looks like
you got your own
index card of fate.
What's your dream?
Nothing, nothing.
Well, I'm sure
it'll come true.
(humming)
One cran-bran
for the Flan-man.
My pleasure.
What did he want?
Beats me.
I just gave him a banana.
Well, thanks again, Bart.
This store has definitely
turned my life around.
Yup. I'm off the hook now.
What do you mean by that?
Well, I guess I can tell you,
'cause everything worked out
for the best.
Everything? What everything?
(laughs)
Well, it's funny, really.
I'm the one
who put booze in your coffee
and got you fired.
(laughs)
You did what?!
Please don't kill me.
You ruined my life!
It's your fault I have to work
at this stupid muffin store.
But this place
was your dream!
My real dream was
to be a teacher,
and you got me fired!
Now I'm up to my eyeballs
in debt with this stupid store,
and four more muffin stores
just opened on this block!
No!
But-But-But you found
The Answer!
No! I wrote a phone number
in there!
No matter what you've done,
I always thought
there was a spark of decency
in you, Bart Simpson,
but I was wrong.
I never thought
I'd say this to a child,
but you are bad
on the inside.
(gasps)
(humming)
Dad, am I bad on the inside?
No... but the layers of bad
on your surface
go almost all the way
to the center.
But you think there's, like, a
kernel of good inside me, right?
Hmm. I don't know.
Kernels are kind of big.
Oh! Listen, I was thinking.
If someone did a really
bad thing to one teacher,
and then did the same bad
thing to another teacher
to get the first teacher her
job back, would it be okay?
When you sayteacher,
do you really meanparent?
No, I mean teacher.
Great. Go nuts.
But remember, we never
had this discussion.
What discussion?
The one we just had
about you doing bad things,
you stupid kid!
Oh.
So, you see,
it was my fault.
I got Mrs. Krabappel drunk.
Then I was gonna do
the same thing to Zack,
but I decided it was better
to just tell the truth.
Bart, you deserve a reward
for telling the truth.
And that reward will be in
the form of a severe punishment.
Doesn't matter, as long
as Edna gets her job back.
Sorry, Bart, but I can't just
get rid of a teacher
if he's doing a good job.
Or an adequate job.
Or just shows up
and doesn't touch anyone.
ZACK (chanting):
I hate children!
Children suck!
What the...? Faculty lounge talk
out in the halls?!
I hate children!
You and you and you
and you and you!
(slurring his speech):
You are wasting your lives.
Hilary Swank didn't graduate
high school.
She won two Oscars.
And one of them she deserved.
Bart, you said you
didn't get him drunk.
I didn't. I swear!
No, he's right.
I mixed a little vodka
in with my Blue Bronco.
Does anybody else want
to ride the indigo pony!
Is there extra credit in it?
Oh, they're gonna eat you alive
at Cal Tech, boy.
Alive!
(laughs)
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
* This place is a prison! *
* Dow, dow *
* All you kids are screwed! *
* Kids and vodka! *
Yeow!
(laughing)
It's always the good ones
that go crazy the fastest.
Get off me!
You can get rid of me, but you
can't get rid of the truth, man!
This school is
a glorified hamster wheel
run by incompetent bureaucrats
who can get you
through a test,
but you will fail
the test of life!
Children, fingers in your ears
and make the la-la sound.
* La-la, la-la,
la-la, la-la... *
Every class is a joke.
English-- a joke,
homeroom-- a joke.
Free period-- a joke.
Nutritious
lunch-- a joke!
Only alcohol can
make life bearable.
You must drink!
Always drink!
Well, class, I've got
to say I'm glad to be back.
And there's no
hard feelings?
Nope.
Now, everyone enjoy one
of my yummy muffins.
But it's stale.
Eat the muffin.
WOMAN:
A simple schoolteacher
found fulfillment
and muffin-based revenge
all thanks to... The Answer.
("O Fortuna" from Carmina Burana
plays)
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com