done by YesCool
edited by YesCool & Arcinboldi
www.addic7ed.com
Hello, everybody.
Welcome to Under the Wrapper,
where I, Huell Howser,
apply the art of detection
to your favorite confections.
Now, here's some opening titles
to sweeten the deal.
Hey! Aah!
Wow!
Now, we've seen
how cookies crumble
and soda gets its pop,
so let's take a close-up look
at America's favorite drop--
the gumdrop!
Ooh!
Every gumdrop is made
of a succulent substance
called gelatin.
Amazing.
Gelatin comes from the skin,
bones and hooves
of only the sickest horses.
That's amazing.
Change it!
You just increased
the volume!
Welcome back
to the 62nd annual
Creative Arts Emmy Awards.
In Outstanding
Lighting Direction,
Electronic, Multi-camera
for Variety, Music
or Comedy Programming,
we have... a three-way tie!
Back to the horses.
Back to the horses!
God...
Gee, Lisa,
looks like tomorrow
I'll be shoveling ten feet
of global warming.
Global warming
can cause weather
at both extremes--
hot and cold.
I see. So you're saying
warming makes it colder.
Well, aren't you
the Queen of Crazyland?
Everything's the opposite
of everything.
I'm Lisa Simpson.
Really?
Uh-huh,
all right.
Mush, nerds, mush!
I'm part of a team!
Oh, look how the snow glistens
on the tiniest branches.
Yeah, yeah,
miracles are all around us.
Now, please. I am trying
to hear the school closings.
The following schools
are closed.
Springfield High School,
Springfield Middle School,
Springfield El...
...Excelente
Spanish Language School.
Oh!
Springfield
Element...
...al Center
for Periodic Table Studies.
Oh!
Springfield Elementary Sc...
...uba Diving Academy.
Oh, for crying out loud!
And of course, Springfield
Elementary is closed.
We were just messing
with Bart Simpson.
I've got one.
Springfield El...
bow Macaroni Factory.
Skinner! What factory makes
just one kind of pasta?
Uh, well, I just
thought, uh,
specialization being
the wave of the future?
Uh, probably, uh...
Snow day!
What the...?
What a smart way
to spend a snowy day.
Good grief.
Headshot! Headshot!
Oh, right in the carrot.
Headshot.
Huh?
A branch must have knocked out
the power lines.
Fine. I'll see what's on TV.
That runs on electricity, also.
All right, I'll watch a DVD.
There's no way
that runs on electricity.
Really?
Does Obama know about this?
I can't believe
this is how pilgrims lived.
Huh?
When Maggie's
nightlight goes out,
her onesie becomes a funsie.
This announcer has never
seen diapers so dapper.
What do you want?
I... want to play with you guys.
Fine. Get this on in
two minutes, lose the attitude,
and for God's sake,
suck in that pooch.
Go, go, go!
And now,
making his debut on the catwalk,
Bartholomew!
Belt is by Twizzler,
vest courtesy
of Nelson,
tights are by
Hello Kitty...
Hello Kitty?
I thought
they were Spider-Man heads.
Ew! Ew! Ew!
Oh! Stupid shoes over tights!
Why did I want to play
with a couple
of lame-o girls?
Because you
envy us.
Maggie and I share the deepest
bond there is: sisterhood.
We'll be closer
than best friends
for the rest
of our lives.
But you'll never know
what that's like,
because you won't
ever have a brother.
I don't need a brother.
I'm a bad ass loner
like Wolverine,
who leaves whenever people
beg him not to leave.
"'Off with their heads!'
said the Red Queen."
Now, pull the tab.
More.
Oh, I don't need a brother,
and no dream will convince me
I do.
I want a turn!
You've got the bike.
It's not the same.
That's a perfect spiral, Eli.
Winning a Super Bowl
just doesn't compare
to chucking the ball
around with my brother.
It's easy being
a winner in the pros.
Try winning two high school
basketball championships
like I did.
Good for
you, Squirt.
I'm the oldest!
Keep away from Cooper!
Hey.
Why'd you stop?
I-I... I just... I just
wanted to say something.
What?
Dick?
Yes?
You-You're
my brother, and...
...I love you.
Well, I love
you, too, Tom.
Thank you very much.
But if you hadn't
fought CBS,
they would never have
fired us from our show.
Oh, they-they didn't fire us,
Dick.
They didn't?
We quit.
We did not quit.
They fired us.
You... You were fired.
They fired us
from the show.
No, they fired you.
They didn't fire me.
Why wouldn't they fire you?
Because they can't fire...
the yo-yo master!
And here is "shoot the moon."
I'm so cool.
Now look what
you've done.
Bart was having a
perfectly nice dream
about brothers,
and you ruined it.
Yeah? We? Well, huh.
Oh, my God, I want a brother!
- You can have mine, but he's
kind of an idiot. -Oh.
Dad, I want
a baby brother.
Son, I love you kids.
But I'm only going
to the hospital
one more time in my life,
and I ain't coming out.
Lisa got a sister.
Why can't you have another boy?
Girls are easy.
Girls love Daddy.
Girls make birthday cards
with glitter on them.
Girls can marry
a hockey player
and get me seats
to hockey games.
Girls don't steal
my knives...
...and I don't have to tell
girls how their bodies work,
'cause I don't know.
You never told me
how my body works.
Point and shoot.
My dad
is such a jerk.
I want a baby brother,
and he said no.
Maybe you could trick
your parents into making a baby
the way my Mom nearly tricked
Charles Barkley.
Trick 'em.
I like it.
But how?
A romantic
dinner?
That's
a great idea!
Oh, my God!
I killed Kenny!
Ralph.
No, I killed
Kenny yesterday.
What did I do now?
Do I smell tarragon-crusted
Atlantic salmon?
Bart's cooked us
a five-course romantic dinner.
You had me at "five-course,"
you lost me at "romantic," and
you got me back at "dinner."
Oh, what a lovely evening.
And it's not over yet.
Oh.
Hope you saved room
for passion fruit soufflé
with crème anglaise for two.
And one for Mom.
There comes a time
in every marriage
when it comes
down to this.
Do we eat dessert,
or do we make love?
Maybe we could do both.
Yeah!
We couldn't do both.
No... we could not.
Are you sure this'll work?
Hey, this is the DVD
my parents used to make me.
So it kind of works.
Homer Simpson,
look what the snuggle fairy left
in our DVD player.
Hmm. People in other
countries make love?
It's about time.
Which position
should we try?
The Yawning Monkey?
The Pair Of Tongs?
Ooh, look.
Congress Of The Crow!
Okay!
All right, all right, um,
your ankle goes there...
Uh-huh, and now
hand me your neck.
And turn that upside down.
Mm-hmm, and swivel that till
you hear a grinding noise.
Don't look at that.
A few more minor
adjustments, and...
Ow!
Ooh! Oh!
More Vicodin
and eggs, please.
Um.
Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Oh.
What do you want, Simpson?
Can't you see we're
busy hockin' loogs?
Nice loog!
Wish I'd hocked that!
Look, I want
a baby brother,
but I can't get
my parents to do it.
Here's the thing,
Simpson.
No matter how dead their
relationship seems,
all parents eventually commit
the heinous act of love.
Mine do it once
a year
on the magical day
when the prison
and the insane asylum have
their annual mixer.
What you've got to worry about
is the pill.
The pill? What's that?
It's medicine doctors give moms
to keep babies up in Heaven.
Well, I need a baby now, and
I'm not getting any younger!
Then get rid of
the pills.
Got it. How can I thank you?
Uh... give yourself
a wedgie.
Don't you want
to do it?
Can't.
Carpal-nurple syndrome.
The doctor said if I
didn't take it easy,
I might never shove a kid's
face in the drinking
fountain again.
Scary.
A wakeup call for all of us.
Mom'll never know.
Bart Simpson!
Tac-Tics?!
Bart, you've always
been a handful,
but you've never interfered
with my reproductive freedom.
Why now?
I just wanted a baby brother,
but Dad said I was one "Uday"
who didn't need a "Qusay."
I just wanted what Lisa
and Maggie have.
Oh, Barty, I'm sorry.
But your father and I think
that three kids is just perfect.
What about what I want?
I'd help you take
care of him.
Remember those hamsters
you were going to take care of?
Oh, my God, the hamsters!
And even if we did
have another baby,
it might not be a boy.
It might be another sister.
Another sister?!
How could you possibly need
all these clothes?
Shopping: it's the most fun
you could have standing up.
Hey, you didn't see
what I cooked up
in the galley of my last
flight to London.
They don't call it "Virgin"
Airlines anymore.
You're right.
I can't risk another girl.
Use whatever birth
control you want.
It's your body.
That's right!
It is!
One boy to go, please.
Easy on the freckles.
A ten-year-old can't
adopt a child.
Oh, you think he's for me!
You know, the orphan
is for my folks--
they can't have more kids.
It is so sad--
a real-life Jaws bit
off my dad's wiener.
Come on, I'd be an awesome
big brother!
I've got videogames!
A tree house!
A garage stuffed to the rafters
with illegal fireworks!
Oh, sweet Meerschaum,
take me away.
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry, kid.
It's not gonna happen.
I'd give my brother
everything I have!
He could be the race car
in Monopoly!
Monopoly!
The race car!
Wake up!
I'm Bart Simpson.
Who the hell are you?
I'm your new brother!
Are you from the orphanage,
or do I really not understand
how babies are born.
So, Charlie, how did you escape
the island of misfit boys?
Shinnied down
a drainpipe.
You like to shinny?
I like to shinny.
Where do you see yourself
in 20 years?
One-armed drummer
in a prison rock band.
Nice! Favorite Beatle?
Dung.
Me, too!
There must be some reason
no one ever adopted you.
Is one of your
feet a hand?
People only want
to adopt babies.
Babies?
We've got one of those.
Overrated.
Shop it somewhere
else, sister.
Dad, this is Charlie,
my new, um,
best friend.
Hello, sir.
You're going to be seeing a lot
of him around the house.
Well, welcome,
Charlie!
Nice to meet ya!
No glasses--
way to go!
This one's a keeper!
Yo!
Check out my brother, Charlie!
Brother?
What are you talking about?
How come I've never
seen him before?
Uh, he was born
with two noses
and we hid him away
till we could afford
to cut one off.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah.
Two noses!
You deserve
a brother, Bart.
good things!
When poking a
dead animal,
don't go straight
for the eye.
Build up to it.
My son, afraid
of water.
So, Lisa, how do you like
sharing a bathroom
with two brothers?
Two brothers?
Bart, who is
this kid?
Be cool, be cool--
he's an orphan.
You know,
just like Annie,
except he's a dude
and he hates tomorrow.
I hate it so much!
Bart, you have to take him back!
You're just jealous 'cause now
I've got what you've got
with Maggie, only better because
we're dudes with 'tudes!
Kids, calm down! Here.
Have a Not Very Berry Blast.
It goes great with our
"notton candy."
Awesome, they made
a sequel to Sever IV.
This movie's going to be
great, full of blood and gore
and torture and guts and...
Two kid's tickets for
The Diversity Kittens.
...and murder and swears
and brains and basements
and bones and saws and lungs
and faces worn as hats.
Hmm.
Now, you probably think Sever V
is a rip-off of Sever IV,
but it's actually based
on the rich history
of Hong Kong torture films.
Uh-oh.
The boogeyman's going
to eat my brain!
I'm sorry. I guess having
a little brother
is more responsibility
than I thought,
especially
'cause I thought
it'd be no
responsibility at all.
Aah, it's the
boogeyman!
There is no such thing
as a boogeyman.
Boogie, boogie,
boogie, boogie, boogie!
Simpson, step away from the orphan.
Do not give him any more love.
I repeat,
do not give him any more love.
Mr. Policeman,
please take me home.
That mean boy took me
to a scary movie
and he covered
his sister's doll
in peanut butter
and bird seed.
Charlie, you'd rat on me?
Hey, no, no, what do
you think you're do--?
My snout,
my beautiful snout!
Sorry, dude, I didn't see you.
How could you not see me?
My arms are like hams.
Hams!
Hey!
Go ahead, leave.
That's what you're good at!
Where are we going
to hide?
The same place Eskimos
hide from penguins.
Now, Charlie,
we'll have to live
off what we find
in the garbage--
banana strings,
muffin liners--
but it'll be cool
'cause it's just you and me.
Hello, Bart.
How did you find us?
You left a trail
of lost winter clothes.
Are you gonna turn us in?
No, I'm gonna convince you
to turn yourselves in.
Never.
Never, huh?
What are you going to eat?
Snow-- God's cotton candy.
Huh, snow, hmm?
Better change
your mind quick, Bart.
A snow plow is coming
to seal us in.
The Plow King lives!
And Bart, maybe Charlie
can't be your little brother,
but you'll always be
a big brother to me.
Please don't send me
back, Bart.
This was
the best day of my life.
Oh, no!
You took too long to make
an obvious decision!
Don't worry,
me and Charlie have
one thing
you'll never have.
Point and shoot, bro,
point and shoot.
Oh, gross, gross,
gross, gross.
Hey, you're alive,
aren't you?
I wish I weren't.
I'm here to visit Charlie.
Charlie?
He's gone.
A nice new family
adopted him.
Now he has six
wonderful sisters.
He's so cute.
Let's do his nails.
He's my baby.
Mom!
I'm telling.
Dad!
I want ice cream.
I'm a princess.
No, I'm a princess.
She got juice
on my sweater.
Big cheater.
You're the cheater.
Ugly.
So many sisters.
Save me, Bart.
I know
you miss him, boy,
so let's you and me spend some
quality father and son time.
That's so fake.
I don't know how they--
Too real!
Oh, come on.
Look out!
Why would that guy--?
That's fake.
Take it, Tom!
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait, hold it, hold it.
I said, "Take it, Tom."
Did you hear me say,
"Take it, Tom"?
I didn't hear you say, "Take it."
Well, what did you think you heard?
I didn't, I didn't think I heard what
you think you said.
Well, what do you think I said?
Well, I... I heard...
It sounded like you said
"naked bacon." "Naked bacon"?
Sounded like "naked bacon."
It sounded like I said...
Did somebody say "naked bacon"?
- Yeah, see?
- What?
We all thought it was "naked bacon."
Yeah, it sounded like
"naked bacon" to me.
I don't know why they say
you're the dumb guy, Tom.
I don't know, either.
You said "naked bacon."
I definitely said, "Take it, Tom."
But if you... No, you
said "naked bacon."
That's what I thought. We both agree...
You may both agree, but folk singers
never say, "Take it, naked bacon."
Do you guys know "Funkytown"?
done by YesCool
edited by YesCool & Arcinboldi
www.addic7ed.com