Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, I love going to aquatic parks.
Sure, they have worse rides
than amusement parks,
less fish than aquarium
s- but the parking is ample!
Now to seal you in for safety.
Oh, there's so many photo ops,
but I already filled up my
camera in the parking lot.
Parking lot C sign, the tram,
a license plate from Canada,
a bird eating potato chips,
my feet walking,
that boy who got sick on the tram,
Grampa talking to a mermaid hedge,
the park rules in Spanish,
a fat baby,
Grampa telling a story to a trailer hitch.
Oops! I erased them all!
I want to do that!
I'm going to take stuff
from the lost and found!
My feet hurt!
left ear's freezing!
My right ear's burning!
I got fish smell in my wrinkles!
Attention, exploro-nauts!
That's us!
In one minute, we'll be starting
our rock-quatic roll-tacular!
Hurry! If we don't get a
seat in the splash zone,
I've worn my bathing suit
under my clothes for nothing!
A splash-'em-up show?
Reminds me of the time I hig
h-dived into a damp sponge
for the amusement of Federal
Reserve Chairman Paul Volcker.
Grampa, no stories!
You can come with us,
or sit here on the shark bench.
You know, I did sit on a shark once...
d, bathing suit!
Oops! No bathing suit.
* *
Let's give a wet and wacky welcome
to Springfield's oldest
performing mollusk...
Get to the show!
This is the show!
Here's the original Octomom: Slimu!
* Whoa! *
* I feel good *
* I knew that I would... *
Slimu! Did you get my letters?
Slimu wasn't expecting company,
so he's got some cleaning up to do!
*...I wouldn't now *
* So good *
Slimu looks kind of uncomfortable.
Wouldn't you be if you were a saltwater fish
in a freshwater aquarium?
The country has its first black president.
Maybe it's time for the
first octopus president!
And when it comes to signing bills,
he can provide his own ink!
Ahh, oily!
They'll cheer a dancing octopus,
but not an old man
complaining about everything.
Excuse me, sir. Is this seat taken?
Well, not for a pretty girl like you!
Well, this is the first
time I ever sat on a shark.
Not me-- sat on a real one once!
Tell me more! More?!
Play it cool, Grampa.
Play it cool!
It was back in World War II.
I was a Seaman First Class
on the USS World War I.
We were minding our own business
when we were attacked by a hea
t-seeking torpedo
we had fired the day before.
Don't worry about the sharks, boys.
Just play possum and
they'll leave you alone.
Unfortunately, sharks love possum.
Hey, boys, these sharks can't
bite us if we're on their backs!
Yeah.
It's like riding the Cyclone
back at Coney Island!
Whoa!
It's like riding a dust devil back in Yuma--
like I read about in a book back in Boston!
By the time the rescue planes came,
we had those sharks trained
pretty good.
I still keep in touch with all those men
and some of the sharks.
Why, here's us in Hawaii last year.
Good times.
Sir, my name is Marshall Goldman.
I'm a newspaper columnist
specializing in human interest stories.
You're in the newspaper business?
Something that's gonna die before I do!
You have any other stories
you'd care to tell me?
Someone's listening to me!
Now I know how a radio feels!
Well, class, it's Friday afternoon.
That means it's time to find
out which one of you gets
to take Larry the Lamb home for the weekend.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
And don't forget,
the lucky student gets
to add his or her page
to Larry's personal journal.
Just like Martin did last week.
Ha!
I want him first! No, me!
Oh, not that stupid stuffed lamb again.
This isn't learning!
Do you want to learn?
No, no, no. I'm just saying...
This weekend,
Larry will go home with...
Please, God, I need this.
...Bart Simpson.
Oh, cruel irony!
Hey, the only thing I bring
home are notes to my parents,
and those do not arrive
the way that they left.
Hmm.
Oh, what a nice note!
I'm not sticking my hand in that can again.
You're getting the lamb.
Not so fast.
Tell the diary how special
he makes you feel!
More adjectives!
That's an adverb!
Top of the morning, Homer.
Seen the paper?
No, I get my news off the Internet.
Well, sir, it looks like your
dad is a quotable notable.
Huh?
That's a... It's funny.
It's poignant...
It actually happened!
My father is interesting?!
The whole world's upside down!
That must mean Cathy is funny.
Nope.
Abe, I never knew you were so full of...
! What does that mean?
It's like ,
but with a pinch more !
Yep, I may just be
the best known Abraham in history.
So, Abe, what else you got for me?
Hmm, well, let's see.
Ooh, I was working as a shoeshine boy
at Springfield Union Station.
* *
Every Monday, the Tinseltown
Starliner would stop
at 1:17 p.m. on its way to Hollywood.
I never rode that train,
but I'd palaver with the movie stars
when they got out to
stretch their legs.
Hiya!
But none was more memorable than...
Clark Gable!
Looks like someone has seen my work
as an extra in Du Barry, Woman Of
Passion.
I sure have, Mr. Gable.
How come you ain't a star yet?
Maybe my ears are too big. I don't know.
Hey, what you reading there? Oh, it's called
Gone with the Wind. You can have it.
It's only got one swear word,
and not a very good one.
Gone with the Wind, eh?
Well, let's see: garbage, garbage, my line.
Garbage, garbage, my line.
Atlanta burns, nice dresses. I like it!
Thanks, kid.
Don't tell this story
to anyone for 60 years.
"Clark Gable owes me a book.
"And he never paid me for the shoeshine.
"But his big blue eyes could melt the butter
"you kept in your pocket for lunch.
Lunch butter we called it."
How come Grampa never shared
those stories with us?
He does all the time.
You just never listen.
Marge, my brain is like a computer,
and I file away Grampa's stories
in a very special place.
Hmm, while I'm up there.
Uh-oh.
That's it, boy! Go for the nards!
Bart!
If you're not gonna take care of him right,
then give him to me.
How come you don't get mad
when I torment real animals?
I do! It enrages me!
I thought you Hindus were
supposed to love everybody.
I'm a freaking Buddhist!
A Buddhist!
Larry, please don't judge
our whole family by Bart.
He's the black sheep.
I mean, not that black sheep
are in any way inferior to white sheep.
I do not judge wool by its color--
only by how itchy it is.
Ooh, look!
Jazz!
Larry, what sub-genre of jazz do you like?
Fusion? Neo-bop?
Afro-Cuban?
Larry!
Gotcha!
Larry? Oh, Larry?
Larry?
Larry?!
You're coming off desperate, honey.
That's how I got my idea
for a suitcase with wheels,
from watching a commercial
about a suitcase with wheels.
Hey, Abe,
great stories.
I'm Mitch Albom, author of
Tuesdays with Morrie.
Never heard of you.
Yeah. Sure you haven't.
Take a hike, Hollywood.
I've already got a college boy
to turn my every word into syndicated gold.
Yeah, beat it, sports page.
And what if I don't?
Clouds are God's sneezes.
Ooh, I like this kid.
Oh, Dad, I got you some Scotch.
One of those fancy ones
the checkout lady had to
unlock the cabinet to get.
Well, well, well,
look who decided to visit
me twice in one year.
This man's more of a son to
me than you've ever been.
What the...?!
Well, he's more of a father
to me than you've ever been!
I don't think that's true.
Stay out of this, Dad.
Uh, no. O-Okay.
You only care about me
now because I'm famous.
That's it.
Here's your ring back.
Ring? What ring?
It's a father-son commitment band
that I bought and never told you about.
And now I'm telling you.
Okay, I need the stupid lamb back.
He's in here, safe and sound.
Let me just staple that bag for you.
Hmm.
This isn't Larry.
It's just cotton balls
on toilet paper rolls.
Where's the real Larry?
Well, what do you care?
You don't even like him.
Of course I don't,
but other people do.
Hey, Bart, can't wait to see Larry again.
Um, what if someone were to lose Larry?
They'd see a dark side
of me no one knows about.
* Nelson loved a little lamb *
* Little lamb, little lamb *
* He kept me nice and sane. *
You've reached Abe.
And Marshall.
Abe can't come to the phone right now.
And if this is Homer,
you're too late for my love.
Stupid Grampa.
I try to end the cycle of neglect,
and he hits me with some super neglect.
Maybe you're not really mad at Grampa.
Maybe you're mad at yourself
for taking him for granted all these years.
Marge, how can anyone be mad at himself?
It's impossible. Watch.
Why, you little...
Oh, I can't.
When I look at those
beautiful chubby cheeks.
Come here, you.
Ow!
Ow! I'll kill you, you son of a...!
Oh. No, no, don't-don't look hurt.
Okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I'll show Grampa.
I'll find my own surrogate father
full of heart-warming stories
I can share with the world.
And that's how you win an opium war.
Oh, great stuff.
And the life lesson is?
The Yangtze River swallows all secrets.
Hmm.
I'm just gonna put "Haste makes waste."
Yes, although, these days,
I can make neither haste nor waste.
You know, Simpson,
this has truly been a lovely afternoon.
Release... a hound.
Isn't that cute?
He thinks he's a pack.
Where'd you get this rope?
Swiped it from gym class.
Climb that rope!
There is no rope.
Well, you better get to the ceiling somehow!
Ceiling, ceiling, ceiling!
Bart, I'm losing my grip.
Put the rope in your teeth.
What will that do?
It'll shut you up.
Hmm.
Larry?
Larry the Lamb?
There you are, you piece of crap.
There's rats in my pants!
Chief, my brother fell in the storm drain!
Um, I'm strictly an abov
e-the-ground policeman.
What you need is the sewer cops.
Fine. What's their number?
Lisa, you're old enough now
that I can tell you the truth.
There's no such thing as the sewer cops.
It's just something we tell
kids to make them feel safe.
What about Bart?
Well, if you miss him, yell into a toilet.
BART : It's dark down here!
I have a column I'd like to submit.
Pay me whenever.
I'll just take this to our editor.
Hmm.
What?
Pulitzer Prize application form?
"When I rode with Abe Simpson on
t Tinseltown Starliner,
"I never dreamed his first
voyage would be his last?
"At 3:00 on Monday,
Abe passed away peacefully in his sleep."
How would he know Grampa
was going to die today?
Unless he was going to kill him!
But would someone really kill a man
just to win a Pulitzer Prize?
All aboard the final run of the Tinseltown
Starliner,
the last ride into a nostalgic past.
Anyone without a ticket will be beaten
by classic railroad bulls.
* Old Dan Tucker was a fine old man *
* He washed his face in the frying pan *
* He combed his hair with a wagon wheel *
* And died of the toothache in his heel. *
You don't get a beatin' like
this traveling by plane.
Ow!
I'm finally riding the Tinseltown
Starliner.
I could die a happy man.
D'oh!
Drink up, Abe.
Live each moment as if
someone's about to kill you.
I mean,
as if it's your last.
Sorry, my hearing aid's on the fritz.
The only word I heard was "kill."
Hey. Aah.
Look at that.
They've recreated the '30s.
Tent cities, failing banks.
No, those are real.
Oh!
Beware of Marshall Goldman!
What was that?
Um, an elephant on a circus train
bellowing for his mother.
Oh, I remember the first time
an elephant tried to eat me like a peanut.
I was on the set of a
Warner Brothers cartoon.
Jack Warner came by and said...
Hey, Slimu!
Huh?
Yeah, you'd better run!
Sewer cats!
Larry?!
Larry, you saved my life!
You're the most wonderful
stuffed lamb in the world.
I'm sorry about the mean things I said,
and we'll have the rest of the weekend to...
Whoa!
Huh?
Larry!
Man, everybody loves this guy.
Give him my number.
I'll teach him things.
Things he can use.
The older I get,
the more I like the taste of hot water.
* Here comes the prize *
* Pulitzer Prize *
* I'll finally be successful
in my mother's eyes. *
A little ler...
little lower.
Drop that pillow!
It gets worse.
Ow! Yeah.
See you tomorrow at yoga.
Jane is sick, so Tricia's filling in.
As long as it's not a du!
How can you stand up to this punishment?
I'm the toughest S.O.B. there is--
a biweekly human interest columnist.
And your father's gonna make me a fortune.
Pathetic old fool.
Maybe so, but I know how to play possum.
Um...
So many hat boxes.
Dad, I don't have the right words
to say how I really feel about you,
but at least I know how
to beat up a guy who does.
Well, at least you never tried to kill me.
Just with indifference.
You did good, kid.
This is for the shoeshine.
It's a ghost quarter,
but you'll be able to spend it pretty soon.
So, Grampa, you really saved Dad's life?
I sure did.
But why don't we let Homer tell the story?
Really? Me? u mean it?
I think you're ready for your first ramble.
Oh, I've been waiting for
this day for so long.
The year is 1946.
In a war-torn world, a single flower blooms.
And that flower is an angry
Japanese monster named Godzilla.
How am I doing, Dad?
I'm hanging on every word.
Fortunately, there was
one man who could help--
Colonel Tom Parker.
The Colonel took this monster,
cleaned him up
and put him onstage under the name
The Rolling Stones.
The first concert was a sellout
with many, many, many people eaten.
But those that survived raved
about the undeniable harmonies
and brutally honest lyrics
of what they had just seen.
And that lasted for about five years.
But then, Godzilla dropped out for a while
to do movies,
all of the awful movies
we see now today
in the driv
e-ins that no longer exist.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Shh!