Previously on Shogun.
They died because
they belonged to a greater fight.
It's your turn.
For his safety, I need the Anjin
brought to your fishing village in Ajiro.
Lord Ishido was confused
by your sudden departure.
Please remind your lord,
I keep my promises.
The Black Ship
will bring us out of Osaka.
But you must stay.
Fuck this.
Anjin!
Look out!
He did it!
I would like him to train a regiment
in foreign tactics
using the weapons from his ship.
I proclaim him…
'Hatamoto'.
Which is a very great honor.
Would the Anjin join me?
My lord would like to
race you to the shore.
But I warn you not to let him win.
My lord hates that.
- I wouldn't dare.
- Mmm.
Lord Omi!
A message from Osaka!
Everyone!
Lord Yabushige is coming to this village
with a guest…
Lord of the Kantō… Yoshii Toranaga!
Hurry and get ready!
I beg you, take this sentence off my head.
Lord Toranaga has given the Anjin
- the title he felt was appropriate.
- Ridiculous!
As hatamoto, the Anjin needs a consort.
Then I beg you…
Allow me to leave this clan
and become a nun.
You will do no such thing.
What have I done to deserve this?
Is it not enough
that I must survive the death of my child,
only now to serve a barbarian?
How cruel of me.
After the loss you've just suffered.
Buntaro died with honor.
I will inherit his wishes
and continue serving our lord.
I trust Lord Toranaga.
One year is all he asks.
She'll give six months.
Everything in Ajiro
will be in order.
My nephew is handling every detail.
Good.
- There's no moment to waste.
- Mmm.
Our forces must be ready
before the Council finds
a replacement for my father.
Replacement...?
Had I neglected to tell you?
I gave Hiromatsu an order…
As soon as we left Osaka,
he was to deliver
my letter of resignation.
Sorry… you have resigned
from the Council of Regents?
It was the only thing to do.
But, then you've… killed yourself.
Destroyed your cause…
all your vassals, allies, friends.
We're finished!
Oh no, wait.
All of Izu is finished.
Oh.
I apologize for my bad manners…
I assume it's proper for you
to commit seppuku at once.
Thank you.
But until a legal order arrives
my head will stay where it is.
Lord, Ajiro is approaching!
Whose army is that?
Yabushige-sama's.
All loyal to Toranaga-sama.
Let's hope so.
Should've bought better saké.
I've been waiting for your return, Uncle.
Is that the same barbarian?
The barbarian is hatamoto now.
Please see that he's given a home.
His consort and Lady Toda
will stay there as well.
With the Council hamstrung,
your head would now be of great value.
An ally with ambition is no ally.
We are honored
by your presence, Lady Mariko.
Anjin-sama, this is Omi-sama.
The lord of this village.
Actually, we've met.
Pardon me.
And fuck yourself,
you sniveling little shit rag.
Lord!
Your arrival brings your men great joy!
Please listen!
Yabushige-sama!
Lord, it would be my pleasure
if you would inspect my guard.
Samurai of Izu
I am honored to witness
the forces of my friend and ally,
Kashigi Yabushige.
Dark clouds are gathering over Japan.
We must protect it against treachery.
To those who stain the Taikō's legacy...
May the gods blast you without pity!
And to those who fight
in the name of loyalty...
It is I, Yoshii Toranaga,
who humbly bows to you!
Toranaga-sama!
Uncle,
the whole village has prepared
for your arrival.
My father has to leave
on urgent business.
We must fully train our gun regiment
before he returns.
Should've bought the cheap stuff.
Uh. The men, from the hole.
You seen them?
They safe?
Muraji?
- Uh…
- Welcome, Anjin-sama.
Uh… My men.
I'd like to see them now. My...
Where are they?
Actually…
everyone was moved to a different place.
It's a safe place.
- I'm sorry, I-I don't, um…
- Oh.
Look, maybe you can help me? Here.
What are you doing?
He seems to want to go to his ship.
What now? Let go!
This ship is not your property…
entry is forbidden!
I am afraid you are forbidden
from boarding without permission.
My own ship?
- If there is something you need...
- Well, there is, yes.
My pistols and my men...
I keep asking to see them.
Your men were brought to Toranaga-sama's
city of Edo for their safety.
As for your guns,
we can fetch them if it becomes necessary.
Now look here, Mariko.
Your lord and I had an arrangement.
That ship and its crew now belong to me.
You're quite mistaken.
Your ship and crew
now belong to Toranaga-sama.
And he will use them as he wishes.
Well, thank you for the clarification.
Anjin-sama. This is Uejirou, the gardener.
Uh…
Sorry,
we do not use "sama" for Uejirou.
It is not proper.
Ah.
Your house is ready for inspection.
Right this way.
My house?
Everything here has been prepared
specially by your staff.
My staff?
You will find your sleeping room,
as well as Fuji-sama's room.
And the guest room
where I will be staying.
Perhaps you would like some tea
after a long journey?
Why have I been given all this?
It is only fitting for a hatamoto.
No... W-wait a minute.
How long am I expected to be here?
Nagakado-sama says
training will take at least six months.
Sorry. Six months?
You agreed to train these men,
you remember?
I do, yes.
For the return of my men and my ship.
Please be patient, Anjin-sama.
As hatamoto, you have been given a home,
a generous salary of 240 koku a year...
I don't want any generous cukoos.
And Fuji-sama as a consort.
Well, I'm sure she's very nice,
but I don't want a woman.
I don't wish to pillow her,
pillow on her or near her.
Or do any damn pillowing at all.
In any case, she will look
after your house and your servants,
and all your financial matters.
To refuse would be
a terrible insult to our lord.
Well, I do refuse.
I refuse all of this.
I came here under clear terms
with Toranaga.
Sorry, Toranaga-sama.
Now he's bloody vanished.
And I'm a bloody prisoner all over again.
Just with better living quarters.
Six months.
Six months…
To not even drink this saké…
That Toranaga…
You saved his life in Osaka,
and now he spits in your face.
So, Omi...
Have you found the rodent
who leaked word of the barbarian ship
to Toranaga?
Not just yet.
What have you been doing all this time?
Huh?
Perfuming your kosode?
He's only a boy.
Too young to be in charge of this village.
The gods are laughing at me!
Ishido probably thinks I've betrayed him.
I look fully committed
to this losing cause.
To train a gun regiment
with a barbarian
pretending to be hatamoto.
What the hell am I supposed to do?
This gun regiment…
It's still your regiment.
Huh?
If I may…
For now, you have the guns and the cannon.
Until Lord Toranaga returns,
it's all yours.
For all we know, the Council
may still find its fifth member.
Lord Toranaga can still be impeached.
So what?
You'd be left
with these guns and artillery,
which could still be
offered as a gift to Lord Ishido.
You really don't have to be here.
Go away.
She won't let me alone.
Wherever I go, she is.
It's not customary for one's consort
to sleep while he's awake.
Well, it's a foolish custom.
You should not walk on moss.
It is very disrespectful.
If I may…
I believe Fuji-sama merits better.
She is my late husband's niece.
Accomplished and highborn.
Well, that's absolutely wonderful for her.
And recently her husband
and infant son were put to death.
Her husband had insulted Ishido-sama,
and something had to be done
in order to prevent bloodshed.
Shouldn't she be grieving then?
Instead of following around
marooned Englishmen?
We grieve those we have lost
by continuing their fight.
Rubbish.
A child has no fight.
The child's father served Toranaga-sama.
And now, being your consort
allows Fuji-sama to do the same.
It gives her a place.
Well, you'd never know it to look at her.
Bereaved mother…
or widow.
Do you know of "The Eightfold Fence?"
From the time we are small,
it is something we are taught
to build within ourselves.
An impenetrable wall behind which
we can retreat whenever we need.
You must train yourself
to listen without hearing.
For instance, you can listen
to the sound of a blossom falling or…
the rocks growing.
If you really listen,
your present circumstance vanishes.
Do not be fooled by our politeness,
our bows, our maze of rituals.
Beneath it all,
we could be a great distance away.
Safe… and alone.
Tell him he can go to hell!
Omi-sama insists it is forbidden
to bring your weapons today.
Nonsense. Your people
bring swords wherever they go.
He says guns are different.
You must turn them over.
- No, understand? No!
- I'm not his prisoner anymore!
Where I come from,
you ask guests to do things.
Please wait! Please!
There is no need for this!
You are protected as hatamoto.
For some reason I just can't shake
the memory of our first meeting.
Give me the guns.
No!
No.
Mariko-sama.
Tell the Anjin to give his guns to me.
Give the guns to Fuji-sama.
She is your consort.
She will give her life to defend them.
- I can damned well defend myself...
- Anjin-sama!
Please give them to me.
Tell this milk-dribbling,
fuck smear I am ready to go.
With utmost respect,
the Anjin apologizes
for the misunderstanding.
The guns.
Please be on your way.
That was very good.
Very good.
Yabushige-sama says
his men do not need to learn basic skills
like loading or cleaning muskets.
The Portuguese brought us guns
50 years ago.
We are very experienced with it.
Yes, of course you are.
I want to start with tactics.
Foreign methods
that my enemies have not yet seen.
He asks about any tactics
our enemies might not yet know.
Right.
Tactics…
That was the agreement.
Lord Toranaga made this man
his great hatamoto…
Let's see him live up to it.
Well, then let me tell you about tactics.
I will begin by describing for you
a great battle.
We call it the Siege of Malta…
Malta… there was a siege…
Apparently it was a great battle.
Sixty thousand Islamic Turks,
the cream of the Ottoman Empire,
had come against 600 Christian knights
supported by a few thousand
Maltese auxiliaries
at their vast castle complex at St. Elmo.
Now, the knights had successfully
withstood the six-month siege,
and incredibly,
had forced the enemy to retreat in shame.
We are taught this victory saved
the whole Mediterranean seaboard,
- and thus christened them with the...
- Sorry. You said taught?
Yes.
When did this battle occur?
Well, it... 35, 40 years ago.
So you yourself
did not fight in this battle?
You were not even born
when this battle was fought.
Hey.
What are you asking him?
Sorry, I was trying to clarify something.
Perhaps you might start again,
except this time describe
a battle you have actually fought in.
Well, as I may have mentioned to your lord
on multiple occasions,
I am a sea pilot. Yes?
Not a great deal
of infantry battles at sea.
What's happening?
Mariko-sama,
please tell him that in my opinion,
gun tactics are useless
compared to the fine art
of English naval warfare.
Instead of tactics,
he wants to teach us
about English naval combat.
That castle in Osaka,
it's impregnable, yes?
With swords, even matchlocks,
to lay siege would take months.
But, anchor my ship and cannon
within a few thousand yards,
and your army
could breach the castle walls
without so much as an arrow's fletching
to graze their cheeks.
Just let me demonstrate.
Lift it up!
Alright. Move forward!
How do I say, um, "back"?
- "Back."
- "U-shi-ro."
How is it possible
for a cannon to hit this target?
Would you mind hitting the wedge?
This is foolish.
Cannon are never accurate.
The Portuguese tried this years ago.
Pierce your charge.
Prime. Now clear the hubs.
Fire!
Hmm.
Clear the hubs and fire!
Well done.
Perhaps his cannon are better.
And prime.
Prime!
Tell the men
to force the enemy to retreat.
Outline your vectors.
No, no. It's too early for that.
Excellent work.
This is beautiful.
The men are learning
a decent amount at a decent pace.
Yes. Toranaga-sama will be pleased.
There are other ways I could help him.
My Erasmus is a single ship,
but a fleet would be
something else entirely.
My men in Edo could help me
build him a navy.
Forgive me, Anjin-sama,
but I think you should remember
your oath is to Toranaga-sama
and not to the orders
that brought you here.
What orders?
Your crimes against the Portuguese.
I've read them in your own words.
It will be useful for you to know our lord
will never be turned against your enemies.
And it will be useful for you to be
reminded that we are at war,
both your lord and my queen,
and it happens that we have
enemies in common.
Those were Catholics
trying to kill him in Osaka.
Yes, trying to kill you.
Because they fear what I can offer him.
A modern navy. Ships built for war
would be to his benefit.
You have no idea what is or is not
to my lord's benefit.
Well, I suppose we both have
our masters to serve, don't we?
Jesus!
The hell was that?
Just a baby earthquake.
A... A baby what?
You will most certainly
experience more while you are here.
There are also tsunami
that come from the sea
and fires that break out
in the villages and cities.
It is why our houses are built to go up
as quickly as they come down.
Because death is in our air
and sea and earth.
It can come for us at any moment.
Before you meddle with our politics,
just remember
we live and we die.
We control nothing beyond that.
Baby earthquake.
I love you, Kiku…
Those cannon again…
Since that barbarian arrived,
all these bad tidings.
Mistress Kiku,
the Bird Who Sings at Night…
looking out for
the welfare of her village.
How impressive.
Don't tease me.
The whole village is uneasy
when your uncle is around.
My uncle is our lord.
He's a difficult man,
but whether or not this village prospers
is up to him.
If only you were our lord.
And then… Push.
Push.
Number four. Um... uh…
Four. Four.
Bring forth a chain shot.
Chain shot. A chain shot.
Push.
Yes. Yes.
Please. Thank you. Yes.
Now, the chain shot increases the radius
within which the damage occurs
and the nature of the damage itself.
You'll see, you'll see.
And…
That's it.
And clear.
And there we are.
Lord Ishido's men coming from the west!
They breached the checkpoint!
Nebara Jozen is leading the pack.
What's going on?
You look as if you're preparing for war.
Please understand…
That night, I had no idea
that Toranaga would escape.
An invitation.
You are to return to Osaka.
Renew your oath of loyalty to the Council
and accept the consequences
of your actions.
This is all a misunderstanding.
Then you refuse?
Kill me, and Ishido will lose
an essential ally.
So your mind is set.
I'll tell Lord Ishido
you've declared yourself his enemy.
Don't you see? There's a war coming.
Would you keep Ishido
from his only path to victory?
Huh?
Look.
The barbarian's cannon…
They're unlike any I've ever seen.
Enough to shrivel Christian balls.
I've known you for ages.
Please stay the night.
There's another practice tomorrow.
If you're not impressed,
I'll submit this head to Ishido myself.
Okay?
Fine.
Prepare quarters for Jozen and his men.
Tomorrow, they will witness
a demonstration of our artillery.
For what reason?
I wish for him to see
what our weapons are capable of.
Then he'll return to Osaka,
where all lords will quake
in the immensity of your father's power.
I look forward to quaking.
I've been summoned to Osaka.
To pledge my loyalty to the Council.
And you'll refuse.
Of course, Lord Nagakado.
That I'd betray your father…
the suspicion alone is upsetting.
I would give my life for your father.
I can't believe
I'm giving my life for this man.
If you go, they'll see your belly slit.
There's no way out.
It's absurd, this being my end.
There may be a solution.
And so the regents in Osaka
are pressuring Yabushige?
He will be declared a fugitive
for refusing their order,
but if he returns to Osaka, he will
no doubt be ordered to commit seppuku.
Eat. Please.
What have you got there?
This may be not for you.
How do you mean? Let me try some.
The Anjin
would like to try natto.
He seems quite determined.
Mariko-sama, would you mind
telling Fuji something on my behalf?
I wanted to apologize for the way
I behaved when I was first brought here.
The Anjin wishes
to apologize for his bad manners.
I believe this is how you offer gifts,
so excuse my crude wrapping.
I'd like to thank her
for her excellent service to this house.
I ask that she accepts this gift
as a gesture of my gratitude.
Those are the best guns a sailor can have
and I'll miss that one greatly.
But if she is one to do her job well,
she'll need the best.
He wishes to give you this gun.
What could I even do with this?
I'll teach you how to use them.
She'll be the most fearsome lady
in the Japans.
It's so you can
protect him well in the future.
I'd sooner pull a gourd from a horse.
He's trying to be kind.
Did I offend her?
They belonged to my father,
who is dead.
Please tell him
I can't be consort
to a man without swords.
Fuji-sama, as your consort,
would like you to carry her family swords.
They are a symbol
of her late father's bravery.
I can't accept this.
Please take them.
Fuji-sama rightly points out
that, as hatamoto,
it is not proper for you
to have no swords to carry.
So you must accept.
Please.
Thank you so… "gozirimasuru".
It's "gozarimasuru".
I'll get it right
one of these bloody days.
I remind you that you are
under no obligation to try this dish.
Hmm. Hmm.
It's a bit like cheese.
Very stinky…
possibly spoiled, cheese.
But, uh, quite enjoyable.
It is unfortunate
that Jozen witnessed the cannon.
I fear he'll bring news
of our tactics to Ishido.
Those cocky shit-eaters!
Perhaps we send word to your father?
Ask what he would do?
Everyone thinks I'm useless.
Just a spoiled, soft-handed Minowara brat.
But someone needs to stand up
for our name.
Still…
Without your father's permission,
best not to start a war.
Now you sound like him.
"Never make the first move."
"Wait for your enemy to make a mistake."
We're in a serious predicament.
If only your father would understand.
He never listens to others.
Then tomorrow
we'll have no choice
but to reveal our tactics to the enemy.
Omi.
Don't send word to my father.
I'll handle it.
Beautiful.
Oh.
- Shit.
- Sorry.
Fuji-sama said you were off on a walk.
Yes, I was.
I am happy to see
you have changed your mind about bathing.
Would you care to sit?
I came here to thank you
for your gift to Fuji-sama.
It was very meaningful for her to receive.
As her gift was to me.
I also wanted you to know
you're wrong about my service in Ajiro.
It has nothing to do with the church.
Oh.
Go on.
I have not told you my family name.
But it is well-known in Japan.
Many years ago…
a great injustice
stole everything from me.
For a long time, I have been unable
to seek resolution for what happened.
But recently
Toranaga-sama offered me a way.
What sort of resolution?
You said…
your houses here are designed to be…
rebuilt as quickly as they're destroyed.
So if a house is ruined and rebuilt,
and ruined and rebuilt 50 times over,
if I see it, I-I fail to see its ruins.
I see only a house.
And here I see much woman.
And one who owes me no explanations.
What is the name of it again?
The city of your birth?
London.
A city like Osaka?
Well…
A city, yes, but nothing like Osaka.
It's crowded, filthy.
Plenty to do though.
What would you do there
on a night like this?
Well, if you were with me,
all the way from the Japans,
I'd take you to see my queen.
Would she receive us?
Oh, yes, I'm sure.
And we'd tour
the grounds at Richmond Palace.
And sit down for a stuffy dinner.
And then to make up for it,
I'd take us all to see a play.
Do you have plays here?
Hmm, yes. They're very popular.
Though quite sad and tragic mostly.
Yes, we have tragedies.
Doomed lovers, cursed kings.
And after that?
I suppose we'd go for a walk.
Yes.
We'd sanpo suru along the Thames.
It's a big river.
Runs right through the city. And at night,
it's really... It's quite something,
and you can almost forget yourself.
And all your troubles and your past, and…
all the ways life seems to…
leave you wrecked.
They all just disappear.
And then you are free.
Yes.
I think so.
Good night, Anjin-sama.
The rain is very beautiful today.
Rain.
Good morning.
You seem in good spirits.
As I should be.
- After a night of good company.
- Hmm.
The courtesan was acceptable then.
I'm glad to hear it.
Fuji-sama and I thought
she would make a pleasing gift.
I don't understand. You're not, uh…
It was a very thoughtful gift.
Now he's carrying swords?
Talk about bad omen.
The targets for today's demonstration
have been coordinated by Nagakado himself.
Splendid!
Nagakado, maybe there's
a career for you in theater.
For this exercise,
the cannon will fire across the plain
and blast the targets
with perfect accuracy.
Nagakado.
Why don't you start.
Everyone, step away!
Step away!
- What's happening?
- I do not know.
- Step away!
- Yes, sir!
Nebara Jozen!
Your presence here is intolerable.
You have offended my father's name.
I demand compensation!
What is this?
Put away your sword.
Jozen is an official messenger
sent by the Regents!
Who ordered that?!
I did.
Son of Yoshii Toranaga…
Yoshii Nagakado ordered this!
This is a shocking act of provocation!
Your father will know of this!
I don't care.
In fact, I would like for him to know.
- Is no one going to stop him?
- Do not intervene.
This is not how samurai fight!
You're savages.
All of you...
Jozen...
It is war.