Previously on Shogun
She has always been ice.
But... With him, it's different.
Say something!
Buntaro! Look at me!
Don't move!
Thousands dead.
Our forces are in shambles.
The time has come
for Crimson Sky.
A single, violent
rush on Osaka Castle.
Lord Toranaga's half-brother...
Saeki Nobutatsu.
We could join forces with him.
I expect to be falsely impeached
Crimson Sky it will be.
The war is over!
Lord Toranaga has won!
My compliments, Lord Toranaga.
Not many men win
their first battle
before pillowing with
their first girl.
I formally surrender.
Tell your scribes that
Mizoguchi fought with honor.
It was fate that forced me into
declaring an unwinnable war.
I want it recorded that I was
seconded by the boy warlord.
Maybe we'll meet again
in the afterlife.
Maybe the one holding the sword
will be me.
How long since they last spoke?
Too long.
And if his brother says no?
Then this war is lost
before our swords are even wet.
Make sure the barbarian knows
to keep his mouth shut.
He understands, Lord.
In that nearby valley
I spied a decimated army.
Was it just me?
It's true.
My garrison endured much loss
in the recent earthquake.
So in your desperation,
you had no choice but to summon
the vast legions of
your mediocre brother.
You piss-drinking bastard!
I was looking forward to
a grand welcome by your forces.
My consorts were all
trembling in fear!
You look well, brother.
If you had nothing to do but
guard the still waters of Yuzenji,
you would also look good.
So the rumors are true.
You've tamed a barbarian.
Anjin.
Anjin-sama,
do not forget to bow.
It is an honor
to meet my liege lord's kin.
The honor is mine.
The Anjin is my hatamoto.
His cannon tactics are crucial
to our cause.
You have a proposal for me.
I do. The kind best
discussed tomorrow.
Tonight, we'll get
good and drunk.
I like this proposal already!
Samurai of the Kanto!
My men are eager to
spill blood by your side!
Thank you for coming, Saeki.
But first, I'm told there are
hot springs in the area.
Follow me.
It's usury...
One night for Kiku's services
cost 300 monme,
one week, twelve thousand?
Just to flirt with my
mongrel of a half brother.
Gin did begin
at a much higher price,
but I was able to
reduce her fee...
if you agreed to a private
meeting for one stick of time.
Absurd...
My lord wanted to see me?
During tonight's banquet
the Anjin will be on
his best behavior.
And he will wear his swords,
not his pistol.
As he is hatamoto.
Our lord urges you to be at
your best, and to please carry your swords
as is befitting a hatamoto.
Lord, may I ask...
Does this order of
Crimson Sky mean that
I am to be given maritime
command during our attack?
He asks about his
role during Crimson Sky.
As for the Anjin's
ship and his role...
I've decided nothing.
And that is the end of it.
Our lord has made no
decision regarding you or your service,
and I suggest you
take this no further.
Perhaps I misunderstand
these honors he has done to me.
Well, here I am bestowed countless gifts.
Titles, swords and fiefs.
But when it comes time to
actually serve him, I am ignored.
I'm beginning to wonder if these
gifts have any bloody meaning at all.
What exactly is...
Crimson Sky?
I did not bring him here
to discuss Crimson Sky.
I urge
you to let this go.
Please tell him I am ready
for whatever our fate may bring.
He says
he stands with you...
whatever fate may bring.
Well, if it isn't Lord Omi.
I came to request Lady
Kiku's company later.
Is she available?
A pity she's not.
For his brother, Lord Saeki,
Lord Toranaga has bought
one week of her time.
Surely I can just
speak with her...
For an eager young
samurai like you,
perhaps we could find
a more suitable courtesan?
No, I think not.
Ever since Kiku pillowed here
with the barbarian,
your Tea House has been spoiled.
What the Anjin does
in my Tea House
is not my business to discuss...
But from what I recall,
his mind was on someone
else that night.
Fuji!
Grandfather!
I'm so embarrassed,
I didn't know you'd be visiting.
I wished it to be a surprise.
You keep a clean home.
It's adequate.
I wanted to deliver
these myself.
When we parted in Osaka,
I promised I'd keep them safe.
Thanks to you, we are reunited.
When my service is complete,
I will end my life
and become ashes too.
Why not live?
And bask in the victory
they died to achieve.
Will there be victory?
Forgive me.
With so much
strength on our side
of course we'll have victory.
Your son, Buntaro...
We're honored to have him.
I hope Ishido sends
all of Osaka to face us.
I hear that your first
kill on the battlefield
is better than your first woman.
Where did you hear that?
Many speak of it that way.
Depends on the woman.
Your boy is finally a man!
The last time I saw Nagakado,
his chin was as
hairless as his balls.
Hey nephew,
I bet you have a different girl
for every day of the moon.
Just like your father.
Slander.
Your uncle is far more gifted with women.
More lies!
--What's funny?
Saeki-sama remarks about how long it has
been since he has seen Nagakado-sama.
It must bring you great honor...
Seeing your
wife perform her duty
to the Anjin with such devotion.
You mean her duty to our lord.
Uncle, you honor me
with these stories.
What was my father
like when he was young?
This is a good story!
Did you know that
your father was still a boy
when he won his first battle?
Yoshii Toranaga,
the boy warlord.
But that's not even the good part.
I'm told when the disgraced
Mizoguchi bowed to him in surrender,
it was your father,
just twelve years old,
who struck his enemy's head from
his shoulders with a single blow
Lord Saeki,
did you receive our lord's gift?
The courtesan, yes.
Many thanks.
She's beautiful, but
beauty's a fleeting pleasure.
Like trying to grasp a river,
or fuck a sunset.
Tomorrow we'll speak formally
on the matter of our alliance.
Why not tonight?
Patience.
Nonsense.
I can't live in this suspense!
What will the great Yoshii
Toranaga offer me for my army?
I quite like it here.
Perhaps my brother
would give me Izu?
Wouldn't
that be something.
Nephew.
I do have one more
story about my brother.
Not many know it.
He was once sent
away as a hostage,
to ensure our alliance
with the Imatani clan.
Our mother told him to be brave.
That a Minowara
does not feel fear.
But the moment he left her arms,
I'm told my brother
shat his pants
and rode his horse
for ten messy ri.
I mean no disrespect, of course.
I just meant to say,
I always felt for that horse...
Nagakado.
What do you prefer?
Stories, legends...
or the truth?
This proposal, for example.
What a legend that would make,
for me to become Lord of Izu.
Unfortunately...
I already received
another offer.
Huh?
Lord!
Saeki's army has blocked off
every road leading out of Izu!
Every checkpoint is
now being guarded.
On whose orders?!
"By order of the
Council of Regents:
we invite Lord Toranaga
to submit before us in Osaka,
and answer for his treachery.
He is to deliver his response
to Saeki Nobutatsu,
our ambassador
and newly appointed Regent."
Regent...?
So Ishido finally
managed to fill my seat.
What lord could
refuse this honor?
You're damning the Realm.
Nagakado...
Your formal sentence
for the murder of Nebara Jozen,
and the order to commit seppuku.
Don't accept it!
I am honored to consider
the Council's request.
I will thoroughly
contemplate this,
and submit my answer
tomorrow by sunset.
You and your vassals will remain
in Ajiro until your decision.
What happens if he surrenders?
We will be marched to Osaka and
forced to grovel at Ishido-sama's feet.
Toranaga-sama will be
sentenced to death.
And half his men will commit
seppuku out of allegiance to him.
My Erasmus is
still moored in that cove.
If you could get me the
clearance I need to go aboard,
then tonight I could go below, test
the bilges. Easy dive over the side.
Check the keel, she'll
need cleaning and scraping.
Yabushige's men could help with
stepping the spare bowsprit in the hole.
I fix the sail myself.
And then we could be out of
that channel in... We could...
What could we do, Anjin-sama?
Anything is better than
standing here pissing around.
Recently
you sent your general, Igarashi,
to negotiate a secret peace
with the Council.
Lord Ishido wanted
your general returned
with his response.
Muraji,
whose crest is that?
Ishido-sama.
Bloody wonderful.
Not even
a whisper of a plan?
Our lord is in contemplation.
At least let me ride out and
get word to our troops in Edo.
Saeki has eyes all
over this mountain.
We'd be dead before you got there.
Father.
What have you decided?
Do we die with
blood on our swords?
Why is it that only those who
have never fought in a battle
are so eager to be in one?
Well, well.
Lord Toranaga...
Forgive me for the trouble,
but Lady Mariko did promise me
a stick of your time.
Go back to counting your silver.
Can't you see we're busy?
No, Nagakado.
A promise is a promise.
Who can say how many sticks
of time we have left?
I humbly thank you
for this honor.
Even when your future
is out of reach,
you would kindly
indulge my ideas for it.
What is it you want?
Do you know what it means
to live in the Willow World?
It means pouring out your life
in service of great men.
Your youth, energy,
wit, and charm...
all of it is given away.
Then your flower wilts with age,
and you are discarded.
Why is any of this my concern?
You're building a
new city in Edo.
I think it could set a standard
for the future.
There is no future
for some of us.
Still, in Edo...
Please take the Willow World
under your protection.
Even after you're gone.
Imagine a district contained
within its borders.
No longer brothels, but Tea
Houses like I've made here.
All gathered in the same place.
And the formation of a guild
for courtesans.
Grant us this bright future.
Let us age with the grace we
devote our youth to cultivating.
Please...
Thank you for this
novel distraction.
But...
I'm afraid my future is too short
for your far reaching plans.
Is it?
Your advisors believe
your end is near,
but myself, I wonder...
My fate is written.
Fate is like a sword.
Useful only to those
who can wield it.
I was born in a gutter.
Raised as a ukareme.
Most would curse such
a loathsome fate.
But my hardships taught me
ambition and guile,
and made me
the most successful Lady in Izu.
Just as your hardships
made you into the cunning man
you are today.
It's only that it
doesn't make sense...
Lord Toranaga.
Any spy could tell him
about the army coming his way...
Why leave your weakened garrison
so exposed?
Why make such a
careless mistake?
Do you assume any of
this to be my will?
After the earthquake
that decimated my army?
My apologies, Lord.
I must have misunderstood.
What do I know?
I'm just an old whore.
And my stick of
time is finished.
Seems there's not
enough water to share.
Huh?
So good.
What makes you so certain
our lord has a plan?
What else is there?
Surrender?
My father wouldn't know how.
Sometimes I wish we could
go back to our old lives...
before that barbarian
ship arrived.
When this was just
a sad and poor fishing village.
That's true.
But life here was peaceful.
So much has been taken
from us since then.
Every good thing we've ever had
is now gone because
we reached for more.
We just need a plan.
We'll bring down as many of
these spineless pigs as we can...
"Spineless pigs"?
Your insults are as
dull as your blades.
None of this has been easy for
me, you know.
Your father and me...
we've had our troubles.
But we are still family.
Aren't you ashamed
of what you've done?
There's no shame
in thinking about one's legacy.
Think about yours, Nagakado.
To be slaughtered
like chickens...
Forgotten before
you could even be remembered...
If it's my fate, then it
will be a beautiful death.
That's not beauty.
Death...
is just a lonely
path in the woods.
Bet by now you're wishing
it had been you in that pot.
Your end would
have been swifter.
I'm bound to this fate.
Every death I escape,
there's another waiting.
First on that cliff.
Then in Osaka.
Now this.
Why am I speaking to you.
It's like pissing in the wind.
You don't even know
how to use that.
Draw it.
Hurry.
This
appears to be occurring.
Hold it properly.
Two hands.
One more time.
Pick it up!
Again? Uh...
I see what this is. I'm a fucking sailor.
I don't know this blade from the handle.
I don't understand
a word you're saying.
Pick it up now.
Um... Now I am
picking up the sword calmly.
What's so funny?
What are you doing?
Well, go on then.
Might as well be now.
You would have died
if I wasn't here.
You idiot.
You're still too hurt
to swing a naginata.
If there will be
war, I must fight.
It will be good
to finally fight.
We'll honor the memory of those
who've gone ahead.
Like your late husband.
What Tadayoshi did for
my father that day...
It should have been me standing
up to Ishido and his insults.
If I'd been braver,
maybe Tadayoshi and your son
would still be with us.
We do what we can, when we can.
We can only hope it's enough.
All lands in Okazaki
should be passed to my
grandchildren when they come of age.
And also...
Gin.
Have two cho of land
in Edo set aside
for her to use as she wishes.
Lord, Toda Hirokatsu!
Lord, with due respect...
I have something urgent
to discuss with you.
I ask that my wife remain.
Before we die,
I beg permission
to take the barbarian's head.
Why?
He's only aligned with you
out of his own interests.
And...
I don't like the way
he looks at my wife.
You accuse this man of soliciting
the affections of your wife?
Yes.
And Mariko is encouraging this.
Is that what you're saying?
I ask permission to take his
head, not hers.
Answer the question!
If you thought this true,
you would have to take her head
the same instant.
What do you say?
My life is for my
husband to take.
I...
I don't accuse my wife.
Then you cannot
accuse the Anjin.
How is this to end?
My words were petty.
Please forgive me.
Where do
you stand in this?
I am your servant.
You keep saying that,
yet you constantly confuse your
priorities with this barbarian.
There is no confusion.
No more having things two ways.
We are one thing or the other.
Are you with me in our fight
against your father's enemies,
or are you with the barbarian?
I order you to choose!
Lord...
I have...
served you loyally
and utterly.
But I beg you...
every hour I wait for death
is like drowning in
a river of anguish.
Tonight...
Let it end.
Free me
of this cursed life.
Last night,
when my brother told
that ridiculous story...
why didn't you speak up?
Forgive me for not defending you
from those insults.
No. Not that one.
The one about
beheading the general.
Mizoguchi.
Oh.
It's absurd.
A single stroke?
You were there.
It was nine times
before that head came off.
What a fucking mess you made.
Who picks a child
to be his second?
Your formal answer, please.
Lord Saeki...
I bow before you
and agree to travel to Osaka,
where I will submit to the will
of the Council before Lord Ishido.
He has surrendered.
Lord, if I may...
- You may not.
- But father...
I've decided.
Even when there's
evil in this land,
no one has the right
to tear the Realm apart.
Crimson Sky...
was a mistake.
Yabushige-sama.
Nagakado-sama.
Behold,
the great warlord.
The brilliant
master of trickery...
who tricked his own loyal vassals
into a noiseless smothering.
You're all dead.
Crimson
fucking horseshit.
We'll send word to the Council.
Tomorrow you will
leave for Osaka
under my escort until you've
reached the castle gates.
From this day, you
have nowhere to go...
and nothing left to be.
When this is over,
I'll bring you to my castle in Edo.
Build you a palace of your own.
My seventh consort.
Luckiest of them all.
Lord...
Would you allow me
to... elevate our play?
We have other tools
to enhance your pleasure.
Show me.
Trying to finally become a man?
Lord!
Where is the beauty in this.