[Toranaga, in Japanese]
Previously on Shogun.
[in English] My name is Toda Mariko.
I am to be your interpreter.
[in Japanese] He claims there is
a Portuguese base in Macao.
What do you seek in Japan?
[in English]
To vanquish our common enemies.
Lord Toranaga invited Mother
to meet a barbarian.
If you had this barbarian,
and a vassal to control him,
things might be different.
You do have a way
of being in the right place
at the right time.
[in English] I found this on your ship.
We show these to the Japanese
and he will be hanged for piracy.
[in Japanese]
There's so much I don't know.
Perhaps we should learn more
about these bases
before negotiating further arrangements.
[in English] He's denied
our departure papers for the Black Ship.
Let this be my burden, Father.
[grunts]
[in Japanese]
The assassin didn't come for me.
[pants, grunts]
She came for him.
[chuckles]
It's a good will.
Our best yet.
[squire] Will it really be today?
[sighs]
Your sword.
You heard about last night's attack?
What do you know
about the society of the Amida?
[inhales deeply]
Only what everyone knows.
They are assassins.
Sworn by the most sacred oaths
of the Buddha Amida.
And for my head…
What might you pay?
[door closes]
[breathes deeply]
You've decided to take my life, fine.
Let's be done.
Aren't you my reliable friend?
Or has Ishido poured poison in your ear?
I'm told he visited your home.
What was his offer?
Your seat on the Council.
Did it interest you?
[chuckles]
Absolutely not.
Then what do you want?
The Suruga Province.
To expand my fief.
But I'd need my head to rule.
You shall keep it.
The assassin was sent to kill the Anjin.
So for their safety,
I need the Anjin and Lady Kiri
brought to your fishing village in Ajiro.
Do this,
and Suruga is yours.
And what will you do here?
Watch the morning with me.
[Martin, in English]
My apologies, Captain-General.
But your Black Ship must stay where it is.
Toranaga has come to better understand
the great profits being made
from our monopoly over the China trade.
He has invited us to provide a report
on our rates of exchange.
You… [stammers] …men of the cloth
with your impotent pricks.
We bring the profits. We dictate terms.
And we are here at their pleasure.
Until Toranaga receives this report,
you won't get clearance to leave.
I am sitting on one million ducats
that has to get to Macao.
I won't lose this wind.
That pilot should have been taken care of
before he even reached Osaka.
Captain, you forget yourself.
And you forget I don't work
for the Church. I work for the Crown.
Let it be known
the Black Ship sails tonight.
[groans]
Get all the cargo on board.
We're leaving anyway.
H-Hey, hey. [grunting]
We... We leave without clearance,
we don't get invited back.
The longer we sit around,
the worse that pilot makes it for us.
We're on the wind tonight.
A pilot?
[chuckles]
He's still alive. I'll be fucked.
[Blackthorne] He's going to bleed me then.
I'm sorry? I do not understand.
This warlock here.
He aims to bleed me to release
the foulness from my blood. [winces]
I'm not familiar with this warlock,
but I can assure you this man is a doctor
- who cares for the sick and injured.
- [winces]
[in Japanese] Please hold still.
[in English]
What's been said about the assassin?
Only that she belonged
to a very dangerous sect.
[Blackthorne groans]
She had served as a palace maid for years.
Some train their whole lives
for a single kill.
It is very costly.
[Blackthorne] A price few could afford.
You refuse… [grunts] …to see it,
what those priests
are capable of even now.
Christ! [groans]
How much are the Jesuits
paying this one to kill me?
[in Japanese] He's too tense.
He doesn't need a doctor...
He needs a woman.
"Onago ja." What did he say?
What did the warlock say?
Since you are so upset,
the doctor suggests we send a woman
to pillow with you instead.
Pillow?
Uh, it is polite for the physical joining
of a man and woman.
[grunts] If he's not a warlock,
he's most certainly a pimp.
Would you prefer a male companion?
Dear God, where am I?
[in English] Who's he?
[in Japanese]
Is the animal behaving himself?
Yes, Buntaro.
We're leaving Osaka immediately.
The barbarian is to join us.
Where are we going?
Back to Ajiro,
with members of Toranaga's clan.
I don't understand...
It's not for you to understand.
[sliding door closes]
[sniffles]
[gasps]
Thank you for this gift of their remains.
I'm grateful, Grandfather.
There's a party leaving for Ajiro tonight.
Our lord commands you to join them.
Your father gave his life
for those swords.
In Korea,
we fought until we were as good as dead,
and then we kept fighting.
Those are the swords of a samurai.
I'm sorry for your husband and baby.
But they died because
they belonged to a greater fight.
And now…
it's your turn.
[samurai speak Japanese]
We'll move around the city
by cover of the forest,
then regroup at the galley.
Expect a fight.
There are many who want the Anjin dead.
[samurai speaks Japanese]
Your father isn't coming?
He insists on staying.
Then it's goodbye for good.
Lord, your will.
Not today.
[in English] May I at least speak
with Toranaga before we go?
I'm afraid it will not be possible.
[in Japanese]
The barbarian will walk beside the litter,
and remain within sight.
[in English] Yabushige-sama asks that
you stay close to the litter as we walk.
[in Japanese] Mother!
Please don't go.
You'll be brought to your
grandfather's castle, where it's safer.
You're not a suckling child!
Go back inside.
What is Kiri no kata doing?
Coming, Hiromatsu.
I'm a tired old woman.
You must forgive me.
On any other day I would.
I wish I could leave this prison with you.
When I see you again,
your child will be here.
[Hiromatsu] This is taking too long…
[speaks Japanese]
Hurry. You should be on your way.
Lord! There's someone at the gate!
[samurai] Someone's coming!
It's Lord Ishido!
[grunting]
[sighs]
[grunts]
A fine afternoon, Yabushige.
I was just informed
the barbarian was leaving Osaka.
And Kiri no kata as well.
A surprise, I must say.
[Yabushige speaks Japanese]
With all due respect...
Lady Kiri is not a hostage
who begs favors.
She's free to come and go.
This is true,
but your father and I agreed on protocol
during his visit.
A day's notice
before the departure of high people,
so I can pay respects.
Jozen. Proceed with the inspection.
Grays are forbidden through this gate!
That's agreed by protocol.
You haven't even seen a battle,
you brazen brat.
Why not here?
- Why not now?
- [laughs]
A misunderstanding, I'm sure.
Lord Ishido honors us
by paying his respects.
Let him through.
Excuse me.
[Ishido speaks Japanese]
Lady Kiri.
Sorry to see you go.
And I'm sad to leave,
but my lord says
there are too many assassins in Osaka.
I feel the same way.
I'm told the barbarian
was attacked last night.
I'll have Jozen and my men
escort you to the galley.
That won't be necessary.
As protector of Osaka Castle, I insist.
- [Shizu grunts]
- [servant speaks Japanese]
- [samurai speaks Japanese]
- [Shizu groans]
[servant] Here, sit down.
Lady Shizu is having pains again.
[Shizu] I'm all right, really…
[servant] The doctor said
she needed more rest.
[Shizu pants] Please don't worry.
[servant] She's in her final weeks!
[servant, Shizu speak Japanese]
I'm fine.
Well, everything's in order.
[speaks Japanese]
I wish you a safe journey.
[horses approaching]
Lord Ishido was confused
by your sudden departure.
No doubt he understands
I must serve my pledge to Toranaga.
And please remind your lord,
I keep my promises.
Well done.
[sighs]
Now…
it's in the hands of the gods.
[in English] Did you know?
I think no one knows.
My lord is famous for his trickery.
When he was six years old,
his father traded him to a rival busho.
As a hostage, he learned one truth.
That enemies are everywhere
and friends, nowhere.
To show your true heart
is to risk your life.
What happens if he's found?
He will be killed. And all of us.
Hold them at the gate!
I need to verify all members of the party.
Lord Ishido cleared us to depart.
It is Lord Ishido's order.
[groans]
All travelers are to be verified.
[travelers murmur]
- [in English] No one's going to stop him?
- [guard speaks Japanese]
[door closes]
[in English] No one's going to stop him.
This is unacceptable.
Peering into ladies' private quarters?
It's not proper!
What is the barbarian saying?
[in English] Worse than that, it's vulgar!
Unholy perversion!
[in Japanese]
I think the barbarian is offended.
In his country it is improper to…
leer at women.
This is Japan!
[in English] Am I the only man present
who treasures the purity of a woman?
- [grunts]
- [gasps, breathes shakily]
[in Japanese] You must excuse him.
He's ignorant of our customs.
[grunts, shouts]
[in English]
A woman's virtue is her glory!
A blight on us all!
My God, the shame of it.
[in Japanese]
His customs are very different,
and I find it's very hard to reach him…
[in English]
You, sir, are a silly little man.
And your hair looks
like the tail of a pony!
[in Japanese] What is this buffoonery?
Lord Ishido has ordered us all
to the harbor.
Let them through.
- [horse whinnies]
- [samurai speaks Japanese]
[in English] Well, I hope he didn't mind
the part about the pony.
[sighs]
[in Japanese] This is the man
we're risking our lives for…
[in English] What happens when
Ishido's men learn who they are escorting?
I'm certain my lord has a plan.
Is it true what you said
about the purity of women in your country?
Christ, no.
Foul slatterns and trollops
everywhere in London.
Like your doctor friend,
whoring women to injured guests.
[chuckles]
You yourself insinuating that I would have
an interest in casual buggery.
We think pillowing is necessary
to good health.
In fact, some say
the moment of the clouds and the rain
is as near to heaven as they can get.
The clouds and the rain.
- It means...
- Thank you, I understand the metaphor.
I've just never heard it
put so poetically.
Especially by a married woman.
I'm assuming that man's your husband.
Yes. His name is Toda Hirokatsu.
Though friends call him Buntaro. He's, uh…
a strong and admired warrior.
- And the boy your only child?
- Mm-hmm.
Do you have children?
Yes.
My boy Tudor and my daughter Elizabeth.
And what are they like?
[sighs]
[arrow whistling]
- [grunts]
- [travelers gasp]
- [Mariko gasps]
- [Buntaro shouts in Japanese]
[Blackthorne, in English] Get down! Fast!
- [breathes heavily]
- [arrow whistling]
[grunts]
[samurai shouts]
- They're on the ridge.
- [samurai 2 speaks Japanese]
[grunts]
- [in English] Is it Ishido-sama?
- [pants]
No, I do not think so.
- [gunshot]
- [samurai speaks Japanese]
[samurai 2 shouts in Japanese]
- [grunts]
- [ambusher yelps]
[servant speaks Japanese]
[grunts]
Father…?!
[servant whimpers]
- [grunts]
- [ambusher 2 yelps]
[grunts]
[in English]
Get back before we're all killed.
[samurai 3 shouts in Japanese]
It's the Christians.
They've come again for the Anjin.
[samurai 2 speaks Japanese]
Lord Kiyama...
Ishido's men are down there too!
Then they'll die with the heretic.
- [samurai 2 speaks Japanese]
- [samurai shouting]
Here they come.
[samurai grunting]
It's Toranaga…
We've been betrayed!
Lord Jozen...
Toranaga was hiding in the caravan!
He's here!
Huh?
Don't let Toranaga get away!
[Jozen grunts, speaks Japanese]
[samurai grunting, shouting]
[in English] We have to help him.
[grunting]
[shouts]
[ambusher 3 shouts, grunts]
[in Japanese]
Are they… fighting each other?
Something isn't right…
[samurai grunting]
[ambusher 4 grunts, yelps]
[panting]
One of these days
I'd like to know about your plan
before it happens.
I'll keep it in mind.
Lord Ishido must be informed!
[samurai 4 speaks Japanese]
[samurai 5 speaks Japanese]
[samurai speak Japanese]
- [samurai 3 speaks Japanese]
- [sighs]
- [shouting]
- [Mariko grunting]
[grunting]
Hurry to the ship!
We'll hold them off here
and catch up to you later.
[grunts]
Alert the men in the harbor.
The heretic is on his way.
[speaks Japanese]
[Blackthorne, in English] To the galley
while we still have the chance.
[Mariko] Wait, this crew may be hostile
to Toranaga-sama.
[indistinct chattering]
[Blackthorne] Well, I'll be damned.
I know this crew.
You think I'm friendless?
[pants] Captain-sama.
[in Japanese] Anjin!
[chuckles]
[in English]
We sailed together out of Ajiro.
Is that what I think it is?
The Portuguese Black Ship.
Their trading vessel.
[Blackthorne] Ready the oars.
What was that damn word again? Ah!
[in Japanese] Now, row.
[ambusher 5] Toranaga is escaping Osaka!
Everyone get to the harbor!
[ambushers shouting]
[ambusher 5 speaks Japanese]
Wait!
Buntaro! He's coming!
[in English] We got to go back.
We must continue on!
[in English] Oh, for Christ's sake,
he could still make it.
[ambusher 6 speaks Japanese]
[Buntaro grunts]
[grunts]
[panting]
[in Japanese] Toda Hirokatsu!
[breathes shakily]
[shouts]
[ambushers shout]
[Buntaro shouting, grunting]
Lose the rowboats and sound the drum.
There's no time to spare.
[samurai speaks Japanese]
[samurai speak Japanese]
[samurai 2 speaks Japanese]
[samurai 3 speaks Japanese]
[samurai 4 speaks Japanese]
- [in English] Ah, Mariko-sama.
- [samurai 3 speaks Japanese]
- [in English] Do they fish at night here?
- [samurai 4 speaks Japanese]
Toranaga was with them all along.
Yabushige betrayed us.
Those boats blocking their escape…
are they Kiyama's men?
[in English] If we attempted
to break through those men
- would they board and attack us?
- Yes.
Then we're sunk.
[in Japanese] We die.
[in English] But they can't sink her.
[in Japanese]
He wants us to approach the Black Ship.
Towards that carrack!
[in English]
If you leave without clearance,
you will ruin any chance
we have left at diplomacy.
I will ruin more than that with pleasure.
This is not a debate, Captain-General.
It is in your best interest
to follow protocol.
Captain-General,
it's, uh, quite a show upstairs.
Might want to see it.
[speaking indistinctly]
Ahoy, Inglés! [chuckles]
Still alive, I see!
How's your leg?
[Rodrigues] Fine! How's your mother?
- Dead!
- Ah.
Behold, I bring you Lord Yoshii Toranaga,
who seeks an audience!
Ferrying around the man himself!
It's one way to die!
[chuckles]
[Martin] Toranaga claims
the men in fishing boats are pirates.
He requests an escort through the harbor.
[in Japanese]
If your Black Ship protects my galley,
you have my permission
to leave Osaka harbor.
[in English] He's giving clearance
for the Black Ship to leave Osaka.
[scoffs] Thank him for permission
I don't need,
but the price just went up.
[in Japanese]
The Captain feels this is not enough.
[Toranaga scoffs]
In that spirit, how about this…
When the Black Ship leaves Macao,
it will carry
ten thousand tael silver coins for me
to invest in the silk trade.
Half the profit would be his.
[Martin, in English] Toranaga offers you
10,000 silver coins to invest.
- [chuckles]
- He would retain half the profit.
Yes.
[Toranaga] Hmm.
[in Japanese] Also Tsuji,
I offer something to you.
In my home city of Edo,
I will allow the construction
of a Christian church.
[in English]
He's giving us a church in Edo.
[in Japanese] In exchange,
I need your help
with Lords Kiyama and Ohno.
How do you mean?
They are allied with Ishido right now.
I need you to bring them to my side.
[in English] He asks us to turn
the Christian lords in his favor.
That is bribery. And impossible.
Eminence, it is a church in Edo.
We will not compel men by faith.
Especially not on this man's behalf.
Although, we could suggest such an idea.
Prayerfully, of course.
[slurping]
[in Japanese]
The Father-Visitor pledges his assistance.
Fine.
Now rid me of these pirates
so I may leave Osaka.
[Captain, in English]
There is just one more thing.
That English pilot, he stays behind.
[in Japanese] He asks that
you leave the heretic in Osaka.
The Anjin is my guest.
[Martin speaks Japanese]
I must warn you
about this man you've taken in.
He is not the merchant he claims to be.
[in English] Well done, Martin.
We will be able to hold him
to that promise of a church.
Even after he is dead.
[in Japanese] All lords and ladies
are to be brought to the Portuguese ship.
And our guns?
Lord Toranaga has been forced
to abandon them.
And the Anjin.
[distant shouting]
[in English] The Black Ship
will bring us out of Osaka.
But you must stay.
I'm sorry.
[samurai speak Japanese]
[sailors speak indistinctly]
[sailor, in English] Tie down that line.
[sailors shouting]
Fuck this.
Captain-sama, sound the drums.
[in Japanese] Sound the drum!
[sailors speaking Japanese]
[sailor speaks Japanese, grunts]
[sailors continue speaking Japanese]
[sailors grunting]
[shouting indistinctly]
[sailor 2, in English] Hoist it up!
Come on! I thought you were sailors!
Race them out!
[speaks broken Japanese]
He means 'faster'!
[sailors grunting]
[sailor 3, in English]
Sir, he's coming up alongside us.
[sailor 4] H-Hey! Steady!
How fast can that bitch go, Rodrigues,
you black-eyed son
of a shit-festered whore?
Your lips are on the devil's arse!
They're on your mother's first!
[chuckles]
Might even miss the son of a bitch.
He gets any closer, sink him!
[chuckling] With pleasure, Captain.
[whispers indistinctly]
[speaking Japanese]
[laughs]
[sailors shouting indistinctly]
They'll never get through, Lord.
[sailors speaking indistinctly]
[sailors grunting]
[in Japanese] He's mad.
[sailor shouts indistinctly]
[sailors continue grunting]
- [in English] Five points to port.
- Aye, sir. Five points to port!
- [sailor 5] Five points!
- [sailor 6] Go watch the gulch!
Five points it is.
[ambushers shouting]
- [ambusher shouting in Japanese]
- [laughs]
[ambusher 2 shouts]
- [shouting continues]
- [ambusher 3 shouts]
[in English] My sincerest gratitude!
My sincerest "fuck yourself!"
I warned you once, Rodrigues.
They'll never keep me here!
You're not out yet, you salty whale's tit!
[in Japanese] Anjin!
Look out!
[sailor 7 speaks Japanese]
[laughs, in English]
Let's see him ride out of this one.
[breathes deeply]
[sailors grunting]
[in Japanese] Hurry! Hurry!
[grunting continues]
- [in English] Bring him over broadside!
- [sailor 8] Maintain speed, maintain!
Damage the hull, Captain.
[sailor shout indistinctly]
- Five more points!
- [sailor 9] Hold steady!
[sailor 10]
They're going to crash into the shores!
[sailors grunting]
Either sink me or let me pass,
but make up your fucking mind.
[sailors shouting, groaning]
[laughs]
By Christ's blood, Captain-sama!
[shouts] What the hell are you doing?
You're giving him the edge!
No. No, he already had it.
[in Japanese] He did it!
[chuckles]
Well done, you glorious bastards!
- Yes! Yes!
- [stomping on floor]
Well done, you glorious bastards!
Well done!
That's a debt repaid.
God be with you. You'll need him.
[chuckles]
[in Japanese] It appears they got through.
[samurai speak Japanese]
Mariko.
Please thank the Captain-General
for the use of his ship.
But seeing as my pilot has left Osaka,
I'll now return to my galley.
Men wish to conduct their affairs
with the blade, I do not object.
But when there's violence in the city
I swore to protect
I consider it a personal affront.
I share your outrage over last night.
Too many bandits in this city.
We agreed on a lawful execution
of that barbarian.
Yet Toranaga stole him from my custody,
and you did nothing.
In a matter of days,
there would have been no Toranaga.
I'd have handed you the heretic myself.
- [Jozen speaks Japanese]
- [footsteps approaching]
Pardon me.
[speaks Japanese]
Lord Hiromatsu has come with a message.
Esteemed Regents.
Lord Toranaga regrets that
for personal reasons
he has decided
to resign from the Council.
With apologies.
This piece of paper changes nothing.
We'll impeach him, four to none.
As would be your right.
But if I recall…
the Taikō required five Regents
for any vote.
And now…
I fear you have only four.
[inhales deeply]
This galley will carry me to Edo,
where I have business.
You will remain in Ajiro
and help Yabushige train a new regiment.
But Yabushige conspires with Ishido.
He was betraying us in the open…
And?
…and I am your son.
Why am I so unworthy of your trust?
When will you understand,
you are playing a game
of friends and enemies…
when you have only yourself in this life.
[grunts]
[in English] Good morning.
Good morning.
I'll never tire of this weather.
Soon it will be winter.
It is a very difficult season in Japan.
Try England.
It's humid in the summer.
Endless winters.
And, of course, famine every six years.
Still, you must look forward
to going home.
To be reunited with your family at least.
Last night you asked about my daughter.
The truth is I've never met her.
I left England before she was born.
One year, eleven months,
six days from Amsterdam.
She'll be two years old now.
You serve your lords honorably.
I have no lords.
I left of my own accord.
And this, this is what beckoned me.
The horizon more than the deep.
The freedom more than the horizon.
The fair wind.
To be far enough out that you look around
and there's nothing but open seas.
No yesterday. No tomorrow.
Just today.
I'm sorry about your husband.
[in Japanese] Please thank the Anjin
for his assistance in Osaka.
He acted bravely.
[Mariko, in English]
He thanks you for your bravery.
[in Japanese] Our Christian friends
gave me a gift before we parted…
[in English] My lord says
this was a gift from the priests.
[Toranaga, in Japanese]
I'm told they are proof of piracy.
[Mariko, in English]
They prove you are a pirate.
[in Japanese] A crime punishable by death.
[in English] Which means death.
[sailor speaks Japanese]
Of course…
these will take a long time to translate.
[in English] My lord says
he will have to have them translated,
and that it will likely take a long time.
[in Japanese] In the meantime,
we must prepare for war.
I would like him to train a regiment
in foreign tactics
using the weapons from his ship.
[in English] He would like you
to assemble a regiment
and teach them your tactics.
I'm sorry but I'm just a sailor.
I'm not familiar with…
[Mariko speaks Japanese]
Please tell him it would be a great honor.
[in Japanese] He says he would be honored.
All I ask for in exchange is
the return of my men and my ship.
[Mariko speaks Japanese]
- Yabushige.
- [speaks Japanese]
You and my son will learn
everything there is to know
about the way barbarians war.
I understand.
And as he will now be my vassal,
we can't keep calling him 'barbarian'.
I proclaim him…
'Hatamoto'.
[in English] He has made you hatamoto,
which is a very great honor.
Oh.
Uh…
[in Japanese] Thank you.
[sighs]
[in Japanese] Now, please ask the Anjin
if he would join me for a swim.
[breathes heavily]
[in English] My lord would like you
to teach him how to dive.
[grunts]
It's best to start
from the top of the gunwale.
Jump in headfirst while extending
your hands to break the water.
[in Japanese] Show me.
[pants, in English] Observational learner.
[panting]
[in Japanese] Again.
- [in English] He says, "Again."
- Ah.
[grunts]
[panting]
How many more times must I do this?
- Until he is satisfied.
- [grunts]
[continues panting]
[in Japanese]
Perhaps he can try again tomorrow.
[breathes heavily]
Tomorrow is tomorrow.
Today I will learn how to dive.
[panting]
Wait.
If I asked for a race to the shore,
would the Anjin join me?
[in English] My lord would like
to race you to the shore.
But I warn you not to let him win.
My lord hates that.
I wouldn't dare.
[in Japanese] Here we go.
[speaks Japanese]
[grunts, inhales deeply]