Previously on Shogun
Look who it is!
He's alive!
Tell him about the disgusting,
filthy line you come from.
I am daughter
of the late Lord Akechi Jinsai.
My father's Lord was ruler of Japan
before the Taiko.
So my father killed him
out of love for the Realm.
Get back!
Your husband's brutality
is no fault of yours.
We should not be seen together.
From this day forward, the only words
we share will be from others' lips.
Father!
Father. Look…
Mother!
Glad you've returned safely,
Lady Ochiba.
I'm told the Council is outmaneuvered.
The time for politics has come to an end.
The Council will answer to me.
This is Mariko.
She's the daughter of Akechi Jinsai,
my new vassal.
Make her feel welcome.
You got something to say to me?
You insolent lout!
Why are they so angry with each other?
Akechi wait…
Be patient.
I know how you're feeling…
Now is not the time.
Go back to bed, Mariko.
You're only dreaming.
Ippon!
She's good.
Enough!
I don't understand
why he's doing this…
Your marriage to Buntaro
will be an alliance
for both families to smile on.
That's a joke.
You know the Toda clan is
a worthless alliance.
But your father treasures you.
Then why is he casting me away?
Mariko.
All these years
and I still don't understand you.
We have every privilege.
Let us choose to look away
from what we cannot control.
Mariko…
my most cherished daughter.
It pains me to see you
with so many questions.
You have always been an obedient child,
but now I ask that you serve
something greater…
Your duty is what endures.
There is nothing more.
We have all suffered
so much loss…
You may feel unable
to bear the weight of it.
But death is the end of having lived.
It is an affirmation of life itself.
Anjin.
Come forward.
During the earthquake,
the Anjin saved my life for a second time.
I will grant him
a fief near Kanagawa, worth 600 koku.
For your bravery,
he has decided to grant you a fief
that will provide an annual salary
of 600 koku.
He is now chief admiral of the Kantō.
And general in charge
of our cannon regiment.
He has also made you his chief admiral
and general of the cannon regiment.
For all those who lost their lives…
their deaths will not be wasted.
Thousands dead.
Reports are even worse in the north.
We'll never be able
to face Ishido like this.
So…
The Anjin now commands
the cannon regiment?
It's Toranaga's decision.
The army used to be mine,
but now it's out of my hands.
Even so...
For a barbarian...
What are you on about?
Our forces are in shambles.
Any day now
we'll be dragged into this fruitless war,
and your concern is just one barbarian?
Time to write another will.
Our Father, who art in heaven…
…hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on Earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread.
And forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
For thine is the kingdom…
…the power and the glory,
for ever and ever.
- Amen.
Lord, for the way I've embarrassed you…
I am truly ashamed.
Not me.
You've embarrassed your household,
and the home of my hatamoto.
I am no longer useful to you.
I lose myself when I'm around her.
Then divorce her.
Please forgive me…
Not now, after all these years.
After her father's treachery,
I thought she'd be grateful
I spared her life.
But she has always been ice.
Asking for death, again and again.
For years, the ice has not melted.
But…
With him, it's different.
My Lord,
you have another visitor.
Mariko is only doing what I demand of her,
which is more than I can say of you.
I order you…
To isolate yourself from her
for seven days.
Yes, sir.
Anjin.
The Anjin asked for my time.
Please tell him I am sorry
about what happened to his army.
He says he is sorry for your army.
However, I must ask
why he lavished me with the gift
of his cannon regiment last night.
These many gifts
you've blessed him with...
He wishes to know why.
He questions my generosity?
He asks if you refuse them.
It's not a matter of refusing.
I've already explained this to him before.
I'm unable to serve him
in the way he wishes me to.
So I wish to leave.
He cannot fulfill
the service you ask of him.
And says he still wishes to leave Japan.
Which service does he prefer?
He asks what service
you would rather be given.
If I were to remain in the Japans,
I would formally ask again
for the return of my ship…
He asks for the return of his ship.
…so that I may sail
against his enemies and mine,
the Portuguese.
So he might sail against the Portuguese.
As his chief admiral,
there are still ways
I can disrupt his enemies.
For example, I could attack
the Portuguese Black Ship at sea,
harming trade to the port controlled
by his Catholic rivals on the Council.
I'm told their names are Kiyama and Ohno.
Thus stifling the flow of Portuguese
Catholic wealth and its accompanying power
which will ultimately be brandished
against him and his country.
This is not in our Lord's interest.
I'm sorry, were you going to translate?
The Anjin wishes
to attack the Black Ship
in order to harm trade in ports
controlled by the Catholic Regents.
What cause would I have
to attack a friendly nation?
He says that
the Portuguese are a friendly nation,
and he would never attack their vessel.
The Portuguese are neither here
for the good of Japan nor Toranaga-sama.
They're here to gain
in the name of their God.
Why do you cling to this?
What is this arguing?
Excuse me. I am reminded
an interpreter should interpret only.
Well, seeing as you're my interpreter
and nothing more,
I would politely ask you to tell him
Portugal is friendly
only to their profits.
He believes
the Portuguese are only here to profit.
I will not be discussing this any further.
That is all for now.
You stay.
What is between you and the Anjin?
Nothing.
Only words.
I won't tolerate
this disruption in my clan.
We are dangerously close to defeat.
I understand.
One cannot serve themselves
above the cause.
The Anjin will not be granted his request.
But to settle his mind,
please arrange for him
a night at a brothel.
Hire their finest courtesan.
I will negotiate personally.
And join him.
As a translator.
In case he talks while he pillows.
Arson! Run away!
Ishido's taken the Regents hostage.
They've been locked in the castle,
along with their families.
He's forcing their vote against Toranaga.
We leave now.
Come, this way.
Please hurry Shizu, get on this.
She won't make it.
We'll only slow you down.
You must warn Toranaga yourself.
No.
Please, I beg you.
- Hurry!
- I'm sorry.
Stop him! Stop!
By Lord Ishido, I order you to stop!
Don't let him through! Stop!
It's Toda!
Refused at the gates.
It is even worse than we thought.
What has happened, Eminence?
Osaka Castle's been locked down.
Ishido claims
there is a plot to kill the Heir.
And he's order...
And he's ordered that
no Regent shall be allowed to leave
until they can elect the fifth member
and sentence Toranaga to death.
This is her doing.
Lady Ochiba?
This campaign to eliminate Toranaga,
it has accelerated since her return.
That woman has no such power.
I would not underestimate her, Eminence.
Child of a murdered busho.
The only consort
to give the Taiko an heir.
And she despises the Church.
I think the time has come for us
to turn towards Toranaga as an ally.
That man is a Minowara, Martin.
I have never understood
this hold he has on you.
Let us pray that we can bring him
to our side when this is done.
There's no time!
Lady Ruri!
Dress.
You must leave at once.
Your father was murdered in Kyoto.
Keep that fire in check! Protect the lady!
Never return.
Mother…
It's time for you to go now.
He slays the false vassal.
We're prisoners to that woman.
It serves no one to say such things.
This will be over soon…
When?
When the fifth Regent is confirmed
and Toranaga's threat is eliminated.
Then Ishido will release the hostages.
We'll always be their hostages now.
We're just puppets.
It's the end of the Realm.
Is this the era of peace
our Taikō fought to build?
We cannot be too safe these days.
Nonsense.
Ishido is nothing more
than the Taikō's favored koshô.
Good at some things, never great.
You are choosing the wrong ally.
Dear Lady Ochiba…
I was sorry to hear
of your father's death.
Terrible, how powerless we can be to fate.
We are all just pebbles,
pushed and pulled by the currents.
My husband is the ruler of Japan,
and I was unable to give him an heir…
did you know that?
This has been in my family
for over a hundred years.
It is the only one of its kind.
I am prepared to pass it on
to the consort who can bear us a son.
You would be known
as "Ochiba no kata" from now on.
A woman may lose everything
she's ever had...
But she may also take it back.
She must stare without fear
into the cruel eyes of fate...
And make herself seen.
If we have a son,
prestige will spread in every direction…
Lord Ito…
Your depiction of our late master was
quite profound.
Too kind, Lord Ishido.
I am but a weak flicker
to his glow of light.
You're not alone.
As a boy,
I looked up to the Taikō as proof
that even a peasant like me
could lift himself to great heights.
Some are born under a banner of greatness,
others must claim it.
Your nōh skills are unparalleled,
Lord Ito.
Though you are taller
than the Taikō I once served.
If only I could cut myself at the knees…
A minor fault, of course.
I take it seriously.
Acting is my grand passion.
And how about politics?
Have you heard of the plot
against the Heir?
Toranaga's provocations
must come to an end.
Would you join the Council
and vote for his death?
I'm grateful for your wisdom
in suggesting Lord Ito.
In all my time with the Taikō,
he never spoke of a woman
like he spoke of you.
I'm beginning to understand why.
I miss the Taikō's strength.
Truly.
It's as if we live in his shadow.
In most ways.
Though, in the end, he fell short.
He failed to rid us of Toranaga.
Why is it you hate him so much?
Eliminate Toranaga…
and it will be your shadow we speak of.
All of Osaka belongs
to Ishido now.
You are lucky to have escaped alive.
This is lunacy.
My father has only ever been
loyal to the Heir.
They are the ones who conspire!
Our allies are pressured
into becoming our enemies
with each passing day.
Unless they see
through this obscenity and protest.
If we wait for that, it will be too late.
The time has come…
…for Crimson Sky.
What is Crimson Sky?
A plan formulated long ago…
A single, violent rush on Osaka Castle.
We would eliminate the Council
and form a new government.
With Toranaga as sole Regent.
Shōgun…
An attack on Osaka is
like strangling your own neck.
Ishido's allies control the city.
Lord Toranaga's half-brother…
Saeki Nobutatsu.
We could join forces with him.
It wouldn't be enough.
What would you do, Omi?
A fifth Council member,
obedient to Ishido,
will mean your death sentence.
Then it is Crimson Sky.
Perhaps that could work, but…
Why take the risk when there's still time?
There's no time for waiting.
Father...
Reclaim our family's legacy
and become Shōgun.
You have never lost a battle...
Because I've never been first
to declare one!
There will be no Crimson Sky.
I have never sought to be Shōgun,
and I never will.
Find me a plan that isn't certain death.
You will forgive
the late notice, Gin,
but Toranaga instructed me
to inquire if the Lady Kiku is
free tonight.
What an honor.
And such lovely lacquerware too.
Unfortunately, it's nothing special.
I'm ashamed we must use it,
but so much was destroyed
in the earthquake.
Mmm.
Lady Kiku would be honored
to attend to this client.
Although…
I'd have to reimburse others
who booked her.
And, after the earthquake fires,
poor Kiku had four kosodes
ruined by water.
Hard times for us all.
500 monme would be acceptable.
So sorry, perhaps I wasn't clear.
I do not wish to buy
all the Tea Houses in Izu,
only the Lady's services for one evening.
I don't know if you've heard
of my Tea House,
but please understand
it is no ordinary brothel.
I might even say there is no place
like it in all of Japan.
My ladies are artists
of the very first class.
They enrich the mind
and nurture the spirit.
I assure you
the price is quite merited.
Then 100 monme.
400 monme would be the lowest I could go.
Surely Lord Toranaga
would want to enjoy his evening.
Oh, so sorry...
Lady Kiku is not for Lord Toranaga.
She is a gift for the Anjin.
He is hatamoto now,
and chief admiral
of Lord Toranaga's cannon regiment.
I would think 200 monme are enough.
Then, will you be joining him?
It's only…
I've heard you and the Anjin
are never seen apart.
It is my duty to translate, yes.
Then I think you will enjoy your time
in my Tea House.
Some call it the Willow World,
because my ladies
are like lilies in a lake.
There you will find no prying eyes
from the outside world.
All of this I guarantee…
for so very little.
300 monme will suffice.
You will be treasured guests.
Lady Gin says with Lord Toranaga's support
I could become
the most cherished courtesan in the Kantō.
I don't understand why Lord Toranaga
values the barbarian so much.
The barbarian is nothing to me.
This is a great honor you have received.
Lady Kiku is
the most coveted courtesan in Izu.
It's not the honor so much
as being unable to understand
why in Christ's name I'm receiving it.
Usually wives like me are not permitted
to go through the gate.
But in this case
a special exception has been made.
Does Toranaga-sama know about…
There is nothing to know.
Gin's Tea House is
famed for its many wonders,
but you must be careful.
Our every gesture is being observed.
Welcome.
I hope you will enjoy
your private evening.
What do I say?
It is fitting
to share your reaction.
Tell her she's beautiful.
"Sonata wa utsukushii."
I am honored to serve the Anjin
on this beautiful evening.
And I'm grateful that Lady Mariko
has also come to this place.
It does feel
like we're being watched.
We must try our best to find this
as pleasurable as possible.
And how am I to find this pleasurable?
By not making a scene.
For both of our sakes.
Compliment the way she poured your sake.
It is considered a rare art.
Courtesans like Kiku-dono
study it for years.
You pour very well.
The Anjin compliments your service.
I imagine everything is quite different
from his homeland.
She assumes it is different
from where you're from.
I'd say so.
Where I come from our prostitutes
are neither this well presented
nor as inquisitive.
He seems to prefer his homeland.
May I?
Why not?
Another fine pour.
Hana, look where the flask just was.
What do you see?
I see nothing, Elder Sister.
You see where the flask is no longer.
Presence is felt most keenly in absence.
Yes, Elder Sister.
Kiku-dono teaches
her young apprentice
about empty space and its symbols.
Mariko.
Where we are is a private place.
Dark… if one wants it dark.
A woman cannot look away
when another suffers.
Perhaps the Anjin would allow me
to explain
why the Willow World is among
the most treasured planes of existence.
She wishes to explain to you
the meaning of the Willow World.
People who come to this
place have something they wish to forget.
Be it boredom, pain,
hardship, disappointment.
Most come here to escape
from boredom or pain,
hardship or disappointment.
They believe this place is
about physical pleasure…
about physical pleasure,
which it is.
But it can be more.
The people I meet…
The people she meets wish
for a different life or circumstance.
They want to be
anyplace other than where they are.
I offer you relief from this.
I offer you relief from this…
…and safety
to create one perfect moment
that you wish to inhabit completely.
Settle your eyes on what you desire.
My unclothed form.
Just as I am with nothing between us.
I ask you into my openness.
I ask you.
…to be here with me now.
I would like to invite the Anjin
into a private room.
She invites you away with her now.
Will you join us?
It must only be you.
It's the barbarian.
- That's Lady Kiku.
- She's so pretty.
Thank you kindly.
All my father does
is lavish him with gifts these days.
Fortune does appear to smile on him.
Please tell Lady Kiku
I don't have the words to thank her.
He expresses his gratitude.
Tell him, please visit again.
I will count the moments.
She is honored.
How did it go?
The Anjin was pleased with his gift.
Kiku is exceptional.
Mariko…
What do you remember of your childhood?
I recall you being close
with Ochiba no kata.
She was Ruri then.
After she became Ochiba no kata,
I have not seen her since.
The way she wars against us…
What could have turned her
into the woman she is today?
Fate.
Hardship.
We all have things we must war against.
Yet most of us do it with honor.
Forgive me…
but most of you are men.
A man may go to war for many reasons.
Conquest,
pride,
power…
But a woman
is simply at war.
Your father once told me
he wished you'd been born a man.
Now I see why.
He had great plans for you.
Then he should have married me better.
Mariko…
You didn't know?
It was all his plan.
Marrying you off.
To put you as far away
from his fight as possible.
So that you might survive
and one day return to finish it.
All these years, you must have known…
I've failed him.
No, Mariko.
Your war isn't over.
The time for discussion
has now concluded.
Lord Ito is loyal to the Heir,
and to this Council.
In one voice, let us vote.
Yes to Ito.
What say you, Sugiyama?
I'm sorry.
But no.
There has been no evidence
of any plot against the Heir.
I will conduct no vote
until all hostages are released.
Hostages?
You dishonor the wishes
of our great Taikō.
Then you dishonor
the most loyal servant of this Realm.
I alone here
serve the Realm.
It will mean a delay,
there's no doubt about it.
I will propose Sugiyama's impeachment,
then plans can move ahead.
So sorry, but I'd like to know...
When is "then"?
Please be patient.
You're playthings.
You have no idea the enemy you face…
You asked before
why I hold these feelings
against Toranaga.
It began in my childhood in Azuchi.
All those years I watched him…
whispering…
plotting…
Sure, it was Akechi Jinsai
who took my father's life,
but it was Toranaga who planned it.
His secret heart is no secret to me.
Serious accusations.
Tell them in public
and his end will be swift.
What would be the point?
None of you can stop him.
Have you heard what I went through
to give the Taikō a son?
No one else could achieve it.
Hundreds of women… consorts…
Not Daiyoin…
Daiyoin… who drugged me with bitter herbs,
forced me to endure unmentionable things
in order to conceive.
Only I become mother of the Heir.
And do you know how?
By compelling fate to look at me.
So I could
scratch out its eyes.
Wife, wake up!
We're leaving the castle.
Wake up!
My Lord, someone's there.
It was wrong
to side with a simple bureaucrat.
That's all you will ever be.
Lord Sugiyama is dead…
Killed by bandits
while trying to leave Osaka.
Ishido will soon control the Council.
I expect to be
falsely impeached
and war will be declared on my clan.
I desire no lands.
I want no honors.
But if traitors place
the Taikō's heir in danger,
then I must defend him.
Crimson Sky it will be.
We'll send a message
to my brother asking for his support,
then we'll rush Osaka
and obliterate our enemies.
The time has come.