[speaking Japanese]
[Blackthorne] I'm assuming
that man's your husband.
[Mariko]
His name is Toda Hirokatsu,
though friends call him Buntaro.
For Christ's sake,
he can still make it.
[men shouting]
Toda Hirokatsu!
[Blackthorne]
Shit.
[Mariko]
Sorry.
I'm happy to see
you have changed your mind
about bathing.
You seem in good spirits.
[Blackthorne]
After a night of good company.
The courtesan
was acceptable, then.
Nebara Jozen!
[shouts]
[grunting]
[distant rumbling]
[horses neighing]
[man shouting in distance]
♪ ♪
[man yells in distance]
[scoffs]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[coughs]
[Sugiyama coughing]
[indistinct shouting
in distance]
Hmm.
[exhales]
[speaks Japanese]
♪ ♪
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
As I live and breathe.
The most precious gift there is.
You see that?
I do my part,
and the old man does his.
Now we're getting somewhere.
You can't understand a word
I'm saying,
but when I was your age,
one of my first chores
was cleaning game
my father would poach
from an estate in Chatham.
Watch this.
Now, we'll hang it up
for a few days to mature,
maybe a week,
depending on the weather.
There we are.
Yes, yes. There will be
a terrible stench.
But this is a gift
from Toranaga-sama.
It must be the best pheasant
this village has ever prepared.
Now, this next part
is very important.
No one is to touch this bird.
Um...
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[groans]
[laughs softly]
[grunts]
[Yabushige grunting angrily]
[grumbling]
[Omi exhales]
[Yabushige exhales]
Huh?
[laughs softly]
Oh?
Huh? Huh?
[exhales]
[insects buzzing]
[grunts softly]
I understand your husband
is to stay with us now.
Is there anything you feel I...
should be preparing for?
- Dinner?
- Dinner.
And you will be a gracious host.
[grunting]
[Mariko]
My husband wishes for you
to address him as Toda-sama,
as Buntaro is reserved only
for those close to him.
Tell Toda-sama it's a relief
he was able to escape Osaka
and an honor for him
to have observed
our cannon regiment today.
[insect buzzing]
He believes that,
in the hands of a true samurai,
the bow and sword will always
outmatch the cannon.
Oh. Well, perhaps
we should have
a friendly contest sometime.
[insect buzzes]
[buzzing stops]
[sniffs]
[Blackthorne]
Now, for my esteemed guests
on this wonderful evening,
I am proud to present to you
a taste from my home country.
We call it English rabbit stew.
Now, admittedly,
I had to substitute
a few of the ingredients...
sake for sherry,
a few other things...
but that's
the beauty of a good stew.
It all tastes
like gravy in the end.
Mariko-sama wa?
We are particular eaters,
Anjin-sama.
It is our loss.
It's not the same
without sherry anyway.
There you go.
Oh, please. Eat.
[chuckles]
What did he say?
My husband comments
on the way you eat your noodles.
The sound you make while eating
reveals the depth
of your pleasure.
[laughs]
[slurps]
[slurping]
Hmm.
[liquid pours]
You know, where I come from,
only women
drink from a tiny cup like that.
The polite size
of the sake cup helps us
- to enjoy the drink and...
- [clatters]
This is how we drink.
[slurping]
[sets down bottle]
[both slurping]
[exhales]
[Blackthorne] Seeing as we're
toasting, I have a toast to propose.
If you cheat, cheat death.
If you steal,
steal the heart of a woman.
If you lie,
lie in the everlasting warmth
of her bosom, and if you drink,
drink with me.
[both slurping]
[exhales]
[liquid pouring]
What did he say?
Perhaps it is getting late.
I think Fuji-sama
appears to be tired.
Fuji-sama...
[Blackthorne]
Oh, nonsense.
Mariko-sama,
ask your husband
if he'd share the...
the story of his escape
in Osaka.
Never too late for a good story.
Well, go on. Ask him, then.
[exhales]
[Buntaro slurps]
He would like to know about
a war you have fought in.
Oh, I don't know.
All of my war stories
are full of holes.
[Mariko]
Please listen.
My husband is tired
and has had a lot to drink.
You must tell him a story.
But choose your words carefully.
[pops lips]
[exhales]
The gateway of your house.
He asks you to choose a post.
What, he's going to shoot it?
The left or the right post?
Well, the man can't
even see straight.
Please choose.
Right?
[Blackthorne]
Mariko-sama.
You should move.
- [gasps]
- Mariko-sama, move.
Mariko-sama.
- [thump]
- [gasps]
Mariko-sama.
Get out of the fucking way.
[liquid pouring]
Please tell him
that while I understand
that in this country,
like mine, a man's wife
is his property,
but I believe strongly
that his wife merits better.
[chuckling]
[Mariko] I am to tell
you about my family.
I am daughter of the late
Lord Akechi Jinsai.
Mariko-sama,
you don't have to do this.
Just make up a story, he'll
never know the difference.
My father's lord
was Kuroda-sama,
ruler of Japan before the Taiko.
Kuroda-sama was corrupt
and murderous,
and so my father killed him
out of love for the realm.
For this he was hunted,
along with my family.
All of my brothers, sisters...
...and my mother...
...they all knelt
before my father,
who was forced to execute them
one by one...
...before committing seppuku
himself.
I was just married
and not permitted to fight.
Each year on the anniversary
of my family's murder,
I ask my husband
to let me take action
against this injustice.
But I can do nothing.
Because my husband
orders me to live.
I ask you to remember
the Eightfold Fence.
Excuse me.
Mariko!
[owl hoots]
[snoring]
- [Buntaro grunts]
- [thud]
[Mariko crying]
[thumping]
[panting]
Get out of the way.
I said move, damn you.
[Mariko crying]
Get back.
Oh, Christ.
♪ ♪
Buntaro!
Look at me!
♪ ♪
Oh, what are you doing? Get up.
Sake?!
Is that your excuse?
Get up, you bastard.
On your feet!
[indistinct whispering]
Sake.
You piece of shit.
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[seabirds squawking]
[laughs softly]
[insects buzzing]
Morning.
Where is Mariko-sama?
I don't understand anything
you're saying. Where is she?
[horse clopping]
You all right?
All of this is my doing.
Mariko-sama,
your husband's brutality
is no fault of yours.
We should not be seen together.
Oh, the pox on that.
Don't put it behind
that folded fence of yours,
whatever you call it.
I-I see you.
Your disgust for him.
If you want to be free
of that shitless coward,
then be free of him.
Still, you understand so little?
Your swords.
Fuji-sama believes they were
given to her father
as a battle honor.
The truth is, he died a coward,
begging for his life.
Her grandfather bought them
from a drunken samurai
for three bags of rice
to spare her the embarrassment.
But she knows nothing
and we say nothing,
because our silence
is what she merits.
I will give my husband nothing,
not even my hatred,
because that is what he merits.
♪ ♪
It's a good story, Mariko-sama,
and I understand the sentiment,
but you take it too far.
Honestly, you're shuffling
around with your manners
and your buried self, for what?
I would not expect
for you to understand.
Well, forgive me, but you'd
die to avenge your father,
you'd live in anguish
to spite your husband.
Which is it?
What becomes of you?
My life is mine
and yours is yours.
If you can't see that,
you'll never be free
of this prison.
No, Anjin-sama.
It is you who is imprisoned.
If freedom is all
you ever life for...
...you will never be free
of yourself.
I will honor my duty
as your translator.
But from this day forward,
the only words we share
will be from others' lips.
[sobbing]
What's the matter with everyone?
What is it?
Pheasant?
Our gardener?
Old bastard should get a medal
just for being able
to climb up there.
It's fine.
It'd been up there
long enough anyway.
What have you done?
You put that old man to death
over a stinking,
God-cursed pheasant?
[sniffles]
What the hell is wrong with you?
Why in Christ's name
didn't you ask me?
Go away.
All of you!
Go away!
[birds chirping]
Lord, when we were at sea,
we discussed my training
your army in European combat.
I feel I have now fulfilled
that duty.
I ask that my ship and my men
be returned to me
so that I may leave
and not return.
He asks what troubles you.
I'm troubled
by your whole damned country.
Life has no value to you.
Only the meaningless rituals
you are trapped in.
Like Uejirou.
Who died for nothing.
It is my understanding
that you ordered
no one to touch that bird.
And by law, your house
could not disobey that order.
Nor could they allow
the rotting pheasant
to ruin the peace
of the village.
The bird meant nothing to me.
Your words gave it meaning.
[horse neighing in distance]
A meeting was called
with Muraji,
who is the village headman,
but he determined
it was a house problem.
So someone had to steal it
and bury it.
Uejirou announced
that he had been sick lately,
so he volunteered.
He died for a great purpose.
It was a better end
than he could have hoped for.
♪ ♪
I killed him.
Lord forgive me,
I killed that old man.
There is no use dwelling
on what cannot be undone.
How can you believe that?
We live and we die.
We control nothing beyond that.
- [birds squawking]
- [low rumble]
[rocks crashing]
[distant shouting]
[rumbling intensifies]
[panting]
[shouting continues]
Jesus!
Where the hell is he?
[grunts]
He's here!
[exclaims]
There he is!
[all grunting]
[panting]
[coughing]
[wheezing]
[gasps]
[panting]
These belonged to Fuji's father.
They may not be much,
but I'd be honored
if he would accept this gift.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
[men shouting]
[distorted shouting]
[sobbing]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
[horse neighing]
[birds chirping]
♪ ♪
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org