Previously on Shogun..
Your father treasures you.
We're prisoners to that woman.
You must stop these games.
Promise to release the hostages.
I now wish to forge
allegiances benefiting this country.
I just need a new banner to sail under.
You wish to sail
on Yabushige-sama's behalf?
Which is more important?
Survival of our clan, or Japan?
Do not give up on our lord.
Even when it appears
he has given up on himself.
Hiromatsu…
…knew his duty well.
Now are you ready to do your part?
I'm ready.
She's been caught
three times now.
Her father was
the treacherous Akechi Jinsai.
She's the last of his line.
Her husband showed her mercy,
yet still she seeks death.
May I sit with her alone?
Mariko-sama, is it?
In my culture, we would say Maria.
A beautiful name.
You are too young to be this sad.
I'm not much older.
I've known sadness and loss too.
But I believe God spared me for a purpose.
And now he's spared you.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name, thy kingdom come,
thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil…
For when you have no words…
and you just need something to hold onto.
Well, we're making our approach.
Yes.
Why did he send you here?
It has nothing to do with you.
We are simply traveling
to Osaka at the same time.
Well, my life is mine and yours is yours.
Ah, your friends are back from Macao
with the overpriced silk they traded for
criminally underpriced Japanese silver.
True friends of the Jappos.
Tell him as soon as we arrive at
the castle we'll be met by Ishido's men.
He's to remain close.
You are instructed to stay close
once you are met by Ishido-sama's men.
You translated honestly?
I did.
I hate this fucking city.
Lord Ohno's family.
Everyone in the castle is
now a hostage to Ishido-sama.
If a member from every noble family is
trapped here, none can oppose him.
We'll meet Lord Ishido tomorrow.
I want you there with me.
No.
We'll make our proposal then.
Understand?
- Uh... Lord Ishido.
- Mmm.
Mmm.
Tomorrow. Yes.
Yabushige, thank you for trusting me.
When I deliver to you the Catholic gold,
you won't regret it.
Do you understand?
Certainly.
Mmm.
Well, we're together again.
Get some rest, Anjin-sama.
It's true… you're here.
I apologize for the tight quarters.
We had to give up rooms
for Lord Otomo's family.
I'm so sorry for what you've endured.
And Lady Shizu,
welcoming a son in this cruel place.
I wish I could have been with you.
Is there word from Lord Toranaga?
Let's hope this works.
You are certain it was the heretic?
It's hard to miss the foul smell
coming off of the galley.
Whole escort of Jappers with him.
And the lady translator too.
- Lady Maria?
- Mmm. Your little friend.
Toranaga is planning something.
We have got to find out what it is.
I do not think the heretic is
here on Toranaga's behalf.
When I was in Edo, he had been cut loose.
Toranaga has given up.
Or you are blind to their trickery.
This felt different.
His most loyal vassal killed himself
right in front of him.
If John Blackthorne is here,
it is only because he is trying
to find his own way out.
Tempest in a bottle.
War is coming.
What a handsome gift.
Show me your bow.
No, not like that.
If we're going to win over our enemies,
the least you can do is bow right.
Your back, here! That's it.
What are you doing?
You show him how.
Good, great! Great. That's it.
- Why…
- Mmm.
Now, don't speak.
And don't disappoint.
Ah, Yabushige.
I see you made good time from Edo.
How kind of you to return my prisoner.
My pleasure.
But he isn't for you.
He wishes to pledge himself to Ishido.
After all, no one lord should possess
all the guns in Japan…
wouldn't you agree?
It won't matter.
The barbarian will soon be
at the mercy of the Church.
Carry on with your boring
Christian squabbles.
But don't wrinkle him.
He's mine.
Good evening.
I am Kiyama Ukon Sadanaga.
Member of the Council of Regents.
Ah, yes. The most humble servant
of the Lord on high.
And a servant of the Portuguese.
Which comes first?
God or your purse strings?
I don't trouble myself too much
with the matters of faith.
I am, however, a student of trade.
And I can tell you that
we have quite enough pirate merchants
in this country already.
Your kind arrived here too late.
My kind?
But I'm not a pirate.
Welcome, Yabushige.
On Lord Toranaga's behalf,
I surrender to the Council.
And offer my condolences for the death
of the Taikō's brilliant wife.
Hollow words from a traitor.
As I once explained to Nebara Jozen,
I was deceived into leading Toranaga
out of Osaka.
Was that before or after you were deceived
into killing him?
If you wish for my head,
you shall have it.
But before that,
might you take a look at my gift.
The Anjin was once
Toranaga's prized hatamoto.
Now he is loyal to me.
He's well-trained,
and an excellent sea captain.
The Heir has no interest in a barbarian.
Dismissed.
Bow.
Move back.
We tried, Anjin. I don't know…
Welcome back to Osaka,
Lady Mariko.
I congratulate you and Ochiba no kata
on your joyous engagement.
I'm surprised you joined
this spineless traitor on his journey.
Do you bring news
of Toranaga's progress from Edo?
Only that my lord still mourns.
Naturally, he has been devastated
by the death of his son.
He has others.
It's a pleasure to see you, Mariko.
It's been too long.
Yes.
Since we were girls.
Mariko and I spent many years
in Azuchi together.
Do you remember how we used to compete
in poetry competitions?
I remember.
In Daiyoin's memory,
there will be a poetry competition.
If you could choose the first line,
it would be a great honor.
I think it should be…
While the snow remains
Veiled in the haze of cold evening
A leafless branch…
Excellent.
If a bit bleak.
It will give us something
to look forward to
amidst all this death and treachery.
Unfortunately, I won't be competing.
What are you saying?
I'm sorry,
but I will not be here.
I'm leaving Osaka tomorrow
with Kiri no kata and Shizu no kata.
Leaving for where, Mariko?
To meet our liege lord in Edo.
He has requested I escort them myself.
He...
Toranaga will be here in a few weeks,
as you said.
It's been months since
the Lady Shizu has seen Lord Toranaga.
And my lord hasn't yet seen
his newest son.
Lady Mariko...
Let's find another time
to discuss this private matter.
Perhaps you can call on us...
Thank you, but no.
I am leaving tomorrow.
You forget your manners!
Forgive me,
that was the last thing I intended.
I will return with my lord on the day
we are required to be in Osaka.
Unless we are confined here.
No one is confined here.
But since you choose to speak
in this outrageous fashion,
it is my duty to ask the Regents
for a formal review.
Lord Kiyama?
What do you think?
I agree.
Good.
Mariko will remain here until then.
I would be honored…
However…
my first duty is to my liege lord,
and I am ordered to leave.
You will be patient!
I cannot delay my departure,
even for a little time.
The matter is closed!
The matter is closed…
when you have the manners
to let me finish.
I am no peasant to be trodden on.
I am daughter of the great Lord…
Akechi Jinsai.
My line has been samurai
for a thousand years,
and I will never be captive,
or hostage, or confined.
I am free to go as I please…
as is anyone.
You will await the meeting of the Regents.
There is nothing more to discuss.
What in the name
of all gods possessed you?
Has your mind left you?
And is this body of yours… stupid?
So sorry.
Tonight was unexpected.
You knew exactly what you were doing.
On Toranaga's behalf.
I know it, Ishido knows it…
What are Toranaga's plans?
I can help him, we can do this together.
Tell me your orders!
- Yabushige.
- What is it!
It is not my intention
to disrupt your peace.
Or any peace.
I suppose this one's part of it.
The Anjin is here on his own business.
I'm sorry, but please excuse me.
I am very tired from the day.
"Leafless branch"... what a terrible poem.
Who writes about leafless branches
in the spring?
Come on, idiot!
Why have you done this?
I need rest.
I must leave in the morning.
But you can't leave.
They'll stop you.
Judging by the armed guards
everywhere I look, probably by force.
Then Ishido-sama would be admitting
I remain here by force.
As well as every lord and lady
being kept prisoner in this castle.
You'd walk into a sword
just to prove the blade is sharp.
Please, Anjin-sama,
you must not involve yourself.
Can you do this…
for the sake of everything
we have been through?
As your son,
I am concerned for our house.
I am only doing my duty.
To whom?
Your family?
It's difficult to explain.
What about your duty to God?
Please, Lord Kiyama's a fellow Christian
of highest rank.
He asks you to remain in Osaka.
He says that our families are one
under the banner of God
which is why I am to become betrothed
to his granddaughter.
We serve Toranaga-sama.
You will marry as our lord instructs.
I am tired of being in this family.
These things they say about your name,
I am always ashamed.
And for what?
What have I done?
We have nothing to be ashamed of.
Then stop this.
If you try to leave today, you'll be held.
And if you are disgraced…
…then I am no longer your son.
My Lady, are you ready?
Let's go.
Everyone get ready!
We're leaving.
Excuse me, Lady Mariko,
do you have a permit to leave?
Excuse me, but we require none.
Lord Ishido has instituted orders
throughout the castle.
You must have a permit.
I have been ordered by my lord
to escort his ladies to Edo.
Please let us pass.
I'm sorry, but without a permit,
no lord or his retinue
may leave Osaka Castle.
It is Lord Ishido's order.
You leave me no choice.
Please kill him.
The Lady will leave now!
Miyai, would you please take charge?
It would be an honor, my Lady.
Kill them!
I'm honored to have served you.
Lord Kiyama, Lord Ohno…
Please order these men out of my way.
They are not ours to order.
Those men belong to Lord Ishido.
We are powerless.
Then it's true we are all being kept
here against our will.
I will call for a meeting!
I am a vassal of Lord Toranaga
and my orders are clear.
I must be permitted to obey my lord.
Mariko-sama.
Please get out of my way.
Lady Mariko must not be harmed!
It is not possible
to fight through all these men.
We must go back.
However…
these men have prevented me
from doing my duty to my liege lord
and I cannot live with the offense.
I will take my life at sunset.
Lord Kiyama.
As a Christian, you understand
it is a mortal sin to take my own life.
I formally ask that you be my second.
I am obligated to her
as a fellow Christian.
Otherwise she faces eternal damnation.
That is her choice.
It's a bluff.
She won't forfeit
her eternal soul with suicide.
You're all wrong.
Lady Mariko will do as she says.
It is her vengeance.
On fate.
On all of us.
She will die to be free of the disgrace
that has burdened her.
And then all of Osaka will be disgraced
for letting her die.
A bit extreme, don't you think?
What is your counsel?
I have no counsel for you, Lord Ishido.
If you allow her to die,
there will be a revolt
from every high family in Osaka.
If you allow her to leave,
the hostages will also demand to leave.
Ishido's men began locking
all the palaces…
we managed to leave just in time.
We ask for the honor of joining you
in waiting for Lady Mariko.
We are pleased to have you.
The Anjin has been summoned
for an audience with the Heir.
I'm told your Japanese is decent.
Can you understand me?
Yes.
But I respectfully request
you use simple words.
A prepared phrase.
Smart of you.
I wonder if Mariko taught you that.
Thank you for coming.
The Heir requested an audience
with the Anjin.
As we need a translator,
I asked you to come.
She asks of me to translate.
It is a ruse to bring me before her.
Please let her speak.
It would be an honor
if I can be of use.
The Anjin thanks the Heir
for this audience.
These games must stop.
I play no games.
I have only my duty to uphold.
You can't bring nobility
to your lord's warmongering.
By being a worm on Toranaga's lure,
you will not win your freedom.
So sorry, but you're mistaken.
My lord wishes only to end this fight.
Would you translate
for the Anjin?
I want him to understand
the relationship we once had.
When we were girls,
Mariko did everything well.
She always knew where to stand,
when to leave the room
without being asked.
It was easy for her.
She talks about our childhood together.
She and I grew up like sisters.
But our fathers were
enemies, you see.
Their misery was ours.
Wars raged, even in our castle.
But I had Mariko.
She was my happiness.
And then she was sent away.
For years, I couldn't recognize
this woman I was told she'd become…
That Mariko, in her father's name,
wished to become a martyr…
But I see her now.
The girl who did everything right,
with anger growing in her chest.
All she seeks is destruction.
Aren't you tired of all this?
What should I do?
Surrender to some pointless death?
Wither like your "leafless branch"?
Only you can end the games
you accuse me of playing.
I don't have that power.
I don't exist, except to protect my son.
Tell me, how will piercing your heart
protect your son?
We should go now.
Accepting death isn't surrender.
Flowers are only flowers
because they fall.
Toranaga has thousands
of warriors at his disposal.
Vassals coming out of his kosode.
It's the mark of a coward
to send a woman to do his bidding.
You misunderstand him.
No, I understand perfectly.
He's taking advantage of your loyalty.
Your life is worth more than this.
Life and death are the same.
Both can have value and purpose.
Only one is permanent.
You have nothing to prove to these people.
You've made your point.
There's no need to die for it.
There is every need.
It is the very reason
my father kept me alive.
What I'm asking...
What I'm begging is,
if not for good sense,
if not for God,
then will you consider living for me?
A message from Lord Ishido.
Your offer of service instead of death...
He accepts.
But he has a request…
All these years,
you still have your cross with you.
Your mind is set again.
Yes, it is.
I wish to be confessed.
Then speak it here.
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
But I can only confess
that I am not worthy to confess.
Daughter of God,
I wish I could say proper Mass for you.
But here we have no altar or vestments.
Then let us drink cha from an empty cup
for all the years we have known each other
and for the little time that is left.
I, Toda Mariko,
daughter of Akechi Jinsai,
leave this poem as my final statement.
Lord Kiyama,
please come forward to second me.
I will do it.
Hell is no place I haven't already known.
Let it from your mind.
Please wait until I have fallen.
Your permits.
Stupid as it is
to have to come right back,
you are free to leave in the morning.
Lord Ishido!
I also ask to leave.
And me. With my family.
May we expect safe passage too?
Are we jailers?
No one is hostage in this castle.
If you wish to leave, then apply
for your permits and it will be done.
A mere woman, threatening her own suicide,
and flouting the Heir's welcome…
Disgusting.
I'm all right, Setsu.
Lord, if you'd like to rest,
we have the watch covered.
I was going to sleep,
but those hens unearthed
all the saké in the castle.
I suspect they'll be up all night.
I can understand
their desire to celebrate.
Go ahead, drink.
I insist.
Good.
Huh?
What is it?
Intruders!
Come quick!
Wake everyone!
Who are they?
Shinobi. They have come for me.
It's Ishido…
he'll never let us leave alive.
They've infiltrated the castle.
Quiet!
Listen.
Tell them to move back.
Step aside.
Look out!
We should go to the dozo.
Its doors will protect us.
No, we should go to the gate!
I will not risk being captured.
Outside, there is a storehouse
with heavy doors.
Yabushige-sama!
There's nowhere for us to go.
Ready the fuses!
They're going to blow it open.
An explosion will kill us all!
Yabushige-sama, help me.
Yabushige-sama.
For the love of God, get over here and
help me push this against the damn door!
Anjin-sama.
Let it come.
For God's sake,
help me push this against the door!
- I, Akechi Mariko…
- Mariko-sama, get away from the door.
…protest
this shameful attack by Lord Ishido…
Lady Mariko, get over here!
And by my death…
Mariko-sama!