Captain.
I was unable to take
any celestial destinations
- due to...
- The clouds.
Yes, the clouds.
However, white sand
by the mark ten.
Ten fathoms.
White sand in the tallow.
You see what you want to see.
Well, the son of a bitch
Spaniard's rutter was right
- about Magellan's Pass, was it not?
- Oh, give it here.
The cursed bastard thing
is to be the death of us all.
The time has come for you
to start making plans.
You have no food.
As of tonight, no water.
We'll make land.
Goddamn English pilots.
You never know when to give up.
We'll reach the Japans.
Japans. Listen to yourself.
That is the scurvy talking.
We'll lay claim
to that dark land.
Then it's back to Holland, rich,
- having gone round the world.
- Eh.
No.
No, Pilot.
Not me.
Five ships when we began.
A crew of over 500.
We are now barely
a single vessel.
At my age, you draw your line.
That would be a coward's
way out.
The Erasmus remains home
to a dozen men
- still looking to you.
- Looking to me for what?
We cannot fulfill our mission.
Don't you see, there is nothing!
All right, there you have it.
Pilot.
Pilot, it's nothing to fear.
It's a blessed release.
It's like only a soft wind
in your face.
Can you feel it?
That is the breath
of the Almighty.
He's calling us. Listen.
He is calling us home.
Move over.
Can you see what they're doing?
- Come on.
- I think they're towing her in.
Can you tell what they are?
A-Are they Cathay?
Quiet!
It's what
I've been telling you.
They're Japanese.
Well, don't all thank
your good fortune at once.
We've reached it.
Portugal's secret empire
in the East.
Impossible.
The orders are still on.
- What part of this is still on?
- All I know
is we had Spanish ships
to the south and north of us
out of Santa Maria.
And this pilot got us through.
We can still negotiate.
We have goods to trade.
Not to mention I speak
fluent Portuguese.
As soon as the Portuguese
tell them who we are,
we'll be hanged.
They don't know who we are
because the rutters
are still locked in the
captain general's quarters.
And as long as they stay
that way, we are safe.
We're just merchants,
lost at sea,
looking for safe passage home.
You really think it'll work?
Here's what you're missing,
the lot of you.
We've been caught alee,
windless,
a speck on a current.
We've endured pestilence,
known starvation.
We've chewed the calfskin covers
of the ropes.
We should be corpses by now,
but here we are.
12 shit-smelling...
...but generally able-bodied
Protestant scoundrels
on a mission
against a savage horde
and the entire goddamn,
motherless,
shit-picking Portuguese fleet.
Aye.
I'd say our chances are fair.
This is not where we die.
Hello there.
You the leader of these men?
My name is John Blackthorne,
and I would very much like
to speak to you.
If it's agreeable,
I will come up alone.
You can't.
They'll kill you, Pilot.
Pilot, look at their swords.
Look out!
No, no, no, no,
don't fight them.
No! No violence!
We need him alive.
You fucking savages!
Now I will come up alone
and speak for my men.
You keep hold of him
in case I don't come back.
Bastards!
I submit. I submit.
We are merchants.
I request we be released
to the safety of our ship.
We mean you no harm.
Omi-sama say, "Be good."
Is this the Japans?
Hai. Yes.
How do I say "I understand"
in your language?
I ask for my men to be freed.
- Not possible.
- I beg you.
In the name of decency.
Please, in Japan, must be good.
If this is how he treats guests,
tell this poxy little bastard
I piss
on his whole damn country!
Our busho, Lord of Izu, Kashigi
Yabushige, he asks to know
who you are and how
you came to this land.
Who are you?
A servant of God.
Your god?
First make that distinction,
you papist prick.
My name is John Blackthorne.
I'm English.
Pilot of the Erasmus,
a Dutch merchant vessel.
- We were blown off course two months ago.
- Lies!
That is a Dutch privateer.
And you're a pirate,
come to war on a peaceful
Portuguese settlement.
They don't know about us,
do they?
You told them Portugal
is the only flag in Europe.
Which means I am
the first English sailor
to reach your Catholic treasury.
And you have no intention
of translating my words.
I beg your king for parlay.
I humbly ask for safe passage.
Yabushige-sama says
your heretic ship now
belongs to him.
You will soon be executed,
as will your men.
I am not one of them!
And I will not be
spoken for by Catholics!
Not in Europe, and certainly not
in this dark land.
Well, I'm sorry, Father.
We'll be all over
this continent soon.
Go back in your sty,
dick up your arse.
Please, we're just merchants!
Please!
We're just merchants!
For the love of God!
Oh, please, no! No!
Please, no!
Please! Please!
Please!
Ah, Christ.
Good morning.
Where are my boots?
I heard a man screaming
last night.
Sounded as though
he was in terrible pain.
This is very tight.
Well, listen, if it's amenable
to, uh, to either of you, I'd...
I'd... very much like
to speak to your leader again.
With the swords.
The man with the swords.
Wonderful.
Where am I being taken?
You. You look at me.
You murder prisoners
without a trial.
Is that how it's done here?
You go...
- Osaka.
- I go nowhere
until I see my men!
Hey, hey, piss-eating bastards.
Bow.
Bow to the bastard-sama
if you wanna live.
The man is like a king here.
And tell him "goyosha wo."
Goyosha kudasare.
To all the shit-eating samas,
huh?
Come.
You pilot of that Dutchman, eh?
Who are you?
Young little shit, aren't you?
What's the latitude
of The Lizard?
49 degrees, 56 minutes north.
And watch out for the reefs,
south-southwest.
Or they'll send you tits up.
By God, you are a pilot.
And Inglés, too. Fuck me.
Listen, sir, you speak Japanese.
I must know if my crew is alive.
Well, that's good news.
Only one of your crew is dead.
And the Jappers say
they'll free the rest of them
- if you play nice.
- Who of my men's dead?
Here it is, Inglés.
Your crew belongs to them now.
Maybe you'll see them
if you get back.
Maybe not, but it-it is
out of your hands.
- Where are we going?
- Osaka. Big city.
The Great Lord Yoshii Toranaga
wants to meet you.
- And what does he want with me?
- Play with your balls, maybe.
How should I know?
But he's a powerful sort,
so I might let him.
More powerful than those men?
Lord of the Kanto?
A million of them fanatics
would die for the honor
of wiping his arse.
I didn't catch your name, friend.
Rodrigues, and I'm a Spaniard
who sails for the Portuguese.
I'm not your friend.
Any chance of me boarding
my ship, Rodrigues?
Yeah, yeah.
Just as soon as you lick my jib.
Listen, Inglés, no more tricks.
I told these samas that
I'd be responsible for you.
So, do us both a favor,
blow her a kiss.
Be a storm by sunset.
Eh, we should head northwest.
This crew would love to keep
within sight of land.
You came over
with the Portuguese?
Sailed for a living, hai.
How'd you get here, anyway?
Came by Magellan's Pass.
Merchant mission.
Captain-General held us
in Chile too long.
I warned him
the winds would die.
He wouldn't listen.
And now command rests on you.
That's some fate. Shukumei.
- What is that word?
- Shukumei?
Shukumei, it's like
an attitude out here.
It's, uh, karma.
Uh, fate. Fixed destiny.
Everything is connected.
Part of a whole. Life, death.
You just have to accept
your-your wee place.
These people
are godless savages.
Or maybe they just don't
give a shit what you think,
young, scheming little pirate.
Why do you believe I'm a pirate?
You had 20 guns on that ship.
20 guns to defend ourselves
from unlawful
Portuguese galleons
piloted by Spanish dogs.
We drifted here by accident.
We're just merchants
hoping to once again
cast eyes on our coast of origin.
I like you, Inglés, I do.
In fact, given we have
a long night ahead of us,
I think I shall allow you
the honor of taking this watch.
Come.
Kind of you to trust me.
Why not? You are a pilot,
not a godless savage, huh?
Hai.
Hai!
We've got to turn ourselves
into the swell!
Where are your cojones, eh?
Where they should be, by God,
and where I'd like them to stay!
Go below, get them to row.
Can you swim?
- Can't you?
- Never learned.
Better to drown quickly, right?
Goddamn it, into the swell!
What? What are you
still doing up here,
you pirate bitch?
Piss on the Spaniard
who serves the Portuguese.
Piss on all English.
Que viva España.
Pull!
Big swell coming!
Turn into it!
Row!
Rodrigues! Rodrigues!
Rodrigues!
If you bastards want to live,
pull!
Rodrigu-sama.
The pilot is somewhere here.
For all we know,
he could still be breathing.
Naran.
I don't care what sort of savage
whore-bitch turd you are,
where I come from,
we don't leave a man behind.
Rodrigues!
Move a limb!
I'm only trying to get a look.
I'll bring him up.
Me.
Oh, I see.
You can't turn down a challenge
in front of your men, can you?
Go on, savage.
Maybe the fall will kill you
before you drown.
Sorry about your
sack-of-shit lord.
What the hell is he doing?
Huh?
My leg is on fire,
my head is bursting
and my piss pot's full.
You make a foul nurse, Inglés.
That man was going
to kill himself
up on that cliff.
He risked his life to save you.
And then when he was done for
in those waves, he didn't fight.
He could have tried,
but he just turned
and drew his blade.
He chose his death.
What better end
can a man hope for?
Will I die here?
Likely.
How can you just accept being
powerless to this madness?
Uh, you-you mean to this life?
Zehi mo gozaimasen.
One cannot resist
the unseen path of nature.
All we can do is accept
our small part.
It's bollocks.
I fought too long
and too hard to get here.
I won't succumb to this madness.
I won't, I can't.
That's funny, I thought
you washed up by accident.
Listen, Pilot,
I-I think it's only fair.
I found this on your ship.
It's a rutter, stolen off
a Spanish sailor, I imagine.
How you must have found your way
through Magellan's Pass.
Which means this belongs to you.
It's a-a list of all
the Catholic bases
that you and your
so-called merchant crew
were putting to the torch.
I mean, real savage business,
if you ask me.
Your orders:
"Plunder any Spanish territory,
reach the Japans,
open trade in the New World."
Which is why I'm warning you,
these go to the Portuguese
as soon as I arrive.
This isn't the end for me.
I won't die
in this wretched land.
This wretched land?
I'll tell you what, Inglés.
We're coming into port soon.
Why don't you go on up there?
Go up and tell me what you see.
And tell me,
when you set eyes on Osaka,
if you really think our world
is the hilt of civilization.
And then ask yourself,
"What kind of man
wields power
in a land like this?"
The one who schemes
in the open...
...or the one you never see?
There's a saying out here
that every man has three hearts.
One in his mouth,
for the world to know...
...another in his chest,
just for his friends...
...and a secret heart
buried deep
where no one can find it.
That is a heart
a man must keep hidden
if he wants to survive.
You'll understand soon, Inglés.
And who knows, maybe-maybe fate
brought you here for a reason.
Maybe you'll live long enough
to find out what it is.
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org