-[door opens]
-[bird squawks]
[adventurous uplifting music plays]
♪ In a place full of mystery
Where the past comes alive! ♪
♪ There's a hero of history
Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones
Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give into her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Art of the Steal.
[laughing]
-[man] There it is.
-Huh?
I want to see! I want to see!
What's going on in there?
Must be good if it's this crowded.
[gasps]
Maybe the History of Candy
exhibit is back!
Or Anatomy of Adorable Puppies! Or…
A blank space on a wall.
Huh?
Grandma, what's with the big crowd?
A famous portrait called
A Lady from Milan
used to hang in that very spot
until the day it vanished
without a trace, that is.
Whoa. So all these people just want
to see where the painting used to be?
Yep. Today is the anniversary
of its disappearance.
The mystery always draws
a lot of visitors.
Ooh. Mystery? Vanishing without a trace?
Tell me everything!
I was your age
when I first saw A Lady from Milan,
and it's been my favorite painting
ever since.
-Paola was one of a kind.
-Paola?
The woman in the portrait,
and an old friend.
Sylvia, Ridley, I think we have
our biggest crowd yet to see that wall!
Paola, I mean,
A Lady from Milan deserves it.
And these posters
are selling like hotcakes.
I had to get more copies made
for the gift shop.
Ah, If only I could find
the real painting, I'd be rich!
See if you can steer the crowd
to the gift shop on their way out.
He'll never find Paola.
Not if I can help it.
Wait. You know where she is?
Of course I do. I'm the one
who hid her all those years ago.
[gasps]
What?
Well, with a little help from my friends.
It was a night I'll never forget.
A greedy art collector wanted
to take Paola from the museum,
but she wanted to stay.
So my museum pals, same as yours,
helped me sneak her out of the exhibit
and into a hiding spot.
[jazzy music plays]
You saved her. Can I meet Paola?
I thought you would never ask.
Huh! My grandma, a master art thief.
Who knew?
I am so stoked for you to meet Paola.
She's, like, the coolest.
Cooler than the dark side of the moon.
How do I look? Gotta be my feathery best
for our favorite painting.
[Paola] Do I have visitors?
It's me, Paola. Ciao! Muah. Ciao!
-Ciao, Paola!
-What's up, Paola!
Sylvi-yucha!
Paol-ucha! I've got someone
who wants to meet you.
Is this the Ridley Jones?
Granddaughter of Dr. Sylvia Jones?
The girl who wields
a compass eye and protects the museum?
Yes. Yes, and, well, yes!
Thrilled and thrilled to meet
another Jones woman.
Did you know your grandma
was the first person
who bothered to ask me my name?
She was?
I was always A Lady from Milan,
or "the most famous portrait
in the history of art."
[yawns]
No one ever asked, "Who is
the woman in that painting?"
Until Sylvi-yucha.
Oh, you looked like someone
who'd be fun to talk to.
And you were right. I'm a hoot.
We have been good friends ever since.
Even though I had to
hide you in the storage room?
Bah! I have made the most
of my confinement.
I've learned three languages,
do yoga every morning to keep
my frame flexible,
took up opera…
[sings operatic run]
And yet, I miss my fans.
I long to see a crowd around me.
What can I say? I'm a people portrait.
There's a big crowd in the museum today,
since it's the anniversary
of your "disappearance."
Think we can sneak Paola out
for just a little bit, Grandma?
Ooh, we could give her a disguise!
I don't know.
[Fred] Ahem.
The princess here should have some ideas
you can at least live with.
It's queen. And yes, I do.
We want to hide you, but with style!
No, not style.
Somehow, someway,
you must blend into the crowd.
I will make you unfashionable.
Good luck with that. How do you
make this anything but fabulous?
Oh! Mm! My mustache tickles.
Hang tight, Paola.
We're almost to the art exhibit.
[Paola] I see them! My fans!
Bring them to me,
or at least get me a little closer.
[girl laughing]
Yum! Ice cream!
Hey, kiddos, careful with that ice cream.
We'll be back in two seconds.
Then you'll finally see your fans.
I hope they hurry.
My mustache is so… so… ticklish!
[sneezes]
Mamma Mia!
[Peabody] Mamma Mia! It can't be!
[gasps]
The real deal? A Lady from Milan
was here all of this time?
Ah!
[snickering]
It's finally mine…
- to sell.
-[cell phone rings]
Mr. Peabody, you'd better
have a good reason for calling me.
I'm not interested
in another wild goose chase.
Who could have predicted those statues
I sold you were just geese painted gold?
Ahem.
Anyway, would you like to own
A Lady from Milan?
Of course I would.
But no one's seen it in decades.
Well, you're seeing it right now.
[cackles]
Gimme! Gimme! Gimme!
I can have it wrapped up and ready
for you first thing in the morning.
[Ridley] Whew! Chocolate crisis averted.
-Sorry about that-- Paola?
-[gasps]
[muttering]
Mr. Peabody has her. Come on!
He's putting Paola in his office.
That's a top-of-the-line security system.
How are we gonna get her out of there?
By stealing Paola! Again!
♪ Calling the perfect crew
We're on a mission ♪
♪ Stick to the master plan ♪
♪ First up, we rendezvous
At this position ♪
♪ Quietly as we can ♪
♪ The moment is so ideal
That's the art of the steal ♪
♪ Everyone knows your role
Peaches, you're lookout ♪
♪ Ismat's in charge of gear ♪
♪ Fred's on the first patrol ♪
♪ With grappling hook out
Dudley, well, stand clear ♪
♪ And Dante's behind the wheel
That's the art of the steal ♪
♪ When a friend needs some help
To escape ♪
♪ Her crew will come through
With the perfect caper ♪
♪ All of our comms are linked
So when it's go time ♪
♪ There is no way we'll fail ♪
♪ Get all your watches synced
It's almost showtime ♪
♪ We mustn't leave a trail ♪
♪ And nobody's gonna squeal
That's the art of the steal ♪
♪ That's the art of the-- ♪
[gasps] Shh!
First, we need to turn those lasers off.
Ready, Fred?
Make way for the bison!
Twinkle-hooves, activated.
[scatting]
Fred's hoofwork is next level!
Ridley, I got the code to turn off
those pesky lasers.
Fred, press the green button twice
and the red button once.
[Fred] Copy that. Bye-bye, lasers.
-[Dudley] Whoo!
-[Ridley] That was royal!
Aw! The door's totally locked!
A little help, Peaches?
[Peaches]
I can't unlock the door from up here!
Time to fly like an eagle.
If I could fly, that is,
and if I was an eagle, that is.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Anyway, you can get
in the office through the ceiling.
Great work. Dante, do you mind
giving us a boost?
One dino-pault, courtesy of Ralph,
coming right up.
Ha-ha!
[Ridley, gasps] Mr. Peabody!
O-M-Ra! Is he down there?
Phew! No, just a really big
portrait of him.
-[shudders]
-Do you see Paola anywhere?
She must be in there.
Peaches, think you can get me
the combo for Peabody's safe?
[gasps] Wait, cancel that.
He left the safe open. Oh, Mr. P.
Ridley! Oh! My cannoli-sized heroine!
[Peaches]
Get your keisters out of that office!
Mr. P and Luann just pulled
into the parking lot.
On it, Peaches.
Grandma! Ismat! Bring us up!
Mr. P is back.
We need to get out of here fast.
That's why your getaway board
and bison stuck around. Hop on!
Museum Mayday!
Everyone, get back to your exhibits!
That's Luann, a greedy art collector.
We got you out of Peabody's office
just in time.
Grazie! Now I am safe.
I'm afraid not.
Now that Mr. Peabody
knows you're in the museum,
he'll never stop looking for you.
You'll be in danger forever.
Well, it's the price I pay for being
the most famous painting in the world.
Curse my charisma,
flawless brushwork, and mysterious smile
that leaves everyone wanting more.
Eh, I guess it's back to storage.
No, I won't let you go back in there.
You deserve to be seen.
You've done your best
to protect me, Sylvia.
[chuckles]
After all, where can I go?
It's not like I can hide in plain sight.
[gasps]
Maybe you can.
Grandma, stall Mr. Peabody and Luann.
What you thinking?
I might know how to get Peabody
off of Paola's trail for good.
Behold! The most expensive--
Ahem, I mean,
exquisite painting in the world.
A Lady from Milan.
You've really done it this time.
Eh, sometimes I even surprise myself.
Is this a joke?
That's a poster from the gift shop.
The price tag is still on it.
Uh, I-I-I can't believe it.
[laughing]
Luann, wait!
I thought it was the real portrait!
Luann!
Arrivederci!
[sings operatic notes]
Mamma mia!
Are you really hiding me in plain sight?
Do you think that'll work?
We're about to find out.
I can't believe I thought one of these
gift shop posters was the real portrait.
Sometimes we can't see
what's right in front of us.
[sighs]
Looks like A Lady from Milan
has truly disappeared,
and the mystery
will stay a mystery forever.
[man]
It looks just like the real portrait.
-Take my picture.
-[camera shutter clicks]
Hey there!
Ha-ha!
Sylvi-yucha.
Paol-ucha!
I love it here. Grazie.
Thank you, both of you.
You Jones women
sure know how to make a lady smile.
-I wanna see what's on the second floor.
-This is so cool!
I guess being a protector of the museum
really is an art.
-[man] Simply stunning!
-[girl] I wanna paint.
[boy]
I wonder why she's smiling.
[Ridley]
Gift of the Mummy.
Welcome, all,
to Dudley's very first flying recital!
[all whoop and cheer]
Oh, we couldn't be more proud
of the progress our D-Man has made.
I'm so happy you all were able to make it
and, uh-- Hey, where's Ismat?
[Ismat] Not in that corner!
Is that gingham in gold?
Sorry, Dudley.
I think we better go check on Ismat.
Uh, hey, Pierce and Flo?
We'll need to take a rain check!
Yes, that looks good.
And remember,
everything has to be perfect.
Hey, Ismat, what's going on in here?
This is over-the-top, even for you.
I'm setting up
for my dads' anniversary party.
It's the big one.
Forty-five hundred years.
[Fred] Bisonic!
I know! Look,
I even made matching lockets as a gift.
I'm so excited to give them to my dads.
That's a great photo of the three of you.
I'm sure they'll love it.
[Aten] Wow!
Ismat, the place looks fabulous.
[gasps] You even made the baklava cake
that we love!
We've been looking forward
to this party all millennium!
And check out all the gifts
the other mummies got us!
♪ Two bedazzled robes
Made out of fine Egyptian silk ♪
♪ Jewel-encrusted bowls so that
Our royal cats can drink their milk ♪
♪ When you own a golden throne
Well, your perspective shifts ♪
♪ We are oh, so grateful
For the greatest gifts ♪
♪ Luxury sarcophagi
To rest our weary bones ♪
♪ Goblets with our faces there
In gilded semi-precious stones ♪
♪ Living in such luxury
A mummy's spirit lifts ♪
♪ We are oh, so grateful
For the greatest gifts ♪
♪ And from the commoners
Who worship and admire us ♪
♪ Hieroglyphic cards
Of highest-grade papyrus! ♪
♪ Chariots of gold with rims
Well-suited for a king ♪
♪ Plus the stylish headdress
With the fiercest of Egyptian bling ♪
♪ Gifts so grand and numerous
They pile up in drifts ♪
♪ We are oh, so grateful
For the greatest gifts ♪
Ooh! Gold cotton candy. It looks deli--
Ah! Ouch!
[laughs]
It's actually gold, Dudley.
You can't eat it.
My un-queenly little gift can't compete
with all these other fabulous ones.
Wait. I know!
Dads, I gotta run
one last errand before the party.
Okay, Ismat. Seeya soon.
Well, we'll just be here eating cake.
Thanks for making one
for every year we've been together.
-Delicious!
-Yum!
-Ridley!
-Whoa!
Will you open the entrance
to the real pyramids?
I need to get a new gift for my dads.
"A new gift"? What about the lockets?
These little trinkets? Ugh!
You saw all those
magnificent presents my dads got.
I need to get them something like that.
Something big and extravagant.
What did you have in mind?
A golden statue that was made
in my dads' honor a really long time ago.
It'll be the perfect gift.
-Wow!
-[Peaches] Sounds fancy!
Where is it now?
The exact location's been lost to time.
Hashtag "mummy problems."
But I'm sure it's
in the Pyramid of Secrets,
and with all your help,
I know we can track it down.
Yeah, we can. Right, Ridley?
I still think the lockets
are the right gift.
[sighs]
But if you think the statue is better,
then Eyes Team, let's head out.
Peaches, do your thing.
Okay, I'll mosey on over
to the security room.
Call if you need help.
-Let's do this!
-[all] Eyes!
Ancient pyramids, here we come!
There it is. The Pyramid of Secrets.
-Cool!
-Whoa!
It's bodaciously beautiful.
It is, but don't be fooled
by how it looks.
The Pyramid of Secrets is a maze
of secret passageways,
booby traps, and hidden dangers.
-[Fred] Wow!
-Uh, is it too late to, uh, turn back?
The statue should be
in the pyramid's vault.
Though I'm not exactly sure where that is.
Peaches, think you can find
a map of this pyramid?
Already on it, Ridley. Okay.
What do we have here?
Ancient Athens. Ancient Atlantis.
Ancient Atlanta.
Bob's Banana Palace?
Wait, that's a takeout menu!
[laughs]
Just let us know when you find it.
Okay, Eyes Team,
let's see what we can see.
Halt! None shall pass.
-Ah! You don't have to tell me twice!
-Dudley!
Hold on! You don't have to run away!
[Dudley screaming]
-[Ridley] Dead end!
-What do we do?
Ralph! Do something!
There is no escape!
You shall pay for trespassing!
[sighs]
I'll handle this.
[all]
Huh?
You all remember
I'm mummy royalty, right?
Guards! Look!
You are in the presence of your queen!
Your Highness!
I mean, hi! It's Ismat, Mummy Queen here.
How's it going?
A thousand apologies.
We, uh, didn't realize.
Did you do something different
with your wraps? They look amazing.
What are you doing here, my liege?
Well, I need to get something valuable
out of the treasure vault.
What? But it's rumored to be hidden in
the deepest darkest corner of the pyramid.
Surely, whatever you seek isn't
more valuable than your royal safety.
-Oh!
-Never mind.
It is not our place
to question our queen's wishes. Farewell.
Okay, handled. Now, let's keep moving.
I have to find that statue.
Peaches? Any luck with the map?
Affirmative. Looks like the vault
is on the lowest level of the pyramid.
So you're gonna need
to take the corridor to the east,
next to the giant banana peel--
Oops. That's my bad.
Now go down the corridor
with the funny-looking floor tiles…
[Fred snorts]
Easy. We've got this.
[laughs]
[Ridley] Fred!
[whimpers]
Maybe not so easy.
Ismat, any idea what that symbol means?
Yes! It's the ancient Egyptian symbol
for the number one.
And that tile there has the number two.
There's three, four, five, and six.
I'm guessing we'll need to jump
from one number tile to the next
to get down the hall safely.
Stay on the numbered tiles.
Got it.
Whoa!
[snorts]
Here we go!
I'm surfing the gnar!
And by surfing,
I mean hopping, and by gnar,
I mean giant tiles. And by--
Dante, you can hop quietly, you know.
Ready?
Huh?
Don't worry, Dudley. I'll help you.
[both grunt]
See? It's just like hopscotch.
Like hopscotch with a side of doom!
[Ridley] Okay. Now let's keep going.
[Peaches] Great work, team!
You're just one corridor away
from the pyramid vault!
Perfect gift, here we come!
Uh, did I do that?
[all scream]
Peaches, we're going down a big slide!
[Peaches] What? We have a problem!
That slide isn't on the map!
[all screaming]
Ridley, y'all okay?
Uh-huh. We're now in a room
with a big pit.
[gasps]
And there's a staircase
with daylight behind us!
Copy that, sunshine.
I know where you are.
Those stairs lead safely outside.
The treasure vault
is on the other side of that pit.
Yeah, and the only way across
is using that slippery-looking rock.
Whoa, I can't even see the bottom.
If we fell-- I'm calling it. I'm sorry,
Ismat, but it's too dangerous.
Go if you want, but I need
to get that statue for my dads.
Otherwise, they won't know
how much I love them.
Ismat, wait!
No bottomless pit is gonna stop me!
Stay here. I'll go after her.
Whoa!
Ah-ha! Whoo!
There it is. Yes!
Oh, why'd they have to make
solid gold statues so heavy?
[grunts]
[rumbling]
Uh-oh!
[gasps]
Whoa!
Need a hand?
[gasps] Ridley!
Ismat, I can't hold on to you
and the statue.
It's too heavy. You've gotta let it go.
No, I can't.
I need this statue for my dads.
This is such a big day for them.
I can't let them down.
[Kosy] Listen to Ridley, Ismy.
[gasps] Dads?
Peaches called us
and explained everything!
We don't need the statue,
but we do need you. Let it go!
[sighs]
Goodbye, perfect gift.
[grunts]
Ismat, what were you thinking?
Heading wrap-first into
a dangerous booby-trap-filled pyramid?
I'm sorry, Dads.
I wanted to give you
the statue for your anniversary.
It would've been the greatest gift ever.
No, it wouldn't.
We already have the greatest gift.
You do? What's that?
-You!
♪ Jewels and statues may look nice
But who needs all that flair? ♪
♪ There is not a present
That could possibly compare ♪
♪ To the thing that fills our hearts
And makes our spirits lift ♪
♪ Ismat, don't you realize
You're the greatest gift? ♪
Thanks, Dads.
Now I wish I still had
the lockets I made for you.
You mean these lockets?
[gasps]
I fished them out of the trash
before we left.
Just in case you changed your mind.
Ridley! Thank you.
-Beautiful!
-Oh, Ismy.
Mm. Mm.
-[Ismat laughing]
-[Aten] Woo-hoo!
Whoo! Fabulous party, Ismat.
But the lockets you made us
are the best part.
Icing on the cake.
Which reminds me,
I'm gonna need more of that cake, pronto.
[laughs]
Thanks, Dads.
[all laughing]
[adventurous uplifting music plays]