-[door opens]
-[bird squawks]
♪ In a place full of mystery
Where the past comes alive! ♪
♪ There's a hero of history
Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Daring and bold and courageous ♪
Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give into her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[Ridley speaking]
[whimsical music playing]
All done.
Not a single spot on her.
[Ridley] Wow, Peaches.
The ship looks great.
All finished with the preparations?
Yes, ma'am. Every inch is shining
like a ladybug's shell.
Guess you're pretty excited about the
anniversary of your first space launch.
You bet your banana britches I am!
This is the medal from the first trip,
for out-of-this-world banana bravery!
And I'm gonna celebrate by taking
this pretty little thing for a spin.
Haven't flown her in ages.
Wow! A real space flight!
Who gets to be your co-pilot?
Oh, I don't need anyone else
to come with me.
I like flying solo.
-[loud crash]
-Whoa!
Did someone say space dinosaur?
What? No, I don't think
anyone's ever said that.
Then I might have just heard
what I wanted to hear.
But I know I heard
that you need a space bro!
Please let me go with you!
Uh…
Isn't it astronaut monkey protocol
to have a backup commander?
Well, that's true.
I wouldn't want to violate the protocol.
Darn rules! And double darn my integrity.
Okay, I'll let you come aboard,
but only if you survive training.
Oh! What kind of training?
Whoa! I can't feel my face!
It's awesome!
[laughs]
Just watching this makes me dizzy.
Oh, that speed is not fur-friendly.
Dante must really want to go to space.
I'm just glad it's him who's going
and not me.
I'm afraid of space spiders, you know.
[laughs] Dudley, you've been to space.
You know there's no such thing
as space spiders.
That's what they want you to think.
-[Dante] Whoa!
-I reckon he's had enough.
[sighs]
How you feeling, Dante?
No way you want to go to space now, right?
No, I do. I do.
Just, please stop spinning first!
[groans]
Well, a promise is a promise.
You can join the launch, sunshine.
But don't expect to do anything.
And I know this mission
is going to be the best one yet.
Space travel is about bravery.
But even more importantly,
it's about teamwork.
-Oh…
-[clears throat]
I'll say it again.
It's about teamwork. Right, Peaches?
Uh, sure. Sure. Thanks, y'all.
Now let's start the countdown.
[all] Woo-hoo!
-Safe flight!
-Good luck!
Uh-oh! Uh, Peaches?
I just need to do one quick thing
before we leave.
No time, sugarplum.
The countdown has started,
and space waits for no monkey.
Or dinosaur.
[whimpers]
But it's an emergency.
Psst! Dodo dude,
can you cover for me real quick?
I need to use the little dino's room.
Oh, I don't know if I should.
Just pretend to be me for two seconds.
I'll be right back.
No one will even know I was gone.
[panting]
What?
All right.
There you are, Dante.
Don't forget to strap yourself in.
Definitely, dude-bro.
Hang nine on the surf-skate thing.
Dante, where are you?
[gasps]
[Ismat gasps]
-[Ismat] Mummazing!
-[Fred] Whoa!
[gasps and whimpers]
Come on, what's taking so long in there?
[toilet flushes]
[sniffs and gasps]
Wow, this is amazing!
Are you sure you wouldn't want
to visit space again, Dudley?
-[computer] Ten… nine…
-Dudley? Where is he?
-Huh?
-…eight… seven…
-…six…
-Wait!
-…five… four…
-…three… two… one.
Oh!
Whoa!
Okay, here's the situation.
You're Dudley, not Dante.
Correct!
And you got no training!
Affirmative!
Well, I guess it's fine.
I don't need a partner to begin with.
It doesn't matter who it is.
I can do this all by myself.
[adventurous music plays]
[both] Wow!
Ain't it just as purdy as possum pie?
Earth to Peaches. Come in, Peaches.
This is Mission Control Ridley Jones.
Do you copy?
[Peaches] Uh, copy.
[sighs] And Dudley is up there?
Yes he is! Uh, Peaches,
are those safety precautions?
Nope, fruit protocol.
Everything's hunky-dory.
Now turn that frown upside down, Dudley.
Huh! Maybe a bite of birdseed
will calm me down.
[grunts]
Ah! Whoops!
-[console beeping]
-Ship is on-course.
Reaching our destination shortly.
Oxygen and banana levels
are both good.
Great. How's Dudley doing?
He's fine. Nothing to worry about.
Dudley! What in Neptune happened here?
I, uh, turned my frown upside down.
Well, it's good someone
is up there with you,
even if it's not who you expected.
Not so happy about that
at the moment, Ridley.
Hold on, sugar! I'm a-comin'!
[both grunt]
Thanks. Can we, uh, go home now?
[Peaches] Oh…
Yeah, we better be getting you home.
This is Peaches to Ridley.
We're homeward bound. Just have to…
[Peaches and Dudley grunting]
Earth to Peaches.
Everything okay?
Steering mechanism's not responding.
Oh, it's being stubboner than a mule
on bath day.
[gasps] The birdseed!
It's clogged all my instruments.
And now I can't turn the booster around.
Is that a problem?
Only if we want to get back to Earth!
[whimpers]
-Sorry, Peaches.
-[sighs]
It's all right.
This is just why I wanted to go
on the mission by myself.
Things are simpler when you fly solo.
Okay, Mission Control, let's figure out
how to get our friends home.
Oh! Oh! Oh! I know!
They should command the ship to fly.
That always works
with my mummy subjects.
Stampedes are the fastest way to get home,
but can you stampede in zero-g?
Or they can just, like, forget all
their troubles with a dance party!
[clears throat]
Sorry, my bad.
Uh, Peaches, hold on a second.
I'm checking the ship's manual to see if…
Aha!
Here we go. Peaches, you can put
the booster in the right direction
by turning it manually
at the bottom of the ship.
Copy that. Thank you kindly.
Of course. It helps to have
backup sometimes, right?
Oh…
Please tell me you have a plan
to get us home.
I got a plan, all right.
I'm gonna spacewalk right out that door,
mosey on down the rocket
and fix the booster!
"Spacewalk"? Like walk in space?
No need to unbuckle, Bucko.
I'm going out alone.
But the manual says it's a two-person job.
And besides, going out
by yourself in space?
Yep. Like I said, things are
just easier when I fly solo.
Whew! That's one giant climb
for monkeykind!
[gulps]
There's that pesky booster.
Now all I gotta do is push, and…
[creaking]
[whimpers]
Oh, feathers!
[straining]
Whoa!
Hot biscuits and space gravy!
[grunting]
[Ridley] Peaches?
Everything okay?
Well, I'm out here, all alone,
which I thought was how I liked it,
but I can't do this by myself.
[Ridley] That's okay.
You don't have to fly solo anymore.
You're part of a team. I'll radio Dudley.
I'm sure he'll be happy to help.
I have to what?
Climb down the rungs and help out Peaches.
I know you can do it.
But what about asteroids,
and gravity, and space spiders!
You're gonna be fine.
You can do this, Dudley.
Peaches needs you.
Peaches needs me!
Hmm! I'm a-comin', Rocket Monkey!
[whimpers]
[Ridley] You're doing great.
Now, just work your way down to the fin.
Dudley? You brave, brave bird.
[straining]
[triumphant music playing]
-Whoo-hoo!
-He did it!
Great. Now you can fix the ship
all by yourself.
Oh, heck! I can't do it alone.
I'm sorry for being so impatient
with you earlier, sunshine.
I thought it was easier to go it solo.
But I know now there ain't nothing better
than having a wingman.
♪ So this once solo chimp
She has made, it would seem ♪
♪ A discovery that's quite climactic ♪
♪ When an astronaut
Works as a part of a team ♪
♪ That's when she's at her most galactic ♪
♪ I prefer to fly
Through space by myself ♪
♪ With no co-pilot
Right there by my side ♪
♪ Now, I know I was wrong ♪
♪ And I'm glad
You're along for the ride! ♪
♪ Well, a star's pretty great
When it's all on its own ♪
♪ But it's better in collaboration ♪
♪ 'Cause that very same star
When it's not all alone ♪
♪ Becomes a brilliant constellation ♪
♪ So together
We will soar through the stars ♪
♪ We are stellar
That cannot be denied! ♪
♪ Now we're doubly strong ♪
♪ Because you are along for the ride! ♪
So, what do you say?
Will you lend me a wing,
Backup Commander Dudley?
It would be my honor.
Okay, one, two, three… push!
[both straining]
-We did it! We did it!
-Yes! Yes!
Now, let's get our keisters
back in that ship.
All right.
[console beeps]
Yee-haw!
The booster is back in action!
I think I've had enough starshine,
sunshine. Let's scurry on home.
[Dudley] Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
[Fred] They're back!
-Yes!
-Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
You did it!
Peaches, you were facing
a full-blown crisis up there.
How'd you get back home?
It's a good story, but here's the gist.
I couldn't have done it
without the out-of-this-world bravery
of my co-pilot,
Backup Commander Dudley.
You may be a flightless bird,
but I'd fly with you any day.
-Aww!
-[Ridley] Go, Peaches!
[overlapped chatter]
[Ridley speaking]
Look at me, I'm an octopus!
-[all laugh]
-Great mask.
But watch out for me.
I'm a vampire giraffe.
A vampiraff. Be careful I don't bite you!
-No!
-[all laughing]
I'm a glitter monkey!
Whoa! My mask needs glitter, too.
Glitter? Whoever heard
of a sparkly vampire?
No! No more sparkly vampires
or glitter monkeys!
But Mr. Peabody--
Glitter is expensive.
And we pay by the can.
Lonny, get all the glitter you can grab.
You got it, Mr. P.
I'll use my glitter grabbers.
Now hurry up.
The gift shop isn't going
to overcharge itself.
[sighs] All that glitters
is certainly not gold.
[Lonny humming]
You should have
a vampire giraffe bite him.
[sighs]
Bye! Enjoy your masks.
You're the best glitter monkey
I've ever seen.
-[boy laughs]
-Hmm.
Have you noticed Mr. Peabody's
been getting even more greedy lately?
Oh, I have, all right.
But don't worry, there's nothing
we Jones women can't handle.
You're right, Grandma.
And now that the museum's closed,
I can show the Eyes Team my new mask.
Aww.
[Dante] Whoa!
[giggling]
I don't wanna make you nervous,
Peaches, but if you don't mess up here,
this will be the tallest banana tower
in the history of the whole museum.
I got my eye on the banana pie, sunshine.
Wanted to make sure you're not nervous.
I know I'd be nervous.
[all] Dudley!
Oh, sorry.
No. Come on, Peaches, you can do this.
If you could fly to space, you could put
a banana on top of another banana.
Oh…
Hi, everybody!
[all scream]
[Dante] Bananas!
Whoa!
[all sigh]
Hi. Just me.
Ridley, you can't scare
the last of the dodos like that.
Sorry. I was just really excited about
the new mask exhibit.
Come on, I'll show you.
This exhibit has masks
from all over the world.
It's gonna be here
for the rest of the month.
This one's named Aesop.
Could I try it on?
I wouldn't if I were you.
Legend has it that
all these masks are cursed,
and trying one on
can make strange things happen.
-[all gasp]
-Anyway, I got to go clean up.
The caribou slipped on some bananas
lying around in the rotunda.
Oh! Bananas? [laughs nervously]
How could that have possibly happened?
We should probably help you clean up,
Grandma.
Well, I won't say no
to additional cleanup crew.
Over here, Lonny. The Mask Exhibit.
If we make fake masks, we could
sell these real ones for lots of money.
Oh, I love masks!
Can we try 'em on
before we sell 'em?
[gasps]
Amara, look! Arms and legs.
'Tis a boon for a mask such as I.
I feel like a hoppy spring bunny.
[laughing]
My feet are filled with happy
warm fuzzies.
-Huzzah!
-[gasps]
Let's frolic and play!
[titters]
All done!
Oh, I don't want to see
another banana for a long time.
[gasps]
-Happy, happy day!
-Huh?
Walk this way. No! This way!
Huh?
Wait, is that Mr. P and Lonny
wearing masks from the exhibit?
-[Lonny giggling]
-[Peabody] Ah!
M'lady, Amara, this is wonderful!
'Tis hardly true, Aesop.
Amara and Aesop?
Those are the names of the masks.
Ah! The curse! Grandma said
strange things would happen.
Wait, it couldn't be.
Are the masks making Lonny and Mr. P
run around like that?
[Peabody, gasping] Whoopsie!
-Whoa!
-[trumpets]
Sure looks like it.
We better get the masks off them
before they wreck the museum.
And before Lonny or Mr. Peabody get hurt.
It wouldn't exactly be a Greek tragedy
if something happened
to Lonny or Peabody.
-[Lonny] Look, Aesop!
-[gasps]
[laughing] Whoo!
These body thingies
are a flagon of fun!
Look upon what I can do.
Impressive! Now watch this!
-Hey there, masks.
-Ah!
I'm Ridley. I thought maybe you'd like to…
That face. It hath no mask!
We cannot trust someone without a mask!
We should run away. Silly style.
-[all] Huh?
-Follow that Peabody!
And that Lonny-body!
Uh-oh!
Don't let them get away!
[all] Eyes!
Look, Amara! Musical instruments!
Now that we have hands, we can jam!
If music be the food of love…
[both] Play on!
Huh?
Run away!
[Peabody giggling]
Come on, team!
No, wait!
[Lonny laughing]
Oh, wait!
[all panting]
Well, they got away.
But at least out in the Serengeti,
they won't mess up
the museum anymore.
We still need to follow them
and make sure they're okay.
Eyes Team, move out!
Okay.
Oh, such magnificent open space!
[Peabody exclaiming and laughing]
[gasps]
What splendid kittens.
Come dance with us, fair felines.
-[roars]
-Ah!
These felines are fierce, not fair!
We're in danger. Run away! Run away!
[all roaring]
[both gasp]
Oh, no! They're surrounded by lions.
We gotta save them.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Yeah. I mean, are we really gonna
put ourselves in danger
to save Lonny and Peabody?
Those two have been causing
more and more trouble at the museum.
I know. They are a lot of trouble.
But just because
you don't agree with someone
doesn't mean you want them to get hurt.
♪ The world is full of people
With whom you'll disagree ♪
♪ But we treat each other kindly
That's the way that things should be ♪
♪ We must keep each other safe
We must not give in to a spite ♪
♪ Oh, no matter what
We always do what's right ♪
♪ When you see someone who's in need
Here's what you do ♪
♪ You go and do the thing for them
You hope that they would do for you ♪
♪ Mr. Peabody and Lonny
Are a little short on charm ♪
♪ But when we see them in danger
We don't let them come to harm ♪
♪ Put our differences aside
For it's time that we unite ♪
♪ Oh, no matter what
We always do what's right! ♪
Wow, Ridley just dropped
some epic truth on us.
We're museum protectors,
which means we gotta protect…
-[lions roaring]
-…Peabody and Lonny, too.
Fred could go chase the lions away.
Princess, I'm a big, strong bison,
but bison are grazers, and grazers
do not pick fights with lions.
Even if we could scare off the lions,
we'd still need to get those masks
to stop running away from us.
Masks? That's it! I have an idea.
Come on, gang. It's crafting time.
How's everybody's mask?
Wildebeest! Rawr!
Robot!
Swamp monster!
Another wildebeest.
I, uh, couldn't decide.
Still vampire giraffe. Great work.
Now let's go get our rescue on.
-[snarling]
-[Peabody whimpering]
Be gone, foul kitty!
Howdy, lions! I'm a wildebeest!
Yummy, yummy wildebeest! Come and get us!
[Peaches]
Starting countdown. Ten, nine, eight…
[Ismat]
Three, two, one. Blastoff!
[Peaches] Whoa! Whoa!
-[Dante] Hey, mask dudes.
-[both] Ah!
What's shaking?
Look, Aesop, other masks.
Ah! They appear trustworthy masks indeed.
Hey, there! Follow us.
We're having a mask party.
Definitely no lions invited.
Ah, that sounds magnificent!
-[Ridley] Well, come on then.
-[Peabody] Wonderful!
[Peabody and Lonny giggling]
Huzzah!
[all laughing]
Whoa!
They don't have masks.
But they did save us from lions.
Perhaps they're not so bad.
Sorry for pretending,
but we just wanted to help you.
And stop y'all
from wrecking the whole museum.
-[all gasp]
-[Lonny] Oh.
We do apologize.
I guess we sort of lost our heads
when we gained arms and legs.
'Tis true. After that crazy adventure,
I should be glad to return to our exhibit.
But once the masks are off,
I'm gonna have to explain everything
to Lonny and Peabody.
You should hide.
I'll try to deal with them.
We'll be here if you need us.
Ready?
[gasps]
-Lonny!
-Ah!
W-W-What's going on?
Mr. Squidbody-- I mean, Peabody--
What? W-w-what are we doing here?
Wait, you don't know how you got here?
I took the bus to the museum this morning
like I always do.
No, I mean you don't remember running
all over the museum,
high-fiving robots,
and getting chased by lions?
Chased by lions?  Don't be absurd.
I would never be-- Masks!
I don't know why but suddenly,
I'm scared of masks.
I-I-I just remembered.
I have important things to do.
Somewhere else. Somewhere not here.
Somewhere not here sounds good.
Wait. You still have
that confiscated glitter, right?
Mm-hmm.
-Huh.
-Here you go!
Good. That stuff is expensi--
-Whoa!
-[loud crash]
-[Lonny] Glitter bomb!
-[Peabody] Lonny!
[laughing]
I may no longer have hands,
but I still have to hand it to them.
It was a grand exit.
-[organ music plays]
-[gasps]
Hey, masked dudes,
we promised you a mask party.
So I figured we should give you
a mask "partay."
-Whoo-hoo!
-Yeah!
What do you say? Wanna boogie?
If music be the food of love…
[both] Play on!
[all laughing]
[adventurous uplifting music plays]