-[door opens]
-[bird squawks]
♪ In a place full of mystery
Where the past comes alive! ♪
♪ There's a hero of history
Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Daring and bold and courageous ♪
Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[Ridley speaking]
-What's that star?
-[Peaches] That's Antares.
What's that one? What's that one?
What is that one?
That's Vega. That's Capella.
-And that there's Rigel Kentaurus.
-Got it. Got it. Then what's--?
[Dudley whimpering]
Oh, thanks for catching me, Peaches.
I'll always be there to catch you,
sunshine.
The view in here is so beautiful.
[Peaches] Pretty as possum pie.
Sure do wish I could
go back up to the stars.
Well, maybe we can't go to space,
but is there anything we can do
that reminds you of space?
I reckon I might have a couple ideas.
[Ridley laughing]
You mastered Mars mode, all right.
Now, rock it up a notch to Jupiter gear.
Shifting to Jupiter gear.
-Whoo-hoo!
-Now that's what I'm talking about.
Ooh, what's this button do?
Ah! Banana surprise!
Houston, we have a pyramid!
[both scream]
Marmalade and mayflies! Brace for impact!
Ridley! Are you two okay?
Pleased to report
that our mission status is A-okay.
We're fine, Mama.
Wish I could say the same
for my rover's tire,
which I could fix if I had my tools,
but I lost 'em in the black hole incident.
[all gasp]
Black hole incident?
[gasping]
What was the black hole incident?
[all exclaiming]
I got you, sunshine!
We try not to speak of the incident,
but you're a protector of the museum now.
It's time we told you what happened.
Years ago, before you were born,
I was setting up a brand-new exhibit.
The Future of Space Travel.
But my compass eye
accidentally activated the black hole.
It expanded and expanded,
and sucked in the whole exhibit.
We haven't seen hide or hair
of that poor exhibit since.
So, we moved
the black hole display down here.
It was way too dangerous
to stay in the rotunda.
I lost my red toolbox
to the black hole that day,
and a whole bunch of bananas.
Those brave bananas.
I hope you're happy up there in that
great big banana bread bakery in the sky.
Well, if we're going to fix your rover,
we're gonna have to brave the black hole.
Hot biscuits and gravy!
You mean I get to go
on another astronaut adventure?
Gear up, gang.
Guess we're going
to outer space tonight after all.
-Yay!
-Whoo-hoo!
[thrilling music plays]
Oh, careful with that.
Flares are only for emergencies.
[yelps]
[frantic music playing]
Sorry. But it was pretty.
[exciting music builds]
[all] Whoa!
Sorry, dudes.
Ralph's just totally stoked
to go to space.
[mysterious music playing]
Let's do this.
-Whoo-hoo!
-[all] Yeah!
[gasps and screams]
Wow!
Whoa!
[Dudley] Ay, Chihuahua!
[majestic music plays]
-Wow!
-Amazing!
[Peaches] Brace for impact!
[grunts]
[Ridley] That was royal!
Check it out!
My dance moves are even
more bisonic in space!
-In space, I can almost sort of fly.
-Whoo-hoo!
[laughs]
Hold on, sugar, I'm a-comin'!
Wowee!
You sure look like
you're at home out here, Peaches.
You bet your buttermilk I am.
That's one giant leap for monkeykind.
Come on, everybody.
We need to find that exhibit.
-Whoo-hoo!
-Let's go!
[Peaches] Yippee!
-[Dante] Tubular.
-[Ridley] Amazing!
-[Dante] Juras-sick!
-[Fred] Wow!
[gasps]
There it is!
I spy with my bisonic eye
the Future of Space Travel exhibit!
Then keep those peepers peeled
for my toolbox.
-Whoo-hoo!
-Yeah!
I can't believe how good
this stuff still looks.
[all gasp]
Hi, there!
Oh, hello. I'm Ridley Jones.
Hello, Ridley, my name is G.L.A.D-Six-S.
But you can call me Gladys.
I am your host
to the Future of Space Travel exhibit.
A robot? I never knew
there was a robot in the exhibit.
Understandable. I was still in my crate
when I came through the black hole.
Once we landed on the asteroid,
it broke open.
And I have made my home here ever since.
Well, don't that beat all?
Once we finish our mission,
we can take you to the museum with us.
I appreciate the kind offer.
But if it is all the same to you,
I would prefer to stay here.
I like the view.
It is pretty amazing in outer space.
♪ Up where you float and you fly
As you please ♪
♪ While all the planets swirl around you ♪
♪ Have you seen nebulae
Brilliant as these? ♪
♪ Don't all the shootings stars
Astound you? ♪
♪ See our amazing galaxy
Filled with such cosmic grace ♪
♪ Free as a bird in zero G ♪
♪ The beauty of outer space! ♪
♪ Comets and quasars
The asteroid belt ♪
♪ Black holes and meteoric showers! ♪
♪ Closer to heaven than you've ever felt ♪
♪ Watch supernovas shine for hours! ♪
♪ Colors and lights you won't believe ♪
♪ Earth is a pale blue trace ♪
♪ Mind-blowing sights you can't conceive ♪
♪ The beauty of outer space! ♪
♪ Outer space! ♪
Guess I can't fault you
for wanting to stay up here.
But for now, we're looking for some tools
that Peaches needs to fix the rover.
I do not have any tools in my camp,
but when I came through the black hole,
some of the exhibit landed
at the bottom of the ravine.
Follow me, folks. I will show you.
You know, Peaches, instead of me
coming back to the museum,
you could just stay here.
It is beautiful up here.
Here we are, as promised. One ravine.
-Wow!
-Oh, cool!
Whoa! Help me, I'm falling!
Oh, uh, falling slowly
so someone will need to save me
in the next, hmm, 15 minutes or so.
I'll always be there to catch you,
sunshine.
Look! What's that over there?
Oh, bless my monkey heart.
It's my missing bananas.
Oh, brave and delicious bananas.
Ooh, and being in space, frozen solid.
[clack]
But I bet they'd still be yummy
with a little butterscotch.
Okay, gang, let's start looking around
for the toolbox.
We'll keep searching no matter
how long it takes to--
Found it!
That was easy.
Yeah, almost too easy.
I'm not sure I'm ready to go home yet.
Oh, an asteroid! Look at this!
I bet no queen in all of Egypt
has ever had a space stone before!
[grunts]
[rumbling]
Oh, it's an avalanche!
A totes sluggish avalanche.
Huh.
[Ismat exclaims]
I got you.
Oh, no! The toolbox!
Don't worry. We're in low gravity.
This avalanche is no match
for a mighty bison.
[grunts]
Catch you later, space rock gator.
Someone get a picture of me looking
all strong and send it to the eagles.
[laughs]
I don't think asteroids have Wi-Fi.
Ow!
Whoa!
[screaming and sobbing]
Don't you worry!
My astronaut training
taught me what to do!
Hang on, honey bunch!
Peaches is a-comin'!
Heavens, I missed this.
Help me, Peaches! You're my only hope!
Dudley, you gotta slow yourself
down a smidge.
I'm trying, but I don't think dodo wings
were made for interstellar flapping.
I think I got me an idea.
Yee-haw! I love outer space!
Almost as much as three
whole banana butterscotch sundaes.
Birds, am I glad to see you!
I'll always be there to catch you.
And I'll always be there to be caught.
That was incredible.
You really do belong here in space.
Peaches, if you wanted to stay,
we'd understand.
I'm not gonna lie.
The view up here is prettier
than peas in a pork chop,
and the adventure of the cosmos
makes my little heart pitter-pat
like a whole lotta--
Uh, Peaches. I'm floating away again.
But I can't always be there
to catch Dudley if I'm out in space.
Thank you kindly, Gladys, but right now,
my greatest adventure is helping Ridley
be the best protector she can be.
That's where my heart is.
[all] Aw!
We should head home.
You know Mama, she'll be worried.
Take this communicator
and give me a call anytime.
Now that we know how to work
that black hole doohickey,
I'll be here the next time
I get a hankering for space adventure.
I will miss you. I will miss you all.
Until then, goodbye.
[all] Whoa!
[uplifting music soaring]
How's the rover handling now?
Smooth as Saturn.
How's your frozen banana?
I think asteroid frozen
butterscotch bananas
might be my new favorite.
What say we try and rock it up
a notch in Jupiter gear.
[Peaches] Let's go, antigravity!
-Dude!
-Go, Peaches!
I'm gonna give that pyramid another try.
Still okay with coming back down to Earth?
Bless my soul. I'd never want to miss
an adventure like this one.
-Whoo-hoo!
-Yee-haw!
[Ridley speaking]
[band playing rock music]
♪ Take a look at these hallowed halls ♪
♪ History and stunning beauty ♪
♪ We cannot forget our sacred duty ♪
♪ We must look out
For each ancient artifact ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ So we will not rest
Until the case is cracked ♪
♪ We are the Eyes of the Museum ♪
♪ We are the Eyes of the Museum
Time to watch! ♪
-[crowd cheers]
-[girl] Yeah! That was royal!
How's everybody doing out there?
We're the Rotundas!
[Dante] Go, Rotundas!
The Rotundas sure know
how to rock it up a notch.
They're the best band in the whole museum!
Technically, they're the only band.
But yeah, they're the best, too.
Now, take it away, Fred!
[drumming]
[Ismat] Go, Fred!
-[Dante] Whoa, those beats are dino-mite!
-[Peaches] You're a star!
Whoo-hoo! Fred, you got skills!
Well, right back at you! Look at you go!
[laughs and snorts] Yes.
You, Evie.
Whoa! Wait, really?
Head to the gift shop after the show
for Rotundas merch.
Kidding.
[Peaches] That was out of this world!
Wait up, Evie. You can really play.
That means a lot coming from you, Fred.
I see a lot of me in you. Here.
[gasps]
You should join the Rotundas.
We could do a dueling drums thing and--
Oh, I'd love to, but I can't.
Oh, okay. But why?
I'm too small to be in your band. See?
I can barely reach the pedal.
You know, I wasn't the big, tough bison
you see before you
when I first started to learn the drums.
I was just a calf.
No way!
I used to rock out
in the Saturn model all day long.
The echo made my drumming sound bisonic!
That's super cool.
Don't let your size hold you back!
-[laughs]
-[Peabody] What is going on in there?
-Uh-oh!
-Museum mayday!
Code, Peabody. Everyone, hide!
Hide!
Scatter, dudes and dudettes!
Don't panic!
[Peaches]
Take your own advice, sunshine!
Uh-oh!
[Peabody] What was all that racket?
This is a museum, not a concert.
I don't like music. The way it makes me
feel things is horrifying.
Wait. All that noise
was coming from this?
Hey, Mr. Peabody. Just practicing.
All by myself.
-Hmm.
-[laughs nervously]
Well, no more of that.
I have a very rich--
[chuckles] Ahem.
I mean, a very special guest
visiting tonight,
and everything must be perfect.
A special guest? Who's that?
Never mind who, just keep quiet.
Music is too joyful.
-[clanging]
-Huh?
Now, what is that?
I have to make it stop immediately. Lonny!
Well, that was a close call
if I've ever laid my eyes on one.
Yeah, and I wonder who
that special guest is.
Knowing Mr. Peabody, it can't be good.
Hey, my cymbal is missing.
It's gotta be around here somewhere.
What in ancient Egypt is that?
I don't want to freak anyone out,
but it's gotta be a ghost!
Naw, it's probably the pipes.
I accidentally flushed a board
the other day.
Turns out the inside of a toilet
does not make a good half-pipe.
Doesn't it kind of sound like
the beat to a song?
Like a ghost drummer?
-[rhythmic clanging continuous]
-That's my beat.
The one I was playing at the concert.
That's gotta be Evie.
She loved my drum solo,
so I tried to give her my cymbal to play.
The one that's now missing.
That means Mr. Peabody
is looking for Evie!
We gotta find her before Mr. P does.
Follow that beat!
[Ridley] Evie?
Evie, if you're hiding
in this queen's domain,
I demand you show yourself!
Please?
Ground control to Evie.
Come out, come out wherever you are.
-[clanging continuous]
-I got you!
[grunts] And there's nothing there.
[Dante] Where are you, little one?
-[Ismat] Evie!
-Now what?
Well, we checked in every
sarcophagus and pyramid…
Not to mention up the Sphinx's nose.
Gnarly!
-[Peabody] I got you now, sound!
-It's Mr. Peabody! Again! Hide!
[Dudley] Oh, feathers.
Miss Jones? But where were
all those voices coming from?
Oh, that was all me, Mr. Peabody.
Well, that makes no sense.
I heard at least four different voices.
I was just seeing
how many different voices I could do.
"Heya, sunshine."
"Mesozoic."
"It's queen, remember?" "Bisonic."
"Honk!" "Dodos don't do deserts."
I don't sound like that, do I?
Okay, keep your voices to yourself.
Tonight is too important to be distracted
by Jones family shenanigans.
Coast is clear, everyone.
-[all yelp]
-Aw.
Shh! Eyes, our search needs to be
a lot quieter from now on. Okay?
Roger that.
Look out, plushies. Here comes Fred!
You in here, Evie?
Fred, we gotta be quiet, remember?
I am!
I don't think she's in here.
Me neither. Let's go, everyone.
Oops. I guess Ralph
didn't get the quiet memo.
[gasps and laughs nervously]
-Dante! Stop moving!
-[Peabody] Aha!
Now I got you, mystery noise!
Mr. P!
Again? We're running out
of hidey holes, sunshine.
I have an idea.
You again? Hold on.
Something is different in here.
Hmm.
Yeah! We got cool new merch.
I don't remember getting a shipment of--
Wait a minute.
That new stuffed bison is adorable.
[gasps]
Huh?
[scoffs]
I don't have time for this.
Whew, he really almost
caught us that time.
And we're not any closer
to tracking Evie down.
-Her drumming keeps echoing all over.
-[clanging]
Wait. Echoing.
I know where Evie is. Come on!
You think I could keep these?
Dudley, it's nighttime.
Hey, the sun doesn't set on cool,
you know?
Evie! There you are.
Fred! You were right.
This is the perfect place for drumming.
Why did you run away with Fred's cymbal?
Oh, right. Here you go.
Oh, no. I want you to have it
and I want you to join the Rotundas.
Now, I know you think you're too little
but you shouldn't let that stop you.
You're really talented.
Thanks, but the other mice
would just laugh at me.
Mice are supposed to be quiet and small,
not cool, loud rock stars!
I mean, name one mouse rock star.
Huh. That is a tough one.
Oh, Beethoven wasn't a mouse, was he?
Evie, you're a rock star!
Thanks.
I feel pretty cool on the inside,
but I'm still just a mouse.
Oh, you can be any kind of mouse
you want to be.
Big or small, quiet or loud, you name it.
I never thought about it like that before.
[Peabody] Welcome!
Uh-oh. Mr. Peabody.
It sounds like his visitor's here.
Come on.
[gasps]
I'm sure you'll find
something you like tonight.
-Who is that?
-I don't know.
But I have a bad feeling about this.
Love her hat, though.
Let's get closer and find out.
Wait till you see our Egyptian wing,
Miss Luann.
Lots of mummies to choose from.
As I always say, you can never have
enough mummies.
Hold up! Enough mummies for what?
Or may I interest you
in an ancient chessboard?
Perhaps a rather large whale?
They're all for sale.
[gasps]
She's here to buy stuff from the museum?
[gulps] Meaning?
Any one of us!
Oh! What if she wants a dodo to go go?
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Oh, they're coming this way!
Everybody freeze!
Hmm.
-Too big.
-Oh, ahem.
I take back what I said about her hat.
She has such bad taste.
[all gasp]
Hmm. Too green.
We have to get her out of here
before she decides to buy anything.
But how?
Mr. Peabody, as you know,
I have a bottomless budget.
Oh, really? I had no idea.
But I am very particular, and…
none of these pieces
are truly speaking to me.
I'll be on my way now.
Wait.
[gasps]
That is a masterpiece.
I've never seen such beauty.
Ah, that cute bison.
Yes! I simply must have it.
Oh, excellent. I'll get it ready.
Oh, no! Fred!
There's got to be something we can do.
[strains]
I got this. I think. Yeah, I got this.
[whimpering]
Oh! What is that?
[both scream]
There is no way I'm buying anything
from this creepy museum.
Wait! Wait! Miss Luann!
That was a close one!
Evie! You saved me!
Way to go!
That was thrilling.
I guess I'm small and larger than life!
Oh, I never doubted it for a second.
Sometimes, you have to tell people
who you are on the inside.
[rock music plays]
♪ The world may think
That they know you ♪
♪ They see a mouse who is rather small ♪
♪ But sometimes you have to show
You are not what they see at all ♪
♪ Because big--
Big is a state of mind! ♪
♪ Your inside and outside
Aren't always aligned ♪
♪ The size of your heart
Can't be confined ♪
♪ Big is a state of mind! ♪
[Evie]
♪ They say that looks are deceiving ♪
♪ I'm living proof
That they sometimes are ♪
♪ 'Cause now I've started believing
I'm a really big rock star! ♪
♪ Because big--
Big is a state of mind! ♪
♪ Your inside and outside
Aren't always aligned ♪
♪ The size of your heart
Can't be confined ♪
♪ Big is a state of mind! ♪
Lady lemurs and gentle mummies,
presenting the newest member
of the Rotundas!
Give it up for Evie!
-[laughing]
-[drumming]
[Dudley] Oh! You sound great!
Yeah! You rock, Evie!
Yeah, I do, don't I?
Now, let's take it from the top.
[band plays rock music]
[adventurous uplifting music plays]