-[door opens]
-[bird squawks]
[adventurous uplifting music plays]
♪ In a place full of mystery
Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history
Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Daring and bold and courageous ♪
Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones!
Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[Ridley speaking]
[Dante] Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
-I'm bringing the heat. About to blow.
-Wow!
Whoo! Eyes of the Museum,
are you ready to see
the most "Jurassick"
skateboard-genius move ever?
[all] We're ready!
Then prepare to have your minds blown
by the Eruptor!
-Amazing!
-Behold! The Erupto--
-Whoa!
-I got you!
Phew. Thanks, Ridley.
That was a Cretaceously close one.
Was that bump always there?
It's definitely new and weird.
I better have Mama look at it.
What in blazes is that thing?
Huh. It's a bump made
by one of the roots of our tree house.
Whoa! They must be really long!
Long and old.
In fact, this is the oldest tree in town.
The museum was built around it.
It's the backbone of this place.
An expensive backbone
that I'm going to dig right up.
Who knows
how many more roots could pop up.
It has to go!
[all gasp]
But Mr. Treebody--
I mean, Peabody, it's our home!
And has been for generations!
Uh-bup. My mind's made up.
I am not spending a fortune on this tree.
It's being removed tomorrow morning.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have some beautiful bills to count.
-Mr. Peabody. Watch your--
-[Peabody yelps]
-…step.
-[growls]
You've made a powerful enemy today, tree.
I never liked nature.
[sighs]
Hey, Mama, maybe we can pay
to take care of the tree?
I'll go get my piggy bank.
It's almost full and--
Rids, I hate to tell you this,
but we just don't have the money.
Wait, then does that mean
we're gonna lose our home?
I'm afraid so.
But how can we protect the museum
if we're not in the museum?
I don't know, but we'll find a way.
[sighs] This is what happens
when you put profit before people.
I better start boxing things up.
O-M-Ra! Mr. Peabody can't
just tear us apart like this!
Makes me want to snort! [snorts]
His heart is colder
than all the moons of Jupiter.
I hope you and your mom
and grandma don't move too far away.
Will you come and visit
your favorite dodo bird
to make sure he's still one of a kind?
My family is staying put.
I'll find the money
to save our tree. Somehow.
-[Ma] What in tarnation?
-[Pa] Whoa!
Hey, by the way,
what in tarnation is a tarnation?
-Beats me!
-[Ridley chuckles]
Hi, Ma. Hi, Pa!
Howdy, Ridley!
Who put up this here speedy bump?
We've got loot that needs a-stashin'.
Loot, huh?
What about our loot?
Well, you and Pa are experts
at finding hidden treasure, right?
The best in the west… wing of the museum.
The east, too!
Do you think you could help me
find some loot? To save my house.
Hmm.
Of course we'll help you save your house.
You Joneses are good people.
Well, we've been searching for a
special treasure and could use some help.
And when it comes to treasure,
finders keepers.
We'll split it with you fair-like.
-Shake on it.
-Deal.
No going back now.
But I best warn you, little lady,
finding that there treasure won't be easy.
[laughs]
Why is she laughing? I'm creeped out.
Just nod and smile. Nod and smile.
[horse whinnying]
[Pa]
Welcome to our secret hidey-out.
Whoa! The old empty exhibit space.
I always wondered what was in here.
Look at that emerald!
[Ma] Worth a fortune.
But it's in that there old mine.
It'll be rough going,
even for an adventurer like you.
I am a protector of the museum, remember?
I got this.
Come on, team.
[whimsical music playing]
Never gets old.
Huh. Minecart tracks…
But, like, no minecarts?
Y'all will just have to go on foot.
Keep an eye out for our chuck wagon.
We scouted our own little path.
Yah! Let's go, horsies!
Peaches? Think you can lead us
through this old rickety mine?
[Peaches]
I'm sorry, sunshine.
That mine is falling apart quicker
than my grandma's famous monkeybread.
Okay, Eyes. We'll just take it slow
and not make any sudden moves.
Oh, cool!
-[thud]
-[cracking]
-Uh-oh!
-[gasps]
[all  yelp]
Whoa! My bad. I mean, Ralph's bad.
I mean, our bad.
That's not good.
Hmm. Just walk like this Egyptian!
[grunts]
Almost…
Afraid this tunnel
isn't dino-sized anymore, big guy.
Fred's right.
Dante, you head back to the rotunda.
We'll see you soon.
Aww! Bummed to miss the treasure hunting.
Well, good luck, dudes and dudettes.
[Ridley] Huh.
I'm no abandoned mine expert
but I think we've hit a dead end.
The scariest kind of end!
-[Ma] Giddyup! Yee-haw!
-[Pa] Yee-haw!
Looks can be deceiving.
Make way for the bison!
[grunts]
Whoa!
Hurry up! Can't hold it for long.
I can't believe I'm gonna say this
but Ridley, Ismat, go!
I'll stay here and help Fred!
Dudley? Are you sure?
No, but I'm gonna do it anyway
for Ridley's home!
Thanks, you two. See you when we get back.
[grunts]
[loud crash]
Phew!
[horse whinnying]
There's the chuck wagon!
Y'all better keep up!
[Pa] Yee-haw!
Oh, no!
[clicks]
Wait. Much better.
You know how
this queen feels about the dark.
Ismat, wait!
Whoa!
Oh!
-Whoa.
-Thanks, Ridley.
Also not a big fan
of falling into bottomless pits.
Me neither.
I don't see a way
to get across this thing.
Unless we could fly, that is.
Maybe we can by using my wraps!
This fashion line
is about to become a zip line.
Great idea.
[grunts]
-Yes!
-Cool.
[both laugh]
But what about you?
You have to get that treasure
by morning or it's goodbye, tree house.
The Eyes Team all gave up the adventure
to push you forward, Ridley.
We know how important that tree is.
It's the backbone of the museum.
I won't let you all down.
Here I go!
[heroic music playing]
Have Fred and Dudley
move the boulder again,
and I'll meet you all back in the museum.
Good luck storming the rickety old mine!
Whew! No bottomless pits.
No wall of boulders.
[Pa] Ridley! Over yonder!
[horses whinny]
Welcome to the end of the line.
I gotta say, you two breezed
right through this old mine.
So why do you need my help?
And where's the gem?
We think it's behind
that there big bucket.
[Pa] Which is too heavy for us to move.
That's not a bucket. It's a minecart.
[grunts]
-[Pa] There it is.
-[Ma] We're rich!
Whoa! The emerald. It's beautiful.
[blows]
[grunts]
It's stuck in the wall.
We'll need some muscle to get it out.
We got some muscle for you.
-[whistles]
-[horses whinny]
Give it the old heave-ho on three.
A one, a two…
[Ma & Pa] Heave-ho!
[gasps]
Whoa! Got it!
-[Pa] Yee-haw!
-[Ma] Whoo-wee!
-[rumbling]
-Oh, no, the mine. It's collapsing!
[Ma] We best skedaddle outta here!
Whoa! Rocks!
Oh! Giant hole in the tracks.
Hang on!
Whoa!
[thrilling music playing]
-Whoo-hoo!
-[Ma] Yee-haw!
We made it!
Next stop, the Jones tree house.
Mama, look what Ma and Pa and I
found in the old mine.
Treasure! We can sell it to save our home.
[gasps] That's quite an emerald.
Must be worth a fortune.
-But I can't accept it, honey.
-Why not?
Ma and Pa said when
it comes to treasure, finders keepers.
That gem is an artifact, not a treasure.
And us Jones women
are protectors, not profiteers.
It isn't our place to sell artifacts.
We give the artifacts
that explain history a home.
♪ This rare and priceless gem
You managed to unearth ♪
♪ Has a story it can tell
And that's its truest worth ♪
♪ We'll keep it safe right here
Beneath this giant dome ♪
♪ Doesn't everything deserve
To find a home? ♪
♪ The dodo and the dinosaur
We Joneses strive ♪
♪ To shelter and to cherish them
To keep the past alive ♪
♪ We share their tales
With all the people, young and old ♪
♪ 'Cause they all deserve
To have their stories told ♪
♪ They teach us lessons ♪
♪ And we gladly learn them ♪
♪ And if we find a better home
We return them ♪
♪ A place to call your own
No matter where you roam ♪
♪ Doesn't everything deserve
To find a home? ♪
You're right.
Finders keepers is not something
a protector of a museum should say or do.
And think about it.
If we sold the gem, the buyer would be
the only one who could ever see it.
[gasps] That's it.
We can still use the gem
to raise money to save our house
by putting it in an exhibit.
That way, we can protect the artifact
and share it with people.
That's a fabulous idea, Miss Jones.
[giggles]
Good morning, Joneses.
Ready to say goodbye
to this bump-causing tree?
-That won't be necessary.
-Not with our new lost gem exhibit.
Huh? Hmm.
The museum now houses a one-of-a-kind
beautiful priceless emerald.
Hello!
We've already sold out tickets to see it
for the entire summer.
Which is enough money to take care
of our tree for a long time.
Oh, boy! I'm going to make so much money.
Ow! What was that?
Uh, what was what?
Hmm.
So our tree can stay?
Yes, it can stay--
[grunts]
-Yes!
-Whoo-hoo!
Eyes Team, did you hear that?
-Amazing!
-Hurray!
[Ma] Yee-haw!
Big thanks to Ma and Pa
for sharing the emerald.
So now kids from all over can see it.
-Shucks.
-Anything for those adorable guests.
And to my Eyes Team.
Without all of your help, I wouldn't
have been able to save the tree house.
-What are friends for?
-Any time.
[Ridley speaking]
Mama, I'm glad we're giving stuff away.
But can you really have a garage sale
if you live in a tree?
[both laugh]
I just know it's time for the Jones women
to do some spring cleaning.
Now, keep or give away?
Easter Island paperweight.
Does it spark joy?
Yup. Keep. It looks just like Lou.
Old Amazon treasure map?
Keep. You never know when you'll get lost
in the Amazon.
And you can't exactly ask piranhas
for directions.
Huh.
-Old dodo feathers?
-Ah-choo! Toss.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Ridley, it's your old snuggly!
My what?
Snuggly. Your baby blanket.
When you were little?
Oh, you took it everywhere.
It was so cute.
Eh, toss.
What? But it's your snuggly. Your snuggly.
[laughs]
Mama! I think I'm a little too old
for a baby blanket.
Plus, I'm a museum protector now.
Adventure is my blanket
and danger is my pillow.
Whoa! My baby shoes.
I can't believe I was ever that little.
[sighs]
-[Ismat] Amazing!
-[Dante] Whoa!
What's going on out there?
-Whoa!
-What do you see?
Hey, Eyes Team! What's shaking?
We're trying out
the new virtual reality machine.
Or we would be if a certain princess
wasn't hogging the headset.
It's reality, but it's virtual.
Wrap your ginormous brain around that one,
'cause mind… blown!
[all chuckle]
VR is pretty cool.
Yeah, Mr. P bought it for a new exhibit.
Can't believe I'm gonna say this,
but that Peabody did something right.
Hmm, weird.
That was royally awesome!
Ooh! Ooh! Let me try.
Whoa, dude!
It looks so real and feels so real.
That's because they are real!
Hands off the horns!
Oops. Sorry. Wanna try, Rid-dude-ly?
You bet I do.
[Peabody] Absolutely not.
[gasps] Mr. Peabody!
There's a virtual Mr. Peabody?
Oh, why can't technology
just be used for good?
No! I hear him. Here, in real life. Hide!
[all whimper]
I'm just saying if you're going
to be opening a new exhibit,
you should let us know first.
I'm opening the VR exhibit to make
this museum more modern and profitable.
Uh, ahem, I mean fun.
Let's start construction over there,
Lonny, where that hunk of junk is.
Aye-aye, Mr. P!
Wait, that's not a hunk of junk.
That's Anniematronic.
She greeted guests
the day the museum first opened.
She's an important part of history.
Our history.
She sticks out like an old thumb.
She doesn't fit the sleek,
modern museum I'm building.
Get rid of this exhibit or I'll happily
get rid of you. Come on, Lonny.
Uh-oh. Not again.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Annie really means a lot to you,
huh, Mama?
You used to love greeting Annie.
I can't imagine the museum without her.
Don't worry.
We'll find a way to save her. I promise.
[Annie] Oh, don't worry about me.
Greetings, Jones women,
and welcome to hallway 3C.
Home to several notable exhibits
including me, Anniematronic. Hello!
Annie, you don't have to give us the tour.
We live here, remember?
Oh, right, right. Sorry, force of habit.
Anyway, I heard what Mr. P said,
and you don't have to sweat saving me.
[groans]
I've been part
of this museum since forever.
I wouldn't mind a break.
Plus, Mr. Peabody might be right.
I don't really fit in
with all these newfangled exhibits.
Wait, that gives me an idea.
Mr. Peabody said you stuck out too much
next to the new VR technology, right?
So, we just have to find a part
of the museum where you fit in better.
If you think it's possible.
It has to be.
I won't let them get rid of you.
First up is the tundra exhibit.
We can move you here, and during the day
you can greet guests
and tell them about the exhibit.
Like how it was discovered
5,000 years ago by Marianne Tundra
after her Frisbee was stolen by a walrus.
Whoa, really?
Wait. Dudley! No, it wasn't.
Oh, sorry. When I don't know something,
I usually just make things up
and hope I'm right.
And I'm never right.
Well, this is new to me.
But I'll give it a try.
How's it going in your new spot?
Great.
I just invited the Lemurson kids to visit
and enjoy the wonders of the tundra.
-They're out there playing right now.
-Out there? Uh-oh!
Stampede!
[all] Stampede!
Whew!
Sorry. Guess I was a little too inviting?
-Yes!
-Come on!
Now this is a great spot for Annie.
The train's been here since forever too.
[train whistle blows]
Greetings, and welcome
to the museum train.
This is a replica of a steam engine
commonly found in--
As engineer, shouldn't you
be keeping your peepers on the road?
Actually, steam trains run on tracks
instead of roads.
Though I guess since this
is a museum train, it wouldn't run on--
-[gasps] Whoa!
-[all] Whoa!
-Oh, no!
-Look out!
Dude!
[loud crash]
Everyone okay?
-I think so.
-Yep.
Can someone stop the rotunda?
I'd like to get off.
[sighs]
[groaning]
Oh, we tried everywhere.
All over the museum.
From the aardvark habitat
to the Zimbabwe exhibit.
And still couldn't, like,
find a cool new crash pad for Annie.
But we can't give up.
Mama's right. We… Hmm.
[sighs]
Annie, what are you looking at?
Oh, just taking in
the beautiful sight of the snowfall.
The Arctic exhibit is amazing, isn't it?
I've never been.
We couldn't find the right place
for you in the museum,
because there is
no right place in the museum.
It's true!
I've never stepped foot
in the outside world.
I think now I just want to explore
what's beyond the museum.
Then you should go.
We'll help you pack and see you off.
-Great!
-[all] Yeah!
[sighs]
Well, I think I'm all set to go.
Thanks for all the gear, Ridley.
Goodbye, all!
And thank you
for attending my goodbye party.
Make sure to get your parking validated
on the way out and--
[laughs] Annie!
Right, right. Not a greeter anymore.
Also, we don't have cars.
Are you sure you don't want
to stick around a little while longer?
I'm ready to go, Sarah.
Thanks for all the wonderful years.
[Ismat] Have a mummerific trip!
-[Dante] See you!
-[Dudley] Be safe!
[sighs]
Wait. No!
Mama!
[all] Huh?
[Sarah panting]
Sarah, what are you doing out here?
You can't leave the museum.
The Arctic is cold.
And there are polar bears,
which seem cute in pictures,
but are actually really big and--
Wait, don't move.
-[cracking]
-Okay, Annie, we're on thin ice.
It'll be okay. Just slowly head toward me.
Slowly. Slowly.
-Now run!
-Oh!
[intense music playing]
Greetings, and welcome to a huge disaster.
What do I do?
[Ridley] Don't worry.
We're on our way!
Yeah, we're on our way!
Okay, penguins, do your penguin thing.
[grunts]
Ridley! Where'd--?
-Did someone order a penguin rescue?
-[both laugh]
Are you okay?
I am now.
Now push.
[all squawk]
Whew! I haven't had an Arctic adventure
like that in a long time.
All I wanted to do was get Annie
to reconsider leaving the museum.
Yeah, why were you
so against her leaving, Mama?
[sighs] I guess, so much
has been happening lately.
All the new exhibits, technology, and you.
-Me?
-You're growing up so fast,
and a full-fledged protector
of the museum now.
I guess I just didn't want
another thing to change.
Mama, if things didn't change,
I wouldn't know about all of this,
or made all my new friends, or been able
to use my protector training to save you.
Change can be good.
♪ When this was all beginning ♪
♪ So much has changed
Since way back then ♪
♪ And though my head's still spinning ♪
♪ I'd gladly do it all again ♪
♪ 'Cause things will work out
The way they should ♪
♪ Trust me
Change can be good ♪
♪ This change we're undergoing
It's not an easy thing to do ♪
♪ But as I keep on growing
I'll keep on growing close to you ♪
♪ But things will work out
The way they should ♪
♪ Trust me
Change can be good ♪
♪ Change can be hard and scary! ♪
♪ But change is also necessary ♪
♪ Oh, things will work out
The way they should ♪
♪ Trust me
Change can be good ♪
Welcome back to dry land.
I'm so glad you both are all right.
Never been better. Thanks to my daughter.
[giggles]
[all squawk]
I'm sorry for trying to stop you, Annie.
You deserve to see the world.
You've made this museum brighter
for a long time, but…
change can be good.
Have a good trip.
Thank you.
[laughing]
Princess, you're hogging the goggles.
Again!
It's "queen," and I'm seeing
what it would be like to rule over Mars.
I kind of like it.
Mama, how are you?
I'm good, Rids.
Just missing Annie a little bit.
Well, we have a surprise for you.
[gasps] A "surprise"?
I'm, uh-- Okay, I'm in the museum…
[gasps]
It's Annie!
Welcome to the museum.
We have a new exhibit about plankton open.
So make sure to stop by the gift shop
for some teeny, tiny souvenirs.
[gasps] How did you--?
Ridley recorded Annie before she left
and uploaded it to VR.
Now she can, like, greet guests
in the museum for a long time.
And whenever you miss her,
you can see her in here.
-Oh, Ridley.
-[laughs]
Huh. Where did Ridley's snuggly go?
I know I put it here earlier and…
Ridley, have you seen--?
[gentle music playing]
[chuckles]
Some things never change.
[adventurous uplifting music plays]