Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
Who is Dexter Morgan?
He's just a jerk who works
for Miami Metro Homicide.
Now can I please go?
Yes.
So you're not interested in alcohol
or looking at naked women?
You may be in the wrong place.
I'm taking out the trash
that would otherwise
be left to putrefy.
There is a legal system for that.
If it worked as well
as you think it does,
I wouldn't be so busy.
I'm just gonna get
a swab from your cheek.
You do this for a living?
Well, I hate it, but I get it...
what you do.
But what I don't understand
are the blood slides.
They're trophies.
They're like Speltzer's earrings.
I'm nothing like Speltzer.
My bosses at the club,
they ordered me to get close to you.
These men are dangerous.
I-I can't go back to them
with nothing.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
- He's gone.
- Motherfucker...
He has a girl in here.
We have to find her.
She's dead.
Just when it seems like
Deb and I are making progress,
we take a left turn.
I showed her a monster, Ray Speltzer.
The killer who chased his victim
through a maze.
I could have prevented that murder.
And Deb accepts that.
But she hasn't accepted me--
what I am.
And I'm not sure she ever will.
Yep.
I'm getting nothing.
You?
No.
That maze man--he's good.
He knows what he's doing.
My hat's off to any killer good enough
not to leave any DNA behind
at a murder scene.
Plenty of his DNA
in this place though.
Well, if this cemetery was his office,
it's like this place was
his break room.
Something was here.
Something special,
like a trophy maybe?
From one of his victims.
Killers hate to leave
their trophies behind.
Well, that means Speltzer
stopped by here
after he killed that girl.
But there's none of her DNA here.
No blood, no fibers, no hair.
No reception.
Speltzer is loose in the world,
and Deb will do everything
in her power to find him.
But will she and I be able
to find our way back to each other?
Deb...
will you...
Will you be mine?
Morning.
Coffee.
Now.
- Rita...
- Another left turn.
Trinity killed her.
Yes.
- Yes.
- Why?
She didn't fit the pattern at all.
Because I was coming after him.
So while we were hunting Trinity,
you were too.
I figured out who he was
before you did.
And didn't help us fucking get him?
He knew who I was, where I lived,
that I had a family.
I was trying to protect them.
You wanted to fucking kill him.
And I did.
When?
He's dead.
That's what matters.
But when?
I took care of him.
Did you love her?
- Why would you ask me that?
- Because I suddenly
have no idea what's the truth
and what's a fucking lie
with you anymore.
I loved her.
If you were so concerned
about your family,
then why were you going after Trinity?
Is that what a loving husband does?
Are you even capable of love?
I love you.
How?
How can you love me
and also love to--
It's how I've lived my whole life.
Before the moment
you walked into that church,
did you ever question
the way I felt about you?
- Why is it any different now?
- Why?
Jesus, Dexter.
Morgan.
Okay.
It was Batista.
They found Speltzer.
A security guard spotted him
at the scrapyard,
and he had the good sense
not to try and be a hero.
It took four officers
to take Speltzer down.
He put up one hell of a fight.
They came close to shooting him.
If Speltzer had a weapon,
they would've.
Speltzer is a weapon.
He was mine.
He hasn't asked for a lawyer yet.
This is your one shot.
A confession is our only shot.
He was wearing a mask
when he came at me,
so I couldn't make an I.D.
that would stick.
I can't believe his DNA wasn't
at the crime scene.
Masuka and I went over it twice.
Yeah, Dexter and I,
we checked Speltzer's
mausoleum man-cave
for evidence of his victim there,
but no luck.
I mean, Dexter and I
can't make evidence appear,
you know.
If you don't get a confession,
you won't get Speltzer.
Are you two ready?
Fuck, yes.
That's Dexter Morgan.
His face.
It looks familiar.
I put everything Jurg
dug up on Morgan in there.
He's not a cop.
He's a lab rat.
Blood splatter.
It's spatter.
- Blood spatter.
- Whatever.
He's from Miami.
Normal guy.
Except his wife was murdered
by a serial killer
a few years back.
The man we killed on the boat?
Louis Greene.
He was an intern for Miami Metro.
The boat's owner, this Dexter Morgan.
He works for Miami Metro too.
Viktor's death--
is it payback for killing
that detective?
Viktor fucked us real good here.
Of all the people he could've shot,
it had to be a fucking cop.
So it's Viktor's fault he's dead?
Uh, yeah.
He was a loose cannon.
Never listened.
At least not to me.
Everything was going great
until he showed up in Miami.
Viktor was a good man.
He was loyal.
He was committed.
And he was here to do
what you couldn't.
Keep the Colombians from taking
over our traffic!
Fuck.
Here we go again.
Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm Detective Quinn.
I'll be your official
pain in the ass for the day.
Could we get that music turned off?
Ladies, to the left,
customers to the right.
Keep it behind the bar.
Ma'am, I need you to go ahead
and stand over there.
Officer.
It's detective.
Detective Quinn.
Do not tell me you are fucking her.
No.
What makes you think that?
You're not the only one
who's a detective.
You really think a stripper's
a good idea?
No, it's a horrible idea.
Seriously, how long
is this gonna go on?
I'm thinking every day
until we lock up
Mike Anderson's shooter.
Or you could say a number,
and it'll be just like old times.
You know, leave your car unlocked,
you'll find some cash,
maybe some blow.
And all this goes away.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Get the fuck out of my face.
None of this makes any sense.
Viktor's dead.
They got him!
Not everyone
at Miami Metro knows this.
Otherwise, they wouldn't be here.
Maybe this Morgan and Greene
were working alone.
Well, why the fuck would
these two assholes
cover up Viktor's murder?
I believe Dexter Morgan knows why.
Just say the word.
I'll take him out.
No.
I want to talk to him.
Talk?
What are we supposed to do
in the meantime?
We got two boats waiting
to drop off our supply,
even though we can't move
what we already have.
We are bleeding money.
The bartender, Alex.
One of ours, isn't he?
Yeah.
So let's give them what they want.
For my money,
four on one is not
really a fair fight.
I did a little boxing myself
back in the day.
I didn't take on four cops,
but I, you know--
I held my own.
You don't want to chitchat.
I get that.
Here's the thing though.
My lieutenant is gonna come in here
and say that she saw you at the maze
where that waitress died.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Right. Guy like you
was probably at the gym.
But she's a woman.
They get shit wrong all the time.
And this one, man, she's my boss.
If you can believe that.
I have to fucking answer
to her skinny ass every day.
And she's always squawking
at me, you know.
Her beak goes "Squawk, squawk,
squawk, squawk, squawk,
squawk, squawk."
To tell you the truth, I envy you.
I've been wanting to pop my lieutenant
in that beak of hers for years.
She's dying to get a shot at you.
Should we let her?
Could be fun.
Right?
All right.
Nice job in there.
He's all ready for you.
Deb.
Good luck.
He was mine, but Deb needs this
more than me.
And she needs to get him her way.
Remember me?
I saw you just the other night.
That is some maze that you built.
What is it for, Ray?
Are you sure you don't remember me?
Maybe I'm not pretty enough.
Your mom sure was pretty.
She died a few years ago, right?
Cast a long shadow, I bet.
Hard for any girl
to measure up to those looks,
but you keep trying, don't you?
What do you think about
the girls that go home with you?
That they're stupid?
Easy?
That they're whores?
They'd have to be, right?
To go home with you,
take their clothes off for you.
Girls like that are vulgar.
But girls like that,
sure do look like your mom.
So I have to wonder...
Your mom was so pretty.
She probably had
a lot of admirers, right?
Men who would go home with her
and watch her take her clothes off.
And then take her any way
that they wanted her?
Shut up.
There were many ways
to break a body down.
You could hear it, couldn't you?
You could hear her through
those thin walls
that the two of you shared.
You could hear how much
she loved getting fucked
by all those men.
You could hear her kissing them,
all the things that
she might do with her mouth,
that same mouth
she would kiss you with.
But be honest, Ray.
You kind of liked it, didn't you?
Weren't you kind of wishing
that it was you inside her?
I should've killed you like
I killed that other bitch!
Go to hell.
We got him.
Way to go, lieutenant.
- All right.
- Good job.
Hey, Deb.
Jamie said she was good
to watch Harrison till late tonight
if you want
to grab a drink or something.
I thought you'd be
in the mood to celebrate.
I'm really glad we got Speltzer.
But celebrate?
No.
Melanie Garrett is still dead.
But you got Speltzer.
He'll never hurt anyone again.
Well, outside of prison.
Dexter.
I've been thinking a lot
about Rita--
about how she died.
She died because of you.
Because you were selfish.
You have a son.
Harrison is three years old.
Someone needs to protect him.
I do.
Someone needs to protect him from you.
He could go live with Astor and Cody,
with their grandparents in Orlando.
I am a good father.
I am the right person--
the only person who can
and should raise my son.
Who, like me, lost his mother.
It is not fair of you
to expose a child to your life...
choices.
You have to decide!
Your desires or--
No, I don't.
You said it yourself, Dexter,
that you can't stop,
that you don't want to stop.
And if you keep doing this,
you're like a fucking magnet.
Bad shit is gonna find you.
And if that happens, I'll handle it.
What if you had been
three minutes later
to Speltzer's fucking maze?
But I wasn't.
You were too late for Rita.
I should have killed Trinity
the first time I saw him.
That's the mistake I made.
That's the mistake that you made?
Yes!
And I will never,
from this moment on--
Do you hear me?
I will never ever
make that mistake again.
It is not in your control.
Everything is in my control.
I am not giving up my son.
Mr. Sirko.
George.
I wasn't expecting visitors.
That's all right.
We don't stand on ceremony here.
Have a seat, Alex.
You have a beautiful family.
Thank you.
That is why I came here.
They are still in Kursk.
Your son and daughter,
what are their names?
My son's Zakhary and my girl,
her name's Yulia.
They're twins, yes?
How old?
Five.
Their birthday's in April.
Wow, five.
That's the best age, huh?
Learning to read, walking,
seeing the world,
and yet, they still want to be held.
You're probably wondering why
I stopped by.
Well, you see--
Tell me...
How much money do you send back
to Kursk each month?
From your job at the Fox Hole?
$750.
I take out only my rent, my food,
some money for my car.
A sacrifice for you, I'm sure.
Yeah, but still,
it's not very much.
What if your family could have
a lot of money?
Security.
And college for Zakhary and Yulia?
You'd want that for them.
I would give anything for them.
That pleases me.
Because that is why
I came by here today.
To ask you a favor, Alex.
Yes, of course.
Anything.
I have a problem.
One of my men killed a police officer,
and I have
to give the police a suspect
so they'll stop harassing us.
And that suspect is you.
But I didn't kill anyone.
Sure, you did.
I want you to write a note.
Pen, paper?
This is what I want you to write.
"Kaja.
"I cannot live with what I have done.
I'm very sorry."
I will take care of your family now.
Zakhary and Yulia
will want for nothing.
That's for you.
It's the gun that killed
the police officer.
What do I do with it?
Bang.
Look at your children's faces.
They're looking at you.
Wanting you to give them the best life
this world has to offer.
You will do this for them.
And if I don't?
We'll kill you anyway.
And throw your wife
and fucking kids in the river.
No need for threats.
We're all friends here.
But I think you understand
the situation.
You won't feel a thing.
It'll be quick,
like turning off a light.
For my family?
Hannah McKay.
She spent six years in juvie
after pleading guilty to being
Wayne Randall's accomplice.
She always claimed she was just
another one of his victims.
Wayne called her the Robin
to his Batman,
but with better legs.
Dexter Morgan.
You look a little lost.
Well, I haven't been inside
a police station
in 15 years.
Still smells the same,
like fast food and sweat.
Well, hospitality isn't
exactly our main concern.
I heard the sheriff's
department found the body
of one of Wayne's victims.
Yeah, they went back one last time
after Wayne... died.
And expanded the perimeter.
Is that what you're doing here?
To help us find
the other bodies Wayne buried?
My lawyer said it was for the best.
There's a rumor going around
that you were the last person
to talk to Wayne
before he...
died.
His last words were about you.
Oh.
He said something about
every day being like
an unwrapped present.
Yeah. Yeah.
I remember when he got
that fortune from a cookie.
You two didn't stay in contact?
Too painful.
Where were you and Wayne going anyway?
Was there a plan?
Not much of one at first.
We were just trying to get out
of Clopton, Alabama,
which isn't even a town.
It's an intersection and a cemetery.
But somewhere around Sarasota,
a plan did begin to form.
Argentina.
We were gonna go find
a farm in Argentina
and settle down.
What?
We were living on farms in Alabama.
Like, somehow,
it would all be so different
in South America.
Do you miss him?
I miss the way I felt with him
on the road.
That life was just beginning,
and that anything--
anything was possible.
You know the feeling?
No.
It's my lawyer.
I'm sure he's wondering
where I got lost to.
We have a big problem.
What's the problem?
Watch the Miranda.
Put him on the fucking car!
You know how this goes.
If you want an attorney,
we'll get one for you.
Even if can't afford one.
Do you understand your rights?
Huh?
Do you understand?
- Say yes.
- Did you guys see that?
Looks like a "yes" to me.
Fucking cock sucker.
They never got a verbal confirmation
that Speltzer understood his rights.
No.
But Speltzer fucking nodded.
He didn't say, "Yes."
And at Speltzer's arraignment
this morning,
his P.D. was able
to make the case--
Don't.
That because Speltzer
at one point knocked unconscious,
it is entirely possible
that he did not understand his rights,
that it wasn't a nod, that
it was a temporary blackout.
And the judge fucking bought that?
The judge threw his confession
out of court.
He walked.
- When?
- Two hours ago.
Motherfucker.
And apparently, Speltzer's planning
to file a lawsuit against us.
Use of excessive force?
I don't believe this.
So all that's left to do is--
is what?
Wait around till
he kills someone else?
There's nothing else we can do.
But there is something I can do.
Fuck that.
Fuck all of this.
The bartender from the Fox Hole
blew his brains out last night.
Why don't they wear uniforms?
There's no respect.
You'd never know they were police.
Unless you knew
who you were looking for.
We got a single gunshot wound
to the right temple.
What appears to be GSR
on the right hand.
It was through and through,
based on the height
of the bullet in the wall.
Alex was sitting at the table
when he put his gun to his head.
We got a White Russian on ice.
Very funny.
I'll have you know I have
a major following on Twitter.
This gun is a 9-mil.
Same type of weapon used
on Mike Anderson.
I'll go to ballistics
and run this through.
And confirm this turd is our shooter.
But I know that Viktor
killed Mike Anderson.
Why would Alex take the fall for him?
Unless there's someone at the club
who wants the investigation to end
as much as Miami Metro does.
Quinn, read that note again.
"Kaja, I cannot live with what
I have done.
I am very sorry."
- Sorry to Kaja?
- Yeah.
I mean, it makes sense.
It's obvious that this Alex
Dubrozny had feelings for her,
and she was in love with Tony.
Which probably didn't sit
very well with him.
So he kills her, kills Tony.
And Mike was just
in the wrong fucking place
at the wrong fucking time.
I mean, this guy still has pictures up
of his kids, his wife.
Yeah.
He probably feels horrible
having to look at her face
all fucking day.
That's just it.
He doesn't have to.
Take the pictures down.
Put them away.
Leaving the pictures up
just tells me that
he still cares for them.
He's a guy.
Once something's up on the wall,
why bother even taking it down?
- I don't know.
- What don't you know?
I don't know if it all adds up.
Well, look.
We'll talk to the neighbors.
See if they saw anyone coming in,
or out of Alex's apartment last night
if it'll make you happy.
It's not about happy.
Angel.
Angel, this is our fucking guy.
Everyone yearns
for clarity, for closure.
But is that ever really possible?
Jamie?
Harrison's outgrown half his toys.
I know we had to go through them.
I just didn't know
it was gonna be now.
I'm almost done.
I wanted to do it while he's asleep.
Anything we're unsure about,
we can put in
the keep-for-now pile.
What's the other pile?
Trash.
You put Lamby in the trash?
Lamby smells like pee.
And Harrison hasn't slept with Lamby
in more than a year.
It used to be he couldn't
go to sleep without it.
Aw, I remember.
Keep?
Nah.
Yeah, a lot of kids sleep
with security blankets
when they're little,
but once they start socializing,
you know, learning how
to be part of a group,
they don't need it.
And Harrison, because he's a genius,
hit this milestone early.
He was so small.
Lamby was a gift from Rita's mother
when he was born.
Maybe we should keep it for Harrison.
For Harrison.
Of course.
Some toys are more difficult
than others to part with.
Speltzer's already back at work,
digging graves.
He should start by digging his own.
Miami Metro impounded Speltzer's
little Pied-a-RV
when he was arrested,
but they had to give it back
once he was set free.
Ray's been juicing--
at least he doesn't mind needles.
I can hide up here,
wait for Speltzer to come home.
I'll use the RV as my kill room
and transportation
to get rid of Ray's body.
And his trophies.
I'm still alive,
but I don't think I'm going
to like the reason why.
Speltzer couldn't have
done all of this in a day.
Is this place his masterpiece?
I don't run.
I make people run.
However, I do run
if there's a bull
coming after me with an ax.
You should really try taking
a shower once in a while.
Where are you?
Speltzer keeps forcing me down
to the next floor.
So if he wants me to go down,
what happens if I go up?
He knows my face now.
If I want a rematch,
I'm gonna have to be smarter.
To take Speltzer down,
I have to make sure
I have nothing to lose.
Mmm, yummy.
Whoa, Harrison's only going to Orlando
for a few weeks, Dexter.
Yeah, I know.
He's gonna be fine.
All he'll want to do
is follow Cody around.
Thanks for driving him up.
I actually might spend
a few days there,
see what trouble I can get into.
Knock yourself out.
Thanks.
I'll take these down to the car.
Astor and Cody are excited to see you.
I want you to be good for
your grandma and grandpa, okay?
I'm not sending Harrison to Orlando
because Deb asked me to,
but because Speltzer
is a problem I need to solve.
Once I do, Harrison will
come home where he belongs.
You mean more to me than...
Pizza!
That's right.
Pizza.
Let's go.
I will avenge your death.
Everything I do...
is for you.
Deb, you okay?
Ye-yep.
I want to get back to the station
and finish up the paperwork
on Mike's shooter.
I'll be there in a minute.
Motherfucker.
You impotent fuck.
You got some mouth on you.
The fuck are you doing here?
Haven't you done enough?
Oh, I'm just getting started.
You fucking motherfucking cocksucker!
- All right, all right.
- You fucking piece of shit!
Get your shit together.
You're so easy, just like the others.
Get the fuck out of here.
Come on.
Fuck you up.
I'll you see around.
Batista called.
I'm sure he did.
Wha--what happened?
I fucking lost my mind.
I saw Speltzer at Melanie's funeral.
Fuckin' smiling
at the hearse, and--
What'd you do?
I fucking attacked him!
I wanted to fucking kill him.
Fuck you.
Is that why you came here?
To prove some fucking point
that everybody
wants someone dead?
I came here to see how you are.
That's all.
I'm just fucking great.
Is this ever gonna get easier?
Nothing's really
all that different, Deb.
The only thing that's changed
is now you know more about me.
What I know about you...
makes you a completely
different person.
But I'm not.
I'm the same person I've always been.
Your brother, the same person
who will always be there for you.
Maybe the question is whether
you'll be there for me.
I don't know if I can
feel the same way about us.
I do.
I do
And I don't too.
Are we sure this Alex Dubrozny guy
shot Mike Anderson?
Why the fuck are you
trying to rattle this?
'Cause it smells like a setup.
And what does a setup smell like?
This bartender had no record
back in Kursk.
Suddenly he decides
to murder three people?
Alex had a short fuse,
a broken heart, a loaded gun.
A gun that Masuka confirmed
was the same one used on Mike.
And we got a sweet little suicide note
that helped us solve not just
Mike's murder, but two others.
That's what a setup smells like.
It's all too neat, too easy.
Alex wasn't even on our radar.
Why would he off himself now?
His conscious got to him.
Let's just swing by the club
one last time, ask around.
This is Mike we're talking about here.
Fine--
not tonight.
- What's her name?
- Nadia.
- The stripper?
- She's a dancer.
Just doesn't keep
a lot of her clothes on.
You serious about her?
I don't know what I am about her.
But she was real close
to Kaja and Tony,
and all this is real hard on her.
Oh, I'm so glad
you're there to comfort her.
- Come on.
- I'm just jealous.
At least you got someone in your life.
She's got a lot of pretty friends.
I'm a twice-divorced
detective
staring down the barrel of retirement.
I'm already a cliche.
No need to add fucking
a stripper to that list.
All right, fine.
We'll go by the club tomorrow,
make sure Alex isn't
some patsy for the mob.
Have a good night.
Fight or flight.
That's a part of everyone's
lizard brain.
Speltzer may have
a lizard brain like me,
but his shortcoming is he doesn't
have much of a human brain.
What the fuck is this?
The end of your run.
Get me out of here!
Yell all you want.
No one's gonna hear ya.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Feels good.
Fuck!
Normally now is when
I'd slice your cheek
with my scalpel
and get a drop of blood
to remember you by, but I can't risk
anyone finding a blood slide
ever again.
You're a fuckin' freak.
I do things different now.
The memory of killing you
will have to be enough.
I'm gonna kill you.
That would be a twist--
and not one that's
gonna happen tonight.
No!
You were supposed
to be a way out of the tangle
I was in with my sister,
a thread she could follow
to understand me better,
to accept me, even.
But she and I lost each other.
She almost lost herself,
going after you.
She wanted to catch you
just as much as I did.
Who knows, maybe our relationship
can rise from your ashes.
No.
No!
It's time for everyone to move on.
Good-bye, friends.
You came.
I wasn't sure you would.
Me neither.
What am I doing here?
Uh, that smoke...
it's Speltzer.
Did you do this for me?
No.
How do you feel?
Glad.
What does that make me?
Human.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com