Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously, on Dexter...
- Where's your lug wrench at?
- No--
We are investigating the homicide
of a Miami Metro police officer.
Viktor left on an evening flight.
He arrives in Kiev at 5:25 P.M.,
your time.
What about the dead police officer?
- I'll make it go away.
- Good.
Hello, Viktor.
Is there anything I can do
to keep you from killing me?
No.
In my game, you can be
the serial killer.
I think this is offensive.
Who would choose
to be a serial killer?
It's a bad idea.
Do something else.
Only one person who ever
worked at Miami Metro
ever took blood slides.
Sergeant Doakes,
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
What happened was too strong.
It got into you too early.
You mustn't ever tell Debra
the truth about yourself.
If you think she's upset now,
that's nothing compared
to how she'd feel
if she learned what you are.
Dexter, what the fuck?
You said Travis
came at you with a sword.
Where did you get the knives?
There was, like, a whole roll of them.
I'm just trying to put this together.
Are you a serial killer?
Yes.
I've dreaded this moment
my whole life...
but I never pictured it like this.
Don't you fucking touch me.
I just want to know you're okay.
I am not okay.
I am never gonna fucking be okay.
- Just try to take it easy.
- Ohh...
Oh, my God, I can't believe this.
How long have you been doing this?
How long have you been
fucking doing this?
Since I was 20.
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ, Dexter.
Those blood slides
that I found in your apartment,
they look like the ones
we found in Doakes' car.
Deb...
Are you the Bay Harbor Butcher?
This is not the place
to talk about this.
Deb...
I only kill certain kinds of people...
- Oh, God.
- Like Travis.
Deb, dad taught me.
He gave me a code.
Dad knew?
It was his idea.
He knew everything.
- Oh, fuck.
- Deb.
Please, just...
just come back inside with me.
Please.
Harry found me sitting
in a pool of my mother's blood.
He understood why I had these...
urges.
A lot of horrible things
happen to a lot of people,
and they don't turn out like you.
I don't know about other people.
But I have this... need
deep inside me.
I call it my Dark Passenger.
You gave it a name?
Harry said it got in me too early
and too deep.
He said I couldn't change it.
And so...
he thought up the code.
He said if I had to kill,
I might as well kill people
who deserved it.
You make it sound like
it's okay--
like you're the victim here.
The people in that box,
Dexter--
they're the victims.
Victims?
A choir director who raped
and murdered little boys?
A married couple smuggling refugees
who killed the ones who couldn't pay?
A psychiatrist who manipulated women
into taking their own lives?
There's this place
called the police department.
Sometimes the system doesn't work.
Killers fall through the cracks.
Don't I fucking know it?
I'm talking to one right now.
I am the worst fucking detective
in the world.
You're my own brother.
How could I not see
what you were doing?
You're not responsible for this.
Well, I am now.
I helped you cover up Travis' murder.
I'm an accomplice.
You walked in on me.
I had to think on my feet.
Well, fuck me for ruining your night.
What am I supposed to do here?
My name has the word
"Lieutenant" in front of it.
I can't turn my back on this.
All of this is very,
very fucking wrong.
So...
What are you gonna do?
Uhh!
I never wanted her
to go through this, Dex.
Neither did I.
Then you should have been
more careful.
At least she didn't arrest me.
Not yet.
What is this doing here?
Is it some kind of message?
Maybe someone else is on to me.
"According to FBI
Special Agent Frank Lundy,
"it's almost certain that
the Butcher is still at work.
"Serial killers have an addiction
and will continue to kill
until they're caught."
If the ITK hand
in my apartment is genuine,
then it can't still be in evidence.
Not here.
Then I was sent the real thing.
No record of it being checked out.
Could it have been stolen?
Sorry.
Sorry. Saw you come in here.
I just got curious.
- Now I wish I hadn't.
- Why?
You're looking for the hand,
aren't you?
Look, I can explain.
Look, remember my former intern Ryan?
Blonde, stacked, and the cause
of many sleepless nights?
Yeah.
Well, she needed some extra dough,
so she stole the hand
and auctioned it online.
That's why I fired her.
Who won the auction?
Don't know.
I put Louis on the case to find out.
Louis?
Now, even with all his digital skills,
he couldn't dig up a name.
At least he was able to erase
the electronic trail.
Did Louis find the hand and keep it?
No one needs to know, right?
But why send the work
of a serial killer to me?
Does Louis know what I am?
Dex?
What?
We're cool, right?
Yeah.
No one needs to know.
Oh, thank God.
I was ready to blow you.
Not necessary.
Briefing.
- Are you coming?
- Yeah.
I have to find out
what Louis knows about me.
Some time alone with him,
and he'd open up--
one way or another.
But I need to put out fires,
not start new ones.
Remember him?
It's been three days
since Mike was gunned down,
and the son of a bitch
that pulled the trigger
is still walking the streets.
Where are we?
We're continuing to hit the club
where Miss Soroka was employed.
Someone there must've seen
something related to her death.
We still think it's our best
shot at a lead,
so we're going to shut them down
every night.
You know, those places do big
business during lunch too.
Just saying.
Start shutting them down twice a day.
- With pleasure.
- Moving on.
This pretty face
belongs to Wayne Randall.
15 years ago, Randall
and his teenage girlfriend
went on a three-state killing
spree that ended here in Miami.
He's currently serving two
consecutive life terms at Dade.
Randall now claims to have
evidence on three other murders
that he committed in the Miami area,
and he wants to come clean.
He wants to lead investigators
to where he buried the bodies.
Hmm.
That's nice of him.
He says he wants
to clear his conscience.
I think his lawyers are just
trying to swing a deal.
- What's he telling us?
- He told us about one victim,
a brunette in her mid-20s
that matches a missing persons
report from that time,
a Janice Dubois.
So then there's a chance he's
not completely full of shit.
County has requested
one detective and one lab tech
to help them process the scene.
Miller, you're volunteer number one.
- I'll go.
- No.
I want Masuka on this.
Aw. I don't to work
a dumpsite.
Come on lieutenant, I'm up
to my ears on Mike's case.
I'm sorry.
You're with Miller.
Contact info will be in your boxes.
You'll start tomorrow.
That's it.
Thank you.
Can I talk to you outside
for a second?
I was this close to arresting
you this morning.
I even thought about
what I would say to the press.
I wouldn't want to have
to write that speech.
I don't know what to do.
Every alternative I can think of...
is fucking crazy.
Such as?
It's fucked up.
Try me.
The say people like you are addicts.
Like drugs.
It's not untrue.
Well, when addicts want to get
better, they go to rehab.
I don't think there are
clinics for what I've got.
We can make one.
I could be your clinic.
- How?
- You move in with me.
I watch you 24/7
and make sure that
there's no way in hell
you can...
do what you do.
And...
If it is an addiction,
then maybe--
maybe you can get over it.
You're right.
It's crazy.
Dexter, if you can channel your urges,
why can't you control them?
What if dad had taught you how to quit
instead of teaching you
how to live with it?
He fucked up.
Deb, there's a big problem
with this idea.
What?
I've tried stopping before.
It didn't work.
Well, now you have me.
Someone who loves you more than
you will ever fucking know.
And in spite all of this,
I still believe
that there is good in you.
Maybe more that's in most people.
What if it doesn't work?
I don't want to think about that.
And how much choice do I have here?
None.
Okay.
Thanks for getting back to me
so quickly.
I'm curious.
Your facilities
are state-of-the-art.
Why go through a private lab?
Just trying to lighten the load.
It's been a hectic few months.
But just to confirm,
the blood you sampled
from the glass fragment
is a positive match
with Travis Marshall's?
No question about it.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Remember, keep this confidential.
And when you send back the findings,
address them to me personally, okay?
- No problem.
- Great. Thanks.
Yes, captain?
Regional FBI office, please.
We are back.
Hey.
I won't allow this to go on.
This is harassment.
No, this is an inconvenience.
We're working our way
up to harassment.
I told you the last time
you were here,
I don't know who killed Kaja.
I don't know who shot your policeman.
Kaja was clubbed to death
in the parking lot
15 yards from where we are now.
- No one here saw anything.
- Sell that shit somewhere else.
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna keep coming here
every day and shut me down?
No, I'm coming back tonight too.
What the fuck do you want from me?
I want the shooter.
Now, you better rack your brain
and give me something,
or I'm gonna turn this place
into a fucking monastery.
Mm-hmm.
You got that list?
Follow me.
You know, the money we make
here is all we have to live on.
What you're doing is really unfair.
What's your name?
Nadia.
Come here.
Have a drink.
We're not supposed to drink
while we're working.
Come on.
You hear any music playing?
Now, what you said isn't true.
I do care who killed Kaja,
but no one around here
seems interested
in helping me find out who it is.
Okay?
Do you know anybody
who might be interested
in hurting your friend?
You've been told
not to cooperate with us?
Kaja was dating someone.
Tony Rush.
He's one of the bouncers here.
They were on and off,
but Tony is a good guy.
Can you point Tony out to me?
He's not here today.
Mm-hmm.
I really hope you catch
the person who did this
and put a bullet through his head.
That's not generally how we work,
but I get where you're coming from.
Here, if you can think
of anything to help,
just give me a call.
I will...
Detective Quinn.
Joey.
Excuse me.
- Tell me you got the shooter.
- Possibly.
One of the bouncers
hasn't come to work
- since the night of the murders.
- Tony Rush.
- How'd you know?
- He and Kaja were an item.
Suspicious timing, don't you think?
- The sudden absence?
- Mm-hmm.
Come on.
Hey.
You're gonna sleep in the bedroom.
I'm not gonna put you out.
Yes, you are.
I'm sleeping out here.
Deb, that's ridiculous.
This isn't a fucking
pajama party, Dex, okay?
You're gonna take my bedroom,
and I'm gonna sleep
out here on the couch.
Between me and the front door?
I will be by the door.
You've really thought this through.
Yeah, well,
I found this website--
"How to cure a serial killer
in ten easy steps,"
and this is the first step.
You'll have to print me out a copy.
I'm figuring this out
as I go along, Dexter.
But if we're gonna do this,
we're gonna do it all the way.
We're gonna eat together,
we're gonna watch TV together,
we're gonna drive
to fucking work together.
Hope you got a big shower.
Why don't you go unpack.
I'll heat us up something to eat.
You have to be
completely honest with me.
That is the first rule.
My new code.
Don't you think Deb
has gone through enough
without you lying to her again?
I'm not lying.
You're a killer, Dex.
Deb didn't raise you.
I did.
She never saw
what you were really like.
I did.
I was right to channel your urges
instead of trying to suppress them.
You think I can just walk out of here
and call the whole thing off?
If it were this simple,
watching you for 24 hours a day,
don't you think I would have tried it?
Maybe you should've.
How does it feel...
this need to kill?
What do you call it?
My Dark Passenger.
You make it sound like
you're possessed or something.
That's how it feels sometimes.
Do you know how many
assholes in prison
blame their actions on someone
or something else?
I'm not copping a plea, Deb.
I'm giving you honesty.
It's rule number one, right?
How's the spaghetti?
Overcooked.
First rule.
So how does it feel?
It starts with blood.
Blood?
Yeah, the image of it.
Trickling down the back of my eyelids.
The trickle becomes a stream
and then a flood.
It fills me up...
all my empty spaces.
But then the blood isn't red anymore.
What is it?
It's black.
And pressing.
It feels like my head
is gonna explode.
The only way to relieve the pressure
is to open the floodgates
and let it spill out.
I can't believe you're like this.
You're a sick fuck, Dexter.
Jesus Christ.
Well, maybe we shouldn't
talk about it.
Yeah, maybe not while I'm
serving fucking tomato sauce.
Are you seeing blood now?
Nope, just spaghetti.
Well, if you start seeing red,
will you fucking call me?
And say what?
"Deb, I'm seeing blood"?
Say, "I really feel...
like wrapping someone up
in plastic and stabbing them."
And I can say,
"No, Dexter, don't."
Second rule.
There have to be families out there
that are more fucked up than us.
But I sure as hell
wouldn't wanna meet them.
What the fuck am I doing here?
What you think's right.
Right would be turning you in.
I'm doing this because
you're my brother,
and I can't stand the idea
of you living the rest
of your life in prison.
Or worse.
I told Deb I'd be honest with her,
but it's not like I'm stalking a kill.
I just need to get
into Louis' penthouse
and find out what he knows about me.
Are you okay?
It's late.
Yeah.
I'm just doing some work.
I'll sit with you.
Deb, I'm fine.
No. You shouldn't be
alone right now.
I mean, awake and alone.
Yeah. Maybe I should
try to get some sleep.
Just know that I'm here for you.
How could I forget?
Now that Deb is my Siamese twin,
getting into Louis' penthouse
is going to be next to impossible.
But how long can I wait?
You know, for the tenth time,
I barely saw Kaja that night.
I was working.
She got off at 2:00 A.M.,
and I don't know
what she did after that.
Whatever you decide to get
into after this, forget writing,
'cause you could not make up a story
to save your fucking life.
Security tapes back him up.
Shit.
Are you sure?
No doubt.
He was at the club all night working.
Well, it looks like some of
what you said wasn't bullshit.
You were working when Kaja was killed.
We still don't like the fact
that you vanished
the day after she died.
Smells like guilt to me.
You could have had
someone else do it for you.
- No way.
- What happened?
She start sleeping around on you?
- Kaja was loyal.
- Loyal, huh?
Mm-hmm.
So she was doing you.
At least we're getting somewhere.
The problem is now we know
you've been lying to us
about you and Kaja.
And that's bad form, Tony.
We tend to get cranky
when people bullshit us.
Now, if you think what we're
doing to the club is bad,
wait till we start on you.
She was with Viktor.
Say again?
The night that Kaja died.
She left the club with Viktor.
Fucking sleazebag.
Who the fuck is Viktor?
Hey.
How's it going out there?
Don't ask.
- Bad as you thought?
- Worse.
We sit in the sun waiting
for the diggers to find a body.
I mean, so far they've uncovered
a telephone cable
and a bag of used diapers.
I mean, all this waiting around...
It's like dating
a born-again Christian.
If I don't have Deb
watching my every move,
it'll be a lot easier to slip
away to Louis' apartment.
You know, I'm getting
a little stir crazy.
I wouldn't mind a day out of the lab.
Dude, oh, my God,
I would be eternally grateful,
but you'd have to clear it
with your sister.
For some reason,
she really wants me out there.
You think she secretly hates me?
I'll see what I can do.
Masuka's miserable on this whole
Wayne Randall thing.
He's begging me to take over
for him today.
Okay.
Great.
I'll drive.
You'll drive?
I could use some fresh air.
Let's go.
We just got a break
on Mike's shooting.
What?
The last person to see Kaja
alive was Viktor Baskov.
He's a Russian expat.
We couldn't find anything on him
in here,
but we got a hit
on the Interpol database.
It turns out he's a member
of the Koshka Brotherhood
in the Ukraine,
known for narcotics
and human trafficking.
Hold on.
I have to take care of this.
Are we good?
Deb, I'll be surrounded
by federal marshals.
I think I'll be okay.
It was 15 years ago.
Give me a fucking break.
Where are the bodies, Wayne?
Closer to the road.
But why'd you tell us to dig here?
Because this place
looks completely different.
Look at these mini-malls.
You think I like being out here
with you in the fucking heat?
All right.
Listen.
We're moving.
Strike this.
Okay.
Ha. One more wit,
he'd be a fucking half-wit.
God.
Oh, it's hot as a pig's asshole.
All this asphalt.
You know, this used to be
a real pretty place.
Field, trees.
Now look at it.
Nothing stays the same.
That's the truth.
Well, at least the Frosty
Swirl's still here.
You surprised a lot of people.
How's that?
Leading us to these bodies.
Why the change of heart?
Why do you care?
I'm just curious.
People say you grew a conscience.
It was always there.
It was just buried under
a lot of Wayne Randall.
I just surrendered.
Surrendered?
All right.
Let's break for lunch.
We'll pick this up in an hour.
Oh, here we go.
Getting to Louis' penthouse
and back in an hour
will be tight,
but I'm not exactly
flush with options.
I can appreciate the mind-set
of a collector...
But toys?
Seems like a waste
of a good obsession.
My charge card numbers?
So Louis killed my credit cards.
Why is he messing with my life?
Uh, it features
29 points of articulation,
five more than the last figure
they put out,
so at least they're listening
to the collectors.
Uh, still, they could have--
Idea: A video diary app.
One touch, device starts recording.
Tap again, and it uploads
directly to--
Still waiting.
- Yeah, I'm almost done.
- Your hour's almost up.
I'm only thinking of you.
Oh God.
There'll never be an app for this.
Jesus.
This is going to be worse
than Bob Henley.
He got off easy.
I want to see Dexter lying
in his own piss and vomit,
and I won't stop until that represents
the high point of his day.
No one fucks with me.
No one.
Now, on to more important things.
4.99--
Bob Henley.
"Henley arrested after the FBI
found child pornography
"on his workstation.
"Skanda Tech has announced
his dismissal
pending charges which could
fetch up to 15 years."
Is this how Louis took control
of his software company,
by setting this guy up?
What's he planning for me?
With Deb on my case,
I don't know when
I'll have this chance again.
Why are you fucking with me, Louis?
God, please, don't hurt me.
You better give me a good
reason not to hurt you,
because right now I really
want to break your neck.
Why'd you send me the hand?
It was just a--
it was a stupid joke.
I just--you know, the lifelines,
you know, time is short.
It was a clue.
I was screwing with you.
Why?
Uh, because...
I came to you for help
with my game, and you said no.
Your game?
Uhh!
Yes, I swear that's the reason.
Gah--
This is about your game?
I spent five years on that game,
and you shit all over it.
And now I'm too depressed
to even look at it, okay?
It was my whole world.
I never wanna see you again.
Work.
Jamie.
Do you understand?
I'm done.
I'm totally done.
Where the fuck have you been?
Running an errand.
What errand?
Deb, I didn't kill anybody.
How the fuck do I know that?
I've been calling you and calling you.
Well, I didn't get the messages.
Well, check your fucking phone.
I need to know where you are
at all times.
That is what we agreed on, right?
It won't happen again.
Finish what you need to do here,
and then we'll go visit Harrison
together.
Okay.
Here you are.
Seems you rode that wagon
until the wheels came off.
- Trouble in paradise?
- No, she's my sister.
Also my boss.
Congratulations.
You just redefined hell.
What crawled up her ass?
It's a long story.
Randall, what'd you mean earlier
when you said "surrendered"?
I just accepted my situation,
you know,
of being where I am.
Prison.
People watching your every move.
It is what it is.
Once I stopped fighting it,
the anger just fell off...
Like a bad scab.
Left me open to try
and make things right.
They still use real ice cream.
At least everything
hasn't gone to hell.
We're still not getting
anywhere, George.
I mean, you really must like us
coming here.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Well, stop protecting Viktor Baskov.
- I told you...
- Yeah, he doesn't work here.
Just comes in for a drink
now and then.
- That's all I know.
- Right.
We'll see you soon.
I might even bring a portable
polygraph next time.
You know how long it would take
to poly everyone in here?
Okay. Everybody
get your asses back to work.
Rough day?
Isaak.
Mr. Sirko.
What are you doing here?
I heard the police.
It would appear that I'm here
for the same reason,
to find Viktor.
Yeah, I swear.
I have no idea how they got his name.
I'm sure of it.
But we'll get to that.
Anyway, I thought
he was in Kiev with you.
If Viktor was in Kiev,
why would I be here?
Viktor never made his flight.
I checked.
I don't understand.
Where is he, then?
Viktor's caused us some problems.
I won't deny it.
Shooting a policeman
is never good for business.
I can't help but wonder
if someone in the brotherhood
decided to make an example of him.
Without your approval?
No, no, no.
Viktor was impulsive, yes.
He did a stupid thing, yes.
But he was one of us.
And we would always protect him.
You're in luck.
Why?
I believe you.
I've had a long flight.
We have a lot to discuss.
- Hello?
- Hello, Joey?
It's Nadia from the Fox Hole.
Yeah, how many Nadias
do you think I know?
- What's up?
- My car won't start.
I was wondering
if maybe you could give me
a ride home tonight.
Yeah, sure.
What time do you get off?
Hey, we were just having
a little dinner.
Look who's here.
Hey, bud, I missed you today.
- How was school?
- We had toy share.
- Toy share?
- Mm-hmm.
Did you bring your train set?
Fire truck.
Fire truck beat out the train set?
Yes.
Oh, hey, Dex.
Just grabbing one for the road.
I know you don't like me
being on this side alone,
but it's all right
when Jamie's here, right?
Why not?
Sweet.
This is such a great place
to hang out.
Right by the bay.
- Yeah.
- I love coming over here.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I better get going.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll catch you at work, right?
He's not scared of me at all.
And he's not going to quit
unless I stop him.
You're a lifesaver.
Not all cops are so nice to strippers.
To tell you the truth,
I was hoping you had something
more for me.
More for you?
About the murders.
What? You think this is
just some ploy so I can get you
alone and spill my guts?
Look, I told you everything
that I knew.
My car really did break down.
Sorry. If you want,
I could pay you for the gas.
Stop it. It's fine.
It's the least I can do
after all I'm costing you in tips.
You'll have to do a lot more
than give me a lift
to make up for that.
This is it.
On the left.
What'd you have in mind
as far as compensation?
I don't know.
Use your imagination.
Well, you're gonna have
to give me a hint.
I'm very unimaginative.
Okay.
George says the problem with my
car could be the transmission.
Mm-hmm.
It means it's going to be in the shop
for at least a few days.
Yeah.
Well, maybe you could
pick up the bill.
I'd really appreciate it.
You're awfully quiet tonight.
Anything you wanna talk about?
Anything I can do?
Yeah.
What?
Do you have any A.1.?
I think so.
Just enough for a good night's sleep.
That's all I need.
Success!
Thank you.
Just finishing what you started.
I promised Deb.
Hello?
Where are you?
Sorry.
I got here as fast as I could.
I almost drove off the road.
I'm so fucking tired.
What are you doing here?
I snuck out of the house
while you were asleep.
Dexter, what the fuck did you do?
Nothing.
I couldn't go through with it,
but I wanted to.
I needed to.
I didn't care about anything else.
I lost control.
All I could see was blood.
All I could feel was the pressure...
in my head.
Fuck.
It is too deep inside me.
Harry was right.
I am a monster.
You should arrest me.
You should take me in.
Get me off the street.
Dex, dad was wrong.
The fact that we're here tonight
proves that you are in control.
- But I wasn't.
- But you stopped.
That's what's important.
It must've been so hard for you
to call me,
but you did, and that's a huge step.
It makes me think
maybe you can control this.
You really believe that?
I didn't,
but maybe now I do.
What happened tonight is a good thing.
It was really, really good.
I'm not gonna give up,
and I'm not gonna let you give up.
Are you okay to drive?
No, I'm gonna stay with you.
I just need to be alone
for a couple of minutes.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Okay.
You'll wake up with a headache,
probably have a decent idea
how you got here.
Maybe that's a good thing.
I still have to get you
out of my life.
But not by taking yours.
What the fuck?
- Who the fuck are you?
- I'm your employer--
or rather, former employer.
I believe you recently gave notice.
Bullshit.
I work for George.
- Well, worked.
- And he works for me.
My name is Isaak.
I'm the owner of the Fox Hole
chain of gentlemen's clubs,
amongst other enterprises.
What do you want?
Well, it would appear
that George neglected
to do your exit interview.
It's company policy,
and I'm a stickler
when it comes to rules.
You got--
you got to be kidding, right?
Keeping good employees is essential
to running a successful business.
Your feedback is important.
Would you mind telling me
why you quit?
Well, I trust it wasn't
the hostile working environment.
No, I, um...
I just felt it was time to move on.
So it was nothing to do
with the tragic death
of one of our dancers?
Kaja, I believe her name was.
Because if it did,
I would completely understand.
It must have been quite
a traumatic loss for you.
What do you mean?
Maybe that's why
you talked to the police.
No way.
I had you followed.
You know what?
I didn't say a word.
I swear.
I lied.
I didn't have you followed.
You were just
the most likely candidate.
- You loved her, didn't you?
- What?
Kaja.
You were in love with her.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's the one thing that gives
meaning in this life.
I would have done the same thing
if I was in your position.
It's terrible to lose someone
you love.
You still thinking about last night?
Actually, I'm thinking about
how much I could go
for a Frosty Swirl.
That's good.
A sudden craving for sugar is good?
Well, if you're thinking
about normal things,
then maybe you're becoming
more normal.
I'm never going to be normal, Deb.
Yeah.
None of us really are.
Where are you going?
I want a Frosty Swirl.
I'll bring you one.
She'll always be watching me.
But maybe that's okay.
If Wayne Randall can make peace
with his sentence,
who am I to complain?
Especially considering
the alternative.
Well, well.
Looks like you two are ready
to eat each other's shit.
Oh, yeah.
We kind of patched things up.
I'm happy for you.
I never got to do that with Hannah.
Robin to my Batman.
I was never as alive
as I was when I was with her.
Every day was like
Christmas day--
unwrapped present.
I wish I had a chance
to tell her how I felt.
You can still tell her.
Yeah.
I'm afraid the clock has run out.
Damn, I sure as fuck...
gonna miss that.
Hannah used to think
I was something special.
Now she sees me as just a killer.
And you know what?
She's not wrong.
There's just one last person
I need to kill.
He never cared
if anyone found the bodies.
He just wanted a couple of days
of sunshine and Frosty Swirl.
Randall didn't change,
and he couldn't take life in prison.
Can I?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com