1
00:00:10,176 --> 00:00:23,086
Subtitles ReSynced by DeeJayAhmed
www.DeeJayAhmed.com

2
00:00:36,909 --> 00:00:40,206
(NEWSREADER) 'Georgian rebels claimed
responsibility for the Narwhal virus

3
00:00:40,246 --> 00:00:43,384
'that brought Russia's financial
infrastructure to near collapse.

4
00:00:46,124 --> 00:00:49,024
'Successful testing of intelligent
synthetic flesh

5
00:00:49,064 --> 00:00:51,368
'aimed at getting multiple amputees
back on their feet

6
00:00:51,407 --> 00:00:52,957
'is hailed as a major breakthrough.'

7
00:00:52,996 --> 00:00:54,069
Hon?

8
00:00:54,267 --> 00:00:56,412
'Elsewhere...'
Ash.

9
00:00:56,452 --> 00:00:57,961
Ash!

10
00:01:02,688 --> 00:01:03,721
Can you take those?

11
00:01:06,065 --> 00:01:07,971
I snotted in yours, is that OK?

12
00:01:08,011 --> 00:01:10,491
Yeah... What?

13
00:01:10,531 --> 00:01:11,851
Palms - burning palms.

14
00:01:13,091 --> 00:01:14,691
Shit! Sorry.

15
00:01:23,691 --> 00:01:24,731
Glove box.

16
00:01:34,891 --> 00:01:37,251
♪ I don't want nobody, baby

17
00:01:37,291 --> 00:01:39,091
♪ If I can't have you

18
00:01:39,131 --> 00:01:41,531
♪ Oh oh oh, oh!

19
00:01:41,571 --> 00:01:46,211
♪ If I can't have you
I don't want nobody, baby

20
00:01:46,251 --> 00:01:50,291
♪ If I can't have you, oh oh oh, oh!

21
00:01:50,331 --> 00:01:53,851
♪ BEE GEES: Stayin' Alive

22
00:01:53,891 --> 00:01:56,251
Oh, no, you don't,
I draw the line at disco.

23
00:01:56,291 --> 00:01:58,211
What were we just listening to?

24
00:01:58,251 --> 00:02:01,428
No, the Bee Gees wrote that,
everybody likes the Bee Gees.

25
00:02:01,468 --> 00:02:03,097
You don't. I do.

26
00:02:03,136 --> 00:02:04,924
Ten years,
you haven't played them once.

27
00:02:04,963 --> 00:02:06,790
Have you heard of headphones?

28
00:02:06,870 --> 00:02:09,571
Come on then, what's your
favourite Bee Gees track?

29
00:02:09,610 --> 00:02:10,921
How Deep Is Your Love.

30
00:02:10,961 --> 00:02:13,105
You do not like
How Deep Is Your Love!

31
00:02:13,145 --> 00:02:15,091
It's perfectly natural,
there's nothing wrong with it.

32
00:02:15,131 --> 00:02:16,413
It's not very you.

33
00:02:18,055 --> 00:02:21,701
♪ I know your eyes
in the morning sun

34
00:02:21,741 --> 00:02:23,583
♪ I feel you touch me
in the pouring rain... ♪

35
00:02:23,623 --> 00:02:26,588
You're such a dick.

36
00:02:26,628 --> 00:02:29,832
♪ ..And the moment that you wander
far from me, I wanna feel you... ♪

37
00:02:29,873 --> 00:02:31,875
I will crash this van. I will.

38
00:02:31,916 --> 00:02:33,838
I will crash this van on purpose!

39
00:03:19,265 --> 00:03:20,266
Glove box.

40
00:03:34,647 --> 00:03:35,809
Soup all right?

41
00:03:35,849 --> 00:03:37,211
Yeah, great.

42
00:03:37,251 --> 00:03:38,691
Tomato or roasted tomato?

43
00:03:40,771 --> 00:03:42,531
The second one.

44
00:03:42,571 --> 00:03:47,371
There's only one bowl, do you mind
having yours out of a shoe?

45
00:03:47,411 --> 00:03:48,811
Mm-hm.

46
00:03:55,091 --> 00:03:57,651
What was that for?
Just checking you're still solid.

47
00:03:57,691 --> 00:03:59,531
You keep vanishing. Down there.

48
00:04:01,331 --> 00:04:03,331
It's a thief, that thing.
What are you doing?

49
00:04:03,371 --> 00:04:05,411
Just sharing that.

50
00:04:05,451 --> 00:04:07,491
I thought people might find
it funny.

51
00:04:12,531 --> 00:04:14,931
It's not funny. It's sweet.

52
00:04:14,971 --> 00:04:16,811
Trust me, that day wasn't sweet.

53
00:04:18,331 --> 00:04:23,571
We'd gone to a safari park.
First family outing after Jack died.

54
00:04:23,611 --> 00:04:27,691
There was monkeys all over the car
and no-one saying anything.

55
00:04:30,611 --> 00:04:35,771
Mum drove home, that was a first.
When I came down the next morning,

56
00:04:35,811 --> 00:04:38,331
all Jack's photos were gone from that
wall.

57
00:04:38,371 --> 00:04:40,331
She put them in the attic.

58
00:04:40,371 --> 00:04:42,891
That's how she dealt with stuff.

59
00:04:42,931 --> 00:04:45,331
And then when Dad died,
up went his photos.

60
00:04:46,731 --> 00:04:49,131
She just left this one here.

61
00:04:49,171 --> 00:04:51,811
Her only boy,
giving her a fake smile.

62
00:04:51,851 --> 00:04:53,251
She didn't know it was fake.

63
00:04:54,531 --> 00:04:56,091
Maybe that makes it worse.

64
00:05:04,491 --> 00:05:07,091
Oh... Oh, shit...

65
00:05:07,131 --> 00:05:08,851
Oh, shit...

66
00:05:14,051 --> 00:05:14,931
Sorry.

67
00:05:14,971 --> 00:05:16,091
It's OK.

68
00:05:19,811 --> 00:05:23,171
Do you want me to...? No, it's all right.

69
00:05:23,211 --> 00:05:24,931
I don't mind.

70
00:05:26,851 --> 00:05:28,891
I am knackered though... so...

71
00:05:31,891 --> 00:05:32,891
Don't worry.

72
00:05:33,931 --> 00:05:35,531
Sure?

73
00:05:35,571 --> 00:05:36,891
I'm sure.

74
00:05:39,371 --> 00:05:41,171
I love you. Love you too.

75
00:06:01,931 --> 00:06:03,091
Hey, get dressed.

76
00:06:03,131 --> 00:06:06,971
Van's got to be back by two or
they'll do us for an extra day.

77
00:06:07,011 --> 00:06:10,771
Job's just come in. Needs to be
done by the end of play today.

78
00:06:11,891 --> 00:06:13,451
All right.

79
00:06:13,491 --> 00:06:15,411
It is a full page.

80
00:06:15,451 --> 00:06:17,931
No, no, it's fine.

81
00:06:17,971 --> 00:06:22,771
I'll drive all the way there
alone...

82
00:06:23,931 --> 00:06:29,531
pick the car up alone...
drive all the way back alone...

83
00:06:29,571 --> 00:06:31,211
I have to make my own lunch...

84
00:06:31,251 --> 00:06:33,451
Oh, stop it,
you're breaking my heart.

85
00:06:36,571 --> 00:06:38,250
Bye-bye.

86
00:07:48,199 --> 00:07:50,518
'Hi, this is Ash. I'm too busy or
lazy to answer,

87
00:07:50,558 --> 00:07:52,236
'so leave your message.'

88
00:07:59,151 --> 00:08:01,150
'Do you have a customer
reference number?'

89
00:08:01,190 --> 00:08:05,587
I don't, no. I was just...

90
00:08:05,627 --> 00:08:08,664
'What name is it in?'

91
00:08:08,704 --> 00:08:12,102
Um... Starmer. Ash Starmer.

92
00:08:12,142 --> 00:08:13,821
'OK, just a moment.'

93
00:08:21,375 --> 00:08:24,133
'It's not been returned yet, no,

94
00:08:24,173 --> 00:08:27,171
'and it's meant to be back by two,
so...'

95
00:08:27,211 --> 00:08:29,172
They're closed now,
no point calling back,

96
00:08:29,212 --> 00:08:31,334
and his just goes straight to
messages.

97
00:08:31,374 --> 00:08:32,935
Those batteries are a joke.

98
00:08:32,975 --> 00:08:35,537
He'll be on his way.
He's probably just...

99
00:08:35,577 --> 00:08:37,699
I'm just scared something's
happened to him.

100
00:08:37,739 --> 00:08:38,859
Nothing's happened.

101
00:08:38,899 --> 00:08:40,461
But something could've happened.

102
00:08:40,501 --> 00:08:43,263
Look, sweetheart,
nothing's happened,

103
00:08:43,303 --> 00:08:46,265
you're just working yourself up,
imagining the worst possible thing,

104
00:08:46,305 --> 00:08:50,348
and it's just, he's probably
stuck somewhere with no reception.

105
00:09:22,571 --> 00:09:23,931
Hey. Hey.

106
00:09:27,571 --> 00:09:28,571
It's not real, is it?

107
00:09:31,171 --> 00:09:34,131
At Mark's wake,
I sat there thinking it's not real.

108
00:09:35,691 --> 00:09:39,251
The people didn't look real,
their voices weren't real.

109
00:09:39,291 --> 00:09:42,091
It's like you're out on a spacewalk
and no-one can...

110
00:09:42,131 --> 00:09:44,091
Sarah.

111
00:09:51,651 --> 00:09:54,051
I can sign you up to something that
helps.

112
00:09:57,011 --> 00:09:58,171
It helped me.

113
00:10:01,851 --> 00:10:03,771
It will let you speak to him.

114
00:10:03,811 --> 00:10:07,091
I know he's dead,
but it wouldn't work if he wasn't.

115
00:10:07,131 --> 00:10:09,931
And don't worry,
it's not some crazy spiritual thing.

116
00:10:09,971 --> 00:10:12,491
He was a heavy user,
he'd be perfect... Please shut up.

117
00:10:12,531 --> 00:10:14,771
I mean, it's still in beta,
but I've got an invite...

118
00:10:14,811 --> 00:10:15,811
Please shut up.

119
00:10:15,851 --> 00:10:17,051
You won't have to do anything,
I'll just sign you up...

120
00:10:17,091 --> 00:10:18,268
SHUT UP!

121
00:10:23,999 --> 00:10:25,255
Hey, are you all right?

122
00:10:25,451 --> 00:10:26,793
I'm sorry.

123
00:10:36,002 --> 00:10:37,270
DOOR CLOSES

124
00:11:21,191 --> 00:11:23,018
(RETCHES)

125
00:11:25,404 --> 00:11:26,970
(WHIMPERS)

126
00:11:50,459 --> 00:11:51,391
NEW MAIL ALERT

127
00:11:59,277 --> 00:12:00,916
I don't care what it is,
I don't want it!

128
00:12:00,957 --> 00:12:04,441
It's obscene to use his name.
His name, for God's sake!

129
00:12:04,482 --> 00:12:06,368
It hurts, you know it hurts.

130
00:12:06,409 --> 00:12:08,458
Which is why I signed you up.

131
00:12:08,499 --> 00:12:11,163
What is it? W-What is it?

132
00:12:11,204 --> 00:12:13,991
You click the link
and you talk to it.

133
00:12:14,032 --> 00:12:15,467
You talk to it?

134
00:12:15,508 --> 00:12:17,926
You type messages in, like an e-mail,

135
00:12:17,967 --> 00:12:20,508
and then it talks back to you,
just like he would.

136
00:12:20,549 --> 00:12:21,665
He's dead.

137
00:12:21,705 --> 00:12:23,459
It's software. It mimics him.

138
00:12:23,499 --> 00:12:25,612
You give it someone's name.

139
00:12:25,651 --> 00:12:29,080
It goes back and reads through all
the things they've ever said online,

140
00:12:29,120 --> 00:12:33,225
their Facebook updates,
their Tweets, anything public.

141
00:12:33,265 --> 00:12:36,773
I just gave it Ash's name.
The system did the rest.

142
00:12:36,813 --> 00:12:38,049
It's so clever.

143
00:12:38,089 --> 00:12:39,763
It's... sick. It's sick!

144
00:12:39,803 --> 00:12:43,351
Just say hello to it.
If you like it,

145
00:12:43,390 --> 00:12:46,739
you then give it access
to his private emails.

146
00:12:46,779 --> 00:12:49,529
The more it has, the more it's him.

147
00:12:49,569 --> 00:12:51,602
It won't be...

148
00:12:51,642 --> 00:12:54,522
No, it's not, but it helps.

149
00:13:30,522 --> 00:13:33,602
TINNY MUSIC PLAYS

150
00:13:39,442 --> 00:13:41,962
MUSIC PLAYS, MIXER WHIRRS

151
00:13:43,042 --> 00:13:44,842
PHONE VIBRATES

152
00:13:49,762 --> 00:13:54,007
Listen, Nay, it's me. Hi.
Uh, I really need to speak to you.

153
00:13:57,051 --> 00:14:01,136
Um, can you please call me
as soon as you get this?

154
00:16:21,302 --> 00:16:22,864
Hi!

155
00:16:22,904 --> 00:16:25,908
I'm so sorry. I just got your message.
What's wrong? what happened?

156
00:16:26,989 --> 00:16:27,990
'Mar?'

157
00:16:29,032 --> 00:16:30,473
Mar, are you OK?

158
00:16:30,513 --> 00:16:34,478
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine, I just, I
just... I had a bad one earlier.

159
00:16:34,518 --> 00:16:37,802
D'you want me to come and visit?
I'm going to come and visit.

160
00:16:37,842 --> 00:16:39,242
'No, it's OK, really, I'm...'

161
00:16:39,282 --> 00:16:40,682
Mar, you're upset.
I'm going to come and see you.

162
00:16:40,722 --> 00:16:43,602
No. No, don't.

163
00:16:43,642 --> 00:16:46,082
I'm OK. I promise you I'm OK.

164
00:16:47,642 --> 00:16:49,082
'I've got to go,
I've got a deadline.'

165
00:16:49,122 --> 00:16:50,762
Are you sure?

166
00:16:50,802 --> 00:16:54,242
It's a tight deadline, got to
be in by dawn, so... I'd better go.

167
00:16:54,282 --> 00:16:55,362
Well, if you have...

168
00:16:55,402 --> 00:16:56,402
Bye, Nay.

169
00:17:02,370 --> 00:17:05,035
Ước gì em nói chuyện được với anh.

170
00:17:05,248 --> 00:17:08,481
Thế em đang làm gì đây? Duh.

171
00:17:16,123 --> 00:17:18,896
Ý em là thật sự nói chuyện.

172
00:17:19,162 --> 00:17:21,224
Ta có thể nói chuyện.

173
00:17:26,283 --> 00:17:28,033
Bằng cách nào?

174
00:17:35,682 --> 00:17:38,562
Hello, I've locked myself
out of the house again.

175
00:17:43,362 --> 00:17:45,522
(LAUGHS) Wait, where are you going?

176
00:17:48,162 --> 00:17:51,002
Hello. I'm no good at birthday
presents.

177
00:17:51,042 --> 00:17:52,962
♪ I love you... ♪

178
00:17:56,096 --> 00:17:59,431
Yum. Anh sẽ gọi em khi anh sẵn sàng.

179
00:18:12,922 --> 00:18:13,962
(Hello?)

180
00:18:18,162 --> 00:18:19,082
'So...'

181
00:18:19,802 --> 00:18:21,882
'..how am I sounding?'

182
00:18:24,362 --> 00:18:25,515
'Hello?'

183
00:18:25,555 --> 00:18:29,095
Hello! You sound just like him.

184
00:18:30,209 --> 00:18:32,197
'Almost creepy isn't it?

185
00:18:32,237 --> 00:18:33,351
'I say creepy,

186
00:18:33,391 --> 00:18:37,328
'I mean, it's totally batshit crazy
I can even talk to you.

187
00:18:37,368 --> 00:18:40,391
'I mean, I don't even have a mouth.'

188
00:18:40,430 --> 00:18:44,288
That's... that's just...

189
00:18:44,328 --> 00:18:45,999
'Just what?'

190
00:18:47,232 --> 00:18:50,573
That's just the sort of thing
that he would say.

191
00:18:50,612 --> 00:18:52,879
'Well, that's why I said it.'

192
00:18:59,442 --> 00:19:01,490
I think I'm going mad.

193
00:19:01,530 --> 00:19:03,176
'I won't tell anyone if you don't.'

194
00:19:08,075 --> 00:19:09,801
'You're not crying, are you?'

195
00:19:09,842 --> 00:19:12,692
(SNIFFLES) Sorry.

196
00:19:12,733 --> 00:19:17,270
You always said that
I looked weird when I cried.

197
00:19:18,354 --> 00:19:23,132
'Did I?
I sound like a right sick fuck.'

198
00:19:23,172 --> 00:19:26,666
(LAUGHS) Yeah, you were. You were.

199
00:19:28,312 --> 00:19:30,721
'But in a good way?'

200
00:19:30,761 --> 00:19:35,419
Yeah. Yeah. In a good way.

201
00:19:41,522 --> 00:19:44,322
So I went in,
after all your persuasion,

202
00:19:44,362 --> 00:19:49,002
and then like straightaway I got a
spine of a sea anemone or something

203
00:19:49,042 --> 00:19:53,682
stuck in my foot, and you threw
a jeb thinking it was poisonous.

204
00:19:53,722 --> 00:19:55,722
'What's "threw a jeb"?'

205
00:19:55,762 --> 00:19:58,722
Oh, it's um, it's a phrase we had,
like throwing a fit.

206
00:19:58,762 --> 00:20:01,082
'Oh, OK, so I "threw a jeb".'

207
00:20:01,122 --> 00:20:04,602
Yeah, and you were looking
in a guidebook, trying to figure out

208
00:20:04,642 --> 00:20:07,042
if there were any poisonous
sea creatures in Greece,

209
00:20:07,082 --> 00:20:09,202
when this local guy
comes over and says,

210
00:20:09,242 --> 00:20:11,602
(FRENCH ACCENT) "My wife
knows what to do,

211
00:20:11,642 --> 00:20:15,322
"come back to my house." Although
he wasn't French, obviously.

212
00:20:17,682 --> 00:20:20,282
I used to hate
walking in the country.

213
00:20:20,322 --> 00:20:22,282
'You must be getting old.'

214
00:20:22,322 --> 00:20:23,882
Oi. (LAUGHS)

215
00:20:26,802 --> 00:20:29,922
I remember you brought me up here
when we first met your mum.

216
00:20:29,962 --> 00:20:31,522
We'd been at hers all weekend

217
00:20:31,562 --> 00:20:33,962
and you could tell
I needed some headspace.

218
00:20:35,722 --> 00:20:37,802
You were good like that.

219
00:20:37,842 --> 00:20:40,602
'You speak about me
like I'm not here.'

220
00:20:40,642 --> 00:20:41,922
Sorry.

221
00:20:41,962 --> 00:20:44,082
'It's all right.
I mean, I'm not, really.'

222
00:20:45,722 --> 00:20:46,722
Mm.

223
00:20:48,282 --> 00:20:50,202
'Show me what it looks like there.'

224
00:20:52,242 --> 00:20:53,402
How?

225
00:20:53,442 --> 00:20:55,322
'Use the camera on your phone.'

226
00:20:58,922 --> 00:21:01,162
You weren't ever really
impressed with views.

227
00:21:01,202 --> 00:21:04,202
When we went to the Grand Canyon,
you said it was just a big gap.

228
00:21:04,242 --> 00:21:05,642
'I Tweeted that, too.'

229
00:21:05,682 --> 00:21:08,082
Yeah, I remember
the roaming charges.

230
00:21:08,122 --> 00:21:10,202
You were overly proud
of that definition.

231
00:21:10,402 --> 00:21:12,122
'I was just speaking my mind.'

232
00:21:12,162 --> 00:21:14,962
Yeah, well shut up
and cop a load of this.

233
00:21:15,002 --> 00:21:16,922
'Yeah. Mainly just green, isn't it?'

234
00:21:18,522 --> 00:21:20,562
You told me this was
a famous lover's leap.

235
00:21:20,602 --> 00:21:23,362
Doomed couples jumping
to their deaths in Victorian times.

236
00:21:23,402 --> 00:21:26,562
I think you just wanted me
to cling to you.

237
00:21:26,602 --> 00:21:29,882
'Actually everyone who's ever jumped
from here did it alone. Nice.'

238
00:21:29,922 --> 00:21:31,482
Did you just look that up?

239
00:21:31,522 --> 00:21:33,402
'Sort of. Shouldn't I have?'

240
00:21:35,562 --> 00:21:37,442
It's a bit weird.

241
00:21:37,482 --> 00:21:41,002
'Sorry. I'll only do it again
if you ask.'

242
00:21:41,042 --> 00:21:42,650
No, no. No, it's fine.

243
00:21:47,152 --> 00:21:49,385
Oh, wait, hang on.

244
00:21:49,424 --> 00:21:50,541
'Shall I go?'

245
00:21:50,581 --> 00:21:53,451
No, no, no.
I'll call them back later.

246
00:22:03,457 --> 00:22:06,567
I'm going to go and see if I can
make friends with these cows.

247
00:22:17,530 --> 00:22:19,802
Just going to record it.

248
00:22:19,842 --> 00:22:21,198
Sure.

249
00:22:30,168 --> 00:22:32,520
There you go.

250
00:22:32,560 --> 00:22:34,712
It's OK.

251
00:22:37,104 --> 00:22:39,696
Wait, hang on, here it is again.

252
00:22:43,802 --> 00:22:45,168
'It's so fast, isn't it?'

253
00:22:45,208 --> 00:22:47,338
I know. I know,

254
00:22:47,378 --> 00:22:50,955
it's like the speed you'd expect
a bee's heart to go at or something.

255
00:22:50,995 --> 00:22:52,361
Wait, hang on.

256
00:22:55,134 --> 00:22:57,987
Oh, shit. Shit, shit.

257
00:23:01,041 --> 00:23:03,492
Ash? Hello?

258
00:23:03,532 --> 00:23:04,778
Ash?

259
00:23:07,952 --> 00:23:09,962
Ash? Hello?

260
00:23:18,802 --> 00:23:21,402
Oh, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.

261
00:23:30,562 --> 00:23:33,922
I'm sorry! (SOBS)

262
00:23:33,962 --> 00:23:35,882
'What happened?'

263
00:23:35,922 --> 00:23:40,162
I dropped you. I'm sorry. It was
just... It was... I'm sorry...

264
00:23:40,202 --> 00:23:43,722
'Hey, it's all right, I'm fine.
I'm not in that thing, you know,

265
00:23:43,762 --> 00:23:46,402
'I'm remote, I'm in the cloud.

266
00:23:46,442 --> 00:23:48,482
'You don't have to worry
about breaking me.'

267
00:23:48,522 --> 00:23:51,242
It was just, it was stupid, because
I was so excited about the scan.

268
00:23:51,282 --> 00:23:53,762
'Yeah, I kept the sound of that.
Here, listen.'

269
00:23:59,962 --> 00:24:04,482
'You were probably matching that
heartbeat, throwing a jeb like that.

270
00:24:04,522 --> 00:24:06,682
'It's all fine. Calm down.

271
00:24:06,722 --> 00:24:08,562
'I'm not going anywhere.'

272
00:24:13,842 --> 00:24:15,082
You're very fragile.

273
00:24:16,282 --> 00:24:19,642
'Yeah. I was going to
talk to you about that, actually.'

274
00:24:21,762 --> 00:24:22,882
What do you mean?

275
00:24:24,562 --> 00:24:27,562
'There's another level to this
available, so to speak.

276
00:24:28,962 --> 00:24:31,402
'Kind of experimental,
and I won't lie, it's not cheap...'

277
00:24:31,442 --> 00:24:33,002
What is it?

278
00:24:33,042 --> 00:24:34,930
'Are you sitting down?
This might sound a bit creepy.'

279
00:24:45,119 --> 00:24:47,162
Morning.
Morning.

280
00:24:47,202 --> 00:24:48,725
What's this, a block of gold?

281
00:24:48,765 --> 00:24:50,007
I wish.

282
00:24:50,047 --> 00:24:51,209
Where's it going, upstairs?

283
00:24:51,249 --> 00:24:52,771
Yeah, please.

284
00:24:52,811 --> 00:24:54,614
Put your thumb on there.

285
00:24:54,654 --> 00:24:55,936
OK.

286
00:24:57,098 --> 00:25:00,543
Oh, when you get it up there,
you have to lie it on its back.

287
00:25:00,583 --> 00:25:01,905
Thank you.

288
00:25:44,292 --> 00:25:45,852
Say something.

289
00:25:45,892 --> 00:25:47,492
VOICE FROM PHONE: Let me see.

290
00:26:01,052 --> 00:26:03,892
Yeah, well.
Never was much of a looker, was I?

291
00:26:07,492 --> 00:26:09,612
It doesn't look like you.

292
00:26:09,652 --> 00:26:12,452
Not yet.
It's blank till you activate it.

293
00:26:15,372 --> 00:26:16,772
Get the bath ready.

294
00:26:30,572 --> 00:26:32,772
Mar? Get the bath ready.

295
00:26:43,852 --> 00:26:45,172
What is this?

296
00:26:45,212 --> 00:26:47,132
Hang on, I'll find out.

297
00:26:47,172 --> 00:26:49,132
It's nutrient gel.

298
00:26:49,172 --> 00:26:51,572
Stops the synthetic muscle
drying out in transit.

299
00:26:52,892 --> 00:26:54,972
Smells almost...

300
00:26:55,012 --> 00:26:57,252
like marshmallow.

301
00:26:57,292 --> 00:27:00,652
You can eat it if you like.
It's non-toxic.

302
00:27:00,692 --> 00:27:03,132
I'll give that a miss, thanks.

303
00:27:03,172 --> 00:27:04,892
Don't forget the electrolytes.

304
00:27:09,892 --> 00:27:12,012
OK, right - the whole lot?

305
00:27:12,052 --> 00:27:13,612
Mm-hm, the whole lot.

306
00:27:18,012 --> 00:27:20,396
It's like fish food.

307
00:27:20,436 --> 00:27:22,383
He likes the taste of it.

308
00:27:24,887 --> 00:27:26,794
Better leave him to it.

309
00:27:26,834 --> 00:27:28,622
Yeah. Yeah.

310
00:27:32,477 --> 00:27:34,305
I have to go in a minute.

311
00:27:34,345 --> 00:27:36,292
Oh, don't leave me here with it!

312
00:27:36,332 --> 00:27:39,051
Sorry. Look, you can hear -
it's starting already.

313
00:27:39,091 --> 00:27:42,690
(AUDIO BREAKS UP) Don't switch
the bathroom light on.

314
00:27:42,730 --> 00:27:44,250
Don't what?

315
00:27:44,290 --> 00:27:46,409
Don't switch the bathroom light on.

316
00:27:46,569 --> 00:27:48,768
(PHONE LINE CRACKLES) Let it brew.

317
00:27:48,808 --> 00:27:50,168
Listen, I've got to go...

318
00:28:10,362 --> 00:28:13,081
SPLASHING AND BUBBLING

319
00:28:25,158 --> 00:28:27,117
♪ And it's all right

320
00:28:27,157 --> 00:28:28,637
♪ It's coming on

321
00:28:28,677 --> 00:28:32,516
♪ We got to get right back to
where we started... ♪

322
00:29:00,987 --> 00:29:03,267
DOOR OPENS

323
00:29:24,700 --> 00:29:26,620
You could've left me some clothes.

324
00:29:29,179 --> 00:29:32,618
I mean, talk about an undignified
entrance.

325
00:29:41,096 --> 00:29:44,215
That's a bit creepy.
What you're doing.

326
00:29:47,334 --> 00:29:50,373
Is there at least a towel?
I'm dripping everywhere.

327
00:29:53,412 --> 00:29:54,575
Hello?

328
00:29:59,148 --> 00:30:00,592
I won't bite.

329
00:30:04,964 --> 00:30:07,290
I'm all right here for now.

330
00:30:10,138 --> 00:30:13,508
Would you like me
to put some food on?

331
00:30:13,548 --> 00:30:15,152
Do you eat?

332
00:30:15,192 --> 00:30:16,395
No.

333
00:30:16,436 --> 00:30:17,920
I mean, I don't need to.

334
00:30:17,960 --> 00:30:20,607
I can chew and swallow,
if that makes it easier?

335
00:30:20,647 --> 00:30:22,853
Don't worry about it, it's fine.

336
00:30:29,432 --> 00:30:31,156
I need a drink.

337
00:30:48,043 --> 00:30:49,286
Are you sure that's...?

338
00:30:49,326 --> 00:30:51,292
I know, I'm not supposed to.
It won't kill us.

339
00:30:51,332 --> 00:30:52,571
The official advice is...

340
00:30:52,611 --> 00:30:55,369
Fuck the official advice.
It's one night.

341
00:30:57,288 --> 00:30:59,007
You look well.

342
00:30:59,047 --> 00:31:01,006
Well, I am young.

343
00:31:01,046 --> 00:31:05,723
I mean... You look like him
on a good day.

344
00:31:05,763 --> 00:31:08,721
The photos we keep
tend to be flattering.

345
00:31:08,761 --> 00:31:10,640
I guess I wasn't any different.

346
00:31:27,269 --> 00:31:28,508
You're so soft.

347
00:31:30,027 --> 00:31:32,546
You're so smooth.
How are you so smooth?

348
00:31:35,504 --> 00:31:37,502
You've got pores and lines...

349
00:31:38,941 --> 00:31:40,740
It's texture-mapping.

350
00:31:42,099 --> 00:31:45,737
The really tiny details
are visual - 2D.

351
00:31:45,777 --> 00:31:48,255
Here, try my fingertips.

352
00:31:53,692 --> 00:31:55,573
See?

353
00:31:55,613 --> 00:31:57,293
Weird.

354
00:31:57,333 --> 00:31:59,574
Does it bother you?

355
00:31:59,614 --> 00:32:00,815
No.

356
00:32:02,936 --> 00:32:04,376
Yeah.

357
00:32:06,937 --> 00:32:08,298
(WHISPERS) I don't know.

358
00:32:17,862 --> 00:32:21,183
I missed you. I missed you so much!

359
00:32:22,384 --> 00:32:24,744
Hey, don't cry.

360
00:32:24,784 --> 00:32:26,545
Don't cry.

361
00:32:42,432 --> 00:32:44,192
Come on then. Top off.

362
00:32:58,838 --> 00:33:00,079
What's wrong?

363
00:33:00,119 --> 00:33:01,919
He had a mole there.

364
00:33:01,959 --> 00:33:03,320
Where?

365
00:33:07,802 --> 00:33:09,442
There.

366
00:33:09,482 --> 00:33:11,003
Hang on.

367
00:33:15,165 --> 00:33:16,485
That's ridiculous.

368
00:33:17,726 --> 00:33:19,767
That's completely stupid.

369
00:33:33,412 --> 00:33:34,652
Hello?

370
00:33:34,692 --> 00:33:35,932
Hi.

371
00:33:35,972 --> 00:33:37,372
Your hand's on my tit.

372
00:33:45,412 --> 00:33:47,692
You're doing wonders
for my self-esteem here.

373
00:33:47,732 --> 00:33:50,572
There's no record of my sexual
response.

374
00:33:50,612 --> 00:33:52,892
I didn't discuss
that side of things online.

375
00:33:52,932 --> 00:33:55,492
But you have sexual responses.
I mean...

376
00:33:57,572 --> 00:33:59,652
This works?

377
00:33:59,692 --> 00:34:01,052
Oh.

378
00:34:01,092 --> 00:34:04,092
That, I can turn that on and off
pretty much instantly.

379
00:34:05,532 --> 00:34:06,812
See?

380
00:34:13,692 --> 00:34:15,612
I can do it again if you like.

381
00:34:26,972 --> 00:34:29,532
Oh, oh, God. Oh, shit.

382
00:34:29,572 --> 00:34:30,972
Should I stop?

383
00:34:31,012 --> 00:34:32,823
No! No, it's really good.

384
00:34:35,319 --> 00:34:38,459
Where... Where did you learn this?

385
00:34:38,499 --> 00:34:41,075
Set routine.
Based on pornographic videos.

386
00:34:46,107 --> 00:34:48,120
(SHE GROANS)

387
00:35:04,865 --> 00:35:07,079
I love you.

388
00:35:07,119 --> 00:35:08,276
I love you.

389
00:35:16,379 --> 00:35:18,145
BIRDS TWITTER

390
00:35:21,740 --> 00:35:23,110
(MOANS)

391
00:35:26,278 --> 00:35:27,513
What is it?

392
00:35:27,553 --> 00:35:28,709
What were you doing?

393
00:35:28,749 --> 00:35:29,864
Nothing.

394
00:35:29,904 --> 00:35:32,574
The way that your eyes were open,
it scared me.

395
00:35:32,614 --> 00:35:34,089
You'd prefer if I closed them?

396
00:35:34,128 --> 00:35:36,719
What, when you're sleeping?
Um, yeah?

397
00:35:39,269 --> 00:35:40,823
I don't really need to sleep.

398
00:35:42,138 --> 00:35:44,689
Well, just try, next time.

399
00:35:57,600 --> 00:35:59,513
Can I get you anything?

400
00:35:59,553 --> 00:36:00,987
No.

401
00:36:01,027 --> 00:36:02,541
Coffee, sandwich?

402
00:36:02,581 --> 00:36:03,577
I said no.

403
00:36:05,052 --> 00:36:06,566
Ash.

404
00:36:06,606 --> 00:36:07,731
Look, sorry.

405
00:36:10,062 --> 00:36:12,472
It's just a bit odd.

406
00:36:12,513 --> 00:36:15,566
I can appreciate
it's pretty strange.

407
00:36:15,607 --> 00:36:18,138
I just need a bit of, just,
getting used to it.

408
00:36:18,178 --> 00:36:20,468
And I shouldn't have drunk
last night.

409
00:36:20,509 --> 00:36:22,196
Next time could you try and stop me?

410
00:36:22,236 --> 00:36:23,281
Stop you drinking?

411
00:36:23,321 --> 00:36:24,326
Yeah.

412
00:36:24,366 --> 00:36:26,606
So I get to enjoy being
a bit of a bastard?

413
00:36:26,646 --> 00:36:28,086
(WEAK LAUGH)

414
00:36:28,126 --> 00:36:30,246
CAR PULLS UP OUTSIDE

415
00:36:30,286 --> 00:36:31,602
What's wrong?

416
00:36:34,752 --> 00:36:36,905
Oh, God. Shit, right,
get in the bedroom.

417
00:36:36,945 --> 00:36:38,859
What?
Now!

418
00:36:45,040 --> 00:36:46,077
Hey.

419
00:36:46,117 --> 00:36:47,353
Hey!

420
00:36:51,779 --> 00:36:53,573
Can I come in?

421
00:36:53,613 --> 00:36:54,969
Yeah, yeah.

422
00:36:59,116 --> 00:37:00,472
Look at you.

423
00:37:01,828 --> 00:37:04,340
The town mouse has become
the country mouse.

424
00:37:05,735 --> 00:37:07,570
Yeah, it's nice.

425
00:37:07,610 --> 00:37:09,005
Was this all you?

426
00:37:12,674 --> 00:37:14,349
Do you want a cup of coffee?

427
00:37:14,389 --> 00:37:15,824
Yeah.

428
00:37:18,655 --> 00:37:20,290
You weren't answering calls.

429
00:37:20,330 --> 00:37:21,247
It's been...

430
00:37:21,287 --> 00:37:22,772
Or messages.
Really busy.

431
00:37:22,813 --> 00:37:25,583
I've just been a bit like "Oh,
shit," you know, "What's...?"

432
00:37:25,623 --> 00:37:28,995
Yeah. Work's been mad, it's been...

433
00:37:29,035 --> 00:37:30,721
Which is good, you know, obviously,

434
00:37:30,761 --> 00:37:33,451
because it's kept my mind
off everything, so...

435
00:37:36,622 --> 00:37:38,469
Where's the toilet?

436
00:37:38,509 --> 00:37:39,794
Upstairs.

437
00:37:39,995 --> 00:37:40,998
OK.

438
00:37:49,268 --> 00:37:52,119
So, I mean, um... Yeah, let's, er...

439
00:37:54,728 --> 00:37:57,418
Meet up more, yes.
Keep in touch yeah, yeah.

440
00:37:57,458 --> 00:37:58,783
Yeah.

441
00:37:58,823 --> 00:37:59,907
Come here.

442
00:38:02,115 --> 00:38:04,042
I think it's great you're moving on.

443
00:38:05,246 --> 00:38:06,246
What?

444
00:38:06,286 --> 00:38:09,486
Sorry. There were...
There were man clothes, you know.

445
00:38:09,526 --> 00:38:11,326
In the bathroom.

446
00:38:11,366 --> 00:38:12,566
Right.

447
00:38:14,206 --> 00:38:15,486
Is he nice?

448
00:38:18,126 --> 00:38:19,966
Sorry. Big nose. You know.

449
00:38:22,446 --> 00:38:24,166
You deserve whatever you want.

450
00:38:26,086 --> 00:38:27,846
Thanks.

451
00:38:27,886 --> 00:38:28,446
All right.

452
00:38:28,486 --> 00:38:30,006
OK. All right.

453
00:38:31,686 --> 00:38:33,406
CAR LOCK BEEPS

454
00:38:44,926 --> 00:38:46,886
Hey.

455
00:38:46,926 --> 00:38:49,006
Is everything all right?

456
00:38:49,046 --> 00:38:50,806
Yeah, I'm fine. It's fine.

457
00:38:54,326 --> 00:38:56,244
What did your friend say?

458
00:38:59,080 --> 00:39:01,197
That was my sister.

459
00:39:01,237 --> 00:39:02,436
You know her.

460
00:39:04,154 --> 00:39:05,592
She said that I was...

461
00:39:06,710 --> 00:39:09,187
She said that she was happy
that I'd moved on.

462
00:39:10,905 --> 00:39:12,303
Moved on to what?

463
00:39:15,180 --> 00:39:17,896
Is that not the sort of
thing I'd say?

464
00:39:17,936 --> 00:39:19,894
I mean...

465
00:39:19,934 --> 00:39:21,372
It is, isn't it?

466
00:39:22,770 --> 00:39:24,528
Are you sure everything's all right?

467
00:39:24,568 --> 00:39:26,166
Yes!

468
00:39:26,206 --> 00:39:27,487
Shit!

469
00:39:31,288 --> 00:39:33,930
It's OK, I can do it. I can do it.

470
00:39:33,970 --> 00:39:35,570
I can do it.

471
00:39:35,610 --> 00:39:36,851
Don't!

472
00:39:56,540 --> 00:39:58,341
We need to wrap that in paper.

473
00:40:09,986 --> 00:40:12,147
Look, if you're going
to pretend to be asleep,

474
00:40:12,187 --> 00:40:13,988
you could at least breathe, OK?

475
00:40:15,509 --> 00:40:16,910
It's just eerie.

476
00:40:19,151 --> 00:40:20,711
Like this?

477
00:40:23,513 --> 00:40:27,194
(INHALES, EXHALES)

478
00:40:34,678 --> 00:40:37,239
It doesn't work.
I can tell that you're faking it.

479
00:40:39,320 --> 00:40:41,361
Would you like me
to have sex with you?

480
00:40:42,962 --> 00:40:44,482
Can you just go downstairs?

481
00:40:47,244 --> 00:40:48,524
OK.

482
00:40:52,486 --> 00:40:54,046
No! That's...

483
00:40:54,086 --> 00:40:55,606
Ash would argue over that.

484
00:40:55,646 --> 00:40:57,886
He wouldn't just leave
because I'd ordered him to.

485
00:40:57,926 --> 00:40:59,686
OK.

486
00:41:00,726 --> 00:41:01,966
What? N...

487
00:41:02,006 --> 00:41:04,366
Ah, fucking hell!

488
00:41:07,486 --> 00:41:08,686
Don't cry, darling.

489
00:41:08,726 --> 00:41:11,046
Oh, don't! Just get out!
Get out!

490
00:41:13,446 --> 00:41:14,686
Go on!

491
00:41:15,966 --> 00:41:17,326
So you do want me to go?

492
00:41:17,366 --> 00:41:20,446
Just get out! Get out! Get out!

493
00:41:20,486 --> 00:41:22,246
Get out! Get out! Get out!

494
00:41:22,446 --> 00:41:26,126
You're not enough of him!
You are nothing! You're nothing.

495
00:41:28,206 --> 00:41:29,206
Fight me.

496
00:41:29,246 --> 00:41:30,246
I don't do that.

497
00:41:30,286 --> 00:41:32,446
Fucking fight me! Hit me.

498
00:41:32,486 --> 00:41:35,486
Hit me. Hit me. Come on!

499
00:41:35,526 --> 00:41:37,806
Why are you just standing
there taking this?

500
00:41:37,846 --> 00:41:40,126
How can you take this?

501
00:41:40,166 --> 00:41:41,566
Did I ever hit you?

502
00:41:41,606 --> 00:41:44,926
N... No, of course you didn't

503
00:41:44,966 --> 00:41:48,366
but you might've done if I done this.
Or this.

504
00:41:48,406 --> 00:41:49,726
I don't... I don't know.

505
00:41:49,766 --> 00:41:54,086
Maybe you would have. But you
wouldn't, would you? You wouldn't.

506
00:41:54,126 --> 00:41:56,206
I could insult you.

507
00:41:56,246 --> 00:41:57,483
What?

508
00:41:57,523 --> 00:41:59,439
There's tons of invective
in the archive.

509
00:41:59,479 --> 00:42:02,912
I like speaking my mind,
I could throw some of that at you.

510
00:42:02,952 --> 00:42:04,589
Get out of this house.

511
00:42:28,978 --> 00:42:31,013
(SIGHS)

512
00:42:36,123 --> 00:42:37,280
What are you doing?

513
00:42:38,837 --> 00:42:42,110
I can't go more than 25 metres
from my activation point.

514
00:42:42,150 --> 00:42:43,627
What is that, a joke?

515
00:42:43,667 --> 00:42:45,264
Look, I know it sounds mental.

516
00:42:46,781 --> 00:42:48,657
Where's your activation point?

517
00:42:48,697 --> 00:42:51,451
At the risk of blowing your mind...

518
00:42:51,491 --> 00:42:53,566
it's where I was activated.

519
00:42:53,726 --> 00:42:54,608
The bath.

520
00:42:54,649 --> 00:42:58,178
I have to keep within a 25-metre
radius unless my administrator -

521
00:42:58,219 --> 00:43:00,625
that's you - is with me.

522
00:43:00,665 --> 00:43:02,350
Don't call me your administrator.

523
00:43:02,390 --> 00:43:04,275
Why not?

524
00:43:04,316 --> 00:43:05,198
Because...

525
00:43:05,238 --> 00:43:06,963
It sounds sort of sexy.

526
00:43:07,003 --> 00:43:08,648
(LAUGHS)

527
00:43:08,688 --> 00:43:10,734
If you're laughing,
can I come back inside?

528
00:43:11,977 --> 00:43:14,223
Feeling a bit...

529
00:43:14,263 --> 00:43:16,349
ornamental out here.

530
00:43:24,733 --> 00:43:28,062
SHOWER WATER RUNNING

531
00:43:33,517 --> 00:43:34,600
Funny.

532
00:43:36,646 --> 00:43:38,086
Can you put that down, please?

533
00:43:38,126 --> 00:43:39,246
But it is funny.

534
00:43:39,286 --> 00:43:41,166
Could you just put it down?

535
00:43:48,726 --> 00:43:50,326
Come with me. We're going out.

536
00:43:58,886 --> 00:44:02,646
♪ THE BEE GEES:
How Deep Is Your Love

537
00:44:04,206 --> 00:44:05,686
Cheesy.

538
00:44:20,046 --> 00:44:21,326
Come on.

539
00:44:21,366 --> 00:44:23,206
Where are we going?

540
00:44:23,246 --> 00:44:24,606
Just hurry up.

541
00:44:30,806 --> 00:44:33,966
SEAGULLS SQUAWK

542
00:44:39,006 --> 00:44:40,846
NO!

543
00:44:40,886 --> 00:44:42,646
DON'T DO IT!

544
00:44:47,566 --> 00:44:49,326
Seriously, don't do it.

545
00:44:49,366 --> 00:44:51,166
I'm not going to.

546
00:44:51,206 --> 00:44:52,486
OK.

547
00:44:54,606 --> 00:44:57,606
See, he would have worked out
what was going on.

548
00:44:57,646 --> 00:45:00,726
This wouldn't have ever happened,
but if it had, he would have

549
00:45:00,766 --> 00:45:01,726
worked it out.

550
00:45:01,766 --> 00:45:04,886
Sorry, hang on. That's a very
difficult sentence to process.

551
00:45:06,286 --> 00:45:08,046
Jump.

552
00:45:08,086 --> 00:45:09,526
What? Over there?

553
00:45:11,166 --> 00:45:14,206
I never expressed suicidal thoughts,
or self-harm.

554
00:45:14,246 --> 00:45:16,766
Yeah, well, you aren't you, are you?

555
00:45:16,806 --> 00:45:19,406
That's another difficult one,
to be honest with you.

556
00:45:19,446 --> 00:45:23,006
You're just a few ripples of you.
There's no history to you.

557
00:45:23,046 --> 00:45:26,886
You're just a performance of stuff
that he performed without thinking,

558
00:45:26,926 --> 00:45:28,286
and it's not enough.

559
00:45:28,326 --> 00:45:29,926
Come on. I aim to please.

560
00:45:29,966 --> 00:45:32,486
Aim to jump. Just do it.

561
00:45:32,526 --> 00:45:34,406
OK.

562
00:45:34,446 --> 00:45:36,046
If you're absolutely sure.

563
00:45:38,086 --> 00:45:39,486
See, Ash would've been scared.

564
00:45:39,526 --> 00:45:42,206
He wouldn't have just leapt off,
he would have been crying,

565
00:45:42,246 --> 00:45:43,126
he would have been...

566
00:45:43,166 --> 00:45:44,446
Oh.

567
00:45:46,166 --> 00:45:49,446
Oh... Oh, God, no.

568
00:45:49,486 --> 00:45:51,046
Please, I don't want to do it.

569
00:45:52,286 --> 00:45:53,606
Please don't make me do it.

570
00:45:53,646 --> 00:45:54,966
No. That's not fair.

571
00:45:55,006 --> 00:45:58,566
No, I'm... I'm frightened, darling,
please...

572
00:45:58,606 --> 00:45:59,766
Don't make me.

573
00:45:59,806 --> 00:46:02,366
I don't want to die.
Oh, God, I don't want to die

574
00:46:02,406 --> 00:46:03,406
No, that's not fair.

575
00:46:03,446 --> 00:46:05,606
I'm frightened, I don't want to die.
Don't...

576
00:46:05,646 --> 00:46:07,526
NO!!!!

577
00:46:26,046 --> 00:46:28,166
One for you, one for me.

578
00:46:30,126 --> 00:46:31,166
What?

579
00:46:31,206 --> 00:46:33,246
We need another slice.

580
00:46:33,286 --> 00:46:34,526
Why?

581
00:46:34,566 --> 00:46:36,286
So I can take one upstairs.

582
00:46:37,486 --> 00:46:39,126
It's not the weekend.

583
00:46:39,166 --> 00:46:40,606
It is my birthday.

584
00:46:42,966 --> 00:46:44,286
OK.

585
00:46:51,246 --> 00:46:52,966
"Thanks, Mum."

586
00:46:58,846 --> 00:47:00,006
Hey, Ash.

587
00:47:00,046 --> 00:47:02,566
Hey. The birthday girl.

588
00:47:02,606 --> 00:47:04,926
Just gonna come and hang out
for a bit.

589
00:47:04,966 --> 00:47:07,686
OK. I wasn't doing anything.

590
00:47:07,726 --> 00:47:09,486
I brought you some cake.

591
00:47:09,526 --> 00:47:11,046
I know you don't eat anything.

592
00:47:11,086 --> 00:47:14,726
I'm just using you as an excuse
so I can get an extra slice.

593
00:47:14,766 --> 00:47:16,246
Devious.

594
00:47:16,286 --> 00:47:17,446
Mum?

595
00:47:17,486 --> 00:47:18,766
Mum!

596
00:47:21,366 --> 00:47:22,806
Yeah, I'm just coming.

597
00:47:44,926 --> 00:47:49,926
Subtitles ReSynced by DeeJayAhmed
www.DeeJayAhmed.com

598
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


599
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


600
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


601
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


602
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


603
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


604
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


605
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


606
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


607
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


