( theme music playing )
- ( footsteps )
- ( bird cawing )
- We shouldn't
be out here alone.
- Why not?
- If your father--
- He'll never know
we're gone.
But if he finds out...
You don't need
to be afraid of my father.
( insects buzzing )
Are you sure?
Yes.
- We shouldn't go in.
- Of course we should.
( insects buzzing )
- ( screeches )
- ( shrieks, gasps )
Get out.
Get out!
- Let's go.
- No.
Listen to your friend.
They said that you
were terrifying
with cat's teeth
and three eyes.
You're not terrifying.
You're boring.
You don't know
what I am.
I know you're a witch
and you can see the future.
Tell me mine.
Everyone wants
to know their future
until they know
their future.
This is my father's land.
My land.
Tell me my future
or I'll have your
two boring eyes
gouged out of your head.
( chuckles )
Your blood.
Give me a taste.
( whimpers )
Three questions you get.
You won't like
the answers.
I've been promised
to the prince.
When will we marry?
You will never
wed the prince.
You will wed the king.
But I will be queen?
Oh, yes.
You'll be queen.
For a time.
Then comes another,
younger,
more beautiful,
to cast you down
and take all you
hold dear.
W-will the king and I
have children?
No. The king
will have 20 children
and you will have three.
That doesn't make sense.
Gold will be their crowns.
Gold their shrouds.
( laughs )
Girl:
Come on,
we have to go.
( laughter echoes )
We have to go!
Cersei!
( litter creaking )
Man:
Bearers, put it down.
- ( thuds )
- ( creaking stops )
- ( door opens )
- ( bell tolling )
Man:
Bearers, up.
Away.
( bell continues tolling )
High Septon:
Your Grace, we are
honored by your presence.
The mourners are waiting.
They will keep waiting.
I want a moment
alone with him.
But, Your Grace,
many of these lords
and ladies have travelled
day and night
to be here from
all seven kingdoms.
They will wait.
( door closes )
( footsteps echoing )
He never wanted you
to be a Kingsguard,
but here you are,
protecting his dead body.
What he built, it's ours.
He built it for us.
He meant it for us.
They're going to try
to take it away.
- All of it.
- They?
All of them out there,
our enemies.
They're waiting
in line to make sure
he's really dead.
And as soon as they see
the stones on his eyes,
they'll set to work
on tearing us apart.
They have nothing
to do with it.
The man who
murdered our father,
he tore us apart.
He's the enemy.
I've been telling
you for years.
You've been defending
him for years.
This is exactly
what they want.
And now our father
is dead
and that little monster
is out there somewhere
drawing breath.
Did you set him free?
Tyrion may be a monster,
but at least he killed
our father on purpose.
You killed him
by mistake.
With stupidity.
You're a man
of action, aren't you?
When it occurs to you
to do something, you do it.
Never mind
the consequences.
Take a look.
Look at the consequences.
Here they are.
He loved you more than
anyone in this world.
( waves crashing )
- ( bell dinging )
- ( seagulls screeching )
( chattering, laughing )
( heavy breathing )
( distant dog barking )
( birds chirping )
- ( thuds, wood creaking )
- ( heavy breathing )
( grunts )
( groaning )
Apologies.
I still don't see
why I had to stay
in this fucking crate
once we set sail.
I saved your life.
If they catch you,
they catch me.
I cannot say
I feel overly guilty
about leaving you
in that fucking crate.
Do you know what it's like
to stuff your shit
through one
of those airholes?
No, I only know
what it's like
to pick up your shit
and throw it overboard.
Pentos?
The home
of my colleague
Illyrio Mopatis,
a merchant.
He and I met
many years ago
through mutual friends.
A group of people
who saw Robert Baratheon
for the disaster he was.
We tried to do what
was best for the realm
by supporting
a Targaryen restoration.
And thus began
the chain of mistakes
that has led us
both here.
Things have
gotten worse,
not better.
Westeros needs to be
saved from itself.
Mmm.
Much better.
My lord?
I don't think
I am anymore.
A lord.
Are you a lord
if you kill your father?
I don't imagine
they revoke your nobility
for killing a whore.
It must happen
all the time.
You already drank yourself
across the Narrow Sea.
In a box.
Why stop now?
Because we are talking
about the future
of our country.
The future is shit.
Just like the past.
( wine pouring )
( men shouting )
( creaking )
- ( dog barking )
- ( chatter )
( woman moaning )
( speaking Valyrian )
Shh.
( humming )
( gurgling )
( gasping )
Daenerys:
The Sons of the Harpy?
Yes, Your Grace.
They left it on the body.
They've never
killed before.
It was only a matter
of time, Your Grace.
Conquerors always meet
with resistance.
I didn't conquer them.
Their own people did.
( speaking Valyrian )
He did not risk his life
fighting for his freedom
so cowards in masks
could take it away.
And I did not take up
residence in this pyramid
so I could
watch the city below
decline into chaos.
What was the name
of the man you lost?
White Rat,
Your Grace.
I want him buried
with honor, publically
in the Temple
of the Graces.
The Sons of the Harpy
will hear that message.
Make them very angry.
Angry snakes lash out.
Makes chopping
off their heads
that much easier.
Find the men who did this
and bring them to me.
Your Grace.
Torgo Nudho.
Missandei hin Naath.
I wanted
to speak with you.
Why do you come?
White Rat,
the Unsullied who...
I have heard they found
his body in a brothel.
I have heard that
more than one Unsullied
has been known to visit
Meereen's brothels.
May I ask you why?
Why would an Unsullied
go to a brothel?
I do not know.
I must go.
( shouts, grunting )
- Get your shield up.
- It's too heavy.
If it wasn't heavy,
it wouldn't stop a sword.
Now get it up.
Come.
Try it again.
Drive at me.
Keep your shield up.
Or I'll ring
your head like a bell.
Shouldn't you
be training, too?
Well, I'm hardly
a new recruit.
How many brothers
can say that they've killed
a white walker and a Thenn?
I might be the first
in history.
- Man: Shield up.
- Alliser: These men
need a firm hand.
Always have.
They're poachers
and thieves.
Not soldiers.
That one hates me.
Sam: If Ser Alliser
is chosen as the new
Lord Commander...
- He hates the wildlings.
- ( baby fussing )
All the wildlings.
- Don't let them send us away.
- It's not a sure thing.
Ser Denys Mallister
has commanded the Shadow
Tower for 20 years
and people say
he's a good man.
He's running against
Ser Alliser--
Sam, don't let them
send us away.
I told you.
Wherever you go,
I go, too.
You can't leave.
They'll execute you.
- Good, good, pivot.
Don't forget to pivot.
- Yah!
Shield up.
The king wants a word.
( chains rattling )
( wind howling )
You're not cold,
my lady?
Never.
The Lord's fire lives
within me, Jon Snow.
Feel.
Are you a virgin?
No.
Good.
Your Grace.
The bastard
of Winterfell.
You know who rules
at Winterfell now?
Roose Bolton.
Mmm, the traitor
who plunged a dagger
in Robb Stark's heart.
Don't you want
to avenge him?
I want a great
many things, Your Grace.
But I'm a sworn brother
of the Night's Watch now.
I've been talking
to your sworn brothers.
- Many of them love you.
- They're good men.
Many don't.
You were seen taking
the body of a wildling
girl north of the Wall.
Why?
It's where she belonged.
Some of the Night's
Watch feel you have
too much affection
for the wildlings.
They were born
on the wrong side
of the Wall.
That doesn't
make them monsters.
No matter.
I shall take back
the North
from the thieves
who stole it.
Tywin Lannister is dead.
He can't protect them now.
I shall mount
Roose Bolton's head
on a spike.
But if
I'm to take Winterfell,
I need more men.
The men of the Night's Watch
are sworn to play no part--
I'm not talking about
the damn Night's Watch.
I'm talking about
the wildlings.
Your Grace,
you want the wildlings
to march in your army?
If they swear
to follow me,
I'll pardon them.
We'll take Winterfell.
Once the North is won,
I'll declare them
citizens of the realm.
I'll give them
land to live on.
It's a fair offer.
More than fair.
I'll offer them their lives
and their freedom
if Mance kneels before me
and swears his loyalty.
I don't think
that's likely.
You admire him,
don't you?
- I respect him.
- He likes you.
- Convince him
to bend the knee...
- Your Grace.
...or he burns.
How much time
do I have?
Nightfall.
The sun drops fast
this time of year.
Hurry, Jon Snow.
( boys grunting )
Master-of-arms:
Shield up.
- ( Robin whimpers )
- Master-of-arms: Attack,
my lord!
Attack!
- Don't cross your feet.
- ( grunts )
My sons had swords
in their hands
from the time
they could walk.
This one...
Littlefinger:
Lord Arryn will never
be a great warrior.
Royce:
Great warrior?
He swings a sword
like a girl with palsy.
My lord.
Master-of-arms:
Sword up, my lord!
( Robin whimpering,
gasping )
Some boys develop
more slowly.
He's still young.
He's 13.
Boys go to war at 13.
- He has other gifts.
- Does he?
The gift
of a great name.
Sometimes that's all
one needs.
( Robin whimpering )
Good-bye, Lord Royce,
and thank you for all
you've done for me.
I have done nothing more
than my duty, my lady.
I have no doubt
that on my return,
Robin's skills will have
improved immeasurably.
He'll be safe here.
As for his skills,
I make no promises.
( birds screeching )
Will we head north
at some point?
He said
Sansa had a brother
at Castle Black.
We're a few days' ride
from the Kingsroad.
- But that will take us--
- Us?
The only reason you're here
is because Jaime Lannister
told me you weren't
safe in the capital.
You're hundreds of miles
from King's Landing.
No one knows
what you look like.
No one cares.
You're safe.
- But I'm your squire.
- Do you even know
what a squire is?
An attendant
to a knight.
I'm not a knight.
That means
you're not a squire.
Well, where would I go?
I don't care.
I'm not your mother.
You swore to find
the Stark girls.
I found Arya.
She didn't want
my protection.
- Sansa still might.
- Will you shut your mouth?
I didn't ask
for your advice.
I don't want anyone
following me.
I'm not a leader.
All I ever wanted
was to fight for a lord
I believed in.
The good lords are dead
and the rest are monsters.
- ( horse whinnies )
- ( hoofbeats approaching )
( horses neighing )
You told Lord Royce
we were going to the Fingers.
I did.
- But we're heading west.
- We are.
If he wanted to betray us,
he already would have.
Lord Royce
might be as honorable
as he thinks he is,
but he's not alone
in that castle.
Do you trust all those
knights and ladies,
stable boys
and serving girls?
No, do you trust
the carriage driver
or the knights escorting us?
No.
( chuckles )
But I pay them well
and they've seen what happens
to men who disappoint me.
So where are we going?
To a land where
you trust everyone?
To a land
so far from here,
even Cersei Lannister
can't get her hands on you.
It was such a deep,
deep shock to us all.
Your father was a--
a force to be
reckoned with.
He truly was.
I wouldn't
presume to claim
to have known him
as such, but--
but just being
in his presence was enough
to make it so clear
just how formidable
a person you were
dealing with.
What a-- what a force
to be reckoned with.
( sighs )
Thank you so much
for your kind words.
Deepest condolences,
Your Grace.
This tragedy...
I never trusted Varys.
I often warned...
Your Grace.
Cousin Lancel.
I hardly recognized you.
My deepest
sympathies.
I apologize
for my son's
appearance.
Uncle, it's quite
all right.
They call themselves
sparrows.
( chuckles )
Bloody fanatics.
Religion has its place,
of course,
but at a certain point...
They never would
have come to the capital
when Tywin was alive.
I'm sure he'll
grow out of it,
whatever it is.
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
Your wounds
from the Blackwater
seem to have healed.
It wasn't my wounds
that needed healing.
What can I do
for you?
You can forgive me.
What could you possibly
have done to warrant
my forgiveness?
I led you
into the darkness.
I doubt you've ever
led anyone anywhere.
I tempted you
into our...
unnatural relations.
And, of course,
there was the king...
his boar hunt.
His wine.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm a different
person now.
I've found peace
in the light of the Seven.
You can, too.
They watch over
all of us,
ready to dole out mercy
or justice.
Their world
is at hand.
I will pray for
your father's soul.
( laughs )
The day Tywin Lannister's
soul needs your help...
- Olyvar: It looks like Dorne.
- Loras: It doesn't.
( laughs )
It does.
That's the--
that's the Sunspear
bit right there.
And that's where
the mountains are.
And over here is--
is Sunsnake?
Stonespear?
Sandstone.
Yes.
Yes, Sandstone.
( kisses )
Just there.
Fine.
It's Dorne.
We should go there.
I think we would
have a lovely time,
judging by
my experience.
That would be wonderful.
Dorne, Highgarden.
Anywhere but here.
We're late for dinner
as it is.
You're very respectful.
I'm very hungry.
What's your name?
Olyvar, my lady.
I'm afraid my brother
is keeping the king
waiting, Olyvar.
My lady.
Perhaps you might
consider being a bit
more discreet?
Why?
They all know
about me anyway.
Everybody
knows everything
about everyone.
What's the point
in trying to keep a secret
in a place like this?
In any event, you shouldn't
keep your intended waiting.
My intended?
Please.
Tywin's dead.
That means no one
can force Cersei
to marry me.
- Lucky you.
- Unlucky you.
You think I want
that woman married
to my brother?
If she doesn't marry me,
she doesn't go to Highgarden.
Which means she stays
in King's Landing.
Which means you're trapped
here with Cersei Lannister
as your mother by law.
Perhaps.
Perhaps?
( birds screeching )
Eunuch,
the Spider,
the Master
of Whisperers.
Imp, Half-man.
There are faster ways
to kill yourself.
Not for a coward.
You are many things,
my friend,
but not a coward.
You never told me
why you set me free.
Your brother
asked me to.
Could have said no.
Refuse the Kingslayer?
A dangerous proposition.
Not as dangerous
as releasing me.
You risked your life,
your position, everything.
Why? You're not family.
You owe me nothing.
I didn't do it for you.
I did it for
the Seven Kingdoms.
A drunken dwarf
will never be the savior
of the Seven Kingdoms.
I don't believe
in saviors.
I believe men of talent
have a part to play
in the war to come.
You're going to have
to find another soldier.
I'm done with Westeros
and Westeros is done
with me.
You have many
admirable qualities,
self-pity is not
one of them.
Any fool
with a bit of luck
can find himself
born into power.
But earning it for yourself,
that takes work.
I'm not well-suited
for work.
I think you are.
You have your father's
instincts for politics.
And you have compassion.
Compassion? Yes.
I killed my lover
with my bare hands.
I shot my own father
with a crossbow.
I never said
you were perfect.
What is it
you want exactly?
Peace.
Prosperity.
A land where the powerful
do not prey on the powerless.
Where the castles
are made of gingerbread
and the moats are filled
with blackberry wine.
The powerful have always
preyed on the powerless.
That's how
they became powerful
in the first place.
Perhaps.
And perhaps we've grown
so used to horror,
we assume
there's no other way.
If you sat
on the Iron Throne,
would you spread misery
throughout the land?
I will never sit
on the Iron Throne.
No, you won't.
But you could help another
climb those steps
and take that seat.
The Seven Kingdoms
need someone stronger
than Tommen,
but gentler
than Stannis.
A monarch who can
intimidate the high lords
and inspire the people.
A ruler loved by millions
with a powerful army
and the right family name.
Good luck finding him.
Who said anything
about "him"?
You have a choice,
my friend.
You can stay here
at Illyrio's palace
and drink yourself
to death,
or you can ride with me
to Meereen,
meet Daenerys Targaryen,
and decide if the world
is worth fighting for.
Can I drink myself to death
on the road to Meereen?
- ( chatter )
- ( goat bleating )
When did the Unsullied
start patrolling the streets
of Meereen?
Looks like
your friends haven't
been behaving themselves.
Our mission to Yunkai
was a resounding success.
The Wise Masters of Yunkai
have agreed to cede power
to a council of elders
made up of both
the freed men
and the former
slaveholders.
All matters
of consequence will be
brought to you for review.
Good.
They did ask
for some concessions.
Concessions?
Politics is the art
of compromise, Your Grace.
I'm not a politician.
I'm a queen.
Hizdahr: Forgive me.
You're right, of course.
Still, it's easier
to rule happy subjects
than angry ones.
I don't expect
the Wise Masters
to be happy.
Slavery made them rich.
I ended slavery.
They do not ask
for the return
of slavery.
They ask for the reopening
of the fighting pits.
The fighting pits?
Where slaves fought
slaves to the death?
In the new world
that you've brought to us,
free men would fight
free men.
The pit fighters
you liberated
plead for
this opportunity.
Bring some here
and ask them yourself.
No fighting pits.
Opening them would show
the people of Yunkai
and Meereen that you
respect their traditions.
I do not respect
the tradition of
human cockfighting.
- If you--
- How many times must I say no
before you understand?
Whatever he wants from me,
he's not going to get it.
If he really believes
I'm going to reopen
the fighting pits...
You should reopen
the fighting pits.
What?
My mother was a whore.
I told you that.
She liked to drink
pear brandy.
The older she got,
the less she made
selling her body,
the more she wanted
to drink.
So one day when I was 12,
she sold me to a slaver
she fucked
the night before.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I was a bad child.
I wasn't big,
but I was quick.
And I loved to fight.
So they sold me
to a man in Tolos
who trained fighters
for the pits.
I had my first match
when I was 16.
You were sold
into slavery,
forced to fight to the death
for the amusement
of the masters,
and you're defending
the fighting pits?
( laughs )
I'm only here
because of those pits.
I learned to fight
like a Dothraki screamer,
a Norvoshi priest,
a Westerosi knight.
Soon I was famous.
10,000 men and women
screamed my name
when I stepped
into the pit.
I made so much money
for my master,
he set me free
when he died.
I joined the Second Sons.
And then I met you.
You're the queen.
Everyone's too afraid
of you to speak truth.
Everyone but me.
You've made thousands
of enemies all across
the world.
As soon
as they see weakness,
they'll attack.
Show your strength
here, now.
That's why
I have the Unsullied
patrolling the streets.
( scoffs )
Anyone with a chest
full of gold can buy
an army of Unsullied.
You're not
the Mother of Unsullied.
You're the Mother
of Dragons.
I don't want
another child's bones
dropped at my feet.
No one's seen
Drogon in weeks.
For all I know,
he's flown halfway
across the world.
I can't control
them anymore.
A dragon queen
with no dragons
is not a queen.
Viserion?
Rhaegal?
( snarling )
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
( roaring )
( roaring continues )
( door opens )
So here we are.
Here we are.
When we first met,
you were my prisoner.
And now,
for our last meeting...
This doesn't have to be
our last meeting.
No, but it will be.
You know
what Stannis wants?
He wants me
to bend the knee.
And he wants
the free folk
to fight for him.
I'll give him
this much,
he's bold.
Shouldn't a king
be bold?
Oh, aye.
I respect him.
If he gets what he wants,
I expect he'll be
a better ruler
than the fools
sitting on the Iron Throne
the last hundred years.
But I'll never serve him.
You told me you weren't
here to conquer.
You told me your people
have bled enough.
That's right.
I don't want
them bleeding for
Stannis Baratheon either.
You spent your life
convincing 90 clans
to come together
for the first time
in history.
Thenns and Hornfoots,
the ice-river clans,
even the giants.
A life's work uniting them.
You didn't do it for power.
You didn't do it
for glory.
You brought them
together to save them
because none of them
will survive the winter,
not if they're north
of the Wall.
Isn't their survival
more important than
your pride?
Pride?
Fuck my pride.
This isn't about that.
Then bend the knee
and save your people.
They followed me
because they respected me.
Because they
believed in me.
The moment I kneel
for a southern king,
that's all gone.
And how many
tens of thousands
are out there right now?
How many women?
How many children?
And you won't
go out and rescue
them because why?
You're afraid
of looking afraid.
Oh, I am afraid.
No shame in that.
How will they do it?
Beheading?
Hanging?
They'll burn you alive.
Bad way to go.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't want to die.
And burnt to death,
I don't want people
to remember me like that,
scorched and screaming.
But it's better
than betraying
everything I believe.
And what happens
to your people?
You preserve your dignity
and die standing
and they'll sing
songs about you.
You'd rather burn
than kneel.
The great hero.
Until winter comes
and the white walkers
come for us all
and there's no one
left to sing.
You're a good lad.
Truly you are.
But if you can't
understand why I won't
enlist my people
in a foreigner's war,
there's no point
explaining.
( pounds on door )
I think you're making
a terrible mistake.
( chuckles )
The freedom to make
my own mistakes
was all I ever wanted.
( door closes )
( latch clanks )
Mance Rayder,
you've been called
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
Westeros
only has one king.
Bend the knee,
I promise you mercy.
Kneel and live.
This was my home
for many years.
I wish you good fortune
in the wars to come.
We all must choose.
Man or woman,
young or old,
lord or peasant,
our choices are the same.
We choose light
or we choose darkness.
We choose good
or we choose evil.
We choose the true god
or the false.
Free folk,
there is only
one true king
and his name
is Stannis.
Here stands
your king of lies.
Behold the fate of those
who choose the darkness.
( gasping )
( Mance crying out )
( coughing )
( groaning stops )
( crowd murmuring )
( theme music playing )