Do we really want
what we think we want?
Or is it only when we get
what we want,
...that we understand if
we want it because we want it
or...
...want it because
we think we want it.
One, two, three, four...
I declare a thumb war.
Yes! I won.
What do you get?
Squat.
By the way, your family driver
is fully shocked.
So?
I don't care.
Do you?
Let's go to the Maldives?
You and me.
The sand. White bikini.
On or off.
Just enjoy the moment.
And...
...I might show you my
white bra.
On.
And off.
Fuck!
Where has this sexy nymph
been hiding all this while?
Took a while to wade
through the traffic.
Sexy and funny.
What else have you been hiding
from me, Ms. Patel?
Leaving?
Ya.
Aren't those the rules?
Stay?
And what about your cocoon?
You can be my cocoon.
Why not. It's been my
childhood ambition.
To be someone's cocoon.
Perfect.
Mom!
Happy Diwali Umi!
Pinky...
-What were you up to?
We've been ringing
the bell for so long.
You've come unannounced.
We wanted to surprise you.
And we wanted to experience...
...Mumbai's famous festival
of lights!
Come...
I got it.
Coffee.
Mr. Workaholic.
Thanks.
Just thanks?
Mehta and Mehta's file
is pending.
Yes but...
...you can take
a two minute break, right?
No, I actually can't.
Because my boss
is a hard-ass.
She never says what
she thinks.
And she doesn't think
about what she says.
That's a bit harsh.
Listen,
can we please
go inside and talk.
Because I have no idea
what's going on here.
Ya well...I don't either.
So let's go inside and talk.
Please.
Please Arjun.
I am not your puppy.
You can't pet me
when you like...
...and then send me off to
a kennel when you don't.
Just because
I'm younger than you...
...does not mean that
I don't have feelings.
God, Arjun...
-First, you yell at me in Goa.
Then you ignore me for
three days. And now...
coffee!
Seriously?
Arjun, this is not easy
for me.
I have a daughter.
I have responsibilities.
Yes, you don't think
I know that?
Look...
I like you.
I genuinely like you, okay.
I want to be a part of
your life.
Not to be some dirty
secret that you hide away.
I never said that.
Please. You behave like
you're embarrassed of me.
Not to be seen in
public with me.
But guess what,
I'm not a toy boy.
Arjun.
Arjun, I'm really sorry
if I made you feel that way.
Honestly, that was not
my intention.
Listen,
I...
...really like you too.
But it's just that...
I'm very sensitive
about Arya.
You know and...
I have my own shit going on
with this whole...
...mommy guilt.
My own misplaced
insecurities. It's...
You won't understand.
You're going to decide
that for me as well?
Okay.
Dinner.
Tonight.
With Arya and me?
Please. Please.
Are you sure?
-Yes, very sure.
Okay, I think I'd like that.
Okay.
And now you get back
to work...
...before your hard-ass boss...
...catches you bunking work.
Yes, Ms. Menon.
Morning, viral sensation.
Viral?
Like your article on the
troll cells?
It's gone viral.
What?
Yes!
30,000 shares?
-Yes.
Where's my phone?
7,000 retweets.
9,400 mentions on Twitter.
Oh my God!
You trolled the trolls!
I have to call Vaibhav and...
Karan and that...
...crazy Asha.
They'll be fucking
jumping in joy!
Damini, according to
your story,
there is a powerful
person behind all this.
Largely, trolls...
...have paid jobs.
They hide behind their
anonymity and...
...spew venom on whoever
they are told to.
In this case,
the main culprit is...
...the big guy.
Top industrialist Badani.
In order to save his
politician friends and...
...secure his business
interests,
he runs these troll cells.
Don't you think these
trolls will retaliate?
Take their revenge on you?
These people won't even
show their faces.
Why would I fear them?
Good evening, Ma'am.
Good evening.
-Good evening.
Stop it.
What?
I bought wine...
...which...
Hey!
Hi.
I thought...
...you two were coming
over tomorrow for the...
...festival thing.
No...
It was...it was...
...it was today.
-Today. Today.
Ya.
Oh...
Ya. Of course.
Of course, I remember.
Of course.
Should we?
Of course!
Ya, please.
Hi, I'm...
I'm Kavya, by the way.
Arjun.
That's Varun.
Arya's dad.
Ya.
Arjun and I...
...work together.
Oh.
-Nice.
You look...
...fairly young to be a lawyer.
Oh no, just an intern.
Intern?
-Ya.
I'd be careful if I was you,
you know.
These buildings...
They're not very
comfortable with...
...uncultured behavior.
So...
CCTV cameras so...
...you don't know
who's watching.
Please, go ahead.
-No.
After you.
No, you first.
Bro...
I was the first one.
You go first.
Okay.
So what is this?
Reliving your youth?
Actually, living it for the
first time.
Does HR know about this?
I'm in it just for the sex.
Wow.
You should be a
stand-up comedian.
Well, after our divorce,
you now know that...
...I'm funny too.
See what I mean.
Very funny.
Let's join these two.
Put this one here.
Put blue here.
Okay...
Miss Bossy Pants.
Blue.
Just like her mother.
-Ya?
Dadda says Pookie Aunty
bossy pants.
Pookie Aunty bossy pants?
Pookie Aunty.
-Pookie Aunty bossy pants!
Before introducing him
to Arya,
couldn't you have waited
a few days?
Like you did?
Ya, like I did.
Six months.
Only after that did
I introduce Kayva to her.
Everybody can't be
as perfect as you are.
Mr. Tighty-Whitey
Varun Khanna.
I wear boxers now.
Airing yourself out?
Does Kavya want a baby?
Maybe.
See that's the difference now.
Kavya would like to
have a child.
And you would like to
date one.
That's really below the belt.
Babe, everything is
below the belt.
What?
You guys started drinking
without us?
Sorry...
-So sorry...
C'mon.
Okay.
Why are you behaving
like this?
Like what?
Like you're...
...jealous or something.
Jealous?
No.
Don't be ridiculous.
Hey guys! Who wants
some pizza?
Me! Me!
Pizza! Pizza!
-Pizza! Pizza!
-I'll be up for some pizza.
Pizza! Pizza!
-Pizza! Pizza!
Hey Damini!
Dr. War...
Aamir...
-Ya.
Hi...
Been busy?
No replies to my texts,
my calls.
My birthday wishes.
I was in Goa for my
birthday and...
...my phone wasn't working.
Sorry.
Also been really swamped
with work...
...ever since I got back so...
Being swamped with
work is the best way to be.
But you look like you
need a drink.
Can I...
...offer you one?
No, no...I'm fine.
-C'mon.
I've been meaning to go
in for the longest time.
But I'm okay...
Really, I'm fine...
-C'mon!
C'mon, one drink.
-It's...okay...
It's fine, c'mon.
-I...
Anything else?
No, thank you.
Dee?
Yes, your friends call you
Dee, right?
Ms. Rizvi Roy.
Actually, I'm quite a regular
at this bar.
Me and my friends.
Not that I'm an alcoholic.
We're here a couple of
times a week.
Which means I will
have to...
...become a regular here.
Sorry?
From the clinic to the cafe...
...to the bar around the corner.
Here's to us...
...becoming regulars.
Quit smoking.
It's wreaking havoc on
your body.
Cheater.
You're stubbing a
finished cigarette.
Aamir...
Oh my God.
I'm sorry, I just...
Just needed some stock.
Jeh!
You're with that boy?
No, no, nothing like
that. I mean...
...not that we're not
together. I mean...
We weren't together
when you and I were...
I don't know what I'm up to.
What he's up to.
Or what we're up to.
You're so hot and...
I was low and...
...you were there
and I was there...
Do you always ramble like
this with everyone or...
...am I special?
Aamir, I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Don't forget to come
by for your check-up.
Fuck!
Jeh...
Hey, your friend left.
I wanted to explain.
Explain what Damini?
About what happened.
And what happened.
What you saw?
You don't have to.
Don't worry about it.
He's my doctor.
He's quite the friendly doctor,
isn't he?
As in, my gynac.
As in, he was my gynac.
God, it's all coming out
so wrong.
Yes it is.
There is nothing between us.
Why are you explaining
yourself?
It's not like we're dating,
are we?
Jeh...
Listen to me.
Hey, hey, hey...
Just chill, it's cool.
Really, okay?
Umang, this city is
really nice.
I really like it here.
Mangoes out of season?
And that too Alphonso?
Let me take a look.
You said Mumbai really
suits you?
It does. Why?
Then why do you look
so low?
Are you crazy?
Forget it.
I've got lots of sweets for
Siddhi's mother.
She will really like that.
Should I buy some vegetables?
There isn't much at home.
Aren't you going
to ask me how I've been?
Why don't you tell me.
Your brother and mother
want me to have a baby now.
I'm taking the pill.
Why?
I'm not ready Umi.
Why don't you just tell
them that?
Maybe I was never ready
for marriage.
And you're saying this three
years after getting married.
Not all of us have
the kind of clarity you do.
What do you really want?
To live here.
With you.
Pinky,
I've bought fresh
vegetables for you.
I'll make some juice for you.
Your periods will regularize.
And then we'll have
good news very soon.
I ordered orchids.
What kind of florist doesn't
know the difference between...
...lilies and carnations
and orchids?
Wow!
Siddhi, you're glowing.
Did you get the gold facial?
No Sne...mama.
And you've used the new
foundation I left for you.
Gorgeous.
You know you're
actually a very pretty girl.
Thank you.
I've taken after my mother.
That is true.
Now please,
keep up this perfection.
Don't mess it up.
I'll get changed quickly.
If our guests arrive,
please look after them.
Shyamprasad! Where are
the decorations?
Damini, we miss you so much.
And we're so sorry.
We're wimps.
And traitors.
Please don't be silly.
Without your hardwork
and research,
this article wouldn't have
been possible.
So...
Congratulations to all of us.
Thank you. How sweet.
And...
This is for you.
Champagne for the occasion?
You guys have become
too fancy.
The champagne is to
celebrate the nomination.
What nomination?
The Fearless Journalist
of the Year nomination?
For the fourth time
in a row, Damini.
What?
Really?
I mean...
Wow!
-Wow!
To fearless journalism?
To fearless journalism!
So how is I-can-ksha?
She's busy.
With a big scoop story.
What scoop?
Morally and ethically
it's all wrong.
She's outing someone.
Outing someone?
Yes.
A huge celeb.
Samara Kapoor?
Apparently, she's in a
lesbian relationship.
With her personal trainer.
Stand still.
You'll ruin the pleats.
What's wrong Umi?
Are you not happy to
see me?
Mom.
Since when do you worry
about what your mother says?
I'm not saying it for me.
It's for you.
None of this is your
cup of tea.
You won't be able
to adjust, Pinky.
Yes, I know.
I know your life is
very exciting.
I keep seeing your photos
online.
I'll change myself over time.
I'll learn to speak in English.
I'll change my appearance.
I'll do it all.
What do you think?
That life in Mumbai is
one big party?
It takes sweat and blood.
It takes pain.
It takes hard work.
You'll go back home in a week.
And when you do,
no one's going to give you
your old life back.
I don't want to go back.
I regret letting you go once.
Pinky.
Are you angry with me?
Why are you saying my
name like that?
Is there someone else?
That girl on Instagram?
You've done a full
investigation,
haven't you?
Don't you love me anymore?
I loved you Pinky.
A little too much but...
But you don't anymore.
Should I wear gold or diamonds
around my neck?
Our hosts will prefer diamonds,
won't they?
Wow!
My daughter and my
daughter-in-law
are looking so beautiful!
May God protect both of you.
Gorgeous!
Gold is fine?
What a pretty little girl.
Thank you. You also pretty.
Why, thank you.
Are you Mamma's Pookie aunty?
Hi!
-Hi!
Festival greetings!
-Festival greetings!
-Hi! Festival greetings guys!
Arya, you cutie pie!
Festival greetings!
-I'm Viju Patel.
Don't ruin your mood.
We're at a party.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Festival greetings!
-How are you?
Hello! How's Mama?
-She's fine.
Welcome, welcome.
Festival greetings!
Hi!
What are you doing?
What?
Okay, fine.
What's wrong?
Please, please.
Festival greetings!
-Festival greetings!
Festival greetings, uncle.
Guys, where's Dee?
I can't wait. I really need
this guys, I'm sorry.
Here.
Hey!
Hang on.
No wasting alcohol.
Festival greetings!
-Festival greetings!
Umang, I need to speak to you.
Where were you?
Siddi-Piddi!
-Umang!
Siddhi Patel, can you come up
and join me?
Go!
Go Siddhi...
-Go!
Okay, I'm going...
From diapers to kindergarten,
to all those dance routines
we practised!
To dancing in Goa.
I just know that...
...Mihu-Pihu and
Siddi-Piddi are forever so...
Siddi-Piddi!
Will you marry me?
Say yes!
My darling baby is
getting married!
Congrats.
Welcome to the family.
Thank you.
Congratulations!
Oh my God.
Siddhi, I always wanted
for you to be my
daughter-in-law.
God bless you.
So excited!
Oh my God!
Sids, your
'Knight-in-shining-armour
-on-a-white-horse' wish...
...actually came true!
Actually!
Mihir is scared of horses.
Sids, you're going to live in
New York.
New York man!
I hate New York!
You have to walk everywhere.
And it keeps snowing there.
I hate the cold!
You'll get used to it.
What's the big deal?
Ya!
And anyway, Mihir seems like a
really great guy.
Ya.
It's only been a week
since we've met.
Wait a second, aren't you guys
childhood friends?
Sids...
What's wrong?
What happened?
Why're you crying?
Sids.
-What happened baby?
Did I do something wrong?
No. It's not you.
But you said yes!
Actually, I didn't say anything.
You mean, you don't want
to get married?
I do.
Someday, I guess.
You guess?
I don't know.
Okay, okay...
If you do...
...get married...
...it will be to me, right?
Oh man.
Look Mihir...
You're the perfect package.
You're smart, you're
intelligent.
Good looking, successful.
Classy on the outside,
massy on the inside.
And you treat me
like a princess.
And you make me laugh.
-Then what's the problem?
That I'm parent approved?
No.
Shall we elope?
Just for thrills?
Let's just run!
You know Mihir...
I always wanted this.
Or at least I thought
I wanted this.
But now I think marriage was
just an excuse...
...to get Sneha off my back.
And now?
And now...
...when this is actually
happening...
...Mihir, I'm really scared.
I mean, I don't even know
myself yet.
How can I make such
a big lifelong commitment?
And you know what?
How can the solution to all
my problems in life...
...lie in finding a husband?
Mangs, they're outing her.
And you.
She has that amazing
PR agency of hers.
I'm sure they're already on it,
doing damage control.
They can't help her this time.
They have proof.
Photos of you and her in
Goa in...
...compromising positions.
I'm sorry I can't stop the
story.
This is not even your fault.
That's what I get for
falling in love.
Fuck me!
So this...
...is a no?
-No.
So this is a yes...
...with footnotes.
Yes.
No.
I mean...
Man!
Look Mihu-Pihu...
I also really, really like you.
A lot.
But what's the rush?
Let's...
Let's hang out a bit.
Let's travel.
Let's fight.
And then make up.
And...
...let's have some...
...great unattached sex?
Fuck! I think I just fell
in love with you all over again.
Really?
You're not upset with me?
No, of course not Siddhi.
I mean...
This is what a relationship
is built on right?
Trust and...
...honesty and respect.
I mean, that's the only
way we'll ever be happy.
Really?
Siddi-Piddi!
Hell, even I don't know
who I am.
I would love to go on
this adventure with you and...
...even if we don't reach the
finish line at least...
...we'll be together.
One second. One second.
-Oh man...
Siddhi?