They say the universe fights
for souls to be together.
Somethings are so strange
and yet powerful that...
...you cannot call them
a co-incidence.
And I've begun to agree.
Good morning beautiful!
Oops.
Fuck.
Surprise!
-Surprise!
What the fuck!
I baked you a cake!
Happy birthday to you!
-Happy birthday to you!
-My birthday isn't till day
after...
...you freaks!
Happy birthday dear Dee!
-Are you guys insane?
I really thought
I was going to die in there!
At the rate you're working,
yes you will die.
Dee...we're kidnapping you
from yourself.
So deep ya...so deep!
-So deep bro...
We're taking you to Goa bro.
And we've packed some
clothes in for you, so chill.
And by the way,
I've got front row passes to
the Arambol Festival.
And who the fuck are you?
Oh Mohit, Dee...
Dee, Mohit...
-Hi Dee!
And you're welcome.
For what?
Giving me a heart attack?
I'm going to really kill
you guys, you know!
Throw that damn...
-No! No!
Okay, okay! Just chill!
-No, don't. Don't touch my cake.
Happy birthday to you!
-Happy birthday to you!
Can we go?
Happy birthday to you!
-Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Damini...
-Happy birthday dear Damini...
Happy birthday to you.
-Happy birthday to you.
Obviously, they'll keep a
hawk-eye on you.
You please keep in
touch, okay?
Ya, I'm available 24/7.
Fucking network!
I can't hear...
-Are you thinking what I'm
thinking?
ZNMD!
-ZNMD!
Siddhi, what the hell!
What!
-Guys, quiet ya!
Please! Quiet!
Siddhi, stop it!
Sids, stop it please!
-What are you doing?
What?!
-Oh!
Guys!
Stop the car!
Umang, stop the car!
Is this supposed to be funny?
You think it's funny?
Siddhi, give me your phone.
This is for your own good, Dee.
It's my birthday weekend!
Hand it over! Please!
I'll put my sim in
your phone.
Give!
Giving!
And what'll I do?
Have a phone free weekend.
Besides, the only people
you know are...
...right here in this car.
Dee!
Dee, that's really mean.
Okay, I didn't mean it
like that.
Sids!
No, you're right.
I'm unemployed,
unambitious.
And I have just one goal
in life.
Finding a husband.
But I love my life.
-Sid...
Even though you think
I shouldn't.
Siddhi, you know I love you.
I'm fine, really.
Really, I'm fine.
-Oh...
Awww...
-Oh!
We love you Siddhi Patel!
Siddhi, we love you!
Sids, give me my phone.
-No.
Something urgent's come up.
I'll be right back.
Hey! What! Mangs!
Housekeeping.
Surprise!
Oh my God!
You gorgeous idiot!
Now today we have to
shoot the final...
...training tournament montage.
My fest won't start
for another three hours.
Can I come?
Hired a big time American
stunt co-ordinator.
He probably won't like it.
Besides, you should chill,
you know.
Stay here.
Go to the spa.
Room service.
Pool.
Just pamper yourself.
But I've never seen a
shoot in my life.
I would really like
to see you in action.
But you always see me
in action babe.
You know what I mean.
Anyways, if you come to set,
I won't be able to concentrate.
What are we eating for
breakfast?
-Bottoms up ladies!
Whoa!
-Mohit, it's 11 o'clock in the
morning.
Which is why the tomato
juice chaser.
Healthy breakfast and all!
Nonsense!
-Nonsense!
Okay, let's go for it.
-C'mon...
Mangs! Where've you been?
-Where were you?
Happy birthday weekend
Damini!
Happy birthday Damini!
-Happy birthday!
From 'Don't kiss me,
I'm prudish' to...
...'whip-lady Dominatrix'
in one month?
Siddhi!
Mohit...
I just can't describe it to you.
You know, for the first time
in my life I feel...
I feel free.
I have started liking
my body.
Infact...
I love it!
Enough. Please.
I charge for these
shrink sessions.
You'll have to buy me
vodka shots.
C'mon.
C'mon Dominatrix.
Madam, the concert is
on that side.
C'mon, get up!
-Oh shit.
Oh shit!
You guys! Get up!
We're so late!
What?
-Get up guys!
C'mon ya...
-Oh my God!
What!
10...
9...
8...
7...
6... 5... 4... 3... 2...
Are you ready!
I can't see anything!
What is happening!
-My head is spinning!
Relax!
It's not a Coldplay concert.
Enjoy the ambience!
Did you kidnap me to
show me this ambience?
Beach,
two hundred meters.
Booze, fifty meters.
Hot guy, 10 o'clock, 3 o'clock.
5 o'clock!
Fair enough!
Guys, fuck this.
I need a drink.
Anyone needs a drink?
Fine.
Sissies.
Excuse me please.
Hey bartender!
Hey Ms Menon!
Oh my God!
Arjun! What...
What're you doing here?
Are you stalking me?
Sure.
Need help?
No, thanks.
I've been to thousands
of concerts.
I wasn't always like this.
A lawyer, a boss.
A 'Ms Menon'.
Ya, okay.
Excuse me!
Excuse...
Oh God!
Fuck this shit.
I'm going.
A little help please?
Up! Up! Up!
There you are.
Four G&T's and one beer.
What do you guys want?
Four vodka reds.
Kids.
Four vodka reds please.
Here, hold this.
Our generation can do
things themselves.
Well...
-Keep it there please.
Technically, we're the
same generation.
Seriously...
We're both millennials.
You're a kid...
...and I'm a woman.
That's that.
-Damn.
You know because...
...I thought I became a man
when my balls dropped.
Made you look.
See, you're still a kid.
Well...
This kid is at your service.
Whenever you want.
Ms Menon.
Hey, there you are!
Guys! Guys!
Drinks!
Thank you!
-Yay!
Hi!
Where have you been
all my life?
Drinking beer.
Playing video games.
So straight.
It's my birthday and Anj is
getting personalized service?
Guys, he's Arjun.
He's my intern.
Just like that movie!
The Graduate?
With that old lady?
Shut up!
No, no, no...
That one...The Proposal.
Hot young intern,
older female boss.
What?
He murders her because
she's a horrible boss?
No, actually...
...they sleep together!
Oh!
I think I should leave.
It was great to meet
you guys.
It was lovely meeting
you too!
Stalker.
Thank you Sids!
Love you too!
I think Ms VeeVee's
about to wake up!
Whoo!
-Whoo!
Guys! Guys!
He's a kid.
Can I have him?
For me, age no bar.
Anj, he totally gave you
the look.
So time to say bye
to Varun.
For good!
Hey rebound!
Rebound!
-Rebound!
Please shut up!
Rebound!
Just shut up!
-Rebound!
Hello?
Rebound!
-Shut up guys.
No! Please!
-Yes, this is Damini...
Please!
Shut up!
Excuse me?
Rebound!
I'm not listening. Bye!
-Rebound!
Rebound!
Whoo!
These guys don't waste
any time.
Fucking assholes!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Om Shanti.
Fuck Shanti!
A little something
to release your tension.
If you want more,
call me.
Give me that.
Hey! What the fuck!
First Anjana disappeared.
Now Dee.
Everyone knows
where the hotel is.
Just chill!
Look! There's our peeps!
Our people, our country!
Mohit!
You told me there'll
be cute guys here for me!
Beer, beer...
Cheers!
Siddi-Piddi!
Mihu-Pihu?
Oh fuck!
What a small world man!
Shit!
I'm so sorry! I'm really sorry!
-Relax.
I know what you need.
Cold, cold water!
It feels so good!
Siddi-Piddi and Mihu-Pihu
together in Goa.
Who would've thought?
Ya dude!
What are you doing here?
Weren't you in New York?
Yes but I came back
two days ago...
...and I came straight
to Goa.
I can't handle my parents
in India...
...without an easy transition,
you know.
When we were eight
year olds...
...I still remember that you
were
obsessed with water.
You remember that Holi?
When you did...
...this?
Siddhi!
Take that!
Want more?
Get lost.
Fucking...
...asshole.
Two words.
Fuck off.
Fucking assholes!
Think I'll drop the
story through intimidation.
I will show them!
Water please!
Excuse me!
Is one fucking bottle
of water...
...too much to ask for!
One bottle of water please...
-No, it's not.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
-Excuse me.
Oops.
Thank you so...
-C'mon!
Spending a few minutes
with someone as beautiful as
you...
...is payment enough.
And may I ask...
...why a beautiful girl like
you is
standing here all by herself?
Your guy's an idiot to
leave you out of his sight...
...even for a minute.
There is no guy.
I'm divorced.
What a co-incidence.
Me too.
I'm Vinil.
I run a hedge fund
in Mumbai.
Hi,
I'm Anjana.
I'm a lawyer.
And...
I'm from Mumbai too.
Legalese and money.
It's like rum and coke.
Speaking of which,
can I get you one?
One G&T please.
"Of all the gin joints,
in all the towns, in all the
world,
she walks into mine."
Casablanca.
Seriously?
This?
Old guy?
With a beard?
Leave me alone.
I'm flirting.
Oh.
And what happened
to the other Anjana?
Who...
...climbs up on the bar...
...and gives me a spiel about
her generation?
You know what,
I met someone who's
older, wiser.
We kind of hit it off...
What's the problem?
Ms Menon,
the problem is...
...you know what you want.
But you don't know
what you need.
And what do I want?
This financial duffer...
...who listens to jazz
while sipping his single malt.
Never misses Sunday
golf and...
...owns a posh apartment
in a high-rise.
He never opens the
windows...
...because 'No ya. Mumbai's
air smells of sea.'
And...
...what do I need?
Someone you can smell
the sea with.
I think you're being
very judgemental.
Oh God.
Okay, how about this.
Imagine what he'll
look like in five years.
And then imagine...
...what you'll look like.
Have you heard of
one night stands?
You can do better.
"To the kingdom far,
far away my queen."
"That's where we should go."
So, Casablanca Vs Shrek.
No brainer.
Let's go.
How are Hetal aunty and
Jayesh uncle?
You know, honestly,
I really don't know.
I mean, because
every time I get here...
...they're like marriage,
marriage, marriage.
I lose it.
I go to my room.
Rinse and repeat.
Remember that Lonavala trip?
When we filled Sneha's
bed with mango fudge...
...and thought she had a
diarrhea attack!
Jesus!
Wait, you still call
her Sneha?
Ya, I guess...
...somethings never change.
Thank God they don't.
Siddi-Piddi...
Your hair is like...
...a cobweb!
Don't you shampoo?
Mihu-Pihu!
I'll beat you up!
Shit! Fuck!
Sorry, sorry!
-Sorry!
You bloody dog!
What?
-Motherfucker!
Cocksucker!
-Bro...
Take it easy man!
Relax.
Siddhi, just come here
one second.
You ruined my t-shirt asshole!
-Bro...
Bro, I just...
-You going to buy me a new one?
One second idiot.
Shut up!
Is the size of your brain...
...inversely proportional to the
size of your biceps?
If you can't speak civilly...
...then go back to
wherever you came from.
Siddhi just...
You don't have the balls...
...so you're hiding behind
your girlfriend?
No, we're not looking
for a fight.
Where are your balls?
I'm not looking for a fight.
-Stop barking in English!
C'mon bite me you dog!
Bite me!
Oh!
Oh shit!
That was amazing!
-Run!
You bastard!
Siddi-Piddi!
When did you turn into
sexy Siddhi?
That was...
...that was so fucking hot!
I should...
...I should go find
my friends.
Wait, wait...c'mon!
Spend some time with
an old friend?
I have a great idea.
What?
Sings folk song
That folk song?
Oh my God!
The dance festival!
Remember we practiced
the shit out of that routine!
Of course!
And what did we get?
Consolation prize.
-Wait, wait...
At least we got to go to
Bachelors...
...to eat chilli ice cream...
...and drown our sorrows!
Ya!
-Right?
Continues singing folk song
Ashes to ashes...
Dust to dust.
My puppy!
Where are you?
Puppy...
Jeh!
Damini?
I miss Xerxes.
He was such a cute puppy.
He was my....
...friend, you know.
My best friend.
Was?
He's still alive, you know.
Where is he?
I miss his happy face!
Just like the pill!
Puppy is my happy pill!
You can visit him anytime
you want.
Now?
I'm in Goa.
In Goa?
Ya...
But I don't know
where I am...
I had a happy pill...
...just like puppy.
He was so cute!
Damini, Damini!
Who're you with?
Alone.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
My friends...
They kidnapped me...
...and then they
abandoned me.
Wait. What?
'We're kidnapping you
and taking you to Goa!'
Then life came and went
and kept going...
And some politician
is trying to scare me now.
Calling me Babygirl!
Damini...
Damini, pay attention.
No!
I have a girlfriend.
So? I don't care.
Ya but...I do.
Mohit!
Mangs, little busy!
Give me your phone!
The number you're trying
to reach is busy.
Please try again later.
The number...
The number you're trying
to reach is busy.
Please try again later.
Eight ero...
...erogenous zones.
Go away Dr Warsi!
Hello Jeh...
Why're you being so...
...hot and so nice...
...like pizza.
Fuck.
These pills are fucking
with my head.
Nope.
It's actually me.
C'mon...
Drink up Ms Rizvi Roy.
How did you get here
so fast from Mumbai?
I've been in Goa since
the morning.
Parent's big fortieth wedding
anniversary tomorrow.
I'm fucked Jeh,
my life is...
Enough.
...fucked.
-Enough.
Just a few more hours
and the pill will wear off.
And all will be okay.
Promise?
-I promise.
That's Walia's house right?
I've always wondered
how it looks on the inside.
Me too.
I've heard he throws
legendary parties...
...like with top models.
Arjun, I meant the villa.
Not the girls.
Ya. Me too.
I'm not interested in girls.
Only women.
Wait a second.
You're hitting on me.
Ya, finally.
After four long hours!
Seriously?
I'm sorry,
I'm just out of practice.
Shall we get some
practice then?
Let's go in?
How?
Easy.
Trespassing.
Are you nuts?
What if someone's inside?
There's no one inside.
Walia's hiding abroad...
...so the government has
seized his villa.
No guards.
But there's a big wall.
No.
No! No! No!
Arjun no!
Seriously?
Shit! You made it!
It's gorgeous.
C'mon!
Okay fine!
Woah!
Shit!
Again.
Yes!
Again!
Wait.
-Well, I like this new look.
Okay.
No, I don't need your hand.
Let's go!
Oh my God,
I was almost there!
Arjun...
Arjun!
Fuck, let's do this.
C'mon.
One, two, three...
Go! Fuck!
Hey!
The gate was open the
whole time.
What the fuck!
I couldn't find any
of the girls.
Damini.
Da...
If we can have iced tea,
why not hot champagne?
Shit.
Oh my god!
What did you just do!
Well,
only one solution.
Really?
The water's fucking amazing.
C'mon in.
C'mon...
You know what.
Fuck it.
There it is.
It's fucking cold!
Ya but it worked.
Fuck. You tricked me!
-Ya.
Fuck.
You okay?
Ya.
-You sure?
You're a goddess.
Oh my God.
You truly are a goddess!
Ya, you said that.
-I did?
That was amazing.
Thanks?
I'm losing...
It's okay.
Just go to bed.
I'm losing the battle.
You're too strong.
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
You can do anything
you want.
And you're one of the
smartest people I know.
Everything will be okay.
Okay?
Jeh...
Yes?
I like you Jeh Wadia...
I like you too Damini Rizvi
Roy...
No, I mean...
What?
Can we have some more
champagne please?
Hot champagne.
Right now?
Ya.
Go!
Fuck!
My balls!
Oh!
Great.
Laugh at my pain.
It's not funny!
What else am I
supposed to do?
Oh!
Just give me...
Just give me a second.
-I'm sorry.
Ya?
Samara?
Don't forget I'm your producer.
Your shenanigans are
going to get me in trouble.
Promise me that.
-Let me take care of that.
Ya sure...
-Please.
Alright. That's fine.
-Hi...
Hi! Hi!
Oh! My goodness.
Hi.
-Hi! You just arrived?
Ya...
Ya! Umang...
Guys, meet my absolutely
fantastic trainer...
...Umang Singh.
-Hi.
Who got me all fit
and ready for our film.
Oh! She's the one.
Yes.
-That's a great body
transformation.
I mean Samara looks like...
...as if she's been an
MMA fighter for a decade.
Absolutely.
-Not bad.
Good job Umang!
Training tomorrow at 7am...
...because we have to get
ready for the Thai schedule
and...
...food is over there,
so help yourself.
Here.
You're trying to get me
fat now?
C'mon...
I'll also have some.
Nice try.
C'mon!
One more. One more.
What?
Damini, I like you too.
Infact I like you too much.
But not now, not like this.
You get some rest.
I'll be right here.
Tomorrow.
Day after.
The day after that
and the day after that.
Okay?
Promise?
I promise.
Happy birthday Ms Rizvi Roy.
Shalom.
So...
...nothing...
...happened?
Siddi-Piddi...
I still can't believe
you were a virgin.
Were?
Fuck.
Were.