Why is it that...
...we find it hardest to stand up
to the person we love the most?
Is it because we’re scared
of hurting them?
Or hurting ourselves?
I wandered lonely as a cloud...
...that floats so high...
-Ready?
Siddhi...
...what is this?
Julie Didi's birthday gift.
Take it off now!
You look like a
three-tiered birthday cake!
No!
What do you mean no?
Julie! I mean...
-What is going on here?
This is what is going
on Viju!
She looks like a
strawberry meringue!
You know I need this
evening to be perfect.
I have to prove to these
people that we're a perfect family.
And now this...
-What are you saying Sneha.
Aren't we already perfect?
Oh please!
Julie, ten minutes.
Change her.
Our guests will be here
any minute.
This is important for
your mother.
So let's do this for her.
Quickly change your dress
and come sweetheart.
I wandered lonely
as a cloud...
...that floats all high...
...over valleys and hills.
When all at once...
...I saw a crowd...
...a host of golden daffodils.
Besides the lake...
...beneath the trees...
...fluttering and dancing...
Whoa!
Siddhi!
I'm so sorry.
So this pretty gift is from...
Sejal!
Very sweet.
-They're all the same.
Well done Sejal.
These botoxed women...
Their eyebrows are
permanently surprised.
When I break our news
to them...
...their eyebrows
will fly off their faces.
If you hate them so much,
why are they your friends?
Grow up Siddhi.
That's life.
Sometimes you socialise
with people...
...even if you don't
like them.
??
There she is!
Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Congratulations darling.
Thank you.
And you look lovely.
Thank you Aunty.
And ladies...
I have big news.
So do I.
You know my nephew Pavan?
He just got engaged.
Kinjal Lakhani.
Ms. NRI 2014 runner up!
With her.
Wow!
That's really good news.
Siddhi, what did you do that...
...Pavan just got engaged
to the very next girl he met?
Karate chops?
By the way, you know whose
daughter Kinjal is, don't you?
Surpriya and Akash Bhatt.
Oh no.
Sneha, wasn't your engagement
with him called off?
And didn't your father
gift him a car as good omen?
Then why did the
engagement break Sneha?
Mona, today my Viju's
net worth is...
...three times more
than Akash.
And your nephew, Pavan?
I'm sorry to say but he
eats chicken.
I'm thrilled that Siddhi
narrowly escaped him.
In any case,
I believe in destiny.
Kuki's son, Mohit?
-Yes?
Siddhi and he clicked
like that.
And you know that
family, right?
Only Mercedes and BMWs.
And they have this exquisite
home in Dubai Marina.
Ladies, please save
your dates for December.
I will throw Siddhi
a destination wedding...
...no one will ever forget.
He's such a
handsome boy, Mona.
And great personal style.
He does all of Kuki's
personal shopping for her.
Really?
Once you two get married,
I'm appointing Mohit
my personal stylist.
But Sneha Aunty...
Mohit is gay.
Isn't he?
How long have you
known this?
Since the beginning.
Why Siddhi!
Why do you always embarrass
me in front of others?
Sneha is such a liar.
Do you know why her
engagement broke?
Her father gifted Akash
a car alright...
...but he hadn't fully
paid for it.
Really?
-Yes.
Why is Mummy so mean,
Julie Didi?
Listen baby,
Madam is always on a diet.
That's why her blood
sugar level is always low.
You know, in our Goa,
there is one saying.
Always hungry means...
...always angry.
See...
My favourite.
Lemon and chocolate!
That's why I made them.
When will you teach
me how to make cupcakes?
The next time Madam
leaves town.
Promise.
I love your cupcakes.
I love you.
But I hate her.
Hey Sidi-Pidi...
...it's me.
Take this...
Your papa's famous Mojito.
Papa, why did you
marry her?
I wish I was never born.
Siddhi, please.
Don't say such things.
Why don't you ever
say anything to Sneha?
You know Papa,
mom has never once...
...looked at me
with love.
She's always judging me.
It's like I can never
do anything right.
I'm a perpetual
embarrassment for her.
You know still, every day,
I just wait for her to say...
...I love you Sidi-Pidi.
Like you do.
But she's never going
to say it, is she?
You know your mother
sweetheart.
She loves you very much.
But in her own
Sneha Patel style.
Papa, please don't lie
to me.
I swear on your cupcakes.
Now take this...
...our only companion
when we're sad.
I don't want it.
How can you not
want it?
I've made it extra strong
just for you.
Take it quickly.
Drink up...
Come.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Really?
Cheers, darling.
-Cheers.
Oh my God...
Don't do that.
You're not going to
miss me at all.
Here. Xerxes' toys...
Did I hear Xerxes?
And...
his food bowl...
-I did, didn't I?
His favourite blankie,
everything's in here.
Also tell your mum his
favourite is milk bread.
And you have to force
him to drink water...
...otherwise he gets
dehydrated.
Ok?
And also...
O how the mighty
have fallen.
What?
Ms. Rizvi Roy's in love...
Oh please!
C'mon, out with it.
The minute I wake up,
he licks my face.
Ok fine, I admit,
maybe I'm a little...
...tad bit attached.
Oh my God!
Your maternal instincts
are awakening.
Shut up!
Shhh...
What is that noise?
Is that the sound of your
biological clock ticking?
Out.
Out of my house!
Right now.
-Yes, it is.
Go.
So I was watching this
TV show...
...about women,
you know,
doing crazy things!
TV show?
Ok, I did an online search.
I don't have experience.
No worries.
I'll show you.
Mamma, I want princess dress!
I want princess dress!
-Arya, no tantrums.
-You know better than that.
I want princess dress!
Okay, I'm going.
-I want princess dress!
What are...
leave it.
Arya...
Fuck.
Arya, very bad.
Hi Arya!
Hi, Pookie aunty!
-Hi!
What are you guys
doing here?
Nothing, we were just like...
You know just...
Just walking around.
Pookie aunty,
I want princess dress.
Oh!
A princess dress?
She's just driving me mad.
Arya...
Only boring girls
wear princess dresses.
You're not a princess.
You're a warrior.
Like Wonder Woman.
Yes?
Mamma, I don't want
princess dress.
I'm Wonder Woman.
Wow! Finally.
Do you want to get
a coffee?
Ya, sure.
Sure!
You're quite good
with kids.
Sister to...
...three siblings.
So you were shopping?
Out buying socks
for Varun.
Wow!
Varun finally shifted
from slippers to shoes?
I wish!
I'm trying.
A little cleanliness,
is that too much to ask for?
Oh my God.
Please don't remind me.
Wash basin used to be filled
with his post shave stubble.
And his clipped toe nails
in the pot.
Wet towel on the bed,
on the sofa...
Sometimes on top
of ironed clothes and...
...under the treadmill,
his slippers!
Does he still wear...
...his undies in reverse
the next day?
Oh God! Yes!
Why! Why! Why!
-Ugh!
Fuck!
Hey...
The equation I have
with Arya...
I don't want to be
her mom.
And I can't, even if I tried.
It's just that...
Arya's very important to
Varun and...
I just want to be the
fun aunt.
Sometimes,
I wish I could be
the fun aunt.
Work pressure,
mother's guilt,
household chores...
I wish I had one day...
...to just be me.
And not Arya's mamma.
I mean is it too much
to ask for?
Like just...
one fucking day!
I know what you're saying.
In all the roles we play,
whilst living for
everyone else,
we forget to live a little
for ourselves.
Maybe it's time we
reclaim that!
We all need to learn
how to please ourselves.
Did you just say that?
Ya!
I've done it.
I've bought myself
a vibrator.
How'd you do it?
Like did you have to
stick it in like a fire stick?
Dude! Clit play!
I'm going to make you
google vagina.
Seriously.
I know what a clit is!
Mostly Ms. VeeVee
won't need it.
My meet and greet is
about to begin.
Dude!
Oh my goodness!
You're the only person
who'd call an online date...
...a meet and greet!
Seriously!
But it is right?
Hey, hi!
How do you do?
Doggy style?
Missionary?
Anal?
Okay, so what role
are you going to play?
Is it going to be like
lost babe in the woods?
Or is it going to be like...
Come here! Let me teach
you a thing or two!
Hey! MPDG!
What is MPDG?
Sounds like a disease.
It kind of is.
Manic Pixie Dream Girl.
This bohemian dream
girl who writes poetry.
Can drink any guy
under the table.
And...who pees in
the streets.
Ya. She talks to
the clouds.
And whose IQ is like
that of a five-year old.
The one who dances
in the rain.
Wow!
Not for cardio.
Just because she's
free spirited!
They're like horny unicorns!
They have carefree sex and...
...then just like that,
they disappear.
Because commitment
is a myth.
Basically, every guy's
fantasy come true.
That's my fantasy as well.
Mangs,
they exist just so that
they can...
...save the hero from his
disgusting, boring life.
You are the antithesis
of that.
You live only for yourself, ok?
By the way, where can I
find these strange creatures?
Like in the zoo?
In books, films...shows.
Written by men.
Made by men.
For men.
Wow.
I can understand this...
...drinking-them-under-the-table
business, right?
But peeing in the streets?
I mean, c'mon!
I do Kegels.
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
Wow!
What is Kegels now?
Okay wait.
Who is Kegels?
Not who, what.
So basically, it's a pelvic flow
muscular exercise.
On the count of three,
clench and then release alright?
One, two, three...
Clench!
And then release.
One more time, clench!
Oh shit!
-Yes!
I think I just peed a little.
What!
Listen, you got your
peeing-on-the-streets fantasy!
Fuck! Finally!
Where should we head?
She has to pee!
I'm ok, I think.
I'm so hungry.
Let's go eat.
We have to find her
a loo!
Oh my God.
Did you read about
Karan and Shaina's love child?
Seriously, what the fuck!
I was so shocked!
This Investigator.com app
is so cool. See...
Show.
Check it out.
Amazing!
Where do they get
this stuff?
I know!
Damn cool!
Excuse me.
Ya?
Reading about people's affairs
and love children is not fun.
It's ridiculous.
I'm sorry?
You should be,
for reading crap like this.
Don't you read real news?
This is news.
Ya...
Investigator.com
used to be one of the...
...most trustworthy news
sites for the last three years.
And because of low IQ
dumbos like you,
we have to now publish
cheap gossip.
You should be ashamed
of yourself.
You know what?
Why don't you stop thinking
about who's fucking whom...
...and actually start
thinking about...
...how you think you're
fucking the system...
...but actually, it's the system
that's fucking you!
Idiots!
Hashtag weirdo!
Hey!
Oh hi...
How are you?
Good.
You...
Are you okay?
Ya...
You're crying...
I'm so sorry...
I'm so sorry.
What happened?
Oh my God.
This is so embarrassing.
-What's wrong?
I'm so sorry.
Is everything okay?
-Ya, ya...
I'm so sorry.
This doesn't happen to me.
-It's okay. It's alright.
It's alright.
Should I take you home?
I'll take you home.
Feeling better?
Ya...
Are you sure you're okay?
Damini...
You're my patient.
Not right now.
A woman has eight
erogenous zones.
The ear.
The neck.
The breasts.
Ouch!
Sorry you okay?
Ya ya...that's fine...go on.
Wait!
Those were...
...expensive.
The vagina.
The cervix.
And finally...
The piece de resistance...
What's that?
Getting to your...
G-spot.
Okay...
Here?
No...
Uh...not there either...
Here.
And they say the G-spot
is a myth.
We are done?
Well, today was about you.
Next time...
...will be about both of us.
Oh!
Okay.
Hi baby!
Check out the new books.
Hmm...
So you and Kavya are
bonding now?
I knew it.
She told you?
It's just a fucking vibrator.
I'm sorry, what?
Mom has a rocket
in her bag.
Wow!
From no sex to sex on tap?
Anj,
you're beginning to
worry me now.
Awww...
Don't be worried sweetheart.
I'm just an overworked,
single mom...
...whose ex-husband...
...doesn't contribute a
single penny.
Who thinks he's twenty
years old...
...and changes his girlfriend
every six months.
So I'm really sorry...
...if I decided to relieve
myself of...
...some of the stress.
Bye Arya!
Bye.
It's a date not a
meet and greet.
Ya, I'm meeting him
at the bar.
Dinner is too much
commitment.
If I don't like him,
I'll just say bye to him.
Besides I'm meeting a...
...meeting a new intern
for a job interview later.
Ya.
Hi!
Ok, I gotta go. Bye.
Hi.
I hope I didn't make
you wait too long...
No, not at all.
Okay.
Ya.
You're very good looking.
Your photo does you
no justice.
You look a lot younger
than your picture as well.
Well,
sue me for being hot.
So, is it your first time or...
...you're like a pro?
Actually, this is my
fourth meeting.
Window shopping?
No, I've actually just given a few...
It's alright.
I'm window shopping too.
I think we all deserve the best.
Of course.
Do you want to play
a little game?
Sure.
Boxers or briefs?
Legal briefs.
Nice...
Lawyer joke, nice!
Your turn.
My turn, right.
Civil or criminal?
Civil when you're nice...
and criminal...
...when you're dirty.
For fear of contempt of court.
Oh shit.
Shit, he's early.
Can you just give me
five minutes?
Ya.
-Ya?
And...
...order me a Chianti,
will you?
Ah...sure.
Don't be so nervous.
Just...
...imagine me without clothes.
You'll be fine.
Hi.
-I'm Anjana Menon.
Nice to meet you.
Please sit.
There is no need
for formality.
Actually it's my first time so...
Ah! Don't worry.
I'll teach you everything...
...as long as you are
willing to learn.
Ya, I'm more than willing.
Super. Let's get started.
Now?
Ya.
Okay, so...
...should we go to a hotel or...
Why a hotel?
Why not here?
Here?
You mean like...
...in the washroom?
Oh!
You need to go?
No.
Sorry I...
I'm a little confused.
Okay...
You know what?
Let's start afresh.
Ya.
-Ya?
Let's do that.
-So tell me about your strengths.
Okay.
So, I'm extremely fun loving.
Easy going.
I'm a great listener.
Right.
-Very caring.
And I...
...give the best
foot massages.
Okay!
And your weaknesses?
I don't have any.
I can go five times
in one night.
Let's start again.
Hi, I'm Anjana Menon,
Senior Associate at
Lalwani and Jhunjhunwalas.
Arjun...Nair.
It is an absolute pleasure
to meet you.
I'm a huge fan.
I have read all your
articles in Lawyers Today.
And I have also studied
your cases in NLS.
Thanks.
So did you hire the intern?
Obviously.
Else, he would've sued
me for sexual harassment.
See you Jeh...
Hey, no last order?
Nah, I'm done.
Hey listen,
I'm really sorry
I crossed the line.
When?
You know when
I said all that...
...biological clock nonsense.
Can I give you one advice?
Yes, tell me...
Please, never be a
stand-up comedian.
Bad jokes are in my genes.
If you ever come
to Goa to meet Xerxes...
...you'll see how crazy
my Parsi family is.
And how unfunny.
Seriously though, anytime.
I also make a mean fish curry.
Sold.
You always leave too soon.
I thought I always overstayed.
No, never.
Hey, hang on.
Irish single malt.
The best.
Stay?
Mamma!
God you scared me!
Look at the state you're in.
Are you drunk?
From tomorrow, you will
stop hanging out...
...with those loose girls.
Loose?
Mama, Umang works out
everyday.
She's so tight, you know...
It's no wonder even
Pavan rejected you.
Good riddance.
He wanted to suck
my toes.
So?
Some guys like toes
and some guys like breasts.
But if you keep rejecting
boys like this,
you'll be alone forever.
And if you don't get married,
what do you have Siddhi?
Do you even love me?
Excuse me?
You tore me up coming out
of me Siddhi!
Then why did you give
birth to me?
You should've had
an abortion!
Or you should've just handed
me over to Julie Didi!
Atleast she loved me!
All our problems would
be solved!
All our problems!
Julie?
The one who kept feeding
you cupcakes as a kid...
...and gave you so
many problems?
And you think she cared
for you more than I do?
Yes, she did.
I loved her more than
I will ever love you.
Infact I just...
...hate you!
Yes yes...you can hate
me all you like Siddhi!
But that won't get
you a nice boy to marry!
One meeting with that
Mohit boy...
...and he turned gay!
He chose men over you!
Shut up!
Just shut up Sneha!
You know what?
Maybe...just maybe...
...you should try eating
once in a while!
It might make you a
nicer person!
Julie Didi! Cheese toast!
Siddhi baby, salad.
Siddhi!
This is our new maid,
Lekha Didi.
Where's Julie Didi?
I had to fire her baby.
That witch had turned this
place into a cupcake factory.
C'mon, eat your salad.