In life, if you don't take a
few risks,
you haven't lived.
So every once in a while,
take off those shoes,
let go,
and dance on the edge.
What do you mean
you're pushing it?
I mean, we'll decide in a
few days.
How many days?
I don't know at this point.
What have you done this time...
...to make this boy run
away too?
I haven't done anything.
This boy was ready to
marry her today!
Now she's messed
this up as well.
I haven't done anything Mom!
Every single time, Siddhi.
Every time.
Why do you do this to me?
Don't you worry, Siddhi.
You want more time?
Take it.
Only once you're ready...
...will your father sign off on
your wedding checks.
Love you Papa.
Love you too my child.
Mamma...
Yes baby...
You're my best friend.
Even more than Teddoo.
And you're mine.
My sweetheart!
Umang,
have you thought
about getting married?
I'll do it.
All the other girls
your age are married.
I said I'll do it.
Really?
I hope you're not joking.
I've found the perfect boy for you.
His family is very wealthy.
Set up a meeting.
Pinky,
now all we need is
some good news from you.
Hey!
Hey.
I just dropped in to finish
off some editorial work.
Okay. Sure.
I'm sorry.
For what?
You know...
...replacing you.
No one can replace me.
Well,
good luck.
You too.
Is anyone going to say anything?
Seriously...
...how can you be so dumb?
Excuse me?
How can you put yourself in
such a compromising position, Siddhi?
Anj, have you lost your mind?
You're victim blaming?
That's just horribly
sexist and disgusting.
And that's very harsh
and presumptuous.
Guys, we're living in
a world full of shitty...
...misogynistic men who
are predators.
And until this thought
doesn't change,
we need to protect ourselves.
Why? Aren't we human?
Can't we, for once, do what
we want?
I did it for myself, okay.
Because it felt good.
And I'll do it again in a heartbeat.
So please, go ahead and
judge me like you always do.
I don't care.
Great.
Throw a tantrum.
Like you always do.
Siddhi, your Sneha hangover
makes you do stupid things...
...and then you suffer.
Ya?
Sneha's hangover is any day
better than Varun's hangover.
I don't give a fuck about
Varun okay!
I don't care!
Famous last words.
This is what happens when you sleep
with just one person your entire life.
At least I'm not sleeping around
with the whole world.
Like you.
Anj...
Between Arya, your child groom and
obsessing about that Kavya...
...you don't know whether
you're coming or going.
What exactly are you implying?
If you weren't so distracted,
we wouldn't have lost
all those cases...
...and I would still
have my fucking company.
And if you had fact checked...
...before putting out such
blasphemous articles...
...maybe you would still
have your fucking company.
Shut up guys!
Both of you!
All of you!
We came here to discuss
my problems right?
But, as usual, you've made it only
about yourselves.
You want to know why I
went onto SexyBods?
Because no one constantly
criticizes me there.
At home it's Sneha and out here,
it's you guys.
You know, for once...
...for once I felt good about myself.
Being a SexyBods girl has given
me more confidence...
...than all of you have
in the last three years.
So fuck this shit.
I don't need you guys.
I'll handle that bastard
on my own.
Shit.
Siddhi...
Hi, uncle.
What a surprise.
Come, sit.
I didn't know that you come here.
I haven't seen you here before.
We have a date, right?
Me and my soon to be daughter-in-law.
Babygirl.
I'm sorry, what?
Ever since I saw Babygirl
on that site for the first time,
I've been anxiously waiting
to meet her.
I kept wondering who it could be.
And then, right behind you...
...I spotted Sneha and
Viju's wedding photos.
That was it.
I instantly realised...
...who Babygirl is.
Aren't you ashamed?
Why?
I was only admiring you.
C'mon, Siddhi.
You're an adult.
Figure it out.
What is that supposed to mean?
Our society is such that...
...it makes us live two lives, Babygirl.
Stop it!
Stop calling me that.
Isn't that what you call yourself?
And I am on your side.
In fact,
in our entire family...
...if there's anyone who
can understand you,
it's me.
I'm not your family.
Nor will you ever be.
What?
Call off your engagement
with Mihir.
This is our secret.
And it will stay that way.
And if you still want your...
...'happily ever after'...
...then why just Mihir.
I'm available too.
You are sick.
You need help.
I see...
You're the one taking off your
clothes for strangers.
And I need help?
You bloody prostitute.
Siddhi's still here.
Isn't that Mihir's father?
You think you're going to
expose me?
I will expose you!
I don't want to be a part
of your family.
Sneha's made a family
WhatsApp group with all of us.
I'll post this on the group.
Poor Sneha.
Her engagement broke
years ago.
And now yours.
I fear...
...she may jump to her death.
You bastard!
How dare you talk about
my mother like that!
Siddhi! Leave him!
Asshole!
I'll kill that bastard!
It's been a pleasure meeting you,
Babygirl.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Bosco, can we get an
ice pack please...
Fuck this.
Siddhi, wait.
Please leave me alone.
I can't do this. I have to go.
I have to go too.
Awards ceremony.
So go! Who's stopping you!
Bosco, a double whiskey
straight up please.
Hey...
Drink?
No...
I have to leave.
There's an awards ceremony today.
I've been nominated.
For the troll story.
Congratulations.
So I was wondering if you...
...wanted to...
...go, I mean, come...
...I mean...
...go with me.
Damini, like this? Last moment?
To leave the bar?
I'm sorry but...
-Ya, ya, of course.
I understand. It's okay.
I'm sure you will win.
Fourth time lucky.
These are my so called 'friends'.
No, you should've seen the way
they were attacking me.
As if there's nothing likeable
about me.
Look,
I really want to hear everything.
But a two minute loo break?
Arjun...
-Please?
Such a mood breaker. Go.
I'll be right back, sorry.
Hey, Kavya...
All okay?
What?
Have you given her some medicine?
Cold compress?
A hundred and five?
Where is Varun?
What do you mean by you can't
get a hold of him?
You have the car?
Just...
You...you can't fucking drive!
Okay fine, you know what.
I'm coming, okay!
Just...
And the award goes to...
The Aurorus Media Group.
Damini...
I'm sorry to hear that they snatched
your company from you.
It's okay. I'm fine.
Well, good luck for the award then.
-Very well deserved guys. You guys have done...
...remarkable job.
-Thanks.
Fuck.
For our next award, I would like
to invite the Chairman of MD Group.
Mr. Rajiv Chopra.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome him on stage.
Pick up, Umang.
C'mon, Umang.
Believe it or not,
my sister Umang and
my wife Pinky...
...are best friends.
And very soon, we'll be
best friends as well.
Yes, of course, brother-in-law.
Cheers.
Are the 'tattus' real?
A horse is called 'tattu'.
These are tattoos.
You're very funny.
So many 'tattus'?
They must be fake.
They are.
I stick them on every morning.
Once we're married,
we'll get real ones.
Of each other's names.
I must say,
you have great biceps.
I deadlift a hundred and twenty kilos.
Every alternate day.
Wow!
Which means...
...after our marriage, my
personal training is guaranteed.
Oh. So I will be allowed
to work after marriage?
Yes, of course!
I'm not so narrow-minded.
Please take some more
butter chicken.
Your plate's empty.
Yes. Of course.
Pinky, will you please...
Pinky,
careful please...
It's alright.
Once you're married,
Umang will wash it off for you.
She's an expert at removing stains.
Not at all.
I will keep her like a princess.
We have plenty of staff at home.
Oh, my God.
Shocking news.
Samara Kapoor is a Lebanese.
Lebanese?
The shawarma?
Not Lebanese.
It's Lisbon. They're called Lisbon.
Lisbon. Okay.
Bizarre.
-Look at these photos.
She's locking lips with another girl.
Weren't Samara Kapoor
and Raghuveer getting married?
Did you see that film?
'Your Killed Me With Your Eyes'...
That's when Raghuveer
had an affair with his co-star.
The inevitable happened.
The wedding was called off.
These film stars...
They don't know the
meaning of decency.
This Samara Kapoor...
...is an immoral woman.
What is this Lebanese-Lisbon thing?
It means nothing, uncle.
It's a mental illness.
Enjoy your drink.
-It's the latest trend these days.
Some spiritual leader has
created a tonic...
...which can cure these Lisbons.
-Lesbian!
It's not Lisbon or Lebanese.
It's Lesbian!
And it's not a mental illness.
Umang, what are you ranting
on about?
Sit down!
All of you have so much fun...
...passing judgements on others!
Your own lives are so empty...
...that by demeaning someone else's life...
...you feel so good about yourself!
Each one of you is a hypocrite!
And I am the biggest
hypocrite of us all.
That girl with Samara Kapoor?
That's me.
Your daughter.
Your sister.
Is a lesbian, bi-sexual, queer,
part of the LGBT community.
You can label me as you like.
All I know is that...
I love Samara.
Does that mean...
...there's no chance of us
getting married?
From all the girls I've met,
you're the best.
I'm coming...
Anjana, I've called the doctor and...
...and Varun's also on his way.
Anjana, what are you doing?
I'm taking Arya to the hospital.
Anjana, listen to me.
You're drunk.
You're stinking of alcohol.
I'll book a cab, okay?
There's no time, Kavya.
-No, no, just...
I have to take her to the
hospital now.
Okay, just...
-Okay?
...just hold on, I'll come along
with you.
Anjana, let me at least
come with you!
And the award for Fearless
Journalist of the Year goes to...
...Damini Rizvi Roy
from Investigator.com.
For her scathing expose
on troll factories.
Few words, Damini.
Fearless Journalist award.
You know, the first time
I won this award,
I felt as if I had
conquered the world.
Then I got it a second time
and a third time.
It was like a rush that
I was addicted to.
To win it, I would work relentlessly
through the year.
But today...
...as I stand here holding
this for the fourth time...
...it feels...
...meaningless to me.
I stand here for a story that I wrote.
Ironically enough...
...I was removed from a
news organization I founded...
...for writing the very same story.
So then, what do these
awards really mean?
When all of us...
...have been reduced to
mere puppets...
...who do anything for ratings
and advertising revenues.
And moving along...
-I'm not done yet.
These foreign junkets, bonuses,
the free lunches,
will all come to an end.
The only thing that stays...
...is good journalism.
Don't let them take away
your integrity.
Don't sell out.
Because then,
shame on us.
Shame on us.
And now it's time for our next award...
-Yes.
It is indeed...
...time.
You can have this.
I'm done.
Arya!
Arya, please stay awake!
Please stay awake baby!
Please! We're almost there, okay!
C'mon! Please go!
Arya, please stay awake!
Please stay awake!
Arya!
The number you have dialled...
Please stop calling me.
Samara, please!
I'm leaving for Koh Samui tonight...
...for my last schedule.
Don't ever call me again.
Please, Umang.
Careful.
Just...just two minutes baby, okay?
You'll be fine in no time.
Then we'll go get an
ice cream, okay?
Arya!
Dadda...
Hi, baby...
Hi, my sweetheart...
Are you okay?
Hi, my little one...
What the fuck ya!
What if something happened
to Arya?
I had to drive her because
you had the car.
You could've taken a cab.
You should say this to Kavya!
She let Arya's temperature rise
to a hundred and five...
...waiting for your damn car.
You're the mother, Anjana!
But you're too busy...
...getting sloshed with your buddies!
-Yes!
Because I thought
my daughter was safe.
You need help, you know.
You've completely lost your mind.
Really?
And who are you?
Father of the year?
Where's the Anj I know?
You used to be the most
responsible person.
And now...
You're drinking all the time.
Drunk driving.
Hanging out with some moron
who's half your age!
What else are you into?
Drugs?
Do you even love our child any more?
-She is my life, Varun.
You know what...
...I've decided.
We're moving to Bangalore
and Arya's coming with us.
What?
Kavya's father offered me
a job in his ad agency.
At first, I thought maybe
we'll chat about joint custody.
But after seeing this shit, no way.
I want full custody.
Have you fucking lost it?
You are an unfit mother.
Where were you guys?
Arya's feeling much better.
Her fever's reduced.
"You know, sometimes I wish...
...I was Arya's aunt.
Not mother."
Isn't that what you said?
That's what she said, no baby?
You pretended to be my friend.
I said this to you in confidence, Kavya...
...and you're using it against me?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
Varun, that is out of context.
You...you can't just...
No, you can't!
You can't steal my family!
Have your own child!
Stay away from my daughter!
Anjana,
just calm down.
Please.
Arya is my daughter!
She is my life!
And she will stay with me!
Samara! Samara!
Who is your mystery lover?
Did you leave Raghuveer
Singh for this woman?
Samara, how long have you
been a lesbian?
No comments, thank you.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
-Ma'am, please comment!
Taxi!
Damini?
Look.
I don't know what this is
between us, okay, but...
...that day in Goa when...
...when we were
counting tiles together?
...I realized that no matter
what the situation,
you...
...you just sort me out.
Damini...
I feel good with you.
I feel better than good.
I feel fucking great and...
...and I can be myself with you,
you know.
With all my...
...quirks and...
...and my OCD shit and...
And you're funny and
kind and generous and...
...and the sex, I mean.
The sex, c'mon, it's...
Sometimes it's too good
to be true, right?
And you brought Xerxes
into my life.
Damini...
Do you know what the highlight
of my day is?
Staying back for that
extra drink with you.
Damini...
Jeh Wadia...
All I'm trying to say is that...
...I want to make this work.
I really,
really fucking do, okay?
What are you doing?
What are you...
-Stay away from her.
No, put her on the bed now, Anj...
-No, you stay away from her.
Anj... Anj she's unwell.
-Stay away from her.
Just put her...
-No, I'm taking her home.
I'm taking her home. Leave her.
-No, no, no... you can't do this.
Leave her. She's going with me. No!
-Let her go, Anj...
No! No! No!
-Baby, come here. Come, come...
Varun, leave her!
Varun, please stop!
Varun, please!
-You're scaring her.
Varun, please no!
-Leave her!
I said leave her!
Why don't you understand!
She's her mother!
Please stop him, Arjun!
They're taking my baby away!
Stop!
No!
Papa...
What is this?
Who are you?
Papa...
Siddhi.
Oh, my God, Jeh.
Nothing's changed here.
Can we please go home now?
Oh, I didn't realize we had company.
Hi, I'm Myra.
Sorry.