Most days, I'm Wonder Woman.
Invincible.
But some days, I'm not.
Everyone teaches us to be tough.
But why don't they teach us to
accept our vulnerabilities?
After all, who has created
these glass ceilings?
We did.
Us.
Women!
We feel we cannot break
through this glass ceiling.
But actually...
...if you believe...
…that there is no glass ceiling…
...then the sky is the limit.
Thank you so much.
Any questions?
Yes, Ms. Roy.
Hi, Uma.
I'm sorry but...
...did I just hear you say
what I think I did?
You really think that
women are hallucinating…
…about being held back by men?
All I am saying is that one
needs courage to be successful.
Not excuses.
Patriarchy is not some excuse.
Women have to work twice
as hard to reach half as far!
And this is the problem
with millennials…
…who look at everything from
a male vs female point of view.
When fighting for feminism, then yes.
Feminism is not about hating men.
Feminism means equality.
And this equality will only come…
…when we stop feeling
sorry for ourselves.
Papa, I made my first headline.
Really?
Breaking news!
The dining table has
brown sticky things underneath it.
Further investigations have revealed…
…that this is Ashok Rizvi Roy's booger.
Ashok?
No way Mom!
She's lying!
Mrs. Rizvi Roy,
would you like to check it yourself?
No! I believe you. Thank you!
Ashok Rizvi Roy…
…would you like to say
something in your defense?
When I grow up,
I'm going to be a journalist.
Just like my papa.
Ah!
There are my glasses.
Uma…
Hello.
I clearly remember
our first board meeting.
You said you were happy because...
...a woman was starting the company.
And now you're just
ganging up against me.
This is not some bus Damini…
…where you'll find a ladies seat.
I'm not asking for favours or handouts.
I'm asking for support,
woman to woman.
Support?
Ya!
I'm not your mother.
And please,
don't come to me with
your problems.
Come to me with your...
...solutions.
What are the solutions?
To undermine my editorial decisions?
Because the legal department
is just an excuse for you to censor me.
There is one solution, Damini.
Why don't you finally...
...take responsibility for your actions.
I take full responsibility Uma!
That's why I go after the lawbreakers
and offenders! You know that!
Oh…so you think you're a crusader?
You're a vigilante, girl.
There is a difference.
I'd rather be a vigilante
than be someone's puppet!
Stand up for me, Uma.
That's the least you can do.
I won't report a word
about this conversation...
...to our other board members.
And this…
This is me standing up for you.
Oh! Look who's here!
My baby!
Did you have fun at Dadda's?
Yes!
What did you do?
One big poo and three little poo.
Oh my god!
We also went to the park…
...and we went swimming.
Wow!
But nothing is as exciting as a poo.
You can never compete with a
good poo, right Arya?
Here you go…
Dadda, doll house.
Oh yes! Doll house!
C'mon! C'mon!
May I go up?
Yes? Oh my God. C'mon!
Let's go before she changes her mind.
Anjana!
Hi!
Hi.
I'm...I'm Kavya.
Of course!
Hi Kavya…Hi…
I'm sorry, I didn't realise
there was someone in the car.
That's not your fault.
I mean brown dress…
...brown car upholstery.
Who even wears brown right?
Actually, I told Varun that I
will get camouflaged with the car seat
But he said that the brown
really brings out the color of my eyes.
Oh really?
He said that?
Ya, I know right?
By the way,
it's really nice to meet you finally…
…and I hope Arya didn't
trouble you too much.
No, no, she's such a doll!
And she's got a great sense of humour…
Smart and witty and...
...she picks up things so quickly!
I mean…I know…I'm her mother.
Oh and by the way, before I forget…
She wanted me to give you
the recipe of this ragi dosa…
And it's just…
Actually, it's very simple.
I'm sure you know…
Only don't forget to add
jaggery and butter on top.
She just…she loves that.
Thanks.
Wow…friends already?
Of course.
In fact, do you want to
do lunch sometime next week?
Sassy Spoon? Ya?
Ya…
It's close to our office...
...and we can exchange
notes about Mr Grumpy here.
He's so grumpy from the minute
he wakes up!
I am not grumpy. I'm chirpy.
No, of course you're not!
He's not…
Okay, so before you
guys become besties and all…
…we gotta go. Bye.
Bye.
See you.
It's so nice to meet you.
You're so sweet.
What a bitch.
With inspiration like this,
anyone can make six packs.
C'mon, five more.
I'm from Haryana.
Hot blood.
Give me one chance,
you won't regret it.
That's it.
Session over.
Did you get offended?
Oh my god!
Die! Bastard!
Fucking bitch!
Umang, we have security footage.
There's enough evidence.
They could sue us for
willfully harming a person.
That wasn't wilful.
He forced himself.
Didn't you see that?
Everyone knows what's
going on with you and Amit.
So he must've thought
you're easily available.
You can't demand respect, Umang.
You have to earn it.
I don't want respect
from these fuckers.
Tell them to keep their hands
off me and their junk in their pants.
Then, perhaps, you should also
learn how to keep your legs together.
You don't like that you're
a woman?
Do you hate yourself for it?
Didn't your parents love
you growing up?
Sorry, what?
Please transfer my
salary to my account.
I quit.
Umang, come back here.
Excuse me, where is the
beginner's ballet class?
3rd door.
Ok. Thank you.
By the way, parents are not
allowed to stay with their kids.
I should hope so.
Hi.
This is the ballet class, right?
Yes.
The class will start in 5 minutes.
Please leave your child there.
What child?
Kid.
Kit?
Of course, I have my kit!
No ma'am, kid.
Good afternoon, sir!
Good afternoon.
New ballet teacher?
She looks stupid to me.
I don't like her.
I'm going to tell my mom.
I'm not your ballet teacher,
I'm Siddhi Patel.
And I've also enrolled for this class.
Ma'am, this is beginner's ballet.
So? I'm no Anna Pavlova.
I mean for kids between 6 and 10.
What?!
Yes.
But…but your website
didn't mention that!
God, Sneha's going to kill me.
Shit! I even sent my driver back!
What do I do here now?
Sir, but why can't she
also take class with us?
No, but...
Yes!
Sir, please!
Okay, okay, quickly go change.
And 5, 6, 7, 8 and point...
Bring it back.
Plie.
And up.
And up 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
And open.
3, 4…Plie.
Repeat.
And point.
And back.
Plie.
And...releve.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
And open 2, 3, 4...
There's no glass ceiling.
We're all just imagining our problems!
She is so fake!
You can't even tell she's faking it!
She calls herself a liberal...
...but she thinks like a conservative!
Even the colour of her eye is fake!
What is that!
This is me standing up for you,
she says!
If liberals are like this I wonder
what a conservative is!
Her nose is definitely fake!
There is no glass ceiling!
This is a woman's world,
where men take women's last names!
Ladies.
Getting drunk in
the middle of a workday.
I'm confused.
Should I be happy or worried?
Worried.
Happy.
Muddied.
Bloodied.
Ok guys,
I know that currently
the villain in your life…
…is another woman.
Just like Sneha is mine.
But.
To tell you the truth…
Your cribbing?
It makes my world go round.
I mean, whenever
I hear you guys blabber…
I feel like I'm home.
And that…all is well with the world.
Awww.
All is well with the world!
Cheers!
The board, our own people,
want to censor us.
So what should we do?
Should we be scared?
Should we just sit idle?
Never.
We are going to go all out
with the kind of...
...journalism Investigator.com
is known for.
Bold, shocking, ballsy
fucking stories!
We are going to investigate
the hell out of Investigator.com!
Are you guys with me?
Yes.
Louder people!
Yes!
Good!
So give me those fucking stories!
I have one…
Walia’s extradition.
Who is protecting him?
Meth.
The new weight loss drug.
How deep is the
doctor-cops-drug dealer nexus?
On one hand,
we're becoming the world's
number one rape country...
and on the other hand,
women can’t even protest
against rape...
without being violently
attacked!
That's our story Asha.
Let's give women a voice
to express their dissent.
Let us be their voice.
Asha…you’re going to lead the story.
Get to work!
Umang.
Umang!
Please spare me.
I don't want any advice.
Not advice.
I've come to congratulate you.
You're a rock solid woman.
Truly, respect.
Are you playing with me?
I'm in no mood for a joke.
There's a private client.
Very elite.
She has rejected everyone.
She needs a hardcore trainer
like you for personal training.
They say they need
a personal trainer...
...but they end up treating
you like a personal assistant.
It's a lot of money.
And you'll have to travel
with the client as well.
Set life.
Give me the number.
It's a high profile client.
I'll pass on your message
to her team.
They'll get in touch with you.
You know, you don't look
it but you're a pretty stand-up guy.
Was that an abuse or a compliment?
You're the one who comes
to me to get tortured!
Kavya, where are the depositions?
What? I am talking to you!
Ma'am, me?
Yes.
But ma'am, I'm Prachi.
And that's what I said.
No, ma'am. You said Kavya.
I'm…I'm so sorry.
Prachi, right?
You know Kavya was my
previous associate so...
...just a little confusion.
Can I have the deposition, please?
Sure ma'am.
Two weeks.
My periods are two weeks late.
They're never late.
I'm not pregnant.
Unless it's an immaculate conception.
Don't worry, you're not pregnant.
Thank God!
Not that I have a problem
with babies.
I don't mind babies.
I like babies.
But tell me something…
…why do all women
need to feel maternal?
I think perpetuating the myth
of the maternal instinct...
...actually harms women.
And impairs their growth.
Don't you think?
I know I'm a gynac but as
a doctor can I ask you a question?
Sure.
When was the first time
you started exhibiting...
...signs of compulsive behavior?
Like this?
I just don't...
You know what…as a Muslim,
I've never felt like a minority.
But as a woman I have.
Amina, c'mon...
Arundhati Roy has
just now won the Booker.
Ya…Diana Haydon is
Ms. World.
Phoolan Devi just got
elected to parliament.
Ya…
Indian women are everywhere.
Please.
Three women amongst a million men.
And we should celebrate!
We can't even sell a car
without a half naked woman.
Women are looked upon
as sexual beings!
Look at the kind of
songs we have.
"You bloody sexy thing!"
Damini, what do you
have to say to this?
C'mon, Mahesh. She's just a child.
What would she know?
No, no, we don't differentiate
in this house. Right?
Mama…I'm hungry.
Food's ready in the kitchen,
sweetheart.
Go have it. Good girl.
So I'm going to recommend…
…a therapist.
A therapist?
Yep.
As in a shrink?
I don't need a shrink.
It's my shitty hormones
and vagina that need fixing.
Not my brain.
Your vagina is fine.
It's perfect.
To a great first date.
Proost!
Proost means cheers in Dutch.
Oh...
Okay…
You know, I mean I just love to travel.
Like especially since I
got that new chartered airplane.
You know my friend's dad
also owns one.
Yeah well,
you know, that's the difference.
I'm a self-made man, Sindhi.
Siddhi.
Siddhi, ya of course.
Look, to be honest Siddhi…
Everytime I come to India…
…my parents set me
up with some eligible girl.
But somehow I've never really
found someone who truly gets me.
Like the real me.
You know what I'm saying?
I think I need to meet someone
who knows where I've come from…
…and where I'm going.
Hibiscus. Have you heard of us?
Not really.
But, you know, my friend Damini?
She has her own company…
Yeah, well I mean, I'm sure
that's great for her here in Mumbai…
…but babe, you're really
nothing till you haven't...
...made it big in Silicon Valley.
I mean, c'mon…
Oh…okay.
It's like, you know,
Mark is my neighbor.
Mark?
Zuckerberg? Facebook?
Really?!
Ya.
So do you guys like
hang out and stuff?
Well, we go to the
same coffee shop.
So do Salman and I
but we're not friends.
Rushdie?
Khan.
Salman Khan?
I hate Bollywood.
You know, as a kid,
when I used to travel to America…
…I used to love sticking
my head out of the sunroof.
Driver, sunroof.
Really?!
Ya.
God! Your feet are so beautiful!
If your feet were on a
dating app…
…you'd get maximum right
swipes baby!
Owww! What the fuck!
Oh my God! I'm so sorry!
I really didn't mean to… shit!
Blood! Blood!
I think you've broken my nose,
you psycho!
Oops.
What am I going to do?
I love my nose!
According to Leonardo
Da Vinci's golden ratio…
…my nose is perfect for my face!
Listen, relax! It's just a nose bleed!
What?! Are you crazy?!
What if it's permanently damaged?!
God!
What are you doing?!
I don't have a tissue
but here…use this.
Oh my God. No!
You want me to put this
on my face?!
It's not used.
Driver, stop the car.
Seriously?
Shut up!
What did you tell Sneha?
Simple.
That Pawan is a non vegetarian.
And will expect the
same from me after marriage.
Shame…
John Mayer has said
'My body is a wonderland'.
How can I just defile…
Ooh! Chicken wings!
By the way,
Kavya called Varun Mr. Grumpy.
Anj, you're still
obsessing with that girl.
She is playing a game
with me and I will not…
Shit!
Woah!
I'm so sorry. My bad!
Nice catch, Jeh.
Guys! Samara Kapoor!
Guess who yelled at her…
And I still feel shit about it.
She is my childhood crush.
I love her!
I mean she's bubbly,
she's pretty, she's hot…
I wish I could
take her to the fields...
...and do some body
weight exercises with her!
One more time.
I've got the trick now.
Siddhi, c'mon do something.
Something.
Sneha!
Look up and smile bitches!
Hey, all good?
What?
Nothing.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Ya...
How come you've been
hanging back here lately?
Is that a problem?
No, no. Not at all.
Of course not. I'm...
I'm just curious.
I've just been stressed
with work lately…
And I guess I don't
feel like going back...
...to that empty house
all alone anymore.
The walls feel like they're...
...closing in on me.
You know what I mean?
Trust me, I do.
The Japanese have invented something.
It's called the
boyfriend-girlfriend coat.
So you wear it and…
then it hugs you and…
...asks you how your day was.
I should leave.
No wait.
Hang on.
What?
Japanese single malt.
To the dichotomy of living alone.
Can't live with someone…
Can't live without someone?
Cheers.
I love it.
Hi Anj…
Hey…
She sleeping?
Ya...
What's going on?
You want to come in?
No, I'm sorry I…
…I shouldn't be disturbing
you at this hour.
Look...
Kavya's not home.
Please.
Just come inside.
Don't be so formal.
Coffee?
The one thing I did well…
...when we were married.
No, I'm fine.
Come.
Actually, we were watching TV…
…there were these cartoons on.
And she fell asleep here so...
It's…
It's okay.
Sit.
Sometimes I can't believe
she's ours.
Remember as a baby how
she would sleep?
Those little froggy legs.
And her arms by the side
of her head.
She's too beautiful.
And we created that.
Can you imagine?
We.
The two of us.
Two complete nutcases…
…created that.
Shit. I totally forgot to tell you.
Kavya had written
down that dosa recipe.
And she said to give it to you.
You know, I think I'll just
book a cab.
I have like a 9am meeting.
Ya?
Ya.
You sure?
Rish.
Hi…
Hi, hottie.
When did you get into town?
Just this weekend.
A message would've been nice.
Ya but this is so much
more spontaneous.
And…
Sexy.
Did you come?
Nope.
No?
Okay...
Every time.
How's work?
Same old, same old.
Always the secretive Damini.
Rishabh…
Let me stay tonight…
You know me.
You know how I am…
Ya...I know.
I know.