[birds chirping]
[gun cocks]
[gunshot]
[tense music]
[birds tweet]
[panting]
[Caitlyn breathes heavily]
[breathes deeply]
-Hmm.
-[distant gunshot]
[Caitlyn pants]
[grunts]
[huffs]
[bullet whooshes]
[pants]
-[cork pops]
-[whistles]
[indistinct chatter]
[crowd laugh]
[birds whistle, chirp]
[background chatter]
[Grayson]
That was quite some shooting, Kiramman.
Did my parents pay you to let me win?
Hmm… That's a serious accusation.
You held your shot, I saw you.
The trophy is yours. You earned it.
You haven't answered my question.
[chuckles]
No, your parents didn't pay me.
I just thought you deserved it.
[breathes deeply]
I'm an enforcer.
For me, knowing how to handle this weapon
means being able to protect people.
To be of service to the city.
And that's trophy enough.
Begs the question, young Kiramman.
What are you shooting for?
[birds cawing]
[eerie music]
[Caitlyn] I took a look at your file.
There's no record of you or your crimes.
What are you here for?
[Vi] My sunny personality.
You attacked an inmate. Why?
[Vi] Why not?
He was a witness
in an ongoing investigation.
[Vi] Hmm, bummer.
[sighs]
This was a waste of time.
[Vi] Couldn't have put it better.
Hey, give Silco a kiss
on that winning eye of his, will you?
[sighs]
Silco? The industrialist?
Okay, this is getting old.
Can you just send in whoever's gonna kick
the shit out of me,
so I can get on with my night?
[sighs]
Does this mean anything to you?
[suspenseful music plays]
-[gasps]
-Where did you get this?
[exhales]
-My question first. He worked for Silco?
-Uh, they all do.
How can anyone not know that?
Where did you find this?
There was an attack. This is evidence.
I need proof if I'm to believe
what you're saying about Silco.
[scoffs]
I could get it for you.
Just not from in here.
[snickers]
In what mad world
would I trust someone like you?
Someone like me?
You enforcers are all the same.
Just asshole criminals in fancy uniforms.
You know what? Find Silco yourself.
I will, thank you.
Hmm… Undercity's gonna eat you alive.
[breathes deeply]
I've got orders from Councilor Talis,
concerning Inmate 516.
[chuckles]
Not cooperative, huh?
You, uh, you want us
to have a chat with her?
-No.
-Oh.
It's for her release.
Huh. Since when's he a Councilor?
Since today.
[scoffs]
How many chats have you had with her?
You know, I never even thought to count.
-[metal clanging]
-[breathes heavily]
[gate clanking, bangs]
[sighs]
["Enemy" by Imagine Dragons playing]
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that arouse ♪
♪ From my mind to run around
Put my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that I told ♪
♪ My back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
[somber music plays]
[Marcus] These brave Enforcers
sacrificed their lives
to defend the values of our great city.
To some, they are mothers…
fathers, sons…
daughters…
but to all, they are heroes.
[rifles cock]
-[rifles fire]
-[crows caw]
[somber music continues]
[rifles firing]
Who was this, Daddy?
A good woman.
[gun fires]
You said you could control her.
I lost six officers. Six!
She pushed it too far this time.
The Council's up in arms.
I can't make this go away for you
unless you give me something to work with.
-Arresting her would be doing you a favor.
-[rasps]
I don't need favors.
I need you to do your job.
-[lighter clinks]
-[flame sizzles]
[puffs]
The Firelights have been a thorn
in both our sides.
They ambushed my shipment at the Hexgates
on the same day as the attack.
It seems to me
the Council has its culprit.
Oh, that's tidy for you.
What if I'm not interested
in playing along?
We've accomplished a lot together, Marcus.
Sheriff.
And there is more yet to achieve.
I hope you can remain a part of it.
For their families.
From an anonymous, concerned citizen.
-[grunts softly]
-[chair scrapes]
[door opens, door closes]
[huffs]
[Jayce]
Yesterday's smuggling fiasco was nothing.
These manifests are full of discrepancies,
dating back months.
[Viktor] This is a poor use of our time.
I'm a Councilor now, Viktor.
It's my responsibility to make sure
the Hexgates are safe and protected.
What about our pledge to improve lives,
for those in need? For the undercity?
[sighs]
Look, I'm sorry I didn't announce
our other projects in my speech.
-Soon, we can do everything we--
-Soon?
There are people
who need our help now, Jayce.
[Marcus] You wanted to see me?
Have your people ever reviewed these logs?
-Mr. Talis, I assure you--
-Councilor.
And the only assurance I need is that
you will search and seize
any unauthorized merchandise.
I've made a list
of suspicious transactions.
All due respect, Councilor,
-today's your first day--
-Second.
[stammers]
Right.
You sure you don't want to confer
with the other Councilors before--
[Jayce]
This corruption runs deep, Sheriff.
I intend to root it out.
Have you made any progress
with the stolen Gemstone?
-Yes. Chief suspect is an undercity gang.
-[coughing]
[Marcus]
They call themselves the Firelights.
They operate like phantoms,
doing hit-and-runs on civilians
and disappearing into the night.
-[Jayce] How soon till we track them down?
-[Marcus] I've got my best officers on it.
[muffled chatter]
[mysterious music]
Viktor? You all right?
A… a headache. I just…
I need to get to the lab.
[rock music plays]
[Jinx] Boring…
Boring. Wow. Super boring…
Here we go!
It's all about these runes.
They form some kind of math-y,
magic-y gateway.
To the realm of heebie-jeebies.
And this… Turns it on.
So… here goes.
[huffs]
[groans]
[suspenseful music]
[panting]
[crackles]
[sobs]
No!
No! It was a mistake! It was a mistake.
[crackles]
-[sighs]
-[train chugging]
[train bell dings]
[Caitlyn]
I heard the bathysphere has a nice view.
That could be a good way
to get a lay of the land.
Too risky.
What…
[grunts]
[Vi grumbles]
[scoffs]
[grunts]
[groans]
[action music plays]
[action music continues]
[panting]
[Vi grunts]
-[sighs]
-[man 1 whistles]
[woman breathes heavily]
[woman chuckles]
-[puffs]
-Nice jacket.
[gasps]
[panting]
-[man groaning]
-[Caitlyn breathing heavily]
[grunts]
Welcome to the Lanes.
You almost got me killed.
My little sister could do that
when she was seven.
All us fissure folk can.
Don't you want to blend in?
[man 1 groans]
[mysterious music]
[Jayce] You had a vision?
What if we've been looking at it
backwards?
[Viktor] We've been trying to discover
runes that invoke specific effects
and then molding them
to a useful function.
Tools, as you like to put it. But, but…
If the legends are true,
mages aren't bound to single functions.
It's said the Arcane speaks through them.
I'm still not following.
[Viktor] They think. They adapt.
You think Hextech can… learn?
Are you sure this is safe?
Of course not.
[festive music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
[slurping]
Oh, Jericho! Have I missed these.
[Jericho gibbers]
[laughs]
[Vi] Hmm?
No. Thank you.
You're missing out.
Are you going to question him?
About what? The meat?
Definitely not above board.
Silco. His connections?
Isn't that why we're here?
We're here because I'm hungry.
Do you know what prison food is like?
No, of course, you don't.
Unbelievable. I didn't break you
out of jail to eat… slop.
I knew this was a terrible idea.
You don't actually know anything, do you?
Mm. Better than I remember.
[gibbering]
[crowd chattering, laughing]
[Caitlyn] Hmm.
[violin music playing]
[Jayce] I haven't been here in years.
Since my parents brought me
for the winter fest.
We're not here for the performance.
Your House is in trouble.
That merchant formerly enjoyed
certain leniencies
with regard to her trade in exchange
for her generous Academy patronage.
By leniencies you mean corruption?
Hmm, Amara's harmless.
Oh, look at those two stooges.
Councilors Hoskel and Salo.
Don't they hate each other?
Hmm. But they share a taste
for the finer Noxian spirits,
technically an illegal import.
I tightened our security.
And in so doing,
put a target on your back.
There are those who covet your power
over the wealth the Hexgates afford.
And would take any opportunity
to seize it from you.
You've just made yourself
everyone's common enemy, Jayce.
[violin music continues]
[Jinx sighs]
[mysterious music]
[metal clanks]
[sniffles]
[scrapes]
[exhales]
[Claggor] Oh, what's the matter, Mylo?
You worried Powder's gonna beat you again.
[echoes]
[crow chirps]
[crow caws]
[chuckles]
[huffs]
[Vi grunts]
-[puffs]
-[metal clanks]
-[grunts]
-[machine powering up]
[Vi] Vander.
Because you're a jinx!
[grunting]
[indistinct yelling]
What makes you different makes you strong.
[grunts]
[grunting continues]
[screams]
[groans]
[yells]
[shrieks]
[panting]
[metal clanks]
[panting continues]
[groans]
[upbeat music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
[man 1 talking indistinctly]
-[man 2 grunts]
-[man 1 groans]
[Vi] Hmm.
Well, that place does look like
it has bodies buried in the basement.
[Vi breathes heavily]
You don't know anything.
[gasps]
[playing violin]
[Jayce] I can't compromise the safety
of the Hexgates for collateral.
No one's asking you to.
These are simply favors amongst friends.
I never wanted anything to do
with politics. You pushed this on me.
You're a symbol of the future now, Jayce,
whether you like it or not.
With that comes the potential
to shape your own destiny.
The Council assumes you'll fail.
Time to prove them all wrong. Once again.
[Mel] Welcome, Amara. How's little Rohan?
[Amara]
Councilor Medarda. Councilor Talis.
[scoffs]
He's just as precocious as ever.
[Amara and Mel chuckle]
I had quite a shock this morning.
Enforcers banging on my door.
[Mel] Oh, I hope you'll understand,
Jayce had to make a show of safety.
But he's here now to negotiate
all his deals personally.
Councilor Talis is willing to reinstate
former trade privileges
to those who share his vision.
Can we count you amongst them?
Councilor Bolbok seems to think other
arrangements would be more profitable.
[scoffs]
The man's a fool.
With him, you'd be investing in the past.
With us, you'd be investing in the future.
[breathes sharply]
You know, Councilor Medarda's right.
The Hexgates are only the beginning.
In fact, we're currently looking
for new partners in our Hextech research,
and as a supporter of House Talis,
you'd be the first in line
to any of our advancements.
[playing violin continues]
How can I say no
to such an auspicious offer?
Hextech partners?
Has a nice ring, doesn't it?
Mm. Your audience awaits, Councilor.
He's been quite the investment.
Indeed. Better than expected.
[playing violin intensely]
[inaudible]
[clinks]
-[applause]
-[pants]
[crowd cheering]
[chuckles]
[knocks on door]
[Caitlyn clears throat]
[guard groans]
[rasps]
-[lock clicks]
-[door opens]
[wicked laughter in distance]
The one place all the secrets are spilled.
[sighs]
-[woman 1 chuckles]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[inhaling]
-[dog whimpers]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[gasps]
[woman 3] Oh.
[giggles]
How exactly do you propose
we go about this?
-[humanoid humming]
-[Vi] Let 'em think you work here.
Excuse me?
I will not.
You know what your problem is?
Please. Tell me.
You expect everyone
to give you what you want.
If you really want people to talk to you,
you have to let them think
you have what they want.
And what do I have?
You're hot, cupcake.
[gasps]
So what'll it be, man or woman?
-Um… [stammers]
-[woman 4 pants]
Hi.
[stammers]
I'm Pim. What's your name?
Matilda. But you can call her
whatever you want.
[gasps]
Ah, yes. Matilda.
My parents named me Matilda.
After my great-grandmother Matilda,
the, uh…
Would you believe it?
[indistinct chatter]
[coin clinks]
[groans]
Sheriff, what a lovely surprise.
The Hextech wonder boy
is on the Council now,
and he's asking questions.
It's only a matter of time
before he finds the truth.
What is truth, but a survivor's story?
If I'm discovered, we're both finished.
Good thing you've located proof
of the Firelights' involvement.
This has gone too far.
Hmm? Imagining yourself a hero?
One final act to make you the martyr
you've always seen yourself as?
-[Silco chuckles]
-[pants, yells]
[explosion]
[muffled rumbling]
[Silco] Then what are you waiting for?
[sighs]
[door opens]
-Ah, he's faltering.
-[door closes]
You need to weaponize the Hextech soon.
Once we've cracked their prize,
topside will have no power over us.
I can't do it.
Just… give it to the doctor.
You're the only one
I can trust with this, Jinx.
I keep… seeing them. That day.
Fear haunts us all, child.
Sweetheart, I was real sad
to hear about Vander.
And the kids. Just terrible.
By the looks of it, no one down here
lifted a finger to stop Silco.
A few tried but Silco's got the muscle…
and the money.
He took over the Last Drop.
I saw.
Things have changed
without Vander looking out for us.
Have you heard anything about Powder?
I think Silco has her.
I have to find her.
Silco's number two's a regular.
I can have Miguel tell you
where to find her.
I owe you.
It's nothing.
-[woman 1 laughs]
-[Caitlyn giggles]
[woman 2]
I've only ever imagined the gardens…
[chuckles]
This is all I've seen.
[scoffs]
You did well today.
I had a good teacher.
It's only a matter of time
before those old fools on the Council
-officially accept your research.
-[sighs]
My father put hammers
in the hands of the people,
and they built this magnificent city.
Imagine the wonders they could create
if we put magic in their hands.
The world will never be the same.
The Medardas usually only take
from the world.
We're not often in the position
to give anything back.
I couldn't have done it without you.
[Mel] Hmm.
[moans]
[rumbles]
[sizzles]
[clanking]
It's beautiful.
I can't figure out why it's not working.
You will.
Are you headed home soon?
I thought we could walk together.
I'm, uh, probably going
to sleep here tonight.
Again? You know
there's always tomorrow, right?
[Viktor] Good night, Miss Young.
[sighs]
[chimes, whirs]
[Mel moans]
[clanks]
[dramatic music plays]
[groans]
[gasps]
[disembodied voices]
[coughing]
[body thuds]
[cane clanks]
Mm.
[crackling]
[tranquil music]
[thunder rumbling]
[Silco] I almost drowned in these waters.
[Jinx] You told me a million times.
[Silco] Vander wasn't the man
you thought he was.
Right, he was like a brother to you,
and he turned his back
and blah, blah, blah.
Did I miss anything?
[snickers]
I've got a new one for you.
[water dripping]
That day, I let a weak man die.
[water sloshing]
And another was reborn.
Betrayal, that pain that feels like
it'll eat you from the inside out,
can either break you or forge you
into something greater.
You need to let Powder die.
So the fear of pain
will no longer control you.
[thunder rumbles]
You're strong now.
Just like you were always meant to be.
Jinx is perfect.
[mysterious music]
[exhales]
[water burbling]
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that arouse ♪
♪ From my mind to run around
Put my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that I told ♪
♪ My back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
[grunts]
♪ Spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ But I'm ready ♪
♪ Your words up on the wall
As you'rе prayin' for my fall ♪
♪ And the laughter in thе halls
And the names that I've been called ♪
♪ I stuck it in my mind
And I'm waiting for the time ♪
♪ When I show you what it's like
To be worse than am I ♪
[Marcus yells]
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
[Viktor breathing deeply]
Jayce?
Viktor, the doctors, um, they said you're…
[exhales]
How much time do I have?
Rotten luck, boys!
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
-[both gasp]
-[crowd clamoring]
Vi?
[both grunt]
-[Vi screams]
-[Sevika groans]
You filthy traitor.
Vander had his chance.
[both grunt]
[gasps]
[both grumbling]
I see you never learned patience.
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[Vi grunts]
[groans, growls]
-[grunting]
-[clanks]
[yelps]
[Sevika grumbles]
[Vi groaning]
[grunts]
[both grumble]
[Vi breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[Vi grunts]
[Vi grunts, screams]
[breathing heavily]
[both grunt]
[clatters]
[Sevika spits]
[groans]
[Vi] Where's my sister?
Where's he keeping her?
Keeping her? You mean Jinx?
She works for him.
-[gasps]
-[breathes heavily]
-[grunts]
-[Sevika pants]
She's like his daughter.
[Vi groans]
[pants]
I'll give her your regards.
[gunshot]
[tense music plays]
[groans]
[Vi] Why did you let her go?
Do you ever say "thank you?"
-He's gonna know we're here now.
-Whose fault is that?
You're an all-right shot.
I'm an excellent shot.
[Vi sighs]
You gonna help me out, cupcake?
Stop calling me that. My name is Caitlyn.
[Vi grunts]
But you're so sweet.
Like a cupcake.
[Caitlyn chuckles]
Shut up.
[rock music plays]
[sizzling]
You're making a mess.
[Sevika] The sister.
She's back.
From the dead?
[dramatic music plays]