I knew it was a mistake trusting you.
You've been a real picnic yourself.
I'm not the one who walked us
into, not one, but two of Silco's traps.
This isn't Silco, it's someone else.
How do you know?
'Cause we'd already be dead.
Oh, very nice.
When were you planning to tell me
that your lunatic sister works for him?
Just as soon as you came clean about
what the hell
you're really doing down here.
- I told you the truth.
- Bullshit.
What was that glowing stone?
That's what I thought.
What's going on?
- Hey, stop! Get your hands off of me!
- Leave her alone!
- Let me go!
- Vi?
Vi!
Hey.
You shy? Or just ugly?
You look good for a dead girl.
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that arouse ♪
♪ From my mind to run around
Put my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that I told ♪
♪ My back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
Ekko?
What do you know about this?
Nothing. What the hell is this all about?
What were you doing with Jinx?
Her name is Powder.
And I just found her
when you and your goons showed up.
It's me. Vi.
Same person who used to take you down
to the junk heap
and hose you down
when you got covered in grease.
That was a long time ago.
People change.
Yeah. I'm getting that.
Are you working for Silco?
Fuck. You.
I thought you were dead.
Now you show up with a Piltie
and give her a tour of the Lanes?
You were following us?
Why didn't you say something?
I didn't know if I could trust you.
So... so you just come out swinging?
Gee, I wonder who I learned that from?
Ah, well, you shoulda learned more.
You still punch like a little boy.
And you still block with your face.
I remember when
you wouldn't stand up to me.
I missed you, little man.
How long have you had those off?
How long have you been whining?
Hmm. Fascinating.
I would very much like to see the device.
This, uh, Hexcore.
That may be difficult to arrange.
I've tried every combination of runes,
but... it's always the same.
The subject, wither and rot.
Uh, perhaps the error resides
not with your calculations but...
with your subjects.
Nature has made us intolerant to change,
but fortunately,
we have the capacity to change our nature.
- And this is... Shimmer?
- A variant.
It should provide everything one needs
to survive a violent transition.
Will it work on plants?
You aren't here about the plants, are you?
I know the look of a doomed man.
I must warn you.
If you take this path,
they will despise you.
Love and legacy are
the sacrifices we make for progress.
It's why I parted ways with Heimerdinger.
- Jayce will understand.
- Perhaps.
Hammer work is such a delicate art.
How'd you find me?
You're the de facto head of the Council.
People notice where you go.
Huh. Don't remind me.
This border shutdown
has people agitated.
They should be.
Marcus brought this to me.
It's an explosive.
I tried taking it apart
and it nearly killed me.
Whoever built it
knows exactly what they're doing.
This and Shimmer. It's hard to believe
what they're capable of.
Is that what's really bothering you?
He was my mentor, Mel. And I betrayed him.
Everything you said about him was true.
My family cast me out
and yet, part of me still loves them.
Heimerdinger will understand eventually.
It's your time now, Jayce.
No more red tape.
You can bring Hextech to the masses,
just like you've always dreamed.
Hmm. First, I have to save Viktor.
Where is he?
I don't know.
He disappeared.
He does that sometimes.
- No sign of Caitlyn either.
- The Kiramman girl?
It's just...
- Uh, never mind.
- Hey. We'll get through this.
I'll stall the Council
but they'll soon need their leader.
In the meantime...
Try not to lose your nuts.
All our business is down. Enforcers are
searching anyone who crosses the bridge.
Marcus is following my orders.
Preventing Vi and Caitlyn from returning.
Or he's finally flipped.
Hmm.
The chembarons scheduled an assembly.
Oh.
- I've had enough headaches.
- It didn't sound like a request.
Where are you going?
I need to find Jinx.
- Sir.
- What?
I got more in common
with cave lice than Jinx.
But let's just say I didn't always see
eye-to-eye with my old man.
And?
She'll come to you when she's ready.
Hmm.
You lost her.
I didn't lose her! They took her.
She cares about
that enforcer, you saw it.
She was there for me! Not the enforcer.
Remember her name?
Why would I remember her name?
Well, she's just some stupid topsider!
Caitlyn.
Pow.
Come on. Go!
I got it.
Whoo-hoo!
Is that real tree?
Pretty cool, huh?
When I first saw it,
I knew this was the place.
If a single seed could make it down here,
so could we.
You built all this?
Not alone.
After Vander...
...died,
Silco flooded the lanes with Shimmer.
He didn't care
what it did to people.
Everyone here was an addict or a victim.
Hi.
They needed
somewhere safe to start again.
I should have been there.
For you. For everyone.
That's a good way to drive yourself crazy.
If I just went with you that day,
maybe none of this would have happened.
Or maybe you'd be dead. Or... changed.
Powder's gone, Vi.
All that's left is Jinx
and she belongs to Silco.
You're wrong. She's still in there.
I can reach her.
You can't.
I know my sister.
I got one more thing to show you.
This is everyone we've lost.
The price of our freedom.
Some of it was Enforcers.
Most was Silco.
Your sister works for him not because
she has to, but because she wants to.
I'm sorry, but that's who she is now.
Get down!
- Let us through!
- Come on!
We understand.
Just stand down!
- Thank you for alerting me, Sheriff.
- Not a problem, Councilor.
Jayce, what is this?
Do you have any idea how this looks?
I order a blockade
and my own partner violates it?
You ordered this? Why?
There are people down there
who seem hell-bent on destroying us.
What were you doing?
I was consulting a friend
about our quandary.
I told you, I knew someone.
Well, you didn't say
they were from the undercity.
What difference does that make?
What diff... They're dangerous.
I'm from the undercity.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I've had a lot on my plate.
Was your friend able to help?
No.
No, he said, "Nature was resistant
to this sort of tampering."
All right, we'll keep at it.
First, this wild attack
in the heart of Piltover.
Now, the border's closing.
We're bleeding money and for what?
His dreams of rebellion?
He's losing control.
If we stand together...
We aren't due for an assembly.
We should be.
Ever since your stunt topside,
profits have been plummeting.
He's right.
Merchandise is frozen at the border.
Topsiders are too afraid to cross.
We're all wondering,
what's your plan to fix this?
You're all wondering, are you?
Way I see it, we should cut a deal
and give back the Gemstone.
Better to have some trade
than none at all.
The border issue is temporary.
Jinx will deal with it.
Huh.
Rumor is, your dog's off her leash.
How you meant to bring Piltover to heel
if you can't handle your own people, huh?
What's that?
Oh, you don't recognize it?
Have you forgotten
where we came from?
The mines they had us in?
Air so thick it clogged your throat.
Stuck in your eyes.
But I pulled you all up
from the depths.
Offered you a taste of topside.
And fresh air.
I gave you life.
Purpose.
But you've grown fat and complacent.
Too much time in the sun.
We came from a world where there
was never enough to go around, Finn.
That is why we fight.
Do you remember?
Sorry. Please.
Please.
Don't forget again.
Good meeting.
I've had word from
our friends overseas.
This threat from the undercity
is drawing attention.
Piltover looks vulnerable.
It's too soon. Jayce isn't ready.
There's one other thing.
This arrived for you.
Hmm?
What have you done with Vi?
Listen, let her go. I brought her here.
It's me you want.
- My hero.
- You're...
But I thought you...
I thought they were hurting you!
Vi tells me I can trust you.
You get
a pass back topside, that's it.
Let's go.
Let me help you with that.
Where've you been, Jinx?
Oh, you know.
Here, there, chasing down dead ends.
And guess what? They're not all dead.
I can explain.
Don't move, silly. I might hurt you.
I didn't know. Marcus never told me
she was in Stillwater.
But you found out she came back.
You lied.
- I wanted to protect you.
- From what?
She and the enforcer are back
for the crystal. Not for you.
Have you forgotten how she left you?
Who found you? Who cared for you?
Gave you a home?
I am your family.
Everyone else betrays us.
I need you.
Now more than ever.
You have to complete the weapon.
It's beautiful.
If your people had your way,
it'd be rubble and ash.
It's a misunderstanding.
They think you work for Silco.
Your people hunt us like animals.
Silco pays them to do it.
That's not possible. You're wrong.
Say that one more time.
Ekko, she believes what she's saying,
okay? She's not your enemy.
Oh, yeah? Then what's this?
You got it.
You have to let me take that back.
What is it?
It's a Gemstone.
It was stolen during the attack.
By your sister.
You just forgot to mention that?
With this, someone
with the right knowledge could build...
any Hextech device.
If enforcers are becoming
more... aggressive, that's why.
We could beat Silco with this.
That won't solve things.
Easy for you to say. Your people
aren't dying all around you.
Ekko, it's wrong what's been done to you.
You'd be well
within your rights to keep it.
I couldn't blame you.
But... if you do,
this cycle of violence will never stop.
This is our best shot
at setting the record straight.
This city needs healing.
More than I ever realized.
Please, let me help you.
You got a plan?
I have a friend on the council.
Let me take the Gemstone to him.
He'll listen to me.
Your people wouldn't have to hide anymore.
One condition.
I'm the one who gives it to them.
Um, the form is crude, but...
uh, the engineering is... inspired.
You think they could crack Hextech?
Mm. It's a leap.
It's been suggested that they may
have found a way to utilize the Gemstone.
If we are to assume the worst, that would
mean they've turned it into a weapon.
Well, do we know this for certain?
We can't afford to wait to find out.
Wait. What are you suggesting?
We should prepare our own countermeasures.
You want us to build weapons?
Absolutely not.
That is not why we invented Hextech.
We would shatter
any attempt at peace.
- Heimerdinger would never go for this.
- Heimerdingers' inaction
is what brought us here.
You said so yourself.
The peace is already broken, Jayce.
I'm only asking you to prepare
to defend your people.
If we're lucky,
we'll never need to use it.
The decision is yours.
Ridiculous.
You cannot be considering this.
What if she's right? Are we just
gonna stand by while they attack us?
We're scientists, not soldiers.
We have the knowledge to defend ourselves.
We agreed Hextech was to improve lives...
...not to take them.
We may not have a choice.
There is always a choice.
I need to think.
What are they?
We call them firelights.
Never seen so many though.
I'm worried I have to do something
I never thought I would.
Vi?
I can't leave her again.
You can't change her.
I have to try.
Don't get yourself killed.
No promises.
It's been real, Cupcake.
Thanks. For everything.
Shut up. It's just a goodbye hug.
She wouldn't do that. Not again.
Halt!
What the hell is this?
Sir! I have proof.
Silco's behind everything.
Show me.
No.
Hmm.
Shit.
Caitlyn!
Liar.
I told you to leave this alone.
Tell my...
Tell my daughter I...
Go!
Oh, look who it is. The boy savior.
Hah.
Yes!
No.