♪ Dear friend across the river ♪
♪ My hands are cold and bare ♪
♪ I'll take what you can spare ♪
♪ I ask of you a penny ♪
♪ My fortune it will be ♪
♪ I ask you without envy ♪
♪ We raise no mighty towers ♪
♪ Our homes are built of stone ♪
♪ So come across the river ♪
♪ And find... ♪
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that arouse ♪
♪ From my mind to run around
Put my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that I told ♪
♪ My back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
We're almost there.
Aw, man.
Hey, Powder.
Come take a look.
Whoa.
It's nice getting above it all, huh?
One day, I'm gonna ride
in one of those things.
And one day,
I'm gonna shoot one of 'em down.
Vi, are, are you sure about this?
- Look, if we get caught, we're...
- We're not gonna get caught.
We'll be in and out before anyone notices.
All right, everybody, follow me.
Just don't look down.
Couldn't we have at least
just walked there?
Gotta stay out of sight for this one.
Called it.
This is on you, Vi.
- I'll get her.
- No.
Powder, look at me.
What did I tell you?
That...
...I'm ready.
That's right! So?
Phew!
Thanks.
What if Vander finds out
we're all the way up here?
Look around you.
You think anyone topside's going hungry?
Besides, this is exactly the sort of job
Vander would've pulled
when he was our age.
I'm going. Are you with me or not?
Vander's gonna kill us.
Yeah, only if we screw up.
So don't screw up.
All clear.
Who locks their balcony?
Hmm.
Whew.
There's tons of enforcers
down there.
Means we're in the right place.
You gonna get that door open
any time soon?
Working on it.
Seeing as I'm the only one
who knows how to pick locks,
I suggest...
Animals.
You know, Claggor, for once you're right.
We are definitely not supposed to be here.
Hmm.
Must be an inventor.
Huh.
Whoa, I think this is a real Valdiani.
Oh, yeah? What about this?
That's a nose hair trimmer.
Keep an eye out for anything
that looks valuable, Powder.
Before Mylo fills the bag with junk.
Uh... guys?
Wait, Vi, how the hell
did we find this place?
It was a tip from Little Man.
- Little Man?
- Just leave it.
Come on.
How can anyone
have so much stuff?
Simple, just get born lucky.
Woo-hoo!
Mm.
Huh.
Whoa.
Mylo.
Powder, we gotta go.
Hello?
Is someone in there?
Come on.
We'll be fine. Just get back on the roof.
Hold on!
Whoa! Look out!
Watch out!
Hey.
Shit.
Stop right there!
Get them off!
Faster!
Hey! Hey!
Look out!
Down there!
You can't get away!
- Hey!
- Come on!
Oh.
This way!
Keep going!
Go, go, go!
Oh, man, not again.
I just got this shirt...
Thought last time was the last time
we were gonna do this.
Well, this time's the last time.
Guys, what was that?
What the hell happened back there?
I don't know. I didn't do anything.
You could fill a damn library
with all the things you didn't do.
Guys, we just emptied a Piltover penthouse
right under the enforcers' noses.
So, if you're done beating yourselves up,
let's get this home.
- Nice haul?
- You could say that.
I heard there was some action
across the river.
Someone, uh,
someone really kicked the nest, huh?
Is that so?
But now you're, you're tracking
this mess of yours through my streets.
- Your streets? What makes you think...
- Listen, we don't want any trouble, okay?
Hear that, Deckard?
They don't want any trouble.
You know, in my experience,
trouble finds you.
There's no reason this has to get ugly.
How about you share
a little taste of your treasure there
- and we'll call it even?
- No, no, no. We worked too hard to...
Just a taste?
Just a...
Huh?
Huh.
This day's turning out all right
after all.
Wait!
Wanna see how that ends?
Where's Powder?
Oh! Oh! You little...
Oh!
Come on, Mouser, I need you!
No.
- You did what?
- I'm sorry.
I tried to fight him off with Mouser,
but... she didn't work.
- Who saw that coming?
- We never should have gone over there.
Doesn't matter. The stuff's gone.
It's all right, Powder.
At least you're okay.
Okay? What about us?
I get my face bashed in,
and she just gets a pass?
Yup.
Every time. Every time she comes,
something goes wrong.
She jinxes every job.
Just drop it, Mylo.
♪ Come along if you want to peek ♪
♪ I've seen your face around here ♪
♪ Come along and tell me under the table ♪
♪ What do you see? ♪
♪ Welcome to the playground, follow me ♪
♪ Tell me your nightmares ♪
♪ And fantasies ♪
♪ Sinking through the ways down... ♪
Sit still!
Come on, get out of here!
- You gotta pay!
- Look at that!
♪ What brings you
to the lost and found to me? ♪
- Hey! Watch it.
- Hey!
Well, I, uh, suppose
that concludes our business, then.
Mm. I suppose it does.
Wait...
Uh, wait a minute.
This, uh...
uh, this... isn't what we agreed on, so...
Well, demand for your wares has dropped
since we made our arrangements.
This is the new value.
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We, um...
we shook on it.
Ten thousand.
- Such are the risks of business.
- Ten.
It's a fair price.
I think you should take it.
No, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no.
I can't do that. I can't do that!
Make your choice.
You folks need anything?
Leave us.
You sure about that?
- Sounded to me like...
- Piss off.
Ah.
I think I know what you need.
- You don't seem to listen, barman...
- A bit of advice.
Don't threaten the guy
who pours the drinks.
So you're Vander.
Hound of the Underground.
I expected something... younger.
We were expecting traders
who would honor their word,
so I guess we're all disappointed.
You got us all wrong, my friend.
We were just... negotiating.
Now you're speaking my language.
How about you just give Huck
the rest of what you owe him,
and I'll let you walk out of here
in one piece?
Do we, uh... have a deal?
This is vile.
You'll learn to love it.
Welcome to the Lanes.
Vander learns none of this.
No worries there.
Powder took care of the evidence.
I tried, okay? You don't get it.
You're older, you're bigger.
- It, it isn't fair.
- So stick with us!
Take a punch or two.
- Everyone all right?
- Never better.
Good.
I don't suppose you can explain why it is
that I'm hearing about an explosion
and a foot chase topside?
Four children fleeing the scene.
What the hell were you thinking?
That we can handle a real job.
A real job?
We got our own tip, planned a route,
nobody even saw.
- You blew up a building.
- That wasn't...
Did you even stop to think about
what could have happened to you?
Eh? To them?
Where did you even get this tip?
- We just heard it at Benzo's shop.
- From?
Little Man.
I took us there.
If you wanna be mad, be mad at me.
But you're the one who always says
we have to earn our place in this world.
I also told you time and time again,
the Northside's off-limits.
- We stay out of Piltover's business.
- Why?
They've got plenty, while we're down here
scraping together coins.
When did you get so comfortable
living in someone else's shadow?
Everyone out.
Sit down.
- I'm fine.
- Sit. Down.
Those kids look up to you.
Yeah, I know.
You know, but you don't know.
When people look up to you,
you don't get to be selfish.
- I'm not...
- You say run, they run.
You say swim, they dive in.
You say light a fire,
they show up with oil.
But whatever happens, it's on you.
Just like it's on me
what happens to us down here.
We make ourselves a problem for Piltover,
and they will send the enforcers.
So? Why answer to them?
These are our streets.
Someone should remind them of that.
You're not hearing me. That path?
This?
It's not gonna solve your problems.
Just makes more of them.
We clear?
How'd you get this?
Some idiot was following us.
On our side? Who?
I don't know. He was after the stuff.
Where is it now?
We lost it.
All of it?
Good.
Nothing can tie you
to what happened up there.
You're gonna have to lay low
for a bit, understand?
Okay.
We're gonna be fine, right?
I'll take care of it.
Oh, you did put that idiot
on his ass, though, right?
Mm.
Get up, Claggor. We're going out.
Wait, now?
Hey, hey, that's mine!
You wanna be treated like adults, right?
Then you should know better than
to come back from a job empty-handed.
I'm gonna have a little word
with your informant.
All right, give me the details
of exactly what happened up there.
She's a problem.
Mylo, I'm really not...
Do you remember
what was in that bag?
The biggest payout
we've ever seen and she just lost it.
She made a mistake.
Name one time she hasn't.
- She's young.
- Don't bullshit me.
You were twice the person at half her age.
You know what, Mylo? You're right.
There's a bunch of things Powder
just can't do.
You don't have to tell me twice.
- Like, complain about everything.
- What?
- And brag nonstop.
- Okay, okay, I see where this is going.
Pick fights with the group
when we need to focus.
Vi, I...
And tell strangers on the street
that we got a nice haul?
- I, I didn't mean to...
- Powder's my problem, okay?
Your problem is never knowing
when to shut up.
But I'm gonna help you with that. Ready?
You see this look on my face?
This will always mean
it's time to shut up.
But... I...
Nobody comes in.
We're closed.
Well, open up.
For good. You can take
your worthless junk elsewhere.
Just as well.
Owner's the shittiest businessman I know.
Ekko. What's going on with that thing?
Give me a few seconds.
The cannon pinion's still busted.
Finish it later. Vander and I need a word.
- But...
- Uh-uh. Off you go.
- Claggor.
- He-he-hey, Little Man.
You're a little early.
My guys are still roundin' up
this month's collections.
Won't have numbers until next, um...
Whoo.
Why are you muckin' about with this?
I assume you've heard.
Yeah, me and half the undercity.
How could they be so stupid?
The younger folk think
it's the right thing to do.
Yeah, and Vi's one of them.
Throws herself at trouble
wherever she can find some.
Eh, they're growing up, Vander.
Looking to write their own stories.
You can't protect them forever.
Someone was following them.
- Whole lot of someones, from what I heard.
- Not enforcers.
- Someone on our side.
- Who?
There's worse things
than enforcers out there.
We both know that.
Yeah, I was hopin' you'd be working today.
- Did you guys go?
- Sure did.
Hey, listen, how did you find that place?
- I just...
- Whoa, did you fight the enforcers?
What? Oh, no. Eh, just some bums.
Oh, did Vi kick their asses?
Yeah, I mean,
I wouldn't be here otherwise.
Oh, she showed me
a couple moves to practice. Look.
- Yeah, it's... it's coming along.
- Ya!
Hey, so, how'd you find
that place, anyway?
Uh, this weirdo came into the shop.
Bought a whole bunch of stuff
Benzo only keeps there for display.
He paid in gold and didn't even haggle.
I charged him double price. Sucker.
- But how did you know where he lived?
- Uh, followed him.
- How else?
- Oh. Right.
Oh, crap.
- Uh...
- They'll be fine. Go.
Well, hello.
Evening, friends.
Shit.
Something I can help you with?
Some trencher trash attacked one
of the buildings in the Academy district,
but you already knew that.
We're looking for the culprits.
Got a description?
Yeah, it's exactly who you're picturing
in that thick head of yours.
Mm. You think my head is thick?
Uh, just past the average.
Listen, you shady son of a...
How about you go
for a little walk, Marcus?
Cool off a bit.
Go.
Lovely chap you've brought.
Don't mind the kid.
Doesn't know when to pipe down.
Some things are the same
topside and bottom.
You know this crossed a line upstairs.
Was anyone hurt?
A building was blown to bits.
What do you think?
Those who did this will be dealt with.
That workshop belonged to the Kirammans.
You know what kind of stuff
they had in there?
Makes this place look like a candy shop.
The Council needs someone
to make an example of.
People need to feel safe.
Yeah, topside people.
We had a deal, Vander.
You keep your people off my streets,
and I stay out of your business.
Give me a name. We'll do things quiet.
No one will know you were involved.
I can't do that.
You don't seem to grasp
how serious this is.
If I don't put someone
behind bars tonight,
the next time I come down here,
I'll have an army of enforcers with me.
We both know how that'll go.
I'm sorry, Grayson,
but I can't offer up my own people.
If you change your mind,
this will reach me.
And only me.
What are you calling this one?
Whisker.
- You wanna talk about today?
- What's the point?
I ruined everything. I always do.
Nobody said that.
No. Just that you were
"twice the person" at half my age.
You heard them.
I'm not a fighter.
You don't have to be.
Look, I've got these and you've got those.
They never work.
They will.
- Come with me.
- What?
Come on.
What are we doing here?
See that gutter running along the canal?
That's where Claggor got his foot
stuck running from enforcers.
They thought it was funny,
so they left him there.
He was out all night before we found him.
That sign?
- You see it?
- Uh-huh.
Mylo tripped over his own paint bucket
and nearly fell off trying to draw
a giant middle finger.
His ass made that splotch.
And that?
When I was a kid, some guy took
my favorite toy and threw it up there.
I used to come out here at night
and stare at it,
hoping maybe the wind
or a bird might knock it down.
We've all had bad days.
But we learn. And we stick together.
Oh, I forgot.
These were in my pocket.
- They're from the apartment.
- What are they?
I don't know.
- Should we show Vander?
- No.
Let's keep this our little secret.
Mylo's wrong, Powder.
You're stronger than you think.
And one day...
this city's gonna respect us.
You were supposed to follow them
and not interfere.
I'm sorry.
They just caught us by surprise.
Now his accomplice
is asking questions about you.
That's not a risk I'm willing to take.
The kids. It was their fault,
the explosion in the upper city.
That was them?
Yeah. The topsiders
are up in arms looking for 'em.
Vander's in trouble.
Smartest thing you ever said, boy.
Get him a meal.
But keep him off the streets.
Our timeline has moved up.
It's almost ready.
Show me.
Feeding time.
And the side effects?
Stabilizing.
You have a subject in mind?
Someone just volunteered.
♪ Who told you I was scouting? ♪
♪ Come along if you want to peek ♪
♪ I've seen your face around here ♪
♪ Come along and tell me under the table ♪
♪ What do you see? ♪
♪ Welcome to the playground, follow me ♪
♪ Tell me your nightmares and fantasies ♪
♪ Sinking through the ways
Down underneath ♪
♪ Before the night's out
So you were dreaming ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Welcome to the playground ♪