Extracted from RETAIL by balloumowgly
[woman vocalizing]
[water gurgles]
[Silco] Ever wonder
what it's like to drown?
[woman vocalizing]
Story of opposites.
[water gurgles]
There's peace in water.
Like it's holdin' you,
whisperin' in low tones to let it in.
And every problem in the world
will fade away.
[woman vocalizing]
-But then there's this thing…
-[grunts]
…in your head, and it's raging.
[grunts]
Lighting every nerve with madness.
-[water gurgles]
-To fight.
-[groans]
-To survive.
And all the while,
this question lingers before you:
[gags]
"Have you had enough?"
It's funny. You could pass a lifetime
without ever facing a choice like that.
But it changes you forever.
For that, I thank you…
old friend.
["Enemy" by Imagine Dragons playing]
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that arouse ♪
♪ From my mind to run around
Put my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that I told ♪
♪ My back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Hey-o, I swear ♪
♪ I never be insane ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
-[wind gusts]
-[metal creaks]
[footsteps approaching]
Vander?
[sighs]
We don't have much time.
How did you find me?
I'm proud of you. Always have been.
I'm sorry, I… This is the only way
to protect the others.
-[dog barking in distance]
-Vander.
[Vander] You've got a good heart.
Don't ever lose it.
No matter how the world
tries to break you.
Protect the family.
What are you--
[grunts]
No.
[grumbles]
[lock rattles]
[enforcer breathing heavily]
-[Vi] Vander.
-[clanking]
-Let me out. This isn't right.
-[bangs]
[Grayson] I'm guessing that's for me.
[Marcus sighs]
You gonna let us make the arrest or not?
You'll oblige a doomed man one last smoke.
[puffs]
Won't you?
[Grayson]
I'm not putting you away, Vander.
The Council needs its pound of flesh.
Without you down here, it all falls apart.
[huffs]
Benzo will handle things.
I may not have my devilish charm,
but he runs a tight ship.
[grunts]
Vander, no. You can't do this.
[Grayson]
You won't be coming back for a long time.
-I know.
-[Vi grunting]
-[Grayson] Why?
-Mm.
-It's the only way.
-[Vi grunting]
-Benzo, open the damn door.
-[sighs]
[grunts]
[pants]
[man screams]
What's happening?
[muffled clamor]
[panting]
[Grayson] Hey. Stop right there!
[gasps]
[ominous music plays]
[Benzo] What the devil…
No.
[approaching footsteps]
Silco?
You animal. Go crawl back
into whatever hole you came out of.
Benzo, stay back.
You never did know when to walk away.
-Wait.
-[grunts]
No!
[gasps]
Hmm. Stubborn to the end.
[snarls]
[Marcus] What the hell have you done?
This wasn't the deal!
Deal's changed.
No.
[Deckard squeals]
No!
[dramatic music plays]
[inaudible]
[dramatic music playing continues]
[coin clinks]
[Jayce] This entire time, I thought
I needed to dampen the oscillations.
The crystals will only stabilize
at high frequency.
-You have to--
-Crank it.
Yes. Yes. You have to… crank it.
-It works.
-Eh… On paper.
Well, we could test it
if we had access to my equipment.
Which is being destroyed tomorrow.
-What?
-Oh. I… Yeah. I, I meant to tell you.
That research is everything.
My… my whole life.
[Jayce]
Maybe if we showed them the equations,
-they'd let us--
-[Viktor] We need more than promises.
We need proof.
Not without the crystals.
The enforcers took them all. They're gone.
Yeah. Locked away in Heimerdinger's lab.
No. No. No. You heard the Council.
If we're wrong…
Better be right then.
Why? Why would you risk this?
Do you think it was my life's ambition
to be an assistant?
Scientists seek discoveries.
Ways to make the world a better place.
This Hextech dream of yours
has the potential to do that.
Our Hextech dream.
-[lock rattles]
-[door opens]
[door creaks]
[somber music plays]
[sobs]
[Ekko] I saw everything.
[cries]
Be… Benzo. They…
What about Vander?
[stammers]
They took him.
-[Vi] Where?
-[sobs]
[chilling music plays]
[man growls]
[Vander breathes heavily]
[Vander grunts]
[foreboding music plays]
[Silco] It's a little crude, I'll admit.
The base violence necessary for change.
But we both know
topside won't listen to anything else.
[both grunt]
[spits]
Even with your monsters,
you won't win a war against Piltover.
I don't have to.
I just need to scare them.
They won't dare set foot
in the underground again.
You'll get people killed. For what? Pride?
For respect.
Opportunity. Everything they've denied us.
You had my respect.
The Lanes' respect, but that…
that was never enough for you.
We shared a vision, Vander.
A dream of freedom.
Not just for the Lanes, but the whole
of the underground, united as one.
The nation of Zaun.
Do you even remember?
I trusted you.
And you betrayed me.
[both grunt]
What I did to you…
[grunts]
I've never forgiven myself.
You were my brother.
No, you still don't understand.
[Silco] Can you imagine what it's like?
When your blood mixes with the filth
and the river toxins
eat through your nerves.
Oh, I hated you for what you'd done.
But as time passed, so did my hate.
And I was left with an understanding.
The only way to defeat a superior enemy
is to stop at nothing.
To become what they fear.
I hated you, but you kept my respect.
Until you made peace with them.
Played lapdog
after everything we suffered.
[metal clanks]
I had no choice.
Perhaps.
But now you do.
Shimmer. We have the power.
We can finally realize our dream,
brother.
Look at what you've done.
Benzo. These kids.
In fighting topside,
you'd sacrifice everything that we are.
It's not the way. Can't you see that?
Kill me if you have to,
but please spare the Lanes.
You'd die for the cause,
but you won't fight for one?
[scoffs]
I'm just… not that man anymore.
I'll show you what you really are.
[foreboding music plays]
Hmm.
[footsteps approaching]
[ominous music plays]
[keys jangle]
So far, so good.
-[chimes]
-[grunts]
Hmm. Willing to risk exile
for your endeavor.
That's quite the conviction.
Councilor.
-What a surprise to see you, huh?
-Wait a minute, this isn't my bedroom.
How could I have…
Please. We can prove that it works.
Hmm. You couldn't do so earlier today,
how is tonight any different?
We figured out how to stabilize it.
You're the Professor's assistant.
No, he's my new partner.
Even if you manage to prove your theory,
the Council would destroy it.
Heimerdinger will recognize the potential.
[scoffs]
He already does.
It scares him. It scares them all.
What about you?
I recognize that any worthwhile venture
involves risk.
[man whistling in distance]
[whistling continues]
Councilor, this technology, it's real.
And no matter what happens here,
it's going to change our world.
We should be the ones to lead it.
Piltover, the land of progress,
equality, innovation.
I know it sounds impossible,
but when have we ever let that stop us?
Please, just give us a chance.
One night, gentlemen. Impress me,
or I'd suggest you pack your bags.
-[man whistling]
-Harold.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, Councilor Medarda,
you… you nearly scared me to death.
Ah. Another late night.
The work just doesn't end.
[Harold] Well, I suppose that's a sign
of good business, huh?
[keys jingle]
[clangs]
Well, if the enforcers hit tonight,
we'll be ready…
-I think.
-[Claggor] Dibs on the bat.
-[Mylo] No, no, no, no. I found it.
-[Claggor] But I called it.
-[Mylo] But I found it.
-[Claggor] Respect the dibs.
-I called it already.
-[Mylo] Respect the…
-Stop being such a big baby.
-[door opens, closes]
Vi?
-Where's the--
-[Powder] Oh, you're back.
[gasps]
[shaky breath]
Hey. Those are Vander's.
Slow down. What's going on?
-Benzo's dead.
-Dead?
-They took Vander.
-[Mylo] Who took Vander?
I don't know. But I need to help him.
We're going with you.
Whatever killed Benzo…
was like nothing I've ever seen.
It tore him apart.
[sobs]
You're not doing this alone, Vi.
[Mylo] He's our father too.
Do we know where they took him?
[Vi] Ekko followed them.
The old cannery next to the docks.
He said…
[sighs]
I need you to sit this one out, Powder.
What?
-You're not coming.
-I'm not afraid.
It's too dangerous.
But families stick together.
You said it yourself.
-I know what I said…
-I want to fight. I can help.
You're not ready.
[exclaims]
You're all I have left.
I can't lose you.
Here. If they come for you,
take this and run.
Where ever you are, light it up,
and I'll find you. I promise.
[door closes]
[electricity crackles]
[sighs]
It's all here.
[crackles]
It's time to crank it.
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
[crackles]
[cracking]
[metal clanking]
I don't think it's gonna hold!
Look at the buildup!
The resonance will stabilize it.
Trust me.
[enforcer 1] Hey, you seeing this?
[Powder crying]
[wails]
-[grunts]
-[clanks]
[screams]
[shrieks]
[grunts]
[breathes heavily]
[sobs]
[crackles]
[tense music plays]
I can help them.
[ominous music plays]
Let's get Vander and get out.
[Viktor] I told you it would work.
All yours.
Wow.
[Jayce] It's never done that before.
All right. Here we go.
[crackles]
[Viktor] Disengage!
[tense music intensifies]
-[explosion]
-[crackles]
-[gasps]
-[electricity sizzles]
[glass shattering]
[Viktor] Incredible.
[suspenseful music plays]
[spits]
-Vi.
-[grunts]
What are you doing here?
We're breakin' you out.
-Mylo.
-On it.
-[puffs]
-[Vander] How… how did you get in?
There's guards everywhere.
It was easy. We found an open window and…
[Vander] Oh, god.
You have to get out. Now.
[Silco] Welcome.
[footsteps approaching]
You have my congratulations.
But I'm afraid
this will be a very short reunion.
Hmm.
Have you heard the rumor?
Vander the coward
fled town with his children.
And they were never seen again.
-[Vander grunts]
-[Claggor sighs]
[grumbles]
Claggor, see if you can find
another way out of here.
Okay.
[Vander] You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
Vi.
[foreboding music plays]
[exhales]
[bone cracks]
[Powder gasps]
[foreboding music playing continues]
[gasps]
[snorts]
-[yells]
-[grunts]
-[screams]
-[grumbles]
-[groans]
-[metal clanks]
-[man 1 pants]
-[Vi grunts]
-[screams]
-[groans]
[both grunting]
[grumbles, gasps]
[Powder grunts]
[clatters]
Mylo.
[yelps]
Take a breath. You can do this.
[both men scream]
[grunting]
[man shrieks]
-[clanks]
-[Vander grunts]
We're gonna get you out.
[clangs]
[grunts]
[both scream]
[all grunting]
[screams]
Ready to rise to the surface?
[gasps]
[both grunt]
[man grumbles]
[grunts]
[both groan]
[Deckard grumbling]
[squeaks]
[both grunt]
[Deckard screams]
[growls]
-[man grunts]
-[Deckard hisses]
[bones cracking]
Mylo, hurry.
[Vi shouts]
[both grunt]
Vi.
[gasping]
Silco. Let her go.
This is between you and me.
You had your chance.
[Vi coughs]
[gasps]
[grunts]
-Vi.
-[grunts]
[winces]
[growls]
[grunts]
[both groan]
-[loud thud]
-[both grumble]
[grunts]
You did good.
-[enforcer 1] Open up.
-Stop this lunacy at once.
-They're almost through. No pressure.
-[enforcer 2] Open the door.
That sounds like pressure!
[chimes]
[enforcer 2 grunts]
Open it.
[chimes]
[tinkles]
[explosion]
-[explosion]
-[chimes]
Excuse me. Underfoot.
[gasps]
[whimsical music plays]
[chuckles]
[gasps, shaky breath]
[Jayce chuckles]
You've actually done it.
But just because it can be done,
doesn't mean…
Will you please stop hovering?
[Viktor] I'm not sure how to do that, sir.
This is not what Piltover's future
looks like, my dear boys.
[Mel] That's for the Council to decide.
Perhaps it's time.
For the era of magic.
Uh, Hextech. For the era of Hextech.
[adventure music plays]
[chitters]
-[growls]
-[gasps]
-[Powder] You have to work. For me. Okay?
-[chitters]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[grumbles]
-[groans]
-[screams]
[yells]
[suspenseful music plays]
[chitters]
[grunting]
[growls]
[clanking]
[Deckard screams]
[grunts]
[electricity crackles]
[Vander grumbles]
[grunts]
[clanks]
[explosion]
[muffled explosion]
[crackles]
[grunts]
[rumbles]
[whimsical music plays]
[explosion in distance]
[crackles]
[grunts]
[somber music plays]
[electricity crackling]
[somber music playing continues]
[growls]
Kill them.
[snarls]
[cries]
[grunts]
-[Vander screams]
-[rumbling]
-[grumbles]
-[grunts]
[man screams]
-[metal clanks]
-[man grunts]
[man grumbles]
[grunts]
[pants]
[man groans, screams]
[Vander grunts]
-[shouts]
-[snarls]
[grumbles]
-[Vander grunts]
[yells]
[both grunt]
[Deckard snarls]
[Vander yelps]
[sobs]
[groans]
[cries]
[grunts]
[heavy breathing]
[yells]
[shrieks]
[groans]
[both grunt]
[heavy breathing]
[gags]
[water gurgles]
[Vander grunts]
-[thunder rumbles]
-[Silco grumbles]
[Vander screams]
[grunts]
[yells]
[groans]
[gasps, pants]
[Silco] I knew you still had it in you.
[glass shatters]
[foreboding music plays]
[Silco] Find the girl.
[Vander grunting]
[groans]
[metal clangs]
[growls]
[metal clanks]
[grumbles]
[Vander growls]
-[Deckard gags]
-[Vander snarls]
[gasps]
[growls]
[grunts]
Silco!
-[explosion]
-[glass shatters]
[fire crackling]
[Vander snarls]
[Vi grunts]
Vander.
-Vander…
-[gasping]
Take care of Powder.
No!
[thunder rumbles]
[Powder] Vi, it worked.
-What?
-[Powder] Did you see me?
My monkey bomb finally worked.
You did this?
Why?
Why did you do this?
I… I didn't…
I was saving you.
I only wanted to help.
[sobs]
-I only wanted to--
-I told you to stay away.
-Please. Please. Please--
-I told you to stay away!
No. Why did you leave me?
Because you're a jinx. Do you hear me?
Mylo was right.
No. No. No. No. Violet, please.
[Powder crying]
[gasps]
[Powder crying continues]
Violet, please.
[Powder wails]
[Powder] Vi! Vi, come back!
Please come back!
Please, Violet. I need you. Please.
[grunts, pants]
[thunder rumbles]
[Powder crying]
Violet…
Violet. Please.
-[crying]
-[thunder rumbles]
[rain pattering]
[Powder crying]
[groans]
Powder.
-Pow--
-[Marcus] Shh.
-[Vi muffled scream]
-[Marcus] He'll kill you if he hears you.
Come on. Let's go.
[ominous music plays]
-[thunder rumbles]
-[rain pattering]
[Powder crying]
[Powder sobbing]
Hello, little girl.
Where's your sister?
[sobs]
[screams]
She left me.
[Powder] She is not my sister anymore.
[somber music plays]
[Powder crying]
It's okay.
We'll show them.
We will show them all.
-[thunder rumbles]
-[rain pattering]
♪ I can hear the sound
Of our hearts beat ♪
♪ Hold me closer ♪
♪ Won't never leave my memories ♪
♪ Blood shed all around ♪
♪ I can see a tear on my father's face ♪
♪ Before it falls down on my enemy ♪
♪ How could I have ever let you down? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ When all these trace, highest crow ♪
♪ Cut our teeth and break our bones ♪
♪ Right here ♪
♪ Plain of shields were made of stone
Share our dreams and sit our thrones ♪
♪ Be still ♪
♪ Cause I see smoke ahead ♪
♪ And I got steel in my head ♪
♪ Turn that quarter, to you I swear ♪
♪ That we'll find glorious ahead
Down here ♪
♪ Where is my home? ♪
♪ I don't recognize the faces any more ♪
♪ Where is my friend? ♪
♪ We've known since
I was only just a kid ♪
♪ I think it's time to say goodbye ♪
♪ Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye ♪
♪ It's time to say goodbye ♪
Extracted from RETAIL by balloumowgly