(CHEERING)
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
Danke. Danke und willkommen
in der Grosse Tour
which this week
comes from Germany!
- (CHEERING)
- Ja. We're here. We're here.
Specifically...
Specifically, we are
in the city of Stuttgart.
Except we nearly weren't.
Because one of your
local Green politicians
tried to ban us
from coming here.
I don't want to embarrass
the poor man on television.
So I've hidden his identity.
(LAUGHTER)
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- That's good.
That's appropriate.
I certainly don't want to
tell you his name.
Which is... Andreas Kasdorf.
- Uh...
- (BOOING)
Not a popular man.
But you elected him.
Anyway, he says that
we'd be unwelcome here
because this is a very
bicycle-friendly place.
It... It isn't. It's the home
of Mercedes and Porsche.
- And Germany--
- (CHEERING)
- Exactly.
Germany...
Germany is the cradle
of the automobile.
The car was
actually invented here.
It's the last place on Earth
you can drive a car
as fast as it will go
on the motorway.
(CHEERING)
- It's true.
- All true.
This is a true fact.
The Germans are
the only people on Earth
who really know
how to make a car.
- This is--
- (CHEERING)
- It's a true fact.
- It's true.
I'll tell you a story.
There was a Mercedes engineer
and a Jaguar engineer
having dinner one night.
The Mercedes engineer
said, "Ve haf..."
Forgive the accent.
"Ve haf a quality test
at ze Mercedes factory.
Every night, ve take a car
off ze line at random.
Ve put a cat in it,
close ze doors.
If... When ve come back
in ze morning,
ve know the door seals
are vorking correctly
if ze cat has suffocated."
(LAUGHTER)
- Nah.
- (LAUGHTER)
The Jaguar engineer said,
"We've got something very
similar at our factory.
We take a car
off the line at random.
We put a cat in it.
We close the door.
And we know the car's
been built properly
if, when we come back
in the morning,
the cat hasn't escaped.
- (LAUGHTER)
- That is...
- True story.
- Yeah. True story.
The strange thing is,
it isn't just cars
that are built well here.
- It's absolutely everything.
- Except wine.
Yes, except wine. Sorry.
- (JEERING)
- Well, come on!
- Now come on!
- You drink that stuff?
I wouldn't
wash my hair in it.
- (LAUGHTER)
- Are you sure?
It is literally everything,
though.
German soft toys,
better than anybody
else's soft toys.
Cameras, kitchen appliances.
The Queen of England,
she's German.
She is. That's why
she's still working
even though she's a hundred
and forty seventeen years old.
There is no word here
for "that'll do".
There is no ambiguity
at all in Germany.
You certainly see this
with films.
The names you have
for American films.
I've got some here.
Remember Airplane?
Airplane, yes.
In Germany, it was called
The Unbelievable Journey
In The Crazy Airplane.
That is a comprehensive title.
You know where
you are with that.
What was Jaws?
- (PEOPLE CALL OUT)
- The what? The Weisse...?
The White Shark.
It should have been
The Massive Shark
That Explodes Eventually.
You know where
you're going with that.
What was...
What was Basic Instinct?
- (PEOPLE CALL OUT)
- Just not
A Brief Glimpse Of
Sharon Stone's Vagina?
- Shall we get on
with the show?
- Yes, good idea.
Because in tonight's
car programme...
Richard walks a dog.
James hangs around a gym.
And I say "Good shot."
Good shot.
But before all that,
I'd like to talk
about the original Honda NSX.
We have a picture of it here.
When that car
was launched in 1990,
it was considered remarkable
because it was fast
and exciting like a Ferrari,
but unlike a Ferrari
of the time,
it was also
incredibly reliable
and very, very easy to drive.
Honda killed that car off
12 years ago.
But finally, they've come up
with a replacement.
So I've been down to our
track to see what it's like.
This is it.
It costs £138,000.
Around the same
as a Porsche 911 Turbo S.
And it has
the futuristic lines
you would expect
of a rare-breed Honda.
Power comes from
a 3.5 litre twin-turbo V6.
Backed up by a squadron
of electric motors.
Together, they give
the NSX 573 horsepower.
So you would assume
the performance
is something to shout about.
Now, if you ask Honda
for the technical
information on this car,
they will email you
a file so enormous
that it actually
breaks the internet.
And yet, nowhere in it does
it mention the 0-60 time.
They simply refuse
to tell us what it is.
I know 0-60 times are
irrelevant in the real world
and they're rather childish,
but look, this is a supercar.
It's top trumps, isn't it?
It's important.
So I'm gonna find out what
it is for you using this.
It is a data-o-logger.
Right. Put it in Track mode.
Here we go. Launch control.
Foot on the brake.
Mash the pedal.
(ENGINE REVS)
(ENGINE ROARS)
Phwoarh!
I'm not sure that was
quite as neck-snapping
as a Nissan GTR,
but it wasn't far off.
Let's see what I did.
(BEEPING)
3.2 seconds 0-60.
Which means it isn't quite
as fast as a McLaren 570S,
or a 911 Turbo S,
or a Ferrari 488 GTB.
That's why they're
not mentioning it.
Honda is happy
to quote the top speed.
Which is 191 miles an hour.
But that too is slower
than its rivals
from Ferrari, Porsche,
and McLaren.
So has the new NSX
got anything
in the performance department
that makes it rise above
its supercar peers?
Well, yes, actually.
Firstly,
there are the brakes,
which are fly-by-wire.
There is no physical
connection to the pedal.
That's because they
have to harvest energy
to recharge
the battery system.
It's a much cleverer
version of that
than you get
on the Porsche 918,
a car that costs
five times as much.
Then there's
the hybrid system.
It uses not one
electric motor,
as you might expect,
but three.
And the way it uses them
is well good.
The one at the back
is the wingman
for the petrol engine,
filling the power gaps
when the turbos lag.
This gives the NSX ballistic
pick-up at any speed.
Look, instant shove.
It's lovely.
But it's the two at the front
that are the real party-piece
because they drive a wheel
each totally independently
of each other.
Which means this car has
a sort of space-age
four-wheel drive.
And that means
extraordinary things happen
when you throw it
into a corner.
So, as you approach
a corner like this one,
computers are
measuring the speed,
they're measuring G-force,
steering input, and so forth.
They're adding power
to the wheel
or taking power away from
the wheel as it's needed.
Then you get perfectly flat,
perfectly controlled corners.
It is a bit like
driving a Honda Civic!
There are people
who would say
that technology
like this in a car,
helping it feel secure,
will make it dull.
But it doesn't
feel dull to me.
It feels tremendous.
I'm going fast
and I'm relaxing.
What's wrong with that?
But the futuristic
four-wheel drive
isn't the only piece of
23rd-century engineering
on the NSX.
The aerodynamics,
for example, are so clever,
they can cool all the motors
while providing vast amounts
of grip-enhancing downforce
to the front and rear wheels.
And it does all this
without anything
as old-fashioned
as huge wings and spoilers.
It's not just the technology,
which is brilliant,
it's that that technology
is on this car.
Yes, we have
hybrid supercars.
We have the LaFerrari,
the McLaren P1,
the Porsche 918.
But they're in the
million-pound bracket.
This is only an eighth
of the price of the LaFerrari,
and it's actually cleverer.
- (ENGINE ROARS)
- I love this.
I love the way it looks.
I love the sounds it makes.
I like the sophistication
of the hybrid drive.
I like the performance.
I like the steering.
I like the interior.
I really, really like it.
And I find myself
wanting one quite badly.
The original NSX made
owning a supercar
less painful
and less expensive.
This has done the same
for the hybrid supercar.
It really is
a worthy successor.
(CHEERING)
(APPLAUSE CONTINUES)
James, Honda...
Honda took ten years
to develop that car.
And?
Ten years is an enormous
amount of time
to do a car.
You can't criticise something
because people spent
too long on it.
People aren't gonna say
"I'm not gonna look round
Cologne cathedral.
They took 600 years
to build it!"
Ooh.
Anyway, I love it.
I love that car.
Anyway, look, we've heard
what you've got to say
about the NSX.
Now it's time to hand it over
to a man who thinks that...
Well, potted plants
are a Communist plot.
Yep. Here he comes.
It's the American!
Come to England.
Shit weather. Shit beer.
JEREMY: And he's off!
Clearly in a tremendous mood.
But it is very wet out there.
Wipers flapping away
as he powers onto
the Isn't Straight.
Looking good.
Where I come from,
this thing's badge
is inaccurate.
Kind of like
a loser's Cadillac.
And yet, strangely,
we're still waiting
for Cadillac's
hybrid supercar.
Right, now,
flying into Your Name Here,
this really is a good day
to have four-wheel drive.
I'm sure even the American
can appreciate
the Honda's
hi-tech features.
What is this
Space Invaders shit?
JEREMY: Clearly not.
Right, full power
for the Isn't again.
Electric ain't for engines.
It's for lights and chairs.
JEREMY: He is not
a modern man, is he?
Right, carving through
the standing water.
Into Old Lady's House.
Slithering about a bit.
Now he's leaning on it
for the Unsettled section.
Past the hangars
and up to Sub Station.
Hard on those wi-fi brakes
for the second-to-last corner.
How's he gonna manage
through here?
Yes, stepping out a bit
under power.
Through Field Of Sheep,
keeping it tidy through
there, and across the line!
(CHEERING)
(APPLAUSE DROWNS CHATTER)
Right,
let's see now where the NSX
goes on our lap board.
Let's have a look.
- Oh.
- Oh, dear, James.
(APPLAUSE DROWNS CHATTER)
James.
Why didn't you tell us
it was very slow?
- It's streaming wet!
- So hang on a minute.
We've had a review from
a tortoise and a wet lap.
Which means we've
learnt precisely nothing.
Um... Yeah, you're right.
Nothing at all.
- Nothing at all.
- So let's move on.
Yes, let's do that by
popping some loose change
in the ticket machine
so we can park awhile
on Conversation Street.
(JAZZ)
(CHEERING)
OK, now...
- I've got some conversation.
- Good.
Last night at midnight,
there was alarm in Stuttgart.
The Green Party
that runs the city
asked everyone here not to
use wood-burning stoves
and not to drive
their car today.
- Why?
- Because of the smog.
(LAUGHTER)
Am I making this up?
- There it is.
- (APPLAUSE)
I can't...
I can't imagine
anything clearer.
That is... That is gin-clear,
but according to
the Green Party...
I'm not making this up.
You're all
from Stuttgart, yes?
There is an alarm today
- because of the smog.
- Yes.
- (LAUGHS)
- Where is it?
How clear is it
on a good day?
- We've got a photograph here
of Beijing on now.
- (LAUGHTER)
Let us compare and contrast
Beijing on a smoggy day
with Stuttgart on a...
- Not the same.
- ...a smoggy day.
Can I just ask,
what would you have done
if they'd have
actually ordered you
not to drive cars?
At the moment,
it's an advisory.
If they said you are
banned from driving cars,
what would you have done?
Come on the train?
That's unbelievable.
But this is the thing
that we don't really
understand about Germany.
Once something becomes
a rule, it is a rule.
I once had a very
interesting conversation
with two friends of mine.
One is from California
and one is from Germany.
We were talking about
losing your driving licence.
The Californian said, "In
Germany, what would happen
if you lost your licence
and then you drove your car?"
The German said,
"No, you cannot do this."
(LAUGHTER)
He says, "I know
you're not supposed to,
but what if you did?"
He said, "No. You cannot
drive. You have no licence."
(LAUGHTER)
The Californian
went, "Yeah, man,
"but late one night,
you just...
hell, you go for a drive."
The German went,
"It is impossible
to drive without a licence!"
- Impossible!
- Impossible.
There's an interesting thing
I discovered here.
On a motorway,
obviously you can drive
as fast as you like.
You get people
sometimes, not often,
cos your lane discipline
is unbelievable,
but sometimes they sit in the
outside lane just dawdling.
If you tailgate them... OK?
I've got the fines here.
You get a 400 euro fine,
two penalty points,
and a three-month ban
for tailgating.
- That is extreme. Ouch!
- Yes.
But if you overtake them
on the inside,
just go past them
that's a 150 euro fine,
and one point.
Well, there you go.
No. This is where
it gets really good.
If you go on the hard
shoulder to overtake,
the emergency lane,
that's also one point
but only a 90 euro fine.
There's your answer.
That's what you do!
No, no.
No, because... Aha.
You may think that.
But if you fit your car
with blue lights,
flashing blue lights,
basically,
you turn you car
into a police car,
you get... I've got
the point fines here.
20 euro fine
and no points at all!
- What? You're joking!
- (LAUGHTER)
- No, you don't understand.
- That is true.
That is very strange
to our ears.
Cos if you tried that
at home in the UK,
you would be charged
with impersonating
a police officer,
and you would never
get out of prison, ever.
People say Germans have
no sense of humour.
If you want to know
what no sense of humour is,
impersonate a policeman
in Britain.
Then you'll know
what no sense of humour is.
Right, that is the end
of Conversation Strasse.
(CHEERING)
We all like the idea of
a sports utility vehicle.
A car that can handle
the Australian outback
at the weekend
and then set a new
lap record at Hockenheim
on a Monday morning.
But even the German
car-makers
can't seem to make
the concept work.
We've got this from Audi.
The RS Q3.
Which is a dismal car.
BMW have the X4,
I think that's called.
Don't want
one of those, either.
Mercedes have
this horrible monster.
They're all just rubbish.
And let me guess.
You have a solution.
- Yes, I do.
- Oh, God.
Yes, I do. A car
that is both sporty
and utilitarian.
This will be good.
Ye of little faith.
Watch this.
JEREMY: This is
a Land Rover Discovery
doing utilitarian things
in Britain's
muddy underbelly.
And obviously
a machine like this
cannot possibly be
converted into a sports car.
Or can it?
First of all, we have to remove
this rather ungainly body.
You can't do that
with a modern car
because the body is the
chassis. It's the skeleton.
If you take it away,
you're left with nothing more
than a collection
of unjoined-up parts.
However, you can
remove the body
on an old Discovery
like this,
using nothing more
than one of these.
(QUIET RATCHETING)
After just 40 minutes
with no help
from anyone else,
I ended up with this.
Obviously
it's still utilitarian.
It will still wade
through rivers
and crawl its way
up muddy banks.
But now there's a...
a sporty flavour as well.
Without the heavy body, it
feels nimble, agile, light.
If it weren't for the fact
that the windscreen is now
very close to my face,
it would feel like
a Lamborghini Gallardo.
The only real problem
with this
is that Britain
is a police state,
and if I took this
on a public road,
I'd be stopped immediately
by the constabulary
who would point out
that I was
contravening about...
4,870 different laws.
It's not warm, either.
Oh, no, that's stupid!
Happily, both these
problems would be solved
when I fitted it with
the body from a sports car.
And this is the sports car
I've gone for.
A 1978 MGB.
Highly-trained men
are now removing its skin
which will then be mated
in a delicate two-hour
operation...
...to the internal organs
of the mud-plugging V8.
The following morning
my incredible car was ready.
It is incredible
that in a shed I have created
something which has...
eluded the combined might
of the motor industry.
It is a proper
sports utility vehicle.
I call it the MGD,
and now I'm going to find out
how well it works on a road.
This is...magnificent.
And it is quick. Oh, yeah.
To demonstrate
just how quick,
I'm going to do a drag race
against the motor
industry's idea
of an SUV.
(BRAKES SQUEAK)
Little bit of play there.
(REVVING)
Let's do this.
Come on! Yes, look at this.
The 1.5-litre diesel...
...is no match
for the 3.9-litre V8 MGD.
Come on, Pride of Britain!
Yes! Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ah...ah...ah.
Oh, God.
The brakes don't work.
With the performance
box ticked,
I continued my testing.
In many ways,
the MGD puts me in mind
of an Audi R8 Spyder.
I mean, OK, in the Audi,
the dials would work.
And the switches.
And the brakes.
And the steering.
And it's a bit less
bouncy, but...
both of them
are four-wheel-drive,
two-seater,
drop-head V8s.
There is, however,
one very big difference
between the two cars.
You can't do this in an Audi.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Moments ago I was haring
round a handling track,
and now look.
(CHUCKLES)
It's brilliant.
- Oh, no!
Not now, you bastard.
- (ENGINE STOPS)
I mean, you wonderful thing.
Choke. Oh.
Yeah, that...
(ENGINE FAILS TO START)
It's on its shutdown thing.
It's just to save fuel,
it goes on two cylinders
sometimes.
(ENGINE REVS)
Once the engine management
thingy had run its...
diagnostic program,
I was back on the move.
Here we go.
Yes.
Mighty four-wheel-drive
system hauling me up that.
- (CLUNKING)
- What the hell?
Argh! Aargh!
I'm stopping. Stopping.
Oh, Lord,
that is not right, is it?
As I got going
for the second time,
I realised
I'd been a bit of a chump.
The mistake I've made,
of course,
is that I've introduced
you to this car
before I've really tested it.
That's not
what car-makers do.
They test a car
and then show it
to the press and the public.
I'm doing that
the other way round.
I'm introducing this to you
before I've done
the testing and...
(ENGINE STOPS)
Oh, for Christ's sake.
(HE CHUCKLES)
You little beauty.
Er, now, yes,
what was I saying?
I think the issue is
really you're watching
my workings-out here.
What you really want to see
is the finished product.
That's what
I should have done.
- Oh, Christ's sake.
- (ENGINE STOPS)
Right.
At this point, I decided,
for no particular reason,
to scrap the MG idea
and go for
something else instead.
This is what I chose.
A 1980s Mercedes SL.
Partly because
it's the very essence
of quiet, urban restraint,
taste and elegance.
It's a car that was driven
by Bobby Ewing in Dallas.
Mostly, though,
I chose it because
it would fit more snugly
on the Discovery chassis.
(TOOLS WHIRRING)
This time,
the men worked tirelessly
for nearly a whole day
to marry the two cars
and the result
was spectacular.
It's a car
I have justifiably called...
The Excellent.
The internal organs
from a Landrover Discovery
mated to the beautiful skin
of a glamorous Mercedes SL.
To create a vision of pure...
What's the word?
- OTHERS: Rubbish.
- It's not rubbish.
RICHARD: Did you paint it
with a brush or a bucket?
It's got those headlights
that swivel when
you go round a bend.
So they point at the road.
OK, let me ask you this.
Which would you rather have?
The Excellent or that Porsche?
BOTH: That Porsche.
- Why?
Because it's better
in every single way.
To prove my cynical
colleagues wrong,
I invited them
to go for a drive.
Oh, kind.
See? It's an optional extra
for the shorter gentleman.
- Are you comfy, Hammond?
- No.
- Is this as in as I can get?
- Yep.
- Right, listen to this.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
Oh, no, it moves!
We'd only gone a few miles
before Richard and James
completely
changed their minds
and realised that The
Excellent was the best car
they'd ever been in.
No, we haven't.
Stop saying things
in voiceover
that aren't true.
I thought you'd
changed your mind.
No! Maybe a bit.
It's worse than I thought.
- Can I put the heater on?
- That's not connected.
- Is it not?
- No.
- What's that dial down there?
- Speedometer.
Why have you got that one,
not that one?
- That doesn't work.
- Has it got a fuel gauge?
- Not as such.
- Has it got
a temperature gauge?
Not really.
There's a lot of wires
hanging out of the dash
that aren't connected
to things.
You haven't given it
an interior.
(HE LAUGHS)
RICHARD: I can see the road.
JEREMY: I can as well.
RICHARD: No, there's
a hole in the floor.
While Hammond and May had
one or two minor issues,
they both agreed that
if I were to put my car
into production,
it would make me a fortune.
No, we didn't agree
to that, either.
JEREMY: Look, I've
done the maths. Honestly.
The Discovery was £2,500.
Mercedes £4,500.
£7,000 for the work.
That's 14,000 quid. I could
sell this for £120,000.
- No, you couldn't.
- Yes, I could.
A Cayenne Turbo is 120.
A Cayenne Turbo is a proper
car built by Porsche.
This is two scrap cars
glued together by a Muppet.
It isn't designed
for people like you.
What, people with eyes?
People who can dress
themselves in the morning?
JEREMY: I'll tell you exactly
who will buy this car.
People who use
roundy-ended scissors.
Footballers.
- No, they won't.
- Footballers like Ferraris.
Yeah, and Bentleys
and Range Rovers.
- And Aston Martins.
- Not this thing.
To prove them wrong again,
I decided to head for
the nearby Chelsea
training ground.
These are people
who understand cars,
not like you two.
JAMES: Yeah, they understand
cars, that's why they buy
Range Rovers
and Aston Martins.
JEREMY: They buy those things
cos they didn't know
that you could do this.
- I like my car.
- RICHARD: It's shit.
They're flocking to it,
aren't they?
- You just watch.
- Do you mind
if I go and stand
next to something else?
Soon some players arrived,
which gave Richard
and James a chance
to show off their
footballing knowledge.
You're really tall.
You should play in goal.
Yeah, I do, I play in goal.
- I'm the goalkeeper.
- I know that.
What part of Chelsea
are you from?
- I'm from Belgium.
- Oh.
How do you know
they're footballers?
Well, do you not
recognise them?
They're in football outfits.
He doesn't recognise you.
Where's...
Where's Alex Ferguson?
Why don't we ask him?
At this point I dismissed
my ignorant colleagues
so that I could operate
the subtitle machine.
(HE SPEAKS FRENCH)
- Can you do keepy-uppy?
- Yeah.
Take a shot at me.
Well, that's ridiculous.
What can I do with that?
You're supposed to jump.
...flipping horrific.
So you've butchered
a classic car?
Right, watch this.
Little toss...
No.
You need to think of...
(CREAKING)
(ENGINE IDLES)
- Ow.
- Saved.
(HE SPEAKS PORTUGUESE)
Having established
that all top professional
footballers loved my car,
we got back on the road.
Did you get any orders?
I noticed that the car park
was still full of
Mercedes G-Class.
- I saw that.
- Listen.
I could put this
into an auction,
one of those posh,
up-market ones,
and it would sell
for £120,000.
It would not!
To prove them wrong again...
(LIVELY CLASSICAL MUSIC)
Gentlemen,
people are examining...
RICHARD: Yeah,
they are the organisers.
JAMES: They're wondering
about their carpet.
"Handcrafted by a renowned
British atelier...
sympathetically marries
the chassis with..."
- Did you write this?
- Course I wrote it.
"The interior would benefit
from some minor attention."
- Well, it would.
- With a hand grenade.
Lot number 132.
Soon the auction
was under way.
Ferrari 308 GTB, at £118,000.
Lot number 127, start me
with this at 300,000.
And many of the punters
were happy
to pay six-figure sums
for the cars on offer.
At 270,000.
285 for the Countach.
The Countach
just went for £285,000.
I think I'm gonna sell
The Excellent
for more than that.
And then it was time.
Moving on
to lot number 138A.
The Excellent.
It's a fantastic handcrafted,
very unusual machine,
as you can see.
I don't want you...
Beautiful, stylish
Mercedes Benz coachwork.
- Very unusual, unique...
- Unusual?
Here for sale this afternoon.
Start me
if you will on this at...
£425.
At £425...
Any advance at 400?
£500. 550 anywhere?
- RICHARD: Somebody's bid?
- 600 here.
650. 650. 700 now.
We're rattling up.
AUCTIONEER:
700 here. 700. 800 now.
Let's go for 1,000.
(SILENCE)
Let's get going.
Come on, let's sell this car.
- £1,000 here on my right.
- Are you bidding?
- No.
- Jeremy, are you bidding?
AUCTIONEER:
2,000 if you wish.
It's 2,000 and five.
Two, five.
3,000 now. It's 3,000 here.
Three, five anywhere?
Three, one.
At 3,100.
£3,200.
At £3,500.
- It cost me 14,000.
- 4,000.
At £4,000...
At £4,000, any more?
(SILENCE)
At £4,000.
Come and see us after.
You just lost ten grand.
He could have just
thrown it down the lavatory.
(AUCTION CONTINUES)
(CHEERING)
It was rubbish.
Hold on.
- You were bidding
on your own car.
- (LAUGHTER)
Well, a bit. I just wanted
to get the ball rolling.
But even then it didn't work
because you only sold it
for four grand.
It cost you 14,000 to make
so you cost our production
company £10,000.
No, no, not true.
- I put a reserve on it.
- What reserve?
£100,000.
- £100,000?
- So it didn't sell at all,
which means
you cost us £14,000?
Well, yes, but we've
ended up with The Excellent.
No, we're stuck
with The Excellent.
It's really difficult to
know, working with you,
things like this,
is it ambition
or are you a lunatic?
Sadly there isn't time
to answer that question,
because it's time to play
Celebrity Brain Crash.
(CHEERING)
Our guest this week
is a local girl
who is responsible
for one of my all- time
favourite pop songs,
99 Red Balloons.
She is a singer,
she's an armpit hair
enthusiast
and she's
an all- round good sport.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Nena!
(CHEERING)
- Where is she?
- I've got no idea. Um...
Oh. Oh, no...
It's hard to see
through the smog,
but yes, that is...
- Oh, no.
- What's happened here is...
Nena...
yes, she's been
carried away by 99...
- ...red balloons.
- Oh, no.
- Bad.
- (APPLAUSE)
Does that mean
she's not coming on, then?
Well, James, she's floated
up into the stratosphere,
her eyelids have frozen over
and her lungs are inside out.
So that is a no.
It's OK, though.
We anticipated
that Nena may float away.
We have a back-up plan.
We'll activate it.
You sit down.
You see, the thing is...
that more and more stuff,
these days, is being powered
by rechargeable batteries.
You know, phones, laptops.
That sort of thing.
And this is giving the world
a bit of a problem.
Because in Britain, our power
companies only produce
five per cent more power
than we need.
We're only just coping.
It's actually worse
in the United States
cos they produce 16% less
than they actually need,
which means they have
to import electricity.
So what is gonna happen
as more and more people
are buying
and using electric cars?
We're gonna need more power.
We may not be able to cope.
The solution, you may think,
is to build
more power stations.
But if you even suggest that,
weird-beard
environmentalists run around
waving their arms
in the air, going,
"What about the polar bear
and the bats and the newt?"
Anyway, the point is
we are going to need
more and more power
to charge the batteries in
our phones, laptops and cars.
- Where are we
gonna get it from?
- This got us thinking.
How much electricity could we
possibly generate every day
just during our normal lives?
And what if we could
harness it in some way?
JAMES: This is
an office block in
the centre of London.
Like many office blocks,
it has a revolving door,
which spins constantly
as people come and go.
So, why not simply connect
that door to a generator
and turn all that spinning
into electricity?
RICHARD: And it's not just
revolving doors, either.
Many of us have dogs
and every day we take
those dogs for a walk.
A dog scampers hither
and thither, running ahead
and snouting under hedgerows.
So why not attach it
to a trailer like this?
Dog pulls the trailer along.
Inside this wheel
is a dynamo.
It makes electricity,
goes along these wires
and into this capacitor,
and when that dial
reads 100%,
I'm charging my phone,
So, dog's harnessed.
That was easy.
Attached to the trailer.
All I've got to do
is set her going.
And I've even planned
for that. So, here we go.
Fetch!
Ah-haa!
Yeah! Your favourite!
Chase!
Maybe this dog's broken?
Meanwhile, back in London,
James was charging his phone
from a contraption he'd
fitted to the revolving door.
And even Jeremy had decided
to get in on the action.
JEREMY: This school
sports day,
in my mind,
is a power station.
All we have to do is fit
the children with harnesses
and I could have this
charged up in no time at all.
- (HOOTER)
- Here we go!
Straightaway we can see
that charge is being
produced.
Not much, but some.
Come on, all of you!
Come on!
Put your back into it!
Catch him! Chop-chop!
This is the work of a genius.
RICHARD:
Back in the countryside,
I'd mended my dog
and things were going
well here too.
As you can see,
the dog is now running,
the wheels are turning,
electricity is being
generated.
He's basically
a four-legged Sellafield!
Sadly, however, in London,
it was the middle of the day
and no one had been using
James's door.
As a result,
his phone was dying.
So he had to get radical.
(ALARM RINGS)
15%.
Nice.
RICHARD: Apart from
a couple of hiccups...
Go!
You'll have to put a little
bit more effort in than that.
...everything was going well.
The power was flooding in.
Oh, yes!
25%.
And we were forced
to conclude
that it had been a successful
day for all of us.
Well, when I say all of us...
No. Look, listen.
I can see why you're
here. Um...
Obviously, fitting
children with harnesses
and then videoing them,
and they're not
my children...
I got... I got 45% charge
in my phone.
I got 41% charge.
I got a different
sort of charge.
Anyway, since we had proved--
well, Hammond and I
had proved--
that it was possible
to charge up a telephone--
I began to wonder
if we could charge up a car
using nothing more
than vanity.
(BIG BEN CHIMES)
JAMES: In London alone,
there are over 750 gyms,
and every day they are
full of people
picking things up
and putting them down again
so they can be
more attractive.
So why not use
all this colossal effort?
Let's harness it!
And that's exactly
what we have done.
Ten of the machines
in this gym
have been connected
to a device
which produces a smooth
flow of electricity
that's sent outside to this
G- Wiz in the car park.
Right now
the battery is flat.
So I'm going to plug it in
and then after eight hours,
we'll see how far I can drive
on electricity that's been
generated in there.
Come on, you're slacking.
Right. Unplug from the gym.
Let's see how far we go.
Look at this. This is epic
because I'm driving along
in a car, sort of.
No fossil fuel
has been burned,
and no atoms have been split.
Nothing's been fracked up.
Look, there's a man
pushing that pushchair.
Stick a little dynamo
on that,
kid gets some fresh air,
I get more battery charge.
It's difficult to see who
loses from this arrangement.
I get a trip home,
effectively for nothing,
the people going to the gym
feel good, look good,
they become healthier,
the NHS saves money,
cos people are less likely
to have strokes
and what have you.
If one person in a hundred
gets a free gy...
Hang on.
I was enjoying
driving on pedal
and cross-trainer power!
(HORN TOOTS)
And with that, I think
it's back to the tent.
(CHEERING)
James... James May,
how far did you get
after eight hours
of charging?
Actually, it was
better than I expected.
I did 21 miles.
Hang on, though. To get
from our office in London
to my home in nearly Wales,
that's 130 miles,
21 miles at...
So six stops at gyms,
eight hours a time,
and the actual driving,
it would take me three days
to get home!
Or, Hammond, just an idea,
you could maybe get
a petrol-powered car,
put some petrol in it,
and be home in two hours.
That's a better...
I'm gonna do that.
Yes. So there we are.
That's the future,
and it's made of petrol.
So we've
addressed that nicely.
Moving on...
Now...
There are people
all over the world
who believe we are permanently
on the verge of nuclear war,
alien invasion
or zombie attack.
It isn't a niche thing.
There's 120,000 of these
people at least.
They call themselves
preppers.
- Morons.
- Shut up.
- Idiots.
- And these preppers,
in order to prepare for
an extinction-level event,
stock their homes
with essential supplies,
they go out into the woods
and practise tactics,
and they create what
they call bug-out cars.
They're brilliant.
Here is one. Look.
- Look at that!
- Yeah! I know!
- No, Hammond,
that is not brilliant.
- It is.
Are you saying we can prepare
for a nuclear attack
by putting some spikes
on the wheels of a Hyundai?
What if the nuclear attack
comes from the back
of the Hyundai?
All you're gonna do
with that car
- is snag your jumper on it.
- Oh, don't be so negative.
In this show you have wasted
14,000 of our pounds
on your stupid Mercedes car.
You have wasted
all of our time
with your sweat-powered
electric car.
This is my thing.
Let me do it.
You do realise
there's no such thing
as a zombie, don't you?
- Don't spoil it for him.
- (LAUGHTER)
I like the idea
of being a prepper,
so I thought I'd have a go
at making my own bug-out car.
(BIRD CAWS)
This is what I came up with.
It started life as a VW
campervan, high-top version.
But I've stripped it
of its hippie heritage
to turn it into a vehicle
that can bare its teeth
in a dangerous,
post-apocalyptic world.
And I love it!
I'm so unbelievably
pleased with this thing.
I feel invincible,
ready, prepared.
Which is hardly surprising,
given the modifications
I've made.
At the front,
a battering ram.
You can be pretty sure
the roads won't be clear.
The ram itself
is fitted with spikes
for fending off zombies
at close quarters.
Then, up top,
a bank of powerful
rally lights
to cut through the murky soup
of a nuclear winter.
Of course, not everyone
I meet will be friendly.
So, up here...
...weapons rack.
Everything I need
to defend myself against
cannibals and zombies.
Round here, water. Essential.
Subtle stuff too.
I don't want to stand out,
hence the camouflage paint.
But perhaps most importantly,
the whole of my
bug-out campervan
has been armour-plated.
I really have thought of
everything!
No, you haven't!
All you've done is ruined
a perfectly good campervan.
No, I haven't!
It's brilliant.
It's bullet-proof all over!
- Bullet-proof? Is it?
- Yes.
- Is it?
- Yes, it is.
- Oh, yeah, sounds like it.
- Tanks feel like that.
OK, then, these are guns.
Use them.
- What, on you?
- No, on the van. Shoot it.
- Are we ready, gentlemen?
- Yes.
- Ha! Didn't go through!
- (FIRES)
Just chipped the paint.
That's all you've done.
- Yes. Hammond?
- Yeah?
What you're suggesting
is these aliens,
they're going to travel
trillions of miles
using a propulsion system
that we can't even conceive
and then they're going to
try and take over the world
using .177 air rifles?
Well, if they do,
I shall be ready for them.
Especially given
what I've done in here.
Inside, I've turned this
once- humble campervan
into literally
the highest-tech
command centre imaginable.
Up front,
carbon dioxide scrubbers,
just like the ones
on Apollo 13.
They will purify the air,
even in case of radiation.
And you can measure
that radiation on these
systems up here.
Water. You may not
be able to find it.
Need to make it.
It's essential.
I've fitted a system
that recycles urine.
Basically you do
your number ones up there.
Operate the pumps.
They send the results up,
across, and into the water
purification system.
It emerges from that as
purest drinking water.
Food. I'm gonna need it.
I've got a chicken.
It lays eggs.
They go in there.
And perhaps best of all,
the pâté de foie gras
of the bug-out community--
chicken soup.
I love all this. Setting
out into the wilderness
in my little house on wheels,
knowing I've got everything
I need, whatever happens.
What the...?
Am I penetrating
his bulletproof armour?
Yes. And his food.
- (GUNSHOT)
- Oh! That's my own urine!
- Are you two doing this?
- Yes, he is!
I'd get out of the way
if I were you.
The trouble with the chicken
is, it moves around,
- making this a...
- (RAPID GUNFIRE)
- Oh, good idea!
- Isn't it!
Right, reloading, James.
Reloading.
- (BULLET RICOCHETS)
- Oh, yes!
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
- Good shot.
- Not bad, was it?
Sort of game over now,
really.
Hm.
Right...
It wasn't game over, though,
because I went back
to the drawing board
and started again.
Three months' work.
I've used the same basic
interior set-up,
but I've completely re-thought
the armour plating,
so that whatever
those two have...
(DISTANT WHIRRING)
Now, this is a Scimitar
light reconnaissance tank.
It's small, it's quite fast,
and it's quite manoeuvrable.
Its job is to skip around
the battlefield like a goat
and find stuff.
Now, look at Hammond, running
around in a mad panic.
He thinks I'm gonna
shoot him, but I'm not.
I'm just here
to mark him with a laser.
He's gonna shoot him.
Yes, this is a Challenger 2
main battle tank.
And this really is
a bug-out vehicle.
It's certainly a lot better
than, I don't know,
a Hyundai with spikes
on the wheels.
It'll totally protect its
occupants from radiation,
nuclear fallout, gas,
even a direct hit, thanks
to its incredible armour,
from any known
battlefield weapon.
Then there's this gun,
which is--
there's no other word--
enormous!
120mm.
And it could hit a target--
let's say
Richard Hammond's van--
while the tank itself is doing
30mph over rough ground.
I think, though, today
I shall fire while stationary
because I want to
savour the moment.
OK, thank you, chaps.
If we could stop there...
Right, going down.
Roger. Going down.
Oh, dear!
I've loaded the gun with
a high- explosive shell.
It's a tracer shell,
so we'll be able
to monitor its progress
as it arcs toward the target.
Oh, Commander Clarkson,
this is fantastic!
I can see him right there.
Have you got him?
Yeah.
You bastards!
Oh, just put him out
of his misery, will you?
Fire!
I'm not sure his bug-out
vehicle was quite as strong
as he may have
led you to believe.
Right...
Many months later,
I was ready to unveil
my third attempt...
...an impregnable fortress.
Oh, yeah!
This is bug-out heaven!
I've used as my inspiration
the armoured personnel
carrier from Aliens,
on the basis that if it can
protect Sigourney Weaver
from that metal bitey
thing with teeth,
it can keep me safe
from Jeremy Clarkson
and James May.
Underneath this beast
are the basic elements
of an Alvis Stalwart.
So it was already
armour-plated, amphibious,
massively powerful,
six-wheel drive
and four-wheel steering.
And what I've gone and done
is improve it.
(HISSING)
It's got a honeycombed
lattice work
of ceramic-steel
armour plating.
It's three times thicker
than the armour you'll find
on the turret of
an Abrams A1M1 tank.
In testing, I fired a 7.62
round at that hull,
and all it left
was a mark like that one.
This thing is incredible.
Whatever those two
are planning this time,
it won't work.
They won't be able
to damage my soup now.
(CONTROL ROOM CHATTER)
JAMES: Drone feed stabilised.
Vehicle spotted in the open.
45 stand by to engage target.
45 stood to engage target.
This shell...
is twice as powerful
as the shell we fired
from the tank.
And it can hit a target
13 miles away.
Loading weapon.
Hot room, gun loaded.
Gun ready.
Fire mission,
target number
Uniform Tango 1805.
Altitude 35.
Direction 4600.
Gun target line 130.
Ready 68.
Command approve.
45. Engage.
Command approve. 45. Fire.
They're bored. They've
realised I'm unhurtable...
...and given up.
Five seconds to impact.
They probably think
it's really funny.
I'm out here all...
45. Target destroyed.
(SIREN PULSES)
(CHEERING)
- Yeah.
- (APPLAUSE CONTINUES)
Now,
we went through
the wreckage afterwards
and this is all that remains
of Richard Hammond.
He's just dust,
and we know it is Hammond
because we found this
suspiciously white tooth...
- (LAUGHTER)
- ...in it. That's...
(APPLAUSE)
- That's him.
So, there you are, preppers.
The tragic remains of Richard
Hammond are proof positive
that your hobby is
utterly pointless.
- You spilled him!
- Spilt him on the floor.
Now you've got him
all over your shoes.
I know. Even when he's dust,
he's annoying.
- Anyway...
- (LAUGHTER)
On that terrible
disappointment,
it is time to end.
He's pretty much gone now.
Thank you very much
for watching.
See you next time. Goodbye!
(CHEERING)