Hello and welcome to
a Grand Tour special,
which begins with this
the Volkswagen Beetle.
It's a car we hate very much
because it appeals only
to Nazis and hippies,
and we are neither
of those things.
However,
if you remove the bodywork
and replace it with something
a bit more fun -
something like this...
You end up with a beach buggy,
and that's brilliant.
We love beach buggies.
However, Mr. Wilman disagrees.
He says that
if they'd been any good,
they would have caught on,
and he points out
that they didn't.
So he hatched a plan.
And it's this:
he said all three of us
must buy a Volkswagen Beetle,
turn it into a beach buggy,
and then report with it
to a wild, rugged
and extremely remote place...
Here... on the coast of Namibia.
This is what I've built.
It's as close
as you can possibly get
to the original 1964 beach buggy
built by Bruce Meyers.
Underneath,
it is a 1950s Beetle...
Beetle floorpan,
Beetle suspension,
Beetle engine, Beetle gearbox.
It's got Beetle lights on it.
I've even got
a Beetle speedometer
and Beetle hubcaps.
It's brilliant!
This is a beach buggy very like
the one that Steve McQueen drove
in the original
Thomas Crown Affair.
And if it's good enough...
- Oh, God.
- Ha-ha!
I've been joined by the 1970s.
Yes.
James May has built
what a beach buggy was,
what I've built is what
a beach buggy can be...
if you have a bit of imagination
and some purple
metal-flake paint.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
There, I believe, is the start
point of our adventure.
What an extraordinary place.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I mean, more seals.
What David Attenborough
never told us about those
is how bad they smell.
Sadly, before our nature
documentary could go any further,
Richard Hammond
emerged from the mist.
Ooh, hello.
That's not a beach buggy.
- Is it?
- Well, I wouldn't call that...
- Ah-ha!
- Oh, geez.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Dick-Tari!
Behold!
What are you wearing?
Well, I'm in Africa!
These trousers,
did they say in the shop,
"I'm afraid
they are yellow, sir"?
When you left, they went, "Yes!
20 years we've had
those on the hanger!"
Shut up.
And then we must
move over to this.
- Yeah.
- We were told
to build beach buggies.
- Yes.
- Beach buggies.
- It's not a beach buggy.
- It isn't.
It is a beach buggy.
It isn't a beach buggy.
It's got a roof!
There's no Beetle
in here at all.
Yes, there is.
Beetle engine in there.
OK, this space-frame chassis...
- Yeah.
- Is it from a Beetle?
- No.
- These enormous suspension components
Yes, That don't even fit
under the bodywork.
- You've got two lots of suspension at the back.
- Twin shocks.
- Twin shocks?
- Well, you know... - I like an off-road sort of vibe.
To get here,
we had to drive on a beach.
- Yeah.
- Ours have made it.
I didn't need two lots
of rear suspension on mine.
Neither did I.
Look, we were told
to come to Africa.
If we'd been told to go to Santa
Monica Beach, then this, with its...
incredibly vivid paint...
That's the most metal flake
I've ever seen.
Any beach in the world.
Um...
- H-Hang on, what's that?
- That's the engine.
- What engine is it?
- V8!
I've put a V8 in a beach buggy!
Well, no, you haven't.
You've parked your
beach buggy quite close.
It's not in it!
- It isn't in it.
- No.
You've reversed into a V8,
but not quite hard enough.
It's only gone in
a third of the way.
Do you have any idea
how difficult it is
to fit a V8 to a beach buggy?
- Well, it doesn't fit!
- It's obviously impossible.
Exactly, it's impossible.
This is no ordinary V8.
It started out in life
as a 3.5 litre V8
from a Range Rover,
but I've modified it, so it
produces 180 horsepower.
Can I just say,
you were doubting
the credibility of mine
as a beach buggy.
Yeah. Yeah.
The defining characteristic
of a beach buggy
is an air-cooled,
flat-four Beetle engine.
No, that's not an engine, James.
That's just a fan.
How many horsepower
does yours have?
94!
So I have twice
as many horsepower.
- Shall I tell you something?
- They're not in the car, though.
- They are, they're near it.
- Yes.
It's interesting, isn't it?
I mean, that is an entire...
Nothing about that
is interesting.
Well, This is a blank canvas
onto which you could
paint your personality.
- Yes.
- Yours has got
a prolapsed V8 hanging
out of its backside
and terrible paint.
Mine is a rather magnificent
"Daktari" -themed off-roader.
That's got nothing on it!
- You can express... All your personality,
- It is a bit boring.
And it's standard.
It's not...
What do you mean, standard?
- Its standard.
- A beach buggy.
It's tasteful.
What?
- Oh.
- The bat sat-phone.
We've got a message from...
Mr. Wilman.
Right, go on.
"Since you're in
beach buggies..."
Well, us two are.
"Since you're in beach buggies,
you will now
drive to the beach."
Uh...
Uh... do you think
he's taken leave of his senses?
Well, he was never that good
at geography, was he?
No, he wasn't. "You'll now
drive to the beach."
Hold on.
Oh, no, there's more.
"The beach
to which you will drive
is located on the
crocodile-infested Kunene River
at the northernmost point of
Namibia, where it meets Angola.
It's 1,000 miles away."
- 1,000 miles?
- 1,000.
What we needed
at this point was a map,
so we decided
to head north up the coast
and find the nearest town.
Let the journey begin!
And what a journey
it would be in these cars,
cars that were born
in interesting times.
So, it's 1964,
the word "teenager"
has started to appear
in the world's dictionaries,
people are listening
to new types of music,
they're smoking
new types of stuff.
And then, in California,
the beach buggy arrived!
It was perfect!
Girls and boys,
beach barbecues...
The first design criteria was
that the front fenders were flat,
so you could stand a beer on it.
That's how you design a car!
Jimi Hendrix had a beach buggy
and President Nixon didn't.
Tells you all you need to know.
What I really like about the beach
buggy is that it's a testament
to the ability of
the human spirit to triumph.
Because somebody looked
at the Beetle and said,
"Well, that's the legacy of
the world's worst dictator.
Let's turn it
into a beach car."
After a lonely hour
of driving north
through the swirling mist,
we still hadn't found a town,
but we did find something else.
Jesus.
I'll tell you what,
he must have been
going at a right old lick
when he hit the beach.
He must have been.
Right, the sea is there.
That's half a mile away.
I'd say so.
So he got it up the beach,
and then sort of did
a handbrake turn.
- Power-slided it in.
- How do you do a handbrake...
How did it get here, seriously?
Can I just say...
my nipples are erect.
- What, 'cause of this jacket?
- No.
- Oh.
- It's cold.
- It is, isn't it?
That's an unwise
wardrobe strategy.
Yeah, well, you know,
Africa, on a beach, I thought...
- So did I.
- I'm surprised.
The beach has got
the sea haar on it -
mist, fog, cold.
- If you look over there...
- Hm.
Sunshine, blue sky.
- Why don't we just go inland...
- The coast road.
Find the coast road which
will take us to a town.
And that'll be in the sun.
That's a better idea.
With a plan worked out,
it was time to get moving again.
Oh, dear.
Did you modify
the battery as well?
Oh...
- It's obviously not charging up.
- No.
Because I didn't modify it.
Yeah.
I'll just see if mine works.
- Oh, yeah.
- Let me just try mine.
Yeah.
- Push?
- Hm?
Can I have a push?
After the film crew
had got me going,
I used my massive horsepower
to catch the others.
But by the time we were
back together again...
it was going dark.
The sun, as you can see
over my shoulder, has set,
and we still
haven't found a road.
It's also going to be very,
very, very cold.
Lights on.
We have got to find this road.
This is not going to be
too clever...
in the dark.
I've rather crudely
rigged up my torch,
wedged in the windscreen rail,
in the hope that you can see
my last pieces to camera.
Oh, bollocks!
Oh, cold!
Finally, though,
it looked like
our luck had changed.
Ooh, hello! Hello!
What's that?
- It's not a hotel.
- No.
It smells of excrement!
Oh, wow, look at this!
There's still, like, plates
and cups and saucers
and things in here.
I'll tell you exactly
what this is.
It's an abandoned mine.
They do mine round
in Namibia, don't they?
What do they mine for?
- Diamonds.
- Diamonds?
Yeah, but they wouldn't
have left if there were any.
They obviously left,
and not yesterday.
Look, there's no road here,
is there?
- No.
Apart from anything else,
we can't find our way
around in the dark
'cause we can't navigate.
- Well, I can.
- How?
- Stars.
- No, you can't.
- I can.
I can't do very many
things, I admit...
anything, but I can do that.
How do you navigate
by the stars?
Uh...
find the Southern Cross.
Yeah, but that's
really complicated.
Right, do you want to sleep
in the excrement mine?
No, this is out.
So, we have to keep going,
whether we like it or not,
till we find...
We have to, so listen.
I shall find the Southern Cross.
You can't find the Southern
Cross with a hammer.
I've found it! Ha! I've found it.
It's there.
It's like a kite.
- That one there?
- Yeah.
It's a kite shape.
It's sort of...
Now, you take
the long axis, yes?
- Yes.
- Mm-hm.
And draw an imaginary line
through it, down to the horizon.
Yes? Now, you intersect it
from a line drawn
between two other stars,
and where those
two imaginary lines meet,
directly underneath it
is due south.
So if it's those two...
Which it is, I'm sure of it...
You draw a line...
Oh, this is a bad idea!
We are now trusting
our lives to an orangutan
who thinks he's Patrick Moore.
There it is.
There's the two stars.
Draw a line...
I'm not getting many directions
from you, Jeremy. Is this right?
You're heading a little bit
too much to the right.
You need to go left a bit.
Good, good.
Oh, I'm so confident.
You two are going to be eating
humble pie when the sun comes up.
Despite the confidence
of Jeremy Columbus,
no road appeared.
Oh, this is grim.
Excuse me.
I've been on the go
a very, very long time now.
Guys, I'm sorry.
I'm not driving another inch.
I can't do this.
It's three o'clock
in the morning.
I'm exhausted.
He does have a point.
The next morning,
we woke, having
slept on the sand,
huddled round our engines
for warmth.
You muppet. What's that?
Um...
"Um" what?
I never knew
Namibia had two seas.
It doesn't have two seas.
No, it has one
massive "cee" in it.
One massive, stupid "cee"
that's navigated us back
to where we started.
- Can I just say...
- It wasn't my... I...
Why did we even believe you
could navigate by the stars?
You can't even read a compass.
There are two "cees".
There's two "cees" here
for believing that
that "cee" could navigate us.
- No, you're right.
- I couldn't possibly...
Really, I don't understand that.
Freezing cold,
sandpapered on the face...
- You've got a coat on.
- It's thin. Have you felt it?
I haven't even got a thin coat.
I've only got
a T-shirt. Anyway,
I'm not going to be
competitive with you
about who's the coldest.
- I'm the coldest!
- We're all the lostest.
Never mind. Look,
let's not get bogged down
with whose fault it was.
There's no being bogged
down with it, is there?
It was yours.
We can either go
back into the desert
to look for a road,
or we can just do what
we were doing yesterday,
and stay on the beach.
At least we know, if we
keep the sea on our left,
we're going north.
- Yes.
- That's a fair point.
- Let's navigate by the sea.
- Yes.
With our new...
Well, newish...
Plan in place,
we set off once more.
So here we are. These are our
wheel marks from yesterday.
24 hours of cold, misery...
to achieve exactly nothing.
I mean, it is exactly nothing.
But, apart from that
and the weather...
and Jeremy Clarkson,
it's all going really well.
As we continued north,
the misery of
the previous day was banished
by the sheer bigness
of our surroundings.
Oh, this is
an astonishing place.
I've got a dune the size
of Mount Everest to my right,
the Atlantic Ocean to my left...
This is absolutely epic.
This is proper
beach buggy driving.
Sun's out, sea's there
with the surf.
It's like being
in the Beach Boys.
Amidst all
this loveliness, though,
there was one small elephant
edging its way into the room.
Chaps, I don't want to
have to say this,
but is the tide coming in
or going out?
Uh... I'm guessing in.
There's no way
up the sides of that.
And if the tide comes in
that far, which it does,
we've had it.
Got to keep moving here.
We cannot afford to get stuck.
With some generous
use of the throttle,
we managed to get clear
of the sea-and-sand-dune
pincer movement.
But then we had another problem.
I'd say that was the end
of the beach.
How does that
just end like that?
- It does just end.
- That is the end.
And the Namibian
government doesn't allow us
to drive on the salt pans,
and that's what that is.
This meant, according to James,
we had only one option.
We've got to go back
the way we came.
But if the tide's coming in,
that narrow bit
will have become impassable.
That's why I think if we see a
good opportunity to turn left,
like we did last night,
we do it.
Are you honestly suggesting
we go back in the...
Well, where else can we go?
We'll either drown
or starve otherwise.
Right, we've just
got to find a bit
where we can get inland
before the tide comes in.
That is getting closer to that,
and when that happens,
we've had it.
But as we thundered along,
the dunes refused
to open up and let us in.
That's the sea!
It's the sea, there!
Oh, it's coming at me!
I still say
we can't get out here, look.
No left turn at the moment.
This is where you need a V8!
Oh, shit.
Oh, Jeremy's in trouble!
That is not looking good!
Come on, come on. Whoa.
Oh, no.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
Not a good place.
Oh, God.
Uh... I'm in the sea.
Because it was
a bit of an emergency,
my colleagues
decided to help for once.
Go.
No.
Is that just spinning?
It's beached under there.
I don't see why
I can't push him with that.
- All right, then. Try.
- All right.
James, count us in.
Three, two, one, away!
- Yes!
- Right, let's go!
Me getting beached cost us time
we never had in the first place,
and we were still trapped.
Jesus Christ.
Ah, it's coming in.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
Whoa!
Oh!
Oh, that's bad.
Shit.
Whoa!
Come on, baby, come on.
Mercifully, the dunes finally
started to fall away
and we were saved.
- And we're through!
- We are, we are.
That's a relief.
So nearly got stuck then.
We'd now been
on the go for 36 hours,
and we were pretty much back
where we started from... again.
We were also soaked,
frozen, worn out,
and because
we had no food with us,
we were also hungry.
But then Bear Clarkson
came to the rescue.
Cold you go and get
some driftwood for a fire?
And could you fashion a rudimentary
barbecue grill of some sort?
OK. Where did you get
the fishing rod from?
It's my whip aerial.
It's a beach buggy.
- I thought of that.
- They're fishing rods.
This is going to make a perfect
little fish grill thing, look.
Have you got a fire lit yet?
I thought you were fishing.
I am fishing.
My car's fishing.
- Look.
- Well, is it?
- Yeah, look, I've got the rods attached.
- It's parked.
- What's that?
- That's the grill.
So we hold that with the
pliers from my multi-tool,
cut the fish up, fillet it...
Can you do that? There's no point
asking him. He can open a tin...
Can you fillet a fish?
- What, is it only fish?
- Well, it's the sea!
What did you think I was
going to catch, a chicken?
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
- No, wait. Yes!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
While Hammond went off
to get more driftwood,
James and I set about
gutting the catch.
Use his car
as the table. There we go.
- That's his gut. Look. You've got it.
- Yeah, right.
Oh, God. Shit. Look,
it's all gone literally
onto his exhaust.
Oh, no. Never mind.
Look, I need your help.
Right, saw its head off.
- Ah, there we go.
- Excellent.
- I think, but I'm not sure...
- It's gone under his seat.
Oh, no. Has it?
It's all right,
I'll get it out later.
Oh, it's done a treat, this.
Look at this, Hammond.
Mm.
Oh, that's all right, isn't it?
Ooh.
It tastes like fish, doesn't it?
OK, does anybody want a beer?
- Have you got some?
- No.
Oh, you...
That deserves a stabbing.
That is a proper stabbing.
That's properly out of order.
After lunch,
we set off once more
into the dunes.
Right,
so let's keep heading east.
And we must come to
a road at some...
There has to be a road.
But, for mile after mile,
there wasn't.
It's the Namib Desert.
"Namib" in the local dialect
means "big nothing".
It must be the prettiest
desert in the world.
It's just a sea of dunes.
Dunes which were getting bigger.
Bloody Nora,
look at the size of that!
Engaging 180 horsepower.
Climbing them in our
two-wheel-drive beach buggies
was becoming tricky.
Come on, you can do this.
You can do this!
But by deploying the V8,
I was sort of all right.
Yes!
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
Hammond had grippy tyres,
so he was all right, too.
Please, make it. Please.
Please!
Ho-ho!
There you go!
However, back in the 1960s...
Come on, little car.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no.
- Stuck?
- Yes.
Two problems. Number one,
he's put a 90 horsepower
engine in it,
which actually
is probably only 40.
- Yeah.
- And number two,
he will not use full power ever.
Well, he's got a 90 horsepower
engine, but a 5 horsepower foot.
And I bet you any money he's
saying "I had a misfire."
You've got to push the
accelerator all the way to...
I know, but... I know that.
It occasionally has
a little misfire moment,
and then I lose it.
He said it!
And so the afternoon continued.
The Grunt Machine and the Grit
Machine would forge ahead...
There is no way in hell
I'm doing this!
Yes!
You star!
And then there'd be
the inevitable radio exchange.
We appear to be a man down,
Jeremy.
James May, where are you?
Because we spent so much time
waiting for Captain Misfire,
we were still in the desert
as dusk fell.
And failing light meant it
was hard to spot obstacles.
Right, sit rep.
Jesus Christ!
Holy...
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit!
Look at it!
Mate, I've got to have a look.
Oh, shitty death...
- I locked up. That was just...
- Look, he's buried!
- You've buried the front.
- I was completely locked up.
'Cause I would have
gone down that.
Look at it!
My close shave was a reminder
that, after dark,
these dunes would become
very, very dangerous.
It's getting harder and harder
to read the terrain now.
Is that a drop?
Is that a hill?
Is that going up? Is that a cliff?
What is it?
Peril... peril.
Oh, shit!
Oh, I think there's
a drop off there.
It's just a black abyss.
That could be
a huge cliff again.
Eventually,
we could take no more,
and we had to settle down for a
second night around our engines.
We will find a road.
There must...
- It can't... It can't go on forever, can it?
- No.
It has to... There will be
a town, a road... something.
Unfortunately,
to find salvation,
we still had to climb
more dunes.
Climb them and then
get down the other side.
Oh, my God!
Well, that's just a cliff!
Whoa! Aargh!
Whoa, this is a monster.
Oh!
I don't think I can do...!
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
Whoa-a-a-a-a-a!
Here we go.
All three of us
simultaneously...
Holy shit.
Oh-h-h-h, shit!
Argh-hhh! Ha-ha!
Whoa-a-a-a-a!
I wasn't scared.
Oh, my God.
Guys, this is the biggest yet
by a country mile.
Whoa-a-a-a-a-a!
Is that the size of the drop
or what's happened to his penis?
Right, then. Let's see
what all the fuss is about.
Holy shit!
Oh-h-h-h-h!
Phwoar.
And now straighten
those wheels, Richard,
straighten them,
because you've got to
go down straight.
Holy shit.
Oh-h-h-h-h, shit!
That is frightening.
Love this desert.
I'm never, ever, ever happier
than I am when I'm in a desert.
And this... this is the best
desert I've ever been to.
You can never really lose
sight of the fact, though,
that what it actually is
is a big, orange killing engine.
Now, a big crest's coming up.
No idea.
Gentle rolling hill
or massive cliff?
I don't know, Hammond!
Hammond, seriously.
Shit, he's gone.
Hammond's gone, everyone.
Hammond's gone. Big one.
Oh, me.
How the did you get down that?
With my eyes shut!
That was terrifying!
Jesus!
As we continued to head east,
the terrain
eventually levelled out...
which meant we swapped terror
for extreme discomfort.
Ah. Oh, God Almighty.
I don't think these cars
were actually designed
to take this much punishment.
And I know we weren't.
The only thing is,
James's car rides lower
than this and will be worse.
Argh! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Agh!
Soon, the relentless battering
started to cause breakdowns.
Sand... Sand in gear shift.
My throttle is
jammed wide open, people.
The problem is that every
time the air filter, here,
turns as I'm driving along...
Which it does...
It's jamming the throttle.
What's going on here?
What's up?
The throttle is now jamming
fully open all the time.
Oh, problem.
Oh, God.
It is still moving.
Many miles ahead,
we'd pulled over for a break
from the endless bumps,
and James was being
very interesting!
The good thing about this hat is you
can angle it, like a heliostat,
to where the sun's coming from.
Yes, that's true.
But you still look a tit.
Luckily for Hammond, who
could do with the company,
I was back on the move.
Right, a new style of driving
is now required.
This arm for steering,
this arm for changing gear,
and then another arm
for deaccelerating, like so.
Yes!
Accelerate.
Deaccelerate.
Sometimes, if you
listen very carefully,
you can hear my genius.
Back as a threesome,
we continued
with our seemingly
endless journey to the east.
Just need to find a road now.
This is not funny any more.
Enough desert.
I don't want another night
in the desert.
I smell pretty bad.
And I suspect that if we manage
to find somewhere tonight
near civilisation,
we should probably
have a ceremonial
bonfire of the underpants.
In truth, though,
I thought we'd be
in the desert forever.
But then,
late in the afternoon...
I'm looking ahead, and I'm not
seeing an endless sea of sand.
I'm seeing green.
Trees!
Those are trees and shrubs!
Pylons!
That means electricity.
Oh, yes!
Civilisation!
And then, best of all...
Oh, my God.
I honestly thought we had
another night of sleeping...
in the sand.
But, no! Look at it!
Nicest thing I've ever seen.
I could go east,
I could go west...
Whichever way you go, it goes
somewhere. That's the point.
It's a road, it goes somewhere.
You know what we've
just done, don't you?
We've just crossed the Namib
Desert in three beach buggies.
- We have.
- We did.
We did.
There is literally nothing
can stop us now.
Admittedly,
our crossing had not exactly
been as the crow flies,
but we had found our road,
and that's all that mattered.
Oh, yes!
That's the best thing
I've ever seen!
Yes, it is the road to freedom!
What the hell was that?
Something has just exploded
at the back of my car.
Oh, dear.
By the time my colleagues
had got back to me,
I'd worked out
what the problem was.
It's really straightforward, OK?
- The top bolt has come out of the shock absorber.
- Right.
It shot up, boinged
into the coolant pipe,
and three gallons of water
have simply burst out,
going everywhere
except into the engine.
- Right.
- So all I've got to do is reattach the top bolt...
mend the pipe and find
three gallons of water...
which I shall get from a passing
motorist, and I'll be on my way.
- Right.
- All I could do with a hand with
is just lifting the car up
so I can reattach the, um...
Yeah. Well,
is there anybody here?
- There's...
- I suppose a motorist will pass eventually.
The one that gives you water
will also lift it up for you.
You could just
lift it up a little bit.
Or we could go and have a beer.
- I hear traffic. - Yes.
- We'd better not be here.
We don't want to interfere
when you're trying to talk
'cause we might put them off.
Right.
Somewhere along here
there will be a place,
and that place
will have a bar in it
that will contain beer.
Do you have any water?
- Huh?
- Water.
Because the radiator has blown,
so I need just three gallons.
Look, you've got some water
there. Just a bucket.
It's an actual water lorry...
leaking water,
and he won't give me any.
Eventually,
I flagged down a local
who had water to spare.
Thank you.
And then I got on
with the repairs.
That is one reassembled
shock absorber.
That's reattached,
so that's the cooling system
back in one piece.
After an exhausting
five-hour drive,
Richard and I finally
reached a town,
which turned out to be Windhoek,
and we too were
taking on liquids.
Mm.
Back out on the highway, though,
things weren't so good.
What I'm driving here - or
attempting to drive - is Apollo 13.
There's some air
trapped in the system
and I've had to make
a small hole in the front
to get at the radiator.
Bled that,
bled all the stuff
going into the engine.
This is the header pipe.
Everything is bled, and yet,
you do a mile, it overheats.
Another mile, overheats.
Well, we've covered...
20 miles in four hours.
This is the sixth time
in 30 miles that's happened.
Whilst my colleagues
embraced beer and bed,
I steeled myself
for the longest, coldest,
most frustrating night
of my life.
The roads are getting worse.
Honestly, my bones
are going to shatter.
Oh, my God!
- I've had a great idea.
- Oh, no.
Oh, shit, it's really high!