[elevator bell dings]
I told you, I know how to moonwalk.
T-Nice's stomach is not cool
with the whole outer space thing.
Irona's olfactory sensors are not cool
with the whole vomit clean-up thing.
You know,
we're always hanging out over here.
When are we gonna go to your house?
I really want to meet your dad.
He is my favorite rapper.
If we go to my house,
my dad's just gonna make me do chores
or sign me up for some activity.
I'm already doing swim lessons,
synchronized swim lessons, water polo,
diving, harpsichord.
Harpsichord?
Yeah, it's the only time I'm dry.
Why does he make you do all that stuff?
Something about growing up
with opportunities, enriching my life.
Fatherly junk, you know?
Actually, I don't.
My dad sometimes forgets my name.
What up, Tahj?
My boy, Stevie!
Well, at least your dad
lets you do what you want.
I just want to rap.
Why won't he let you rap? He's a rapper.
Because he's strict.
And I think it's because
he doesn't want competition.
Wow, you must really be good.
Can I hear you rap?
I would but...
I don't have a beat, or a mic.
My throat's a little scratchy
from the elevated pollen count.
[knock on window]
Hey, Tahj? Are you in there, son?
It's Bulldozah!
No. Don't tell him I'm here.
Bulldozah, I'm such a big fan.
And I'm such a big fan
of that giant Ferris wheel.
I just love late-night carnival music
and bright lights
outside my bedroom window.
Have you seen, Tahj?
He's supposed to feed Snoop Dogg.
Snoop Dogg is at your house?
Snoop Dogg is our cat.
Have you seen him or not?
The cat or Tahj?
Tahj. I never let
my precious little kitty out of my sight.
Uh...
I'm sorry, I haven't seen him.
That's great.
He was supposed to be home.
He missed his harpsichord lesson.
And now I'm late for my video shoot
with Drake and Weezy.
Uh, another private jet
filled with models in bikinis.
Just what I need on a Wednesday afternoon.
That sounds awesome!
It is, if you like listening
to Weezy complain about the catering.
Can I come?
No.
And when you see Tahj,
you tell him he's in serious trouble
and I'm taking away his bracelet loom.
[muffled] Aw!
Hey.
What was that?
Uh, I was saying
how awe-some it was to meet you.
I have this thing where sometimes
I don't say the end of my word.
Isn't that coo?
No, it's not.
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
I can't believe
you made me lie to your dad,
a man who has a song called
"lie to me and I'll break your face."
Don't worry about him.
The label had him change those lyrics.
His original version was
"lie to me and I'll break your vase."
Well, if I shouldn't be worried,
why were you whimpering and hiding?
Because he's always forcing me
to do stuff I don't want to do.
I want to be about that rap life too.
I got sick skills.
I'd hit you with a verse,
but the acoustics in here are all wrong.
You should tell him what
you want to do with your life.
I'm sure he'd support you.
The only thing he supports
is me taking cooking lessons,
cotillion classes, ballet--
You take ballet?
Maybe.
You wear a tutu?
Only for recitals.
You need to be honest and firm,
and tell your dad how you feel.
About him leaving his law firm
to pursue a career in mariachi music?
I did, but he claims his passion
for the Mexican polka has to be pursued.
See? That's how I feel about hip-hop.
When music is in your heart,
you just have to let it out.
You rap? I'd love to hear it.
Ooh, it's almost lunch.
Can't rap on an empty stomach.
Tahj, you need to come clean to your dad.
I guess you're right.
I'm going to go tell him how I feel.
And plus,
I need to clip Eminem's nails anyway.
Another cat?
No, the real guy.
I just know his dad will support him
once he knows how Tahj feels.
That's the same way I felt
when I told my dad mariachi
was a waste of his time.
Now has me spending two evenings a week
learning something
called: el jarabe tapatio.
[cha-ching]
What are you doing here?
- I'm--
- Eh!
Did you just look me in the eye?
What's the rule about making eye contact?
It's either do it or don't do it.
You have a lot of rules,
and they're hard to keep up with.
Listen, Richie told me I could meet up
with my personal trainer/tutor here.
[doorbell rings]
Absolutely not.
I'm going to tell him to--
come right in!
So I hear you're a--
what does he do again?
He's my personal trainer and tutor.
I figure he can do both
because he was accepted into Harvard
and, well, check out those pythons.
Yeah, sorry I'm late.
Some stranger in the park
wanted to sketch me.
I draw.
Sorry, Harper. We'll leave you alone.
No! Maybe I can help.
I mean, I was just telling you
how we need to spend more time together.
A second ago you told me not
to make eye contact with you.
And that was clearly a joke.
Like the time
I put that snake in your purse.
We're always making jokes.
I was in the hospital for two weeks.
And it was hilarious.
[laughs]
So now that we're co-tutors,
should we discuss lesson plans?
Perhaps over dinner and a movie?
We should probably just
stay here with Darcy.
Who's Darcy?
Ooh, I think I found a rhyme, T-Nice.
Let it flow, Lay-z.
♪ I'm the best there is in the nap game ♪
♪ I'm also the man, in the-- ♪
Yeah, that's all I got.
Tahj, what are you doing here?
Chasing my dreams, one verse at a time.
Did you know your dad
also has sick rhymes?
Tap flame? Lap same? Hap rame?
You said you were going
to go talk to your dad.
I was, but on my way out
I bumped into your dad,
and we just started free-styling.
Then we took a break and had corn dogs.
I like where you're going
with this, Lay-z.
Corn dogs! Ugh!
♪ I can fit 12 of 'em in my mouth ♪
He's not kidding.
It was the most horrifying
yet impressive thing I've ever seen.
You said you were gonna go
talk to your dad--
Chill, double R.
My life is so much better over here.
Your dad lets me be me.
Master Richie,
I beg you to do something about this.
It took them 45 minutes
to rhyme "man" with "plan."
But we did it!
Yeah, Tahj, my dad's great,
but you can't just run away from home.
But, please, feel free
to run away from this home.
Sorry, but Lay-z and I
have some raps to work out.
Come on. We still need to find
a word that rhymes with "hat."
Yea, we've been avoiding
that one long enough.
I have to fix this.
Please do. For the last few hours I've
had a pounding processor ache.
Cliff, we need to work on your rap name.
I really feel like Lay-z
isn't as good as Wiz Cliffa.
I'm not sure I like that better.
Tahj Rose Stokes.
[scoffs] That's even worse.
Dad?
Richie, did you tell my dad I was here?
I brought your dad here
because you two need to talk.
Perhaps tell him about your dream.
Uh... yeah, it was crazy.
I was being chased by this giant snake.
And there was a squirrel
running right next to me,
but I could kind of tell he was in on it.
And then I landed on an ice cream cone.
That is a great dream.
But you missed your harpsichord lesson.
Snoop Dogg is starving,
and Eminem looks like Edward Scissorhands!
You're grounded.
So unfair!
Chest hair!
Come on, let's go.
Thanks a lot, Richie.
I can't believe you snitched on me.
Richie, as a rapper,
I'm not into snitchin'.
But as a father,
I'm happy you betrayed your friend.
Come on.
Hey, Irona. Any texts from Tahj?
- Nope.
- Any calls?
- Emails?
Yes, he emailed to tell you to delete
the invite to his ballet recital.
Was there at least
a smiley face in the email?
There was a finger.
Hola, amigo!
Murray, I thought you said
mariachi was a waste of time.
I did, but that was before I inherited
my dad's passion for the Mexican polka.
[lively trumpet melody]
What's wrong?
People don't usually frown so aggressively
during the Mexican polka.
I really messed things up with Tahj.
Can't you talk to him?
No, he won't return
my calls, texts, or emails.
He's your next-door neighbor.
Walk the six miles over to his mansion
and knock on the door.
Good idea. Want to come?
No, I got a gig.
I'm the horn for a taco truck.
"To be, or not to be.
That is the question."
As long as you're asking,
the answer is yes.
Hello? I'm failing math over here.
Great. I knew you'd get it.
So where are you going to college?
I thought I told you. Harvard.
I know; I just love to hear you say it.
I should get going.
I got a polo match later.
Swoon. Did I say that out loud?
Okay. Out you go.
Randolph is incredible!
When's your next session with him?
Never. He didn't help me at all
with my homework.
Who cares about that?
How can I marry him if I don't
have his phone number?
I'll just guess.
It's got to be one of these.
[singsong voice] You're acting crazy.
You have to set up
another study session with him.
We're meant to be.
Why should I help you?
You tried to run me over
with a lawn mower.
We were playing tag!
Come on, if you bring him back,
I'll do anything you want.
I'm going to need proof.
Slap yourself in the face.
We've got a deal.
Mrs. Bulldozah?
I'm Dr. Yvette, Bulldozah's bodyguard.
You're his bodyguard?
Why are you dressed like a dentist?
Everyone is terrified of the dentist.
[drill whirring]
I'm here to see Tahj.
It's been six months since my last visit.
Get lost.
Please, it's important.
Is that a cavity in your bicuspid?
Okay, I'm leaving.
So you say you're here for
the ballet recital after-party?
Yes. I'm definitely not wearing
this to sneak into a mansion.
Tahj is going to be so happy.
None of the other kids showed up.
Here's your lunch, Darcy.
Did you remember to remove the crusts
from the little toast
I eat the caviar with?
Of course.
How's my homework coming?
Almost done--
through your junior year of high school.
Time for my afternoon affirmation.
Darcy, you are the prettiest,
most beautiful,
most stylish, most gorgeous,
most stunning girl in the world.
Excuse me?
In the universe.
This caviar is...
salty.
So sorry. Let me get you some water.
[doorbell rings]
Harper, door.
Harper?
[groans]
Randy? What are you doing here?
Delivery for Cliff.
Usual veggie hold the veggies,
add sausage and bacon.
Is Harper around? I wanted to say hello.
You will say nothing!
She thinks you're her dream guy,
not a delivery boy who's dad
has to drive him around.
[car horn honks]
Coming, dad!
I got your water!
With bubbles and without!
[grunts]
Who was that?
The cable guy, who do you think?
Are you looking me in the eye?
♪ All right, yo, yo, yo ♪
Cool, that's enough for today.
Hey, Tahj.
Richie? What are you doing here?
I came over here to talk to you.
About the fact that
we're both wearing tutus?
I'd prefer we both ignore that.
Look, I'm sorry I told on you.
I just wanted to make things
better between you and your dad.
No, don't worry. Things are fine.
In fact, they're great.
Tahj!
Hide! Run for your life!
I'm eating one of
your point-shoe cupcakes,
because your ballerina friends
aren't showing up.
Richie?
Don't tell me you came over here
to snitch on your friend again.
What'd he do? What'd he do? What'd he do?
I'm sorry. I can't tell you.
The rapper in me respects that.
The father in me...
says I never want to see you
in this house again.
Go! Sashay!
I can't believe it. I went over there
to make things better with Tahj,
and now I'm banned from his house.
You know what will cheer you up?
Not the Mexican polka.
Then never mind.
Hey, Richie.
Tahj! Why are you here?
You hiding from your dad?
Actually, yes.
But I brought you
a cupcake to make amends.
I'm still mad at you...
less than before the cupcake,
but still mad.
Well, I'm glad everything
worked out in the end.
No, it didn't!
All right, good talk.
Tahj, we are going back over there,
and you are going to rap for your dad.
That's a great plan, but here's the thing,
I've never rapped in public...
or private.
What?
Well, I was going to,
but I switched fabric softeners,
then daylight savings.
There was a bee one time...
Enough excuses.
If this is your passion,
you need to step up
and give it your best shot.
Not you, Murray.
So you three are Tahj's posse?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Si.
Wait, you look a lot like that kid
Bulldozah banned from the house.
Show me your teeth.
Okay, come in.
[doorbell rings]
What's with the flowers?
Oh, they're for Harper.
I think I really like her.
What?
You'll like what I tell you to like,
and I'm telling you not to like her.
Why?
Because if she thinks you like her,
she won't need me to get access to you,
which means no more pampering.
That's the whole con!
What if she and I can
make each other really happy?
It's not about your happiness;
it's about mine.
Hello, Randolph.
I bought a new tutoring dress.
What do you think?
I think it's time to study.
[car horn honks]
Dad, I told you I'd be a while!
[horn honks]
Yeah, I know it's hot. Crack a window!
Who are you talking to?
Uh...
Aren't you familiar with
Shakespeare's long lost play,
Car In Driveway?
Randy! Did I order another pizza?
I don't remember ordering one,
but I'll take one if you got one.
Randolph, why is my dad
asking you about pizza?
Uh...
Because...
I got nothing.
Well, in that case, Harper,
I really like you
and want to go out with you.
Yes!
But I'm not a Harvard boy.
I'm a pizza boy.
No!
Well, since this whole thing blew up,
I'm not paying you.
Wait a minute,
you set up this whole thing?
Yup, but don't feel bad.
You weren't the first
and won't be the last.
I can't believe I got conned
by a 12-year-old.
That is so pathetic.
If your confidence is down,
want to reconsider that date?
Before you answer,
think about what dating a pizza boy
could do for this family.
♪ All right, yo, yo, yo ♪
Whoo.
All right, I'm done for today.
Right? That was hot, right?
Yo, pops, I got something to tell you.
I'ma tell you in a rap.
♪ Yo, yo, yo ♪
Did the air conditioner just cycle on?
Abort, Richie!
Richie?
Yeah, it's me.
Now check this.
Money-making-mur-dog,
hit us with just a touch of trumpet.
Like what you think is right, half that.
I-nasty,
the not-so-human-drum-machine,
drop the beat!
[hip-hop music]
[playful trumpet melody]
Yo.
Her beat-boxing skills are nice.
Ready to do this, T-Nice?
That depends on the barometric pressure.
♪ Some rappers say holler at your boy ♪
♪ I say don't holler ♪
♪ Even if he wants to be
more of a baller ♪
♪ Than a scholar,
let him chase his dreams ♪
♪ Like you chased yours ♪
♪ Maybe you could even open up
a few doors ♪
♪ Being different is what
makes us our own individual ♪
♪ Something, something, something ♪
♪ That rhymes with individual ♪
♪ Here is my last piece of advice ♪
♪ Time to listen to my boy T-Nice ♪
Yo...
♪ It's too cold in here ♪
♪ I'm wearing the wrong socks ♪
♪ I can't concentrate with
the ticking of those clocks ♪
♪ Oh, my gosh, I rhymed ♪
♪ This is the best thing ever ♪
♪ I can't believe I did it,
given the barometric pressure ♪
♪ ♪
[music stops]
That...
was...
amazing.
[laughing]
Gracias.
Not you, Nacho Libre.
[snaps fingers]
[drill whirring]
Ay! Dios mio!
So you really liked it?
I loved it, son.
It reminds me of why I got into the game.
The passion, rhyming with my friends,
and not a lot of yes men.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's right.
So you're going to support
my dreams of becoming a rapper?
If that's what you want,
that's what I want for you.
And if your passion is rap,
well, hey, bro, turn in that tutu.
Whoa, I didn't say anything
about quitting ballet.
I don't want to let down my friends.
There are 45 point-shoe
cupcakes in the trash can.
Those ballerinas are not your friends.
But I am.
And I couldn't be happier
now you get to pursue
your passion out in the open.
Look how important honesty
is in a relationship.
Master Richie, I hate dusting.
Not now, Irona.
You got yourself a great friend, Tahj.
I know. Thanks, Richie.
Since you got that mic in your hand,
let's put in some work
and lay down some rhymes.
Oh. I would, but...
forgot to make my bed.