All right, Irona,
are you sure you packed
everything I need for camp?
Everything is in the bag, Master Richie.
Fishing gear, bathing suits,
and your superhero night-light
to keep you safe.
- I don't need that anymore.
- Should I take it out?
Ah, just keep it in the bag
and take it down to the car.
I can't wait to get to camp.
I'm going to be such
an emotional wreck without you.
I'm going to be forced to distract myself.
Speaking of which,
where are the yacht keys?
I am ready for the great outdoors.
Murray, why are you wearing
underwear on your head?
Pfft. Why do you think?
I honestly have no idea.
This is my secret weapon
to keep away the camp bullies.
The Abramowitz twins will see
this underwear ring
and figure they already wedgied me.
Ha, Abramowitzes, I wedgied myself.
Why didn't you just cut the
ring off a pair of underwear?
[scoffs]
Please, Richie, that...
that would've been a better plan.
Guys, did you hear the news
about camp?
The rat infestation
isn't exactly news.
It's just part of the rustic experience.
I always liked the rats.
They never gave me a wedgie.
Nasty case of hemorrhagic fever
but no wedgie.
No, Camp Bohawk burnt down.
both: What?
Oh, my gosh, what happened?
Apparently, a camper wanted
a really well-done s'more
and, well, got it.
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
This stinks--
now that camp is cancelled,
I'm stuck spending the next two
weeks in this palatial mansion.
[Swedish accent]
Richie,I have your morning smoothie!
Oops, I forgot the garnish.
I'm not really in the mood
for a meatball smoothie.
Camp Bohawk burnt to the ground.
I feel for those poor campers.
Darcy, you care about others?
I just know how much joy
the Abramowitzes get
out of giving you wedgies.
I'm hating seeing you so devumstated.
If you can't go to camp,
perhaps the camp can come to you.
I-I guess we could have the camp here.
We could be the counselors
and give the kids the full experience.
Ooh, and I can be one of the campers.
I've always dreamt of living in a shoe.
He's gonna be really disappointed
when he finds out what camping is.
This is great! Camp Bohawk is back!
Just promise me you won't
invite the Abramowitzes.
Too late, they're on their way.
[cha-ching]
Hey, Harper, want some popcorn?
Fresh melted butter.
You're drinking butter?
Yeah, this way,
my hands don't get greasy.
Pretty smart, huh?
- Dad, what are you doing?
- Oh!
I'm writing something really important,
and it has to be done by tomorrow.
[chuckles]
If it's for school,
how important can it be?
It's not for school.
It's my final appeal
to the Harvard admission board.
I'm drafting a 17-page letter
refuting the letter
they sent me.
"Leave us alone."
Dad, you're spilling butter everywhere.
Don't worry,
I got another pound and a half
simmering on the stove.
I'm not worried about your butter.
I'm worried about my papers.
[grunts]
[sighs]
[screams]
Harper!
Your papers.
Ow.
[cha-ching]
So, campers, was that a fun nature hike?
[all groan]
How often do you get to see
a snail in its natural habitat?
I don't know about the snails,
but it was a great excuse
to try out my trail mix recipe.
Those are just meatballs.
And dirt-- I mixed in the trail.
The thing is,
the campers want to have more fun.
Some of them are having fun.
Those Abramowitzes are evil.
Evil!
So what is being next?
Perhaps we could jet ski
around your wave pool.
No, we never did that at Bohawk.
But don't worry, what's more fun
than sleeping outdoors under the stars?
Oh, in Sweden we have a name
for people who sleep outside.
Stupid.
Well, we always had fun
doing it at Bohawk,
so we're doing it here.
Boys, we are sleeping in the tree house
with Counselor Murray.
Girls, you and Counselor Darcy
are in the pool shed.
What?
It's just the natural camp experience,
with the faint hum of a Jacuzzi heater.
[cha-ching]
Dear Harvard.
"Dfhernic hazarnic."
Okay, let's try this again.
[with tongue out]
Dear Harvard.
I wish I tried those in reverse order.
You think that's hard,
you should try drinking nachos.
I mean, the cheese comes out fine,
but these chips are playing hard to get.
Dad, this may be the concussion talking,
but could you help me type this letter?
I'd be happy to help you type a letter.
So which letter we talking?
I know most of 'em.
[cha-ching]
Isn't this great?
The nature, the fresh air, the peace and--
[truck reversing]
Sorry, I'm replacing all
200 mattresses in my guest wing
with ultra-soft pillow tops.
Well, time to hit the wood.
Are you sure it is being safe
to sleep out here?
Totally.
Trust me,
the only time I felt safe at camp
was inside the cabin.
No!
[birds chirping]
That was fun. Right, guys?
Guys?
[Swedish accent]
"The boys wanted to sleep
"on the pillow tops.
See you in the morning."
[pop music]
♪ ♪
Darcy, you are getting smoked
like a meatball
that is getting smoked.
What is going on here?
Oh, hey, Richie,
we are in the middle
of our morning powwow.
Powwow!
Right, just like at Camp Bohawk.
This is not a morning powwow.
Pa-wow!
I love this word.
Kids are supposed to be singing songs.
Come on, everyone.
♪ Bohawk,
campfires every night ♪
♪ Bohawk, not a firehouse in sight ♪
How did we not see that fire coming?
Richie, we were just trying to have fun.
These kids paid good money to be here.
What? We didn't charge them.
Right.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Let's sing.
♪ Bohawk, stop, drop, and roll ♪
♪ Bohawk... ♪
That's all I remember.
Darcy, I will not let you
disrespect our camp anthem,
and I will not let these kids miss out
on the real camp experience.
Okay, but if they ask
for their money back,
I'm sending them to you.
[cha-ching]
[groans]
Yeah.
Okay, I'm ready to type for you.
I can't believe I agreed to this.
Relax, I have lots of computer experience.
[sighs]
How do you turn this thing on?
Okay, just type what I say.
"Dear Harvard."
What was all of that?
The gist.
What do you mean, "The gist"?
I just said, "Dear Harvard."
I Bruced it up for you.
"Bruced"?
Sure, made it more memorable.
Anyone who reads that
is definitely not going to forget it.
Ooh, how many Ps in hippopotamus?
What? There is no need for that word.
Ah, I'll just guess. Let's say 12.
Okay, no, no, no, stop it! You're done!
You're done. Delete it.
Fine. Hey, I'm just trying to help.
If you want me to delete it, I will.
[whoosh]
Is it gone?
It sure is-- I hit "send,"
which sends it to the delete folder.
[cha-ching]
I'm worried you guys
aren't getting the spirit
of the whole camp thing.
And since last night was such a disaster--
Disaster for you.
Sleeping on those pillow beds is better
than sleeping in a shoe.
While I have no idea what you're saying,
I know you guys aren't getting
the Bohawk experience.
Can you speed things along?
The girls and I are getting mani-pedis.
There are no mani-pedis at Camp Bohawk.
All right, today is survival day.
We will be learning
how to live off the land
in my bedroom.
I will be showing you
two different kinds of wild berries.
One is safe to eat.
The other is extremely poisonous.
Knowing the difference
could save your life.
Save my life!
Murray?
What are you doing?
The Abramowitzes made me play dress-up
all night long.
And the worst part is
I look fabulous.
Your mascara's running, sweetie.
Murray, sit down.
And don't forget to cross your legs.
So, if you come across
hozzenberries and traifberries,
just remember this little song.
♪ if it's a traif, then you're safe ♪
♪ if it's a hozzen... ♪
get to the hospital immediately.
So traifs are sweet, while hozzens are--
Uh-oh.
Don't worry, one of the four doctors I saw
assured me I'm fine.
So we can continue with survival day.
[all groan]
My eardrums are pretty swollen,
but I think I heard some cheers.
Glad to hear you're as excited
as I am to get to fire making.
So, if you're out in the woods
and you want to start a fire...
Bring matches.
It's the only time it's okay
to play with them.
And that concludes survival day.
No, it doesn't.
This is important stuff.
I have to teach them
the proper technique.
Come on, you stupid--
great!
Does anyone have another--
Not again!
[cha-ching]
I so needed this, counselor Darcy.
All those years of DJing has
done a number on my cubicles.
I was thinking green would be really cute
but not a heather green, more like a...
What is going on in here?
That's the color.
You would look fantastic with
Richie's face on your nails.
I'm really disappointed in you guys.
Richie, here's the deal.
Nobody's into the whole camp thing.
You're making too many rules,
and everybody just wants to have fun.
Yeah, Richie, these little
piggies went to the market,
and they all came home
with smiles on their faces.
This is not what we do at camp.
Come on, everyone,
let's go craft with pine cones.
[all groan]
Any chance they're going
to collect their own pine cones?
None at all.
Okay, campers,
who's ready to have some Bohawk fun?
"I am, and thanks for being
the best camp leader ever."
[murmuring]
Have you ever seen him like this?
No.
What a rapid five-minute descent
into madness.
Richie, I need to talk to you.
Anything you need to say to me
you can say in front of them.
Listen, I know you're upset
because the campers left, but...
you kept making them do stuff
they didn't want to do.
But they didn't do
a single Bohawk activity.
But they weren't at Camp Bohawk.
They were at the coolest house
in the world,
and you were showing them snails.
When you have
your own personal water park,
nobody cares about your snails.
I guess I was just trying to
give them the experience we had.
Right, and what was the
number one rule at Camp Bohawk?
Never go in the shower without flip-flops.
Okay, what was rule number two?
Always have fun.
Exactly, and snails aren't fun, Richie.
They're just not. Ask anyone.
Even the pine cones will tell you.
"She's right.
And nothing says thank you
like a brand-new credit card."
I guess when I think back,
the best times at Camp Bohawk
weren't doing what was planned.
They were--
The clay fight we got into in ceramics?
That was awesome.
I was gonna say
the water fights we got into
when there was a heat wave.
- Amazing.
- [chuckles]
Wait, I have an idea.
Does it involve the pine cones?
Yes.
But my backup plan doesn't.
Then let's go with the backup plan.
[cha-ching]
[blows nose]
[computer chimes]
Email from Harvard?
Oh, no.
[taps key]
"Upon reading your letter,
we've decided Harvard is
the best place for you."
What?
Admitted immediately?
It happened! It finally happened!
Take that, universe!
You heard about my chicken helmet.
I got accepted into Harvard.
[gasps]
Honey, I'm so proud of you!
Somehow that letter you wrote got me in.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
[chuckles]
Excuse me, Harper Rich?
Harper "Just got into Harvard" Rich?
Who are you?
I'm Dr. Wright-Ihlenfeld from Harvard.
Oh, you got here fast.
Well, it's a pleasure to meet you.
I can't wait to study at Harvard.
Oh, sweetie,
you're not studying at Harvard.
Harvard is studying you.
Huh?
Th-there must be some mistake.
We read your letter. There's no mistake.
Grab her, boys.
Dad, do something!
I am so proud, honey.
Hang on--before you take her,
let me take a picture.
[camera shutter clicks]
Oh, congratulations, Harp.
You're always gonna remember this moment.
I'm afraid she won't have any memory
after the experiments we're doing on her.
[screams]
Please don't take me to Harvard!
[sobbing]
Please!
On behalf of Harvard and
the medical community at large,
thank you for letting us have her.
I'm just happy I could help
make her dreams come true.
Daddy!
[cha-ching]
Oh, great. Crates.
This scares me.
At this point, everything scares me.
Welcome back, campers.
Time for our last activity.
[all groan]
I know we got off to a bad start,
but I think you guys
are gonna have a lot of fun.
All right, everyone, open your crates.
Meatballs?
Meatball fight!
[laughter]
Watch the cubicles!
[rock music]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
Okay.
Yeah.
Boom goes the meatballs!
Whoo!
[applause]
That was amazing.
Where I come from,
after the meatball fight,
we spit on the loser's face.
But maybe we should just high-five.
Take that and that!
Revenge is a dish best served
with a side of meatballs!
- [both] Murray!
- Stop!
I'm done. I'm done.
You can let me go.
I'm cool.
Take that!
Who's laughing now, Abramowitzes?
Enough!
I'm cool. I'm cool.
- [sighs]
- You did it, Richie.
You created memories
of a lifetime for those kids.
And one fully grown Swede.
By the way, Richie,
if you are off to the market,
- we are out of--
- Meatballs?
I was going to say milk,
but yeah, meatballs too.
Thanks, Darcy.
You were right.
This is way more fun than snails.
[cha-ching]
A meatball fight,
because there is no other way to have fun.
I...hate...Harvard.