Ugh, this is so hard.
I can't figure outwhat I want to do today.
Do I want to go to Paris, Tokyo,
or do I just want to ride bikesaround the neighborhood?
We're going to Paris.
You always want to go to Paris.
Or Tokyo.
Anything but the bikes.
Okay, but how do we get there?
Do we want to take my yacht,my helicopter,
or my "yachticopter"?
Anything but the bikes.
Why can't I figure this out?
You, my friend,
have decision paralysis.
What's that?
It's when you have
too many options to choose from.
You start looking for the perfect decision
and never make a choice.
It's what happened with my song sales.
There were too many good options,
so the T-Nice fans didn't buy any.
That's one theory.
Hello!
Look who just rolled in
from the Scandinavian peninsula!
Swedish House Sensation,
Swedish House Sensation!
You're, like, the world's biggest DJ!
Welcome back, dude!
Good to see you, Richie, Darcy...
boy I am not knowing.
No. I'm T-Nice.
The rapper?
[sighs]Bulldozah's son.
Ahh!
I did the remix of his hit song
My Son Got Kicked Off His Gymnastics Team.
I wasn't kicked off.
I was asked to leave.
[cash register dings]My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
So, Mr. Sensation, I--
Please, call me Swedish.
So, Swedish, what brings you here?
A show?
No, no shows.
A new album?
If it comes.
These things, you cannot force,
like eating smorgastarta with no cream.
[camera shutter clicks]
No pictures, please.
I am being afraid
if I get any more famous, I might go poof.
The spotlight, it burns so bright.
I feel you, dog.
The music biz gets to you.
- You are being a musician?- Yes.
Any chance you want to work together?
None whatsoever.
Master Richie, you failed to mention
that this suitcase belongs
to such a strapping, young piece of machinery.
Hello!
You sure are easy on the visor.
Oh, it is you again.
That helmet gets me every time.
Oh, Richie, I got you a present.
Oh, thanks, but...
I think it's broken.
No, assembly is required.
Oh, well, thanks so much. Irona?
There are directions.
This should be easy.
Oh, good, and they are in Swedish--
the one languageI am not programmed with.
So, Swedish, where are you staying?
Well, I was thinking...
Richie Rich's house,
if you say ja.
Say ja! Say ja!
Heck ja!
My first celebrity sleepover!
How about two celebrities
for the price of one?
I'll go grab a sleeping bag.
Can't your dad carry his own sleeping bag?
Ohh! Boom goes the firecracker!
[laughs]
[cha-ching]
The coach kicked me off the debate team
for being too competitive.
What happened?
Well, she said my rebuttal lacked passion,
so I threw my podium at her.
Well, if they didn't want
people throwing podiums,
they'd nail 'em down.
It was nailed down.
Maybe you are a little too competitive.
You know, you could always do what I did
after my football career ended
and join a fantasy league.
Too bad there's no such thing
as fantasy debate.
Too bad there is.
That's right--
two-time fantasy debate league champion.
Not only does this fill me with pride,
but it holds up my pants.
How does fantasy debate even work?
You draft kids from local debate teams,
and you score a pointwhenever they win a debate.
Oh, just like fantasy football.
Two spots did just open in my league.
I had to kick out the Spielman twins
for orange juicing.
They got it all over the carpet.
That's not for me.
I don't blame you.
I wouldn't want to compete
against me either.
What did you just say?
I bolted that into the foundation
after our last game of Go Fish.
[sniffing]
I thought I smelled gold in here.
They're for Swedish House Sensation.
I just wanted to dosomething nice for him.
He did throw that concert for me.
Yeah, I remember.
I was in a full-body cast
after being attacked by gorillas.
Ahh...
You never forget
staring into the eyes
of an angry silverback.
Never!
Well, I was just hoping this'll inspire him
to make a new album.
I just know he'll love them.
Richie!
I could not find your lingonberry jam!
Surprise!
Ohh! Papa!
No turntables!
Away they go!
What's going on, Swedish?
They're just DJ equipment.
Exactly!
But you're the world's best DJ.
Not anymore.
My fame, my fortune--gone.
Truth being,
I am no longer Swedish House Sensation.
I am Swedish house disappointment.
[sobbing]
So how did you lose everything?
Last time I saw you,you were on top of the world.
And now I am being under it.
What happened?
I had a bad show...
a really, really bad show.
It was late on a lorsdag when...
[lively dance music playing]
[crowd roaring]
♪ ♪
[record scratches]
Ooh! That is not good.
[crowd booing]
Please! People, no booing!
I am needing to concentrate!
[beatboxing]
Beat-beat! Cooler beat!
[crowd booing]
[sobbing]
Ohh, papa!
Ja. Not such a great lorsdag.
That sounds terrible.
I'm so sorry.
How did we not hear about this?
I'm usually up onall of the celebrity meltdowns.
You must not read Swede-M-Z.
Well, we're gonna get you back on top.
I consider you a friend,
and I don't let friends down.
Thanks, Richie.
I will give it a shot,
but I am not sure I can get back on stage.
I don't blame you.
I have no idea how you showyour helmet in public.
Boom... goes the firecracker.
[cha-ching]
Okay, let's start this fantasy debate draft.
I want to start winning.
You winning?
- Mm-hmm.- That's cute.
First, we have to elect a commissioner.
It needs to be someone who doesn't work,
has tons of free time,and will never realize
what a thankless job it is.
Why is everyone looking at me?
Did you smell that?
Cliff, you have been named commissioner.
Aw, thanks!
I'm really excited to be...
[growling]
Commissioner!
I have the power!
Okay.
With first pick, I take--
Whoa-ho-ho. Excuse me.
But the reigning champ always picks first.
Mm.
Daddy, it would mean a lot
to your buttercup if I could choose first.
Buttercup drafts first!
Ugh!
I pick Rob Huntington.
No!
Why?
My life is over!
I needed Bob Huntington to win!
I picked rob.
Oh, phew.
In that case, I'll take Sarah Weaver.
Come on, dad.
Respect the hat.
Come on, commissioner. Pick already.
Don't rush me. This is a huge decision.
Pepperoni.
I've made a terrible mistake.
I pick Vanessa Sanchez.
No!
Why?
My life is over!
I'll take Poonam Dashmukhe.
I didn't know she was still available.
Oh, yeah.
Her name must have gotten covered up
by my championship belt.
That is not fair!
Commissioner, we need a ruling!
My decision is...
sausage!
Irona, this is gonna be a while.
Would you mind getting ussome refreshments?
I would be more than happy to,master Richie,
but I am only on step 112
of assembling your present.
Do you have a Gary wrench
and a long-handled schmipple?
I will take your silence as a no.
How is it coming on with the refreshments?
I am so thirsty.
Not well.
I think we need to focus on the music.
We need to get you back
behind the turntables.
No.
I cannot trust them.
The turntables have turned on me.
It's gonna be okay.
Just-- just take it slow.
- Are they unplugged?- Yes.
Hold up the cord. I must see it.
Tahj,
you've gottena lot of pep talks in your life.
Can you give him some advice?
[sighs]
Look...
you may not be the smartest or funniest
or most talented,
but the trash isn't gonna take itself out.
I can't take this anymore.
I'll handle this.
Come on, Swedish!
Snap out of it!
Get...
it...
together!
Darcy!
Thanks.
I think I needed a swift kickin the rumpa,
but I can no longer DJ.
I guess I will just spendthe rest of my life
weeping behind your couch.
So you're done DJ'ing.
There are many different types of music.
I'd stay away from hip-hop.
It's like gymnastics.
There's a lot of politics.
[reggae music playing]
Ja, mon!
No.
[huffing]
[pop music playing]
♪ ♪
Definitely not.
If I hear one more of these,
I'm going to quit music.
Okay, let's do one more.
[sighs]Maybe this is a lost cause.
[gentle acoustic strumming]
♪ I am lonely and hate my life ♪
♪ I miss my doggie but not my wife ♪
Wow, Swedish, that was powerful.
Really touching.
Really?
You are not just playing helmet games?
I don't know.
My musical instincts tell me
that wasn't very good at all.
Well, in that case...
we got ourselves a winner!
[cha-ching]
When is your dad gonna postthe new scores?
Oh, you look nervous.
Are you scared I'm gonna bewearing that belt very soon?
I'm not nervous.
I always sweat this much.
Okay, I figured it out.
Everyone owes $4 for the pizza.
Dad, who's winning the league?
How should I know?
You're the commissioner.
That's why I'm wearing this hat!
I'll take a look.
- Harper!- Yes!
You're in second. Murray's winning.
What? How is that possible?
Because I'm better than you.
[whispering]Dude, ease up.
Not everything is bolted down in here.
I haven't lost a thing in my life.
Look, I still have all my baby teeth.
Under no circumstances will I lose to you.
Well, actually, there is one circumstance.
Two words, five syllables--
there might be a hyphen in there--
Poonam Dashmukhe!
Poonam was mine!
Well, now second place is yours.
And after she wins her debate tonight,
you can kiss the belt good-bye.
But I wouldn't recommendactually kissing it.
It's pretty sweaty.
[cha-ching]
Thanks for coming over, Poonam.
So are you readyfor the big debate tonight?
Actually, I have a lot of research--
That's great. You know what?
Do you want to see my closet?
No, not especially!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Locking you in my closet
so you'll miss your debate
so I'll win the fantasy debate league.
And, no, I'm not crazy.
Another fantasy debate league?
Ugh, every year...
What is all of this?
I put together a showcase
to introduce the world to the new Swedish.
It's gonna go off without a hitch.
I thought of everything.
Hey, guys. I'm here to help.
Obviously not everything.
Ah... what's up, ladies?
Do you girls doa lot of industry showcases?
Wow. Who are these guys?
They're here to watch you perform.
It's time to introduceSwedish Country Sensation
to the world!
The world?
Maybe we start small.
Perhaps Cincin-a-naughty?
You're gonna do great.
I don't want you to get nervous,
so just pretend the most
powerful record executives
in the business aren't even here.
What record executives?
Perfect!
Guys, I'd like to introduce to you
Swedish Country Sensation!
[upbeat strumming]
♪ I am lonely and hate my life ♪
♪ I miss my doggie but not my wife ♪
♪ ♪
[feedback squeals]
Ooch! That is not good!
[feedback hums]
Please, people, no murmuring!
I am needing to concentrate!
[feedback squeals]
Strum... strum...
melodic strum...
Ohh! Papa!
Oh, papa!
So, um...
did you notice the pretty dancers?
Guys, don't let those execs leave.
I have to go get him.
Do either of you know how to say,
"Come out from under the couch"
in Swedish?
Forget it.
We have to come up with a plan.
This is it.
This is T-Nice's chance to shine!
Are you gonna rap?
Nope.
Oh, I wish coach Meredithcould see me now!
Oh, hey, Harper.
Ready for your first taste of defeat?
It might be hard to chew
with those baby teeth.
You seem pretty cheery
for someone whose best debater
didn't show up to today's debate.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
two words, five syllables, and--
I looked into it--no hyphen.
Poonam?
What happened to her?
Aw...
I will tell you what happened!
She locked me in her closet.
You locked her in your closetagainst her will?
I'm calling the authorities.
Commissioner!
What's going on?
I got a big decision here--
roast beef or turkey.
Harper went straight off the deep end
and locked Poonam in her closet
so she could win the league.
Harper!
Oh, you went way too far.
This is the kind of behavior
that got you kicked offyour debate team...
and the soccer team...
and the girl scouts.
But, dad, I--
No.
You need to learn how to lose gracefully.
I'm sorry, but due to your actions,
you are no longer my daughter.
What?
I meant you're no longer in the league.
But you're still my daughter.
Love you, sweetie.
Okay, I deserve it.
I shouldn't care so much about winning,
but I guess I'm just too competitive.
Don't you think
you owe someone an apology?
You're right.
Murray, I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
I was talking about me.
I'm the victim here.
Poonam, I'm sorry.
What I did to you was terrible.
And to make it up to you,
you can keep the shoes.
These are my shoes!
You people are crazy!
Well, you know what that means.
I'm still the champion!
[cha-ching]
Oh, hey, Irona.
I really need your help finding Swedish.
I really need your help building your gift.
It says here, "Attach board to itself."
what does that even mean?
I-I really appreciate all your hard work!
[sobbing]
Hey, man.
You okay?
I'm sorry I could notgo through with it, Richie.
I am not a cowman.
It's--it's "boy," but you're right.
I shouldn't have forced youto do something
you didn't want to do.
The last thing I wanted
was to turn you into more of a disaster.
I appreciate that.
I mean, sure, the fire was mine,
but you poured gasoline on it.
I'm so sorry.
I was just trying to help you.
I didn't want you weeping
into a plate of meatballs...
which happen to smell amazing.
Would you like one?
Mmm! These are delicious.
Where did you get them?
I did not get. I made.
I didn't know you cook.
I cook when I am stressed...
and when I'm hungry.
I really enjoy it.
Then why do you waste your time
in the music business?
Because there's no money in meatballs.
But what if there were?
But there isn't, so...
Oh, no. Now I'm getting stressed again!
Must cook more balls!
I've got great news.
I have better news.
What is he doing?
All I know is that his dad's gonna pay me
so much moneyto keep this off the internet.
So what's your good news?
Hello!
Fresh meatballs!
Get them while they're hot!
Everybody, I'd like to introduce you
to my new personal chef...
Uh, what's your real name?
Well,
it sounds a little bit like a girl's name.
Come on. What is it?
Rebecca.
Can I call you Becky?
That would be weird.
That is my papa's name.
Richie, I met someone today...
me!
Well, I promised you a memorable showcase.
I'm pretty sure I delivered.
Master Richie, I finishedbuilding your present.
That is a table.
I got you the cuckoo clock.
He is getting a table.
A table is good too.
So what are you whipping up for dinner?
Tonight I was thinking meatballs.
But we just had meatballs.
Ja.
That's all I know how to cook.
And boom goes the firecracker.