When do we leave for grandma's, again?
Three days.
- Think we packed too early?- Nope.
Hey, guys.
I got some bad news.
We're not gonna be ableto take our trip to grandma's.
No!
Dad, we've been sitting here for two days.
You don't think you could have told us sooner?
We can't go because I got a job.
A j-to-the-o-to-the--
ob!
That's great, dad.
What did you get? A crossing guard?
Toll booth operator?
Uh, crossing guard?
Better.
The aquarium hired me
to play the Wendell the walrus.
Oh, dad, it's your dream job.
I am so proud of you.
Thanks.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
It's gonna be hard being
away from you all day long.
We know, dad, but this is a big step for you.
Oh, I was talking to the couch pillows.
[cash register dings]My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
my dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
Is that grandma?
Nope. That's the mailman.
No, that's the pool guy.
Is that grandma?
No. That's a hedge.
Oh, here she comes.
Hello, sweeties.
[both] Grandma!
I haven't missed you a bit.
You haven't?
Acting, my dear. Acting!
When you are an actor,the world is your stage.
Well, except for Denmark.
Those Danes just don't knowgood acting when they see it.
I'm so glad you could make it.
Well, how could I not make it
with this talent and this face?
Oh, come. Give me some kisses.
Oh, my flight in brought back
quite a few fond memories.
I was about to play the lead
in Dames of the Sky,
but alas, the director came to me
and said I was simply
too beautiful for the part.
Hello.
Ah, I want to introduce you
to my new boyfriend, Sigmund--
one of the kindest, sweetest,
most handsome men I've ever met.
She really liked me when she found out
I was directing the Boca Vista
retirement community's
stage production ofGuardians of the Galaxy.
Honey, that had nothing to do with anything.
I simply thought casting me as Gamora
would allow us to spend more time together.
Nice to meet you, kiddos.
I've got to go figure out a way
to disguise motorized wheelchairs
as intergalactic star fighters.
Vrroom!
Oh, Richie, thank you for flying me in.
Well, we wanted you to be hereto celebrate the big news.
Dad got a job!
Hey!
I paid for the airline tickets!
I was supposed to deliver the good news.
Dad got a job.
My Cliffy got a job? I am shocked.
But, of course, I need not say that.
It all plays right here.
I know. I still can't believe it myself.
Is he a crossing guard?
Toll booth operator?
Uh, crossing guard?
He's a walrus!
Ah! His dream job.
I'm so happy I could cry.
Give me a moment.
[crying]
Richie?
I think we need to talkabout your fashion choices.
They're not his, they're mine.
Although he did pay for them.
Why do you need all these clothes?
I've only got two outfits.
Business Murray and fun Murray.
Which one am I looking at now?
Fun Murray.
You don't understand.
That's because I'm fun Murray right now.
Let's get down to business.
I don't have time for this.
I'm in the middle of a fashion emergency.
All of these clothes are unoriginal.
A fashion icon like meneeds something unique.
Ooh, I have an idea for a unique belt.
How about you wear the anchor
chain from Richie's yacht?
Come on, let's go take a stroll off the pier.
Wait.
I just had a breakthrough.
I think I'm done shopping.
Darcy, if you're serious, I will kiss you.
Or not kiss you!
Whichever makes you more likelyto never shop again.
We're not kissing.
But I'm serious.
I'm done shopping.
Yes!
I'm hiring a personal fashion designer
to handcraft my outfit every day.
No!
Irona!
I am right here, Murray.
I think it's time I teach Darcy a lesson
about her reckless spending.
I need you to intercept Darcy's call.
I am sorry, but I can only accept commands
from master Richie.
Oh, well, Richie asked me to tell you.
How do I know you're telling the truth?
Because when I lie, I sneeze.
[sneezes]
That was just a coincidence.
What can I do for you, Murray?
Use your voice modulation software
to pose as a fashion designer.
I am sorry, but for security reasons, I cannot--
Richie asked me to tell you.
Right away.
Hello, dahling!
So you're a famous fashion designer?
How come I've never heard of you?
Because Dissue Alassondoes not answer the phone
for just anyone,
Bobby face.
Ish now time to do whatever it ish I do.
Aren't you a fashion designer?
You know me so well.
I can blow up those balloons, grandma.
I have strong lungs.
I once played Moby Dick and wasunderwater for six hours.
Okay. I picked up the cake.
I may or may not have dipped my finger
in a frosting walrus.
Whew!
Tough day at the old office.
[all] Surprise!
Mom, what are you doing here?
I brought her in so we couldall spend some time together.
You don't look surprised.
Here, let me help you.
We'll rehearse that later.
Nice to see you, mom,
but I got to run back to work.
There's a real walrus who wants my job.
He's good. He's real good.
It's weird seeing dad out
of the house during the day.
Yeah.
I hope they're not just paying him in fish.
It's happened before.
I'm happy for my son.
He's off to the aquarium.
Those are just two of the films I did in '64.
Who wants tea?
What year did you make that film?
Oh, no, I was just asking if you wanted tea.
Don't be dense, dear.
Grandma... your wig fell off.
What? I don't wear a wig.
Then your completely natural hair
is just hanging on the light.
- Barb?- Ah! Oh!
Sigmund can't see me like this.
He'll leave me for Ethel
from the yoga class.
He's always commenting how limber she is.
She can bend over and touch her knees.
both: Hey!
Sigmund.
Hey, Barb.
It's Harper, her granddaughter.
But her stress lines do make her look 70.
So you want to tour the grounds?
I have a tree house.
Ooh. A location scout.
Now, who wants to carry me?
Harper, just set Sigmund down by the door.
You are carrying him back down.
both: Dad?
What are you doing here?
Welcome to the aquarium!
Dad, why would you lie to usabout having a job?
Because I don't want to spenda week with my mom.
All she thinks about is herself.
Plus I spent $7,000on this walrus costume.
Dad, grandma Barb loves you.
No, she doesn't.
She proved that at
my third grade talent show.
It was 1983 when...
What are you waiting for?Tell the story already.
Sorry.
So I had spent months preparing
this cutting-edge dance routine,
but when I finally took the stage,
she was nowhere to be seen.
I burst into tears and I ran out of the building,
and I haven't set foot in a school since.
Well, did you tell grandma how upset you were?
No.
And promise me that you won't either.
I know how much you guys love her,
and how much she loves you,
and I don't want this
to hurt your relationship.
I'm just not ready to forgive her.
Cut!
I didn't believe a word you just said.
Let's try that again, but with feeling!
[in garbled foreign accent]
Zere!
You look fabulous!
It's definitely unique.
Ish "amashing."
I guess it is "amashing."
What is going on here?
Who is this person
who looks nothing like anyoneI've ever seen before?
This is Dissue Alasson,
my personal fashion designer.
That sounds really expensive.
How much is this costing Richie?
Is coshen "shoushin obloshin
bloshen" dollarsh a day.
Darcy!
How could you spend a shoushin
obloshin bloshen dollars
of Richie's a day?
Leave me and Dissue alone.
She has to put the finishing
touches on this outfit,
and then--
what did you say you had to do?
Dust.
I mean fa-shion!
Well, I can't wait to see you wear
that not-ridiculous outfit in public.
Keep up the good work.
I can only keep up the good work--
Richie says keep it up.
We have to tell grandma what's going on.
I can't stand to watch two family members
at odds with each other.
You threw a toasterin my bathtub the other day.
It wasn't plugged in.
Well, we may have promised dad
that we wouldn't tell grandma,
but maybe there's a wayto make him tell her.
Grandma!
Sigmund's recastingGamora in the tree house!
That's the role I was born
70 years ago to play!
Good thinking.
You know,
I'm glad that toaster wasn't plugged in.
Thanks, Harper.
Zere!
Simply fah-gious!
I don't know about this.
I do.
You look amazing.
You look so good I could kiss you.
Or not kiss you.
Whichever will make youwear that in public.
Not kiss me.
The answer is always not kiss me.
You look amashing, Bobby face.
I guess if you guys say so.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go laugh in the other room.
It's not about you. I promise.
[sneezes]
Kishes, darling.
I must go dust beforemaster Richie gets back.
"Master Richie"?
I mean Ri-chie!
I mean fa-shion!
I mean--
Irona?
Uh...
sleep mode.
If you'll excuse me,
I have to use the bathroom.
This tree house has a bathroom?
If you'll excuse me,
I have to use the window.
Sigmund!
How dare you recast me!
Cliffy?
Mom, how'd you get up here?
I pulled up the rope ladder.
She scaled the tree like a jungle cat.
No one recasts Barbara Rich.
Grandma, there's something Dad needs to tell you.
Tattle-tale!
You're grounded!
Out of the tree and into the ground!
Just tell grandma why you've
been sitting up here all day.
You're hiding from me?
What are you, a casting director?
I just wanted to be by myself.
And, uh...
not around you.
I see.
Well, if I'm not wanted here,
then I'm going home.
Exit stage left.
We were just trying to help.
I trusted you.
And you did the opposite of that.
I don't even know what that word is,
but it hurt.
I'm never gonna forget that.
A walrus never forgets.
I think that's an elephant.
What's the difference?
We need to talk aboutyour issue with grandma.
And then we should probably go
over those animal flash cards.
Do you even know what it
feels like to have a parent
who doesn't understand you as a person?
[both] Yes.
Well, you guys can handle that.
I can't.
She really hurt me.
[clapping]
Now that is emotion.
For the first time,
you had me actually believing
you were a damaged walrus.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to go rethink everything.
Is he for real?
Guys, you don't understand.
I was so determined to make my mom proud
that I spent months perfecting
my talent show routine.
I stayed up late, I didn't do my homework,
I even skipped class, all for nothing.
I still know all the moves,
but no one's ever gonna see it.
That's not true.
If this dance routine
means that much to you,
why don't you perform it for Harper and I?
We'd love to see it.
We certainly would.
For many reasons.
Dance for us, dad.
I love you guys.
Now don't move.
I'm gonna go get my fog machineand my jazz shoes.
So were you totally humiliated?
Did you finally learn your lesson
about spending too much
on ridiculous clothes?
No.
People loved my baby doll baby doll dress.
What? They did?
I think we need to startour own fashion line.
These crazy designs
can make a ton of money.
Make money?
I've never not wanted
to kiss you so bad in my life.
But to really clean up, we're
going to need a men's line.
That makes sense.
We just need to find a male model.
Are you sure this is gonna make us money?
Absolutely.
Now go out there and strut your stuff.
I called the press,
and everyone from school.
Wait! What?
Darcy! Let me in!
Everyone's laughing at me!
Yes, they are, Murray.
Yes, they are.
Darcy, wait. No, no, no.
Darcy! Come back!
Darcy! Don't leave me out here!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Ow!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Ohh!
Harper, is this really making you cry?
For all the wrong reasons.
Oh!
Shammon!
I still got it.
Oh, dear.
Whoo!
[coughs]
I'm not done.
Mm-hmm!
Oh!
Dad? Are you okay?
Oww!
That was great...
ish.
Hang on.
I haven't turned into a werewolf yet.
Bravo.
Bravo. That was fabulous, Cliffy.
I'm so proud of you.
Mom?
You saw my dance?
And you liked it?
I didn't just see it.
I felt it.
I thought you left, mom.
I was going to, but for some reason,
the limo driver drove
around for a few minutes
and then brought me back here.
What?
I'll have to talk to him about that later.
Continue patching up your relationship.
That was worth a 30-year wait.
Why didn't you watch me in third grade?
I thought that you didn't care about me.
Well, of course I did.
The only reason I was
watching from the hallway
was because I didn't wantto make you nervous.
Every time I was around, you putterrible pressure on yourself.
You're too much of a perfectionist.
Wow.
You guys really need to startspending more time together.
I'm sorry I took so longto tell you how I felt.
I always just wanted to make you proud.
Oh, I've never not been proud of you.
I've played a lot of parts in my life,
but my greatest role will always
be that of your mother.
This is normally where people applaud.
Oh, it's like you're feeding my ears.
I really missed you, mom.
I missed you too.
Get over here, kids.
Where's Richie?
I don't know.
He was here a second ago.
Hey, mom. It's Richie.
Nothing, I--
I just miss you.
Oh, you're watching The Kardashians?
Yeah, I guess you can call me back.
Of course I knew you were kidding.
So how are you? Oh.