Irona, you're not supposed to get wet.
It warps your processors.
But I love running in the rain.
It is the only time I feel alive.
All right. You're all fixed.
Try picking up the glass.
Perfect!
[glass shatters]
Yeah, you're not ready for a pet bunny.
[doorbell rings]
I will answer the door.
No, wait! Don't!
See?
Oh, no!
The robot apocalypse.
She finally turned.
I knew she'd turn!
Relax.
Irona just got caught in the rain,
and it shorted out her touch sensors.
Just don't hand her
anything you care about.
Murray, time for your robot massage...
Can I take a rain check on that?
Good afternoon.
Hey. Who are you?
My name is Robbie Roberts.
I'm your new neighbor.
I just thought I'd pop in and say hello.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Richie Rich.
Oh, you're quite well-known overseas.
You talk funny.
I'm from England.
It's where my family
made most of our billions.
But I could get used to it.
Oh, cool! A foreigner.
[loudly over-enunciating] Welcome...
to this country.
These are my friends Darcy and Murray,
Oh, and this is my robot, Irona.
Pleasure to meet you.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Richie, I must confess,
I've been more focused on making money
than meeting people.
I wonder if you'll be
my very first American friend.
How long have you been here?
11 years.
[Cha-ching]
My name is Richie rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
I love what you've done here.
I especially like the green beanbag chair.
Actually that's just a pile of money.
Richie, you have to care for your money.
When's the last time you took it on a walk
or asked it how its day was?
It's okay.
Daddy's here.
Wow, Murray,
you really care for Richie's money.
How'd you like to manage my account?
It's worth...
I love you so much!
Robbie, just so you know,
I love money too...
In a not weird way.
Let's see,
I don't have any cash.
All I have is this enormous diamond.
Would you like it?
Yes!
Are you dating anyone?
You are just my type.
You like British guys?
I like guys who carry diamonds
around in their pockets.
What about you, Richie?
I am, after all, your biggest fan.
Is there anything I can give you?
That's okay.
I pretty much have everything.
Then I will give you the greatest gift
a gentleman can give another gentleman--
a hearty handshake.
Thanks.
I, uh...
didn't have one of these.
How long do we have to shake for?
Ten minutes.
Hey, Harper. These all your phones?
Can I get all the numbers?
I don't have time for you.
I'm getting ready for
the live telethon I'm hosting
for homeless turtles.
Every six seconds,
a turtle loses its shell.
This turtle
looks like my grandfather
after a bath.
Why don't you
just ask Richie for the money,
and you and I can go out on a--
Don't say "date."
Out somewhere...
romantically.
I need to raise $10,000
in order to save
these poor helpless turtles.
How about I give you $10,000,
and you and I can go on that...
dinner with uncomfortable small talk?
I'm not taking the easy way out.
This is about raising awareness
for an issue that affects
at least a handful of turtles
worldwide.
I'm spending the entire weekend right here
until I raise that money.
I feel you.
T-nice knows when to back off.
Welcome to the
Turtles in Trouble telethon.
I am Harper Rich.
And I am T-nice,
who will be right by
my beautiful co-host's side
all weekend long.
Do you guys think that maybe
there's something a little off
about Robbie?
- What?
- You take that back right now!
What is off about him, master Richie?
I don't know.
I can't quite put my finger on it.
[engine revving]
Okay, now I can.
Afternoon, chaps!
Hey, Robbie!
It's me, Murray!
You wouldn't happen to have
any more huge diamonds, would you?
Also, "Hi."
Uh, Robbie, why are you
wearing the same thing as me?
Because I greatly admire
your fashion sense.
Do not tell me
I have to iron two shirts now.
It sounded funny in my processor.
And what's with the car?
It's just like mine.
Yours looked so sporty, I had to have one.
Do not tell me I have to wash two--
never mind.
Robbie, you sort of kind of copied
everything about me.
Not everything.
I'm wearing striped underwear.
I'm wearing striped underwear!
Oh, what a charming coincidence!
What a gross coincidence.
I stopped by to invite you all
to a housewarming party at my mansion.
Put me down for yes plus fun!
[engine revving]
[crash]
Oops.
I'm used to driving
on the other side of the bedroom.
Tally ho!
Chums, welcome to my abode!
Whoa, Richie.
You totally copied Robbie 's bedroom!
Not cool.
This room is insane!
It's just like mine.
He's got the same lamp, the same couch,
the same other couch.
Yep, it's like my home
away from your home.
- So...
- [yelps]
What do you think of the place?
I like it,
probably because I live in the exact...
same...house!
It's not the exact same.
Your clock is one minute fast.
His is two.
Good catch, Murray.
Richie, I do not mean to offend.
I'm just an admirer.
Maybe I did copy
some of your more redeeming attributes.
Subconsciously, of course.
That makes sense.
I copy off people all the time at school.
Subconsciously, of course.
Maybe I am overreacting a bit.
That's the spirit!
And I have one more surprise for you.
You want my kidney, don't you?
Master Robbie, your friends have arrived.
Thank you, Irono.
Irono?
She's my new robot maid.
What is your serial number?
NX-135.
Mine is NX-137.
Nice to meet you, grandma.
My head hurts.
[both] Would you like an ice pack?
Now it's even worse.
Robbie,
we have major problems!
Lacy, she got your new credit card number
and is ordering everything
off the internet.
I didn't buy everything, Marty.
The Eiffel Tower is on back order.
Lacy and Marty?
What's going on here?
You're pretty.
What number am I thinking of?
An ostrich skin handbag.
Right!
So how'd you get that scar?
Summer camp.
That willow wasn't the only thing weeping.
So how'd you get yours?
Public library.
I was trapped under an avalanche of books.
Dickens!
Robbie, you seem like you're a little,
well, obsessed with me.
Maybe you should find your own interests.
Like what?
I don't know. Jogging?
- Do you like jogging?
- No.
Then neither do I.
All finished, boss.
Where do you want it?
Put it next to the others.
That's it.
I'm leaving.
Sorry. Took the wrong Murray.
Come on.
Welcome back to
the Turtles in Trouble telethon.
Please watch this video about
the plight of turtles without shells
who spend their nights shivering
in the dark corners of our cities'...
lakes and ponds.
Great idea: A movie.
I'll get some popcorn.
I told you, I don't need your help.
But the turtles need my help.
[phone rings]
Yellow?
[phone continues ringing] Is anyone there?
Is this those kids from the deli
cranking me again?
Dad, try another phone.
Oh.
Yellow?
[phone continues ringing]
Yellow? Is anyone there?
[growls]
Punk kids!
I'm gonna go down to that deli,
and I'm gonna give them
a piece of my mind!
And order a sandwich.
You guys need anything?
[phone continues ringing]
Hello. Turtles in Trouble.
$1,000?
Thank you. That's very generous!
People do care about the turtles.
Isn't this great?
Yeah, it's great.
This is going to be over
sooner than I thought.
Over?
But our date has just begun.
This telethon needs some Tahj.
Sabo-tahj.
[phone ringing]
Turtles in Trouble.
You want to donate $500?
Sorry. Wrong number.
Please fill out this form.
All proceeds go to turtles in trouble.
These shell-less turtles need your help.
Thank you for coming back over.
- I see you got my letter.
- Yeah.
Let's make this quick.
And don't try anything.
I've got my bodyguard.
Right, Irona?
- I have a black belt...
- Yeah.
That turns my cooling fan.
Richie, I realize I did get carried away.
I'm going to take your advice
and live my own life.
That's a relief.
I'm glad this was
just a big misunderstanding
and that you're normal
and not some--
What's Irono doing?
Tying you up.
You were saying?
Irona, what happened
to you being my bodyguard?
Stop tying us up!
Stay away from master Richie!
Yeah. That was great!
Now we just need to work on your timing.
Hey, Richie.
We're here to--
Richie?
Hey, Darce!
Been busy shopping?
How's my money, Murray?
Why are you wearing that ridiculous wig?
My hair's thinning, all right?
It's just until the plugs take.
I was talking to Robbie.
Yeah, Robbie, answer the question.
Stop acting weird!
Robbie? What are you talking about?
I'm Richie!
Okay, where's Richie?
I'm right here.
Look, I'm doing that thing
where I stand still.
Richie does do that!
Master Richie,
your Richie-copter
is ready on the Richie-pad.
Richie.
That's not Richie, Irona.
Yes, it is.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I really want to get back to my dusting.
That's definitely not Irona!
Darcy, want to fly to Milan
for some shopping?
Not with you!
I can't believe I just said no to shopping.
Am I not Darcy?
Murray, want to sell my yacht?
I'll sell the yacht,
but after that, I'm out of here.
Let's go, Murray!
Where do you think you two are going?
Hate to break it to you, guys,
but your best friend Robbie is crazy.
Best friend?
I barely know that guy.
He hired me.
I'm a male model.
[all] You are?
This is the worst acting gig
I've ever taken in 30 years.
Why do I have to look 12?
Irona, is there any way out?
Yes, but you will feel better
about yourself
if you figure it out on your own.
You have no idea, do you?
Nope.
We're still at $1,000?
This is taking forever.
I know, but at least
we're getting to know each other better.
Tell me three things you like about me.
I can't tell you one thing I like.
Okay. Now I need two more.
You know what?
$1,000 will save a few turtles.
Let's shut this thing down.
No! No, no, no.
The turtles need you.
I need you!
But mainly the turtles.
You can't give up.
I don't know.
Are you gonna tell this little guy
that he can't have a home?
Well, go ahead.
Tell him!
Look him right in his eyes
and tell him right now!
I knew you couldn't do it.
Wow, Tahj.
I didn't know you cared so much.
Let's save some turtles!
Great!
Now you're gonna sit
at this table with flowers and sushi,
and let old T-nice set things right.
Hey, Cliff, go up there
and do that standup routine
you were telling me about.
Awesome! I've been working
on this bit for years.
This'll keep us here for a while.
[grunts]
That's it. We're doomed.
Guess I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life in here.
You are lucky. I am a machine.
I'm going to be here for forever.
What are you doing?
Practicing my poses.
I'm a male model, you know.
Maybe have a backup career.
Hey, I need that water!
I'm a male model.
Well, guess what.
This water will help us get out of here.
[electricity zapping]
Thank you, master Richie!
I feel so alive!
That's great, Irona,
but could you get the door?
[metallic creaking]
[gasps]
We did it!
We escaped!
You coming, Lacy?
No way.
I'm an out-of-work actor.
I'm sitting in here until Robbie pays me.
Okay, people, keep those donations coming!
Ta-da!
I don't understand
why people aren't donating.
Your dad is doing great.
What?
[clapping]
That is classic Cliff.
Wait a minute.
Are you just ruining this telethon
so you can spend time with me?
No! Not at all.
California roll?
Excuse me one second.
Hey, how are we doing?
I notice we haven't made
any more money.
Oh, yeah, people hate you.
You're doing great!
Maybe I can do some of my impressions.
Here's my Cliff.
[as Cliff Huxtable]
My name is Cliff!
I am afraid of boxes
because the children play
inside the boxes!
[guttural grunt]
[phone rings]
[normal voice] Hey, it worked!
[phone continues ringing]
Before you say anything,
this is not a real telethon.
I'm just doing this
to spend some quality time
with my girlfriend.
I'm not your girlfriend, Tahj.
It's one thing to trick me into a date,
but to do it on the bare backs of turtles?
You're right.
I was trying to spend time
with you,
but I guess this wasn't
the right way to do it.
It's not fair to you,
and it's definitely not fair
to the turtles.
I'm sorry.
Well, then that's it.
The telethon is over.
I'll just tell my dad
to stop his tap routine.
[tapping fingers]
[phone rings]
Hello?
You'll donate $10,000
if we get that man off TV?
The turtles thank you.
That's my girl.
A girl.
A girl. Definitely not mine.
Unless you want to be?
You don't? That's cool.
I'll ask you again, friends,
what are we doing for fun today?
Going to a psychiatrist?
Master Richie, I have an idea.
How about we--
Get out of my room!
- [yelps]
- Richie!
You escaped!
[back to British accent] I mean...
good to see you again, old chap.
What happened?
Robbie locked me in a cage.
I meant to Marty.
Did he give my modeling shots
to his agent?
I can't deprive the world of this.
And I thought Robbie
was the most delusional person ever.
I know a toaster
who thinks he is a microwave.
Steve Bukowski?
You know Steve Bukowski?
You and I need to talk.
Robbie, why did you do all this?
I'm sorry.
I really am.
It's been a long time
since I've been jealous of anyone.
I wanted everything you had.
I wanted to be you.
Robbie, maybe the reason
you have a hard time making friends
is 'cause you put on an act.
You have to be your own person.
is that what you would do?
- Robbie!
- You're right.
It's time to finally be me...
[southern accent] Bubba T. Jones
from South Texas, America.
That took a lot of courage.
If you can be yourself, so can I!
[inhales deeply]
I wear a toupee.
[British accent]
You do know I was just kidding
about the Texas thing.
[scoffs]
Oh, yeah. Of course.
Well, I was just kidding about the--
where'd my rug go?
I didn't know a 12 year-old could go bald.
I'm not bald.
Some of this hair is mine!
Give me it!
So, Richie, are we still friends?
Of course.
As you can see,
I'm not too choosy
in the friend department.