Master Richie.
Master Richie, wake up!
All right, we will do this the hard way.
[loud guitar riff]
♪ ♪
Come on, that usually works.
Master Richie, Harper has moved out.
Yes!
[air pops]
Wait, did you just say that to get me up?
Yes.
Should I read the morning news
while you pretend to floss?
Sure.
Here's an article from today.
Headline: "Is Richie Rich all washed up?"
Wait, where'd you find that?
Washed-up Rich Kid Monthly.
- Who buys that magazine?
- I do.
It has fascinating articles
and a very challenging crossword puzzle.
What'd they say about me?
"Richie Rich had one good idea.
"How long do we have to wait
for a second good idea?
Our guess, a long time."
Ooh, that is harsh.
All washed-up. All washed-up?
I'll show them who's all washed-up.
Hey, Richie, time for school.
Get all washed up.
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have a trillion dollars.
You see,
I used all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad, my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
Wow, Master Richie,
I've never seen you so focused
on your homework before.
This isn't homework.
This is something I actually care about.
People are calling me washed-up.
I have to come up
with a new business idea.
Okay.
What do you think about a leaf blower
for your hair?
I think it is a hair dryer.
What do you think about a hair dryer
for leaves?
I think it is a leaf blower.
Okay, what--
I'm out of scratch paper.
I will get you a new pad
soon as I am done sweeping up these--
[air pops]
- Confetti.
- Sorry, Irona.
My reputation is at stake.
Hey, Richie. I heard the confetti cannon.
- Is Harper moving out?
- No, Harper's not moving out.
I just needed some scratch paper.
I need to come up with another
gazillion-dollar idea.
Yeah, I saw you
in Washed-up Rich Kid Monthly.
Huh, you scored the cover. Congrats, bro.
I've been trying to get
into that magazine for years.
They said I can't be washed-up
until I actually do something.
Well, I think making
more money's a great idea.
- What do you have so far?
- A water-proof hamster.
That's bad.
Look, you obviously need an idea man.
Luckily you know a great one.
- Who, Murray?
- No.
- My uncle Ted?
That kid in science class
who talks to himself?
Me, T-nice. I'm always thinking of stuff.
Like, why isn't the whole
airplane first-class?
That way, I could sit with my dad
and my brother and my dog.
- But I have other ideas too.
- I'm here for you, Richie.
I'll always help you out.
Well, until allergy season starts
and pollen forces me underground.
You guys are the best.
Okay, we need to come up
with something good
to prove I still have it.
I got you, double R.
This is just the thing,
an idea that will take the world by storm.
What if...
oh, man, I lost it.
Shoot, that was a good one too.
Hello, friends.
And Darcy.
I would like to call to order this meeting
for the Harper Society to Help People,
or HSHP.
First order of business,
coming up with a better name than HSHP.
Hold on, what's
this "Harper Society" thing?
You sent me email
saying I won a shopping spree.
Oh, I must not have sent the second email
that said the first email was a lie.
- Sorry.
- You lied about shopping!
I'm not gonna let you see me cry.
Hold on.
Okay, the truth is,
I'm starting a service
organization to help people
and to pad my college application,
but mainly to help
and to pad.
Best of luck.
[laughs]
You can't keep me here forever.
I love it when people tell me that.
Look, Darcy,
I need three people in order for HSHP
to count as an official
student organization.
Three people?
That's, like, a million people.
You lied about shopping.
- Why should I help you?
- You're not helping me.
You're helping some poor
disadvantaged people.
Why should I help them?
- Because I'll pay you.
- Okay, I'll help.
But because I feel for those people.
And for the money,
but mainly for the people
and the money.
Murray and Tahj are ready
to pitch their ideas.
Bring them in.
First into the fish tank is Murray
with an invention that is guaranteed
to heat things up.
What do you have for me?
I have an invention that is guaranteed
to heat things up.
I already said that, kid.
Well, have you ever wondered
why there aren't socks
for your fingers?
- No.
- Really?
- Well, everyone else has.
- I haven't either.
[groans]
Well, let's pretend you've wondered
why there aren't socks for your fingers.
Well, now you can stop wondering,
because there are.
Next.
But, see, sometimes your fingers are cold,
and your palms are sweaty, and you don't--
It is over, sweetie.
Next into the fish tank is--
do I really have to call him this?
Fine. T-nice.
Okay, this is the moment
you've been waiting for.
T-nice--aka the idea man,
aka "Son, get back to coach.
You're in the dog's seat"--
has the best idea in the history of ideas,
and I'm not gonna lose it,
'cause I wrote this one down.
Get ready, because this one is about to--
Oh, man.
What'd I do with that piece of paper?
Do you remember anything about it?
Uh...
I remember it was big and good and--
Irona, have you seen a piece of paper
with an idea written on it?
No, but you can check the pile.
One second.
Oh, okay.
A leaf blower for your hands?
Next.
Hey, Richie. It's time for dinner.
Next into the fish tank, it's Cliff.
- Who said that?
- I did.
Wait, are you the man
who lives in the walls
and puts holes in my underwear?
Dad, it's just my announcer.
Go ahead and take a five, Chuck.
Thanks, Richie.
I'll be right back after this snack.
[bag crumples, chip snaps]
Chuck, your mic's still on.
[chuckles]
I just noticed that.
Dad, I'm desperate for a business idea
that'll prove I'm not washed up.
I got tons of ideas.
Like, what would you use
if you needed to pick your nose?
- A finger?
- Ew, disgusting.
Fingers are for ear digging, Richie.
I'm talking about a compact,
mostly hygienic
disposable wooden utensil
in the shape of a finger.
I proudly present the nose pick.
I 'd say next, but there's no one left.
Think about it, Richie.
There's bucks in boogers.
Check out these prototypes.
I tried them all, and they all work great.
No, dad--
Pink one is for ladies,
and here's the left-handed model.
Mm, efficient.
And then this one smells like mint.
Mmm, refreshing.
[phone vibrating]
This is for circus clowns.
- Long fingers.
- I can't get my phone!
What somebody needs to invent
is a hands-free hovering phone.
Wait, that's actually a pretty good idea.
Hey, I'm Dan Tandy,
editor of Washed-up Rich Kids Monthly.
Please, I know who you are.
I've never missed an episode
of Danny and Spots.
Whatever happened to Spots?
I loved that sock puppet.
He's on my left foot.
Glad to see you're still working together.
So I can't wait to introduce
to you my new invention
and prove to the world I'm not washed-up.
Richie, I am so excited to hear--
[phone ringing]
Sorry, one second.
I'm getting a phone call.
Hello? Dan Tandy.
Yes, I am still alive.
Thanks for calling.
- Is that a hover phone?
- Yeah, just came out this week.
It's great because you don't have
to lift the phone to your ear.
So what's the amazing idea
that you wanted to tell me about?
It's, uh...
Uh...
the nose pick.
The nose pick?
- What were you thinking?
- I panicked.
Then whey did you say
you were unveiling it
at a presentation this Thursday?
I really panicked.
But maybe with your guys' help,
we can put something together
that won't totally humiliate me.
I mean, Murray, you're one of the best
business minds around,
and, Tahj, you're... here.
Thanks, Richie. That really means a lot.
Okay, how do we make this
a little less terrible?
Well, first of all,
you're gonna need to cut costs.
You can't use Bolivian rosewood.
That's too expensive.
One word, balsa.
But wouldn't it just break easier?
People would just
have to keep buying more.
You're getting it.
You're finally getting it.
Okay, I guess that makes sense.
Also, we're gonna need
to train a team of baboons
to manufacture these things.
Okay, that doesn't make any sense.
You have free labor
just hanging out in your zoo.
- Put them to work.
- Look, look, forget all that.
What's gonna make the nose pick
really take off
is a big, flashy introduction.
If you blind them with glitz,
they won't notice you can't rap.
- Huh?
- I mean nose pick.
Or whatever we're doing here.
[cash register dings]
Okay, since we're all here
for our passion for caring
and giving and blah, blah, blah,
we should decide what cause to help.
We should help the fish in the ocean.
- They're in danger.
- Like, from pollution?
No, they're all out in the water
without any lifeguards.
I think I found someone who could use
all the help they can get.
Look, if we want notoriety,
we need to pick a cause
that stands out,
something that people
are afraid to deal with.
Fish lifeguards. Exactly!
No.
- Foot fungus.
- Foot fungus?
Yes, it's a cause no one else is touching.
Yeah, because it's highly contagious.
Which is why we need to end it.
We can make an informational video
about the dangers of foot fungus.
It can have statistics
and facts and charts.
Nobody's going to watch that.
If we do that, the foot fungus wins.
Have you ever tried
to balance a pizza on your head?
Here, Tulip, play with these keys.
No, wait a second. She's on to something.
Huh?
Tulip's idea sounds entertaining.
I would much rather watch
people trying to balance pizzas
on their heads
than watching charts, statistics, or you.
But pizzas have nothing to do
with foot fungus.
You're getting it.
You're finally getting it.
That's crazy.
I'm gonna make a serious,
fact-filled video,
and everyone is gonna see
what a kind and generous
and not shouting person I am.
[cash register dings]
I'm so happy you went
with the nose pick idea.
And thanks for letting me be the mascot.
Wait, when did I agree to--
All right, thanks so much again.
I got to go warm up the audience.
- No, Dad!
- Ladies and gentlemen.
Who is in dire need of a nose picking?
You sir, I bet
you got some bats in the cave.
Ma'am, we can get those
green nuggets out of there--
Whoa!
Tahj, we need to start this thing now.
Are you ready with the lights?
Yeah, man, I'm ready when you are.
Remember, this is your moment.
It's your time to shine.
[pulsing electronic music]
Yo, look at me!
T-nice is up in here.
Tahj, think you can spare
the spotlight for the stage?
One second, I'm still shining.
♪ ♪
- Tahj!
- Sorry.
I needed that.
Now it's your time to shine.
Hello, everyone!
And welcome to the--
Laser show!
Who's ready for this?
Oh, man.
I wore out the battery
playing with my cat.
I thought you knew
how to wow audiences.
I wow'd my cat.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm proud to introduce to you
the next generation
of nostril maintenance.
Feast your eyes on the nose pick.
What are these sticks?
Turns out baboons can't use power tools,
but they can throw them.
Murray, I can't present sticks
as my big invention.
I said that very thing to the baboons.
That's when the situation got out of hand.
People, please, I'm not washed-up.
I beg you, don't leave.
Ah!
It's the one that took
the belt sander to my ear.
Run!
[people screaming]
That's it. I'm washed-up.
Hey, on the bright side,
you just got next month's cover.
Now, give us a nice big frown.
Oh, that's great. Work it, work it.
[loud guitar riff]
Come on, Master Richie, get up.
Guess what. Harper has moved out.
[air pops]
Irona, I'm awake.
I just don't have any reason
to get out of bed.
I'm washed-up.
Master Richie,
you are not washed-up,
and I mean that literally.
You really need a shower.
How's he doing?
He just went to bed at 9:00 a.m.,
so not great.
Hey, buddy. So you failed.
I failed at lots and lots
and lots and lots
and lots of things, like--
oh, nothing comes to mind at the moment.
I consider this pep talk a failure.
Come on, Master Richie.
You have to get out of bed.
Mainly because I need
to change your sheets,
but also because, you know,
feelings.
- Leave me alone.
- That's it.
Richie, you have no reason
to feel sorry for yourself.
So some stupid magazine
called you pathetic.
People call me names all the time,
but do I hide in bed?
No, not unless the pollen count is high.
Then it's just common sense.
Thanks.
You guys make a lot of sense,
some more than others.
I guess just because
I humiliated myself
doesn't mean I should give up.
I mean, I'm sure I can come up
with something else.
Whoa. What did you just do?
I pulled up my pajamas. I was too hot.
- Where did you get those?
- I designed them.
Whenever I sleep, I'm too hot.
Then I'm too cold.
These pajamas keep me
comfortable all night.
You had these pajamas the whole time,
and you went with the nose pick?
What's wrong with you?
You guys really think we can sell these?
Of course.
I'll get the baboons to work right away.
Hold on, I want your help,
but this time, I want
a little bit less of your help.
[cash register dings]
Hey, guys, hate to spoil the pizza party,
but my foot fungus video
has gotten 13 views,
three likes,
and a few hurtful comments,
but those people have been blocked.
Wow, 13.
That's more than I thought you'd get.
Yes, well, people appreciate
straight information
delivered to them by someone
in a tasteful turtleneck.
Guess you guys shouldn't have
hopped off the Harper Express.
Next stop, Harvard.
Oh, yeah, we saw your little train
while we were blasting past you
on the Darcy-Tulip rocket ship.
[imitates explosion]
What are you talking about?
Our pizza balance challenge
is sweeping the nation.
Over 15 million people
have uploaded videos.
Is 15 million more than 13?
I really don't know.
- You can't be serious.
- Care to see for yourself?
Hi, I'm Becky Samuels,
and I accept the pizza balance challenge
to fight foot fungus.
Here I go.
That was harder than I thought.
Okay, I dedicate this to my cousin Joe,
who hasn't been able
to wear sandals since 1997.
Okay.
Yeah. Hang in there, Joe!
Hi, my name is Irona,
and even though my feet are made
of fungus-resistant titanium,
I did not want to miss out
on the pizza balance challenge.
Great, here goes nothing.
Hey, I'm doing it.
This must be what humans call fun.
Sorry. Couldn't resist.
Okay, so people are doing
your stupid pizza thing.
It doesn't mean we're any closer
to finding a cure for foot fungus.
Actually we've raised over $6 million.
They're building a statue of us
at the Foot Fungus Institute.
It's gonna look like this.
She'll stay like that for hours.
- It's amazing.
- That's amazing.
Thank you so much.
Harper, I've never heard you
say the words
"thank" and "you" in the same sentence.
Well, it's just because I feel for those
afflicted with foot fungus.
I mean, I can only imagine how hard it is
to go through the day
with painfully itchy feet.
- Wait, you have foot fungus.
- Ew, no, I don't.
Oh, sweet relief!
That's why you wanted to find a cure.
Okay, I admit it.
I've been living a lie,
a blistered, painful, itchy lie.
Darcy, help me.
I can't help you,
but you can help yourself.
Hi, I'm Harper Rich,
and I really hope they find
a cure for foot fungus,
like, today.
I forgot to breathe.
I'm really proud of you
for not giving up, Richie.
How'd you get everyone to show up again?
I just sent them invitations
printed out in $100 bills.
Hello, everyone,
and thank you for coming back.
I can assure you all the baboons
have been recaptured.
Sleep is a constant battle
between being too hot and too cold.
Well, now that battle is over
thanks to adjustable pajama
pant leg things.
[applause]
Humans will buy anything.
Yeah, I see there are
some T-nice fans in the house.
They're not clapping for you.
They're clapping for me.
I know how to work a runway.
I have to hand it to you, Richie.
No one has ever recovered
from being on the cover
of Washed-up Rich Kids Monthly.
I got to ask, man. How'd you do it?
I have friends
who never stop believing in me.
Friends, huh?
Is there any other way?
Perhaps something
involving a sock puppet?
I'm afraid not.