Okay, everyone, time to award
the employee of the month.
Sure hope it's not me again.
Six in a row would feel a bit gratuitous.
Plus, I don't even knowwhat I'd do with another watch.
I just want to thank you guys
for working so very hard this month.
Especially you, Fritz--my dad wouldn't be here
if you didn't give him mouth-to-mouth
after he nearly drowned
running through the sprinkler.
Well, he saved your dad,
but I saved you $4 on your cable bill,
so...
you know.
Okay, the employee of the month goes to...
Irona.
Irona?
What did she ever do?
Her dusting skills
have really improved this month.
- How?- She started doing it.
I cannot believe I won.
I accept this award, not for myself,
but for all the little robots out there.
Richie, what is the recount procedure?
Uh, do I write a letter, make a call?
Just tell me how to getthe ball rolling here.
-Murray, please, today's
all about honoring Irona.
[doorbell rings]
Doorbell, Irona.
The world press has named meman of the year.
Wow, another award.
I accept this award, not for myself--
Let me see that.
Richie, it's you!
You're man of the year.
Me? Really?
Wow, this is such an amazing honor.
- We should celebrate.- Agreed.
I will plan a partystarting tomorrow morning
since we've already establishedtoday is my day.
[cash register dings]My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family andthe best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
This man of the yeargift basket is amazing.
Look at all these muffins.
And car keys!
Richie, there's a new carout there filled with crumbs
and muffin wrappers.
That is because I'm man of the year.
That's awesome.
What does that mean for me?
It's means we all get to go
to the man of the year gala.
Not only is thatthe biggest party of the year,
but they have a photo boothwith mustache sticks.
I can't wait.
That sounds like a great excuse
for me to go shopping.
There's my son that I'm so proud of.
Thanks, dad, but, uh,
why'd you bring me flowers?
Oh, these are for Fritz.
But I did come in here
to tell you how proud I am
about your award.
[chuckles]
I would brag to my coworkers
about this, but, you know...
Guys, I hope you're not talking about
how I got ripped off forthe employee of the month award.
People, you have to get past it.
Guys, earning this award is great, but...
the most important part
is being able to spend time
- with you at the gala.- Gala?
Oh, that's a big, fancy dinner.
Ooh, night lunches. I like night lunches.
[cha-ching]
What's good, bae?
Ugh, first Richie wins man of the year,
and then you show up?
I just want you to follow me on pictogram.
I'm almost at 10,000 followers.
That won't be happening
mainly because I don't like you
but also because I don't use pictogram.
You're not on pictogram?
Even my grandmother's on there.
I'm swinging by her place after this
to go beg her to follow me.
Social media is nothing buta mind-numbing waste of time.
Oh, sick, Bradley Steven Perry just posted
a picture of a chili dog he's about to eat.
My point exactly.
Posting online is how you stay
relevant in today's society.
Anyone who's anyone is on there.
Musicians, Harvard professors, me.
Wait, Harvard professors are on pictogram?
Oh, yeah, check it out.One just posted a selfie.
That's renowned astrophysicist
Joanne Gergely-Bowling.
Wearing her cat as a scarf.
She tagged it for Caturday.
Everyone posts pictures of themselves
with their cats on Saturdays.
Want to see me and my tabbyat my piano recital?
No.
But I do want to see more pictures
of Joanne Gergely-Bowling.
I have to get on pictogram.
There's no bikini shots. I checked.
[cha-ching]
Richie, do you know who
we're going to be sitting with?
Any celebrities?
Did they confirmwhether they're going to be
validating parking?
Oh, Richie, I have an important question.
Will there be breadsticks?
Yes, there will be breadsticks.
Good, then I won't need to bring these.
- Will there be spaghetti?- Please don't answer that.
I'm just looking forwardto having a great night.
Tomorrow,
at this time.
I know what you're doing.
Guys, I don't want to make
my man of the year award
all about me.
This gala is to celebrate all of us,
especially Irona,
our employee of the--
[doorbell rings]
Irona, could you grab that?
- Oh, no.- What is it?
Are they not validating?
Don't worry, my mom can drop us off.
It's the official invitation
to the man of the year gala.
I can only bring one guest.
Don't worry, you guys.
I'll take a lot of pictures.
Why isn't anyone following me?
What is wrong with you people?
Tahj, it's Harper.
Could you come over?
No, this isn't your dad messing with you.
It's really Harper.
What's good, bae?
I have been on pictogram for a day now,
and I still don't have a single follower.
Well, you have at least one.
I follow you.
I may have blocked you.
Look, I really need your help.
Nobody has noticed me.It's like I don't exist.
Well, you are asking the right guy.
The T-Nice account recentlypassed 11,000 followers,
no thanks to you or my grandma.
You got 1,000 followers in a day?
How is that possible?
You got to know what to post, baby.
Like, take a pic of me and tag it
"man crush monday."
I'm not that desperate.
We'll work up to it.
All right, let's start with a selfie.
Will you take it for me?
[cha-ching]
Hey, Richie, I know it's going to be
really hard to choose whoto take with you to the gala,
so I just wanted to tell you
how much you mean to me
as a friend in song.
Murray, that's really not--
[plays note]
♪ Richie ♪
♪ And Murray! ♪
♪ Murray, Murray, Murray, Murray ♪
♪ And Richie! ♪
♪ Richie and Murray, Richie and Murray ♪
♪ Richie, Murray ♪
- ♪ Richie! ♪- Thanks, Murray.
You mean a lot to me, too.
Please, I haven't even gotten to the bridge.
♪ Murray! ♪
[cha-ching]
Hey, Richie, as your father,
I don't want you to strugglewith who to take.
I'm an adult.
I can handle it.
I appreciate that, dad.
Oh, please! Please take me!
Please! I want breadsticks.
Please!
I want breadsticks.[crying]
[cha-ching]
I can't wait to partywith all of those celebs.
Thank you again for picking me, Richie.
And don't feel bad--I spoke with everybody else,
and they said they were fine with it.
[gibberish sobbing]
Richie.
♪ Richie ♪
♪ And Murray ♪
See? They're good with it.
Master Richie, I found out I will
turn to a pumpkin at midnightif I do not attend a gala.
If only there were one coming up.
[gibberish sobbing]
Richie.
♪ And Murray ♪
Everybody stop!
Yeah, just accept that I'm going.
You guys aren't making
this decision any easier on me.
There has to be a fair way to figure out
who to take to the gala.
Welcome.
The time has come to select one
lucky boy, girl, robot, or man
for the honor of accompanying Richie
to the man of the year gala.
Let the games... snikt!
Begin.
This doesn't seem fair.
I like my chances.
I volunteer!
To go to the gala.Let's stop this charade.
Guys, this is ridiculous.
There's got to be an easier way
to make this decision.
I'm not letting you
fight to the death
Hunger Games style.
That's a relief. I already ate my weapon.
[cha-ching]
All right, stand in front of this poster.
You're about to take a selfie in Aruba.
- That's dishonest.- That's the internet.
Now hold your phone away from your face.
Pucker your lips and snap.
[camera snaps]Oh, more lips.
Squint those eyes. Work it, girl.
You're beautiful. You're gorgeous.
- Will you go out with me?- No.
Oh, I was just trying to get a reaction for the pic.
Unless you actually want to.
In which case, how about this Saturday,
poolside, probably supervisedby my parents?
All right, now we needan ironic caption, like,
"always on the grind."
- What does that mean?- Doesn't matter.
All right, now we need to tagyour pic, so it's searchable.
Since this is your first one,
we'll only start with a few.
Beach, water, sand, no work, all play,
chilling, chilling, chill,sun, sunshine, vacay,
all day every day, follow for follow,
please follow, I need followers,
- I'm desperate.- I think that's enough.
Oh, no, we need a few more. Justin Bieber,
I love the Biebs forever,marry me, Justin.
What does my picture
have to do with Justin Bieber?
Everything on pictogram
has to do with Justin Bieber.
[mouths word]
[cha-ching]
Thanks so much for coming over.
I know you're probably really busy
with planning the gala and everything.
I am.
Look, the invitation said
I could only bring one guest,
and I need to bring four.
Or three with a robot, if that changes anything.
It doesn't.
A plus-one is a plus-one,person or otherwise.
I live with two cats,and every year after the gala,
one of them refuses to speak to me.
Speak to you?
Look, I've already invited them,
and I have no idea
how to choosebetween my friends and family.
The same way I choosebetween cuddles and snuggles.
Hello and welcome
to "who knows Richie best?"
The game show to help me decide
who to take to the man of the year gala.
Okay, let's meet our contestants.
He's a 13-year-old money manager
who collects casserole recipes.
Say hello to Murray.
He's a professional napper
who loves naps and napping.
Say hello to Cliff.
She may be small, but her shopping addiction is huge.
It's Darcy.
Wait. Richie, I don't understand why--
And our last contestant is...
Irona.
Okay, let's start the game.
Buzzers ready.
When was my birthday?
[buzzer]January 40.
Let me stop you there.
[buzzer]
April 6th, 8:27 P.M.
It was a Wednesday.
The wind was out of the northeast, 6 to 7 knots.
The number one song in the country was--
Okay, one point to Murray.
Okay, next question: When was
the last time I wet the bed?
[buzzer]Last night.
Wrong. Trick question.
I've never wet the bed.
But, Master Richie, that is--
That's correct, never happened.
One point to Irona.
Next question, what was Prussia's role
in shaping modern Europe?
What does that have to do
with how well we know you?
Actually, I have a history paper,
and I really need help with it.
[as a game show announcer]
We have a tie.
I sound excited, but that is
the worst possible outcome.
I just can't stop talking like this.
[as a game show announcer]
Come on, Richie,
make a decision.
Oh, wow, you're right.
This voice is addicting.
[as a game show announcer]Now you've got me doing it.
Guys, this didn't work.
I think I know what I need to do.
I know how much it meansto you to go to the gala,
so I would be honored if you'dbe the one to come with me.
[all] Thank you.
Oh, but for everyone else's sake,
let's just keep this between you and me.
thank you so much for picking me, Richie.
Even though I knew
you'd make the right decision,
it still means a lot.
Of course, Darcy.
I couldn't imagine bringing anyone else.
I see you've made your choice.
There was never a doubt.
Thanks, Mom!
Yes, I'll ask Richie for gas money!
Hey, Darcy, is that a Kardashian?
I can't tell. I can only see her face.
She needs to turn around.
Yep.
Hey, Murray.
Glad you could make it.
Thanks so much for picking me, Richie.
Of course, I couldn't imagine bringing anyone else.
Hey, uh, what's with the fanny pack?
Oh, this is for appetizers.
At my cousin's wedding,I got 47 crab puffs in here.
Hey, they're putting outthe bacon scallops.
And they look travel-worthy.
I'm on it.
H-hey, Dad. Glad you could make it.
But, uh, why didn't you takethe limousine I sent you?
I don't get into strangers' cars,
and neither should you.
Well, you should probably lock that up.
Good thinking.
There's a lot ofshady characters in this place.
Hey, go get your own BMX racer, old man.
Hey, Irona. You look great.
I'm glad you could bethe one here with me.
Come back, Khloe.
Look, a wall.
Yes, it is.
This is America.
Nowhere in the constitution
does it say I cannot
fill a plastic bag upwith bacon-wrapped scallops.
Do you know what's
on the other side of that wall?
No? A restroom,
which just so happens to have
the fanciest automated
hand dryers on the market.
No.
My hands do feel a bit dirty.
Whew.
Don't worry. He's with me.
And just to be clear,he's the only one with me.
Thanks for that, Richie.
That guy was way out of line.
Murray, I think you're leaking spring rolls.
Thanks.
[cha-ching]
What is up with this pictogram thing?
I did everything you said,
and I still only have three followers.
You have three. That's a start.
I have a sneaking suspicion
that the Tahj, T-Nice,and Tahj-Barrage accounts
are all the same person.
Sometimes girls block one account
but don't realize I have more tha--
I mean, yeah, I suppose it's possible.
I just don't understand how you have--
20,000 followers? Who are these people?
People who love me. Fans, really.
I call them t-nicesters.
So this guy, "follow for cash,"
is a "t-nicester"?
Uh, yeah.
That's-- that's my homie from way back.
Yeah, it's actually pronounced folo cash.
The "for" is silent.
You pay for all your followers?
Yes, except for my grandma.
Okay, I paid her too.
I can't believe I've beenlistening to you this whole time
and all of your followers are fake.
That is it. I'm done.
[elevator dings]
This has been the biggest waste of my time.
Pictogram is a joke.
This obsession with
impressing strangers for likes
is the decay of our society.
Well, you know what I don't like?
I don't like seeing your catplay the piano.
I don't like seeing your food
that you're about to eat.
And what I don't like--
[grunting]
[screams]Tahj!
Put down the phone! My hair is stuck!
Get over here.
[grunts]
[cha-ching]
And what I don't like--
[grunting]
[screams]
Tahj!
Put down the phone! My hair is stuck!
This is awesome.
Yeah, you have over 2 million followers.
And I didn't pay for a single one.
[cha-ching]
Irona, it's okay.
There are other hand dryers out there.
I am done with them.They are so full of hot air.
You know what?
If you are emotionally ready,
I did see an ATM out in the lobby, and he is loaded.
- Do I look--- Yep, go.
Hey, Darcy.
Did you get that picwith Khloe Kardashian?
Not a good one. Kourtney photobombed it.
Oh.
Did I just hearHarry Styles under the table?
Harry, it's you.
I'm your biggest fan.
Did I just hear Darcy?
No!
Why would she be here
when you're obviously
my one and only guest?
How was I supposed to know you
weren't done with your steak?
You put your fork down.
Um, Dad, where'd your helmet go?
One of these billionairesmust have stolen it.
Have you seen my helmet? Have you?
Murray, put the prime minister's food down.
Why is your backpack moving?
Oh, don't worry about it.
But on a completely unrelated note,
tomorrow night you are welcome at my place
for lobster a la backpack.
I need to search
your backpack for my helmet.
Dad. Dad, no.
Mr. Rich?[screaming]
Something's biting me![grunting]
No, Mr. Rich, wait!
There's close to $1,000 worth
of seafood in there.
Hey, I'm trying to have a conversation
with Harry Styles under there.
- Mr. Rich?- Darcy?
- Murray?- That ATM is a jerk.
- Irona?- Mr. Rich?
Darcy? Murray?
[all] Richie?
You told me I was the only oneyou were taking.
- Me, too.- Sounds familiar.
I think you said that, butI'm in a lot of pain right now.
I--
I guess we should probably do this now.
The man of the year... Richie Rich.
[applause]
I'm really sorryfor ruining your guys' evening.
But I was only allowed one guest,
and I couldn't pick betweenthe most important people
in my life.
They're the only reason I'm up here today.
- Thanks, Richie.- That was really sweet.
if I had feelings, I would probably be feeling something
right now.
Richie, next time just be honest.
This night isn't about us.
We could have worked it outbetween ourselves.
- Right?- Yes.
- Absolutely.- Yeah, I guess if we had to.
Thanks for always looking out for me.
You guys are the best.[all] Aww.
Thanks again for the award.
I really appreciate it.
Oh, and by the way,
they wanted me to say
that we are out of lobster,
and I apologize to the tables
who no longer have salt shakers.
And there will be no dessert.
Start the car, Mom!