I'm telling you, baby,
a game app based on your life
gives me goose bumps.
And the good ones,
not the kind that don't go away
for a few months.
I don't think those are goose bumps.
And I'm not sure I want to do this.
Uh, why not?
I mean, don't you know how much
good can come from this?
I mean, I could finally move out
of my parents' basement,
and you...
can know that you helped me
move out of my parents' basement.
I'm not the kind of guy who wants to
open his life up to the public.
Master Richie,
should I cancel those meetings
with the publishers
regarding your autobiography?
Oh, no, that's different.
Dude, this isn't
some hard-hitting documentary.
It's, as my parents would say,
"It's just a stupid,
little animated game."
Richie, tell your friend
Murray to leave me alone.
He followed me all around the mall
waving this paper in my face.
He made it really hard
to spend your money.
I mean, I still did it,
but he made it harder
than I like it to be.
It's not a piece of paper, it's a memo
declaring you cannot shop
between the hours of "all day."
No one reads your stupid memos.
Richie, Irona, tell Darcy she is mistaken.
[both] Um...
Oh, hey, are you the replacement Murray
I've been begging for?
No, I'm Bixby Knox,
app developer extraordinaire.
I'm the guy who brought
the world Pastry Crunch.
Pastry Crunch is quite addictive.
I have it on my internal processor
and play for hours a day...
during my 15-minute break.
Have you seen the new ultra level?
There's a new ultra level?
Excuse me. I have dusting to do.
Load Pastry Crunch.
Whoa, they added croissants!
So cool.
Memo to self,
write memo about employees
playing video games on company time.
So what are you doing here?
He was trying to convince me
to make an app based on my life,
but I told him no.
- [both] Why?
- We could be famous.
We could make money.
We could move out
of our parents' basement.
I don't know.
- Famous.
- Money.
Basement.
- [cash register dings]
- My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
Come on, scone booster. Come on!
Memo to self, write memo about--
All right, guys, I just want to ask you
a few questions to make
the Richie game more realistic.
Okay? First question.
My mom packed me some carrot sticks.
Who would like to trade for fruit gummies?
Are you sure you've done this before?
What? Traded lunches?
I do it every day.
Let me show you what makes Murray tick.
There's me buying my first long-term bond.
There's my dad holding the baby carrier
up to the banker's window.
Murray, what are you doing?
Simply equipping Bixby
with the knowledge
he needs to fully flesh out
the Murray character.
[gasps]
Here is a suspicious mole
my dermatologist removed from my back.
It was benign.
Murray!
Bixby does not need to see that!
No one does.
Okay, so let's talk about Darcy.
She's smart, beautiful, humble.
She's also the kindest person
you'll ever meet.
Have you met yourself?
Shut up, Murray!
Guys, I think Bixby has a good sense
of your personalities.
Are you sure?
Here's a picture of me with my hero,
renowned economist Alan Greenspan.
I wanted him to sign it,
but the police dragged me
out of his kitchen
before I got the chance.
Here's a pic of my hero.
Darcy, that's you.
Yeah, so?
Who says you can't be your own hero?
Guys, that's enough.
I think I need to talk to Bixby alone.
Yes, please.
We have some very important
business to discuss.
Yeah.
So...
let's talk trade.
[cha-ching]
♪ Grover, the preeminent president ♪
♪ Grover, from New York
to the Rio Grande ♪
♪ Everyone loves Cleveland ♪
Amazing.
Thank you.
Oh, I meant
this new teriyaki dipping sauce.
Dad, focus.
I found out that Harvard School
of Musical Theater has
a 6% higher acceptance rate,
so I'm reinventing myself.
I mean...
♪ Reinventing myself ♪
- Incredible.
- I know, right?
Teriyaki sauce again.
But if you need any help,
I know a few things
about musical theater.
Dad, I appreciate the offer,
but when you try to help me,
it usually ends in disaster.
Always ends in disaster.
Suit yourself.
Boring history is not
a good subject for a musical,
but, hey, what do I know?
I was only the lead in over 30 plays
down at the community theater.
You were? When?
Back when I had spare time.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to get to my game shows.
Just out of curiosity,
if I were to ask for your help,
what would you say about
Grover Cleveland, the musical?
I would say we need to find a new muppet
to write a musical about.
So here he is,
the man of the night, Richie Rich.
How are you feeling?
Are you nervous walking into
the premiere of your game app?
No, I feel quite at home.
But that might be
because we're in my bedroom.
The best part of this is being able
to share this experience
with my two best friends.
Get in here, Darcy and Murray.
Before you ask,
I am wearing Dissue Alasson,
who I adore, and jewels
provided by Richie Rich.
Which he is unaware of.
And I am wearing a rental
from Rupert's Tuxedos on Magnolia
because they were kind enough
to honor my expired coupon.
Hello. Attention please.
Focus spider. Yeah. Hey.
This is a very important night
for me, Richie Rich,
and my parents, who are at home
spending their first night alone
since 1980.
[scattered applause]
Yeah. They're very happy.
So happy.
Now, with no further ado,
I present to you all
the Richie Rich app.
[upbeat music]
- Trish?
- Zeke?
I didn't know about this, I swear.
To think I wasted
an expired coupon for this.
I had no idea Bixby was replacing you.
Oh, please.
I know how much you love the name "Trish."
that's what you call
that strawberry princess doll
you play with.
No.
She's Patricia.
I think. I don't know.
It's Harper's doll.
Did you call for Patricia?
Should I set up the tea party?
No!
Absolutely...
yes.
And Polly Papaya will be joining.
I'll admit,
Zeke has a certain cool factor,
and I'd kill for shoulders that broad,
but this is humiliating.
I sent a memo to all my friends
telling them I was gonna be in the app.
Now I have to call Dave and tell him
not to read my memo.
I'm so sorry.
I promise I had nothing to do with this.
Richie, I don't know
if I can recover from this pain.
But give me your credit card. I'll try.
I'm gonna make this up to you.
I'll tell Bixby if he doesn't
put you in the game,
I'll put him back
in his parents' basement.
I appreciate that,
but for Bixby 's parents' sake,
maybe you should give them tonight
and talk to him tomorrow.
[cha-ching]
Now, before we can create
musical theater,
we have to master non-musical theater.
It's the same thing.
It's just a little quieter.
Now, I want you to act
like a moody teenager.
Dad, stop it. You're being weird.
Wow, that felt really real.
The theater is strong with this one.
Why are you talking like Yoda?
Talking like Yoda, I am not.
My grammar bad, just is.
[as Yoda] Like Yoda I speak now,
young Harper, mm.
Dad, I'm starting to get
a familiar sense of dread.
Beware the dark side.
Dread, fear, crippling,
overwhelming depression--
the dark side of musical theater are they.
[imitating lightsaber humming]
- Prepare to engage in battle.
- This is totally--
[imitates lightsaber swooshing]
Dad!
Defend yourself, actor!
Use the theater.
Okay, fine.
[both imitating lightsabers clashing]
[groaning]
[imitates lightsaber swooshing]
Congratulations! You just acted!
- I did?
- And you defeated your father.
That's right.
I am your father.
That is what all the tests have said.
[cha-ching]
Richie, baby!
Welcome to my rent-controlled
studio apartment.
Come on in. Take a seat wherever you like.
Sure, you can sit on my chair.
Yeah, I'll--
I'll just sit on this trash can.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Mm, comfy.
I'd offer you some carrot sticks,
but I had to trade them for that chair.
Actually, I'm here to talk about the app.
You have to get rid of Zeke and Trish.
I want Darcy and Murray to be my friends.
Dude, I know virtual Richie,
and virtual Richie
wouldn't hang out with them.
But I'm actual Richie,
and virtual Richie's based on me.
Sort of, kind of.
Like, virtual Richie wouldn't
come into another guy's house
and sit in his only chair.
Besides, the app's a hit.
Why would you want to mess with it?
Because it hurt my friends' feelings.
Friends. Friends.
Ah, friends. Yeah.
They only get in the way.
That's why the only friend
I need is money.
[coins jingling]
Okay,
how about I buy you another folding chair,
one that doesn't smell like raccoon?
They make those?
Yes.
All right,
your friends are back in the game.
Oh, it's all happening, Bixby.
[chuckling]
Hey, is that your limo out there?
Yeah.
Because someone's boosting the hubcaps.
[cha-ching]
[upbeat, quirky music]
♪ Teriyaki, ranch ♪
♪ Mustard with honey ♪
♪ Buffalo, barbecue, spicy chipotle ♪
♪ Variety, they say, is life's spice ♪
♪ You have to dip to live ♪
♪ But don't get caught dipping twice ♪
All right. Great opening.
We can clean up
your choreography a bit later.
I think we should run
Ode To Sweet 'n' Sour
a few more times,
'cause that's the number
that'll really get audiences
right in the heart.
Dad, are you really sure
that Harvard School of Musical Theater
is gonna be impressed
with Totally Sauce-ome?
Trust me, Harper.
I've been the lead in lots of musicals,
and I even stayed to watch
quite a few of them.
Watch?
- You said you were the lead.
- I was.
I was the guy who led
the audience to their seats.
You were an usher?
Well, that's the technical term.
No, that's not the technical term,
that is the term.
A lead is an actor.
You did no acting!
Uh, not true.
I acted like I knew where the seats were.
Usually, I was just making it up.
I knew this was a horrible idea
before I put on
the chicken nugget costume.
[sentimental piano music]
♪ Don't go ♪
♪ Let me win back your trust ♪
♪ You can't leave me
with tears running down ♪
♪ My breaded crust ♪
Irona, your Pastry Crunch addiction
has gotten out of control.
What are you talking about?
I have not played that game in months.
On a completely unrelated note,
could I get an advance on my salary
in the form of game credits?
Hey, Richie,
it's just your former best friend
here to gather a few of her things.
And here I am with a resignation memo.
I can't work in a place I'm not respected.
Then you'll never work again.
Guys, I spoke to Bixby,
and I think you're gonna be happy
when you see the new version of the app.
What?
Why do I need to buy more game credits?
I have no idea.
I certainly did not hack into your account
and use them to buy the next level
of Pastry Crunch...
which I do not play.
Credit card number?
I don't have that memorized.
I do.
Okay, I probably should have
previewed that
before I showed it to you.
Ah, it doesn't get better than this.
[knocking at door]
It's open.
Uh, unless--
Unless you're a burglar.
Then it's locked.
And I have a guard dog.
Woof! Woof! Bark!
B--hey.
We need to talk.
No problem. Come on in.
Welcome to the new and improved
casa de Bixby
that your app built.
How does it feel to finally be a success?
- Not good.
- Really?
Because I'm loving life.
[fan whirring]
Bet you never saw one of those before.
What you did to my friends was wrong.
Hey, I had to make the game entertaining.
And, as you can see,
I made the right call.
Check it out.
Doubled our profits.
[coins jingling]
To you, this is just a game,
but it's my life.
Neither of my best friends
will talk to me anymore.
Bro, we can be friends.
Uh, I got a magazine,
and we can take turns reading it.
I'm done with this app.
Take it down.
Oh, I can't do that.
Yes, you can. You have to.
It's an app based on my life.
No, it's not.
It's based on virtual Richie's life,
and he stopped by earlier
and insisted that I keep it up.
You've lost it.
No, I've found it.
Now, please go before I release
my guard dog on you.
Woof! Bark!
Growl! Get out!
[cha-ching]
[twinkling musical flourish]
♪ With the economy in the dumps ♪
♪ Grover never got goose bumps ♪
♪ And made defectors
of the Republican mugwumps ♪
♪ From rich to poor ♪
♪ All but the unions adored ♪
♪ Your stance
on the Pullman strike of 1894 ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ Barrel-chested ♪
♪ And history tested ♪
♪ Number one in my book? ♪
♪ Yes, you guessed it ♪
♪ Grover, the preeminent president ♪
♪ Grover, from New York
to the Rio Grande ♪
♪ Everyone loved Cleveland ♪
♪ Grover Cleveland, yeah ♪
Well, I'm sorry you got rejected,
but I don't care
what the Harvard School
of Musical Theater says,
the theater is strong in you.
Thanks, Dad, but you were right.
Grover Cleveland might not have been
the best subject for a musical.
Well, this doesn't have to be
the end of your theater career.
In fact, I made a few phone calls
and found a producer
willing to put up big bucks
to stage Totally Sauce-ome.
Like on Broadway?
That might impress Harvard.
In a ball pit at a fast-food joint.
But, hey, show business is show business.
[cha-ching]
Darcy and Murray refuse to speak to me,
and there's nothing I can do about it.
That is tough.
Darcy. Murray. Bad stuff.
Irona, are you listening to me?
Yes, master pastry.
I mean Richie.
Okay, I paused my game.
I am listening.
That nut Bixby
refuses to change
that stupid Richie Rich app,
and it's ruining my life.
Well, would you like me
to hack into the game's mainframe
and change the coding?
You can do that?
Why didn't you say anything?
Because I have been busy...
cleaning.
Okay, I have accessed the app.
What would you like me to do?
I had Irona crash the app.
Our online nightmare is over.
Thanks, Richie. That means a lot.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I agree with Darcy.
I care about you guys.
I'm sorry I let someone come between us.
I'll do anything to make it up to you.
You'll let me keep your car and jet?
- Anything.
- You'll read all of my memos?
Almost anything.