- How dare you!
- What?
I will never forgive you!
What did I do?
You missed my ice dancing performance!
You made me watch that alone.
Imagine the worst thing you've ever seen,
and then set that on fire.
I am so sorry.
I can't believe I forgot that.
Let me make it up to you.
You missed me lutzing
better than I've ever lutzed before.
There's really nothing
you can do to make up for it.
How about a few dozen roses?
Some sequins?
And face glitter?
Yes, yes, and yes!
I forgive you.
What about me?
Do you realize
how emotionally scarred I am
after watching Murray, in that outfit,
fluttering around
like a wounded butterfly?
How about a diamond ring?
I have one.
For your diamond ring.
A diamond ring for my diamond ring.
I forgive you.
Master Richie,
I finished cleaning your time machine.
Perfect!
Now we can travel back in time
to watch Murray's performance.
Oh, no.
Sit through that again?
No way.
So does this time machine actually work?
Why don't you ask the caveman?
[growls]
That's amazing!
But do you think it's safe
to let a caveman run wild in your house?
Oh, yeah.
He and my dad get along great.
Hey, guys. Have you seen ugg?
He was gonna teach me how to make fire.
[smoke detector beeping]
Aww, man, he started without me.
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see,
I used all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
So, guys, where in time do we want to go?
I think you mean
"when" do we want to go?
I vote for the day before we met Murray.
[beeping]
[electrical whirring]
Where are we?
Correction. "When are we?"
Okay, we're done with that.
This is six hours ago.
What an angel I am when I sleep.
[snores]
As exciting as this is,
can we go back into time a little further?
Okay, fine.
[whispers]
Sleep tight, little buddy.
You got a big day ahead of you.
[beeping]
[electrical whirring]
Welcome to the ice age.
Why did you take us here?
Uh-oh.
[ripping]
I saved you guys a salchow.
Let's get out of here!
No!
[beeping]
[electrical whirring]
[grunts]
It's gonna be so cool to see a dinosaur.
I have always wanted a T. Rex purse.
I brought stale bread to feed it.
Why would you do that?
They're just large birds.
[dinosaur roar]
[all scream]
[beeping]
[electrical whirring]
[sighs]
[both scream]
It followed us!
Guys, calm down.
That's just my statue.
Oh.
Thank goodness.
Um...
Irona might need to
clean the time machine again.
Well, thank you for giving me
another chance.
Thank you for the marching band.
I've been to a lot of
college applicant's houses,
but never have I been treated
to a marching band.
Snacks, dinner, swedish massage, yes.
Marching band, no.
[laughs]
That is hysterical.
You are so funny.
Has anyone ever told you that?
No, never.
Well, Mr. Legan,
it would be a dream come true
to attend your university.
Yes, you made that very clear
when you sang the song
with that exact title
before the band got here.
Well, I look forward
to getting your application.
Uh, do you know your way out?
Yes, I'll just follow the red carpet.
Sup, boo?
Why are you pacing?
Aww, were you worried
I wasn't gonna come back?
I'm back.
No more worries.
Tahj, I don't have time for you right now.
I'm waiting to hear back from Harvard,
and they're taking forever.
When did you apply?
Two minutes ago.
I really hope they like my essay.
Ooh, did you say anything about me?
Yo, did you mention T-Nice
is dropping an album on the 19th?
Uh-oh, I see a problem.
What? What is it?
Well, for starters, I don't see anything
about my new album,
but worse, you wrote,
"Harvard is not the place for me."
No, I didn't.
I would never write that,
because Harvard is not the pla--
[gasps]
I did it again!
No, that's supposed to say,
"Harvard is the place for me!
Yeah, that's better.
You should have gone with that.
Darcy, that was so funny when you shouted,
"I see land," right before Columbus did.
And now, every year,
we get to take a "Darcy Day"
off from school.
Yeah, well,
I got something named after me too.
Hey, Richie.
Do you have any more Murray paper?
Ugg and I want to M.P. The house.
Check the storage room.
[electrical whirring]
Hey, Richie!
Dad?
How did you change clothes so fast?
Richie, I'm you from the future.
I need you to come back with me.
I think it's time you put your dad
in that home we talked about.
Okay, I know it sounds crazy,
but I can prove that I'm not your father.
In three, two, one--
Hey, I just made popcorn in the microwave
and blew Ugg's mind!
To the ice machine!
Hohh!
And three, two, one--
Whoa! You are me!
I knew you'd get it!
I can't believe I'm looking
at me from the future.
I thought you would age a little better.
[both] Hey!
So I have to ask.
- Do I ever--
- Yes.
You didn't even know
what I was I going to ask.
Vacation on mars?
Yeah!
You are so me.
So last question--
Yes, The Simpsons are still running.
Ha!
Why are you here?
I think you mean "When is he here?"
Okay, I'll stop.
I came back because
I need Richie's help with our son.
He's your age now, so I figured
you could relate to him.
I have a son?
And a baby daughter.
Oh. Who's our wife?
We married Darcy.
[both] What?
[laughs]
What are you laughing for?
You become a mailman.
[both laugh]
I'm just messing with you.
Oh, thank goodness.
No, I was just messing with them.
You're definitely a mailman.
Wait, so I don't marry Richie?
Nope.
Phew!
Can you tone down
the celebration a little?
Check out the Darcy we do marry.
Whoa!
Could you tone down
the celebration a little?
So is she at home watching the kids?
She's an astronaut, so she's gone a lot.
Irona's watching the kids.
I still work for you
30 years into the future?
Yup!
[sighs]
Come on, Richie, we should head back.
I'm coming with you.
I need to see this mailman thing
with my own eyes.
I want to see my future self too.
Okay, we can stop by the cemetery.
What?
Oh, relax. You just work there.
I work?
[electrical whirring]
[all groaning]
Welcome back, Master Richie.
Good to see you again,
young Master Richie.
Irona, you sound just like a human.
Uh, yeah. It's the future.
Welcome to it.
Can I offer you a beverage?
Yeah.
After 30 years of time travel,
I'm a bit parched.
Lemonade.
[gasps]
Whoa!
That's sick!
Wait. This is iced tea.
Yeah. Technology still has some bugs.
[electricity fizzles]
[baby wails distantly]
Oh, your baby is up.
I would help out,
but I'm gonna go meet up with my husband.
You got married?
Yeah, it's legal now...
in 57 states.
So, Murray and Darcy,
would you mind tending to the baby?
I need to talk to myself for a minute.
I don't know anything about raising kids.
What are you talking about?
You have 14.
On a mailman's salary?
Ugh!
So I was hoping you could help out.
Things haven't been great
between our son and I.
For how long?
12 years.
But I was hoping that you could
nip that in the bud.
Ooh, here he comes.
Fix everything.
Good luck.
I gotta go, bro,
my dad's here with some loser.
I'll holotext you later.
Hey, Ronnie,
this is me from when I was your age.
Great.
What do you want?
I just wanted to hang out.
Why aren't you wearing shoes?
Shoes?
No one wears shoes anymore.
This is why I hate
meeting people from the past.
Dad, can I leave?
- No.
- Whatever you want.
I'm hitting the jet tube.
[engine whooshes]
What happened there?
I don't know.
I've never been a dad before.
Have you asked dad how to deal with this?
President of the world, Cliff?
Good luck getting ahold of him.
[presidential music]
Once Mr. Legan reads that email,
I'm out of Harvard!
My one dream is dashed.
My life is over!
You sound desperate.
How desperate?
[cat meowing ringtone plays]
Nice ringtone.
I don't think that's mine.
I can't be sure.
It's been a while since it rang.
Wait a minute.
Mr. Legan left his phone here!
How do you know it's his?
His screensaver's
a picture of him and his cats.
Now I can just delete
the email with my essay.
Aww, you're cute
when you're clinging to a shred of hope.
Ugh! It's locked!
Stupid passcode!
No worries. T-Nice to the rescue.
I can hack into anything,
phones, computers, hearts.
Hurry up. We don't have a lot of time.
Would you relax?
Let the genius work.
The phone's upside down.
[baby fussing]
Look at the pretty calculator.
It graphs.
[baby wails]
You're making it worse.
This is how my parents shut me up!
It's not working now!
[baby stops crying]
Hey, she's quiet.
[baby resumes crying]
I think she liked it
when we were shouting at each other.
You're an idiot!
You don't have to say mean things!
You just have to shout!
Sorry!
Sometimes I get carried away!
It's all right!
We all make mistakes!
Want to take her for a walk in the park?
That would be nice!
Hey...
sport.
Buddy.
Son.
Want to bond?
Look, you may be my dad,
but you're not my dad.
Get it?
I get it.
I was pretty stubborn when I am your age.
Why don't you tell me what's wrong
with you and your dad?
He missed my spaceball game.
I am so sorry.
I can't believe he missed your game.
Let me make it up to you.
How about a new speed boat?
Is there still water?
See? You guys are the exact same.
well, we are technically--
I can't believe my dad couldn't just
talk to me himself.
He had to go yank mini-him from the past
to deal with me.
It's pathetic.
I don't want to be here anymore!
I'm gonna go breed
wolverines with Aunt Harper!
Hey, how's it going with Ronnie?
Did you patch things up yet?
Not exactly.
He's kinda mad
you missed his spaceball game.
What? That's tomorrow.
Tuesday.
Today is Tuesday.
Ugh, it's been so hard
since they got rid of Monday.
Yeah, well, he sort of, kind of ran off
to go live with Harper.
Are you serious?
He'll never come back!
Harper is such a kind and generous person.
Okay, put a pin in the Harper thing.
We're totally coming back to that.
But first, I have an idea how to get
you and Ronnie back on good terms.
The good thing about
having a time machine is,
you never run out of time.
I'm gonna go back and try again.
[beeping]
[electrical whirring]
Want to take her for a walk in the park?
That would be nice!
Hey, Ronnie!
Look what I got you!
Four tickets to a Drake concert!
[scoffs]
That guy's 60!
Besides,
music stopped being a thing years ago.
It's all numbers now.
Oh.
[beeping]
[electrical whirring]
Want to take her for a walk in the park?
That would be nice!
Hey, buddy.
I got you a skateboard.
One with wheels?
Why don't you roll that back
to the time when people rolled on things?
Okay.
[electrical whirring]
Driver-less car?
Really big TV?
[electrical whirring]
Really small TV?
Welcome mat?
[electrical whirring]
Legal pad?
Butternut squash?
This password is impossible.
I tried one-two-three-four.
I tried four-three-two-one.
I'm out of ideas.
Just give me the phone.
Okay, one-one-one-one.
Ugh!
Not so easy, is it?
Harper?
My apologies for barging in,
but your father
and his rather hairy friend
told me you'd be here.
I may have left my phone here earlier.
Have you seen it?
I have not. But I'll keep my eyes open.
If you were to blurt out
four numbers just randomly,
what would they be?
And you are?
Oh, I'm T-Nice.
The rapper.
Bulldozah's son.
Would you mind
just calling my phone for me?
I would, but I don't have it on me, so--
Oh, you can just use mine.
Don't worry.
I hid the phone where he'll never find it
and turned off his ringer
[cat meowing ringtone playing]
There it is!
Yay!
[electrical whirring]
Want to take her for a walk in the park?
That would be nice!
Master Richie, you have got to stop this.
You've been doing this forever.
Yeah, you're right.
Ronnie's not gonna want
this wig and beard.
Still no luck?
I don't know how to make him happy.
He doesn't want any of my apology gifts.
Tell me about it.
I failed.
I guess I'm not ready to be a dad.
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Let me make it up to you.
Here's a million dollars' worth of water.
Wait.
What?
I'm sorry. I can't spare any more water.
I have a family.
No, you always try to
make things right with a gift.
Oh, do I do that?
Yeah.
We both do.
I just want to do something
nice since I messed up.
But gifts and apologies
don't mean anything
if you keep making the same mistake.
Well, now that I've
helped you two figure that out,
I have 15,000
square feet of carpet to vacuum.
Please vacuum.
[loud whirring]
And I'm done for the day.
Would you two like to explain
what you were doing with my phone?
The truth is, Mr. Legan,
I was really embarrassed.
See, I accidentally submitted
my essay with a typo.
And I wanted to delete it
before you saw it.
A typo?
[scoffs]
Don't worry about it.
[sighs]
Really?
I'm so happy to hear that.
It's not like we can be that picky.
We ain't Harvard.
Say what now?
Don't you work for Harvard?
Not after I slashed the dean's tires...
[laughs]
Anyway, don't worry about the typo.
Wait, where do you work now?
The Topeka Kansas Maritime Institute.
See you there, sailor.
[electrical whirring]
Seriously, Richie?
We're doing this again?
Last time, I promise.
[sighs]
Want to take her for a walk in the park?
That would be nice!
Get it right!
Hey, Ronnie.
I got you something.
Another gift?
No, thanks.
It's me.
I want to go to your spaceball game.
Yeah, right.
You won't show up, and then you'll try to
make it up to me with another present.
He's serious.
As your parents, we both realize
money and gifts
aren't substitutes for love.
I'm sorry, Ronnie.
I'm gonna do better.
You promise?
I promise.
He does.
He really does.
Thanks, Dad...s.
Come here.
Hey, Richie.
You'd be really proud of me and Darcy.
Yeah, we are great babysitters.
Ah, I'm glad you guys are
getting all that practice in.
You're gonna need it since
you have 14 kids together.
[both] What?
You get married after high school.
The future is awesome!
Maybe for you!
[doorbell rings]
Ooh. Mail's here.
Don't open that door!
Wow, Murray.
That was an amazing
ice dancing performance.
I'm really glad I made it this time.
Thanks for coming.
Now you know I'm not bragging.
I have mad skills.
It was still awful.
It was just less awful having you there.
Guys,
I'm really sorry I missed the first one.
Seeing myself in the future
made me realize
I need to make some changes.
I'm not letting myself turn into that guy.
There's a few things in the future
I would like to change too.
Well,
I need to wash the glitter off my hands.
That whole time traveling thing
was pretty crazy, huh?
Yup.
So...
Hi, guys!
[both] Irona!
Come hang out with us!
Yeah, for, like, ever!
You two are so cute together.
No, we are not!
You...take...that...back.