Hey, Irona. Have you seen my new tablet?
Irona?
And...
Now it is 9:00!
Good morning, master Richie.
No, I have not seen your tablet.
I must have been robbed. Where's Darcy?
I do not know. But there's her bag.
Gold bars...
wad of cash...
personal mini shampoos?
Yeah, no tablet.
I must have been robbed by a real burglar.
I am sure you just left it somewhere.
Perhaps you will find it
if you retrace your steps
from this morning.
I guess I can give that a shot.
[yelling] Not here!
Nope.
Don't see it.
No tablet.
Don't look down,
don't look down, don't look down!
Hey, Mr. President, did I leave my tablet
in your office?
Ah, don't think so, Richie.
Hey, we on for golf next week?
I'll let you know.
Not up here.
Hey... there it is.
Nope, that's not mine.
Irona, two things are clear:
Someone broke in and stole from me,
and I need a nap.
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have a trillion dollars.
You see,
I used all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
my dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
Guys, I've been robbed.
Relax, Darcy, I'm not talking
about your everyday petty crime.
Petty? She's taken so much from you,
she'd be serving a life sentence
if you decided to prosecute.
In fact, do you want to prosecute?
I have all the forms filled out.
Give me that!
Guys, this is serious!
Someone's breaking into my room
and stealing stuff from me.
You're not calling the police, are you?
I mean--
we don't want them digging around in here.
[metal clinks]
Relax, I'm not calling the police.
I'm a trillionaire.
I take justice into my own hands.
I'm having my engineers
design special suits
to turn us into superheroes!
Uh, you know superheroes don't exist.
Oh, Murray, when you have money,
anything is possible.
And you would make a great superhero.
[gasps]
Because of my physique?
I have been auditing
my grandma's aquarobics class.
I'm in.
I heard something about a new outfit?
Irona, take us to our superhero lair.
Welcome to the hideout
of the Trillion Dollar Trinity!
- Cool!
- Sick!
Irona, this isn't what I asked for!
You told me you wanted
the powers of an insect,
so you are Roly Poly Boy.
Like one of those cute little bugs?
Cute is not going to capture this burglar!
When I said "insect,"
I was thinking spider or wasp
or scorpion, not roly poly!
What could my superpower possibly be?
When you are threatened or nervous,
you roll up into a ball.
Hey, so do I.
[cha-ching]
That was amazing! So cool!
How could this day possibly
get off to a better start?
What happened?
Trash truck day!
And they even backed the truck
down the driveway,
so it made that awesome noise.
[imitating truck backing up]
Oo-oo-oo-oo--
- I get it. Dad?
- Oo-oo-oo--
Stop!
Oo.
Well, I'm glad your morning went so well.
Ah! What are you doing with that thing?
A banana? Eating it.
Are you crazy? Get it away, get it away!
No, it's just a banana.
"Just a banana"?
Bananas are the deadliest fruit
to walk the earth!
What are you talking about?
Bananas don't walk.
And they're not deadly.
They're healthy and full of vitamins.
They're deceitful and full of tricks!
Haven't you ever seen a cartoon, huh?
People and pants-wearing mice
are always slipping
and hurting themselves on vicious bananas.
Those things are terrifying!
Dad, you can't seriously be
afraid of a fruit.
I can, and I am!
[cha-ching]
Trillion Dollar Trinity, unite!
This outfit is so cool!
Yeah, check out these muscles.
If only the ladies at aquarobics
could see me now.
Darcy, you are now... The Shopper.
Hey, that's my nickname down at the mall.
Those credit cards can do serious damage
at your favorite stores and when thrown
at your least favorite criminals.
Give it a try.
[whooshing]
[impact]
Whoa, that just sliced through the cement!
Put your hand up.
[whoosh and slap]
Now put your other hand up.
It also picked up a cute skirt
for the fall season.
Best superpower ever!
And the third member
of the Trillion Dollar Trinity,
Captain Frugal!
Hey, that's my nickname
down at the 98¢ store.
What is his superpower?
Does he clip coupons
at the speed of light?
Captain Frugal,
he has an adding machine
that crunches numbers
and villains!
That's very cool.
So, Roly Poly Boy,
let's see your superpower.
I'd really rather not.
Come on, that outfit looks awesome.
What does it do?
Looks awesome. That's pretty much it.
Richie, the burglar's in
your room, stealing your stuff!
I knew I had a burglar.
Let's get him, Trillion Dollar Trinity!
What?
What's going on?
There's no way my doors
are malfunctioning.
The burglar must be messing with them.
The Shopper has just the thing
to get us out of here.
Huh. That was a huge letdown.
I was really hoping
for a new pair of pumps.
I mean, I was really pumped
to get us out of here.
That's it. We're doomed.
There's not a lot of air in here, and--
Uh-oh. I'm getting nervous!
[mechanical whirring]
[laughter]
It's not funny!
Oh, I gotta post a pic of this.
#imaballer.
Okay, that is funny. Tag me in that.
Then we have to get out of here!
I see you really committed
to the whole "trinity" thing,
considering you built a lair,
for the three of us,
with only one chair.
The leader always gets the chair.
Leader?
I don't consider rolling up into a ball
at the first sign of danger
a leadership quality.
I'm well aware I have
the worst superpower ever.
Let him be leader.
You don't want to take ownership
over this disaster.
This isn't a disaster.
You spent millions of dollars
to catch a burglar
who is currently robbing you blind
while we're trapped in a glorified closet.
That's a disaster in my book.
This isn't a closet.
This lair is equipped
with all the latest
crime-fighting technology,
like this computer has biometric readouts
of all of our vital signs
and high-def drone feeds
from around my property!
Great! So you can email
someone to get us out of here.
Yeah, no Wi-Fi. We're in a dead zone.
But wait, my engineers did install
this lower-tech communication system.
Hello!
If anyone can hear me, please help us!
Yeah, there's no way someone's
on the other end of that string.
Yeah, I have to agree
with captain fake muscles.
Coming to get you, Richie.
Stay on the line.
I'm transferring you to the cordless cup.
And that's why I'm the leader.
Mighty middle-aged dude
saves the day!
Aw, cool costumes!
You guys playing superheroes too?
These aren't costumes.
We have real superpowers.
Well, some of us do.
Me too-- Mighty Middle-aged Dude
has the ability to embarrass
his kids in any situation.
Here's Richie in the bathtub.
[laughter]
Doing a pretty good job in this situation!
Dad, you haven't seen anyone
sneaking around, have you?
I did see one guy dressed in
black with a big sack of stuff,
trying to head into the screening room.
His hands were full,
so I opened the door for him.
Come on, Trillion Dollar Trinity,
to the screening room!
Ooh! Ooh!
Can I come along?
Dad, I'm not sure this job
calls for Mighty Middle-aged Dude.
Oh, it's a job? In that case, I'm out.
[cha-ching]
Okay, dad, today's the day
you overcome your fear of bananas.
I've done some research,
and I think you could be cured
with a little hypnosis.
No way! I'm scared of hypnosis.
Do you even know what it means?
No, but I'm guessing
it has something to do with bananas.
All I'm gonna do is put you
into a deep sleep.
If it involves deep sleep, I'm in.
Okay, I'm gonna need you
to slowly say the alphabet
forwards and backwards.
Um...
Okay, fine,
I'm gonna need you
to focus on your breathing
and count down from 100.
Um...
Look at this watch.
Ooh, shiny!
So shiny.
[relaxed sigh]
Now, when I count to three,
your subconscious mind
with all its innermost thoughts and fears
will be let out.
One, two, three.
Cotton candy!
I like cotton candy!
I'm gonna need your subconscious
in a fully relaxed, happy place.
Hamburger. Ball pit. Hamburger pit!
Okay, let's talk about bananas.
Ooh, can't be trusted!
Slippery landmines!
And so many strings!
Why so many strings?
Bananas are your friends.
They are yellow and full of potassium.
And they are your friends.
Your friends. Your friends.
Mommy, I made a friend.
I made a friend, mommy.
Maybe the kids won't make fun
of me on the banana bus.
Banana bus?
Banana bus! No banana bus!
I'll walk home from school!
- Dad, it's okay.
- Mommy!
The kids are mean!
Wake up, dad! Wake up!
[snaps fingers]
Banana?
No!
[cha-ching]
I hope the burglar didn't get away.
How could he possibly
outrun us while we were
leisurely strolling down the hallway?
I would've strolled faster,
but I didn't want to run
the risk of blisters!
My podiatrist says I have
underdeveloped heel calluses.
Not the only part of you
that's underdeveloped.
If you're referring to my triceps,
Gertrude at aquarobics
promises a few more sessions
will do wonders for my bingo arms.
Guys, the trinity can't turn on itself.
We have to focus!
Wait.
My roly poly antennae
are picking up vibrations.
Either the burglar's near,
or a predatory hummingbird is approaching.
Spread out!
Hold it right there!
Nobody messes with
the Trillion Dollar Trinity!
Captain Frugal!
The Shopper!
And their fearless leader,
Roly Poly Boy!
[laughs]
Hey, don't laugh at our leader!
Okay, don't get nervous, roly.
Nervous? Why would I be nervous?
Why'd you put that thought
in my head, then--
Uh-oh.
[mechanical whirring]
There's no escape!
I'm gonna shop until you drop!
Darn, missed!
But scored an adorable pashmina!
What's happening?
- It sounds scary out there.
- It is!
The Shopper just spent 200 bucks
in five seconds!
Debit or credit? How about both?
[cards whooshing]
Darn!
Hey, hand over that tiara
and gladiator sandals!
You got him, Shopper!
Now it's time for Captain Frugal
to wrap things up!
See? Crime doesn't add up.
Is it safe to come out?
Yes, fearless leader.
Feel free to remove your head
from between your legs.
Whew!
That position is not easy on the back.
Ah!
Well, time to unmask this criminal.
[both] Irona?
Irona, why would you steal from me?
Yeah, how dare you take without asking?
I am terribly sorry, master Richie.
I am so ashamed of myself.
Why'd you do it?
Because,
while I love spending time with you guys,
I miss robot companionship.
I am never around my own kind.
But you know
you can always use my electronics
whenever you want.
Was that directed only at Irona,
and does your private jet
count as an electronic?
You're extremely generous
with me, master Richie.
But I do not miss electronics.
I miss robots.
I took these items
because I was building a robot
to keep me company,
someone who can relate to me.
Someone who I can share my
innermost lack of emotions with.
I always thought I was that guy.
I never thought I was that guy.
Again, I am very sorry
and deserve any punishment
that is coming my way.
Irona, I'm not punishing you.
I can replace my stuff.
Your happiness is more important
than any possessions.
Understood.
Thank you so much for understanding,
master Richie.
I will never let something
like this happen again.
So this robot,
is it making you feel better?
I have not brought it to life yet.
This battery was the last piece.
Well, let's fire it up!
Oh, I am so excited to finally
connect with one of my own!
Welcome to existence, my child.
Detect other robotic being in my presence.
Yes, it is me, your mommy!
Must destroy.
Must destroy!
Arming lasers.
Whoa, that thing's got
more mommy issues than I do!
Run!
Lasers? Why'd you give it lasers?
It was a laser pointer!
I thought it'd be fun
to tease your father
by making him chase it around the room.
[cha-ching]
Dad, I have the answer to your problem.
My back problem? My back hair problem?
My "backing into people
while driving" problem?
The banana thing.
Mm.
All we have to do is take a little ride
on the banana bus.
Kids, there's someone I want you to meet.
Go ahead, introduce yourself.
Hi. I'm Cliff.
Harper! Harper, guess what.
I'm not scared of bananas anymore!
I knew if the kids on
the banana bus were nice to you,
you'd overcome your fear.
And guess what. I even ate one.
Pfft. And I wasn't even scared.
I mean, I was a little scared,
but I did it.
I'm proud of you, dad.
I knew you'd come to see bananas
aren't dangerous
or out to get you.
Thanks for all your help.
I gotta go.
The kids from the bus
invited me to play kickball
with them at the playground.
Be home before the streetlights come on!
Dad, you forgot your jacket.
[sighs]
Ah!
What happened?
Evil fruit can't be trusted.
[cha-ching]
I'm not going out there.
This is over
The Shopper's credit card limit!
I'd go,
but I'm out of frugal catchphrases.
Then I guess there's only
one person who can save us.
It's roly poly time!
Richie, I don't want to see you get hurt!
It's too dangerous!
Murray, get out there.
No, this is my destiny.
Ah! Just let him roll.
[mechanical whirring]
Did that work?
What happened?
You did it, Roly Poly Boy!
You saved the day!
I did?
I mean, I did!
Roly poly power!
Master Richie,
thank you for killing my baby.
Any time, Irona.
I don't wanna see you lonely,
so I have a better idea.
[cha-ching]
Here you go, Irona.
I got you
a less dangerous robot companion.
My very own puppy!
[barking]
Aww!
Who is adowable?
I am adowable!
Don't make me hit you
with a rolled-up newspaper.
Well, today proves
the Trillion Dollar Trinity
does not rest until danger is defeated.
And now that it is,
I need a nap.
I have had a really long day.
[barks]