Good afternoon, boys.
We're not boys anymore, Irona.
We're men now.
We met the three hottest girls ever.
They had the mall cop ask us
to stop following them around.
But then we met the three girls
that actually talked to us.
Not only did they talk to us,
they gave us their phone numbers.
Show her, Murray.
Hurry up, we shouldn't expose
the ink to this much light.
Congratulations.
So are you going to call these girls?
Absolutely.
I've been thinking about it
the entire way home,
and I know exactly what I'm gonna say
when they answer the phone--
"Hello."
Good luck, men.
All right, let's call these ladies.
Hold on, hold on.
[sprays]
Okay, now let's do it.
[line trilling]
It's ringing.
I've never gotten this far!
Chuckie's Pizza. How can I help you?
They work in a pizza place.
Score!
Yes, hi. I'd like to speak
to the three beautiful teenage
girls you have working there.
Oh, why does every girl
give out our number
to losers they don't want to talk to?
I-I cannot answer that.
But are Vanessa, Vanessa,
and Vanessa there?
Hello?
Man, I did not see that coming.
I did think it was weird that
they wrote their number down
on the pizza-place napkin...
and that all the numbers matched.
- This stinks.
- Our lives are over.
We're never gonna meet girls
like that ever again.
[doorbell rings]
Hello.
Is Richie here?
We're staying in his guest
mansion and wanted to say hi.
[all] I'm Richie.
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
my dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
I forgot to mention you now
sponsor the Miss Tween pageant.
I figured it'd be a good investment.
I was right.
Hey, I'm Taylor.
Nice to meet you.
Do you happen to have
an adding machine?
My special talent
is doing corporate taxes,
and I wanted to practice.
I know this may sound crazy,
and I know we just met, but...
will you make me
the happiest boy in the world
and accept my adding machine?
A T-96?
Yes, I'd love to!
Hey, there, beautiful.
- My name is--
- I know who you are.
Oh, let me guess.
Bulldozah's son?
No.
T-Nice, the rapper.
Don't toy with me, girl.
Did my dad put you up to this?
Who's your dad?
Wow.
Looks like our friends
are really hitting it off.
Give it time.
It'll fall apart.
You're funny.
I'm Eliza.
Nice to meet you.
Can I offer you a water...
a private jet, a private island?
Sorry. I'm--
I'm just trying to impress you.
You don't need to try.
Come on, girls, we have a lot
of sequins and sashes to unpack.
- That went pretty well.
- Yeah, they seemed nice.
Not bad.
- Amazing!
- Sick!
Incredible!
Over my dead body!
That could be arranged!
Whoa, ladies, please.
I can't take any more conflict.
I just spent the last 20 minutes
getting yelled at by the gardener
for eating the flowers.
Well, Richie got two tickets
to meet Harry Styles
that he isn't using, and I am going.
No, Master Richie would want me to go
to reward me for all my hard work.
Or work.
Well, I need to go.
The president of Harvard's
daughter's best friend's
coffee barista's therapist's
dog walker's sister will be there.
I have to be there to network.
Guys, there are four of us.
We have two tickets.
We can all go if we cut them in half.
all: No!
You shouldn't use those scissors
without adult supervision.
Well, I am going.
I'm going.
I'm Tulip.
You all make compelling cases,
but if only two of you can go,
I think there is only one fair,
mature way to handle this.
Tag-team wrestling!
Welcome to Cliffmania!
Are those your fire-truck jammies?
No.
Oh, because I have the same ones.
Yeah, they're mine.
Please, T-Nice, will you rap for me?
I think you're really talented.
I love how some of your lyrics make sense.
Oh, you must be talking
about the ones I got from my dad's trash.
Look, D-Nice...
It's Denise.
Either way, you're too good to be true.
Would you like to go out tonight?
I d love to.
Ha! That was a test.
Now I know you're messing with me.
At the grocery store,
I combine the manufacturer's rebate
with the automatic club card savings.
That's 40% off right there.
But I go on Wednesdays,
which are double-savings days.
Boom! 80% off generic dryer sheets.
I do the exact same thing,
except I return those dryer sheets
to a different store for full price.
You can do that?
Not legally.
I love bad boys.
Well, then you wouldn't like me,
'cause I'm a bad man.
So, hey, I was wondering
if you'd like to go out with me tonight.
Like, on a date?
Yeah, but with less awkward pauses.
I can't.
Oh, do you have other plans?
No, I have a boyfriend.
We did it,
real dates with real girls
who aren't gonna call the mall cops on us!
It's like a fairy tale,
but we're the princesses.
Okay, I get what you're saying,
but don't ever say it like that again.
- [crying]
- Oh, look at Richie.
He's so excited, he's crying.
Eliza has a boyfriend.
Dang, you scored
the boyfriend label already?
You're moving at warp speed, bro.
No, Eliza has a boyfriend who's not me.
What? That's horrible.
I mean, good for her.
I'm sure he makes her very happy,
but horrible for you.
She said we could hang out as friends.
- [gasps]
- Ooh.
The "f" word.
Tough luck, Richie, but you
still have to come out tonight.
What are you talking about?
Guy code.
You have to come to keep the ratio right.
If you don't, things might get weird.
He's right. It's the law...
the man law...
the "maw."
See? Things are already pretty weird.
Our first tag team,
coming in at a combined weight
of 2 tons, 60 pounds,
the Iron Maid and Million-Dollar Girl!
[lively music]
♪ ♪
I don't know who Harper and
Tulip think they are,
but no one beats the Iron Maid
and Million-Dollar Girl
when it comes to Harry Styles tickets!
[gravelly voice] Oh, yeah!
They need to back down
before we lay the smack down!
Oh, yeah!
Tell 'em, Iron Maid.
I am going to sweep the floor with them.
[normal voice]
Although on floors like these,
I should really use a dust mop--
much gentler on the marble.
[gravelly voice] Oh, yeah!
Look!
It's the Positive Female Role Models!
[lively music]
♪ ♪
Rar!
I can't hear you!
Uh, Tulip, there's no one here.
Give me that!
Iron Maid, Million-Dollar Girl,
you want to meet Harry Styles?
You're going to have to come through this!
Whoo!
The verdict... is pain!
- Tulip, are you--
- You want some too?
- I don't.
- You're out of order!
Uh, Tulip?
Whoo!
Sorry I'm late.
My family was taking a lot of pictures.
What are you wearing?
Oh, this is what my dad wore
on his first date with my mom.
What is that smell?
Oh, that's my cologne.
I have my own fragrance.
It's called...
"T-Naughty."
Yeah, well, it smells terrible.
Sure does.
Tahj, maybe you should tone down...
everything.
Bro, somehow I managed to land
a real date with a real girl.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
I'm going all out.
What is that?
Carpet sample.
Yeah, we're redoing the basement,
but if D-Nice asks, this is all naturel.
Well, you might want to take the tag off.
Howdy, partners.
Are the little ladies here?
Murray, did you just get
mugged by the 1800s?
Taylor likes me because I'm a bad boy.
And who's badder than a cattle thief?
Okay, guys,
I think you're trying a bit too hard.
[both] How so?
Richie, no offense, but...
we're playing different games here.
[both] Whoa.
Oh, hello, ladies.
Hey. Wow. You almost look as good as I do.
What is that smell?
[scoffs] That's just T-Naughty
crawling up your nose,
making himself at home.
He'll leave when he's ready.
Murray...
is that you?
Yeah, but if the sheriff asks,
you haven't seen me.
Hey, uh, do you know if Eliza s coming?
She's on the phone with her boyfriend.
Wonderful.
Let's bowl.
This bad man's got to be in bed by 8:00.
Want to touch my mustache?
No.
What if I told you it was 100% yak hair?
Still no.
Sorry I took so long.
I had to vacuum my chest hair.
You can eat off of it now.
No, thank you.
Ooh.
Oh, it feels good to get off my feet.
You do realize
you're wearing ladies' heels?
I do now.
Do you know if Eliza is--
Dude! Middle of a conversation here.
So you were, uh,
saying something about a headache
and having to wake up early?
Eliza, I am so glad to see you...
in a platonic-friend way.
You haven't missed much.
Is Tahj wearing carpet?
And Murray's wearing a mustache.
So, yeah, I guess you missed a little.
I'm really glad to see you.
Thanks. I'm glad to see you too.
Well, my evening's been great.
I've thrown three gutter balls,
one of which came with the bumpers up,
and the rest of night,
I've been trying to avoid
looking at Murray's chaps.
How about you?
I broke up with my boyfriend.
Guys, I need your help.
Eliza broke up with her boyfriend.
What? Why?
She's never gonna do better than him.
Let me talk to her.
Murray, no!
This means her and I are on a date.
- What do I do?
- You're panicking, man.
Chicks can smell fear.
- You need some T-Naughty.
- Oh.
No, Tahj!
Don't worry.
The burning means it's working.
Don't listen to him, Richie.
She needs to think you're dangerous.
Tell her you only drink
seven glasses of water a day,
not the recommended eight.
You need a man-kover.
Your room, now.
Go get her, lover boy.
You're a bad, bad man.
[exhales deeply]
You really think Eliza's
gonna like me now?
No.
Now she will.
Woo!
Can someone stop her?
Sure can.
Aah!
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!
Now we just need to take out
Harper to get those tickets.
Oh, yeah!
The Iron Maid is about to go to work.
Dad, stop her.
Oh, I'm sorry-- I took an oath
not to show any favoritism in the ring.
Plunge her! Plunge her!
Going somewhere?
Yes, to the concert.
I am done with this madness.
Oh, the madness is just beginning.
Ooh, good one. Point Darcy.
What--what are you doing?
[cloth tearing]
Ooh.
You ripped my lab coat?
I borrowed this from my biology teacher.
You are going to pay...
in pain and in cash!
Ooh.
You look a little flushed.
What--what are you--
[grunting and screaming]
[chuckles]
Tulip!
I'm on my way.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
[metallic clang]
Ow.
[laughs]
You cannot hurt the Iron Maid.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I have just what the doctor ordered.
Clear!
[electricity buzzing]
Let's go.
One!
Two!
Oh, what comes after two?
Whoo!
Oh...
[groans softly]
Error. Error. Error.
Shoo!
[imitating guitar playing]
- Ha ha!
- So...
how was it?
Tell me all about Har...ry.
He is adorbs.
[sighs]
I'm sorry you guys couldn't make it.
I felt bad,
so I asked himto autograph this poster.
Who wants it?
It's on!
Ooh. Uh-oh.
[wincing in pain]
Interesting outfit, Richie.
Thanks.
I mean...
whatever.
Disco pirate don't care.
Richie, maybe you need some fresh air.
I know I do.
Your friend's cologne
smells like garbage fire.
[sighs]
We're gonna go walk the plank.
Oh, spritz for the road?
Or if you're going outside,
it also makes for
a great insect repellent.
I'll take my chances.
[chuckles]
Dangerous, Richie-- I like it.
Oh...
bring a sweater.
There's a chill in the air.
Oh, sorry about that, ladies.
How about we go get some ice cream?
Great idea. You stay here.
We'll go get it.
Huh. You see that?
Girls only run that fast
when they're in love.
See, Eliza? I'm dangerous.
That's just how I live.
See that wet-floor sign?
Watch this.
I wouldn't try that if I were you.
My knees are soaked.
Why are you acting like this?
What are you talking about?
That's just how I live my life.
[chuckles]
That's the fourth wet-floor
sign you've walked me past.
We could eat,
and then go swimming right away.
- Richie...
- You're right.
There's dangerous,
and there's just stupid.
Richie, I liked you before,
when you were just being yourself.
Really?
Yeah.
Why'd you change?
I guess I'm just insecure.
[sighs]
My first girlfriend did leave me
for a vacuum cleaner.
What?
The point is,
I got nervous when I found out
you didn't have a boyfriend,
because...
I like you.
Well, you have nothing
to be nervous about,
because I like you too.
Eliza, we're leaving.
- Guys, Richie and I were just--
- You don't understand.
Those guys are total losers.
They are so into us.
Obviously, dog.
I just feel bad for Richie.
He doesn't have our swag.
Agreed.
Listen... I like Richie.
Can't you guys just hang in
there for a few more minutes?
No way.
Absolutely not.
I know they're losers,
but I want to spend time with Richie.
Whoa. Losers?
Well, yeah, what would you call them?
My friends.
Look, I'm sorry, Eliza,
but I can't be with someone
who doesn't respect them.
You're a beautiful, cool girl,
but I will not sacrifice my dignity.
[grunts]
Oh!
Ow! I skinned my knee!
Irona, come quick!
Tahj, wake up. I hear someone coming.
It might be our ladies.
Oh, no. I smell my own fear.
Oh, it's just you.
Have you seen Denise and Taylor?
Actually, they went home.
What? What happened?
They were so into us.
They realized they...
couldn't focus on the pageant
being around you guys...
something about being too manly.
Oh, yeah, I get it.
Sometimes I have trouble
focusing on pageants.
Some girls just can't handle
this much Murray.
Oh, so where's Eliza?
Did she realize she made a huge mistake
and get back together with her ex?
Pretty much.
So...
should we hit the mall,
go find some more ladies?
I don't know.
Yeah, that harsh mall lighting
will make this mustache look stupid.