(LAUGHTER, CHATTER)
(CHATTER STOPS)
You're wondering why
I brought you all here.
After all, we just had a feast.
Since when does old Walder
give us two feasts
in a single fortnight?
- (MEN LAUGH)
- (WALDER CHUCKLES)
Well, it's no good being
Lord of the Riverlands
if you can't celebrate
with your family.
That's what I say!
- (ALL CHEERING)
- Yes!
(SNAPS FINGERS)
I've gathered every Frey
who means a damn thing
so I can tell you my plans
for this great house
now that winter has come.
But first, a toast!
No more of that
Dornish horse piss!
This is the finest Arbor gold!
Proper wine for proper heroes!
(ALL CHEERING)
Stand together!
All:
Not you.
I'm not wasting good wine
on a damn woman.
Maybe I'm not
the most pleasant man.
I'll admit it.
But I'm proud of you lot.
You're my family,
the men who helped me
slaughter the Starks
at the Red Wedding.
- (CHEERING)
- WALDER: Yes, yes.
Cheer.
Brave men, all of you.
Butchered a woman
pregnant with her babe.
Cut the throat
of a mother of five.
Slaughtered your guests
after inviting them
into your home.
But you didn't slaughter
every one of the Starks.
- (MEN GROANING)
- No, no, that was your mistake.
You should have ripped them
all out, root and stem.
(ALL COUGHING,
CHOKING)
Leave one wolf alive
and the sheep are never safe.
(ALL GASPING,
GROANING)
When people ask you
what happened here...
tell them the North remembers.
Tell them winter came
for House Frey.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
- Synced and corrected by SOMNATH YADAV -
-- Join me on instagram @somnath66 -
(WIND HOWLING)
(GATE OPENS)
You wildlings?
I'm Meera Reed,
daughter of Howland Reed.
This is Brandon Stark,
son of Ned Stark.
How do I know that's true?
You were at
the Fist of the First Men.
You were at Hardhome.
You've seen
the Army of the Dead.
You've seen the Night King.
He's coming for us.
For all of us.
Okay, come on.
Let's get them inside.
(GATE RUMBLING)
JON: I want every northern
maester to scour their records
for any mention of dragonglass.
Dragonglass kills white walkers.
It's more valuable
to us now than gold.
We need to find it,
we need to mine it,
we need to make weapons from it.
Everyone aged 10 to 60
will drill daily with spears,
pikes, bow and arrow.
It's about time we taught these
boys of summer how to fight.
- (LAUGHTER)
- Not just the boys.
We can't defend the North
if only half the population is fighting.
You expect me to put a spear
in my granddaughter's hand?
I don't plan on knitting by the
fire while men fight for me.
I might be small, Lord Glover,
and I might be a girl,
but I am every bit as much
a Northerner as you.
Indeed you are, my lady.
No one has questioned...
And I don't need your
permission to defend the North.
We'll begin training every man,
woman, boy, and girl on Bear Island.
MEN: Aye!
(POUNDING TABLES)
While we're
preparing for attack,
we need to shore up
our defenses.
The only thing standing between us and
the Army of the Dead is the Wall,
and the Wall hasn't been
properly manned in centuries.
I'm not the king
of the Free Folk.
But if we're going to survive
this winter together...
(GRUNTS)
You want us to man
the castles for you?
- (MEN MURMURING)
- JON: Aye.
Last time we saw the Night
King was at Hardhome.
The closest castle to Hardhome
is Eastwatch-by-the-Sea.
Then that's where I'll go.
Looks like we're
the Night's Watch now.
(CHATTER)
If they breach the Wall,
the first two castles
in their path
are Last Hearth and Karhold.
The Umbers and the Karstarks
betrayed the North.
Their castles
should be torn down
with not a stone left standing.
The castles committed no crimes.
And we need every fortress
we have for the war to come.
We should give the Last Hearth
and Karhold to new families,
loyal families who supported
us against Ramsay.
Men:
Aye!
The Umbers and the Karstarks
have fought beside
the Starks for centuries.
They've kept faith for
generation after generation.
And then they broke faith.
I'm not going to strip these
families of their ancestral homes
because of the crimes
of a few reckless sons.
SANSA: So there's no
punishment for treason
and no reward for loyalty?
The punishment
for treason is death.
Smalljon Umber died
on the field of battle.
Harald Karstark died
They died fighting for Ramsay.
Give the castles to the families
of the men who died
fighting for you.
(MEN CHATTERING,
POUNDING TABLES)
When I was Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch...
I executed men who betrayed me.
I executed men who
refused to follow orders.
My father always said,
"The man who passes the sentence
should swing the sword,"
and I have tried
to live by those words.
But I will not punish a son
for his father's sins,
and I will not take
a family home away
from a family it has
belonged to for centuries.
That is my decision,
and my decision is final.
Ned Umber.
Alys Karstark.
For centuries,
our families fought
side by side on the battlefield.
I ask you to pledge your loyalty
once again to House Stark,
to serve as our bannermen
and come to our aid
whenever called upon.
Stand.
Yesterday's wars
don't matter anymore.
The North needs
to band together,
all the living north.
Will you stand beside me,
Ned and Alys,
now and always?
Both:
Now and always!
(MEN CHEERING,
POUNDING TABLES)
JON: You are my sister,
but I am king now.
Will you start wearing a crown?
When you question my decisions
in front of the other lords
and ladies, you undermine me.
So I can't question
your decisions anymore?
Of course you can, but...
Joffrey never let anyone
question his authority.
You think he was a good king?
Do you think I'm Joffrey?
You're as far from Joffrey
as anyone I've ever met.
Thank you.
You're good at this, you know.
- At what?
- At ruling.
(SIGHS)
No.
You are.
They respect you,
they really do,
- but you have to...
- (CHUCKLES)
Why are you laughing?
What did father used to say?
Everything before the
word "but" is horse shit.
He never said that to me.
No. No, he never cursed
in front of his girls.
SANSA: Because he was
trying to protect us.
He never wanted us to see
how dirty the world really is,
but Father couldn't protect
me and neither can you.
Stop trying.
All right, I'll stop
trying to protect you
and you stop trying
to undermine me.
I'm not trying to undermine you!
You have to be
smarter than Father.
You need to be
smarter than Robb.
I loved them, I miss them,
but they made stupid mistakes,
and they both
lost their heads for it.
And how should I be smarter?
By listening to you?
Would that be so terrible?
A raven from King's Landing, Your Grace.
"Cersei of House Lannister,
First of Her Name,
Queen of the Andals
and the First Men,
Protector of
the Seven Kingdoms..."
What does she want?
(SIGHS)
Come to King's Landing.
Bend the knee or suffer
the fate of all traitors.
You've been so consumed
with the enemy to the north,
you've forgotten about
the one to the south.
I'm consumed with the Night
King because I've seen him.
And believe me, you'd think
of little else if you had, too.
We still have a wall between
us and the Night King.
There's nothing
between us and Cersei.
There's a thousand miles
Winter is here. The Lannisters
are a southern army.
They've never ranged
this far north.
You're the military man,
but I know her.
If you're her enemy, she'll never
stop until she's destroyed you.
Everyone who's ever crossed her,
she's found a way to murder.
You almost sound
as if you admire her.
I learned a great deal from her.
What is this?
It's what we've been
waiting for our whole lives.
It's what Father trained us for,
whether he knew it or not.
He knew it.
Made me memorize
every damn city, town,
lake, forest, and mountain.
It's ours now.
We just have to take it.
You've been quiet
since you came home.
Are you angry with me?
No, not angry.
Are you afraid of me?
Should I be?
Daenerys Targaryen has chosen
Tyrion to be her Hand.
Right now, they're sailing
across the Narrow Sea,
hoping to take back
her father's throne.
Our little brother,
the one you love so much,
the one you set free,
the one who murdered our
father and our first-born son,
now he stands beside our enemies
and gives them counsel.
He's out there somewhere
at the head of an armada.
Where will they land?
Dragonstone.
They have deep-water
ports for the ships.
Stannis left
the castle unoccupied,
and that's where she was born.
Enemies to the east.
Enemies to the south...
Ellaria Sand
and her brood of bitches.
Enemies to the west...
Olenna, the old cunt.
Another traitor.
Enemies to the north.
Ned Stark's bastard has been
named King in the North
and that murdering whore
Sansa stands beside him.
Enemies everywhere.
We're surrounded by traitors.
You're in command
of the Lannister army now.
- How do we proceed?
- Winter is here.
We can't win a war if we can't
feed our men and our horses.
The Tyrells have the grain,
the Tyrells have the livestock.
Will the Tyrell bannermen
stand alongside
a Dothraki horde
and Unsullied slave soldiers?
If they think Daenerys will win.
No one wants to fight
on the losing side.
Right now, we look like the losing side.
I'm the Queen
of the Seven Kingdoms.
Three kingdoms, at best.
I'm not sure you understand
how much danger we're in.
I understand we're
in a war for survival.
I understand whoever loses dies.
I understand whoever wins
could launch a dynasty
that lasts a thousand years.
A dynasty for whom?
Our children are dead.
We're the last of us.
A dynasty for us, then.
We never talked about Tommen.
There's nothing to say.
Our baby boy killed himself.
He betrayed me.
He betrayed us both.
Should we spend our days
mourning the dead...
Mother, father,
and all our children?
- Cersei...
- I loved them. I did.
But they're ashes now and
we're still flesh and blood.
We're the last Lannisters,
the last ones who count.
Even Lannisters can't
survive without allies.
Where are our allies now?
You saw what happened to
Walder Frey and his family.
I heard.
- How could we ever trust a man like that?
- We couldn't.
He was a useless, old coward,
but the Freys supported us.
Now they're all dead.
Whoever killed them
is no friend of ours.
We need allies.
Stronger, better allies.
We can't win this war alone.
You think I listened to Father for
40 years and learned nothing?
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
Jaime:
The Greyjoys?
You invited the Greyjoys
to King's Landing?
- Not all of them.
- Well, it looks like all of them.
I invited Euron Greyjoy,
the new King
of the Iron Islands.
You said yourself we needed
stronger, better allies.
- There you are.
- How are they better allies?
How are they different
from the Freys?
They both broke their promises
and murdered their former friends
as soon as it suited them.
So does everyone
when it suits them.
Unlike the Freys,
they have ships.
- And they're good at killing.
- They're not good at anything.
I know the ironborn. They're
bitter, angry little people.
All they know how to do is steal things
they can't build or grow themselves.
Euron Greyjoy didn't
come here for that.
Oh, what did
he come here for, then?
A queen.
EURON: The moment I was chosen
Lord of the Iron Islands,
they turned on me.
(CHUCKLES)
Their own uncle.
They stole
my best ships and ran.
Sailed them
right across the world
and gave them
to the Dragon Queen
so she could bring her
armies here to attack you.
It's nothing compared
to the treason you suffered
at the hands of a family
member, from what I hear.
But still, it bothers me.
Murdering them would
make me feel a lot better.
And since it appears that all
our treasonous family members
are fighting for the same side,
I thought we rightful monarchs
could murder them together.
You're not a rightful
monarch, though, are you?
The Greyjoys rebelled against the
throne for the right to be monarchs,
but as I recall,
you were soundly defeated.
Come to mention it,
weren't you the one
who started that rebellion
by sailing to Casterly Rock
and burning the Lannister fleet?
You certainly caught us there.
Very smart move on your part.
Of course, we all made it
to the Iron Islands anyway.
I was there.
I remember very well.
I saw you.
I heard so much talk.
The best in the world.
No one can stop him.
I didn't believe it,
to be honest.
But I must say when you
rushed through the breach
and started
cutting people down...
it was glorious.
Like a dance.
The people I was cutting
down were your own kin.
The place was getting crowded.
I enjoyed watching it.
I truly did.
And I enjoyed killing Greyjoys.
A good thing for me.
If you hadn't crushed us, I
wouldn't have gone into exile.
If I hadn't done that,
I wouldn't be the greatest
captain on the 14 seas.
If not the most humble.
You're not humble.
You're the queen
of a great nation.
You don't care about
the Iron Islands.
They're nothing but rocks
and bird shit and...
And a lot of very
unattractive people.
The Iron Fleet,
on the other hand,
that's something else entirely.
It's the greatest armada
Westeros has ever seen.
With the Iron Fleet,
you own the seas.
You can defeat
the invaders of the east
and the pretenders
of the north and south.
What do you want in return?
Ever since I was a little boy,
I wanted to grow up and marry
the most beautiful woman
in the world.
So here I am,
with a thousand ships
and two good hands.
I decline your proposal.
Why?
You're not trustworthy.
You've broken promises
to allies before
and murdered them
at the nearest opportunity.
You murdered your own brother.
You should try it.
Feels wonderful.
(LAUGHS)
I don't expect you
to trust me outright.
You need proof
of my honest intentions.
In my experience,
the surest way to a woman's
heart is with a gift.
A priceless gift.
I won't return to King's Landing
until I have that for you.
(LABORED BREATHING)
- (MAN BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (MEN COUGHING)
(FARTS, GROANS)
(GAGGING)
- (FLIES BUZZING)
- (COUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(CHATTER)
(GAGGING)
(SIGHS)
(GAGS)
(SCRAPING)
(EXHALES)
(GAGS)
(COUGHS)
(GATE RATTLES)
(CHAIN RATTLING)
(GATE CLOSES)
Ah, Maester Weyland.
(GRUNTS) A drinker's
liver if ever I saw one.
Weigh that.
The triumph
of transitory pleasures.
Mankind's curse.
Archmaester, I was wondering...
What's the weight?
Um, 147.
I was wondering if you had
considered my proposition.
I don't remember
your proposition.
I asked you if, in light of
what I've seen in the North,
if I could have access to the
restricted area of the library.
That area is reserved
for maesters.
- Are you a maester?
- No.
Not a very strong
proposition, is it?
Archmaester, with respect,
I've seen them...
The Army of the Dead.
The white walkers.
I was sent here to learn
how to defeat them,
but everyone in the Citadel,
those who will even talk to me,
they all doubt the walkers ever
existed in the first place.
Everyone in the Citadel
doubts everything.
It's their job.
But the tales of the Long Night
can't be pure fabrication.
Too many similarities
from unconnected sources.
Sources in the restricted area?
The very same.
And the simplest explanation
for your grating obsession
with the white walkers
is that you're telling the truth
and that you saw
what you say you saw.
So, you believe me.
I do.
You'll finish
weighing that heart?
That makes you the only person
south of the Twins who does.
We're not like the people
south of the Twins.
And we're not like the
people north of the Twins.
In the Citadel, we lead different
lives for different reasons.
We are this world's memory,
Samwell Tarly.
Without us, men would be
little better than dogs.
Don't remember
any meal but the last,
can't see forward
to any but the next.
And every time you leave the
house and shut the door,
they howl like
you're gone forever.
When Robert's Rebellion
was raging,
people thought the end was near.
The end of the Targaryen dynasty.
"How will we survive?"
When Aegon Targaryen
turned his eye westward
and flew his dragons
to Blackwater Rush...
"The end is near!
How will we survive?"
And thousands of years before
that, during the Long Night,
we can forgive them for
thinking it truly was the end.
But it wasn't.
None of it was.
The Wall has stood
through it all.
And every winter
that ever came has ended.
Be a good lad.
Clean this up.
(MEN SNORING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- Nope.
- (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
- Nope.
- (GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
You're a lucky man.
LITTLEFINGER: I've heard she
beat the Hound in single combat.
She's a very impressive woman.
What do you want, Lord Baelish?
I want you to be happy.
I want you to be safe.
I am safe.
I'm at home,
surrounded by friends.
I have Brienne to protect me
from anyone who would harm me.
What about happy?
Why aren't you happy?
What do you want
that you do not have?
At the moment, peace and quiet.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
No need to seize the
last word, Lord Baelish.
I'll assume it was
something clever.
Littlefinger:
My lady.
Why is he still here?
(SIGHS)
We need his men.
Without the Vale, Ramsay Bolton
would still hold this castle.
Littlefinger saved us.
Brienne:
He wants something.
I know exactly what he wants.
(BIRD SCREECHING)
MAN: ♪ He rode through the
streets of the city ♪
♪ Down from
his hill on high ♪
♪ O'er the winds and the steps
and the cobbles ♪
♪ He rode
to a woman's sigh ♪
♪ For she was
his secret treasure ♪
♪ She was his shame
and his bliss ♪
♪ And a chain and a keep
are nothing ♪
♪ Compared to
a woman's kiss ♪
MEN: ♪ For hands of
gold are always cold ♪
♪ But a woman's hands
are warm ♪
♪ For hands of gold
are always cold ♪
- ♪ But a woman's hands are... ♪
- (HORSE NICKERS)
That's a pretty song.
I've never heard it before.
It's a new one.
MAN #2: Are you hungry?
We've got some rabbit.
I don't want to steal your food.
You're not stealing,
we're offering.
Come on, it's gonna be a cold night.
You heading south?
King's Landing.
- Poor girl.
- (MEN CHUCKLING)
Not so bad, is it?
Depends on your taste, I guess.
If you like your streets covered in shit
and pig's blood, it's the town for you.
(MEN CHUCKLE)
MAN #2: All my life, I
wanted to see the Red Keep,
the Sept of Baelor,
the Dragonpit.
Then when I finally make it,
they wouldn't let me within
a mile of the Red Keep,
the Sept of Baelor's
blown to hell,
and the Dragonpit
is a damn ruin.
- (MEN LAUGH)
- The people who live there,
they'd skin you alive if they could
make two coppers off your hide.
Worst place in the world.
What are you doing
in the Riverlands?
There's been some trouble with
the Freys up at the Twins,
so we're part of the army that's
been sent to keep the peace.
Here you go.
Guests first.
Oh, no, I couldn't.
You don't have enough.
My mother always told me
to be kind to strangers.
Strangers will be kind to you.
You're a long way from home.
I'm sure you've had
some adventures, though.
Yeah, endless adventures.
They'll be singing about
us for a thousand years.
(MEN LAUGH)
The truth is when we left home,
we couldn't wait to get away.
But now we've been gone a while,
we can't wait to get home.
I just think about my dad out
there on his boat all alone.
I ought to be
out there with him.
My wife just had our first baby.
- Boy or girl?
- Oh, who knows?
You think soldiers get
ravens with news from home?
(MEN LAUGH)
- I hope it's a girl.
- Why?
Girls take care of their papas
when their papas grow old.
Boys just go off to fight
in someone else's wars.
MAN #2: Are you old enough to drink?
(LAUGHING)
It's blackberry wine.
I made it myself.
It's really good.
So, why is a nice girl on her
own heading to King's Landing?
I'm going to kill the queen.
(WIND HOWLING)
THOROS: Bad night to be outdoors.
THE HOUND: You've got real
powerful magic to figure that out.
Did the Lord of Light
whisper that in your ear?
"It's snowing, Thoros.
It's windy.
It's gonna be
a cold night."
You're a grouchy old bear,
aren't you, Clegane?
You want some rum?
Don't like that shit.
It's too sweet.
Why are you always
in such a foul mood?
Experience.
This seems like a good
place to spend the night.
These people don't want us here.
BERIC: Seems deserted to me.
No livestock.
No smoke coming
from the chimney.
I don't like the look of it.
For a big, hard man,
you scare easy.
I'll tell you
what doesn't scare me...
Bald cocksuckers like you.
You think you're fooling
anyone with that top knot?
Bald cunt.
Come on.
Maybe they've got
some ale hidden away.
They don't.
(DISTANT MEN CHATTERING)
See if there's a larder.
They always leave
something behind.
(BLOWS)
(DISTANT CHATTER
CONTINUES)
How do you think
it ended for them?
With death.
Girl died in her father's arms.
Both of them covered in blood
and a knife at their feet.
I'd say they were starving.
And rather than
let his little girl suffer,
he ended it for both of them.
Doesn't matter now.
No, doesn't matter now.
(GRUNTS, SIGHS)
I've known you
a long time, Dondarrion.
Aye.
I think the first time we met
was at that tournament...
And I always thought
you were dull as dirt.
(CHUCKLES)
You're not bad.
I don't hate you.
Don't like you,
but you're not bad.
Thank you, Clegane.
That warms the heart.
But there's nothing
special about you.
You're right about that.
So why does the Lord of Light
keep bringing you back?
I've met better men than you,
and they've been hanged from
crossbeams, or beheaded,
or just shat themselves to
death in a field somewhere.
None of them came back.
So, why you?
You think I don't
ask myself that?
Every hour of every day?
Why am I here?
What am I supposed to do?
What does the Lord see in me?
And?
I don't know.
I don't understand our Lord.
Your Lord.
I don't know
what He wants from me.
I only know that
He wants me alive.
If he's so all-powerful, why doesn't he
just tell you what the fuck he wants?
Thoros:
Clegane.
Come over here.
Don't worry.
The fire won't bite.
I want to show you something.
It's my fucking luck I end up
with a band of fire worshippers.
Aye.
Almost seems like
divine justice.
There's no divine justice,
you dumb cunt.
If there was, you'd be dead...
and that girl would be alive.
- What do you want?
- Look into the flames.
I don't want to look
in the damn flames.
You saw me bring him back from
the dead after you cut him down.
Don't you want to know
what gave me the power?
I keep asking and no
one wants to tell me.
We can't tell you.
Only the fire can tell you.
What do you see?
Logs burning.
Keep looking.
What do you see?
Ice.
A wall of ice.
The Wall.
What else?
It's where the Wall
meets the sea.
There's a castle there.
There's a mountain.
Looks like an arrowhead.
The dead are marching past.
Thousands of them.
Do you believe me now, Clegane?
Do you believe
we're here for a reason?
(SHOVEL SCRAPING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (SHOVEL SCRAPING)
What the hell
are you doing, Clegane?
Burying the dead.
You knew these people.
Not really.
We ask the Father
to judge us with mercy.
We ask the Mother to...
Fuck it, I don't
remember the rest.
I'm sorry you're dead.
You deserved better.
Both of you.
(HORSE TROTTING,
NICKERS)
(DOG BARKING)
(CHATTER)
(LITTLE SAM COOS)
Gilly:
Hey.
(GILLY LAUGHS)
(LITTLE SAM GRUNTS)
Mom.
You should really sleep, Sam.
The dead don't.
( LITTLE SAM BABBLING)
"Legends of the Long Night."
The Targaryens used dragonglass
to decorate their weapons
without even knowing what
the First Men used it for.
(SIGHS)
What is it?
It's a map of Dragonstone.
The Targaryens built
their first stronghold there
when they invaded Westeros.
That's dragonglass?
A mountain of it.
Beneath the ground.
Stannis told me,
but I didn't think...
This is important.
Jon needs to know.
(MAN COUGHING)
(MAN VOMITING,
COUGHING)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
Jorah:
Has she come yet?
Who?
The Dragon Queen.
Daenerys Stormborn.
Haven't heard anything.
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
(SCREECHING)
Shall we begin?
- Synced and corrected by SOMNATH YADAV -
-- Join me on instagram @somnath66 -