- Hey.
- Hi.
What's going on?
How was your day?
'Fine, I'm just bummed about
Audrina.'
I mean, I'm done yelling.
I'm done being upset about it.
It's really unfortunate
when somebody you consider
to be your best friend
questions you in that way.
I think that
that's what she doesn't get.
She just, like, acted
like it was no big deal.
'Because it was about Justin'
'somebody she cares
so much about.'
And it felt like
she cared more about him
than in you in this situation.
Considering how
he's treated her...
The way he's treated her over
the past few years is the reason
why she believed this.
It's a hard situation.
But what would you do? Like...
Truly, like, if somebody
questions you in that way
you will always know
that they don't trust you.
- Yeah, that's...
- 'Completely.'
That's the thing for me.
It's about the trust.
Well, I mean, what would it
take for you to forgive her?
For her to actually be sorry.
♪ It's not right ♪
♪ We're so wrong ♪
♪ For another while
I've been trying to carry on ♪
♪ I'm so tired ♪
♪ It's too strong ♪
♪ The will to get away from you
and what's been going on ♪♪
(Audrina)
'Did you end up
doing anything this week?'
- No.
- I wish you went with me.
What, uh, what happened?
'We went to Winston's,
that little bar.'
- But Lauren was there.
- Did you talk to her?
Well, obviously
I had to do something.
She was there with Lo.
So I went up there
and I was like
"Okay, we need to talk
about this whole situation."
What'd she say?
She just kept saying
that I hurt her
I humiliated her.
It wasn't even a conversation,
Chiara.
It was like a scream fest.
Like, I would start talking,
she would yell over me
I would try to yell over her
and it just escalates
so I just sat back
and let her do what she wanted
and say what she wanted.
It's just sad, because there's
a history there, you know.
I've never had a conversation
with anyone like that, ever.
And then I've got a hold
of Justin, finally
and I went and met him
at Cobras and Matadors.
What was his excuse
for not reaching out to you?
He didn't bring his phone
charger, blah, blah, blah.
And I was like,
"Why didn't you text me back
or call me back
when you did get 'em?"
He said, "Because when I did get
'em, beyond the nice ones, like
"I just read all your * * *
ones that were hurtful.
Like, those things you said to
me, I would never say to you."
I'm like, "Well, I was upset,
I was hurt.
- 'Like, what was I..."'
- Nobody was answering you.
And he's like, "Audrina, like,
you should know, of all people
like, I've known you forever.
I wouldn't do that."
He's like, "You've made me just
not even wanna talk to you."
'And then he just walked out and
I haven't talked to him since.'
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
So now you're pretty convinced
and you don't think it happened?
No.
It's almost like I feel better,
but yet at the same time
I don't because it costed
my friendship with Lauren.
So what do I do now?
I just want all this to, like,
be gone and just disappear
and then all go back
to how it was.
♪ On and on and on oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ On and on and on ♪
♪ The waves crashed on
and on and on oh-oh-oh ♪♪
[knock on door]
It's open.
Well, that's safe.
- Hi.
What's up?
You decorate this place
pretty janky.
Like, this should be
all clear and nice.
You got it like it's a bathroom.
Oh, my God, Spencer.
So Heidi and I are gonna
go visit our nana.
Nana the great,
in Huntington Beach.
And, uh, Heidi had suggested
I invite you.
- To go to Huntington Beach?
- To visit Nana.
I have something
called school and work.
If you guys go on a weekend,
maybe I can go.
Can't she come here?
What kind of person doesn't
check in with their nana?
And I go to school
three times a week.
You can't pick up
the phone once a month
and call her
and check in with her?
- I can, but like...
- You don't though.
All she cares about
is how you treat her.
Well, it sounds like you've got
her wrapped around your finger.
Sounds like I'm giving you
an opportunity
to go make good with your nana.
I don't know if I wanna go and,
like, listen to you, like lie
and, like, say
how great you are and...
Well, if you wanna roll,
we're leaving tomorrow.
I'm out of here.
- Spencer.
- 'I'm not trying to be mean.'
Like, you should really
make peace with your nana.
She's 84 years old.
♪ To hear you speak to me ♪
♪ Back and forth ♪
♪ The waves keep crashing ♪
♪ Hold on my head
I keep on sinking ♪♪
(Brody)
You need to get the heat
working in this thing.
(Lauren)
'It's like 100 degrees out.
You want the heat on?'
(Brody)
'Yeah, outside. In here,
it's like 50 degrees.'
[sighs]
So I have something
to talk about.
- What?
- Why you banging Justin Bobby?
Honestly, it's not funny.
'That's a crazy * * *
I've heard my entire life.'
I'm just, I'm so angry.
It's disgusting
and it's embarrassing for other
people to, like,
ask me about that.
It is, but sometimes, it's not
about standing up for yourself...
You're gonna let people say
things like that about you
and not even defend yourself?
[sighs]
- You know what?
- What?
That's not the kind of person
you want in your life.
- I know.
- Plain and simple.
You shouldn't have any dislike
towards Audrina at all.
'You know, just go about your
life and leave people like that'
that are constant drama
and constant, like
leave them to do
their own thing.
It's just lame, honestly.
It's kind of like one
of those lose-lose situations.
I don't think
it's a lose-lose.
I think it's a
win-win situation.
How?
'Cause you don't need somebody
like that in your life.
Yeah, but, like, where did she,
like, where did she turn?
- Everybody changes.
- Yeah, I know, I know that.
Some change for the bad.
Some change for the good.
'You gotta let her go
as a friend.'
I've already done that.
No, you haven't.
♪ Lost in the moment ♪
♪ We almost collide ♪
♪ Explosions of light
in your eyes ♪
♪ I need you on ♪♪
(Audrina)
Had any good ideas?
Yeah, there's a lot of,
like, this magazine
has called the most
romantic rooms ever.
- That's cool.
- 'Yeah.'
Well, not bedrooms.
It's just rooms.
Cool.
So Justin still
isn't talking to me.
Just for him to not even
call me back or text me.
'It's just
he's very good at, like'
manipulating and kind of
turning it back on me.
It's like he likes
seeing you hurt.
I know.
This is the worst of all.
Everything that we've been
through, you know?
Because it involves Lauren.
Yeah, it's not
another random girl.
Random girls don't matter.
I don't know them.
Lauren is, like, someone
that I know and care about.
So it's like I understand why
Lauren is upset because I...
Why would I even
think that of her?
Do you think I should
apologize to Lauren?
- You do, huh?
- 'If you, I don't know if...'
If you really believe that she
didn't do it and she's genuine
about it, like she's not gonna
forgive you for being the victim
until you apologize to her.
I'm kind of nervous.
I don't know why.
'Cause she's all upset
that you accused her of it.
It's just the... Well, the whole
situation just sucks.
♪ Let go ♪
♪ Of everything you know ♪
♪ Of everyone
you thought you knew ♪
♪ 'Cause they had their fun
and washed their hands off me ♪♪
So you didn't hit up the tanning
salon before you saw Nana today?
Oh, my God. No, I hit up
a store to get a nice outfit.
That's your nice outfit
to visit your nana?
For me.
Queen Nana!
Here, Nana, this flower
is from Heidi and I.
- Thank you. What a surprise!
- 'We got you a flower!'
- Oh, thank you so much.
- Hi, Nana.
- It's so good to see you guys.
- Hi.
You remember Stephanie, right?
Hi, sweetheart.
Long time no see. How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- I'm good, I'm good.
- It has been a long time.
- Come on in.
What, you haven't seen
Nana in five years?
This is the first time
you've called?
- Did we see Nana last week?
- Yeah.
- We see Nana all the time.
- Yep.
This is our,
the love our my life.
(Heidi)
Oh, look at all these photos!
- Aren't they wonderful?
- Look at this one, Nana.
(Heidi)
'Oh, the cutest little boy
in the entire world.'
(Spencer)
'You know I can get you frames'
'that only have,
like, one heart'
'and we can just have
one like that.'
(Nana)
Are you thirsty? I have some
lemonade and some and cookies.
I don't think Stephanie's ever
had your lemonade and cookies.
- You take Heidi outside then.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm good. Thank you.
- Okay.
How lovely out here.
My favorite part of coming.
- 'I know.'
- Besides you, of course.
I'll put 'em down right here.
- Alright.
- That would be nice.
Those look good.
So, Stephanie,
what's new with you?
I haven't seen you in so long.
- It hasn't been that long.
- 'How have you been doing?'
Stephanie, not knowing
what family is and loyalty
she decided to become
friends with the person
that was talking mean
about poor, sweet Heidi
'for over a year,
and Stephanie decided to go'
be best friends
with this girl.
- Oh, dear.
- Okay.
Nana doesn't know
the whole story.
Why does this remind me
of years back where you two
'were fighting then
and now you're still doing it?'
I don't remember ever
fighting with Spencer.
I remember playing, like,
Nerf guns.
(Nana)
'I want you to get along
and to be happy, you know?'
Everything is a, is such a nice
time when people are happy.
You know, I wish
I had had a brother
when I was young who would
have been protective of me.
You can trust him
and you can rely on him
and he will always
be there for you.
'I'm just happy
that I got to see you'
and I hope that, uh, our visits
will become more frequent.
(Spencer)
'Speaking of that, Stephanie,
maybe you could'
start visiting more often.
Whenever, whenever
I'm not at school.
Maybe we could get together
tomorrow and...
Stephanie's got her day free.
Of course, she'll go.
Just you and I.
♪ It's a bittersweet life ♪
♪ And it's leaving me a-okay ♪
♪ Bittersweet life ♪
♪ I have loved
and lost my heart ♪
♪ All along the way ♪♪
Do you wanna check and see
if these are checked in yet?
Thanks.
Will you update me
with the boy situation?
'Do you, like, talk to him
on the phone or you just text?'
I talk to him.
So he's so cute.
He just puts, like,
XOs after every sentence.
- Does he really?
- Yeah, they're like XXX.
It's so... He's so cute.
'I hope that I can
see him again soon.'
Has Audrina tried
to get in touch with you
since the last time
you guys spoke?
She texted me
that she wants to meet
at Bond Street tomorrow night
to explain to me
you know, kind of
her situation, but...
To try to make peace,
you're assuming, or to try to...
I don't think she's looking
for round two.
But I really, really,
really don't wanna go.
Just playing devil's advocate,
maybe she just has
something different to say.
I mean,
what would have changed?
She's already heard
from Justin
that it wasn't true and knows
that she was wrong, so...
You guys have been through
so much
'that if she's reaching out
to you this hard'
she must really,
really need someone
to talk to right now,
you know?
Because you guys have
been there for each other
so much in the past, like, maybe
she just needs you right now.
♪ I'm falling ♪
♪ Into the depth ♪♪
♪ Where do I begin? ♪
♪ Do I seem so different? ♪
♪ But I'm really
really nothing ♪
♪ I'm just asking
where do I fit in? ♪♪
- This is really pretty.
- Cute dog.
I'm glad we're doing this.
I think it's much needed.
Yes, it is.
You wanna sit down
for a minute?
Yeah, might as well.
[sighs]
I'm glad this,
this opportunity came
because I don't think we would
have had it otherwise.
There isn't any reason
why you and I can't have
when I come up here, we can have
our time, just the two of us.
It's really good
to spend time with you
but whenever you come into town
I don't even know
you're in town
'cause you were just, like,
with Spencer and Heidi
like holed up.
I'm not even, like, included.
Yeah, well, it's not up to me.
That's the problem.
If it was me, I would
definitely include you.
And, like, I know you don't
know this side of Spencer
but with Spencer and I,
it was just competition.
And this is just
like one battle that
like I should fight
for your attention
but he's just, like the star
in the spotlight.
Well, that's, that's
always tough to have somebody
you know, you're living
in his shadow.
Do you think if you looked
closer at Spencer
he would still be your favorite?
I can only go by the way
he treats me.
I just think that
he wouldn't be your favorite
if you knew more about him.
Well, maybe it's just as well
I don't know more about him
because maybe
I wouldn't like him.
You know, life is sometimes
a bucket of worms
and you don't know
what to do with them.
That's how I feel
about Spencer.
Like, he just, like,
doesn't care
and I don't understand
why he's so mean to me.
Stephanie, you have to wait
till he grows up a little bit.
That's what you'll have to do
and then he'll see
the error of his ways.
Well, I'm gonna start
stealing your time from him.
I'll go shopping with you.
Now that's something
we can do together.
Yeah, that's true, we could.
I am very good at that.
♪ Let it out ♪
♪ And let it out ♪
♪ And let me in ♪
♪ I'm wanting to belong here ♪
♪ I'm trying to hold on
and understand ♪
♪ That you've been through
so much ♪
♪ That's it's hard to trust
someone again ♪♪
- Hi.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Fine.
[sighs]
This is a mess, Lauren.
Well, I came to hear
what you have to say 'cause...
I just,
I mean, I know I'm sorry
that I jumped to conclusions.
You're accusing me things
that are, like, crazy.
'They are so out
of character for me.'
You know I wouldn't do that.
Some crazy person told you
a crazy story.
I know it was in left field,
but whenever someone is so like
"I swear, I was there,"
duh, like...
But it wasn't
about what he said
or anything
that could've happened
it was that you,
after I even told you
it wasn't true,
still believed it.
I know and I believe you
and I believe Justin now.
And it's just, I realize
the damage that it's done
and I'm, you know,
I'm sorry on my end
for what I've caused you
and what you went through.
As far as I'm concerned,
if you have a friendship
with someone and you trust them,
then that's everything.
'You know what I mean?'
'Who, who are your friends
if you don't trust them?'
Which was one
of the hardest things for me
was that I realized
that you don't trust me.
I feel like an idiot
because I didn't trust you
and I didn't trust Justin.
It's like...
Audrina, I get why
you didn't trust Justin.
What really made me upset
is that I've watched you
over the past few years
repeatedly
'go back to Justin
and trust him'
with not just, you know,
your feelings, but your heart.
And you couldn't give me
the benefit of the doubt
on something crazy like this.
I don't trust anyone and
you've known that for so long.
I don't think
it's about trusting people
it's about
knowing who to trust.
'The right people.'
'As bad as it sounds, like,
I feel like'
if Justin wasn't in my life,
I just feel like
I think I would be happier
in a sense.
Happiness comes first.
I just, I just feel
like my happiness lately
like, I haven't been happy.
I've been, like, so torn up
inside and so angry
and so just, almost lost.
Like, I don't know
who I am anymore.
But I just feel, like, inside
I've lost who I am, like...
Audrina, you gotta
believe that there's people
that just really want
the best for you.
And it's almost like
I've learned to become
my own best friend
and not trust anyone
because of all that.
And that's not healthy,
it's bad.
I was not gonna cry today.
I don't know.
'I wish you'd just trust me.'
I promise you, I would
never want you to be sad.
♪ One more minute of pain ♪
♪ Will not change ♪
♪ Everything we are ♪
♪ And time will always ♪
Well, call me and we'll go
out this week, okay?
I will. Bye.
♪ To make me whole ♪
♪ But somehow ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ It won't be the same ♪
♪ And time will always heal
the wounded soul ♪
♪ The scars will mend
and make me whole ♪
♪ That's something ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ And time will always heal
the wounded soul ♪
♪ The scars will mend
and make me whole ♪
♪ And somehow ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ It won't be the same ♪
♪ Won't be the same ♪
♪ Again ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪♪
[theme music]