Hey. So I just talked to Brandon
and he said that, um,
we are gonna have to go
into the studio with Brandy
later this week.
That's cool.
Yeah, and being in the studio
is like.
You just kind of forget
about everything else.
Hey, you're not
forgetting everything.
I'm really on a forgetting kick.
'So Cabo was that bad, huh?'
'Justin's just being a jerk.'
He was torturing me and just,
he knows how to do that...
He knows, like,
which buttons to push.
He knows how to push my buttons
get under my skin.
It doesn't seem like he's
interested in really being
with you
unless it's some kind of game.
Well, he just likes knowing
that whenever I do
start dating someone,
he gets me back
'and then he drops me
and I'm hurt'
and then I go find someone,
it's like the same thing.
And I can't keep jumping
from one relationship
right into the next.
Audrina, I think you're starting
to figure things out
a little bit.
After how long? God.
♪ I try to be with you ♪
♪ But I can't love
without reason ♪
♪ What you didn't say
What you didn't do ♪
♪ Tell me what you feel
what am I to you ♪
♪ What you didn't say
What you didn't do ♪♪
(Stephanie)
'So the assignment is to get'
'fabric samples
for our next class.'
(Lauren)
'How many do we have
to turn in?'
We need, like, four...
...prints and two solids,
or something.
I didn't miss anything,
like, super important, right?
Oh, yeah, how was Cabo? You
really didn't miss that much.
Um...
...I can't say I had
as much fun as the guys.
Why, did the guys partied hard?
Yeah, they just, like, flew
in a shipment of girls though.
- It was really funny.
- No, they didn't.
- Yeah, they did.
- Why did Doug fly in girls?
Um, because I don't know
boys like girls
and it was Brody's birthday.
Speaking of boys...
...I've told you
about Cameron, right?
A little bit. Are you guys,
like, together-together now?
- Yay.
- We had the talk.
- The talk? It's such a step.
- The talk.
But you guys will really
like him. He's cute.
- Why wouldn't we, you know?
- I know.
I think we're gonna do
Crown tomorrow night
if you wanna go.
- Crown Bar?
- Yeah.
Um, the only thing is,
I think Brody's gonna go.
At least, I'll have like,
protection
if Brody, like,
says anything to me.
He has to stand up for you,
I think.
'Cause, yeah,
Brody did make me cry.
But, like, he just met Spencer
and Spencer's like
just totally giving him * * *,
like, to stand up
and like, protect me
and whatever.
It'll be fine.
We'll have fun.
Okay, do you need anything else
from here?
- Well, that's bright.
- I know.
Let's get some, like,
plaids or something.
(Brody)
'I need some heat up
in this pool.'
It's too hot outside to heat it.
Oh, thank you, princess.
Why are you not in your bikini?
'I am under here.'
'So I invited Steph to come
to Crown Bar tomorrow night.'
Oh, you mean
you're besties again?
I mean, we just, like,
I don't know.
'Well, I mean, you know
how I feel about her.'
I know. All BS aside,
Stephanie is actually
in a really good relationship
for once and she's really happy.
Good for her.
I'm happy for her.
'I just don't understand
how you have not seen it yet.'
How you don't, like, how do you
not see that she's shady?
She did all that thing
with Doug.
'It's, like, she's not
the kind of person'
I like to surround myself with.
I don't need you to be
her best friend, Brody.
I just think everyone's gonna
be so much more comfortable
if you guys just get along.
'I just don't wanna
hang out with her.'
I know, but listen,
part of her problem is that
Spencer keeps getting
into her head and saying that
Cameron isn't standing up
for her with you...
You know what?
Please, God, I would love for
Cameron to say one thing to me.
I'll be like,
listen, homey, why don't I
pull you outside
and tell you a couple things
about your little girlfriend
here you don't know.
- Like, please, and if...
- Hey, lighten up.
I'm actually gonna grab a drink.
Do you want something?
Um...
Oh, this is gonna be war.
♪ Oh oh so much work ♪
♪ You're the kind of boyfriend
man I wanna live with ♪
♪ You're the kind of guy
that makes me feel like ♪
♪ I'm home at home ♪
♪ It's all good if you let me ♪
♪ Then you know I'm gonna
give it ♪♪
Guys, how are you doing tonight?
Care to start with some drinks?
I am gonna get
the strawberry lemonade.
- Uh, regular water's fine.
- I'll also have a water.
I know.
♪ I've been waiting for you
in my dreams ♪
♪ To come and break this spell ♪
♪ My prince you feel
as I am old and looking ♪
♪ For your love so come
and give me some ♪
♪ Please wake me up ♪♪
Looks like we're the first.
I'm really not that excited.
- Hello!
- How are you, pretty girl?
- Hi!
- This is Cameron.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
- Good. How are you?
- How are you?
Aww.
(Brody)
'Yo, Lauren.'
- Hey, you.
- How are you doing?
Good.
What up?
♪ 'Cause you believe
you believe in love ♪
♪ And the ever after
I hope you know ♪
♪ This was hardly perfect
and not so earthen ♪
♪ 'Cause you believe
you believe in love ♪
♪ And the ever after ♪♪
(male #1)
'Oh, so, you wanna lower it
or you wanna cut pitch?'
From the bridge.
♪ Stuck where we are
it's so hard you're so far ♪
I just remember, like, it was
this one that we were all
like, going crazy over
at the shoot.
And it was, like, in this family
but I don't, I can't find it.
I can't find it.
This is it.
- That's the one right there.
- That's great.
I think that's the album cover...
And it's strong too.
- 'So, rocker.'
- 'Yes?'
I need you to do one more take.
Okay, I will. Hold these for me.
Don't run off with them.
We're gonna put them right
here and keep the cover.
(male #1)
'Alright.'
How did it go
with Cory last night?
He's really nice. It's just
my heart's, like, not there.
- 'So, rocker.'
- Yes?
I want you to do one more
pass of this vocal.
- 'Okay.'
- Take it from the oh part.
♪ Can you hear me crying ♪
♪ Oh can you hear me crying? ♪
- Who's that?
- Justin. He's here.
- Here, here? Like, outside?
- Yeah.
I told him where I was
and now he wants to talk.
Interesting.
I can't keep running from it.
I have to talk to him.
- Go ahead.
- I'll be right back.
- Good luck.
- I'll be back.
♪ This long distance
is killing me ♪
♪ I wish you were here
with me ♪♪
- Hi.
- How's it going in there?
- It's good.
- Yeah?
- What have you been up to?
- I've been thinking.
- About what?
About some of the things
that happened in Cabo, you know.
I didn't wanna be that guy,
you know what I mean?
- But...
- I don't know.
I feel like I've just been
kind of trying to convince
and make myself like someone
where it's like someone else
is still on my mind.
'I think we have
something special.'
I just think
to be in a relationship
you kind of got to
be, like, together.
Yeah. It's just frustrating
at times.
Like, sometimes,
you don't put forth
as much effort as you should.
I know that.
I'm very well aware of that.
'We're a big catch-22.'
[sighs]
Ninety percent of my time with
you is, it's pretty right on.
It's really good,
when I think about you
I don't think of anything
negative whatsoever.
♪ I come and I go
say yes or say no ♪
I will pretty much always
be there for you.
I just don't know.
I want you to be with me.
♪ There with me ♪
♪ Stay ♪
♪ Please stay ♪
♪ Just stay ♪♪
♪ Give it all up give it up ♪
♪ Give it all up
give it all up for you ♪
♪ I give it all up give it up
give it all up for you ♪♪
Alright, let's think
of how we want to organize this.
Do you want me to hand them
to you?
Yeah, just separate them
and then give me
one page of each
and I'll put them in.
- Okay. Perfect.
- 'So Brandy was cool, right?'
I felt bad, like,
walking out with Justin.
You need to tell me
how that went.
He said all the right things.
And maybe, I don't think
he would do that
just to play with me
especially coming
to work, you know?
But think of how many times
you've wanted to end it
with him though.
'Like, there's a reason
for that every time.'
And he can't just keep coming
and sweeping you off your feet.
But he wouldn't say those things
if he didn't really care.
Well, I think that he get scared
when he thinks
he's gonna lose you,
and he likes when he feels
like he's got you wrapped
around his finger, you know?
I know, but this time,
like, just, what he said...
No, but he said it
last time too.
I don't know, there's something
that Justin and I have
that no one else
that I've met...
Like, we don't have that
connection or chemistry.
So you feel like with Cory
there's just no real connection.
Well, you got to do
what you got to do.
I just don't want you to fall
back into the same trap
you've fallen back
into 15 times before.
'I mean,
I thought you were done.'
I know. It's hard.
I just, I like Cory.
And I feel bad.
Like, I think that he likes you.
I really like him,
but I just...
He would be good to you,
you know?
'Cause do you really think
you can, like, sit Cory down
and be like, you've been
nothing but fantastic
but I don't wanna
be with you at all?
♪ It was a shame ♪
♪ They were getting over ♪
♪ The choirs singing for you ♪
♪ And all is well ♪♪
- Hello, little lady.
- Oh, look who's late!
Oh, we're late.
What's going on?
Well, I thought we were on, uh
I thought we were
on Stephanie-Cameron time
which is 40 minutes late
usually.
Where is Cameron? I thought
we were all having lunch.
- Um, he decided not to come.
- 'What do you mean?'
How are you gonna
flake out on brunch?
He just didn't
wanna get grilled.
He didn't flake out.
Uh, do you see
the open seat there?
You guys, this is why
he's not coming.
(Heidi)
'So on a scale from one to ten,
how much do you like him?'
I have no idea.
Like, Cameron's just
like a really nice guy
and like, we went
to Crown Bar last night
so he could meet,
like, the girls and stuff.
- Did Brody go?
- Yeah.
Let me guess.
He didn't stand up for you.
- You guys.
- Oh, my gosh.
He, like, wanted to. He's like,
I'm gonna pull Brody aside.
He wanted to?
Well, what did you say?
(Stephanie)
'I didn't even know
what to say.'
I'm not a fight-starter.
It's not a fight,
you say to your boyfriend
hey, that's the guy
that's made me cry twice.
I mean, if you're trying
to get your...
Every time I leave, like,
a meal with you guys
I, like, wanna break up
with him.
There you go.
♪ Hey hey hey hey hey oh ♪
♪ Hey oh whoa ♪♪
I did bring you
a little something.
- What?
- It's nothing crazy, so relax.
- Just relax.
- Cory.
- A little koala bear?
- Yeah.
- 'That's so cute. Thank you.'
- No worries at all.
Aw, I'm gonna keep this forever.
'So when do you go back
to Australia? In December?'
Yeah, I get home
on Christmas Eve
just right in time for Chrissie
and then hang out
for maybe two months.
I don't know yet.
Long time,
but I hope you got time.
That would be sweet if we could
just, like, hang out every day.
'Did you just invite me
to Australia?'
For sure. Beach time.
Just chilling out.
See, I can't promise right now.
I know. It's tough trying
to get time together.
It's like our schedules
are so crazy and different.
'I think things just
aren't working out.'
Yeah.
It's like we've kind of been
moving too fast and, like...
So, like, what's up with Justin?
It's just I feel like he's in
and out of my life
but I feel like I need
to go back to him.
You know, you're like one of
the greatest guys I've ever met
and I don't, you know, I want
you to be a part of my life.
'But right now, someone else
still has my heart.'
I respect it, you know?
But like, I'm not gonna...
I don't know,
get emotional about it.
Yep.
So what do you reckon?
You wanna get out of here?
Yeah.
♪ Surround the darkness ♪
♪ In my window frame ♪
Well...
...it's good seeing you.
It's always good.
- Oh.
- Bye.
♪ Here all the colors fade ♪
♪ The empty distance
between us ♪♪
[theme music]