I'm going to New York tomorrow.
- Oh, wow. Quick.
- It's, like, right away.
I mean, that's how Kelly works,
you know.
When she wants you,
she wants you
and you just gotta do it.
'I don't even know how long
I'm supposed to be there for.'
So it's a little nerve-racking.
I don't really know exactly
what to plan for.
Just pack lots of black.
Pack lots of black. Exactly.
You'll do fine. It'll be good.
'Okay, so,
let's talk about Doug.'
What's going on with him?
There's no juicy details.
You don't sound too
enthusiastic about it.
Are you over it?
I don't wanna say I'm over it.
But you're just not
super-excited about it.
That's okay.
You can't force these things.
The thing is,
I think... I just remembered
liking him a lot more,
like, when I was younger
and, like,
I think I thought I would just
hop right back into it but, like
I feel like I'm kind of
leading him on a little bit.
It's just not happening.
The latest person
I can even compare him to
is, like, Brody, and, like
I remember being so
excited, like, about...
When you first
started seeing Brody.
It's just not,
it's not there for Doug.
To be perfectly honest
if you're not
excited about him...
Put it to an end?
If that's what you want.
I just don't wanna have
the conversation.
You just say,
"I really, really like you.
"I just think
things are moving too fast
'"and it's just a little
much for me right now.'
And it's nothing about you.
It's just timing."
How would you
like to be dumped?
♪ I'm gonna let the city
take her ♪
♪ And wouldn't you
like to know ♪
♪ If I could change
any of this ♪
♪ If you could would you
If you could would you ♪
♪ You hold on
it's just another day ♪
♪ If you could would you try
to take it back ♪
♪ And forget all about it ♪
♪ If you could would you ♪
♪ If you could would you ♪♪
- Good morning.
- 'Morning. So, what's up?'
(Stephanie)
'Spencer disowned me
for inviting you to my party.'
I'm just, like, shocked, still.
But he's, right now, he's just
out of sight, out of mind.
'It sucks that you're stuck
in the middle like that.'
Yeah. I was worried.
I actually was totally worried
'that I was gonna lose you
as a friend.'
Well, I think that you've made
a really big effort
on both sides
'and I know I'd like us
to stay friends.'
'You're such a good friend.'
♪ Bright lights TV screens ♪
♪ Feels like looking
in a magazine ♪
♪ You run on the floor ♪
♪ Feels like dancing
is the way to go ♪♪
- Hi. How are you?
- Hi. Good. How are you?
Good. I'm just here
to see Kelly.
- Okay. Hold on.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What took you so long?
Nothing.
I came right from my flight.
Was there
a lot of traffic, or...
- No. Just came right here.
- Where are your bags?
They're dropped off
at my hotel.
Okay, I'm a little crazed
'cause there's a casting
going on upstairs.
If you can maybe help with some
of the styling and the casting.
You can ask the boys
to take their shirts off
drop their pants,
try on these clothes
and we'll see what you can do.
Okay.
They're cute. They're young.
- 'They're in New York.'
- Okay.
♪ Stick with me ♪
♪ I'm hot Sahara ♪
♪ Hot Sahara ♪
♪ I hear death valley's... ♪
- Hey.
- Hey, Kel.
- Whitney's here.
- 'Hi, Whitney .'
Thank God you're here.
We need some help.
We need to pull some items
for them to wear.
- Okay.
- Whoa.
For him.
- Okay.
- Can you come over here?
- A jacket, or a t-shirt?
- You can do, like, a jacket.
Maybe you can do a t-shirt,
which would be good.
- Maybe something like that.
- Something like this? Okay.
This is Alex. You're looking
very casual today.
Alright, let's get you
in some clothes.
Maybe in, like,
some jeans and a t-shirt.
Okay. Thanks.
(Kelly)
'Okay. Come back in a minute.'
[exhales]
Okay.
'Do you want to
go forward and walk?'
And then just walk, mark
and return.
- He's cute.
- Hmm.
- 'Where are you from?'
- California.
- Where?
- That's a state. What city?
From Fresno. I went to USC.
I went to USC.
- 'Yeah?'
- Mm-hmm.
- What house were you in?
- I wasn't in a sorority.
- I was in sigma beta.
- 'You were a frat boy?'
Did you graduate when?
I graduated from Columbia,
actually. I transferred.
Oh, okay.
From Columbia? Okay.
Can we just take one of you
without your shirt on?
You have a nice body.
'But you know that already.
What are you doing later?'
There's a little event
I'm going to for...
It's a launch event for Kobe
in the Hamptons.
(Kelly)
'Why don't you come by and have
drinks with us tonight?'
We're gonna take
a couple of girls out.
- Are you up for that?
- Yeah. Alright, cool.
'Come by and
have a drink with us.'
- Don't act embarrassed.
- No. I'm shy.
No. I'm back and forth.
But, yeah.
8:45 sharp, okay?
See you there.
'Here's your shirt back.'
[laughs]
Next model.
'This is called multi-tasking
in the power-bitch world.'
♪ Man look at them haters ♪
♪ They don't like it ♪
♪ We ballin' boy ♪
♪ Jay look at them haters ♪
♪ They don't like it ♪
♪ We ballin' boy ♪
♪ Listen here's why
'cause I'm a pimp like that ♪
♪ I gots to hustle
'cause I'm about stacks ♪
♪ Get it the best way I can
I'm trying to be the man ♪
♪ But you haters does not
like the mess ♪
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so excited to eat here.
Oh, I feel like I haven't been
alone with you in years.
Every time we were going out
to dinner, you're like.
- "Holly, you wanna come?"
- It was so fun.
It's like three's a company.
I regret so much not throwing
Stephanie's cake in LC's face.
Stop.
She was obviously
just doing that to piss me off
and that's why her and LC
became such good friends
'cause they both
wanna just piss me off.
'Spencer, that's your sister'
and she's gonna be your sister
your whole life.
'I really think
it's time that you just'
'make everything fine with her.'
The day I'm friends
with Stephanie again
is the day I'm friends
with Lauren Conrad.
I don't know.
I kind of miss Stephanie.
- That's sweet.
- I miss hanging out with her.
You should go
hang out with her and Lauren.
Well, maybe I will hang out
with them.
Don't come home to me then.
Time to get in bed and cuddle,
my dear.
♪ Do you feel the way I do ♪
♪ The way I feel ♪
♪ When I'm out with you ♪
♪ Why can't you show it to me ♪
♪ It seems so hard ♪
♪ To recognize what is truth ♪♪
Hi.
Oh. Well, hello.
- Hello, hello.
- 'How are you?'
Good.
Somebody's a little late.
Sorry.
'What are all
these new little...'
...bracelets you have on here?
Well, these are my sparklies,
and these are my friendships.
Whose, whose friendship
bracelet?
Um, this one's my mama,
and this one's Stephanie.
Oh, no... Oh, my...
'Cause you think Stephanie's
being super-genuine
and I, I think that Stephanie
has ulterior motives.
- 'And I think that...'
- Why?
You don't...
Fine, you don't...
You don't have to believe,
or see, or whatever.
'I mean that's,
I can tell you things'
'that you'd be like,
"Whoa, really?"'
'And you'd be trippin' out.'
- Just telling you.
- I know.
I don't wanna hear you say,
"I told you so."
Like I have all the time.
How many times
have you done it?
Only once.
- 'Your guys.'
- One time.
Doug.
'Yeah, well, you could be
right about Doug.'
'Why? What happened?'
Thank you.
I didn't see that
going very far.
It's not his fault.
It's my fault.
I just don't really wanna settle
and I don't think
I should have to.
'I don't know. Your type is...'
My type is someone
I've already dated.
Yeah. Ha-ha.
Can we talk about us
getting naked tonight?
I hate you right now.
Oh, that's pretty funny, though.
[sighs]
♪ When you ♪
♪ Lead me on ♪
♪ We're under the moon ♪
♪ Let's stay ♪
♪ We'll crash
through the waves ♪
♪ Come swimmin' back ♪
♪ Come on swim ♪
- Hi, how are you?
- How's it going?
Good. How are you doing?
Good. How was the rest
of your day?
Um, it was okay.
So, did you guys
book me or what?
I don't-I don't really know,
to be honest.
- I'm joking. I'm joking.
- 'Yeah.'
Is that your first casting
you've done?
No, I've done
a bunch of castings.
'I'm sorry if she made you feel
uncomfortable today.'
Was she like that with all
the guys or was I special?
I think you were special.
I think she eyed you and knew
that you were special.
[Whitney laughs]
[cell phone rings]
'I'm sorry.'
Oh, Kelly's calling me.
Hang on one second.
Hello?
'Yes.'
Okay.
- 'He's here, right next to me.'
- Tell her, I said hi.
He says "Hello."
Okay, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Okay, bye.
No one's coming.
It's just you and me.
I know you planned that.
[laughs]
Oh, I did.
'Oh, my God.'
So, you went to USC.
That's so crazy.
It's a distant memory for me.
- How long were you there for?
- I was there for a year.
So I just, I didn't know exactly
what I wanted to do and I felt
like going to school at Columbia
would open more doors.
- So that was why I transferred.
- Well, do you like being here?
When I,
when I first moved here
I didn't know
a soul in the city.
Yeah, that's how I feel
right now.
Like, every time I come here,
I'm like...
I know, I know what that's like.
But, eventually, you do meet
some good people here.
And you felt like you've met
some good people here?
Well, I ran into you
on a casting.
Yeah.
You wanna go walk around
for a little bit?
Yeah.
♪ For once in my life ♪
♪ Can I get too much
of a good thing ♪
♪ Stay on the upside
of a mood swing ♪
♪ For once in my life ♪
♪ For once in my life can I ♪♪
[knock on door]
Coming.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
Look how cute this is.
- Look how cute you look.
- Thanks.
I have no idea
what I'm gonna wear.
Come sit.
You know what
you're gonna wear yet?
No.
This is where
Spencer was living.
- Do you want to trade spots?
- No. I'm good.
[both laugh]
- Um, where's Doug tonight?
- Who knows?
'Honestly, I don't think
that's going anywhere.'
- Are you kidding?
- No.
Shut up.
'I just don't think
he's right for me.'
'I don't even wanna think
about it.'
Now that, like,
I totally live alone
I say we start
having some kickbacks here.
- Kickbacks?
- High-school style.
Nice. Is it nice
to have your space back?
It's a little bit lonely.
I got to talk to the hamster
a lot, but...
I thought it was a guinea pig.
Hamster, guinea pig.
Guinea pigs are, like, big.
Hamsters are, like, this big.
She used to be a hamster.
Now, she's a guinea pig.
♪ Take your hand with mine ♪
♪ Together we'll dance ♪
♪ Into the night ♪
(Alex)
'Why do you think
you wouldn't move out here?'
I don't know, just
my family and friends...
Not that they're holding me
back, but, internally
I just feel, like,
such a connection to them
that I would miss them
so much.
I mean, you can make new friends
out here. I'll help you.
But I don't wanna make
new friends.
I'll-I'll introduce you
to some cool people.
- Okay.
- You would like New York a lot.
You think so?
You walk out your door
and you see
five different types of people
from five different
walks of life on your doorstep.
You know, in LA,
that's never gonna happen.
And I think that
if I have the chance
to enjoy this city,
like, I might as well.
Like, fashion's almost, like,
a culture here.
- You know?
- Yeah.
It's not just
people's professions
it's their lives,
it's what they live for.
It-it's an art.
It's so nice out tonight.
Is it gonna rain here
a lot this summer?
Soon as it gets humid.
July, August.
Ugh, I don't know
if I can handle that.
Alright, well, this was fun.
Okay.
Well, I'll see you very soon.
Yeah. I'll be back.
Thank you for showing me around
and everything.
I'm glad the way
we hung out today.
(Whitney)
'Basically, I get there'
and there's a line out the door
of all these male models
which was, like,
a little bit refreshing
after stepping off a plane,
you know?
Um, there's, like, this one guy.
He's really cute,
and Kelly obviously
had her eye on him for me.
She said to this guy, "Why don't
you come meet us tonight?"
I'm like, "Oh, my God.
Oh, my God."
I was like, "Kelly, do I scream
lonely, or something?"
Like, "Do you think
I need a guy?"
So, we were gonna meet
for drinks at my hotel
and I get a call from Kelly,
and she's like
"Robin and I aren't gonna be
able to make it."
I was like, "Are you serious?"
Like, I was...
So, it's just me
and this guy, Alex
sitting there at this hotel,
like, total date-style.
- Was it good, or was it awful?
- It wasn't awful.
Well, that's good!
We-we sat and talked
for a little while.
He took me on, like, a little
walk around Soho afterwards.
Stop it. That's cute.
But do you like him at all?
Yeah, I think so.
- How have you been?
- Good.
Good?
Did you end it with Doug?
Well, I've kind of been
avoiding him.
It's hard, but it's better
not to string him along.
'Yeah, I'm gonna
talk to him today.'
It's not a problem. It's good.
'I've waited too long
to pick the wrong guy.'
- You don't settle.
- Yeah.
♪ So don't fade away ♪
♪ Here in my heart ♪♪
[knock on door]
Oh, when somebody, uh,
doesn't answer the door
'that doesn't mean enter.'
(Stephanie)
'Okay, well, I brought you
a peace offering.'
- Will you open it?
- No.
I'm not really in the mood
to open presents.
Will you please?
I'm, like, so excited.
Like, on the car ride
over here, I was like
"He's gonna love it.
He's gonna love it."
There are two things.
So, just one of the things.
I'll look, I'll peek in, but...
Ah, okay, okay.
This was a good gift.
It's a good gift.
'You get, like, a half a point.'
Yay!
Yay.
So...
...anything else new with you?
- Nope.
- How's Heidi?
Amazing.
Yeah?
- You guys are good?
- Phenomenal.
'Well, maybe we could
hang out sometime.'
'What? You, me, and LC?'
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
♪ And it's these things ♪
♪ That hold you down ♪
♪ When they're supposed ♪
♪ To keep you safe and sound ♪
♪ And it's these things ♪
♪ You claim to believe ♪♪
[doorbell rings]
- 'Hey.'
- Hi.
- Come on in.
- Thanks.
Sorry, I didn't know
you were gonna come by.
I would have got you
something too.
No, no. It's alright.
So, what's going on?
I've been trying to reach you.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to be, like, cold.
I was just...
'I keep thinking
about this thing with us'
and I just, it's just not there.
- Really?
- I mean...
After you said, "I have a crush
on you" in the club.
Okay, a crush.
Uh, okay, a crush.
That's fine. A crush.
But I'm just saying, you know...
And it's not, honestly...
'Things are moving really fast.'
...it's not you at all,
and I'm sorry.
'I just need you
to understand, like'
it was just, like,
a lot at once.
'Sure, I totally agree.'
I-I thought something different
and I didn't know where
I came in asking for anything.
I've been nothing
but respectful and nice
and tried to treat you
like a princess.
Did I, I... You've been
way too nice to me.
'What did I always tell you?
I told you'
'you were way too nice to me .'
Okay, then, I'm too nice.
- You know what I mean?
- It's not you.
'No, I-I just, I mean'
'I didn't even know
anything was wrong'
so, I-I don't know.
It kind of hit me
like a ton of bricks and I...
[chuckles]
'Yeah, you're,
just like I said, Lauren'
'you're totally different
than any girl I've ever met'
and that's what I,
that's what I liked about you.
And it wasn't the right time,
it wasn't the right place
and, you know,
what are you gonna do?
I'm sorry.
You know, if we're better off
you know, as friends
and, you know, I still
want to be good friends.
We've known each other forever.
'And I tried to see if,
you know'
it was still there
and it wasn't.
No, I'm glad you feel that way
because it's like...
'We're still gonna
see each other.'
I mean, we hang out
at all the same spots
we have all, you know,
do all the same things.
- And, you know...
- Well, we tried.
Yep. So...
And it was fun.
Hey, we had a lot of fun.
[both laugh]
We had a lot of fun,
but, you know
you never know what happens.
You never know what happens.
- Cool?
- 'Okay.'
- Alright. I'll walk you out.
- Thank you.
♪ I'm not the me
that I started with ♪
♪ I'm freer ♪
I'm sorry, Dougy.
No. Why-Why are you sorry?
- 'Cause I feel bad.
- Everything's good.
'Everything's good. No worries.'
- I'll see you.
- I'll talk to you later.
♪ We are crushed and created ♪
♪ We are broken and built ♪
♪ In the very same way ♪
♪ What I thought
I could handle ♪
♪ What I thought I could take ♪
♪ What I thought
would destroy me ♪
♪ Leaves me stronger
in its wake ♪
♪ Stronger in its wake ♪
♪ It leaves me stronger ♪♪
[theme music]