[music continues]
Alright, so,
take out your magazines.
So, I'm gonna have
my birthday party
at Boulevard three,
on Thursday night.
- This Thursday?
- Yeah.
- Oh, I wanna come.
- Can you?
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool.
Is it okay
if I bring a guy with me?
- What?
- You have a guy in your life?
- Oh, my God.
- 'His name's Doug.'
He plays baseball,
but he's injured right now.
He's an athlete?
That's my favorite kind of guy.
- I know, right?
- Athletes are the best.
Are you inviting
your brother and Heidi?
I don't know. I haven't
talked to them in weeks.
I just want it
to be a fun night
and it's like
drama follows them.
I mean, I don't know
if it follows
as much as they chase it.
♪ The California blur ♪
♪ It's passing by
like a bullet train ♪
♪ The California blur ♪
♪ Now the energy is focused ♪♪
(Doug)
'This is you.'
You look nice today.
Very pretty.
- Thank you.
- Gorgeous.
Love it. Love the white.
You know, what I really,
really want to find
is our prom pictures.
I have 'em. I have some.
At my house. I told you
I found them the other day.
I thought you found them
at your Laguna house.
- Yeah, at my Laguna house.
- That house.
Not the Laguna house.
So, anyway, how's things
with you and Audrina?
Um, I think her and Lo had like
a little, a little chat.
- Yeah?
- It was kind of a disaster.
Ev-everybody in your life...
Your life is hectic.
- You know?
- Mm-hmm.
Let's go do something.
- I have to go to work.
- Why? Take it off.
I'm gonna take you to Cabo.
No.
Let's go do something fun.
My work is fun.
What are you doing this weekend?
Um...
...no plans.
My friend Steph's having
her birthday party.
- Yeah?
- Are you guys in town?
Yeah, I'll be there.
I'll be there.
Yay. I just don't get along
with her brother
so hopefully he won't
be there.
Blood's thicker than water,
you know.
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ I'm leavin' you behind ♪
♪ And that's my perfect plan ♪
♪ Deep inside I wish that
I could run away and hide ♪
Okay, that is
"Real Naked Girls."
- Okay.
- "Shivers."
Those need to be mastered,
and then "Broadripple."
Are the ones that
need to be recorded.
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool.
Um, what are you doing tonight?
Um, I'm going to
Stephanie's birthday
'at Boulevard three.'
- I've never been there.
- Huh?
It's on Sunset, I think.
'The thing is,
Lauren's going with Lo.'
- Ooh, really?
- You know.
The last time I saw her,
she came to my room.
Really?
Because on my birthday
she wanted to apologize
for being absent
but my friends were
being rude to her.
Wait, she came to apologize,
but in reality
what she said was
a stab at your friends?
"I'm going to apologize
for your friends' behavior."
[both chuckle]
It's like Audrina versus Lo.
Battle to the death.
- I'll be on your side.
- Brunettes.
The dark hairs versus
the light hairs.
[laughs]
I'll kick their ass.
♪ We are the world ♪
♪ It's just a war ♪
♪ That we are living in ♪
♪ Don't you hate us ♪
♪ For what we've done ♪
♪ We're not giving in ♪
♪ And it won't do much
if you spill your guts ♪
♪ The tables have turned now ♪
So, tonight, Kelly, Robin
and Emily are coming into town.
Are they flying in for
something or just...
I think they're just coming
just to check up on things
and see how it's going, and so
we're going to this
dinner at Simon LA.
I was totally invited to
this dinner with everyone
so it's a little intimidating
but hopefully I can, like,
not be too nervous.
- Are you nervous?
- I get a little nervous.
- At, like, work dinners. Yeah.
- Really? But you work here now.
- You're part of the team.
- I know.
I know, but I'm a newbie, so...
Do you have anything
going on this week?
The only thing I know so far
is Stephanie's birthday
tomorrow at Boulevard three.
- Oh, really?
- 'Yeah.'
So it should be fun.
Are Spencer and Heidi coming?
- She said no.
- Why would they not come?
I mean, I'm not even gonna try
understand their relationship.
She'd probably tell you
if he was going to come.
Probably. I mean, she gets it.
I would just kind of try to
time, like, going around it.
'Cause it's no fun when we both
end up in the same place.
(Kelly)
'Whitney, can you come up?'
[instrumental music]
♪ Come on come on
and give us that money ♪
♪ I'm on TVs with
supersonic sound ♪
♪ Bow down before the land
of milk and honey ♪
It's good to know you still
know how to order for me.
Think I would forget
what you like?
- No.
- 'Chicken tacos?'
[cell phone chiming]
- Who is it?
- It's Stephanie.
Probably checking to see
if we're rolling
on her birthday party.
You think I'm gonna hang out
with Stephanie?
She's best friends
with the girl
I despise more than
anything on the Earth.
- It's, like, you know..
- I know.
It's like, "Stephanie, we've
been nothing but nice to you
and now all of a sudden, like,
you're hanging out with Lauren?"
'That's so disrespectful.'
Hey, you don't have
to get me fired up.
I'm not gonna be able to eat,
I'll get so mad.
My only logic is
that is your sister,
and regardless of how crazy
and whatever she is, I think
for your family's sake
that maybe we should just go
and be cordial, and it can be
the last time you see her.
You know? It's only one night.
'We can only go for
a couple of minutes.'
I mean, I guess you're right,
but this is my last straw.
If she wants to continue being
friends with LC
that's her choice and she knows,
she knows what happens.
I will never speak
with her again.
- I agree.
- Get lost.
It's done.
[instrumental music]
♪ Hollywood la la la ♪
♪ La la la la
li la la la la ♪
♪ Hollywood la la la ♪♪
(Lo)
How old is Stephanie turning,
22 or...
Twenty-two. She's our age.
'Did she say if Spencer
and Heidi are coming?'
'She told me they're
not coming.'
- Oh, really?
- 'Yeah.'
I'd be kind of
nervous if they came.
I know. Well...
I'm excited that
Doug's coming tonight.
Who would have guessed, like,
four years later?
Well, who would have
guessed that we're going
to Stephanie Pratt's birthday?
I think that a lot
of times I'm...
I trust people I shouldn't
'and it turns out right.'
'And it makes me feel a little
bit better about it.'
I want to think that
you can trust everyone.
- You can't though...
- 'And I know you can't.'
But it's kind of nice to know
that some people,
you know deserve it.
Yeah.
- 'Knock, knock.'
- 'Hey.'
What time are you guys going?
- Pretty soon.
- Like 10:30-ish.
(Audrina)
'Okay.'
(Lauren)
'You're still coming, right?'
Yeah, I'll stop by
for a little and...
I don't know, have a drink,
say happy birthday.
Yeah, that'd be nice
just to, like, chill.
Yeah.
[rock music]
[music continues]
(Kelly)
'So, you guys, I think
we should have a toast'
to People's Revolution
'New York and LA.'
'When east meets west.'
'Chin-chin to everybody.'
We have things going on
in New York with Jeff Coons.
We're gonna do a private dinner
at the Waldorf.
I would like to bring you
there at some point.
That's just...
That's scary.
But I think it would be good
to just talk for a second
about what we're gonna
do with LA.
'I mean, because you guys
are doing a big'
like a big brunt of
the intake, right?
And dealing with stylists
a lot, too. I mean...
No, I really, like,
in my world...
For certain clients, too,
when it's like...
'No, no, no, no,
because it's my company'
'and the answer's no to that,
I don't want you'
'to talk to a stylist.'
I'm just gonna say what I want
since it's my company, you...
pretty, pretty,
happy, happy pitch stories.
'You have to have common sense.'
We want to grow.
'If we do that,
everybody will move up.'
'If we don't,
people are gonna be cut.'
[instrumental music]
♪ Take your coat ♪
♪ Leave their clothes ♪
♪ Midnight in the city ♪
I'm excited for tonight.
Really excited.
- I love birthday parties.
- 'Me too.'
'I'm gonna text Stephanie
and tell we're on our way.'
Oh, yeah. Do you think
she's there already?
- I'm sure she is.
- 'Yeah, probably.'
She's the birthday girl.
She should get there first.
So, Doug is coming with
Frankie and Brody?
He said they're just
finishing up dinner.
'Oh, fun.'
I'm excited that he's
coming out with us.
I know.
I hope Audrina ends up
stopping by.
No reason not to, you know?
'Can't we all just get along?'
'We are all just getting along.'
That's why we're all going
to Stephanie's birthday.
I mean, we're not all
getting along.
Well...the ones who matter
are getting along.
[upbeat music]
♪ Like a movie star ♪
♪ Cruising Sunset Boulevard ♪
♪ I pull up to the club ♪
♪ A scene from film noir ♪
[indistinct chattering]
- Steph.
- Oh, there.
- Hi! Happy birthday.
- Oh, my God, thank you.
Oh my God. No. Lo!
- Happy birthday, sweetie.
- Thank you.
- You look gorgeous!
- Thanks, you too.
- These are my friends.
- Hi.
- Lauren. How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
(Stephanie)
'Okay. I cannot wait
to meet Doug.'
- 'Lo, have you met him?'
- Yeah, he's really nice.
You're gonna like him.
[dance music]
- Hi!
- Hey.
[indistinct chatter]
(Frankie)
'Oh. Oh.'
'Happy birthday.'
'Happy birthday, babe.
How are you?'
Hi. How are you?
Doug, this is Stephanie.
Hello, guys.
- Can I sit down?
- Yeah.
(Brody)
'Lauren, get over here.
Give me a hug.'
- 'Hi.'
- 'Hi, sweetie.'
[indistinct chatter]
How are you?
You look pretty.
- I'm good.
- Okay, good.
Where'd your buddies go?
'Really?'
[hip-hop music]
Shut up.
You're lying.
[music continues]
'You guys!'
I thought you were totally
dissing me
and ignoring my calls.
This is the best birthday
I've ever had.
- Yo, I'm gonna bounce.
- 'Why are you leaving?'
I mean, all this is is drama.
It's ridiculous.
Frankie, Frankie.
(Frankie)
'We're leaving. We got to go.'
Okay.
- I'll go with you.
- You'll stay with me?
I'm gonna steal him from you.
I'll call you in a little bit.
- Say happy birthday to Steph.
- Happy birthday.
[music continues]
Can you get these
obnoxious chicks away?
What?
[music continues]
(Lauren)
'Just let me grab my purse.'
'Oh, here it is, okay.'
You have a really good birthday.
Thank you for having me.
And have so much fun, okay?
Thank you so much
for coming, you guys.
Thank you for the present.
'Have fun at your party.'
'Okay. I'll see you guys later.'
I'm really surprised
you guys showed up.
Really surprised, trust me.
I think we surprised
somebody else even more.
[laughs]
[instrumental music]
♪ I'd be more cosmopolitan ♪
♪ Who needs class
when you've got money ♪
♪ Well I've got cash but
you've got everything else ♪
[knock on door]
♪ Well you can call me crazy ♪
- What's up? What's up?
- Hey.
This place is way cleaner now
that I don't live here.
[chuckles]
What's going on?
I came here to talk to you
about everything
that, uh, went down last night.
It was just, like, so weird,
you guys came
and, like, with balloons
and stuff, and then...
'Cause at the end of the day,
you are still my sister
so I got to go, you know,
all we were was nice to you
and all of a sudden
you jump ship to the bad guys.
I didn't jump ships. I feel like
I was friends with everyone.
There's no...when there's
two ships, that's jumping ships.
And in your head,
you're peacemaker
"I wanna be nice to everyone,"
and you got caught up
and I get that,
it's like, "Whoo-hoo, it's fun
"I'm friends with everybody.
Why can't we all
just get along?"
It's like trying to tell
Iran and Israel
to get along,
it's not gonna happen.
'It's not about
why or what you did.'
I think you're more rash
and I'm more rational.
Like, you'll jump to, like,
whatever conclusion
but you won't listen, and,
like, I was trying to like
still be friends with you
guys and then...
I don't wanna be friends
with you. Do you get that?
'If you're choosing
to be with this person'
who you've known
for...three months?
And how long, how long
have you known me? 22 years?
Yeah, but we haven't gotten
along for 22 years.
I didn't say that.
You've known LC
for three months.
Why should I stop being
friends with her
if we've been getting along?
Stephanie, we're brother and
sister, at the end of the day
I can't change, I can't
make you un-my sister.
Trust me, if I could in
the past, I would have.
That's, like, the most,
like, hurtful thing.
I don't wanna see you. I don't
wanna hang out with you.
Like, as long as you're rolling
around with that posse
you have nothing to do
with my life.
'Like, and that's straight up.'
[instrumental music]
♪ Say what you want to me ♪
♪ Go ahead ♪
♪ I am not listening ♪♪
(Kelly)
'Okay, if you're such a good
assistant, you do that schedule'
and then you tell me
how you feel afterward.
Alright, bye.
- Whitney?
- 'Yeah?'
Can you come up here
for a minute, please?
Hi.
So, a few things that I wanna
talk to you about.
Okay.
I wanna let you know
that I fired Jessica.
The bottom line is that
we've a voice
and a standard that comes
from New York, and we felt that
it was not being maintained
'with an attention to detail.'
That being said, we,
Robin, Emily, and I have talked
and we want to offer you
Jessica's job
and we would also expect you
to be available
to start living
a bi-coastal lifestyle
which is something
we've all done.
- Right.
- 'You would come to New York.'
'Where you'd basically,
like, be my shadow.'
You would come to
business meetings with us.
We would do a two
or three-day intensive.
You can watch and participate
in the upper management
so when you come back to LA...
So I can bring the voice
from New York?
- Right.
- Okay.
I do remember that we talked
about your need to delegate.
Right. I'm working on it.
Definitely working on it.
You're gonna have to learn
how to do that
while you're here
and also from afar.
Okay.
I wouldn't make any plans
for the next couple of months.
[instrumental music]
♪ I don't know
if I can ever be ♪
♪ All the things
that you see ♪
♪ Things that you see in me ♪
♪ I don't know if I can be ♪
♪ All the things that you see ♪
♪ Things that you see ♪♪
Lauren.
Oh, my God.
- What?
- I'm so sorry.
I had no idea that Spencer
and Heidi were coming.
- Don't worry.
- No, I...
Literally, I've never
been so shocked.
I mean, it was
a total surprise.
I hadn't heard
from them at all.
- No one knew if he was coming.
- Yeah.
I think that night
was the last night.
I stopped caring.
It's like they didn't
talk to me after that.
Like, I left in my own car.
You know, they didn't call.
Like, it just wasn't sincere,
or genuine.
- Is it ever, though?
- It used to be.
Things change.
Like, I don't even
know them anymore.
But I just, I don't want you
to think I betrayed your trust.
It's just, like, so crazy.
I mean, it's not a secret to you
that, like, all my friends say
that I shouldn't even trust you
and so you just kind of set
them back on that rampage.
[instrumental music]
♪ The situation we're now in ♪
♪ When you won't come out
from within ♪
♪ And I won't be
the one to fall ♪
♪ To fall to fall ♪
♪ You chose the solemn road ♪
♪ I'll take the one back home ♪
[theme music]