- AUDRINA: [sighs]
So, what's up?
This week has been,
like, hell for me.
You haven't been
yourself today.
You look so angry.
'Cause you don't know
what I've been through
and what I've heard.
What was it?
This guy Dino, who
I've known for two years
and... one of Justin's
close friends,
was like, "There's
something that, like,
"I need to get off
my conscience.
It's been killing
me, and..."
What is it?
Basically that Lauren
and Justin hooked up.
[gasps] Oh, my God.
Have you talked to Lauren?
Right when I found out,
I called Lauren
and she's like, "What are
you talking about?
You know I would
never do that."
And then she hung up on me,
and then she texted me with
"It really hurts me that you
would say something like that.
You know I'm not
that person."
I mean, I was in shock.
Do you think she did it?
I was in shock,
I didn't know what
to believe, you know.
Have you talked to Justin?
Justin can't even give me
the respect of calling me
and tell me that
this never happened.
I don't know what to think.
I don't know what to do.
But you weren't there.
You didn't see it.
You don't know for a fact
if it happened.
So you've got to get
to the bottom of this.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
- AUDRINA: [sniffles]
- CHIARA:
It's okay.
Hey, you'll be fine.
You're stronger than this.
You are.
I know.
I can't really give you
any more advice than that.
It's not very good advice,
but you're gonna be fine.
Yeah.
♪ I turn my head away ♪
♪ But my heart will remain ♪
♪ Till the day I learn ♪
♪ You're no good for me ♪
♪ No ♪♪
♪♪
- LAUREN: She's crazy.
- LO: What?
Audrina is crazy.
What are you
talking about?
I mean, she called me
and she was like,
"Did you hook up with Justin?"
And I, I started laughing
when she asked me.
And she was like
"Answer the question.
Did you or did you not?"
and I was like,
"No."
She thinks I hooked up with him,
like, totally serious.
Are you kidding?
She's not joking.
It's insane. It's so insane.
That's laughable.
You would never do that.
He would never do that.
It's insulting on so many
different levels.
She's calling me a bad friend.
She's calling me a shady person.
She's calling me a slut.
And she saying that I would
hook up with him.
Yeah, it's...
Yes, Audrina, I...
I did. I...
You know what, I couldn't resist
his charm and his manners
and his impeccable hygiene.
I was under
the Justin Bobby spell.
And she's calling all
these people, telling them.
She called Brody,
she called Frankie.
They all called me.
Honestly...
Did she tell you
had Justin said,
"Yes, this happened"?
No, she wouldn't. She's like,
"I'm not even talking
to you about this."
I'm like really,
really upset right now.
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna try to talk
to her about it again?
She's supposed to stop by
later today, but
this isn't a little thing.
I don't want a friend
that's gonna treat me that way.
Unless she apologizes
to me, I'm done.
I'm so done.
♪ I'm putting one lie ♪
♪ In front of the other ♪
♪ Say it so you take a dive ♪
♪ Leave your conscience
all behind ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ No... ♪
[knocking on door]
Who is it?
- HOLLY:
It's Holly.
If it isn't little Miss Traitor.
Um... Is Heidi here?
Excuse me?
Where's Heidi?
Not here.
Do you know where she is?
I know she doesn't
wanna see you.
Alright. Well, if you could
just tell her that I came by.
Uh, I'll be like,
"Hey, that girl
that moved in with LC
"came by,
"but we didn't have anything
in our fridge for her,
so she left."
How did you know that
I was staying there?
Same reason your sister knows.
My little sister
had to tell her,
not her own sister.
It's one thing Heidi and I
definitely have in common,
is unloyal sisters.
I think that Stephanie
and I both have had...
Heidi's best interests at heart.
Really?
I think you're the only
person that doesn't,
really, to be honest.
'Cause all you care about
is yourself.
I'm glad you know what's up.
Well, look, I really don't
have anything to say to you,
and I just...
If you could tell Heidi
that I came by.
Uh, yeah, I will relay
your message to Heidi
but I have a feeling she's not
gonna wanna talk to you.
Whatever.
♪ How can you be ♪
♪ So unfeeling ♪
♪ Unfeeling ♪
♪ How do you sleep ♪
♪ With yourself ♪
♪ Unfeeling unfeeling ♪♪
[doorbell rings]
- LAUREN: Door's open.
Hey.
You need to, like,
converse with me.
Well, until you are gonna treat
me like a friend
I am not gonna talk to you like
one.
We have to talk about this.
Tell me, like, why you're
being so crazy to me.
You know why, Lauren.
[laughing]
No.
It's really [bleep] up
what I heard.
Did you you hook up
with Justin or not?
You are insane, Audrina.
No, I'm not.
You're... you're
serious right now?
Yeah, I'm dead serious.
Oh, my God.
You can believe
whatever you want
but please stop
talking [bleep] on me
to other people
and calling them.
'Cause it's really
screwed up.
I'm not kidding.
Alright, bye.
♪♪
[door slams]
♪ Oh ♪
♪ That's what they say ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ This is no ordinary thing ♪
♪ No no ♪♪
Hey, Justin, it's Audrina.
I don't know where you are,
or what you're doing,
if you got any of my
text messages
or phone calls but...
I really need to talk to you
so we can clear this up, and...
I know I was harsh before
but with you not calling me,
it's kind of freaking me out.
And just everything going on
and...
all the things that people
keep putting in my ear
about you and Lauren
hooking up, um...
It just makes me sick
to my stomach, like...
I don't know.
It's unbelievable, but I really
just need to hear it
come out of your mouth
and...
I really need
to talk to you.
So please,
call me back. Bye.
♪ You may have reasons ♪
♪ To ignore ♪
♪ What you're hearing ♪
♪ That's too bad
you don't explore ♪
♪ What you're feeling ♪
♪ This silence killing us ♪
♪ Inside ♪
♪ Now tell me what we're ♪
♪ Fighting for ♪♪
[whispering]
Hey, Heids.
Hey.
Whatcha doin'?
Uh, just working.
What are you doing?
I thought you had an office.
Um, that used to be my office
and now I'm here
because I got...
I ran into a little trouble
at XIV the other week.
It's a long story.
I don't wanna go into it.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a minute or...
Yeah, but I don't think
we should really talk in here.
So maybe we can
just go in there?
Okay, yeah.
Okay.
So...
It's good
to finally see you.
You know, I was really hurt
by the whole situation.
I've never felt
so unwelcome and unwanted.
I feel like I've done
nothing but try to be
the best sister
I possibly can be to you.
And then I hear
from Stephanie
that you're living with
Lauren, or whatever and...
Do you know how badly
that hurts me?
Lauren was my best friend,
who I've gone
through so much with
and obviously I miss her.
I don't really feel like
I was left with an alternative.
You told me I could
stay there, and I did and...
And I let you stay there
but I didn't think
you would stay that long.
Honestly, my...
issue has nothing
to do with you.
It's just Spencer.
I feel like,
if you have somebody
that loves you so much,
then they want every part
of your life to be great.
I mean, he's been doing nothing
but push everybody away,
push all your friends away.
No, he doesn't.
Did he tell you
I came by the other day?
♪♪
♪ The story ♪
♪ Of a broken heart ♪
♪ Stand up and I'll tell you ♪
♪ Now everything ♪
♪ Was torn apart ♪
♪ And no one else can feel you ♪
♪ Over it was on me ♪
♪ Now it's just another day ♪♪
Hi.
- AUDRINA:
How are you?
Been better.
Me too.
Well...
Hmm?
Let's talk about
you and Lauren.
Me and Lauren.
Well, what is there
to talk about?
Did you do it or not?
You think after all this,
I would run and hook up
with Lauren?
You really do?
There are little things
that kept popping in my mind
and when Dino was
so sincere about it.
I told you, no,
it didn't happen.
And if you don't
wanna believe me
then I don't know
what else to tell you.
But you can't talk to me
the way you... you talk to me.
That's for one...
I know, but...
No, you don't know.
Yes, I do know.
Because I would never talk
to you the way you talk to me.
Justin, when I called you
a whole bunch of times,
you don't answer or text me back
when I did text you back nicely.
Yeah, but some
of the things you say,
I truly would
never say to you.
"You [bleep] I
[bleep] hate you.
You [bleep] use me."
All that...
After you don't call me back
or text me back.
Why would I
wanna talk to you
after all the [bleep]
you were saying to me?
Justin, this was a huge rumor.
Lauren...
I don't wanna hear
it, Audrina.
I will [bleep] leave right now
because this is [bleep].
How would you feel if you heard
something like that, Justin?
You know what?
I'm not even...
You wouldn't even call.
Exactly, I'm not even
gonna deal with it
because I find it
so immature.
I didn't even wanna
talk to you at all.
All I did was ask you.
I talked to Lauren about it.
All I wanted was an answer...
You talked
to Lauren about it?
Okay,
and what happened when you
talked to Lauren?
Your best friend.
She said no.
She said no. Okay.
I wanted to talk to you.
I wanted to talk to you first.
I called her and you
at the same time.
You're pleading like you're
so innocent about this.
And it's not
only you, Audrina.
It's affected all of us.
It's like, I kind of lost
Lauren over it.
Yeah, that's great.
I don't know what's
gonna happen with us.
You know what?
I got to go, dude.
This is so stupid.
You put something
in your head,
and you think that
you really believe it,
when it's really fictitious.
Something's not
right there, dude.
♪♪
♪ I'm so sick of this static ♪
♪ Played out
it's over-dramatic ♪
♪ Give me a break
I won't have it ♪
♪ I'm so I'm so fed up
with this static...♪
- LAUREN: Hey, pretty girl.
Hi.
Hey, you.
I need coffee ASAP.
So, other than that...
What else is new?
I feel like I haven't
really talked to you
about the Audrina thing,
which is not really fun.
I kind of know a little bit.
No way.
I got a text
from Audrina.
Wow, that's amazing.
So what's, like...
your story?
I tried to talk to her
at my house.
She walked out, and...
it was like the most
awful conversation ever.
She wouldn't talk to me,
and I was like,
"You're crazy."
I was so mad at her,
that after knowing
me for years,
she still would
so quickly believe that.
That's because, like,
Justin, like, has hooked up
with Audrina's friends.
But me?
That's the part that sucks.
What did I do
not to be trusted?
After she moved out,
this happened?
It's just sad because we were
getting along really well.
You guys aren't gonna, like...
sit down again?
We're supposed to meet
tonight at Winston's.
But to be honest,
I don't think this is something
we're gonna come back from.
But, you can't let
that happen with Audrina.
Why would I want
a friend like that,
who doesn't even trust me?
This is so nuts.
♪ Look at what
you've done girl ♪
♪ You've made my world ♪
♪ So meaning ♪
♪ So meaningless ♪
♪ Look at what
you've done girl ♪
you've done girl ♪♪
- HEIDI:
Hello.
Hello, sweetheart.
How's my favorite babe?
Long day at work.
It's not like how it was before.
What, pre-party animal?
Yeah,
so I lost my office
and now I just have,
like, a little cubicle.
Oh, yeah,
it's really funny.
I think it's funny.
You couldn't understand
so I don't even
wanna talk about it.
How was your day?
Quite eventful.
Anything unusual happen?
You run into anyone,
or see anything, or...
Nope.
Really nice.
♪ There's angels and demons ♪
[door shuts]
♪ And somewhere between 'em ♪
♪ It's where we lie ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪♪
- CASEY:
Have you talked to Justin?
- AUDRINA:
Yeah.
He's upset that I would...
even ask.
He's kind of turned
it around like,
"Why would you think
I would ever do that?"
Aww.
It just keeps getting worse.
So I'm gonna go talk
to Lauren tonight at Winston's,
just to resolve things.
The last time I saw her,
I was, like, shaking, so mad.
Because it was fresh.
And the look she had
on her face,
she was looking at me
like I was hurting her.
I couldn't even stand
there and talk to her
so I just left.
I'm ready to talk now,
you know.
I've kind of...
Are you gonna apologize?
What's there
to apologize about?
What did I do?
Because she's all upset
that you accused her of it.
I didn't necessarily
accuse her of it.
But obviously I have to ask.
But it's not a big deal.
If someone asked you
something that's like,
completely absurd,
you'd be like, "No."
Yeah.
I think it's time
everyone needs to grow up.
Well, hopefully tonight,
I'll resolve things.
You just need closure.
♪ How ♪
♪ Did you know ♪
♪ We'll pretend ♪
♪ That you took me ♪
♪ Home again ♪
♪ But you know that ♪
♪ I don't want you to go ♪♪
Like, why would you do
something like that?
[indistinct chattering]
- AUDRINA:
Alright...
- LAUREN: You did.
I asked you.
You asked me several times,
and I told you
"No, no, no, no, no.
Someone made this up
and told you."
It's sad that
you don't believe me.
How would you feel
if someone told you this
and they go into detail?
What am I supposed to do?
I'm so, like, insulted
and hurt at the same time.
How do you think I felt
when I heard that?
You don't think I was hurt?
Do you understand
what you're accusing me of?
What was I supposed
to do? I asked you.
You're supposed
to believe me
because I'm your friend,
and I've never been
anything but to you.
Tell me what I've done to you
to make you think
I am capable of doing this?
- Yeah, I do.
Flirting?
Audrina, I would
rather kill myself
than hook up with him.
He is disgusting.
I didn't do anything!
Do you swear to God
that you didn't do that?
Oh, my God!
You needed to ask me,
and you did
and I told you I didn't,
and that's where it ends!
But I wanted to talk to you
in person.
Do you understand
that you did this?
I didn't do anything!
You're doing the same thing
you did to Heidi to me.
No, no, I... I'm not,
because you're
way worse than Heidi.
No, I'm [bleep] not!
[bleep] that!
You went and you did this.
And you know me!
You've known me for years,
and you don't know me that well?
♪ A change has come ♪
♪ A time undone ♪
♪ Like a little splinter ♪
♪ This is how the cold
has come ♪
♪ Without you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I didn't see it ♪
♪ Coming for me ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ I lost my way ♪
♪ And thought I'd find somehow ♪
♪ A way to make it all okay ♪
♪ But I'm far from it ♪
♪ So far ♪♪
[theme music]