You gotta bring some heels just
in case.
No, they said, they were like,
don't even bother
bringing heels
if you won't wear them.
So no one in Italy wears heels?
I guess not.
Hello! What are you taking?
I think you should bring
one fancy outfit
if you guys go
to a nice dinner.
(Lo)
'I'm jealous of your vacay.'
Audrina and I
are gonna have fun though.
Yeah, me and Lo will have
some bonding time.
Me and Audrina,
kicking it without you.
There.
- Okay, have so much fun.
- Love you guys.
- Don't burn the house down.
- E-mail us.
- And keep us updated.
- I will.
You guys have fun without me.
- Bye, Lauren!
- Bye!
- Bye, sweetie.
- Bye.
[instrumental music]
♪ I want it the way
I like it ♪
♪ So give it to me ♪♪
[phone rings]
- Hello? Hello?
- Audrina?
- 'Hi!'
- Hey, it's Stephanie.
- Um, Lauren's not here.
- Oh, I know.
I was wondering if I could
talk to you for a minute.
- Yeah, let me buzz you in.
- Okay. Thanks.
- 'Hey!'
- You look cute.
My God, you're so tan.
I laid out all weekend.
'Had strawberry mojitos
and laid out all day.'
- So how are you?
- I'm good. How are you?
We've been cooking a lot
this week, Lo and I.
- You and Lo?
- Yeah, we've been hanging out.
- Have you talked to Lauren?
- No, she's in Italy phoneless.
Like, we can't get
a hold of her.
Lo and I have both e-mailed her
but she hasn't responded, so...
'What's up with you?'
I need to tell you something.
Doug asked me
to go to dinner with him.
No eyebrow lifts.
He was just like, "Hey, Steph,
do you wanna go to dinner?"
If anything, I would wait
until Lauren gets back
to talk to her
before hanging out with him.
But like, I don't know,
like, what to say.
No, just be like, "Hey,
just to give you a heads-up."
Just you know, like,
I hope you don't care
that Doug asked me out.
[both laugh]
How would she find out? Like...
I don't know.
I would just be careful.
♪ I need ♪
♪ I need my reputation ♪
♪ I need my satisfaction ♪
♪ I need you
to check your brow ♪
♪ Don't need no false friend
by my side ♪
♪ I need my reputation ♪
♪ I need my satisfaction ♪
♪ I need you
to check your brow ♪♪
Did you get all that stuff?
- Yeah.
- Oh, good.
'I was just looking
at skate ramps.'
Whoo! So excited!
I think this is gonna be
one of my favorite events.
I feel like we're completely
set for it.
'I'm gonna bring Spencer,
I think.'
Yeah, 'cause we should be good,
I mean
once doors are open,
like two hours into it
we're cool to hang out,
you know?
- Yeah. Exactly.
- Do that.
You guys definitely need
to start going out more.
- You need to have fun together.
- I know.
'You know how it is
when you're a couple.'
You just get in kind of a rut
of not ever going out.
Oh, yeah, I think it always
happens when you start dating
someone seriously, you know?
But I think it's time
to get out there.
'And I think I'm even gonna
get him to go out tonight.'
It's like, we can stay in
when we're old.
Yeah, I 'm not really
into the whole staying-in thing
at all.
♪ So monochrome ♪
♪ I watched the color
drain from you ♪
♪ Where's the color
in this life ♪♪
This looks good.
Oh, we didn't, oh, wait,
you have silverware.
Yeah, I have silverware on mine.
I was like, no!
- I'm so thirsty!
- So am I.
Oh, wait, I have two knives.
- Oh, I have two forks.
- Trade. Thank you.
'So what's up
with you and Justin'
since he didn't come
the other night?
Did you guys, like,
figure it out?
Not really,
I mean, he apologized
and then, like,
I just kind of got over it.
I feel like at this age
you have to make
decisions for yourself.
Mm-hmm.
♪ La la la ♪♪
- We should go to Goa tonight.
- That would be fun.
I haven't been there in a while.
I was there a couple weeks ago.
Oh, I have to tell you
about Stephanie.
She came to the house
this morning to talk.
She's like about Doug.
- About Doug?
- Yeah.
- What did she say?
- I was like huh?
She's like,
I don't know if I should go
on a date with him or not.
- With Doug?
- I don't know.
Stephanie's going
on a date with Doug?
That's the biggest no-no,
like, with girlfriends.
You never go out with their ex.
I don't know.
I just never imagined them,
Stephanie and Doug.
Why would you want
sloppy seconds?
[upbeat music]
This big table
just for you and me.
You know what,
our friends will come.
- This drink is so good.
- Good.
It's a ginger...ginger lemonade.
I think so.
Really?
Oh, they're right there.
Hi!
Hi, how are you? Hi!
Surprise!
Like, I just wouldn't do that
to my friend, I don't know.
That's so weird.
- 'That would be fun!'
- Okay. Okay.
♪ Dream diva
when will you give up ♪
♪ Do you hear me ♪♪
Um, that's crazy.
Well, when's your next event
you got to do?
What's tonight?
Is that Heidi?
Alright, the wind just blew
something in here.
Tell her I say "Hi."
Love you. Bye.
What are you doing here?
- You don't know anything?
- I know nothing.
I don't have my ears
to the street anymore.
You know how I became friends
with Doug and stuff?
No, I didn't know you had
a new clique of friends.
- How's that working out?
- You haven't met Doug?
I met him
at your birthday party.
- Doug asked me to dinner.
- As friends?
'I think that is a date,
actually.'
LC's gonna gonna freak out.
I'll bet you anything. Trust me.
Look, like, if Lauren gets mad,
if she finds out
like, that we went
and had, like, dinner, then
you know, we're just gonna
tell her we're friends.
How small of a weird,
twisted, little world.
- 'That's crazy.'
- Yeah.
So are you a little nervous that
LC's gonna clip you
from her little posse?
I would be if I were you.
♪ So why'd you have to go ♪
♪ Is there something
I could say ♪
♪ To make you turn around ♪
♪ 'Cause nights
like these I wish ♪
♪ I'd said don't go ♪
♪ Is there anybody there ♪
♪ Can anybody help ♪
♪ To get me out of here ♪
♪ 'Cause you're walking down
a road that I can't go ♪♪
- That's Justin right there.
- 'Justin!'
How are you?
- Long time no see.
- Have a seat, my friend.
- What are you guys doing?
- 'Taking photos.'
Ah, the Hooligans. I like that.
- Hi!
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
Oh, I 'm so glad you came.
- Have you seen "Batman?"
- So good.
Joker. It should have
been called "Joker."
♪ All of you gossiping ♪
♪ Maybe you're just
a bad bad ♪
♪ Bad bad girl ♪
♪ Maybe you're just
a bad bad bad bad girl ♪♪
- Hi!
- What's up?
- Good to see you.
- You too.
You look pretty.
- Thank you.
- How's it going?
- Good.
- Yeah?
Okay, so what's going on
in your life?
What's going on in my life?
Nothing.
You see Brody a lot?
Yeah, he's a good buddy
of mine now.
- Really?
- 'Yeah.'
I-I know you and Brody
have your differences.
I'm staying out of that
you know, but whatever.
'Did you tell Brody
you were going to dinner?'
No.
'Did you tell Lauren?'
'Lauren's in Italy.'
- So she doesn't have her phone.
- Really?
Is it weird
that you dated Lauren?
'Not at all.'
What are you doing after this?
That's Brody's mom. Hi!
- 'How are you?'
- I'm good. How are you?
- Oh, my God. You look gorgeous.
- 'You look beautiful.'
- Nice to see you, sweetheart.
- I'm Doug.
I've talked to you on the phone.
- Oh, my God, you're Doug!
- Yes, I am.
- You look so pretty.
- Thank you. So do you.
You're just getting prettier.
- Are you guys on a date?
- No, we're friends.
'So what's happening here?'
- Just wondering.
- No, no, no.
- Nice meeting you finally.
- So nice to meet you, sweetie.
- I'll see you again.
- Very nice meeting you too.
Nice seeing you guys.
Wow. That's interesting.
It's not good.
♪ La la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la la ♪♪
Oh, my whole body is...
I got a massage yesterday,
you know that good kind of sore
where it's like everything
hurts, but...
- Drink a lot of water today.
- I'm trying.
Maybe coffee
isn't the best idea.
So what's going on?
- Lauren's been in Italy.
- That's awesome.
So Lo and I
had some bonding time.
How's that going?
'It's actually
going pretty good.'
I think it's kind of a good
thing that Lauren's away.
What are you guys doing?
We went to Goa and we ran
into Heidi and Spencer there.
She invited me
to this X Games party.
Does Lauren know you guys
have been hanging out?
'She's been in Italy
and we haven't been
able to get a hold of her.
Oh, my God,
and Stephanie came over
and asked me if she should
go on a date with Doug.
What?
Does Stephanie like Doug
or is she just...
That's what I asked her.
I think she's afraid
because no one really thinks
that Stephanie is trustworthy
of-of being Lauren's friend.
Right,
because she's Spencer's sister.
There are plenty of guys
that Stephanie can date
that aren't Lauren's
recent fling.
Yeah, it's just crazy
how all this is happening
while Lauren's gone.
♪ Hey you keep breathing ♪
♪ Keep breathing ♪
♪ Hey you
it will come back to you ♪♪
- 'Hello?'
- Loey.
Hi!
I'm so happy you're home!
I missed you!
I missed you back.
Where's Audrina?
- I don't know.
- 'I'm in here!'
- Oh, she's in the kitchen.
- I'm home!
♪ Bring your stuff bring
your stuff bring your stuff ♪♪
- Lauren, you're back!
- I'm back. How are you?
- I'm back early.
- I know!
Didn't you have, like,
two or three days left?
Yeah, I left two days early.
Why did you leave early?
I had seen all that
Italy had to offer.
Uh, no, actually, I saw a lot,
I learned a lot, it was so good.
So how are the boys
in Italy? Cute?
Um, you know like when you walk
by a construction site
and like, all the guys,
like, whistle at you?
Italy's kind of like
a construction site.
- Like everywhere you go?
- Really?
The guys there are very,
like, yeah.
(Lo)
'Well, we're glad you're back.'
So what did I miss?
Well, we went out
to Goa one night...
(Audrina)
'And then Heidi and Spencer
were there.'
They sat right behind us.
I'm Audrina. She's Heidi.
They sat this close to us.
I was like, hello.
It was very uncomfortable.
So we said hi.
'And Justin and I met up
with them last night.'
Surprise.
Very shocking.
So what else did I miss?
Um...
'Stephanie came over here.'
She wanted my advice
whether or not
she should go
on a date with Doug.
- My Doug?
- Your Doug.
What did you tell her?
I didn't really tell her
yes or no.
If she has to ask me,
like, she obviously knows
that that's probably not...
It, it has to be.
He has to be trying
to make you jealous.
- 'Yeah.'
- Do you know what I mean?
I just told her, I wouldn't
go there if I were you.
♪ Fake the moment ♪
♪ You don't even mean it ♪
♪ Don't even mean it, do you ♪♪
Finally get a little
dinner date.
- I know, it's been so long.
- It has been a long time.
- I've never been here.
- Neither have I.
Hello. How are you?
Thank you.
[sighs]
This is exciting.
What, that we're getting
Mexican food?
- It's been a while.
- I know.
So what up?
Italy was fun.
I heard some things happened
while you were gone.
What did you hear happened?
I just wanna look at you
and just be like
I told you so.
Wait, what are you
talking about?
The whole Doug-Stephanie thing.
It's kind of funny to me that
she really went and did that.
- So they did go out.
- This is how I found out.
We told him to come out with us,
he's like, I got to handle
a little business, you know,
a little business dinner
you know? No big deal.
He called it a business dinner?
You're gonna die.
My mom calls me up and goes
"I just met your friend Doug.
Why was he having dinner
with Stephanie?"
And I was like
"Come again, mom.
What did you say?"
I think it's kind of ironic,
don't you, kind of?
Are you pissed off about it?
Yeah.
She straight went
behind your back.
I know.
You don't think
that was wrong of Doug?
I think that guys will be guys
'but Stephanie's supposed
to be one of your best friends.'
I just don't wanna
see you get hurt.
You know.
♪ Don't long for the past ♪
♪ Long for what comes next ♪
At least, you know
what I was talking about.
She's shady.
♪ 'Cause when
you're not breathing ♪
♪ I beg for one more breath
with you ♪♪
[theme music]