(Holly)
'What are you guys
doing tonight?'
I think we're just gonna, uh,
cook some dinner.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know.
I kind of wanted
to go out, and...
Well, if I didn't have, like,
work tomorrow
I would go with you.
(Holly)
'Definitely need
to meet people.'
'I mean, the only people I know'
in this whole city
are you and...Lauren.
(Spencer)
'Yeah, you should totally
hang out with Lauren.'
She's really cool.
Have you talked to her
or anything?
Uh, no, I actually haven't.
I tried to keep in touch
with her
'but I just lose touch
with people.'
I don't know, I know that you
guys were, like, really close
for a long time, but...
'Now it's a little
awkward, but...'
That... I don't know.
I can't, like, tell you...
- Who to hang out with.
- 'I can.'
While you're living
under this roof
there's no Lauren,
fraternizing, socializing...
(Holly)
'Well, it would definitely be'
'nice to see a familiar face.'
There's 15 million people
in LA
and she's saying how she wants
to go hang out with Lauren.
'I need to get out of here.'
It's always a pleasure.
♪ Don't give it up ♪
♪ Don't let it down ♪
♪ Don't ever stop ♪
♪ You're a rock
and roll star ♪
♪ Don't give it up ♪
♪ Don't let it down ♪
♪ Don't ever stop ♪♪
Um...
- What kind of muffin is that?
- I don't know.
- So good...
- Wonderful goodness.
Crumbly.
'How are things with Audrina?'
Things actually have gotten
a lot better.
Really? That's good to hear.
I think that that happens a lot
with your friends, you know?
- Up and downs.
- It's bound to.
- Yeah.
- [cell phone ringing]
- 'So random.'
- What?
- Holly...
Heidi's sister just texted me.
That's so weird.
- Yeah.
- What did she say to you?
'She said
she's living here now...'
...and that
she wanted to see me.
Huh. So how do you feel
about seeing her?
I mean, I'd love to see her.
I just... I'm so reluctant
because of the past.
- Of course.
- 'But I love her.'
She was one
of my really good friends.
So then maybe you might
as well see her
and see what she
has to say, you know?
No, I'd love to,
I just don't wanna
cause more problems.
Could always use more friends
in the city, you know?
Doesn't hurt anybody.
It would just help
if some of them weren't related
to people I didn't
get along with.
Seriously.
You can't escape from it.
That's just the way it goes.
♪ Life ♪
♪ Life ♪♪
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
Hi.
Okay, I'll be right in.
Knock, knock.
Hi. How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- 'Good.'
Have you ever met
"The White Tie Affair?"
I've never met 'em but I've
heard of them
just from the label.
We have a showcase
at the Roosevelt
tomorrow with them.
It's like, big, big deal
'because it's the band's
first time in LA'
'and we need to pump up
their new album.'
So we need to make sure
that runs smoothly
'and Chiara can't be there,
so I'm gonna need you'
'there to be my right hand.'
Anything I need you for, like,
you just kind of...
...and you just
have to be focused.
And it's a big deal because
Charlie Walk, the President
of Epic's gonna be there.
I need you there to make sure
that we have all the guests
in there before the band comes,
before Charlie comes
'so it looks full
when he gets there.'
And then we're gonna have
an after party
and you're just the Epic girl.
Kind of be there
for everything.
- Exactly.
- Okay.
'It's just really important'
that it goes on point.
We have
to run a very tight ship
especially this one.
- I'll have it under control.
- Yeah. Alright.
- Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
♪ She only dances to ♪
♪ Rock steady ♪
♪ Rock steady steady steady ♪
♪ Steady ♪♪
[gasps]
- Oh, my goodness.
- Oh, my...
How are you?
Oh, it's been forever.
- Look at you!
- I know.
You look so pretty.
Thank you. You do too.
(Lauren)
'It's so great to see you.'
- I miss you. What's up?
- 'I miss you too.'
'How long have you been back
in LA?'
I just moved back.
And you, like, have
an apartment and everything?
Um, I live with Heidi
and Spencer right now.
Fun stuff.
[chuckles]
Yeah, it's, uh
it's definitely crowded.
They, uh... It's...
I don't know
if it's working out too well.
But yeah, I've been meaning
to call you forever and ever.
Like, I don't want the whole
Heidi and Spencer thing
to affect our friendship,
you know?
'I mean,
it obviously has no effect'
'on, like,
the way I look at you at all'
but I had just gone through
all this stuff with Stephanie
and honestly, it's been really
difficult for both of us.
It's, like, obviously not cool
to break up, like, friends
but, like, family, is like,
that's family.
That's your blood.
You don't mess with that.
I don't ever want to put someone
in that position again.
Right.
And I, I asked Heidi about it.
She was talking about
how lately she's just been
feeling overwhelmed with how...
...bad everything turned out
with you guys.
I was just thinking last night,
we had the best times.
We were like
"The Three Musketeers."
I miss it.
- Yeah.
- So fun.
Well, now that you're here
call me anytime
you wanna, like, chill.
Yeah, it's so nice to be able
to talk to you
and I have your number now
and...hopefully I'll
get to see you more.
[upbeat music]
♪ Oh this couldn't be ♪
♪ The only chance we get ♪
♪ We gotta take it
don't do it now ♪
♪ We'll never make it ♪
♪ Lose this crowd ♪♪
This is cute.
I've never been here.
I know.
You look really pretty tonight.
Like that dress.
- It's a skirt.
- Oh, yeah, wow.
(Justin)
'Cool mini.'
So how is everything?
How's the situation?
- Good, things are better now.
- Good.
I feel like Lauren and Lo are
really trying to make an effort.
They are?
- And I am too.
- That's good.
'Trying to, like,
squash the tension'
which a lot of it is,
it feels so much better now.
You're really good
at accepting people again.
- You know what I mean?
- Like you?
Yeah, but our situation...
- 'It's different.'
- Way different.
I just think it's bad
to hold grudges.
So did you get my text
about "The White Tie Affair?"
- Do you wanna go?
- The band?
'Yeah, I'm in charge
of the guest list'
'for tomorrow night.'
- You're invited.
- Yeah, maybe. I'll try.
I really want you to be there.
If it's gonna benefit you,
I'll go, for sure.
- Okay.
- It'll be fun.
Well, thank you.
It'll be fun.
[instrumental music]
♪ Whoa whoa ♪
♪ You got a friend ♪
♪ A friend in me ♪♪
[indistinct]
(Audrina)
'A tea bag with caffeine.'
- Here, English.
- Does that have caffeine in it?
- Unless it says caffeine-free.
- Do you want one?
It'll say, yeah. Thanks.
What do you got going on today?
'Work, um, have you heard
of this band called...'
- "The White Tie Affair?"
- Yeah.
'Tonight they're having like,
a private showcase'
so if you want to come...
- I wanna come.
- It'll be fun.
If you want to bring anyone,
you can.
'Cause it's my job
to pack the place
'Alright, well...'
So I got to get people in there.
I'll bring Lo and Steph.
'Okay.'
And there's an after party.
- Where is it at?
- The Roosevelt.
I invited Justin and he said
he's definitely coming.
- Yay.
- 'I know.'
Well, that's good.
He's been, like,
super-supportive lately.
I think that
he's always gonna be there
for you in that way.
Yeah.
So how's Stephanie lately?
'She's good.
She's been kind of busy.'
Speaking of sisters, I did...
...a lunch with, um,
with Holly yesterday.
- She's back in town.
- Heidi's sister?
- 'Yeah.'
- Wow.
- It's kind of weird, Steph...
- I know.
- Then Holly...
'She doesn't have
too many friends'
'in the city, so...'
- Is she moving here?
- Yeah.
I think she's living
in their apartment.
- With Heidi and Spencer?
- Yeah.
I think it's a good thing
that she moved here.
I don't think
it'll be good for her
I think it'll actually be
good for Heidi.
Because Holly's
a good influence.
Sometimes friendships are even
harder than relationships.
'As we're learning.'
♪ We kept what we want ♪
♪ And there's no two ways
about it ♪
♪ No two ways about it ♪
♪ It's like a freight train ♪
♪ Hurricane ♪
♪ Can't get around it ♪
♪ I hope you can crash ♪
♪ Imma drag you down with me ♪
♪ There's no turning back ♪♪
(Audrina)
'Everything's set.
The list is good?'
I mean,
there's still people coming
but they haven't
arrived yet, so...
But it's, like, right now
'we have a good crowd,
we could start.'
Cool. Well, Charlie's in the
back with the band. Let's go.
♪ We want to let it happen ♪
♪ We want to ♪♪
I need everyone close.
Little focus.
Little treat. Focus.
Okay, so, we're in LA.
It's your first time here.
The girls put together
an amazing group
'of 250 select kids'
'that love music and wanna
see you kick their ass.'
So thanks to you guys.
- Let's go do it.
- Alright, so grab a shot.
- 'To "The White Tie Affair..."'
- '"The White Tie Affair."'
'First LA Look.'
(male #1)
'Ladies and gentlemen'
'"The White Tie Affair."'
(Chris Wallace)
What's up, Los Angeles?
Put your hands in the air!
Come on!
♪ Gonna rock the floor
gonna dance to the tempo ♪
♪ Da da da
gonna rock the floor ♪
♪ Gonna dance to the tempo ♪
♪ She was thinking Mr. Right ♪
♪ I was thinking right now ♪
♪ Contemplating over it ♪
♪ Over and over again
she was thinking Mr. Right ♪
My friends are here.
I'm gonna go get them.
♪ Thinkin' right now
contemplating over it ♪
♪ Over and over again
Mr. Right ♪
Hey!
- I'm so glad you guys made it.
- Of course!
(Lo)
'Hi, sweetie!'
(Audrina)
Thanks for coming, Lo.
♪ There's gonna be a be a ♪
♪ Oh a party tonight ♪
They're really good.
♪ Oh oh oh
I was thinking right now ♪
♪ Contemplating over it ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ She was thinking Mr. Right ♪
♪ I was thinking right now ♪
♪ Contemplating over it ♪
♪ Over and over again ♪
♪ She was thinking Mr. Right ♪
♪ I was thinking right now ♪
♪ Contemplating over it ♪
♪ Over it over it ♪
♪ She was thinking Mr. Right ♪
♪ I was thinking right now ♪♪
[cheering]
[instrumental music]
♪ I've been feeling ♪
♪ Like everything is ♪
♪ Going downhill ♪
♪ And I don't ♪
♪ Wanna fall off this edge ♪♪
- Hello.
- 'Hi.'
- Where's Spencer?
- I don't know.
- I haven't seen him.
- Hm.
How was your day?
What'd you do?
Not much. Just, uh,
out and about, looking for jobs.
- 'Oh, yeah?'
- Mm-hm.
Haven't seen you, I feel,
like, in forever.
What'd you do yesterday?
'I went to some
little bistro place.'
I actually,
um, I went with Lauren.
Really, you're my best friend
and my sister
and you didn't
wanna tell me, you just
kinda went behind
my back and did that?
I don't know anybody here, Heidi
and it's not like I'm trying
to keep anything from you.
I mean, I'm just seeing you now
for the first time, and...
Yeah, but how am I supposed
to feel about that?
You guys are both
like little sisters to me.
- It's like...
- But I am your little sister.
'And you know that my loyalty
is always to you.'
- Do I?
- Yes. No matter what.
'So can I not
tell you things now?'
- Can I not trust you anymore?
- Heidi...
You should know me
better than that.
- I know, I know.
- I just can't...
It's just this whole thing
has been really hard for me.
It's hard for me to hear even
that you went to lunch with her.
It's kinda... I don't know.
You know me, and you know
that...
...I was there, if anything,
mostly for you.
- I know.
- Nothing's beyond repair.
[instrumental music]
I could tell
that she misses you.
♪ Let's get started come on ♪
♪ Kick the party ♪
♪ Let's get rolling ♪
♪ Come on come on ♪
♪ Kick the party ♪
♪ Let's get started ♪
♪ Let's get rolling ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Kick the party ♪♪
Got all the piercings and stuff.
I got my lip pierced,
took it out, ears.
Only thing I still have left
is my ears
and my nipples are pierced.
You're lying.
Your nipples are not pierced.
'Let me see.'
Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
What was wrong with you
growing up?
You're just like a rebel.
You have a tattoo.
Yeah, one tattoo.
What's the difference?
You're talking
all that stuff to me?
[instrumental music]
♪ That's how I live ♪
♪ Fast in the lane ♪
♪ Searching for fortune
and fame ♪♪
Is Justin coming?
He, um...
I don't know what he's doing.
Way to be a buzz kill.
[guitar music]
♪ Ah ♪♪
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ It's a party ♪
♪ I'm feeling naughty ♪
♪ Baby this is my life ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ It's a party ♪
♪ I'm feeling naughty ♪♪
- Hey, you.
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- Good.
How was it?
Everything ended up
going smoothly.
Did it feel like it was
something that
like you could totally handle?
Yeah, it was...
I, you know.
The guys are cool.
They're such fun guys.
- Oh, I met Charlie Walk.
- That's insane though.
It was like your first time
being by yourself
and Charlie was in town.
- And you weren't there.
- And I wasn't there.
And then they had
an after party.
- Oh, really? At the Roosevelt?
- 'Yeah.'
'By the pool at the Roosevelt.'
They told me I could invite
a few friends, so...
- Who'd you invite?
- I invited, um, Lauren...
And she brought Lo
and Stephanie.
- And then I invited Justin.
- Did Justin go?
No. I didn't even
hear back from him.
- You didn't at all?
- No.
What's going on with that?
I feel like I give,
give, and give.
- 'But he never gives back.'
- Right.
You, like, know not to invest
your feelings.
I know not to invest
my feelings in anything
that I invite him
to or anything at all.
'He needs to act like he cares'
'and not play Mr. Cool Guy
all the time'
and just make
more of an effort.
Do you have, still,
like that kind of
chemistry though
when you're together?
Yeah, we do,
but he just doesn't
show that he actually cares.
So, can't change people.
♪ I will have you inside ♪
♪ Like a flame ♪
♪ That will not die ♪
♪ With a love that ♪
♪ Will not fade ♪♪
(Lauren)
Oh, so I forgot to tell you
that I had lunch with Heidi's
sister yesterday.
Oh, yeah,
I remember Heidi told me
that you guys were, like,
best best friends.
It was great. She's just like
the most, like, positive person.
- She's cool.
- So wait.
- Did Holly call you?
- Holly texted me.
I didn't even know
she'd been back.
Obviously, just because
of everything
I went through, like, with you
I'm a little, like,
reluctant to bounce back
to the way we were 'cause I feel
like, I... You know what I mean?
You think Spencer and Heidi
are gonna do
what they did to me to her?
It's just scary
that she lives with them.
[instrumental music]
My sister went out to lunch
with Lauren the other day.
Did she know Lauren before,
like, when you guys were...
Yeah, we were all friends.
It was like
"The Three Musketeers"
for a while, and we were all
hanging out and we were
all together, so I'm not gonna
say "Don't be friends with her."
It just makes me so sad.
- Well, I mean, it's not like...
- You know?
Yeah, 'cause it's not all bad...
'No, Lauren and I had this
little time of fighting'
but we had years
of a friendship.
We were best friends
for years.
I never even had a best friend
like that.
It's just so unfortunate how...
...things have ended
in our lives
and how we don't have our
friendship anymore
'because she didn't like
my boyfriend.'
And then I said things
out of anger
that I didn't...mean.
I don't know.
Maybe Holly will, like...
...peace everything out,
or I don't know.
It also makes me nervous
because hanging out with her
kinda makes me remember,
like, how much fun
we all used to have together.
'I think
that she feels the same way.'
I just really don't want her
to get it in her head
that she's gonna like fix it.
Maybe one day, by...
...you know, like a miracle
we'll be friends again.
Did seeing Holly
make you miss Heidi?
Yeah.
You always miss a best friend.
Who knows? Maybe one day...
♪ Love has brought us pain ♪
♪ But we will stand again ♪
♪ Just don't forget ♪
♪ Taught me to believe in you ♪
♪ Love has brought us pain ♪
♪ But we will stand again ♪
♪ Just don't forget ♪
♪ Taught us to believe ♪
♪ Taught us ♪
♪ To believe ♪♪
[theme music]