(Whitney)
'Let's move it out here
so it's not in the way.'
Ooh, these got all messed up.
How's it going with Lo
and Audrina at the house?
The same,
we're gonna throw a party
for her birthday
this week, though.
Oh, fun.
Yeah, Lo's helping,
so hopefully it will
'smooth things out at home.'
Oh, and guess what?
I've got a date tonight.
- I know.
- A date!
Where did you meet him?
Tell me everything.
I kind of dated him,
when I was 18.
Like, did he go
to your high school?
No, he went to
a different school.
- I went to his prom with him.
- Oh, my gosh.
And I ran into him...
...last Thursday.
- That is such a small world.
- I know, right?
So, what's his name, this guy?
Doug.
Doug. Doug.
- Doug's such a funny name.
- I know.
I don't even want to talk
about him too much.
I feel like I'm gonna,
like, jinx it.
Yeah. Fair enough.
The last guy I dated, like
more than like one date,
really, was Brody.
And that was when Heidi
and Spencer set us up.
'That's how long
it's been for me.'
- Little bit of a slump.
- I was like, it's about time.
♪ We're almost almost there ♪
♪ Oh almost feel
it in the air ♪
♪ We're almost almost
there oh almost ♪
♪ See it everywhere
we're almost ♪♪
Did I tell you that, um
my sister's coming to town?
Oh, no. Cool.
- When's she coming in?
- Tonight.
- For how long?
- Just for the weekend.
Are you, like, you sound
like you're not excited.
I mean, it's like the worst
time ever 'cause it's, like
Spencer just moved back in
and we're trying
to work things out
'and I haven't told
him she's coming.'
Yeah, might be a good idea
to tell him sooner than later.
Right, and she doesn't
know that he's there
'cause I haven't really
had time to tell her
like, "Oh, Spencer
moved back in."
It's not like
you planned it out
and, you know,
purposely didn't tell him.
I know, I'm just gonna, like
leave work early,
race home, and be like...
- Just a "By the way?"
- Right.
- That's the way I'd pitch it.
- What's the big deal?
As you're like inflating
the air mattress.
Right, exactly. She's coming!
♪ Sound the alarm
sound the alarm ♪
♪ Ready go ♪
♪ Sound the alarm
sound the alarm ♪♪
Oh, my God.
What are you doing
this weekend?
I am house hunting.
'Why? What do you have going?'
My birthday is coming up.
And on Sunday,
Lauren wants to have, like
a pool party, like barbecue.
Lauren's throwing you
a birthday party?
Yeah.
- That's gonna be interesting.
- I know.
'She is making an effort.'
Is she throwing it to maybe
try to release the tension?
Mm-hmm.
I mean, I don't know if
Lo's gonna be in on it, but...
How's that going?
Is there still...
I don't know.
Lo's always super bitchy.
That's just how she is.
♪ And I'm reawakened ♪
♪ Then when we're aging ♪
♪ And in the one
you've become ♪♪
[door closes]
- 'Hi.'
- Hi.
'Yay.'
- 'How are you?'
- 'Good. How are you?'
Good.
Oh, I'm so excited to see you.
So excited to see you.
You're a little early.
(Holly)
'I just got in
a little bit ago.'
I'm gonna let you ladies
catch up with each other.
Um...
'I better check on him
for a sec.'
- Do you want water or anything?
- I'm fine.
Okay, well,
make yourself at home.
I'll be right back.
'She'll just be here
for, like, two days.'
(Spencer)
'I mean, I'm just saying we're
just trying to put things back'
'together, and do you think
all this, like...'
That's my sister.
Like, what am I supposed to...
Nothing. It's too late now.
- Just please be nice.
- That's my middle name.
♪ Give me your attention ♪
♪ I'll show you all
the pleasures of Soho ♪
♪ Give me your worst
intentions ♪♪
(Lo)
'Hey, date girl.'
- Hey, Lo-face.
- Hi. Are you so excited?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yay.
That's so fun.
Your dress is pretty.
- Thank you.
- I would totally date you.
Would you?
Would you ask me out again?
I don't know.
'If it goes well,
you should invite him'
'to Audrina's birthday.'
'I think you and Audrina should
have a fun night tonight.'
Yeah, well...
[doorbell rings]
- Does that mean he's here?
- Yeah. I should get ready.
Okay, I'm gonna hide.
Good luck.
- 'Hello.'
- Hey, babe, how are you?
- Good to see you.
- You, too. Ready?
Yeah. I'm ready.
♪ Just a matter of time ♪
♪ Before I'm gonna make you ♪
♪ Make you mine ♪♪
- Are you hungry?
- I'm starving.
'Are you adjusting well to LA?'
Yeah.
That's good.
'Do you remember?'
Do you remember every time
I used to drive by your house
I would call you to come out?
And I'd pull over
on the side of the road.
How much of a dork was I?
I was like
"I'm driving by. Come out."
I do remember that.
That was a long time ago.
♪ Smile ♪
♪ You take my breath away ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ And you smile ♪♪
So, what have you been doing
the last four years
of your life?
I don't know, I feel like
because I haven't seen you
for four years, we have like
'four years to catch up
on over dinner.'
(male #1)
'Can I start you off
with something to drink?'
Yeah, can I get
a Fuzzy Dragon, please?
- 'Fuzzy Dragon?'
- Mm-hmm.
- What kind of beer do you have?
- 'Beer-wise, we have Stella.'
I'll have that.
I'll have a Stella.
Thank you.
I think your drink
says a lot about you.
So, what does a beer
say about me?
That you're a guy's guy.
- Is that a good thing?
- Mm.
[laughs]
Well, you still look gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Can we do this again sometime?
'Actually, we're having
a birthday party'
'at my house this weekend.'
You can meet some of my friends.
- Really?
- 'Yeah.'
Oh, that'll be fun.
Whose birthday?
'It's for my roommate, Audrina.'
'Is she a good friend
of yours?'
Yeah, she's one
of my best friends.
Well, sure. Tell me when
and I'll be there.
- 'I'm so glad you're here.'
- 'Me too.'
- Where's Spencer?
- I don't know.
Does he want some breakfast,
do you think?
We wake up a lot
later than you.
- 'Really?'
- You're like early bird.
- We are late birds.
- 'Yeah.'
'Good morning.'
- Good morning.
I made some breakfast.
Do you want some, Spencer?
- Is that breakfast right there?
- Yeah.
This one's just for you.
Uh, that would be a pass.
Thank you very much.
'I'm not even hungry yet.'
'Why don't you try
to be nice to my sister?'
Because she's trying to be nice,
and cook you breakfast.
Why don't you mind
your own business?
Because this is my business
and that's my sister
and you're being rude.
- Don't wake me up.
- Don't sleep in until Twelve.
(Holly)
'Some of these dishes look
like they've been in here'
'for a month or so.'
Alright, well, you two
ladies have a great day.
I'm going back to bed.
Goodnight.
He's so rude.
I'm so embarrassed. I'm sorry.
- It's alright.
- He's just grumpy.
♪ Check it check it ♪
♪ Don't wreck it wreck it ♪
♪ Sit back and get connected
and check it check it ♪
♪ Don't wreck it wreck it ♪
♪ Let's get this
feel perfected ♪♪
Oh, fiesta!
Are you guys wearing
matching jerseys?
'We went to the Laker game.
Duh!'
- Oh, happy birthday!
- Thank you.
- Ooh, ooh.
- Whoa, there.
Whoa, what's up with you?
I can't even look
at you two right now.
You're such dorks.
- Jerry! Hi!
- How are you, honey?
'Good. How are you?'
'Ooh! Ooh!'
Hi. Thank you.
'We got you some gifts.'
Thank you.
- I'm gonna do this later.
- Okay, what could I help with?
Um, I think we're just putting
everything out right now, so...
(Doug)
'Alright,
I'll go fire up the grill.'
- Thank you, Dougy.
- 'No worries.'
We're gonna be out there
in just a bit.
- I just want to finish up here.
- Alright, you finish up.
I feel bad,
we were supposed to be done
before everyone got here.
(Lo)
'There's so many people.'
Be friendly. Be my charming
Lo that I know and love.
Do you want 23 candles
or 23 and one for luck?
- Twenty three and one for luck.
- Okay.
(Lo)
'So, um, who did you
invite, Audrina?'
I invited Justin.
I don't know if he's coming.
I invited... It's, like, people
that, like, I go out with.
That whenever I'm not here.
'You guys are like,
"Where is she going?"'
Well...
We're just gonna have to enjoy
the company that comes.
[rock music]
(Holly)
'LA makeover!'
Whoo!
Oh, this is gonna be so cool.
You didn't even tell mom
and dad about all this stuff
with you and Spencer, have you?
I don't need them knowing
every detail of my relationship.
Yeah, but it's just, like,
you used to tell mom everything.
Yeah, and then you grow up.
'You know, I don't always
want my family all'
in my relationship
like that, you know?
'I would think that you
guys would trust me.'
- We do trust you.
- Right.
When was the last time
that you saw Lauren?
A long time.
You don't even
miss her a little?
I don't know.
What happens, happens.
What are you thinking about?
I'm just concerned 'cause
I just don't want you to have
to sacrifice anything else
for your relationship.
- I'm not.
- Yeah.
[crowd cheering]
- Happy birthday, sweetheart.
- Thank you.
- You want to go in the pool?
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
Sit down, hang out with me
for just two seconds.
- So many people.
- I know.
- I haven't even got to see you.
- I'm sorry. I'm the host.
Yes, you're the host.
I was the cook.
Thank you for cooking.
Oh, my gosh. Take this.
I've got to go find Lo.
♪ How far can we make it ♪
♪ How long ♪♪
(all)
Cheers!
♪ How hard can we fall
to love somebody ♪
- Hi.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- Where have you been?
'I haven't seen you in,
like, an hour.'
'I was upstairs,
playing with the dog.'
- What?
- You haven't been down here.
I need you down here.
I just don't know
any of Audrina's friends.
'Yeah, me either,
but this is the part'
where we need
to make an effort.
Otherwise, it's just,
it's not gonna get better.
I feel like
we are making an effort
and I feel like it's not
reciprocated on her end.
'We've been in the kitchen all
day, like, doing stuff for her.'
'Please don't leave.'
- Lo, I'm in the same position.
- Yeah, I know.
But it's just uncomfortable.
- So, I'm done.'
- Okay.
I'm not gonna be put in this
situation again.
You have cake on your dress.
And I have cake on my dress.
[cheering]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
You don't seem good.
No, I'm just stressed
because Lo and Audrina
aren't getting along.
I had a feeling.
And I've hardly hung out
with Doug at all.
This is a disaster.
- So, what are you gonna do?
- I don't really know.
Maybe they shouldn't be friends.
But does that mean, like,
it all ends?
- Do you want it to all end?
- No.
I just...
I want us to be like
we used to be, you know?
♪ Don't let go ♪♪
♪ Wake me up ♪
♪ Before I crash and burn ♪♪
I can't believe It's time
to go home already.
- I know. It's been so fun.
- Yeah.
I had the best time
of my whole life.
I know. You're all
hollywood-makeovered out.
I know. I don't even
wanna go home yet.
- Like, I just miss you so much.
- 'I know.'
When I'm at home, I'm like...
Well, hopefully you can come
out more, you know?
Maybe I should
just move out here.
- 'Oh, really?'
- Yeah.
Like, I don't really have
anything going on right now
in Colorado, and maybe
it's time for a change.
- I don't know.
- Where would you stay?
I haven't thought about it yet,
but maybe I could just stay here
for a little while
until I figure it out.
- 'Yeah, we'll figure it out.'
- 'Okay, well.'
- 'I love you so much.'
- I love you.
- Call me when you get back.
- Spencer.
- Thank you for everything.
- 'My pleasure.'
[scoffs]
- I love you.
- 'I love you.'
Bye.
That was a fun trip.
- What's that look?
- "Yeah, it's cool.
You can stay here.
We'll figure it out."
Why would you say that?
Because that's my sister.
What would you want me to say?
Why wouldn't you say,
"We'll find you an apartment?"
Why can't she just stay with
us for, like, a week or two?
You know it's not gonna be
for a week or two.
- Yes, it will.
- It's ridiculous.
[mellow music]
How was the barbecue that
you and Lo threw for Audrina?
I mean, she wasn't there
for very much of it.
Lo wasn't there,
or Audrina wasn't there?
Lo.
She didn't wanna be
a part of it?
It was really awkward for her
to be there.
She's trying, you know? And
I feel bad because I love Lo.
And I'm really, like making her
jump through hoops for Audrina.
And she just, she doesn't owe
Audrina anything.
No. Not at all.
So, like, Lo went upstairs...
And just, like, shut herself
out out of the party?
I'm like, I needed, like,
another team member there.
What about Doug?
Wasn't Doug there?
- Oh, Doug was there.
- Is that a whole another story?
I felt bad because
he came over.
He was so nice to everybody.
He cooked for everybody.
I was really stressed about Lo
and Audrina and all this stuff.
And I was, like, completely
ignoring him. I felt so bad.
Such a frustrating situation.
'But I told Lo that
she had to talk to Audrina'
"cause I can't
take this anymore.'
[rock music]
[knocking on door]
(Audrina)
'Come in.'
- Hi.
- 'Hi.'
- How are you.
- Good, how are you?
Good.
You haven't been in here, huh?
'You can have a seat.
There's only pillows on here.'
- How are you?
- 'Good.'
That's good. Did you have fun
at the party on Sunday?
Oh, it was crazy. At one point,
I had to go in the front yard
just to get away from everyone.
Yeah, I know. It was fun.
Um, actually,
I wanted to talk to you.
I wanted to apologize. I was
kind of absent at your birthday.
Um, like, the issue is that,
you know
we all moved in with the idea
that we were all gonna be
'friends and our relationship
was gonna grow.'
- And it just hasn't happened.
- It hasn't happened at all.
I feel like we've tried,
though, and you, like
haven't given
very much back to us.
I know. I just don't feel
like I click with you.
Like, I feel like I'm kind
of always on the outside.
I don't think that
I put you on the outside.
I know, like, you and Lauren
have grown up together
and have been friends,
and I think I was just
so used to always like, you know
Lauren and I always
being in the apartment.
'We'd tell each other
everything.'
No, I completely agree
but, I mean
I feel like the blame
is being put on me
for the reason
that you and Lauren
are drifting apart.
And I just, like,
don't think that's fair.
I don't know. It just seems
like there's an attitude.
'Like, I just go on vibes
and tension'
'and energy people give off.'
And now, I'm to the point where
it's like I don't care about
really, really overly
trying anymore.
Yeah, I know. I just, like...
There's like a strong part of me
that like
really wants to be
friends with you.
And I think that Lauren wants
you guys' relationship to like
get better and for you guys
to, you know
get back to the point
where you were.
I just feel like I have friends
that actually treat me good.
And I feel included, and it's,
like, you don't do that.
'I feel like we're
really making an effort'
and if you don't want to like,
put as much back...
'Cause it's just like
I just don't care.
'We'll never be friends.'
Okay.
I'm gonna leave you
to your place.
[pop music]
♪ I tried to make this easy ♪
♪ I tried to understand
you keep it under cover ♪
♪ You keep it if you know ♪
♪ When I see you around ♪
♪ Don't say anything ♪
♪ I see through all the lies ♪
♪ When I see you around ♪
♪ Don't say anything ♪
[theme music]