- 'Lauren, are you home?'
- Yeah, I'm upstairs in my room.
Okay.
Hello. This is so cute.
You guys have little pictures
everywhere.
Yeah, we do that for fun.
We did, like, silly pictures,
though, so it wasn't, like...
- Posey-like.
- 'Yeah, like, cheesy.'
Kissy faces.
- Um, what's up?
- 'Remember Cory?'
The Australian?
I hung out with him all weekend.
And that's it.
- 'Justin was like...'
- How was that?
It was fun. I really like him.
- He was, like, a good guy.
- He's a really good guy.
- We're having dinner tonight.
- 'Good.'
- Wait.
- I didn't tell Justin about it.
He's just like, well,
why didn't you call me back?
Like, I texted you, called you.
Like, I was busy having fun.
It's like I wanna
give more attention to Cory
but then Justin
always makes me feel guilty.
He gets mad at me, but he
can't really get mad at me
'cause we're not together.
I've totally been there
with a guy
where, like,
I didn't really like him.
I totally took him for granted
and then as soon as he,
like, got a girlfriend
or did something else,
I was like, wait a minute.
Then you wanted him back.
So maybe that's how
Justin will feel about you.
I don't know.
He's a weird one.
He's... I don't get him.
- But that's why you like him.
- I know.
You don't want a normal one.
They're no fun.
- Normal is not fun.
- 'No way.'
♪ There's a reason why
you're gonna be a star ♪
♪ And it's easy to see
that you're gonna go far ♪
♪ Great hair great face ♪
♪ And great skin ♪
♪ You're so amazing ♪
♪ With your sprayed-on smile ♪
♪ You're full of grace ♪
♪ You're the reason they all ♪
♪ Want a perfect face ♪
♪ Great lips great legs
and that's all ♪♪
- Hey.
- What's up? What's up?
Must be really important
for you to call me.
What's up?
It's just insane.
'I don't know
who I dislike more'
Heidi's sister
or her mom right now.
Her mom came in town?
Oh, her mom came in town
and started lighting me up.
She was like, "I think you're
"manipulative and controlling
and Heidi doesn't tell me"
"all the details
of her life anymore."
I'm like,
settle down, stalker mom.
Oh my God!
And then Holly is just like
the mooch of the century.
I have to, like, spend my day
in a coffee shop
because Holly's
on my office all day long.
Is she looking
for a new place?
No. She doesn't
even leave the condo.
I can't even imagine
disliking a sister more.
This should make you feel good.
That's like a demented
compliment, but thanks.
Oh, and then Holly
must've talked Heidi
into writing
LC some apology letter
and, like, let's make peace.
- What'd the letter say?
- Oh, I didn't know about it.
I didn't even get to read it
or spell-check it.
No, it's the first secret
she's ever kept from me.
Holly is really throwing
some wrenches in this machine.
Spencer, you can't go to war
with someone's family
who you wanna marry.
They already started the war
when they came out here
and bombed me like Pearl Harbor
the other night.
- Okay, then put up the flag.
- No, I'm out.
It's not worth it
'cause every time I say, like
Holly, move out, Heidi's like
"Don't listen to him.
Spencer, stop. Don't be..."
'Cause you guys
are doing it wrong.
You can't ask her to move out.
Heidi's got to be the one.
'Just talk to Heidi.'
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ He was stuck in the middle ♪
♪ But there's nobody in it ♪
♪ Stuck in the middle
but there's nobody in it ♪
♪ You can take chances
on everyone like I do ♪♪
(Whitney)
'I need the weekend to come.'
- 'You need the what?'
- The weekend to come.
What are you up to?
I may be...
...taking advantage of the nice
weather and going to Malibu.
Ooh.
If you wanna come,
we're gonna go
I think Saturday, to a party.
- That sounds fun.
- A during-the-daytime pool one.
Who's coming?
Audrina will be there with...
...I'm assuming, Cory.
Which one's Cory?
You met Cory, actually,
last year at Halloween.
- Oh, the Australian guy.
- The really cute guy.
Oh, she's seeing Cory again?
Well, she was seeing Colin,
then Colin didn't work out
so she went back to Justin,
but then she ran into Cory
but Justin's never, like,
really left the picture, so...
Mmm.
It'll either be Justin or Cory.
Alright, well,
I'll be looking forward
to seeing either one of them.
- Wanna be my date?
- So there.
[laughs]
I actually
really like Cory a lot.
You like him
better than Justin?
He's great.
He, like, wants to be with her.
- You know?
- Yeah.
And it's funny 'cause
I feel like she's so grateful
for the, for the simplest
things, like, you know
she was like,
he always returns my calls
and he doesn't stand me up.
And I'm like, these are
the normal things, Audrina.
'These are things
that should be expected.'
I think she needs
someone to be able
to appreciate her
for who she is.
Well, I think
that's what she needs.
I don't know if that's
actually what she wants.
♪ The more I see you ♪
♪ The more I want you ♪
♪ The more I need you ♪
♪ For more than a moment ♪
♪ The more I ♪♪
When do you go back
to Australia?
Uh, probably 20th of December
or something around there.
- Just in time for Christmas.
- Yeah.
It's the best time of the year,
I reckon, to be back there
just at the beach
and just ride in the afternoon.
It's like you got summer here
and then you go back for summer
and come back here.
Yeah, endless summer.
It's pretty awesome.
You need to get out there
at least once.
I want to. We should go.
You've been single
for a while or what?
'What's, what's going on?'
- What have you been doing?
- Well, I've been single.
You been hanging out
with any other guys?
I mean, Justin, but not lately.
- Then what's up with you two?
- We're just friends.
- That's it.
- Yeah. That's, that's cool.
I don't know.
- What?
- How long has it been for you?
Just over a year.
- I was five years deep, so...
- That's a long time.
So now I'm just not worried
about anything, really.
- 'Yeah, just kind of...'
- Stress-free, just cruising.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Yeah.
Stress-free.
There's a party in Malibu
tomorrow. You should come.
Go for a swim, hang out
with some random people
that I don't, I don't know,
that would be sweet.
I'll introduce you to everyone.
- Let's get out of here then.
- Okay.
- It's nice out.
- It is.
It's a perfect night
to go swimming.
Yeah.
♪ This lonely place ♪
♪ That you should be
out here with me ♪♪♪
♪ Yesterday I saw ♪
♪ You and your new boyfriend ♪
♪ Were walking hand-in-hand ♪
I'm still recovering
from last night.
- It's so hot outside.
- It's nice out.
♪ Such a sorry old song ♪
♪ You don't know what you got
till it's gone ♪♪
- Here's the kitchen.
- Nice.
As long as you have milk
and that, I'm all good.
You want, um,
strawberries or blueberries?
- Yes, strawberries, please.
- Okay.
- Morning.
- 'Hi.'
- Lauren, you remember Cory.
- Good morning.
- How are you?
- Yeah. Good. How you doing?
- Good. You cut your hair.
- Yeah, summertime.
- It's too hot.
- I know, right?
- It's so hot today.
- I know.
(Lauren)
'It's, like,
perfect Malibu day.'
- It's gonna be so nice.
- 'Hm. Are you coming?'
- Yeah, I'll be out there.
- Yay!
It's a bit of a hike, it's like,
an hour away or whatever, but...
- I'm gonna carpool with Whit.
- Yeah.
- Whitney's going?
- 'Mm-hm.'
Yay! We're going to Cabo
in a couple weeks, right?
You should go with us, Cory.
'We're going
for Brody's birthday.'
We're gonna stay in a big house.
- 'I've never been down there.'
- 'You've never been to Cabo?'
- No.
- It's so fun.
Never been down there.
Yeah, I'll hang out, for sure.
We went to Cabo last year
for a full week
and when we came back,
we needed two weeks to recover.
It was so fun though.
It sounds like
a bit of a big deal.
- Mm-hm. Yeah.
- See you at the house later.
- Alright. Catch you.
- Bye.
♪ Way they'll always be ♪
♪ Girls do what they want ♪
♪ Whoa whoa ♪
♪ Boys do what they can ♪
♪ Girls do what they want ♪
♪ Whoa whoa ♪
♪ Boys do what they can ♪♪
So are you almost ready
to go to brunch?
Yeah, but we are not bringing
your sister to another meal.
- Spencer.
- We live with her.
We don't have to eat
every meal with her.
Spencer, what do you
want me to say?
I want you to tell her
that her free rent
'free food, free living...'
It's just a little bit longer.
This is you
just being a pushover.
[sighs]
It's really hard
because it's my family.
I get it's your family,
but this is our life.
- 'You have your life too.'
- I know.
'And your family shouldn't come
break up your life.'
It's like no one just imposes
themselves on any family member.
You were at your sister's house
for, like, two months.
What do you want me to do?
I just cannot live
with your sister anymore
so it's either her or it's me.
So you just need to tell her
that I'm moving out
or she's moving out.
One of us has to move out.
♪ I can't stop
I ain't giving up ♪
♪ It's like a rush
when we touch touch ♪
♪ I can't stop
I ain't giving up ♪
♪ It's like a rush ♪
♪ So won't you swing it
this way? ♪
♪ Baby baby
won't you swing it this way ♪
I don't know anyone here.
That's awesome.
I don't know anyone either.
♪ Swing it this way ♪
♪ Swing it over here my dear ♪
♪ Whenever something's
missing ♪♪
(Lauren)
'I'm glad Audrina brought Cory.'
I think she keeps Justin Bobby,
like, on the back burner.
Justin is there until
she finds something better.
That's just what he is. Um...
You know, I wandered down to the
kitchen today and found them.
Maybe the cutest thing ever.
It's so cute.
- She's so happy around him.
- She is?
'It makes me so happy.'
- That's pretty adorable.
- 'He's, like, a good guy.'
He's nice to her.
You know what I mean?
But he's not, like,
too nice guy.
'He's still got enough edge
for her.'
- Yeah.
- 'And she just, like...'
She's so, like,
happy around him. I love it.
- 'Hey.'
- What up?
- How's it going?
- Hi.
- What's going on?
- How's it going?
- How are you?
(Frankie)
'Seriously, Justin did call me
right now a little bit ago.'
Tell him it's lame
and not to come.
(Frankie)
'Do you understand
that he's our boy'
and he hangs out with us
every day, like...
(Lauren)
You want your boy to come here
while Audrina's with a guy
she really likes
'cause that's not fun
for anybody.
- That would start some...
- 'I'm not gonna start...'
Just, just be like,
It's lame, don't come.
'That makes nobody get hurt.'
(Frankie)
'I don't want people
to get hurt.'
'I actually think Cory's cool.'
- Cory's awesome.
- 'Yo, dude, I'm in Malibu.'
I don't know
if you were gonna come or not.
Give me a call back.
I'm here with, with everyone.
Don't come. Don't come.
Um, I guess it's kind of lame
here, so I don't know.
Not really.
It's kind of fun, but whatever.
[laughing]
Call me back. Bye.
- The worst message ever.
- I can't lie to him.
Is Cory coming to Cabo
or Justin Bobby coming to Cabo?
- Yeah, how is that gonna work?
- Well, how's what gonna work?
Well, Justin Bobby's supposed
to go to Cabo with us.
He's flying down with us.
So she's not bringing Cory
'cause Justin's coming
on the plane?
I mean,
we invited him this morning
but I don't know if he's coming.
- Oh, so it's kind of like...
- Justin's coming.
- Is he for-sure coming?
- 'I just talked to him.'
(Frankie)
'We're going to Cabo.'
'I'm gonna go get some answers.'
♪ What's up baby?
They call me Donnie ♪
♪ See me on stage
I'll rock the party ♪♪
- 'Hey, Audrina.'
- So what's the deal?
- Who are you taking to Cabo?
- I'm going by myself.
It, it just puts me in
a position when he calls me
and says, "Yo, what's up?"
Are we going to Cabo?
So what do I say?
I told him, like,
"Stop wasting my time."
"If you wanna be with me,
be with me"
"if not, then don't be with me"
"but stop * * * with my head
emotionally."
Like, I am, this has gone on
for four years now.
So I found someone
who actually likes me
and treats me good,
and he's nice.
Um, just so you know
Brody invited Justin to Cabo.
♪ We make better friends
than lovers ♪
♪ Keep a safe distance
from each other ♪
♪ I know you don't agree
but my dear trust me ♪
♪ Some things are better left ♪
♪ Undiscovered ♪♪
(Lauren)
Have you figured out what to do
for Mexico yet?
I don't know,
I know Brody invited Justin
but I don't know
if he's going or not
'cause I haven't really
talked to him.
"Cause I've been hanging out
with Cory.'
- Hey, come here.
- Who knows?
And I didn't tell Justin
about Cory.
I think he knows you're dating.
I don't think you owe it...
I think he does know because
he's been calling me a lot
and wanting
to hang out and, like
saying he misses me
and it's just...
It's 'cause
you're happy with someone else.
- Yeah. I swear, they've radar.
- 'That's entirely unfair.'
[sighs]
My gosh, you're, like,
juggling men.
I know it. This is...
I haven't had this happen
in a long time.
- Well?
- Who to choose?
That's a little weird.
I don't know. It's your call.
I don't know either.
'But I would keep in mind that
I think, things are still
fun and new with Cory.
I don't think
Justin's going anywhere.
I know.
Well...
- Alright.
- Ready to race the sun home?
Yeah. Come on.
♪ I can't keep running down ♪
♪ And I can't
keep fighting outlaws ♪
♪ Oh everything feels
so wasteful ♪
♪ Everything feels so bright ♪♪
- It's gorgeous out here.
- Yeah, it's so amazing.
Surreal.
Um, I kind of got to talk
to you about something.
What?
[sighs]
I think that
it's time that we figure out
somewhere else for you to live.
Why?
Because it was only supposed
to be, you know
for a week or two
until you got on your feet
and, you know,
I've been at work all the time
and I don't really know
if you're looking for jobs
or places.
Of course,
I've been looking for jobs.
But Spencer says
you're here a lot
and on the couch and...
- Spencer?
- How long do you need?
Am I supposed to just
go on the street?
- I don't have a job yet.
- I can't...
But I can't figure out
your life for you.
Like, I don't know
how much more to help you
while sacrificing my life
at the same time.
Like, I love having you here,
and I wanna have you here
but it can't be
at the cost of my relationship.
I just don't understand why
it has to be one or the other.
Well, Spencer said it's either
'he's gonna move out
or you are and...'
What am I supposed to do?
♪ So now it's been spoken ♪
♪ And now it's understood ♪
♪ That now ♪
♪ When it seems like
things may be broken ♪
♪ And somehow
that's good enough ♪♪
You want a little or a lot?
[coughs]
'In between.'
How about a lot?
- Cheers.
'Who's home? Is...
Are the girls home?'
No, it's just you and me.
- What up? You getting in?
- I don't know.
Well, you can go in
and I can watch.
- Really?
- Sure.
Go ahead.
Justin.
- I'm watching.
- Are you coming in or not?
If you took your top off
and went over there
I'd probably have to chase you.
- Would you come in?
- Maybe.
Really?
What are you doing?
Okay. Come in.
♪ I don't wanna let you go ♪
Dude, this is cold.
Dude, this is BS.
This is freezing.
- You're in.
- You got me.
Well, if you go to Cabo
for Brody's birthday...
Just can I, can I,
can I pre-warn you if I go?
- What?
- That I'm...
- I'm gonna get in trouble.
- Doing what?
- You're such an ass.
- No, it's on now.
What do you mean on,
it's on in Cabo? What is on?
I'm just letting you know
I get to use my hall pass.
Well, it doesn't matter
because I shouldn't, but I do.
- Shouldn't what?
- Care.
I'm just letting you know.
- Okay. Fine.
- 'Alright.'
♪ I don't wanna let you go ♪
Alright.
Cabo, it's on.
[laughs]
You're in trouble now.
- You're bad.
- Why?
- 'Cause I don't trust you.
- Hey.
Hey, I'll see you in Cabo.
♪ Said that if you'd
give it all up ♪
♪ Everything worked itself out ♪
♪ You know this ♪
♪ I'm waving my flag
in the air ♪
♪ Believe me when I say
I'm right here ♪
♪ I'm not going anywhere ♪♪
[theme music]