- Cabo. Cabo. Cabo.
- Oh, look who it is.
(Frankie)
'Cabo.'
[all cheering]
Ah, yo, so, what's the plan?
I have a little bit
of a surprise for you.
'Something to add a little fun
to the party.'
- Hey. What's up?
- What's up with Justin?
- Why're you not talking to him?
- We're not together.
He's planning on hooking up
with other girls, so whatever.
- So where's Cory?
- He's out on a tour.
I think we're all leaving
a lot back in LA
and we should just kind
of put it aside and enjoy.
'Except for Audrina, she brought
hers on the jet with her.'
♪ It's your love
it gets to me ♪
♪ 'Cause you wind me up
and you set me free oh ♪
♪ Your love it gets to me ♪
♪ 'Cause you wind me up
and you set me free ♪
♪ 'Cause you get to me ♪♪
- 'It's a pretty house.'
- Oh, what?
- Wow!
- No! Oh, look at the waves.
(Brody)
'Oh, my God, Justin,
there's a wave right out here.'
- Okay, whose room is this?
- 'I think it's you and Justin.'
There's no way I'm staying
in the same room with him.
Just stay in my room. I'm
downstairs, I have my own room.
I'm sure he'll have a girl
in here tonight.
♪ Oh oh oh whoa ♪
♪ I've been taken for
a ride run ♪
♪ Oh oh oh whoa ♪
♪ Now you make me feel
like such a fool ♪
♪ Oh oh oh whoa ♪
♪ It's like diving
in a shallow pool ♪
♪ Oh oh oh whoa ♪
♪ I've been taken for
a ride by you ♪♪
Oh, well, what's the drama?
Nothing?
- What happened? Tell me.
- 'Um, no.'
- I'm not gonna talk about it.
- Why not?
If I'm getting * * * for
Audrina and you know stuff
that's going on, then you should
share with the class.
- Just tell the boys.
- 'Well, she's dating someone.'
Audrina doesn't have
a boyfriend.
Guess, she does, she's dating
a boy who's a friend.
No. She has a boyfriend.
His name is Cory.
- 'Oh.'
- 'So she's coming to you saying
what about this boyfriend?'
Well, she's claiming
that her boyfriend is
like, he's really cool,
treats her right
and then talks about him and how
he doesn't treat her right.
Eh, whatever.
You know what I mean.
Okay, I really am...
'Thing is this.
This is what I think.'
I'd be pissed off.
I'd be pissed.
I'd be like,
are you kidding me?
I have one thing to say.
All girls are shady.
[laughs]
(Justin)
'There it is.'
♪ Oh girl look
what happened to you ♪
♪ You didn't have to do it ♪
♪ Oh why'd you do it ♪
♪ Why'd you have to do it ♪
♪ It's making us ♪
♪ You endanger us ♪♪
Oh, these are pretty.
- Is that shadow?
- I think so.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I haven't seen you in so long.
What is going on?
- I have a boyfriend.
- What?
Well, I don't know...
Yeah, I guess he is.
- We had the talk.
- The talk? Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so nice to have him.
Everyone's out
of town right now.
Why? Where is everybody?
Brody's birthday.
'He flew everyone out to Cabo.'
They're all in Cabo
and I'm here.
So why didn't you go?
Like, you know, Brody and I
don't get along and...
Well, what about, uh,
you and Lauren?
I don't know, we left it off,
like, kind of weird.
I mean, it's like probably
the worst
it's been in a really long time.
Well, why don't you and Cameron
come to dinner
with Spencer and I?
We can all do like
a double date.
Um...
- Are you scared?
- Really scared.
What is the worst-case scenario
that could happen at dinner,
you know?
Spencer will say something
mean to me
and Cameron will like stiffen up
and be like,
I'm not liking this.
Spencer's not dating him.
You're dating him.
'Even if your family didn't
like him'
that couldn't change
everything, you know?
Spencer and my mom don't
get along too well.
But that doesn't change
my opinion.
My mom's not dating him,
you know?
- Yeah.
- I'm sure it will be fine.
'So, are we on
for dinner tonight?'
'Yeah.'
♪ Good ♪
♪ It's really good ♪
♪ But when it's bad ♪
♪ Well you know how it goes ♪♪
- So pretty, right?
- 'It is really nice.'
I'm worried for you guys 'cause
you are with like ten dudes.
Well, apparently, we're dudes
on this trip as well, so...
- Does it look real?
- What was that from?
- 'Cory gave it to me.'
- 'Really?'
So I saw your bag rolling
out of, uh, our room.
(Brody)
'Cut it, you slice it,
you make sashimi right there.'
Rolled right down the hallway.
(Audrina)
'You saw me rolling it off?'
I saw you in
and rolling it out.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Ditto.
You're the one who didn't
wanna be exclusive.
Oh, dude.
So what am I to think?
Then you show up in Cabo.
Already said my yeah before
all this stuff went down.
Is it?
Okay.
I just wanna say not only
are you my best friend
but you're the best friend
a person can have.
- Aw.
- 'Oh, that was really sweet.'
'Happy birthday.
Cheers to everyone.'
When do you open presents?
Well, since we're having
a little, you know, fiesta
'I thought we'd bring
a little party here.'
Did you guys invite sleazies?
Don't lie.
'Don't lie to me, Douglas.'
We just got the cake though.
We just got...
Hold on a second.
You'll wanna see this.
'Come on, girls! Whoo!'
- 'Oh!'
- 'Come on!'
Girls.
[cheering]
Oh, my God. Wow.
(Brody)
'Do I get birthday presents?'
(Lauren)
'I think you have pretty
good odds tonight.'
[laughs]
'There's like,
there's like 18 of them.'
Hey, where are they all
gonna sleep?
[laughs]
(Lauren)
'Look, girls are already
in the beach.'
Didn't we keep our clothes
on long, did we, ladies?
Have you noticed
the awkwardness?
Hmm, I think that
the insects in the air
have noticed the awkwardness.
Maybe you need to tell him
the truth. Tell him, Audrina.
Be like,
you don't treat me right.
I found someone who does
and I'm moving on.
He's still hanging around
and he's still trying to pull
me, you know what I mean?
You gotta let go of it.
You're with Cory.
You've got to completely let go.
I'm letting go. He's, like,
all about mind games.
Well, shut it off.
You can't play by yourself.
Just tell him. You're gonna
stress on it until you do.
♪ Where do we go from here
my love ♪♪
That's gonna make tonight
a little more interesting.
As far as single,
single, single.
Like, all the boys are single.
Well, if this is a weekend
to have a hall pass
and find out
your girl's got a boy
this is probably it, right?
- 'Yeah.'
- With no remorse?
Right?
- Contemplating here.
- Yes.
Those are some hot twins.
Damn.
Oh, I didn't do it.
I didn't start it.
Let's go make friends
with those girls.
It will be so much fun.
Come on.
Hey, who wants to go swimming?
♪ Right now ♪
♪ Oh you left me
with a broken heart ♪
♪ And now I see what I should
have from the start ♪
♪ Well you left me
with nothing but a kiss ♪
♪ And now I'm leaving you
with these lips ♪
♪ Whoa whoa whoa whoa ♪
♪ And now I'm pressing
but I ain't stressing ♪
♪ She's got a man ♪
♪ I'm with her best friend ♪
♪ You left me
with a broken heart ♪
♪ And now I see what I should
have from the start ♪
♪ But you left me
with nothing but a kiss ♪
♪ And now I'm leaving you
with these lips ♪
♪ Whoa whoa whoa whoa ♪♪
Twenty minutes late.
Unacceptable.
She probably is in
a tanning salon.
Actually, I think
she's misting now.
Should we just order
without them?
Absolutely.
You've never met Cameron, right?
No. I have not.
I'm so excited to see, uh...
I wonder what he looks like.
...this lucky gentleman
who has the honor
of dating my fabulous sister.
We don't get along
that great. You'll see.
Well, if he's a jerk,
I'm not gonna be really nice.
You'd have to be.
- No, I don't.
- Always be nice.
- Always be nice. Right here.
- Oh.
I can't believe they're now
legitimately a half hour late.
(Heidi)
'I think they're later
than a half an hour.'
Nice watch. Is that
what you're showing me?
(Spencer)
'No, I'm showing you
what time it is.'
Hi. Nice to meet you.
(Spencer)
'Did, uh, you forget
we were decided'
'to meet up at 9 o'clock,
not 9:40?'
I'll take the blame.
It was my fault.
- Yeah.
- What a gentleman.
(Spencer)
'Once I get some, uh, food'
'in my system,
I'll get a little friendlier.'
Oh, we got this.
This is our food.
Just a glass for this, please.
(female #1)
'Do you all want some pepper?'
We're good, thank you.
I think I'd like
to propose a toast.
(Heidi)
'Hm. That's so nice.'
To the honor of going to dinner
with my sister
and her first boyfriend.
- Cheers.
- Spencer, you are so mean.
I've never gone out to dinner
with you and a boyfriend.
This is your first
real boyfriend.
- 'So how are you guys?'
- Good.
- 'And Holly?'
- I just kicked that Holly out.
- Felt real good.
- Don't say that.
She's, like, the biggest moocher
on the planet.
Was it mutual,
getting Holly out?
It's not mutual, Spencer said
I'm either leaving,
or Holly's leaving.
And so now she's, like, crashing
on someone else's couch.
Um, your sister's really funny.
She makes me laugh a lot.
She makes me laugh a lot too.
I have an important question,
Cameron.
'So have you met
Brody and them?'
Like four or five years ago.
You guys are like old friends?
I don't know.
Brody's alright.
Small world.
Did you know that
Brody made Stephanie cry?
- So have you seen Brody since?
- I have not seen Brody.
When the time's right though
maybe call Brody,
talk about it all.
What happened with you and
Brody? You guys were like...
(Spencer)
'He just hangs out
with somebody'
I can't respect him
for hanging out with.
Who he talked a lot
of crap about?
Yeah.
I don't like hypocrites.
Loyalty is a big thing.
- Did you meet Doug yet?
- You're asking Cameron?
- Dating LC's boyfriend Doug?
- I never dated Doug.
- They just went to dinner.
- Candlelit dinner.
I heard there were candles.
♪ All my life I've searched
for something ♪
♪ To make me whole again ♪
♪ The perfect words I've found
are better left unsaid ♪♪
Get that off his wrist.
I just want my flower back,
you can go on your way.
You can do...
What are you looking for?
Wait, your what?
What are you...
Give it to me.
Now.
- You can keep it. I'm done.
- Thanks.
♪ Nothing is forever ♪
♪ The way it all went wrong ♪
♪ And why ♪
♪ We have to move on ♪♪
♪ Soft kill
you know that my will ♪
♪ Is now in your hand ♪
♪ Understand ♪
♪ Deep kick
no way a cheap trick ♪
♪ How far it goes through
oh oh ♪♪
The one girl told me she
wanted to take this from you
last night, but you wouldn't
give it to her.
Of course not. It's from you.
I'm keeping it.
Justin, that's mine.
Give this back.
No.
- No boat today, huh?
- Nope.
I'm gonna throw you overboard.
I should throw you overboard.
You came to Cabo on a hall pass?
I'm not the one that has
a boy right now.
So you really can't say
anything, can you?
You left me for another guy.
- No. Well, yeah, I did.
- See?
- I ask you what's up...
- I was having fun.
Well, have your fun.
I'm having fun, too, now.
Justin, you're in a spot
in your life right now
where you don't wanna be
exclusive with anyone.
And I found someone
who I really like and...
But I've always asked
you just be straight up.
Um, I've always asked
you to be straight up.
- I think I have.
- You're never...
- No, you're not.
- And you're not.
I'm telling you right now,
me and Cory, I really like him.
He treats me good
and he wants to be with me.
- Okay.
- End of story.
Well, you know, I don't care.
I think it's cool.
- Give me my flower.
- No.
Now, you're definitely
not getting it back.
- Justin!
- You will never have this.
- It's mine.
- Oh, wah!
Whenever you're ready to grow
up, come and talk to me.
♪ It still hurts to let go ♪
♪ But every day I do ♪
♪ I'm looking for some hope ♪
♪ This cloud will pass through ♪
♪ I'm pressing rewind ♪
♪ I'm searching for when ♪
♪ We had blue skies ♪
♪ But it's starting
to rain again ♪♪
Heidi said you were
working out here.
Do you know why I'm here?
How do you think
you behaved last night?
After waiting around
for 40 minutes?
Okay, well, the thing was,
it wasn't my fault.
It was his fault.
- And so he felt so bad.
- He should have!
If I'm trying to go meet Heidi's
brother for the first time
I'm not gonna be
40 minutes late.
I'm gonna be 40 minutes early,
staking out the place.
'And why would you
bring up Doug?'
- I was just curious.
- I never dated Doug.
That's like the one thing
you don't talk about
to a new couple.
He got in the car, and he was
like, "So, what about Doug?"
Only reason I was
giving him a hard time
is that I didn't
understand the fact
that he's chilling with Brody.
I'm not apologizing.
'Cause you just don't get
along with anyone.
You should be appreciative,
A, I talk to you
B, I went to a dinner with you
and your new boyfriend
and, C, I paid for the dinner.
Just like be nicer to me.
- To you?
- Yeah.
Why don't you start being
loyal to your family?
[whistles]
Trade maybe?
I'll be nice to somebody who's
loyal and you'll be loyal.
So I'll be seeing you.
♪ It makes me sick
to think about ♪
♪ Everything you
put me through ♪
♪ And how you left
without saying goodbye ♪
♪ This is the end ♪
Yo, Brody!
♪ Everything I used
to be back then ♪
♪ And then sucked in ♪♪
He can't get mad at me
and try to make me feel bad
for being with someone who...
He can't.
No, he can't at all.
He has no right.
I think that you need to think
about what's right for you.
Honestly, like what
makes you happy.
And that's what
you need to do.
That's what I'm doing.
Cory makes me happy.
Honestly, you need to not
talk to Justin anymore.
But now, this was it.
But I just...
'To be fair to Cory, you need'
'to really,
really cut yourself off.'
But then Justin, like, has
to make things difficult.
Why do you want that
in your life then?
I don't. That's why
I-I've stopped it, Lauren.
But you're here
and you're contemplating.
I'm here and he's here
and it just makes it hard.
Like I still love him like...
I think that Justin is gonna
be someone that you love
and love to be with,
but if you wanna be with someone
and you want a boyfriend,
you can't look to Justin
'cause he's not gonna
give that to you.
'Maybe it's time to let him go.'
Justin doesn't have,
like, a hold over you.
♪ I don't wanna deny my heart
its chance to feel ♪
♪ I don't wanna deny
my soul something real ♪
♪ Is there anything left
in this world ♪
♪ That will satisfy
you and me ♪♪
[theme music]