(Kelly)
Hey, Whit?
Can you come up here?
(Whitney)
'Sure.'
- Hey.
- Hi.
So I ran into Alixe at DVF,
Diane Von Furstenberg
'and she told me that
she was looking for somebody'
to do PR in-house.
'And that made me think of you.'
Okay?
And there's an interview, um
that I've set up for you in
New York the day after tomorrow.
The job is in New York?
- Yes.
- Wow.
You know,
despite how demanding I am
I always kind of
think about the people
that work for me
and like where they're headed
'and what's gonna
be best for them.'
I don't wanna lose you,
but I think that
you've really done a lot
for us and this interview
'is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.'
'Diane's amazing.
She's a legend.'
The amount of experience
that you would have
would just be tremendous.
I mean, it sounds amazing.
It's just scary.
Like, I always kind of
saw myself in New York.
I just didn't think it was
gonna happen this fast.
I really think that you have
a great shot at this job
and I think you will have
a fantastic experience.
Well, then I have to do it.
Okay.
♪ Can you hear me comin'? ♪
♪ Will you catch me
if I'm fallin'? ♪
♪ If I can't find my way ♪
♪ Can you hear me talkin'? ♪♪
(Audrina)
'Well, I'm glad
we're hanging out.'
(Lauren)
'I know!
You're all settled?'
Yeah. I mean, I got that
back house together quick.
This is gonna take me a while.
And it's gonna be, like, your
home, you know what I mean?
- Like, that's like...
- Bachelorette pad.
[laughs]
Bachelorette, huh?
What about Justin?
How you doing with that?
We talked and, like...
So you don't want it anymore?
No, I still want it.
[laughs]
So what about you?
What's been going on?
My parents are moving.
Where are they moving?
Are they moving out of Laguna?
Yeah.
Oh, are you gonna
miss that house?
I loved that house.
'I'm going down
tomorrow with Lo'
and pack up, like,
my whole room down there.
You know, everyone moved away,
everyone moved out of town
and I have, like,
my few friends from Laguna
that I still hang out with,
but they're all in LA.
I mean, the only reason
I went back
was for my family, but now...
Now they're moving.
'It's kind of like growing up.'
Yeah.
Do you want to show me
the rest of the house?
Yeah, I wanna show you upstairs.
- Okay.
- The view is really pretty.
♪ It's just trying to tell ♪
♪ And well all I need
is a chance ♪
♪ And to see you smile ♪
♪ While we're still young ♪♪
What's with you
and always being late?
Is this really
a poor-me afternoon?
No, it's not.
I just don't know what to do.
- With who?
- With Cameron.
I thought you already
broke up with him.
- No.
- What do you mean no?
We keep breaking up
and then, like, he'll be nice
and then two days later,
it'll all change again.
It's stupid, but, like,
one thing was, he was like
"Well, it's because I always
drive to your house.
You never drive to my house."
Then he's not worth your time
if he can't drive
15 minutes to see you.
That's just,
like, straight punk.
Why be sad over a guy that
doesn't stand up for you
after somebody makes
you cry twice in a club?
I don't know
what to do with myself.
Go be a nun.
Join, like, a nun's thing.
Can you stop, Spencer?
How many times
have you broken up?
Maybe like four, five.
Do you know how, I mean, do you
know how immature and stupid
this relationship sounds
from an outside perspective?
'Obviously this relationship
is not meant to be.'
'Because,
from my honest opinion'
I know you can do
better than that guy.
♪ Da da da da ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ Might as well be someday ♪
♪ So predictable ♪
♪ And so the story goes ♪♪
I have to tell you about
my meeting with Kelly yesterday.
She basically told me
that she was talking
to people over
at Diane Von Furstenberg
and she wants me
to fly in tomorrow
to have an interview with them...
- Like a whole new job?
- Like a whole new job.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
This is like so out of nowhere.
I mean, I feel like
I just started working here.
- For Diane Von Furstenberg.
- 'For Diane Von Furstenberg.'
That's gonna be the most
awesome thing ever.
I know, but that would mean
I'd be basically moving
to New York.
- It's out of New York?
- I would be moving to New York.
- Whit.
- I know.
I'm sorry, I'm so happy
for you, I'm just...
'I know.
It's how could I not try it?'
I'd regret it if I didn't.
That's true.
This is really exciting.
Such a whirlwind,
I'll be leaving tomorrow
and then coming back
the same day.
- Oh, wow, in and out?
- 'Yeah.'
'Kelly said I'll
be coming right back'
'cause she needs me
in the office the next day.
Wait, how long do you have?
'Cause you could always see...
- See Jay for a second?
- You have to see him.
I have to see him for a second.
Aw. Dream boy, dream job.
Honestly, I think that
what I really need to keep
in the back of my head
is if I'm doing this
I'm doing this purely
for the job
and not for any other reason,
you know?
[laughs]
♪ You are ♪
♪ Anything and everything ♪
♪ 'Cause of what you are ♪
♪ What you are ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪♪
I don't think
they know you're coming.
- It'll be alright.
- Yeah.
- He'll be really happy.
- I'm sure.
(Heidi)
'Hi.'
How are you?
- 'What's going on?'
- Hello, Cameron.
- How's it going?
- How are you?
I'm good.
So this is, uh, unexpected.
I didn't know you two
were, um, back together.
- Things worked out.
- 'Little surprised.'
I had heard some different
things from you
'so this is quite shocking
to...'
Thought we were having dinner,
the three of us.
Spencer.
You gotta see, I'm coming from
a different side
of the story, so...
My perspective is
a little skewed here, Steph.
And he's a little protective.
It's your sister, I understand.
Last I'd heard,
he was making you cry
so obviously
things have changed.
We're gonna try
things out again.
Start over.
♪ Rainfall ♪
♪ Shut down on broken plans ♪
♪ And try ♪
♪ Give it up ♪
♪ You give it up ♪
♪ Whoa-whoa ♪
♪ Stripped down to the typical ♪
♪ It goes on and on ♪
♪ It won't come back ♪
♪ It's gone ♪
(Lo)
It's so beautiful up here.
(Lauren)
I know.
Enjoy our last visit.
♪ Give it up whoa whoa ♪
♪ Last song
shouted heavens thoughts ♪
♪ It goes on and on
and can't come back ♪
♪ It's gone ♪♪
- 'Hello.'
- Hey, girls.
- Hi.
- I've come to pack my room.
Come here, tall girl.
- 'How are you?'
- 'Good.'
Nice to see you guys.
- How are you guys?
- Good.
- 'Good.'
- Are you coming to help pack?
(Lauren)
'I'm packing the room.
I recruited Lo.'
You know what you should
do though is we wanna put
have some of your pictures
in the new bedroom.
- I'll pick my favorites.
- 'Okay.'
So you guys are just moving
to a smaller house?
- 'Yes.'
- Yep. My kids are grown up.
Lauren's gone.
'Breanna's gone.'
We just have little Brandon
and he's...
Two years, he's graduating
and going away to college.
Seems silly to be livin'
in a really big house
with just two people,
you know.
Alright, well, you guys
better get packin'.
Ready?
Have fun.
Thanks for helping, Lo.
You're welcome.
I love to pack.
You're a good friend, Lo.
♪ Survived another ♪
♪ I've got a feeling ♪
♪ Things are gonna
get much better ♪
♪ I've got a feeling ♪
♪ That things are gonna
get much better ♪
♪ I've got a feeling
I've got a feeling ♪♪
(Whitney)
'Hi, how are you?'
- 'Good, how are you?'
- Good. I'm Whitney Port.
- I'm here to see Alixe Boyer.
- 'Elizabeth will be with you.'
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
- Hi, I'm Elizabeth.
- Hi, I'm Whitney.
- Nice to meet you.
- Go right upstairs.
- Okay, great.
- Alixe will be right with you.
Thank you.
- Hi. How are you?
- Whitney. Hi.
- I'm Whitney.
- Good. Alixe Boyer.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you for having me here.
- Thank you for coming by.
So I spoke with Kelly
and she was very
complimentary of you.
- Oh, good.
- So I brought you my resume.
Great. I did take a look at it
but I'd love to hear from you
what you've been doing.
Okay, well, basically,
uh, as you can see
my most recent job
was People's Revolution.
Which, I was working a lot
with styling.
I particularly helped style
the Sass & Bide runway show
that we did here in New York.
And your role at the Sass & Bide
show was what exactly?
Basically, I was just helping
with all the casting.
I was helping styling
with the designers.
Just everything
that you can think of.
And before that,
I worked at "Teen Vogue."
So tell me, why DVF?
Well, I've always wanted
to work for a designer.
I think it's part
of the fashion industry
that I've never
been able to really do
so I think it would just be
really an awesome opportunity
for me to just learn
a whole new...
- Sort of be in-house.
- Yeah.
In terms of the position,
I can tell you that
I'm looking for someone who can
come in as an image coordinator
in essence, and work with me
on all facets of the brand.
- Mm-hm.
- So, it's a broad position.
(Alixe)
'You know, it's a very
busy time of year.'
- 'It's fashion week, so...'
- Okay.
How quickly can you start?
As soon as you would need me.
So you're ready
to change your lifestyle?
- I'm very ready.
- And start something entirely
new?
I'm very ready.
I would never have taken
this job interview
if I wasn't serious about it
and I feel like
if I'm in this industry
I should just go into it
wholeheartedly
and come to the city.
Great.
♪ I'm falling in love ♪
♪ What's falling in love for ♪
♪ I need to find my way ♪
♪ Back to the start ♪
♪ When we were in love ♪
♪ When things were better
than they are ♪
♪ Let me back into ♪
♪ Into your heart ♪♪
- Hi.
- Hey, Steph.
How are you?
Better days.
Thanks for coming over.
'So what's up?'
I think we know
that this isn't working.
'I think we both kind of
need to compromise'
and work this out
'cause it's worth it to me.
I don't, I don't know.
Maybe we should...
I don't know, like, how much
there is good in what we had.
'It feels
like it was so long ago'
and I don't know
how it got so bad.
[sniffles]
Like, you know, I,
I'm sure I said, I was like
this is the happiest
relationship I've ever been in
and it was,
but it's not there anymore.
Like, what, where I am
right now is
I deserve better than this.
I just want, like
to find a guy
that makes me happy.
If that's what you want,
then that's what you need.
♪ Now that it's over ♪
Yeah.
♪ Feel alive ♪
♪ I just need some time
to breathe ♪
to take ♪
♪ I just need some time
to work it all out ♪
(Lo)
'Oh, my gosh.
You did such a good job
'of keepin' all this stuff.'
These are from, like,
middle school on.
Oh, my gosh. Listen to this.
"This weekend, I am
grounded for bad grades.
Surprise, surprise."
- How funny is this?
- I never had a diary.
This is when my parents
sold our first house
that I, like, grew up in.
"It's weird knowing that the
house I spent the last 15 years
"of my life in
will never be my home again.
"I hate knowing that the people
that just wrote a check
"and purchased so many memories.
"They don't know
about the first kiss
Stephen and I had in my room."
Oh, my gosh.
- That's adorable.
- Oh, my God.
Ring, ring.
No big deal.
It's just my first cell phone.
[laughs]
It's the size
of our house phone.
- Yeah, it's true.
- 'Oh, my God.'
- My will if I died.
- Seriously?
"Mommy, I'm sorry my room
was always so messy
"and I didn't appreciate
everything you did.
"Daddy, you've always been
a fabulous father my whole life.
"Thanks. I love you.
"P.S. I would like to be buried
in my homecoming dress
with my crown on my coffin ."
Oh, my God!
Oh, don't read the back.
It's weird, like, going through
all of this stuff
and remembering
all the fun times
that we had growing up here.
'And think that, I don't know.'
It's like when you're moving,
it closes another chapter.
Just weird for me because no
matter what goes on in, in LA
I always have this to come back
to and it's the same.
Yeah.
It makes LA a little
bit more my home.
Yeah, it definitely does.
(Lauren)
'Wanna go outside?'
We had so much fun up here.
It's sad to leave.
I know. I thought they were
gonna have it forever.
I thought it was
kind of the plan.
'Mm-hm.'
I just grew up
a little bit here
and there's no memories
in the new place.
Well, you have to make them.
You have to make the memories.
Yeah, but this was my home.
That'll never be my home.
With your parents living
there, it'll be homey.
It'll be the same thing.
I think it's time to make
my own home my home.
Or our home.
God, are we that old?
We're not that old yet.
We don't have to do that yet.
Wanna go back to the car?
Okay. Come on.
(Alixe)
'So we'll be in touch soon.'
- 'Okay, great.'
- Thank you. Bye.
- Bye, I'll talk to you soon.
- Great, thanks.
- 'Wow, hi.'
- Hi.
How are you?
- What's going on?
- You made it!
- How's it going?
- Good. How are you?
- I like your dress.
- Thank you.
- How did it go?
- You look good too.
How did it go?
- It was okay. I mean...
- It was good?
Yeah, she said they're looking
at other people
but I guess I'll hear
from her tomorrow and...
I wanna get back here,
like, as soon as possible.
- Are you gonna stay?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Aah!
I really want to, you know.
I wanna get out of LA
and I want to move here
and things could be,
like, different.
- That would be cool.
- Yeah.
Now that's done, what are you
gonna do for today then?
- Um, what am I doing where?
- All day here?
- Um, it's so good to see you.
- I know.
I love this dress, babe.
You look hot.
Thank you.
So you're leaving tonight?
What time is your flight again?
I have to go now.
I guess I'll just have
to see you when I get back.
No, that's not fair.
- I know, right?
- That's not fair.
I'm not gonna see you
till next time?
No, but hopefully, it will
be sooner than later.
A week?
Hopefully. Okay?
- Mm!
- Mm.
It's been too long already.
It's already been a month.
I know. But I'll
talk to you, um...
I'll talk to you once I'm home.
- Okay.
Call me when you
get, uh, back to LA.
- Okay. Bye, Jay.
- Alright. See ya, babe.
♪ You never know ♪
♪ You never know ♪♪
[theme music]