- I have a question.
- Talk to me.
Have you talked
to the cute boy Jay?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
Yeah. We've been keeping
in touch.
We've been talking,
so hopefully
I'll be able to get out
there soon and...
So jealous of your
fairy tale. It's so cute.
It's so cute.
Oh, my gosh!
I forgot to tell you.
- 'Holly's staying with me.'
- 'Are you serious?'
Yeah, she came over last night.
She's like crashing.
That's very nice of you.
Wouldn't you do that
for a friend?
Yeah, I would do that too.
- 'You would do it.'
- Definitely.
Does Heidi know that Holly
is staying with you right now?
'You don't know.'
'Cause that could get
really complicated.
How could it possibly
get more complicated?
I'm just saying,
the longer she stays there
the more the two of them
are gonna resent you.
My only concern
is how they're gonna treat her
but seeing as they didn't leave
her with much of an option.
And I guess if her sister's
the one kicking her out
then she doesn't owe her
anything.
Holly seems like a sweet girl.
- She's great.
- From what I know of her.
She's like Heidi
but without the Spencer.
Ah...
Good old days.
♪ I'm gonna make you see ♪
♪ I'm gonna make you believe ♪
♪ Just don't want this to be ♪
♪ Ah ah undiscovered love ♪
♪ Got to have you by my side ♪
♪ 'Cause I know that
this is right ♪♪
This is so different
than Hollywood.
It feels like
a whole different...
This is my side.
It's not Hollywood.
- So pretty.
- Yeah, love it.
You need to come down more
this way.
- I will.
- Instead of that way.
Speaking of the beach,
when are we goin' to Mexico?
Oh, to make up for Cabo?
- I'm serious, let's go.
- Let's go.
You can bring your surfboard
and teach me how to surf.
I don't know how to surf.
I could teach you.
Are you a good learner?
- Or I'll just watch.
- Well, you can watch.
You can come in the water
with me.
Okay.
- Come up here.
- Ah.
It's so pretty here.
Oh, if I lived down here,
I'd be on the beach every day.
There's something
zenful about it.
The sunsets are nice, too.
- It's nice.
- I don't like to leave here.
- Have you noticed?
- I've noticed.
That's why I think, like,
when I get to your place
and I'm kind of, um...
Yeah.
It's just really stressful.
It doesn't need to be like that,
you know what I mean?
For now, though, it's like
things are finally,
the tension's squashed.
That's good. That helps.
I think, us move on.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
I was always upset
and, like, frustrated.
Well, not when you're down here
with me.
Mm-mm.
It's good.
(Audrina)
'We can try things this way.'
It's what it's about, baby girl.
'Let's go.
You gotta help me up.'
- You have to help me up.
- 'Come on.'
♪ You get me ♪
♪ Caught in this fight ♪
♪ Every time we try ♪
♪ So steady ♪
♪ Girl in this light ♪
♪ You have a darker side ♪
♪ You know ♪
What are you doin', my dear?
Spring cleaning?
Well, since I have
nothing to do
I'm trying to keep myself
occupied and...
...clean out
and organize my closet.
Let's go...to the movies.
- Let's...not.
- This is so boring.
This is what you do
when you get fired
you re-arrange your closet?
Well, I don't think I'd be fired
if it weren't for you.
Oh, I don't remember, uh,
making you drink that night.
I don't think you'd remember
anything from that night.
Oh, really, well,
you don't take
responsibility
at all for yourself?
I do take responsibility
for inviting you.
And I take responsibility
for having a drink
and I shouldn't have done that.
'But you should take
responsibility for saying'
whatever you said
to Sam to get me fired.
Thankfully, Brent's
gonna talk to Sam again
'and hopefully I'll
be able to talk him'
into giving me my job back.
(Spencer)
'You really want
that job back so badly?'
Of course, I do and that's not
the only thing
you screwed up for me.
I mean, I just can't believe
that on top of me losing my job
I pretty much lost my sister.
I don't even know where she is.
Yeah, I'm pretty upset Holly's
not around more often, too.
Yeah, but I don't even know
where she is now.
She hasn't even called me,
or talked to me.
She's 25 years old.
Like, ever since she moved
to LA, it's been...
[whistling]
It's not healthy
for a relationship
for you always
to be horrified at what...
You're the one causing
all the problems.
I'm causing all the problems?
You gonna complain about
your sister, or your job?
What are we gonna complain
about now?
I was comin' in here,
trying to cheer you up
go celebrate,
you have the day off today
and all you wanna do
is complain.
I'm gonna go enjoy life.
♪ Three two three three one ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ LA LA ♪
♪ Can I have it like that ♪
♪ Well Mr. Neezy ♪
♪ You got it like that ♪
♪ Prada bags Gucci shoes ♪
♪ Louis V Jimmy choos ♪
Hi.
Good. How are you?
Thanks.
♪ Louis V Jimmy choos ♪
♪ Prada bags Gucci shoes ♪
♪ Louis V Jimmy choos ♪♪
I...could not tell you
the last time you and I
went out for a drink.
Maybe, like,
when we go out together
we're, like, kinda like trouble.
[laughs]
Lauren, you and I together
attract trouble, like...
- She's a good person.
- She's a very real person.
She is.
- It'll be fun.
- We'll see.
Just go, have a fiesta.
You know what he told me
the other night?
- What?
- He said that, um...
He's over the Hollywood thing
and he's done going out
and partying all the time.
- What does he want now?
- I don't know.
I'm just letting him
call the shots.
You can't force things
to happen.
It just has to happen,
you know, naturally.
And until then,
you just play the game.
There's this like connection
that we have
that I don't have
with anyone else.
But I don't know.
Justin'll always
be your number one.
I told him that.
He'll always be my number one.
Cheers.
[instrumental music]
♪ I saw my life ♪
♪ And it wasn't honest ♪
♪ We stayed up all night ♪
♪ Reliving scenes
from our lives ♪♪
(Casey)
'Audrina,
your place looks so good.'
- 'It's coming together, huh?'
- Looks good.
You're definitely getting
it nice and girly
and...bachelorette-ish.
Yes, my little bachelorette pad.
It's slowly coming along.
It just takes time.
'Justin's been coming over.
He helps here and there.'
Like I need those pictures
hung up.
So everything's going good?
Things are going really good.
We'll hang out here,
we'll go to Venice
to his neck of the woods
and hang out there.
And it's kinda nice
going back and forth.
- That's cool.
- Yeah.
He's been here a lot.
His toothbrush is upstairs.
Oh, goodness.
And we were talking about
going to Mexico
and like getting away
for a little bit.
But he still does
the whole, like
"Oh, I'm gonna disappear
for a week
"and not return your
phone calls or texts
and you're not gonna know
where I am or what I'm doing."
- Like, what is that?
- I know, but...
Where does he go, though?
Even if you talk to him after
does he just not tell you?
But I just, I've gotten
to the point now
where I just don't, kinda
don't sit around anymore...
That's sad, though. You expect
to be, like, convenient.
Like, when it's good for him,
he's all about it.
I feel like he's been making,
like, more effort
in hanging out and just...
What can I say? I love him.
As long as you're happy.
♪ But it's how I survive ♪
♪ On and on ♪
♪ Keep on going ♪
♪ Always running ♪
♪ On and on on and on ♪
♪ I keep on moving ♪
♪ On and on on and on ♪♪
Hi, my name's Heidi.
I'm here for Sam.
- I'll let him know you're here.
- Okay, thank you.
(female #1)
'Hi, Sam. I have
Heidi here to see you.'
- Okay, send her in.
- 'Thank you.'
Hey. How are you? Have a seat.
Thank you so much for taking
the time to meet with me.
I know you're very busy.
'I mean, you've been with us
for a long time.'
Brent called me a couple times.
He asked me to sit down
with you and...
I mean, I don't know
what to say, I mean
from my perspective,
I just don't get it.
I don't get it because we've
actually spent some time
together 'cause Brent's
brought you around.
He really has high hopes
for you.
But I mean, I don't remember
the last person that talked
that way to me.
'Twice already, we've had,
like, the alcohol thing'
'and being disrespectful.'
Wh-What's the issue, what is it?
What is it? You know,
it happened in Vegas...
- With Spencer?
- 'Yeah. No, just in general.'
I mean, Spencer, the Spencer
thing I don't even get.
But that's your own problem.
'I don't like to get involved'
'with the personal stuff,
but...'
I mean, there really
is no excuse, you know.
I love this company
and I'm very sorry
that anything like that
ever happened.
'It should never have happened.'
Listen, you do good work.
Brent's happy with you.
You seem like
a really smart girl.
This is what I'll do,
we're opening a new hotel
'I wanna put you
on a trial basis over there.'
Okay.
'I wanna get you
out of the clubs.'
So I would urge you
I'm not gonna take this meeting
ever again.
I did it once. Um, so it's up
to you to prove yourself.
An-And you know what?
I hope you can.
But just-just keep
that guy away.
I don't wanna see him.
And really, if he
comes on the property
I'm just gonna kick him out.
- Okay.
- Simple.
- You deal with that.
- I promise it won't happen.
And I will be the best employee
that you have.
- Thank you. Alright.
- Alright.
- Thank you, Sam.
- No problem, thank you.
Don't let, please don't let us
down this time, huh?
I promise. Thank you.
♪ Say what you want to say ♪
♪ It's not gonna change
anything ♪
♪ You've got it wrong ♪
♪ Go ahead and blame ♪
♪ Who you want to blame ♪
♪ It's not gonna change
anything ♪♪
(Lauren)
'You look so summery.'
Thank you.
What are you working on?
Um, I'm catching up on emails
and I'm trying to get
this paper done.
'How's your day going?'
Good. I'm just scared
about the final.
'What's new with you?'
We got a new houseguest.
(Stephanie)
'Who's the new houseguest?'
(Lauren)
'Holly.'
And so we've been, like,
getting her in.
You're kidding.
Holly moved to your house?
She didn't move.
She's just, like, crashing.
Oh, my God.
'Doesn't Holly
know anyone else?'
'Like, this is gonna create
so many problems.'
- 'I don't think it will.'
- 'I think Heidi will be hurt.'
That's all.
I think she'll just be sad.
To be honest...
...I don't really care
what Heidi thinks, so...
[instrumental music]
♪ So stay up and get down ♪
♪ Sleep's just fine ♪
♪ Spent wasting time ♪
♪ So get down get down ♪♪
(Lo)
'I can't believe Spencer
got Heidi to kick you out.'
(Holly)
'He is such a hypocrite.'
I mean, he was staying
with his sister.
- Yeah! I remember that.
- 'For how long?'
Remember and Stephanie
told us it was like
"Spencer, like, expects me
to clean up after him
like, wash his sheets
and stuff."
I know, I'm like cooking for
them, I'm cleaning the house.
Holly, we don't have rules here.
You don't have to clean.
Okay. Well, that's part
of being a good houseguest.
- No, no, no, not at all.
- 'I don't know.'
It's just, it sucks
because, you know
Heidi's always been
my best friend our whole lives.
'Like, I can't believe
she put me in this position.'
What did she expect you to do?
I don't, I don't think
she really
is thinking about my situation.
I can't even imagine
talking to her right now.
- It's just I'm-I'm furious.
- 'Yeah.'
It takes a lot for me to get mad
at people that I love.
It really does and...
(Lauren)
'She's, I think she's just
'in a bad place right now.'
'I don't think
that decision was made'
because that's what she wanted.
- Yeah.
- 'That's the other thing.'
It's like she was the one
that was encouraging me
to come out here, so...
- Yes, please.
- 'Good.'
'But, yeah, I mean,
Spencer's just...'
Is he actually mean to you?
- Oh, like openly and...
- 'Really?'
- Unabashedly.
- I'm sorry, sweetie.
'She practically
booted me out herself.'
At first, I thought
it was all Spencer
and now it's just like...
It probably is. You know it is.
(Holly)
'Yeah.'
(Lauren)
'He just drives away'
'everyone that cares about her.'
Yeah.
♪ Unbreakable ♪
♪ No tears here to cry ♪
♪ So go ahead go ahead ♪
♪ Is that best
that you can do ♪
♪ I'll take everything ♪♪
To be honest, I'm like,
actually really excited
'that you're heading back
to work.'
I'm looking at it
as a great thing
'because you won't be
mopin' around here anymore.'
That's really nice.
[knock on door]
(Spencer)
'Oh, just in time
for some free food.'
Oh, yeah,
that's why I came here.
We lose one, um, mooch sister
and we get another one.
What are you guys doing tonight?
[deep breath]
You're lookin' at it.
Just the two of us,
now three of us.
[Spencer whistles]
Oh, thank you.
'This doesn't
look like fried rice.'
It's Thai fried rice.
It looks just like rice.
But thank you.
'Have you talked
to your sister?'
No, she hasn't even been, like
'talking to me
since she moved out.'
She didn't even tell you
that she's staying at Lauren's?
(Heidi)
'What?'
Who'd you hear that from?
Lauren.
Why would Lauren want Holly
to live with her?
'Cause Holly was homeless.
Who's gonna say no
to a homeless person?
- 'Your mom didn't tell you?'
- 'No.'
- Are you talking to your mom?
- Yeah.
I bet your mom orchestrated
the whole thing.
'It sounds like someone's
stalker mom would do.'
Don't call her stalker mom.
She's worse than Stephanie.
It just shows you everything
I've said about Holly
is completely true
and it shows you that
LC gets her karma
by having the mooch of the
century crashing at her pad.
This is my sister. Am I never
gonna talk to her again?
Are we just not
gonna be friends?
I just, I can't even
believe this and you don't care.
I think it's great
that she's livin' there.
Great, Spencer.
'You're so insensitive
and you're so rude and...'
I'm insensitive? Your sister
is the insensitive one here.
- You're just being an ass.
- How was I an ass?
You're not even paying attention
to the problem right now.
Your sister's the problem.
You're, you're
going off-track here.
Maybe you're the problem.
♪ What else can they say ♪
♪ He hit a wall
and lost it all at 23 ♪
♪ On and on we sing along ♪
♪ Not knowing
what had happened this way ♪
♪ All along we set it off ♪♪
Eat your veggies.
What are you doin'?
You're a young girl.
Step it up, dude.
You're an old man.
- I'm just kidding.
- You must like old men.
I've never dated a guy
that's my age.
- I don't know.
- I'm not surprised.
You're so more mature.
Maturity is probably
one of the most key things
'in relationships, I think.'
(female waitress)
'Is there anything
you want me to clear?'
Uh, you done with this?
Yeah, we're done with that.
- Thank you.
- 'Thank you.'
What is this?
Look what I found!
What is that?
- It might be another present.
- You big nut.
Did you come in here early
and set it there?
Are you kidding me?
I just found it on the ground.
Oh, you went back
and got me this shirt.
It's cute.
- That the one you liked?
- Thank you, yeah.
I can be good when I wanna be.
Yeah, when you wanna be.
No bras with that thing,
okay? Thank you.
- What?
- It's cute.
You're getting better at it.
That's right.
I don't know, it's just
really sweet. Thank you.
At least you know
you're loved, you know?
Thank you.
It's all about growin' up.
Livin' and learnin'.
♪ If I'm gone now ♪
♪ I can see the truth ♪
♪ I'm gonna let you be you ♪
♪ Isn't that what you
wanted me to do ♪
♪ I'm gonna let you be you ♪
♪ What's funny is ♪
♪ I'm not even sad ♪
♪ I'm not missing you ♪
♪ Somebody moved on too ♪
♪ I'm gonna let you be you ♪♪
[theme music]