Well, we have Clark County Jail
Las Vegas metropolitan
police department
and Las Vegas City Jail,
and they're not at any of them.
Why did they have to go
and get themselves arrested?
- That's what boys do.
- 'Like, where are they?'
Do you think we can call
a bail bond store
and they'll give us
a list of jails?
There's so many bail bonds.
But we can call
the actual bail bond store.
I don't know
if it's called a store.
It says "The Bail Bond store."
- 'Frankie.'
- Guess what I found?
Oh, my gosh!
- We're alive.
- 'Are you guys okay?'
We were just walking
through the casino last night
'minding our own business.'
We're walking through
and some crazy dude, drunk.
He's like, "Hey, we got girls.
Come party with us."
'We were like, "Dude,
we're going to bed, chill out."'
He's like, "You too cool for us?
You too cool?"
So Doug's like,
"Yo, you need to relax."
I get in the dude's face.
I'm like, "Get away."
And the dude hits me in the...
Hit me in the chest, right?
'And, like, knocks me down.'
My Bloody Mary
goes all over him.
You were in the casino?
We were in casino jail
filing police reports.
So, you spent five hours
in a room to press charges?
Listen,
if you would have seen...
If you would have seen
how obnoxious this guy was...
- Was he worth it?
- Yes. Yes. He was worth it.
I'm gonna come back here and
look at him in court like, "Ha!"
Do you know how many places
we called looking for you guys?
You got the bail bond!
[laughs]
- Tsk.
- 'Whatever.'
- Wow. Fun night.
- Let's go pack.
- I'm glad you're okay.
- Frankie, happy birthday.
Yeah, thank you
for looking out, girls.
'Vegas. Whoo!'
Idiots.
[laughs]
♪ So far from home now ♪
♪ But you are my lighthouse ♪
♪ And just know those stars
that you see ♪
♪ Well that you're seeing they
are looking right back at me ♪
- Bye-bye, Vegas.
- Kinda awkward with Lauren.
- Hate LAX, but whatever.
- Yeah.
Next time,
we'll come by ourselves.
Hello. I think, actually,
we're gonna hop in this one.
Yeah, do you guys wanna take
the first one?
"Cause we're all going
to the same place.'
- Hey, Phil.
- How you doing?
- Whoa!
- Hi.
Lauren, we need to talk.
I know it's not
the right time, but...
Bye, sweetie.
I'll see you at the airport.
- I'll see you at home.
- Okay.
- Later, guys.
- Get home safe.
You, too.
I'll see you at home.
(Brody)
'Mwah.'
We'll see you at the airport.
♪ We're not the same ♪
♪ I won't do this again ♪
♪ Why this space ♪
♪ And why did it take
way too long ♪
♪ We don't belong ♪♪
[door opens]
Oh, what a surprise.
Look who's in my office.
[both laugh]
- How are you doing?
- I'm excellent. How are you?
Still looking, uh... Looking
for jobs and an apartment.
You do that
from the couch all day?
Yeah. I mean...
How about you?
I had a little talk
with Heidi earlier.
Well, it's good to hear
you guys are...communicating.
- She loves having you here.
- Aw.
'Having her big sis around.'
I bet
she'd love you even more
you know, down the hall
but she's not gonna ever
tell you that...ever.
Well, she's my sister,
and she can tell me anything.
You think she's gonna be like,
"Hey, Holly, move out?"
Heidi wants me to move out?
You're telling me that?
Heidi and I want you
to move out, straight up.
[instrumental music]
Fine.
I'm out right now.
♪ No I don't don't ♪
♪ Have to let it bother me ♪
♪ Bother me now ♪
♪ No I don't don't ♪
♪ Have to let it carry me ♪
♪ Carry me down ♪
♪ No I don't don't ♪
♪ Have to let it cover me ♪♪
- Hey.
- How are you?
- So tired.
- Just got back from Vegas.
- 'Right.'
- Did you guys have fun?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay? You seem so...
- 'Yeah. I'm sorry.'
I'm just like,
stressing on Audrina...
- You are?
- 'Yeah.'
- Have you spoken to her?
- No. We went to Vegas.
- She didn't say a word to me.
- Are you serious?
Oh, are you gonna talk to her?
I mean, when I was leaving,
she was like, "We need to talk."
I mean, obviously, we do,
but it's just...
I think we both have been
putting it off 'cause
we're obviously have to say
things we don't want to say.
'Of course.'
- Oh, my gosh.
- Distractions.
'We have to style these jeans
for Dylan George.'
I marked them for you,
where, right here
we need to just fray them
and then rough 'em up
a little bit
so they look more vintagy.
- We'll do this together.
- Okay. I'll do this one.
- 'Alright.'
- Thank you.
♪ Try to figure out tonight ♪
♪ That I would lose it all ♪♪
If I trip,
you're going down with me.
- Oh, if I trip with you.
- Get the door.
You're going down.
Thank you.
Barbecue.
- You ready to cook?
- Yeah.
That's awesome.
What a week. I can't wait
for this week to be over.
'Oh, you have no idea.
Me neither.'
'Cause Vegas was...
You know what I mean like?
- Catty.
- 'Yeah.'
Just uncomfortable.
Why spend any second of your
life to have that unsettling
ulcery feeling for nothing?
And if those people bring that
* * * to your life
then kick them the * * * out.
You guys want to grill
both at the same time?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
Just so you know,
if you need anything at all
help in any kind of way
even a place to stay
for a few days
figure it out, you're
totally welcome whenever.
Okay. But I just feel like
I can't run away from this.
I have to talk to Lauren.
This has gone way too far.
We used to be
really good friends
and I don't know what it is
that caused this tension.
- And we're both stubborn.
- You're in a sticky situation.
- I know, but it's worth...
- 'That's just the reality.'
It worth that last shot.
Otherwise, you'll never know.
I'm not knocking you to do it,
honey.
I just don't want
to see you hurt, that's all.
I know.
♪ Just an ordinary day ♪
♪ The day that I met you ♪
♪ Then it turned into ♪
♪ An extraordinary day ♪
♪ An extraordinary day ♪♪
[cellphone beeping]
(Lauren)
'She's texting me,
"We need to talk."'
- Who? Audrina?
- Yeah.
- Lauren, Whitney.
- Yeah?
Just a quick meeting about
Danny Guez and Dylan George.
- Are you ready?
- Okay.
We're gonna be doing
the Dylan George launch event.
'This is his new brand.'
'The event is gonna be at area'
the club on La Cienega.
And we're gonna be doing it
in conjunction
'with Inters cope Records.'
They're launching some girl
named Lady Gaga
'who, apparently,
is their new big signing.'
And, also, Whitney, I know you
want to do more styling stuff.
There's gonna be an opportunity
for somebody to style Gaga.
'And she's gonna be the star
of the night.'
'So I think you should do it.'
If there's something
that you're feeling that
she should be doing
and wearing and the way that...
I'd rather have you do it
than the client.
- Okay. Yeah.
- 'Okay?'
Lauren, I'm really gonna
need you to help
Whitney with this event.
I'm gonna be back in New York
that night.
'Cause I don't live here, um,
and I'm not here all the time.
We're gonna just put
our faith in you.
'I think the best thing to do'
'is to let you take the lead.'
We'll be watching you
to see how you deal with it.
- Okay, great.
- 'Don't let me down, okay?'
Thanks, everybody.
♪ I want to see it ♪
♪ I wanna believe it's true ♪
♪ It's true ♪
♪ 'Cause I been stuck in a run
but I dream I woke up ♪
♪ Jogging to you ♪♪
- Hello.
- What's going on?
Nada mucho.
- Where's Holls?
- Have not seen her, actually.
- Was she here this morning?
- 'I think so.'
Did you not have a good day
at work today?
- You seem awfully intense.
- I had a great day.
But I haven't talked
to my sister
and I'm really worried
about her.
I had plans with her.
She hasn't called me all day.
Maybe she was in a tunnel.
I go places where I don't have
service for five hours.
Did you say anything to her?
For you, it's been an hour.
You've seen her an hour.
I've seen her
for 48 hours straight.
So, what did you say to her?
I probably said something
about her moving out
and how we both probably
wanted her moving out.
Do you just not think about
anyone but yourself?
Now she probably hates me.
Hey, you're not
the bad guy here.
You know what,
I can't even talk to you.
♪ Now we'll never really know ♪
♪ Take a guess ♪
♪ Who burned down our nest ♪
♪ We'll never put a face ♪
♪ To the name ♪
♪ Who set our hopes ablaze ♪♪
(Lo)
'This was probably
the weirdest trip'
in Vegas I've ever had.
It was weird, the next day,
how everyone was missing.
The boys and Audrina.
She was missing all day.
She was in the whole trip.
Has she even talked to you
since we've been back?
'She texted me that
we need to talk.'
And she lives 20 feet away.
'I mean, like,
we don't have to be'
'this core group
that always hangs out.'
If she wants to move on
and, like
hang out with other people,
that's cool
'cause I want her to be happy,
you know?
'I only want good things
for her.'
But from my perspective
I feel like you're really
unhappy about it
and...something has to change.
When it's finally resolved
no matter what happens you're
gonna feel so much better.
Even from that.
Do you know what I mean?
How can I feel better when I've,
like, lost another friend?
I don't know. I don't know
what the answer is.
I know what the answer is.
I just don't want it
to play out that way.
♪ You better bring your boys
up at the club ♪
♪ Get up under get get ♪
♪ Get up under get ♪
♪ Get up under get get ♪♪
Here, take over.
Take over. One second.
She's just getting
in her outfit right now
and then she's going on stage.
Are you okay?
I just feel sick
from so much stress.
- Oh, so much anxiety?
- 'Yeah.'
'I still haven't talked
to Audrina.'
Yeah.
Oh, well, I'm really glad
that you made it.
Yeah, no. I'm fine.
- Whitney?
- Yeah, I'm right here.
- I have a problem.
- Okay.
- What's the problem?
- Zipper broke.
The zipper broke?
It came unattached
from that thing, yeah.
This is, like, an intense test.
Here. I'll hold it together.
- 'Okay, ready?'
- Yeah.
'The zipper broke.'
(Whitney)
'Alright, I'm trying to think.'
Do we have another jacket?
Can we somehow...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
- I got it! I got it! I got it!
- 'You got it?'
- Okay, up.
- 'Oh, my gosh! Yay!'
You are superwoman.
You're ready to go.
- 'Good luck.'
- Thank you.
Lady Gaga!
[audience cheering]
[upbeat music]
- So, you're really okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
♪ I'm on a mission ♪
♪ And it involves
some heavy touching yeah ♪♪
♪ I've had enough
of the hard and harder ♪
♪ Times are tough ♪
♪ I've drifted farther ♪
♪ Farther from myself ♪
♪ I won't dwell baby ♪
♪ On my failures ♪♪
[door closes]
- Hi.
Where have you been?
Just trying to figure out
what I'm gonna do.
I left, like, 50 messages,
worried sick.
I just didn't know
what else to do.
I mean, Spencer told me
you didn't want me here anymore
and you couldn't even tell me.
So, you couldn't even call me
and ask me yourself?
You think that
I'm gonna send Spencer home
like, "Oh, go tell Holly this."
It's, like, I'm really sorry
that you felt that way
and I'm really sorry
if he said something to you
or he made you
feel uncomfortable
but you should have come to me.
I just don't understand why
'he would say those things,
then, I don't get it.'
Is there any truth to what
Spencer was saying?
You know, obviously, it's been
a little hard on my relationship
but I want you to stay here as
long as you want to or need to.
You're my best friend.
You're my sister.
You're everything to me.
- I love you so much.
- Sorry. I love you.
♪ Somewhere else
so far from home ♪
♪ My voice it calls out
all alone ♪
♪ Somewhere else ♪
♪ You're somewhere else ♪
♪ Somewhere else
so far from home ♪
♪ My voice it calls out
all alone ♪♪
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Can I talk?
- Yeah.
[sighs]
Okay.
I don't even know
where to start.
I don't know how
it got to this point.
I'm not mad at you.
I don't have any bad feelings.
If anything,
I'm just kinda hurt right now
because I feel like
I'm trying so hard
to be friends with someone who
just doesn't have any interest
in being my friend.
I do care, Lauren. I just...
In the beginning whenever
I did try to talk to you
like, there was just that
uncomfortable vibe.
Well, why wouldn't you
just talk to me about it?
Obviously, it was gonna
be uncomfortable
because I'm living with two
of my best friends
and they're not getting along.
And it's-it's really awkward
for me
'but I don't know what to do.'
Like, every time I would try
and talk to you
it felt like
I was bothering you.
Well, I felt the exact same way.
I just, whenever
I would hang out with you
sometimes
you had a bad attitude
or it was like you weren't
listening to what I was saying.
How so? Like, I don't understand
how I did that...
Maybe you didn't realize
you did.
Then why wouldn't you say
something to me?
Be like, "Lauren,
it hurts my feelings."
- I have in the past.
- 'When?'
The night you came into my room
and sat on the couch.
Yes, the night
when I came into your room
because you wouldn't
even talk to me.
I just feel like I never stopped
trying to be your friend
and you just lost interest,
you just didn't care.
I call you...
When is the last time
you called me and said...
When was the last time
you called me?
- Last week I called you!
- Really?
I said, "We're going out
to Teddy's. You want to come?"
'Two weeks ago,
I had a bunch of people over.'
We were cooking dinner.
I walked out, invited you
and said "Hey, we're cooking."
- "You want to come up?"
- My sister was here.
We went to the Thrice concert.
I had tickets.
Okay, this is my point,
is that I'm always inviting you.
When is the last time
you called me and said
"Hey, Lauren, do you want
to do something?"
You don't like to do anything
I do.
You don't like going to shows.
You don't like any of that.
I go for you, though!
I go, I sit.
I'm awkwardly bobbing
my head at the weird shows
but it's just because
we're friends.
I do it for you.
We're friends.
Like, I want to hang out
with my friends
and I'm trying so hard.
Like, the worst part is, like,
at the end of the day
like, you were
one of my best friends
and I feel like
I've completely lost that.
'I've lost another friend.'
[sniffling]
I'm so, just, like, tired
of trying to make
you be my friend
and I don't know what to do
anymore.
- Like, I feel pathetic.
- I don't...
See, this is so frustrating.
Like, I don't know.
This whole situation just sucks.
I don't know
what do you want me to do?
'I don't know
what to do either.'
I don't want to just be like,
"Fine."
You think that I don't want...
Do you think I'm not trying
right now, Lauren?
Right now!
Okay, so, what about the past?
You wanna keep bringing that up?
Like, you can't start
and keep dwelling on that.
You have to start from now.
Fresh start. Move forward.
If you really,
really want to say, like
"Let's go back.
Let the past be the past."
'That would make me so happy
because that's all I want.'
That's all I want.
Is that really
what you want, though?
It's like everyone doesn't want
us to be friends, you know?
All I want is for you
to just be my friend again.
Okay, then let's do it.
♪ No introductions baby ♪
We used to be
such good friends, you know?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
♪ I know we had our problems ♪
♪ Things didn't always go
the way ♪
♪ That we planned ♪
♪ But I'd rather live ♪
♪ With losing you
one more time ♪
♪ Than regret ♪
♪ Never having tried ♪♪
[theme music]