- Hi, guys.
- 'Hi.'
- How's it going?
- Good.
Okay, the opening of the hotel
is a few days away.
We're kind of just
in scramble mode.
I need you guys
to look at the timeline
double-check that
we haven't forgot anything.
We've got, like,
all hands on deck, so...
- Okay.
- That's what's going on.
(Brent)
'How was your vacations?
What'd you guys do?'
Um, Hawaii, Kona.
- 'Yeah.'
- Yeah, what'd you do?
I was in Mexico
and kinda decided
to get married.
- Shut up.
- 'No, really.'
We were down there and we had,
like, a couple margaritas
and there was a chapel there
and we're like
'"Well, let's just do
a ceremony."'
So it's the craziest thing
I've ever done.
Alright.
♪ You can't take my feet
to the ground ♪
♪ I'm in the air
and I'm flying ♪
♪ Let me live my way ♪
♪ It's my life my own ♪♪
What kind of a do
are you gonna do?
I think just like a little bun.
I'm a little nervous
about wearing
lime green to a black-tie.
Lime green is, like, the cutest
thing I've ever seen.
What do you guys
have going on tonight?
Um, we're doing that SLS opening
but it's a black-tie, so...
Great, have a seat.
- 'Have a seat in here.'
- 'Thanks, sweetie.'
(Lo)
We haven't been to a big,
fun party in a while.
- I'm kind of excited.
- I know.
(Lo)
'Do you know who is doing
the event tonight?'
- It's Bolthouse.
Does that mean
Heidi's gonna be there?
Probably.
- Are you gonna talk to her?
You miss her though, right?
'I mean, it's so sad'
but the main reason we don't
get along hasn't changed.
I know.
Holly told me about the wedding.
Holly also told me
that Heidi does miss you.
Well, I'm sure she misses
having friends, period.
Yeah.
I would love to go up to her
and just be fine but I feel like
because we were so close
for so long
I know how to be her best friend
and I know how to hate her
and I don't know how to do
anything in between.
Yeah. Well,
we'll see tonight, I guess.
♪ Is there ever a dream
of mine you? ♪
♪ Oh you haven't heard ♪
♪ I keep running ahead
of the race ♪
♪ Until I put
that sparkle away ♪♪
This is it.
We got a little bungalow.
It's our little getaway, dude.
Oh, my God.
Wow, this is impressive.
You did this all yourself.
- Good, huh?
- Yeah, I like it.
I am going straight
to the bar.
- Straight to the bar? We need...
- You check it out.
- It's so white.
- Look what I found.
'Champagne?'
That's kinda
like a celebration, dude.
It is, out of LA.
Out of LA.
- Here.
- Out of LA. No more drama.
'Oh, crap.'
'We don't need glasses, do we?'
[Audrina laughs]
We should do this,
like, once a month.
You got it.
Did you realize
every time we go away
it's never just the two of us?
- I know.
- It's always...
With a group of people
and then we don't really
get to spend time
with each other.
And you know
what comes with that.
Drama.
Well, this is gonna be
drama-free.
Better be.
These little trips
will make us a little
closer and closer together.
I'm all yours. You're all mine.
- We're gonna have fun.
- 'You're in trouble now, dude.'
You're in trouble now.
- I'm gonna shut the door.
- Alright.
♪ You know
I want a little more ♪
♪ Love from you ♪
♪ Love to do me right ♪
♪ You know you got
to let me say ♪
♪ Your love for me ♪
♪ You got to do it right yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪♪
(Heidi)
'Hi.'
I didn't know you were here.
When did you get here?
- Just got here.
- Mm.
I just came to see you.
What a surprise.
Yeah, I wanted to surprise you.
♪ Make it worth my while ♪
♪ You cry your eyes out ♪
♪ Baby cry your eyes out ♪
♪ Every time you call
for some sympathy ♪
♪ Make it worth my time ♪
♪ You cry about ♪
♪ Cry about it ♪♪
(Heidi)
So what's going on?
Nothing's going on with me.
What's going on with you?
I just came to see
how you were doing and...
- Well, we went to Mexico.
- 'How Mexico was?'
And, you know,
had a couple of margaritas
and we just decided to...
Just that easy,
couple margaritas
beautiful sunset, get married?
I don't want you
to be upset about this.
How can I not be upset?
You chose to go and elope.
That's my choice, mom,
and that shouldn't affect you.
It does affect me
and it affects a lot of people.
A lot of people have been hurt
very deeply by all this.
Who?
There's a lot of people
who your whole life,
contribute to your life
to get you to where you are
and to help mold you
into the person that you are.
I know, mom. I know.
I just feel excluded
from your life.
Well, I didn't mean to hurt you.
I can't not live my life
worrying about everyone else
all the time too.
Is it even legal?
We're gonna make it legal.
'We're going down
to city hall tomorrow'
and we're getting married.
And I would appreciate it
if you supported me in that.
♪ And then it comes ♪
♪ Just over the shoulder ♪
♪ That strange rush ♪
♪ From cover to cover ♪
♪ And when it comes ♪
♪ It feels like a lover ♪
♪ That strange rush ♪
♪ Is taking me over ♪
♪ And then it comes ♪
♪ Just over the shoulder ♪
♪ That strange rush ♪♪
I don't know what it is.
I'm so antsy lately.
I can't sit still.
Maybe you make me nervous.
I get nervous sometimes.
If we don't see each other
for a while
'it's kinda like
maybe an excitement nervous.'
- I get excited to see you.
- Aw.
That's good. You're a rare one.
So are you.
You think the universe
is in our favor?
I don't know.
Well, do you think you're
comfortable with where we stand?
What do you think?
I think we're at this standstill
that's kind of stuck.
'Audrina, I don't have that big
of a connection with people'
that I give myself to
and spend all that time with
and you're definitely
one of those people.
'And I hope that
it stays like that'
'for as long
as it possibly can.'
What is that?
It's just a ring.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
'I wanna see it.'
It's cute. I like it.
- Thank you.
- You're amazing.
Thank you so much.
I love it.
♪ Take me ♪
♪ I wanna dance ♪
♪ I'll have no regrets ♪
♪ Take me ♪
♪ I wanna dance ♪
(Stephanie)
'This is so crazy.'
I know.
This is beautiful out here.
Hey. How are you guys?
- Welcome back.
- Thank you.
- 'Hi.'
- You look amazing.
Hi, Mrs. Pratt.
[laughing]
(Heidi)
'Um, wait a minute.
Is that Lauren?'
(Stephanie)
'Yeah, Lauren and Lo.'
- Should I go say something?
- Hello.
[laughs]
Hi.
Should I go say something?
Yeah, go do that.
One hundred percent.
- Alright, I'll go.
- 'Now's the time.'
It's beautiful.
Oh, Heidi's coming over.
She looks nice.
- Hi, Heidi. How are you?
- Hi. How are you?
Do you mind if I talk to you
for a second?
- Is that okay?
- I'm gonna let you guys...
- Sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- How's everything going?
- I'm good. How are you?
Good.
I hate that this is awkward.
You heard Spencer and I
got married.
- Are you happy?
- Yeah.
That's all that matters.
[sighs]
What about your mom? How's she?
Um, it's, it's really hard.
Parents.
[chuckles]
Yeah, it's been hard with her.
- You know?
- It's okay.
The things that she said is
just a little bit
irreparable, so...
You just gotta know
that that's your mom and...
I know and that's why, you know
and Spencer understands that
and then...
You have an amazing mother.
You know that?
Of course. And sister and...
- Yeah, I know.
- Stephanie, and you know.
The only thing really missing
in my life is you
and I don't think
that's gonna change anytime.
It's just is what it is,
it's not always fair.
I know.
You been working out a lot?
- Working out?
- Yeah.
- No.
- No?
No, I wish.
I'm just hiding it well
in my clothes.
No, no, no.
I don't think so.
- Mm.
- So?
[sighs]
Don't you feel like
you're, like, 18 again, 19?
I feel like
I don't really get older.
Time just keeps, like, passing
by and I'm, like, wait.
Like, two years ago,
three years ago
seems like five minutes ago
so much, you know?
You know that, like
if you ever really needed
anything, that I'm here?
I know.
[sighs]
Alright, well,
I'm gonna go back to work.
- Okay.
- It was good to see you.
- I miss you.
- I really miss you.
Alright, well,
it's good to see you.
We're walking the same way,
aren't we?
Alright, I'll walk you
out, madame.
♪ I think almost maybe ♪
♪ We should ♪
♪ Almost maybe we should ♪
♪ I think almost
maybe we should ♪♪
- 'Good morning.'
You're up very early.
I didn't sleep much last night.
Where's Heidi?
Uh, she's up earlier
than all of us at work.
Got some pictures
on your camera?
There it is.
'Just Heidi and I, the minister'
and an empty chapel.
'That's beautiful.'
So you headed
to the courthouse soon?
Well, I know you manipulated
and plotted this whole wedding.
'And you know
it's not what Heidi wanted.'
Is that what I did?
You know that she had dreams
of a bigger wedding
with her family there.
I can't let you go
to the courthouse
and make this wedding legal.
This is how we wanted
to have our wedding.
This is how you wanted
to have your wedding.
Oh, really?
Well, Heidi's my wife.
And we're gonna be married
for the rest of our lives
and you're gonna need
to accept that.
So we'll go to the courthouse
and we'll make it legal
so then you'll be my mom.
♪ We've all got scars
as big as ours ♪
♪ A token for the pain
we have inside of us ♪
(Justin)
How do you feel this morning?
I have no doubts.
- 'You?'
- Neither do I.
And this ring means
so much to me.
'Aw, of course.'
I mean, like I said last night,
we've been through a lot.
You mean a lot to me.
- You meant it?
- Yeah, of course, I did.
- Okay.
- You're special to me.
I'm sold, dude.
♪ Someone wake me
when it's over ♪
♪ I'm no Casanova ♪
♪ All because of us like this ♪♪
- Hm. You guys nervous?
- Nervous?
It's, like, the happiest day
of my life. You ready, babe?
- 'Are you ready?'
- I don't know.
I just can't believe
my mom's not here and stuff.
I don't know how I'm gonna
tell her about this.
I thought she would, you know,
be here for, like, this part
but it's good, you know?
I got the rings
right here in my pocket.
Alright, well, I'm gonna go
to the bathroom and freshen up.
- Fresh? You look great.
- Thank you.
Where... You know,
come on, let's just do this.
I'll be right back.
You can't do this.
You mean I just got
dressed up in a suit
and I'm at a courthouse
and filled out
an hour's worth of paperwork
to not do this?
She's gonna remember
this day forever.
And you know
what she's gonna think about?
That she's not talking
to her sister or her mom.
I did not force her
to come to the courthouse.
You think I dressed her up
in that outfit
and put on her shoes...
Why do you have to do it
right now?
Just wait till she's on
better terms with her mom.
Seriously, like, I just
I don't even know
what else to say
but I just think this is wrong.
'Just think.'
Seriously.
[Spencer whistles]
- Hey, you.
Ready to do this?
Yeah, I'm, I'm ready.
Are you ready?
- Hello.
- Hello, come on in.
I'm nervous.
Shh.
- Should we come in or...
- Yes, please.
- You stay here.
- Okay.
I am Deputy Commissioner
Donna Jones.
'I see you guys
wanna get married.'
Well, we kinda already did
get married in Mexico
but everyone's saying
it's not legal, so we're here.
- Alright. Are you ready?
- Let's do this.
We are gathered here today
to unite in matrimony
'Heidi Blair Montag
and Spencer Pratt.'
The tradition of marriage
is most sacred
'and with much joy should be
entered into thoughtfully'
and wisely
and with a deep sense of honor
and understanding
of its responsibilities
'and commitments.'
'So why don't you guys go ahead
and join hands?'
Heidi, will you repeat
after me to him?
- I, Heidi...
- 'I, Heidi...'
- '...take thee, Spencer...'
- ...take thee, Spencer...
(Donna)
'...to be my lawful
wedded husband...'
...to be my lawful
wedded husband...
(Donna)
'...for better or for worse...'
...for better or for worse...
(Donna)
'...for as long
as we both shall live.'
...for as long
as we both shall live.
(Donna)
'Spencer, will you have Heidi'
'as your wedded wife'
through all the days
of your lives?
Before we do this part
right here
I need to know
that everything going on
with your mom and everything
'that you honestly,
in your heart'
'after her,
she forbid you to do this'
and we're going so against
what your whole family wants...
I mean,
what are you talking about?
- This is your idea.
- That's the key thing.
It's my idea.
So I mean,
that's what's throwing this
whole thing off for me, like...
It's just, like,
this rain cloud following me
'and I don't want that feeling.'
And I just feel like
we're doing something
sneaky right now and shady.
I mean, of course,
I want my mom here.
I shouldn't have
to tell you that.
Alright, then we can't do this.
I just wanna give you
the wedding of your dreams
that you have been talking
about now for three years.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And, and I will deal with it.
It's worth it to be with you
the rest of my life.
We'll do it the way you want.
I'm sorry.
- I love you so much.
- I love you.
♪ Everything burns up ♪
♪ In the end ♪
♪ Long way to fall ♪
♪ And it'll break your heart ♪
♪ Everything burns up ♪
♪ In the end ♪
♪ Would you leave it and be? ♪
♪ Leave it and see ♪
♪ You leave it and breathe boy ♪
♪ You breathe in ♪
♪ You take what you'll need ♪
♪ And do what you please ♪
♪ And be who you'll be ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause everything rhymes ♪♪
[theme music]