- Hi! I'm Patrick Star!
And I live with my parents!
Ow!
This is my dad.
[zany music]
This is my mom.
[laughs]
This is my sister.
She's shy.
This is my grandpa.
This is my room!
And this...
♪ ♪
This is my show!
[bright music]
- One last chocolate
Schnorkle Schnobble
and the Klopnodian flag...
[chomps]
Ptoo!
And this Klopnodian war diorama
is officially done!
And I couldn't have done it
without you as reference.
- Looks great, honey.
And I love the water feature!
- Water feature?
- [groaning]
- [gasps] Oh, no, you don't!
This diorama is going to
the Klopnodian
Chocolate Fest tomorrow.
So don't you dare take
a single bite, or else...
look at me...
there will be consequences.
[thunder rumbles]
Understood?
- [gulps] Yes, Mom.
- That's my good boy!
Now it's off to bed with you.
- Whoa!
- Got to get up bright
and early for the festival!
♪ ♪
- [snoring]
[rooster crows, Patrick yawns]
[screams]
[humming melody]
Huh?
What the...?
It can't be.
Oh!
It's chocolate.
[door creaks]
- Patrick.
You haven't seen
my war diorama, have you?
- No.
Why do you ask?
- [slurps]
Just as I suspected...
Klopnodian chocolate.
- But I didn't eat
your "doily-rama"!
I swear!
Or at least I don't remember.
- Oh, Patrick, you lied to me.
And now it's time
for the consequences!
Oh, Patrick.
You can run.
[tense music]
But you can't hide.
[whistles]
All right, Tinkle.
Catch Patrick's scent.
- [sniffs] [coughs, flushes]
- You'd think Tinkle
would be used to that smell.
- [panting]
Gotta hide! Gotta hide!
Gotta hide!
Oof!
- I'll give you scale plus five,
and that's my final offer.
Huh?
Jeez, can't ya knock?
- No time!
"Momsequences"!
Please!
You gotta hide me!
Or this might be
the last episode
of "The Patrick Show."
[knocking]
- ♪ Oh, Squidina ♪
[elegant music]
- Yes, Mother?
- I've been looking
for your brother.
Have you seen him?
- No.
[chuckles]
Don't think so.
- Then you wouldn't mind
if I took a look around,
would you?
- [gulps] Be my guest.
[chuckles]
- Aha!
Huh?
[bed rattles]
Aha!
Gotcha now!
Huh?
- [hisses]
- Dust bunny?
Yeah, you better run!
I guess this means Patrick
isn't here after all.
- Phew!
Yep, just me
and the dust bunnies.
- Glug, glug, glug, glug.
- [grunts]
[gulps, chomps]
[slurps]
Aha!
A mother would know
her son's drool anywhere.
- Ah!
- [grunts]
- And I'll be back
for that dust bunny!
- [humming melody]
- Dad!
Oh, hi, son!
I thought the room
could use more light,
so I painted a window.
Now to wait for the sun to rise.
- [grunts] Oh!
Mom's hunting me down
because she thinks
I ate her "dumpy llama"!
You gotta hide me!
- [sighs]
Son, I... I didn't want you
to find out like this,
but your ol' man
is no stranger to hiding.
I've done some things
I'm not proud of.
I assumed a sweet,
innocent man's identity.
My real name isn't even Cecil.
- No time for stories!
You gotta hide me!
- Sure, son!
There you go.
It's a tunnel to freedom!
- Bye, Dad!
Love you!
- Now to buy him
some extra time.
- Patrick?
Aha!
There you are.
- [as Patrick] Uh, hi, Mom.
[normal voice]
Uh-oh.
[yelps]
- I am so disappointed in you.
I ought to tell your father.
- No, please!
Don't tell GrandPat!
- What do you mean?
[gasps]
You're not Patrick!
- No, but I am Cecil
and always have been.
[tense music]
- [grumbles]
Now it's time to show Patrick
some consequences!
[dramatic music]
- [screaming]
[grunting, screaming]
[squelching, slithering]
[grunts, knocks]
Help!
- Is that you, kid?
- She's after me!
- Don't worry, kid.
Get in the bag.
I'll smuggle you out
to Paris, to freedom!
- OK!
Thanks!
[tires squealing]
Whoa!
- All aboard!
[horn blows, seagulls call]
- [grunting]
- Rogue wave!
Brace for impact!
Yah!
Oh, no, it's a storm!
Oh, no, it's lightning!
[cymbals crash]
Oh, no, it's cymbals!
- GrandPat,
have you seen Patrick?
- 'Bout time you showed up.
I got your chocolate chomper
right here.
Case closed.
[together]
Huh?
- Where'd he go?
- [laughs]
Merci bamboo.
Ah!
[chomping]
Hmm?
[screams]
♪ ♪
[both growl]
[screaming]
[moans]
Huh?
[eerie music]
What?
Oh.
♪ ♪
- Oh, hello, stranger.
- Whoa.
Where am I?
What is this paradise?
- Well, every house has a secret
chocolate room
if you look hard enough.
- My mom is after me because
I ate her "dorky grandma,"
which I didn't do but I totally
might have done because
it sounds like something I'd do.
So I need your help, or she's
gonna "consequences" me.
- Don't worry.
We'll do anything you need.
[ding]
- Anything?
- Anything.
- What a sweet, innocent man
you are.
- What are you gonna do
with that cocoa criminal
when you find him?
- Give him his just deserts.
Let's go.
[grunts]
- [screams]
[groans]
[vacuum clicks, whirs]
[suspenseful martial music]
♪ ♪
- [sniffs, slurps]
He's close.
All right!
Show yourself, Patrick!
Huh?
- Holy cannoli.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- [chews, gulps]
- Aha!
Caught you chocolate-handed!
- But I didn't eat
any more chocolate.
I remade your "doily mama."
♪ ♪
- You hand-carved
all this chocolate yourself?
- Yes, with my mouth.
It all started five minutes ago.
- [shrieks] [laughs]
Just kidding.
I told you
I'd do anything to help.
- [chomping, chewing]
- I bet you're wondering
how my family and I got here.
See, my name is Cecil, and...
- [chomps]
No time for backstory.
So I worked and worked and
built it all from scratch.
[triumphant music]
- Well, that doesn't make up
for it!
That little thief
still needs to pay the price
for eating the original!
- [chomps]
- Hey.
Hey! What...
what are you doing?
- [sniffs] [barks]
- Tinkle, what's wrong?
- Yeow!
- [panting]
- That's the chocolate
from the original diorama!
- [laughs nervously]
Where'd that come from?
- From your beard!
[together]
GrandPat?
- It was you all along!
- That's right!
I ate it!
I ate it all!
And I would've gotten away
with it too
if it weren't for you
meddling whippersnappers!
I waited until
the coast was clear,
then used my old army training
to approach the target.
I fought against those
creepy Klopnodian cowards
in the war.
Also, I was hungry.
[chocolate soldiers screaming]
- [chomps, gulps]
[chews, gulps]
Sweet revenge.
Then it was
a simple matter of covering
my tracks by pinning the blame
on the most obvious suspect.
- Time for a lesson
you'll never forget.
[dramatic music]
I hope you enjoy
your just desserts.
- Just desserts.
[moans]
[gulps]
[bright music]
- Introducing the Choose-o-rama!
- On today's episode
of "The Patrick Show,"
you get to vote
on what happens next.
So whenever you see
this special icon,
just hit the button
on your Choose-o-rama remote.
The choice is yours!
- Grandson, is that you?
- [mutters]
- It's good to hear your voice.
- Nurse!
[upbeat music]
- So our first vote is,
"Does Patrick eat broccoli
or cookies?"
[gasps]
Ew.
Please, please, please,
vote for the cookies.
Please, please, please, please.
- Oh, which button do I press
for a sleepover with Patrick?
Hmmm.
- Sorry, but you can only vote
for the options on the screen.
Let's see those results.
And cookies win!
- [gasps]
[vacuum whirs]
[squelches, gulps]
♪ ♪
Hmm.
[sniffs]
[plate shatters]
I could get used
to this voting stuff.
[burps]
- Well, that's great
'cause there's plenty more
where that came from.
So for our next vote,
you get to decide.
Does Patrick sing
a cute little song?
Or does he walk
on a bed of hot coals?
- [gasps]
Vote now!
Decide Patrick's fate!
Looks like it's gonna be...
hot coals by a landslide!
Well, there you have it, folks.
- Are you guys sure
this is what you want?
- Of course they're sure,
Patrick!
Democracy never fails!
- [mutters] What are we doing?
- My bed's not reclining.
- I voted for the hot coals.
[laughs]
- Um, OK.
[coals sizzle]
Hey, this isn't half bad.
Plus, it kind of feels nice
on my toes.
[flames whoosh]
[together]
Oh.
[flesh sizzles, cracks]
- Ow.
- [mutters, growls ravenously]
[rattles like a snake]
- Well, wasn't that fun?
- I think I need
to go to the hospital.
- Why don't we vote on it?
- [grunts fiercely, groans]
Um, the next vote is,
"Should Patrick
go to the hospital
or wrestle a sea bear?"
- Hit those buttons, folks,
and vote, vote, vote!
It was close, but hospital wins!
We're here live at the hospital.
Stay tuned to find out
what happens next!
- I'm just glad I don't have
to wrestle a sea bear.
[screams]
- You're, uh, Patrick Star, yes?
- [nervously] Uh, uh-huh.
- Looks like you're in today
for some pretty serious burns.
- Well, not to worry.
I'll just be prescribing you
a daily antibiotic ointment
and one dose of
a vicious, brutal, relentless
sea bear attack.
[roars ferociously]
- [screams]
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
[crashing]
- Aah!
I think the ointment's working!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[whimpers]
OK, folks.
Do I take the stairs
or the elevator?
It's up to you!
Try to hurry up
'cause that sea bear
is gettin' pretty close.
[teeth chattering]
[bell chimes]
[audience gasps]
Phew!
Stairs it is.
- Wait!
We're still waiting
on the mail-in ballots.
So let's just give it
a few more minutes.
- Sure, no problem.
- [growling, snorts]
- Hey.
[screaming, crashing]
- Telegram.
- Perfect timing!
I just finished a chapter.
[hums softly]
Drum roll please!
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
- [drumming]
- And the winner is elevator!
Take it away, Patrick!
- C'mon, guys.
Vote to send me home,
or vote for the show
to be over!
- Sorry, Patrick.
But say it with me, folks!
[together]
That's not how voting works!
[elevator dings]
- Uh, hey, Doc.
Isn't there supposed
to be an ele...
[screaming]
♪ ♪
Uh-oh!
I can't see
what I'm going to land on
at the bottom
of this elevator shaft!
- That's 'cause the voters
haven't decided yet.
[easy listening music]
- Uh-huh.
The options are
metal spikes
or a whole lot
of delicious lollipops.
Please, vote for the lollipops!
- I like lollipops.
- Hmm.
[remotes buzz]
[bright music]
- Yes!
Bring on
the delicious lollipo...
- I don't like
lollipops no more.
- [groans]
[quirky music]
Oh!
Ooh!
♪ ♪
♪ Lolly, lolly, leedle, lee ♪
♪ Lolly, lolly, lee... ♪
- Hey!
- Hi, monster.
[slurps]
- You're gonna share those
extra poplollies, ain't ya?
- Uh, I, uh, um...
- Or do my associates have to
break every bone in your body?
- Uh...
[hatch squeaks]
- Time for another vote!
- Press red,
and I'll get pulverized
by monsters.
Press green,
and I'll share
my delicious lollipops!
Vote for fighting so I can have
the lollipops all to myself.
- But if we vote for fighting,
they'll kill Patrick,
and then the show's over!
Well, I'm voting
for "pollylops."
[remotes buzz]
[bright music]
♪ ♪
- [groans] Oh, all right.
[together]
Yay!
- [giggles]
- Now I regret
not having Patrick killed.
- Well, I guess
I'll see you guys later.
- Wait a minute!
You ain't goin' nowhere!
[snarling]
- W... why not?
- 'Cause you're gonna be our
new leader, Mr. Lollypop man!
Ain't that right, fellas?
[together]
Oh, yeah!
- Now, come on!
Let's leave
this subterranean prison
and experience our
new leader's world above!
♪ ♪
[all screaming]
- [laughing]
[all laughing]
- [giggles]
We're gonna turn
this city upside-down!
- Wait.
What do you mean?
[dramatic music]
- It's voting time!
[slide whistle warbles]
- OK.
How should the city
be turned upside-down?
Press red, and me
and my monster buddies
will destroy everything.
Press green,
and I will run for mayor.
[bright music]
Ow!
That really hurt!
And I'm running for mayor.
Ma'am!
Can I kiss your baby?
- Absolutely not!
- I'm running for mayor!
- Oh!
In that case, go right ahead.
- Mwah!
- [giggles]
[dramatic music]
- Hey, what's the...
[screams]
[passengers scream]
- [grunting, smooching]
Bleh-ha!
- [giggles]
- Mwah.
[smooching]
So when you step into
that voting booth tomorrow,
vote Patrick Star!
[cheers and applause]
Now, who's got
a baby I can kiss?
- I do!
- [gasps]
[together]
Hey! That's our baby!
Yay!
- [smooches]
[laughs]
[babies crying,
cameras clicking]
- Well, it's official.
Patrick Star has just
been elected mayor.
- [sighs deeply]
[phone rings]
Hello?
- [slurps] Congrats on
the election, Mr. Mayor!
- Hey, thanks, Squidina.
Are we done with all
this voting stuff now?
- Mmmm, not exactly.
Go ahead and open
your bottom desk drawer.
- All righty.
[timer beeping]
[screams]
A time bomb?
Why?
- Eh, our ratings
dipped a little
during the
"running for mayor" bit.
Anyway, all you got to do
is cut the right wire.
- OK.
Uh, which one?
- [slurps, sighs]
We'll let the audience decide!
- What?
Uh, oh.
OK, press red if you want me
to cut the green wire,
and press green if you
want me to cut the red one.
[timer beeps]
- [straining]
- [groaning softly]
- [whimpers nervously]
- [laughing]
[timer beeps]
- Hurry up and vote!
[rapid dinging,
electricity crackling]
Sleepover with Slappy?
How is that even possible?
[timer ringing]
Uh-oh.
[explosion]
Worst episode ever!
[body thuds]
- [giggles excitedly]
Don't you just love democracy?
[laughs]