- Hi! I'm Patrick Star!
And I live with my parents!
Ow!
This is my dad.
[zany music]
This is my mom.
[laughs]
This is my sister. She's shy.
This is my grandpa.
This is my room!
And this...
♪ ♪
This is my show!
[breezy upbeat music]
- Hey, there, everybody.
Have you ever wondered what
it'd be like if I was blue?
[together]
Yeah!
- And if I could fly?
[together]
Yeah!
- Whoa!
Wow.
Oh.
And what if...
- Ready, on your cue, Patrick.
- What if I was
attacked by a Viking?
[horn blares]
- Let's see.
Opening segment's good.
Jugglers at green room.
And...
- And what about another Viking?
- And break for lunch in 10.
Go for Viking 2.
- [roars]
- Ahh!
- Whoa! Ahh!
- OK.
What next, Squidina?
Squidina?
- Mom, what the heck?
I can't just walk
away during a show.
- Exactly.
You work too hard
for a kid your age,
so I'm taking you here.
If I'm not... my clipboard,
my headset, mom!
Can't this wait until
the season wraps?
- Nope.
You need to run around and play.
- Squidina, tell me what to do.
I'm just the talent.
I'm lost without you.
- Don't worry, Patrick.
You got this.
- Ugh! Uh?
- Oh.
I can be your director.
After all,
I am your biggest fan.
[licks]
Hello, Patrick Star, let's make
something wonderful together.
- Uh.
- You see, it is almost ready.
Our dish just needs
one more ingredient.
Now you simply add two eggs.
Spider eggs.
[cackles]
- [screams]
- Soup's on.
- Oh.
Even your skin is flawless.
Oh, what?
An imperfection?
- Who you calling
imperfect, bub?
This whole production is a joke.
- [sobbing]
- Yeah, that's right.
Get lost, you pathetic amateur.
So "The Patrick Show"
has lost its director, ey?
Well, lucky for you,
I happen to be available.
Now, places, people!
And action!
- When I think
edible, I think...
- Cut!
You're too big.
Scooch over a bit.
- This way?
- Yes.
A little more.
Keep going.
More. More.
Perfect.
Now this is cinema.
Hello, gorgeous.
- So, um, do you still need
me, or am I good to go?
- You're still here?
I'm going to make you a star.
[upbeat music]
- No, mom!
- And have fun.
Bye-bye.
- OK, Squidina,
this won't be so bad.
Think of it as a networking
event or a business retreat.
[laughter]
Huh?
♪ ♪
- [roars]
- Ugh!
[chuckling]
- Well, howdy, camper,
and welcome to Camp Kid.
Is the kid like you ready
to have a kid-tastic day?
[whistles]
- All these children
are giving me a headache.
Oh, what I wouldn't
give for an espresso.
- [screams]
- Well,
we don't have any ex-pressos.
But how about a juice box?
- [sighs]
Look, I'll just get
the PA to do a coffee run.
Hey, kid, get me
a redeye double shot
black and an iced mocha
latte for Mr. Happy here.
- I'm making mud pies.
[gentle music]
- Argh.
- Now where am I going to find
someone to direct the show?
- You know,
you have an emergency
director button for a reason?
- Emergency director button?
Oh yeah!
Hmm.
Let's see here.
[beeping]
- One director coming right up.
- [laughs]
It's showtime!
Let's give the audience
what they really want,
father-son bonding.
[together]
Aww.
- Cue title sequence.
Just a little dab'll do ya.
Beautiful.
Good as new.
Now what do you say we go
toss the old ball around?
- Ball!
Fun!
- Ha-ha, let's go.
- Yay.
Ball.
- OK.
You ready, son?
- Ready!
- OK.
Here we go.
Hmm.
Time to break out
the old windup.
- Almost there.
- Son, I don't think
directing TV shows is for me.
Thankfully,
my second job directing traffic
starts in five minutes.
See you at dinner.
- Wait, Dad, you forgot your...
- Traffic whistle?
I got it right here.
[whistle]
Augh!
- Hello.
This is an emergency.
I need a new show director.
[siren wails]
- Let's get this
picture started.
- Grandpat?
- Quiet on the set!
After all, I'm directing
a silent picture.
[giggles]
- Welcome back.
My guest today is Sandy Cheeks.
- Patrick, I've come
here with dire news.
Bikini bottom is doomed.
- Dagnabbit,
this ain't no talkie.
Use the dadgum cards.
[upbeat piano music]
- [silently]
♪ ♪
[silently]
- Geez Louise, a localized
mass evaporation event
is imminent of Bikini Bottom.
[all groaning]
- Oh, boy.
- Well, you can't say
I didn't try to warn you.
[all groaning]
- [grunting]
[upbeat music]
And I'm ready for the
next segment, Grandpat.
- Yeah?
Well, I'm ready for a nap.
Find yourself a new director.
[together]
Hooray!
- Wow-wee, camper kiddos.
This construction
paper chain is amazing.
- Making paper chains
is super fun.
- I beg to differ.
I'm going to take five.
- Welcome back
to "The Patrick Show."
Join me in welcoming
my brand-new show director,
Bubble Bass.
- Thanks, Patrick.
We are going to
start with a brand-new
segment I like
to call You're Fired.
- Huh?
- Oh boy,
I better get back there.
[panting]
[grunting]
Look, Ma, I'm getting
the exercise you wanted.
Ohh-ohh-ohh-ohh-ohh.
- Well, good luck with the show.
- Next order
of business, I shall
fire everybody else
associated with this travesty
of a TV program.
- ♪ Doo, doo, doo ♪
- You're fired.
- [gulps]
- [snoring]
- You're fired.
[duck quacks]
You're fired.
Fired.
Fired, fired, fired, fired.
But delicious.
- Bubble Bass, your services
are no longer needed.
- Oh no, I'm the director,
which reminds me you were...
- The executive producer.
[together]
Uh-oh.
- But don't worry,
I called you a ride.
- Bubble Bass.
[together]
Whoo!
- You are taking
your dear mama shopping.
Let's go.
March, march, march, march.
- But, Mother...
- Am I still fired?
- Of course not.
- Can I come out too?
- Only if you're ready to work
with your favorite
director again.
- Today's show went in all
sorts of different directions,
but I hope you all enjoyed it.
[loud clang]
- Oh, it sure
is good to be back.
Hey, PA, I'll have the usual.
- One mudspresso
coming right up.
- Ah!
[slurps]
Ahh.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
all: Family fun cruise!
Family fun cruise!
- We're almost there.
Get ready to set sail
on the SS "Family Fun."
- Ooh, what should we do
on the ship first?
- Let's check
the cruise brochure.
- Ooh, gimme!
I'll share with everyone.
Here's the all-you-can-eat
island buffet.
- Infinity kiddie pool.
- Senior singles bingo night.
Whoa, mama.
- Say, son,
can we do this later?
Got to keep my eyes on the road.
[together]
Huh?
[all screaming]
Ugh!
Sure is a thick fog.
That means we made
it to the pier.
What a nifty shortcut that was!
- Oh, Cecil, look!
[horn blares]
- Cruise ship ahoy!
All: Family fun cruise.
Family fun cruise.
Ahh!
- Hmm.
It appears I am being
abducted by aliens.
Finally, I get to meet
some intelligent life.
- Look, honey, a full moon.
- Ooh, what a romantic way
to start our vacation.
Both: Mwah!
- Ohh.
- Ugh.
- I am offended.
Ugh.
- Get your metal claws off me.
Ugh!
- [cackles]
Yes, my fellow invaders,
once we've harvested enough
of these primitive
Earth creatures,
we'll be one step closer
to our ultimate objective,
invading planet Earth!
[laughter]
And there will be
no force in the galaxy
that can get in our way.
[cackles]
- Oh, this parking
situation is a mess.
- And what's with
all these green traffic cones?
- No parking there,
none there either.
Nope.
- Ooh, honey,
there's a spot right there!
- I see it.
And it's mine.
[all scream]
- Let the vacation commence.
- Wow.
- [laughs]
[speaking gibberish]
- Ooh, you're an
angry little bellhop.
Room 42, please.
Oh, I mean, cabin 42.
We're on a ship.
And this must be the elevator.
Going up.
[elevator dings]
- [screams]
[elevator dinging]
- Oh, come on.
Come on.
Well, the elevator's broken.
Looks like we're
using our sea legs.
[horn honks]
OK.
We're looking for cabin 42.
These numbers look
like gobbledygook.
- Maybe it's español-ay.
- Let's give it a shot.
Ooh.
- Mm.
All: Wow!
[upbeat music]
- What a beautiful room!
Well-lit.
Hot showers.
And a king-sized vibrating bed.
- Out of my way,
Grandpat's got to take
this puppy for a test nap.
Oh.
- While Grandpat catches
some beauty sleep,
let's explore the ship.
Meet up for dinner?
Both: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Sweet dreams, Grandpat.
- See you later, Grandpat.
- Enjoy your cruise-y snooze.
- [grunts]
This darn mattress needs
some tenderizing.
[grunts]
Ooh, an electric blankie.
[alarm blaring]
- Engine malfunction.
- Dadgum alarm clock.
Ahh!
Ahh.
[snores]
[electricity zapping]
- There's got to be
something fun on this ship.
Whoa.
- Ohh.
Both: Video game arcade.
- Me first.
Me first.
- Get him; get him.
- The action feels so lifelike.
[laser zapping]
Ha-ha, this game's too easy.
- Stop this at once.
What do you think you're doing?
Both: Wow.
Great graphics.
- Why are you shooting at us?
We're supposed to
invade Earth together.
We're invasion buddies.
- Too much talking.
- Yeah, back to the action.
- [speaking gibberish]
- [giggling]
[all grunting]
- Stop!
We surrender.
You win.
- I win?
Huh? Short game.
I wonder if I can
get my quarter back.
Aha!
Ah, guess too late.
Let's get going, Squidina.
- Time to check in
with our invasion buddies.
'Sup, fellas?
[loud explosion]
- Why?
- Uhh.
[whistles]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I think we found
the shuffleboard court.
- [yawns]
[speaking gibberish]
- Now watch the
shuffleboard king at work.
[grunts]
all: Whoa.
We're free!
- Ooh, Cecil, you put some
muscle in that shuffle.
- Thanks, hon.
[grunts]
[both shouting]
- Ahh!
- Excuse me, sir,
this court is in play.
- [speaking gibberish]
- Well, then you can
shuffle off, mister.
- [screams]
- I told him it was in play.
- Dad, stop.
- You guys hungry?
Both: You bet we are.
- [growls]
- Isn't it beautiful?
Once these super
soldier eggs hatch,
we'll be ready to pulverize
this puny planet
even without
our invasion buddies.
- [gasps]
All-day breakfast buffet?
All: Whoo-hoo.
- Nothing will be able
to destroy our invincible army.
[all gulping]
- No.
Stop eating my soldiers!
- [gulping]
both: Cheers, honey.
- [screams]
all: Huh?
- Ooh.
Breakfast with the captain.
- You, you,
you teraferma twerps,
you ate our entire
invasion force.
- Wait.
You sound pretty cranky.
You should have some breakfast.
- [grumbling]
- [speaking gibberish]
- I hope you're taking me
to the bathroom
for both our sakes.
Ahh!
- Well, saboteurs,
any last words?
- Last what now?
- I think the captain's
looking for feedback.
- Feedback?
Oh.
Well, the breakfast buffet
could use a little variety.
- It was pretty good.
- The decor is a bit gaudy.
- The signage is very confusing.
- Your beds are lumpy.
- The arcade's a rip-off.
[indistinct chatter]
[all shouting]
- And your elevator's broken.
[all screaming]
Ugh!
- Whew.
Thank Orion that's over.
- There's the traitor
who destroyed our ship.
- Wait, I can explain.
- Save it.
I can't believe we were
ever invasion buddies.
[alarm blaring]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Mother.
[loud explosion]
- Whoa-oh-oh.
Look out the back window, kids.
Both: Fireworks.
- What a festive sendoff!
- Why?
Why?
I just wanted
to invade the Earth.
[sobbing]
- Well, that sure
was a nice cruise.
But now it's time
to cruise on home.
Next stop, Bikini Bottom.
Uh-oh.
What did we hit?
- Great Scott, Patron,
some Sunday driver
just bendered our fender.
- Uh, sorry, my bad.
You could just buff that out.
[car alarm blaring]
- I still think
we should exchange
insurance information.
- Oh, I think
I left it on the ship.
I'll be right back.
[all shouting]
- [gulps]
[slurps]