- Hi! I'm Patrick Star!
And I live with my parents!
Ow!
This is my dad.
[zany music]
This is my mom.
[laughs]
This is my sister. She's shy.
This is my grandpa.
This is my room!
And this...
♪ ♪
This is my show!
[upbeat music]
- [humming]
Ooh, that reminds me.
It's time to clean Tinkle.
- [humming]
- Ooh, ooh, sorry, Mom.
I gotta tinkle in Tinkle.
- [growling]
- Why are you looking
at me like that, boy?
Down, boy! Down!
Bad toilet!
[gasping]
Well, guess I'll just
have to save it
for the next gas station
we visit.
- Hmm.
Tinkle has been acting
a little weird lately.
He's been eating more
toilet paper than usual.
Oh, poor baby.
He just needs his mommy.
Tinkle!
[gasps]
He's gone!
Tinkle!
- Tinkle!
- Here, boy!
I've got a new plunge-y for you.
- Ew!
- Oh, no.
He's leaking!
- [growling]
- Sounds like him.
Tinkle?
[blubbering]
Call Dr. Plumber.
- I'm on it.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Hello?
Plumber's office?
- Uh, sweetheart,
that's a banana.
- I got your call.
Oh, hey, we have the
same cell phone carrier.
[both munching]
All right,
let's take a look-see here.
Back in a jiffy.
No, no, no, no!
[yells]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Eee!
- Welp, I figured out the issue.
- And?
- See for yourself.
- Tinkle?
- Your toilet was pregnant.
- Tinkle's a girl?
- Uh, no, Tinkle's a toilet.
- Aw, a toilet!
I am so proud of you and
your 8,000 toilet babies!
- Actually, I count...
1, 2, 3, 4...
10!
- [barks]
- [laughs] And one!
11 little basins of joy.
- Careful.
They're teething.
- [laughs]
- Oh, it'll be so nice to have
the pitter-patter of porcelain
paws around the house.
- Yay!
Potty puppies!
- [humming]
[gasps]
[both growling]
- [gasps]
[grunting]
Ugh!
[toilets yapping]
- Oh! Augh! Ugh!
- [whistling]
[toilets yapping]
- Ehh! Ugh.
[toilet flushes]
[blubbering]
- Ahh!
Huh?
[upbeat orchestral music]
[panting]
[blubbering]
[light music]
- [whistles]
[toilets barking]
- [snoring]
- [groans]
These toilets are exhausting.
- Cuckoo, cuckoo!
- [chomps]
- Huh?
Patrick, it's time
to do your show!
- Ahh!
[grunts]
Hello!
I'd like to introduce
my very special guest,
an actual mummy!
- [groans]
[audience screams]
- So why do mummies
get such a bad rap?
[toilets barking]
No! Stop! Whoa!
[groans]
Cut! Cut!
[yells]
[thunder booming]
- My new creation will solve
all our plumbing problems.
Fatgor, pull the lever!
- [whimpers]
[machine powers up]
Uh, I think we're gonna
need an electricity plumber.
- [groans]
Do I have to do
everything myself?
[thudding]
[toilets barking]
- [whimpering]
But I already went
to the bathroom this month.
[whimpering]
- This is a laboratory,
not a lavatory.
Gah!
[cackles]
Plunge, my plunger.
Plunge them all!
- [growls]
[toilets yapping]
- Yay!
- [growling]
- It's plunging my hump!
[all groaning]
[toilets barking]
- The toilets are running again.
[loud explosion]
- Oh!
What's all the ruckus?
I'm trying to rest my wrinkles.
[gasps]
Toilet puppies?
[toilets barking]
You should all be ashamed.
This ain't no way
to raise an animal.
Toilets, puppies,
toilet puppies...
you gotta show 'em who's boss.
Wah!
- [yaps]
[toilet flushes]
- [laughs]
- [whimpering]
- Ha!
Time for potty training.
[toilets barking]
- [whistles]
Don't make me snake ya!
[grunts]
Yah!
- Ahh...
- [chomps]
- Huh?
- [barks]
- Do not eat that donut!
[grunting]
- [whimpers]
- Yay!
[whistles]
[toilets yapping]
[munching]
[all munching]
- Aw, good puppies.
Who wants to go for a walk?
[all barking]
- Is that all of 'em?
- Hmm.
Uh, let's see.
1, 2, 3, 7...
yep, all 11.
[toilets barking]
- Hey, Patrick.
Didn't you say
there were 11 puppies?
- Uh-huh.
- Well, I only see eight.
- I don't know.
Math is hard.
- Look, there's only
three puppies now.
- Oh, where'd the other 12 go?
- I don't know.
And let's never take our
eyes off...
[gasps]
The puppies!
They've been toilet-napped!
What do we do?
- The one thing we can do.
Both: Go get Mom!
- I tell you, Tinkle,
it sure is swell having
another mom around the house.
Ahh.
- Mom! Mom!
- Someone stole Tinkle's babies!
- [growls, barks]
- Here, Tinkle.
Find the scent.
- [sniffing]
[barking]
- Everyone, follow Tinkle!
[dramatic music]
- [sniffing]
[growls]
[tires squealing]
- Tinkle's leading
us to that warehouse.
- [barking]
[growls]
- Whoa.
What is this place?
Fashion sketches?
A sewing machine?
Plumbing manuals?
- What kind
of monster lives here?
- [cackling] A captive audience
to be captivated by my design!
[together]
GrandPat?
[toilets whimpering]
[together]
The puppies?
- [whimpers]
- GrandPat, what are you doing?
- And who are you wearing?
- Oh, you like it, eh?
I used to be part
of high society.
I was the designer
for haute "cou-toilet"
fashion back in the day.
- Your designs
are so lewd, so lavatorial.
There's such a comfort station.
- Made from only the
finest plumbing fixtures,
my designs were on the runways
of every flush-a-ratty event
until I fell out of fashion.
Then when I saw
Tinkles' puppies,
I knew they were the
perfect raw materials for
my commode couture comeback!
- You're turning Tinkles'
puppies into clothing?
- No!
I'm turning them into
high latrine fashion!
Some disassembly required.
[cackles]
- [growls]
- Hee-hee-hee.
Gah!
[toilets yapping]
- [whimpering]
Back, you outhouse mongols!
Ahh!
No biting!
Oh, my ducky!
I trained you better than this!
[yelling]
No, not the swirly!
Ahh!
- GrandPat,
we are very disappointed
in how old and naked you are.
Come on, poopies.
[chuckles]
"Poopies."
Heh-heh, poop.
- [groans]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
presenting the newest line
of toilet fashion
from GrandPat Star.
[crowd gasps]
- Oh, my.
[chuckles]
- Ooh!
A toilet fashion line
that deserves the flush, eh?
- My brand!
[yells]
- [laughs]
- It's so nice to be
back together
as one big happy family.
- [gasps]
- Hey!
What happened to our TV?
[doorbell rings]
Huh?
[all barking]
- The boob tube had babies!
[camera shutter clicks]
[all barking]
[duck squeaks]
- Ahh.
[grunts]
Nothing more
relaxing than making
a big pot of seasoned
savory soupestroni.
All: Soupestroni!
Soupestroni! Soupestroni!
- Aye, aye, family!
[laughs]
[slurping, chomping]
Hmm.
It's perfect...
[all gasp]
- ly ready to simmer
for about 11 more minutes.
[together]
Aw. Boo.
- Hey, you can't rush art.
- [chomps, gulps]
[munching]
Yeah, he's right.
It needs more time.
- Don't look so glum, chums.
We can pass
the time at the park!
- Oh, the park?
[groans]
[birds chirping]
[thunder booming]
- Hey, Dad, are you sure
that sign is right?
- Sign?
[laughs]
Oh, sweetie, you know I can't
read and drive.
- Yeah, that would be dangerous.
- Safety first.
- [laughs] Here's the park.
- Ooh, there's a spot.
- [chomps]
[tires squealing]
[crashes]
- Whoopsie-doodle.
I bumped the curb.
Ha!
Let me just even out a little.
[loud thud]
Ooh, one more time.
Nope.
[loud thud]
- That's enough!
[hacking]
[all groaning]
- Ooh, I know.
Let's have a picnic!
Yeah!
Just a light pre-soup snack.
- Have fun, dear.
Both: Mwah!
- I wanna try that yoga
in the park.
[hums]
- So, big brother,
what do you wanna play?
- Ooh, ooh, hide and hide!
- Uh, how about hide
and seek instead?
- Never heard of it.
Is it new?
- Eh, you learn by playing.
Ready, set, go!
- [blubbering]
- Go!
1, 2, 3...
- [whistles]
You want the stick, boy?
- [panting]
- Go get it.
Hey, I recognize that stick.
I think he owes me money.
- [growls]
- Tinkie, you rascal.
Get back here!
- You got your cheese.
You got your cheese.
Whoops.
[laughs]
I need more cheese.
[grunting]
- Whew, I'm dead tired.
I gotta rest.
Ooh.
[spooky music]
Eternal rest mortuary?
♪ ♪
That's a great name for a spa.
[grunts]
Last nap I took
outside the house
didn't work out so well.
[snoring]
Ahh!
Ah, people are still
talking about it.
[snoring]
- [whistles]
Oh, what a pleasant surprise.
With this amount
of skin slippage,
this corpse must be
at least two weeks' old.
Time to start
the embalming fluid.
This'll be a tough job,
but I will make you beautiful.
- And bread.
[blubbering]
[chomping]
Ahh, that was the best
pre-soup snack I've ever had.
I just wish I had somewhere
comfier to digest it.
Ooh, I can build
something comfy out
of these fun blocks for kids.
Speaking of kids, I wonder what
my kids, Patrick and Squidina,
are up to?
- [laughs] Golly gee, where, oh,
where can Patrick be hiding?
- [giggles]
- Hmm.
[thunder booming]
- [giggles]
- Maybe...
[thunder booming]
Maybe...
Hmm.
- [giggles]
- Found you!
- What?
How?
Oh, you're good.
[thunder booming]
Ooh, ooh,
now it's my turn to hide!
- Hey!
You're the seeker!
You count while I hide.
- Oh.
I get it now.
1, 2, C, uh, banana.
- 1, 2, 3...
- Hey!
You guys are messing up
my counting.
- Hey, you.
- [whimpers]
- You skipped a number.
- We'll help you count.
We're real good at counting.
- OK.
- One platinum watch,
two silver cufflinks,
three gold teeth...
- Hmm, that yoga class has got
to be around here somewhere.
Aha!
Here I go.
Ugh!
[birds cawing]
Hi!
Sorry I'm late.
I had a doozy of a time
finding you guys.
[gasps]
Such perfect form.
Why, it's like
you're made of stone.
[laughs]
Oh, how embarrassing.
I didn't realize
you're doing silent yoga.
Oh.
[whispers] I mean,
you're doing silent yoga.
Well, uh,
I'll just follow your lead.
[grunts]
[spooky music]
- Ahh!
- Uh-oh.
I better check on my saggy,
baggy, corpse-y customer.
- [gulping]
Blah!
Wow, that energy drink
made me feel 75 again.
I'm so full, I'm stiff.
Even my varicose veins
look plump and youthful.
I feel like a new star.
Whoa!
- I hate it when the dead
can't sit still.
Let's get you into
your burial suit.
- A new suit for the new me.
I love this place.
- [sobbing]
- I can't believe this park
doesn't have
a playground for the children.
- Excuse me, Dad.
I need to hide.
- [laughs]
Build it and they will come.
- Whoa!
Whoa!
[blubbering]
Ahh!
Ugh! Ugh!
[giggles]
Patrick will never find me here.
- We are gathered
here to celebrate...
- Me!
Finding Squidina!
[laughter]
[all gasp]
- Tag, you're it!
Tag, you're it!
- Hold it!
You two shouldn't be fighting
without wearing these cool
mallet mittens I made you.
- Oh, boy!
[groaning]
- Tag, you're it, son.
[laughter]
- I can't look.
- Ah, I can't stop looking.
All: Ahh!
It's a zombie!
- Where?
Turn me so I can see him.
- [yells]
[grunts]
[statues rumbling]
- Ooh.
I don't think I know that pose.
- [screams]
[screams]
- [belches]
- Ahh!
- [chomping]
- Can you keep it down?
I was promised eternal slumber.
- Oh, I'm gonna give
them a piece of my mind.
[all grumbling]
[all moaning]
- Ahh!
- Tag, I'm it!
[blubbering]
- [growling]
- You wouldn't believe
the time I had.
And I learned
a great new yoga pose.
- [groans]
- Um, honey?
- They call this
one the silly goose.
- [chomping]
- Ahh!
- Wait a minute.
This isn't a park.
It's a cemetery full of zombies!
[all screaming]
- Run for your lives!
Zombie!
- Hey, it's my old gang!
Long time no see.
- [growling]
- Lloyd, my old driver.
How about once around the
park for old times' sake?
- Nobody told me we were
playing hide and hide again!
[all growling]
[bell dinging]
[light breezy music]
[all yelling]
Ugh!
- [snarling]
[all whimpering]
[triangle clanging]
- Oh, would you look at that.
Soup's done.
Look at you.
You're all just skin and bones.
Soup's on at our place.
[all cheering]
[zombies groaning]
- [scatting]
Pinch of salt. And it's done.
Here you go.
- [groans]
- [slurp] Mmm, tasty.
- Yeah, this soup is delicious.
- [groans]
- More formaldehyde?
- Uh-huh.
- [slurping]
[thunder booming]
[all whimpering]
- And this coffin is just right.
[all screaming]
- [growls]
- Papa bear?
[yelling]