- Hi! I'm Patrick Star!
And I live with my parents!
Ow!
This is my dad.
[zany music]
This is my mom.
[laughs]
This is my sister. She's shy.
This is my grandpa.
This is my room!
And this...
♪ ♪
This is my show!
- ♪ In our tent,
we are roughing it ♪
- ♪ And our pillows,
we are fluffing it ♪
both: Fluff, fluff!
- ♪ Our tummies,
we are stuffing it ♪
both: ♪ 'Cause way out here,
we're roughing it ♪
- [growling]
- Huh?
It sounds like
something's growling.
- Must be my tummy.
[tense music]
I'm still hungry no matter
how many weenies I eat.
Can I have another one?
- [growling]
- Huh?
- [sniffing, slurps]
- A sea bear!
[screams]
- [screams]
- Here, shake my can
of lucky pennies at it.
If that doesn't scare it off,
we can pay it to leave!
- Shake, shake, shake,
shake, shake, shake.
[gasps]
Oh. [laughs]
It's just Bubble Bass.
- Ah... ugh.
Fine smoked meats, gentlemen.
Waiting in line makes me hungry.
- Oh, yeah!
You're gonna need
a hearty breakfast
if you're going to see...
[inhales]
The new Mermaid Man
& Barnacle Boy Pets Movie:
"Mermaid Worm
& Barnacle Barnacle:
"Episode 6:
The Bubble Blowers Revenge,
Part 2"!
[wheezes]
- Good morning, patrons!
Are you ready to see the new
Mermaid Worm
& Barnacle Barnacle movie?
[moviegoers cheering]
Well, too bad.
Screening's cancelled.
All of our employees
took the day off
so they could see the movie too.
- [nervous laughter]
[moviegoers grumbling]
- So unless I can find
two simpletons
who want to work for free...
- Sir, look no farther!
- And no mother!
- We'll work for free.
- Buddy, let me handle this.
Hey, we're not working for free.
Double that,
and you got yourself a deal.
- Fine, you'll do.
You can all see the movie now.
[all cheering]
Except you two, of course.
You two go tear the tickets
and check for people
sneaking in outside food.
[both gasp]
- Oh!
- [laughs]
- [whimpers]
[both grunt]
- Aye, aye!
- Sir, yes, sir!
- [clears throat]
Tickets, pwease.
Thank you. Enjoy the movie.
[coins clinking]
Have a nice viewing.
- [ripping]
- [screams]
- [chuckles]
Enjoy the movie, you four.
- No outside food
is getting past me.
Halt, villain!
- Huh?
- [sniffing]
- Oh!
- [clicks tongue]
Bad old lady.
- [grumbling]
- Hold it!
You may be family,
but you won't get
perforation treatment from me.
- [sniffing]
- Ooh.
Oh!
- Very disappointing.
- Oh.
- [grunts, yelps] Hey!
I learned that one from you!
- [chuckles] So, son, uh,
how's the new job going?
[yelps]
- Aha!
Just as I suspected.
- B-But, son, we're blood!
- Gravy is thicker
than blood, Dad!
[dish shatters]
Enjoy the show!
- Pink guy and square boy,
go man the concessions stand.
Customers need their official,
theater-approved snacks,
pronto!
Hi-ya!
- [panting]
- [grunts, groans]
- Hmm.
One popcorn please,
uh, with a hint of butter.
- Coming right up, sir!
[panting]
- That's good.
- [panting harder]
- That's enough butter.
No more, thanks.
Stop!
- The butter will cover up
the taste of the sea rats.
Trust me.
- Eww!
Could I get a napkin?
- One napkin.
[grunting]
Okay, forget it.
It's on the house.
- Get those snacks moving!
It's almost showtime!
- Ah!
- [whimpers]
- [laughs]
- Let's go!
Those movie reels
won't spool themselves!
- Yes, sir, yes, sir, yes, sir!
[whistle toots]
I don't know how to do this.
- How hard can it be?
Hmm.
[chuckles]
Nothing to it.
Just follow my lead.
[grunting]
- [grunting]
[both whimpering]
[SpongeBob panting]
[both screaming]
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- Ah, ah, oh, oh.
- [babbles]
- [screams]
- "Curse of the Mummies"?
[screams]
- Oh, don't worry, honey.
Mummies aren't real.
- Let's go find the boss.
He's gonna be so proud!
- [screams]
- Why do parents lie?
- Okay, you two!
We've got a 3D short playing
before the main show,
but I didn't pay for
a fancy 3D projector.
So I need you two to make sure
the short "feels" 3D
by throwing stuff
at the audience.
- Hey, um,
some of these look pointy.
[dramatic music playing]
- Put on your 3D specs!
- Oh, no, a meteor shower!
So many meteors!
[people screaming]
♪ ♪
[both grunting]
[audience grunting]
- Hey!
- Wow, it feels like
an actual concussion!
[yelps]
- Oh, these glasses
aren't working.
[monsters roaring]
all: Ooh.
Ahh.
- [grunts]
[laughs]
That's better.
[radical twangy music playing]
[audience sputtering]
- [laughs]
- Good thing I just got
my pilot's license.
[laughs]
[screams]
- These effects
are hardly believable.
[both yelp]
[motor revs]
I stand corrected.
Both: Whoa!
- This isn't a drive-in theater!
You've got to set up
the next reel!
All: Shh!
Both: Sorry.
- Oh, shush yourself!
- [screams]
- No break!
Projector, now!
Both: [scream]
- And now,
our feature presentation.
Both: Where's the next reel?
[frantic chatter]
- Ooh, I think I found it.
- Oh, hey,
this one looks good too.
- How do we know
which one is which?
- SpongeBob,
I say let the projector decide.
- Quick, Barnacle Barnacle!
We've got to save the
litterbox before it's too...
- Why not enjoy a hot dog?
Both: [muffled chatter]
[all cheering]
[people screaming]
- [slurps]
- Don't you think
it's time for a popcorn?
[people screaming]
- Whoa!
[excited chatter]
- [grunting]
You'll never feast on our blood,
you vampire squid!
[grunts]
- Refreshing soft drinks
at the concession stand now!
- S-so c-c-cold.
- [slurping]
all: Eww!
- That is not okay.
- This is the most blatant
product placement
I have ever seen.
[scoffs] Good thing that stuff
doesn't work, right, Dad?
- [slurping
both: Phew.
Time to watch the movie!
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
- And our favorite seats
are empty!
[farty heroic music]
[both grunting]
[both laugh]
- Mermaid Worm Girl,
I think I love you.
- Oh, yeah? Prove it.
Muah, muah!
Muah, muah, muah!
- Oh.
- Why, that's just a mask!
All: [gasps]
- You're not really
Mermaid Worm Girl.
- Oh?
- What?
Oh, man, we're missing
major plot twists!
- This guy should take
his stupid hat off!
- How's this for a plot twist?
[dramatic music]
Get back to work!
- [stammering]
But we did everything!
- We've been good ushers
and we wanna watch the movie!
- Ushers should be ushering.
- Whoa!
- [yelps]
[growls]
- Oh!
Both: Excuse us.
Oh!
[zany music]
[whimpering]
- Running away from
your responsibilities?
You two should be gluing the
half-eaten food back together!
Both: [whimpering]
- Halt, evil doer,
or face the wrath
of Mermaid Worm.
The utter stupidity
of these pathetic,
small-minded simpletons
is not for you to exploit.
Both: [gasp]
We're pathetic!
- Hey!
You keep out of this, movie!
And you two,
what do you think
I'm not paying you for?
[both grunt]
[audience gasps]
- [groans]
where did
those two hooligans go?
- Ahem.
- Huh?
- I said, ahem!
Mermaid Worm
and Barnacle Barnacle!
I've never seen you before.
- [chatters]
- Yes, Barnacle Barnacle,
that makes sense.
He must be a bad guy!
- What?
Why is the boss
always the bad guy?
[screams]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Got any candy bars, Mom?
- Ooh, check my armpits.
- Does anyone have
a plate of spaghetti?
Ooh. Mmm.
- Hey! No outside food
in the theater!
[yelping]
[screams]
[grunts]
- The end!
- That was pretty good.
What did you think, Bubble Bass?
[rats squeaking]
- The ending felt random.
[bright music]
[music winds down]
- [grunts]
- All right,
that's a wrap on the intro!
- [grunts]
Science.
It's all about
matter and energy.
So if something
is the matter with you,
fix your energy with crystals!
Hey, you're just a rock.
- I'm doing my best.
- Well, do it somewhere else.
[grunts]
- A six-leaf sea clover?
Talk about a scientific anomaly.
Ow!
[whimpers, yelps]
Doggone!
My pseudoscience detector
is going nuts.
[arm whirs, dings]
[gasps]
And it's coming from
the Star family house!
- Patrick's selling crystals
again.
- I should've figured.
He's as dense as a rock.
- Hey. I resemble that remark.
- We now return to one of my
favorite scientifical topics:
astronomy!
If you've ever thought,
"coming up with my own
personality is too hard,"
you're gonna love this!
This sea horsey man
is called "Saggy Terry."
If you were born on a Tuesday
in Jan-tember,
Saggy Terry says
you'll be very unlucky
unless you order Patrick Star's
Scientific Guide to Astronomy.
Order now and we'll throw in
this free healing crystal!
- Hot diggity!
I can cancel
my doctor's appointment!
- Hush your pie hole, Patrick!
That's not astronomy.
- Huh?
- It's astrology.
And astrology ain't scientific.
You can't go spouting off
any old cockamamie thing
and call it science.
- Well, but I have a lab coat.
- No, no.
No pseudoscience.
- [hisses]
- All right, kids, Sandy's here,
so get ready for some
genuine real science!
- Uh...
- Say, Patrick, have you ever
wondered how a radio works?
- Ooh, ooh, ooh! No.
- Okay.
Well, wouldn't it be neat
if we could look inside
and see how it works?
- Yeah!
[grunts]
- Ah! You pulverized my radio!
- Where are all the elves
that play the instruments?
[screams]
- No pseudoscience! No!
- Uh...
- Take two.
All right, Patrick,
you ready to see something
you've never seen before?
- Hey, I have seen this before.
The TV is showing my lunch.
- Oh, Patrick, that's not a TV.
It's an X-ray of your insides.
- [gasps]
That's inside me right now?
[laughs]
[grunting]
- What in tarnation
is he doing in there?
- Pizza!
Ah.
Ooh, more pizza!
Ah... ooh!
- What the...
kids, I don't know
how he's doing this,
but that is absolutely not how
the digestive system works.
All right, Patrick,
time for a real easy experiment:
the volcano!
And we're fixin'
to make it erupt
with a chemical reaction
derived from baking soda
and vinegar.
- So that's how volcanoes work.
- [chuckles]
It's not a real volcano.
It's a model.
- Nuh-uh. This is a model.
- Pose.
[camera shutter clicks]
- Here, you need to add
precisely one teaspoon
of baking soda.
- One tea-spork of baking dust.
- [whimpers]
- Get ready to learn!
[dramatic music]
- [grunts] Oww.
- And now for our next
real science topic...
- Status, uh, eel...
- Static electricity.
GrandPat Star will demonstrate
how to build up a static charge
by shuffling his feet.
- [grunting]
- Just keep at it
and we'll check back in on you
in a little bit.
- [laughs] I'll give it
the ol' sawtucket shuffle!
- For our next real experiment,
we'll demonstrate
that plants can hear.
- Wait, what?
- We played this specimen
only classical music,
and look how
it has affected its growth.
He's even devising a theorem
for Neptune's Paradox.
[music winds down]
- Pardon me.
[rock music playing]
- We played this one punk rock.
Whoo! Now it refuses
to clean its room
and keeps talking about
"fighting the man."
And this is our control group.
We don't play it music at all.
- Oh, well, here's something
that's not music.
Squidward!
- [grunts, groans]
- Oh, Patrick, I don't know.
- Oh, it's no trouble.
I love playing for an audience
that can't walk away.
- [whimpers]
[off-tune clarinet music]
♪ ♪
- Creepin' kudzu,
look at it grow!
I guess the plant likes it.
- [growls, blubbers]
- Or not.
[gasps]
- [screams]
- Ooh, hey, look, this crystal
ball said that would happen.
Space.
In the vast biggy-ness
of our universe
lie billions
and billions of dots.
Some dots are small.
- [shrieks]
- Some dots are loud.
And this dot has its own donut.
- Captain, there's an anomaly
with the planet Saturn.
- Put it on display, Pat-Tron.
Oh, no.
It's a Celestial Patrick,
Devourer of Worlds.
Battle stations, Pat-Tron!
That gastric giant
must be stopped.
Charge capacitors.
Raise shields.
Engage ion thrusters.
- Ooh, a sprinkle.
- Battle down the hyperdrive.
- Ahh.
[metal creaking]
- This ain't science.
It's barely science fiction.
[dramatic music]
[rocket whooshing]
♪ ♪
Patrick!
- Aww, are you gonna
spray me again?
- I want to,
but there's no water in space.
[arm whirs]
- No water? Uh-oh.
[grunts]
[ding]
And that is how a star is made.
Isn't astrology fascinating?
Aww, man.
I'm doing it again, aren't I?
- Mm-hmm.
- [whimpers]
- What the?
What in tarnation is going on?
- Mm-hmm.
Work it, work it, work it.
- Oh, no!
We forgot about GrandPat!
He done got static supercharged.
- [cackling]
[grunts]
[laughing]
Cower before me, Bikini Bottom!
[laughs]
Witness my unlimited power!
[grunts]
- We gotta fight electricity
with electricity.
[grunting]
♪ ♪
[electricity whirring]
- [yelps]
- Did it work?
♪ ♪
[energy whirring]
[heroic music]
- Go get 'em, Patrick.
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
- That will be enough, GrandPat.
- Eh! Go suck an egg!
- I see.
Well, I guess I'll solve this
through the process of...
elimination!
- [whimpers] Oh!
[grunting]
- Feel the weight
of the evidence.
- [cackling]
- Missed me. Huh?
- Oh.
[chuckles]
Pardon me.
I'll just be going.
[screams]
- Surprise!
[laughs]
- [farts]
♪ ♪
- [laughs] My leg!
My leg!
- Oh, rats.
I forgot to charge my phone.
[babbles]
Go for Slappy.
- [grunting]
- Uh-oh.
[screams]
- Patrick! Are y'all okay?
- Just taking
a little super power nap.
- [laughs]
[bus horn honks]
♪ ♪
Hey, Patrick,
wanna learn about gravity?
[cackles]
- Talk about
a failed experiment.
- Ooh, this day is turning out
just like
my horoscope predicted.
- Horoscope?
But that's...
[grunts]
- [laughs] Huh?
- Yes, Patrick.
It's pseudoscience.
- Strudel science.
- Eh, close enough.
- [babbling]
[electricity crackling]
[screams]
- Wow, Sandy, we did it!
We used science to stop him
and save the day.
[metal thunks]
- Ha! You didn't stop me!
Nothing can stop...
[crystal clanks]
[babbles]
- Gee, I reckon pseudoscience
is good for something after all.
So if you've released
a super villain
due to your own
scientific negligence,
try out our latest assortment
of gems and essential oils!
They're great for bonkin',
bashin', and smashin.
When science attacks,
they're sure to be a knockout!
- Call now and we'll throw in
other heavy objects!
[phone rings]
- Yes, hello?
I'll take your heaviest object.
[crystal tinkles]