- Hi! I'm Patrick Star!
And I live with my parents!
Ow!
This is my dad.
[zany music]
This is my mom.
[laughs]
This is my sister. She's shy.
This is my grandpa.
This is my room!
And this...
♪ ♪
This is my show!
[bright music]
♪ ♪
- [crows]
[screeches]
- Presenting
the Cecil Breakfast Special:
burnt pancakes, burnt toast,
and, to wash it all down,
burnt orange juice.
Let's dig in.
Mwah!
- [yawns]
Morning, Dad.
- [sputters]
- Oh!
- Morning, Mom.
- [sputters]
- [blubbering]
- Morning, Squidina.
- [sputters]
- [blubbering]
- Morning, GrandPat.
- [gulping]
[sputtering]
- Gee, what's everybody
spitting at?
[dramatic music]
- Son, what's happened
to your face?
- Huh?
- Did you have
an accident, Patrick?
- Uh, I don't know.
Did I?
- I think I know
what's going on.
Patrick is off-model.
[both gasp]
- Off-model?
Does that mean I'm pretty?
- Mm, not exactly, Patrick.
It means you look a little...
different.
- Deh, I'm sure my fans
won't notice.
Speaking of which...
- It's "The Patrick Show,"
featuring your beloved host,
Patrick Star.
- Hey, everybody!
[all scream]
- Oh, it's hideous!
- It's unappealing!
- It's unnervingly symmetrical!
- I think he's cute.
- Change Patrick back!
Change Patrick back!
- No, it's OK, folks.
It's still me.
Squidina, cut to commercial.
- I wish we could, Patrick.
But all our sponsors
got so grossed out,
they fled for the hills.
- You can't sell anything
with a face that ugly!
- Let's got out of here!
- Oh, we need help!
- We got to get you back
on-model
before our viewership
is completely gone.
- What do we do?
- If there's anyone
who can help you
look like your old self,
it's Granny Tentacles.
- Wow.
[giggles]
[doorbell rings]
- Ooh.
Uh, who is this?
- Oh, hi, Granny Tentacles.
- It's Patrick.
- I'm not home.
- Can... we...
come... in...
please?
- [groans]
Fine. Come in.
I don't know how much more
my door can take.
- We've got to put Patrick's
correct face back on.
- Well, I always put my face on
first thing in the morning.
I just don't feel ready
until I do.
[alarm blaring]
Come on. Come on.
Let's have a look at you.
♪ ♪
[bell rings]
- [grunting]
- Well, what do you think?
- Huh?
What the...
I look like that hideous
old hag next door,
Granny Tentacles.
[screams]
So do you!
- What do you want
for free, kid?
I can only do the one face.
- [groans]
Guess I'm still off-model.
[glass shatters]
- Maybe we need
some fatherly advice.
[drill whirring]
Don't worry, Patrick.
Dad can fix anything.
He's always working
on the family boat.
[drill whirring]
- That ought to do it.
[explosion]
Ah, perfect.
[knock at door]
- Hey, Dad.
- Do you think
you can fix my face?
- Well, gee, son, I've never
fixed a face before.
- Hmm.
[bell dings]
There you have it, then.
Just pretend that my face
is something
you've fixed before,
and absolutely nothing
will go wrong.
- Um...
- Great idea, son.
Let's get to work.
- Um!
- [grunts]
- All right, son.
This is gonna hurt you
a lot more than it hurts me.
- [laughing] Stop it!
[jackhammer rattling]
- [grunting]
[blowtorch roaring]
- It tickles.
- Phew!
That ought to do it, son.
Now you look shipshape.
[ship horn blows]
- [blubbering]
- Oh.
- Oh, I'm so sorry, son.
I forgot about the christening.
[glass shatters]
- You OK, Patrick?
- That depends.
[grunts]
Am I on-model yet?
It's gonna take a miracle
to get my face back,
maybe even
the strongest miracle of all,
a Christmas miracle.
- One problem, Patrick.
Today is Easter.
- [gasps] An Easter miracle?
That's even better.
Let's turn the TV
to the Easter Bunny tracker.
- Jolly old EB
has already made it
halfway around the world
at breakneck speed.
[gasps]
But what's this?
He appears to be stuck
inside Plankenstein's castle.
[thunder booming]
- [laughing maniacally]
- Please, let me go.
The children need my eggs.
- Silence,
you cotton-tailed freak!
You're not going anywhere
till we cut you open
and figure out how you lay
those technicolor eggs.
Why, it goes against
the laws of nature.
- Mm, afterwards I'll whip us up
an Easter egg omelet.
[door bangs open]
- Out of my way!
[all yell]
- Wait up, big brother!
- Oh, almighty Easter Bunny,
I've been such a good boy
this year.
Getting my face back
is my one Easter wish.
- I don't usually give
extra handouts on Easter,
but I guess you did save me.
Maybe there's something
that could help
in my magical
Easter Bunny basket.
- Oh!
It's just a stinky old
Easter egg?
- [roars]
- [screams]
- [snarling]
- [with high-pitched voice]
How do I look?
- Ew!
- Yeesh.
- Huh?
[screams]
[glass shatters]
- [grunts]
- [normally] You got to have
something, Easter Bunny.
I'm at my wits' end.
Maybe a lucky rabbit's foot
will do the trick.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold it, kid.
How's about a... a... a lucky
chocolate rabbit's foot instead?
- [munching]
Hmm?
[groans]
- Patrick, look, there's a note.
"To find your missing face
travel forward
through time & space."
- "Lucky numbers:
13, 31, and sideways 8."
- Wow, rabbit's feet
really are lucky.
To the time closet.
- Thanks, Easter Bunny.
[screams]
[all moaning]
- As for you three
troublemakers,
you want to see how I lay
those Easter eggs, huh?
[grunts]
[all screaming]
Ha! There's plenty more
where that came from!
- How far into the future
should we go?
- How about...
to season five
of "The Patrick Show"?
[electricity crackling]
- Huh, everything
looks the same.
- Ho, ho.
Welcome to the new
"Patrick Show."
Today we're gonna talk
about friendship and feelings.
[giggles]
[laughter and applause]
- I love feelings.
Both:
Ugh!
- Not the Patrick
we're looking for.
- We must have moved
to a different network
for season five.
- [speaking backward]
both:
Nope.
- Nuh-uh.
- Not that one.
- [snarls]
- Stop! That's the one
we're looking for.
- [snarls]
- Yup, classic Patrick.
- I don't think so.
- Hmm?
- [grunts]
Stupid dial won't turn anymore.
- Patrick, stop.
I think we made it
to the end of time.
[mysterious music]
Shoot, we went through
all that time,
and no sign of on-model Patrick.
Guess you'll be
off-model forever.
- Hey there, end-of-timers.
- Huh?
Well, you seem chipper.
- I didn't say anything.
- And welcome
to the final episode
of "The Patrick Show."
both:
On-model Patrick?
- Huh?
Off-model Patrick?
Both:
What are you doing here?
[laughter]
I remember now.
- Wait, what?
- We switched times...
- So that I could try...
- My time's version of...
both:
The Cecil Breakfast Special.
- We went through all that
just so you could have
some burnt pancakes?
- Well, duh.
My time's Cecil
makes these gross,
buttery, fluffy pancakes.
Hey, where'd they go?
- Beats me.
[gulps]
Mmm.
Disgusting.
Well, I think it's high time
I head back to my time.
- Aw, leaving so soon?
- We're gonna miss you,
on-model son.
- I'll miss you too,
off-model family.
All:
Aww.
[cheers and applause]
- Hooray!
- Oh, yes, this was
the best final episode.
[electricity crackling]
- Let's agree to never
go off-model again.
- You said it, sis.
- Hiya, kids.
- Mom? Dad?
- We got plastic surgery
so you'd feel less bad about...
uh, about your hideous face.
- But we see that's not
a problem anymore.
- Aww.
Well, in any case,
I think you guys
look more beautiful than ever.
- Oh. [laughs]
Oh, that's my ear.
My cheek is over there.
- This was the best Easter ever.
- It sure was.
All: Happy Easter
from the Star family.
[bright music]
♪ ♪
[bell dings]
- Order up.
One ultra-double-mega
Krabby Patty.
- Oh!
- With cheese.
- Eee!
- [laughing] Oh!
- Well...[chuckles]
I'll just be going.
- Huh?
Hey.
There's something wrong here.
- No refunds.
I mean...
[chuckles nervously]
Whatever could be wrong
with this perfectly good patty?
- There's no cheese on it.
- Phew.
Yeah, well,
you'll need to take it up
with the new fry cook.
He's still getting his sea legs.
- Don't mind if I do.
- Ah, it's still good.
- [gasps]
- Excuse me, Mr. "Chef,"
but I...
[fire whooshes]
Huh?
[grunts]
[gasps]
You're working here now?
- Howdy, son.
Just started this morning.
- Oh, my Neptune.
[alarm rings]
Dad, can I please help you
make Krabby Patties?
It's the only thing
I've ever wanted today.
- To tell you the truth, buddy,
I've pretty much
got things under control.
Oh, what the heck?
Welcome to the team.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Here's your hat, team member.
- I need an extra...
huh?
Patrick, what are you
doing back here?
I ain't paying you a salary too.
- I don't even like celery.
- Welcome to the team.
[fire whooshes]
- Whoa!
- Order up.
- Dad, I'll treasure this
always.
- No, you are going
to serve it to the customer.
- [yelps]
One Krabby Patty.
- Huh?
- Wonder where it went.
Hold on.
Got you a new one.
Oops.
Hold on.
Got you a new one.
What the...
- Oh, boy.
- [moans, gulps]
Enjoy your lunch.
- Has anyone seen Patrick?
He's supposed to be on
"The Patrick Show" right now.
- Sorry, Patrick's
working for me now.
- Oh, well, we'll just
film the show here.
- No, you don't.
No one distracts me employees
while I'm around.
- Hmm.
Not while you're around, eh?
Did I say "The Patrick Show"?
I meant
"The Eugene Krabs Story."
- "Eugene Krabs Story"?
I like it.
Finally, a chance to share
me stories with the world.
Where should I start?
- At the beginning.
And talk real slow.
- Oh, gee, I don't know.
I guess...
[dramatically]
There I was,
adrift in a sea
of amniotical fluid.
I could see a light.
- [grunting]
Time for some
reality television.
- Hey, lady, when's somebody
gonna take our orders?
- This is ridiculous!
- But I don't work here.
- Food, food.
- [whimpers]
all: Food, food,
food, food, food.
- Whoa!
[grunts]
OK, satisfying a bunch
of angry people...
I can do that.
I work in television.
Listen up, people!
We're on a tight schedule here!
Form a line, and no back talk!
All:
Yes, ma'am.
- And I want this tip jar full!
I need 57 hockey pucks,
walk them through the garden,
and don't spare the bride.
And I need them yesterday.
Oh, hi, Dad.
- Oh, hey, Squidina.
I'll have that for you
in uno segundo.
Patrick, how are those
cheese slices coming?
- Sharper than I thought.
I have a couple
of ouchie boo-boos here.
- My mother's intuition
is tingling.
Someone in here
has an ouchie boo-boo.
[grunts]
- Huh?
- [grunts] Mwah!
My brave boy.
I'm never letting you
out of my sight again.
- It looks like we've got
our newest hire.
- Wow, we've got me, Mom,
Patrick, Squidina,
the whole Star family.
- Yeah, the whole Star family.
We're not missing anyone else.
- Hey, coming through.
Move aside.
I'm on a fancy date.
Move it.
Right this way, mon poubelle.
- [groans]
- Ooh, now, this
is some great footage
for our senior citizen segment.
What can I get you?
- [inhales deeply]
- She'll take a small...
- I...
- Fries...
- You...
- From the dollar menu.
Here's a coupon.
And I'll have a deluxe patty
with the expensive fancy sauce.
- That'll be $159.95.
- Sure.
Let me just, uh...
I, uh... [chuckles]
Ah, you've got this,
right, sweetie?
- Well, I got your wallet,
I got your wheels,
and I got to get out of here.
So long, sucker!
- Ah, OK.
[chuckles]
Hey, Squidina,
how's about hooking me up
with the old family discount?
- Sorry, GrandPat.
If you can't pay for your food,
you'll have to work off
your debt.
- Debt?
Work?
[sighs]
All told, one of our
better dates, actually.
- Welcome to the team, Dad.
- [sputtering] Thanks, son.
[indistinct chatter]
- We're serving customers
at record speed.
If only there was some way
we could serve even more.
[sharp crash, glass shatters]
[yelps]
- Oops.
- Great idea, Patrick,
a drive-through.
- A what, now?
- Uh, yeah, can I get
a Krabby Patty...
[tires screech]
Ah!
- Uh, yeah, can I get
a Krabby Patty?
[indistinct chatter]
- OK, now we're getting
a little behind schedule.
[all clamoring]
- Yeah!
Who's running this joint?
- Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Come on, Squidina.
You can do this.
Dad, we need 150 Krabby Patties.
How many do you have ready?
- Uh, one.
- We need help.
You're hired.
You're hired. You're hired.
Hey, you're hired.
- [gibbering]
- You're hired too.
And you're hired.
- [gasps] M-m-m-me?
Hired at the Krusty Krab?
- Not you.
Him.
Squidward, we need your help.
- [yelps]
Get in there.
Get to work.
- [screams]
Ow!
- [groans]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, no.
Patrick, we have
too many workers
and not enough customers.
What should we do?
- I know where we can get
some customers.
- Ah!
- From my time closet.
[electricity crackling]
- [grunting]
- [hooting]
- [yells]
[people clamoring]
- [chomping]
[whinnies, chomps]
- Whoa!
- Huh?
- Need food.
[breathing heavily]
- No hygiene, no service.
Hmph!
- [growls]
[roars]
[chomps]
- Uh, enjoy your meal.
[whistle blowing]
[all clamoring]
[electricity crackling]
- [hooting]
[objects crashing]
- And that brings us
to yesterday.
[sharp crash]
Huh?
Newfangled technology.
[dull thud]
What's going on out there?
- [hooting]
- [screaming]
- [shrieking]
- [gobbling]
[yells]
[glass shatters]
- [grunting]
[explosion]
- [yelps]
- [whimpering]
- [humming]
- [sniffing]
Is that your recipe?
- Yes, it's mine.
[explosion]
[all screaming]
- Who did this to me restaurant?
Star family!
You ruined me!
[sobbing]
- Crybaby.
- Dear Neptune,
please send me someone
who can help me fix
me dining establishment.
Huh?
- [groans]
[dinging]
[electricity crackling]
[dramatic music]
Huh?
What's happening?
- Whoa!
- Whoa, whoa!
- [yelps]
- [yells]
- [grunts]
[all whimpering]
- Well, that wraps up
this segment.
- What's on next?
- The schedule says
customer testimonials,
but I think
that's getting bumped.
[all screaming]
- Hey, it's 6:00.
[watch beeping]
We're off the clock.
All:
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Great day's work.
- A job well done.
- Quitting time.
[both screaming]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
- Huh?
The Krusty Krab, as good as new!
And it's all thanks to you,
young Mr. Squidward.
- Really?
I saved the day?
- Aye, lad, you did.
So I'm hiring you official-like.
Now get to work!
- Right away, Mr. Krabs...
I mean boss.
[laughs]
[humming]
[breathes deeply]
Things are looking up
for Squidward J. Tentacles.
Huh?
[sighs] Typical.