- Hi! I'm Patrick Star!
And I live with my parents!
Ow!
This is my dad.
[zany music]
This is my mom.
[laughs]
This is my sister. She's shy.
This is my grandpa.
This is my room!
And this...
♪ ♪
This is my show!
- Juggle, juggle,
juggle, juggle,
juggle, juggle, juggle.
And I'm all warmed up.
Okay, Squidina,
let's kick it up a notch.
- Roger that.
[grunts]
[zany music]
- [grunting]
all: Ooh.
- [grunts]
- [grunting]
all: Ohh.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Thanks!
[grunting]
all: Wow!
- Nothing can stop me now.
[stomach grumbles]
[toilet flushes]
Except a bathroom emergency.
Squidina! Pause it!
[remote beeping]
[music distorts and stops]
[chuckles]
[grunting]
I need a volume-teer
from the audience.
[grunts]
Now un-pause it!
[remote beeping]
- [screaming]
- [panting] Door!
Give me a shortcut
to the downstairs bathroom!
- What's the big emergency,
Patrick?
- Gotta go potty!
- Oh, no!
- Yah!
[yelling]
[grunts]
[playful music]
[yelling]
♪ ♪
[all panting]
[strains]
[whimpering]
- Ah, there's no greater
thrill in life
than installing a new doorknob.
- Aah!
- Oh.
I guess that means we're done.
You still got it, Cecil.
What is this?
An extra doorknob?
[Tinkle barking and panting]
- Is that a treat for Tinkle?
- Uh, you bet it is.
Here, Tinkle!
[Tinkle barks]
Shall we?
- And now to exit the bathroom
by gently turning the doorknob,
which is always exactly
where it's supposed to be.
Hmm.
No doorknob?
Studio audience: Uh-oh.
- [laughs maniacally]
It's okay.
Nothing to worry about.
[hyperventilating]
I-I'll just push the door open.
Uh.
[grunting angrily]
[panting]
Guess I'll just wait
until someone else comes in.
I wonder how long before
I starve to death in here.
[eerie music]
- There.
Glad I was able
to kill ten minutes
with this arts and crafts
skeleton
made from bar soap
and toilet paper rolls.
- [echoing]
You'll never get out!
[disembodied screaming,
lightning striking]
- Aw, man.
[panting]
Is anybody out there?
[sighs]
There's gotta be another way.
[bell dings]
Hey, a creature hole.
Maybe whoever lives
in there can help.
Hello?
Is anybody in there?
[heavy metal music playing]
[music continues quietly]
Anybody?
Open recipe!
Well, I guess I'm just gonna
have to die in here.
[screams]
- [screaming]
- Ugh.
I don't know how much more
of this screaming I can take.
What the heck is going on
with Patrick?
- [whimpering] I gotta get out!
[suspenseful music]
- Oh, let me help you, Patrick.
[both straining]
Oof!
- [groans]
[shaking lips]
- Hi there, son.
How's your day going?
- The door! The door!
[grunting]
[sighs]
It's no use.
We're trapped.
- Oh, what you call trapped
I call mother-son bonding time.
And maybe I could clean
this place up a bit
while I'm at it.
- [grunts] We're ruined!
The show is a travesty!
Unscheduled bathroom breaks are
eating into our budget,
and the budget is
tight enough as it is.
- [humming]
- I need to sit down.
- Squidina, the door's locked
from the outside,
and I need help getting it open.
- 3:00, second Wednesday
of the month.
You know the drill.
It's time for GrandPat's
monthly shower.
Wah... wah!
- [continues humming]
- Oof.
You guys, the door,
we're trapped!
- ♪ She'll be coming around
the mountain when she comes ♪
♪ She'll be coming around
the mountain ♪
♪ She'll be coming
around the mountain ♪
♪ She'll be coming around
the mountain ♪
- Ha-ah!
- ♪ When she comes ♪
- [vocalizing]
- GrandPat Star, everyone.
- Whoa...
ah!
[panting]
- Great work, GrandPat,
as always.
- Thanks.
- Wonderful, Pop.
- You too.
And them pipes, son.
- Yeah, Dad, great singing.
- Amazing.
- Aw, shucks.
- Anyway, I've got a turkey
in the toaster.
- I've got brain surgery
this afternoon.
- I have to grow a new wart.
- And I gotta get back
to The Patrick Show.
All: So I better get going.
[all gasp]
Where's the doorknob?
- That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
- What?
You mean we're trapped in here?
- Yep.
- Okay, think.
Panicking isn't gonna
help us get out of here.
So, everybody, let's just...
[inhales and exhales deeply]
And calm ourselves down.
[all breathe deeply]
[all scream]
[all screaming]
- [grumbles] That's the worst
barbershop quartet I ever heard.
[grumbling]
[all screaming]
What's going on in there?
All: Don't close the...
[sadly] Door.
[Granny screams]
- Help!
Help!
- Don't fear, fair neighbor.
Help is on the way!
Yah!
SpongeBob to the rescue!
All: Don't close the...
- Sorry, folks,
but I need to use the loo.
All: Don't close the...
- Where's the doorknob?
- Here to fix the pipes.
All: Don't close...
- Knock, knock.
Can I interest you in a lovely
new toilet brush?
All: Don't cl...
- Uh, somebody ordered pizza.
- I did.
- Okay, fellas.
Bring 'em in.
All: Don't...
[siren wails]
- Let me in.
Let me in!
All: D...
- The treasure be
right through here, lads.
[indistinct chatter]
- Say, what's everybody
lining up for?
- I don't know,
but it's gotta be good!
[siren chirps]
- Ugh, Patrick... ow...
what are we gonna do?
What about the show?
- Well, our whole audience is
in the bathroom.
Why don't we just
do the show right here?
- That's a great idea!
- All right!
Yah!
[grunts]
- [screaming]
[remote beeping]
all: Ooh.
- [grunts] [loud crash]
[remote beeping]
Juggle, juggle, juggle,
juggle, juggle, juggle...
[all cheering]
- [weary cheer]
- Hey, hey, hey,
you don't gotta beg,
'cause the party has arrived.
[air horn blasting]
- Dad, you're so embarrassing.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is that Patrick Star I see?
Well, howdy, Patrick.
How's things?
- Oh, you know,
same ole, same ole.
Doing the show,
locked in the bathroom.
You know how it is.
- Locked in the...
well, have you tried
sending a message to anyone?
Maybe with that bottle you've
been juggling the whole time.
- [gasps] [clattering]
I have been juggling a bottle
the whole time.
- Yup, that's your ticket
right there,
ole message in a bottle.
- But I don't have
any paper or pens.
- Well, gosh, I suppose I could
be your message in a bottle.
- Okay!
Then, Mr. Dartfish, sir,
you're our only hope.
Do you understand your mission?
- Sir, yes, sir.
- Good.
'Scuse me, folks.
Just gotta reuse
this background.
[militant whistling]
Good luck, soldier.
[toilet flushes]
I just flushed my neighbor
down the toilet.
How about you guys?
Doing all right?
Huh?
[water bubbling]
[mysterious music]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
Aah!
Tinkle!
- And me!
It wasn't easy, but I found help
and... this doorknob.
Ta-da!
- Huh?
Ah!
[anticipatory music]
♪ ♪
We're free!
But in a way, I'm gonna miss
this time we shared together.
I almost wish
it would never end...
[all clamoring]
- [grunting softly]
Whoa!
- Well, I'm starving.
[stomach rumbles]
If only I had a...
[bell dings]
Ooh.
Who left this doggy treat here?
[chuckles]
[gulps, sighs]
I wonder what...
- Yah!
[screaming]
[musical flatulence]
♪ ♪
[all cheering]
both: Aww.
Happy anniversary, hon.
Mm-mwah.
- Is it just like you remember?
- Squidina, when you get
to our age,
you don't remember a darn thing.
Isn't that right,
sea star with glasses?
- Mm-hmm.
- Ooh!
What's this dance?
- Oh, this is the gahooga hooga,
one small part
of the incredibly elaborate
Klopnodian wedding ceremony.
- Oh! Here comes
the most important part.
The final step to consummating
any Klopnodian marriage,
the kissing
of the Stoinkping Cake.
- Mmm.
- You may now kiss
this Stoinkping Cake.
- Aww.
Hmm.
[giggles mischievously]
- I'll never forget
kissing that delicious...
- [gulps]
- Patrick?
- I don't remember that part.
- Where's Patrick?
Patrick!
You traveled back in time
just to eat Mom and Dad's
wedding cake?
- No.
I also ate the hors d'oeuvres...
and one napkin.
- Does this mean Mom and Dad
aren't married anymore?
- Shh!
[whispers] They'll hear you.
- Who?
[booming footsteps]
[both grunt]
[horn blows]
- We are the Klop-Guardians.
- Uh-oh.
- Wah!
- We have come to take
this unwedded Klopnodian
back to her homeland.
- Goodbye, family.
It was nice knowing you.
- But that's our mom!
You can't do this!
- I'm afraid they can, Squidina.
And I'm afraid
I'll have to return
to my life as a bachelor.
- Whoa.
Do you still have those chips?
- So long, kids.
Goodbye, sea star
with a mustache.
- Wait!
If we can finish
a traditional
Klopnodian wedding,
can our parents stay together?
[suspenseful music]
[both laugh]
- Klopnodian wedding can
take weeks,
even years to finish
the rituals involved.
- We'll do it by sunset,
whatever it takes.
- [gulps]
- [chomps, gulps]
- Very well, pushy squid girl.
But you'll need this Klopnodian
wedding law guidebook.
We'll be watching you
to make sure you get it right.
- [gulps]
- Oh! I'm so excited.
And I have the perfect dress
to wear for the wedding.
- Uh, Mom.
It says here, a wedding dress,
or glangadang,
should be something old,
something bruised,
something stuffed,
and something confused.
Uh...
- Now, there's gotta be
something else
in here that works.
Bruised but not confused.
[grunts]
Old, but not stuffed.
Oh, my. Stuffed,
but in pristine condition.
- You ain't too bad
yourself, lady.
- Fresh!
- Ah!
- GrandPat?
- Conflabbit!
Can't a geezer eat a sandwich
in a dusty old trunk in peace?
- Wait a minute.
Old,
bruised,
stuffed,
confused!
- Who am I?
- [gasps]
- Whoa!
- I've found my wedding dress!
- Homina-what?
Whoa! Wah!
[musical flourish]
Eh.
- Well?
- What do you think?
[both grunt]
- Phew.
We've got a lot more
pre-wedding rituals,
like the Skreek Streak
Marathon...
- Ah!
[pained vocalizing]
[mumbling]
[fire whooshes]
[both grunt]
[all cheering]
- The ceremonial
Shklitza Toss.
- [grunts]
- Over here!
- [groans]
[chuckles weakly]
[both grunt]
[all cheer]
[bouncy music]
- Dakkadakka tent, check.
Unklik outfits, check.
Great job so far, Patrick.
[lawnies cheering]
Oh, barnacles!
We gotta get the lawnies
out of here
to make room
for the Klopnodian guests.
- Leave that to me, little sis.
[strains]
[lawnies cheer]
- Have a great wedding!
- Good luck with the ceremony!
- Congratulations!
- Now to round up some guests,
Klopnodian style.
[panting]
[straining]
Huh-yah!
All: Gahooga hooga!
- Wow.
Great work, Patrick.
- Ah!
- Wah!
- [muffled scream]
- So how we doing on time?
[chuckles nervously]
- Kittoong!
20 minutes till the sundown!
Kittoong!
- [whimpers]
[horn blows]
Places, everybody.
Let's get this wedding started.
Up first, the Ror Faglork,
also known as the ring bearer.
- Blah.
[mumbled] That's my cue.
Klop-Guardians: Hmm.
- Wait, wait.
Oh, it's not ring bearer,
it's ring bear.
- Ring what?
[sea bear growls, huffs]
Ohh.
[sea bear roars]
Aah!
[snarling and screaming]
Klop-Guardians: Mm.
- And now
the traditional
Klopnodian windpipes.
- [laughs]
["Wedding March" playing
in flatulence]
♪ ♪
["Wedding March"]
- My almost wife,
wearing my very own dad.
She's never looked
more beautiful.
- The things I do for love...
- And now to begin
the pinching of the bride.
- Pinch for good luck.
- Then the smiting of the bride.
- Ow! Ah!
- Finally, the lighting
of the bride.
- Wah!
[sobs]
- Aw, GrandPat.
I didn't know
you cried at weddings.
- You're up next, Dad.
Take the Stoinkping
to the end of the aisle.
- This'll be a piece of cake.
- Well, if you can get past
the Argle Gargles.
- Wha?
[Argle Gargles growling]
all: Argle gargle!
- Yah! Charge!
[grunting]
[exciting music]
Yeah!
I'm okay...
[grunts]
[straining]
- Ooh.
All: Touchdown-gadoink!
[crowd cheering]
[cheers and laughter]
- Still got it.
- Hey, Squidina, what'd I miss?
Oh.
[angelic music]
Cake!
- [whispering]
Patrick, remember how we got
in this mess in the first place.
What's your one golden rule
for this wedding?
- Don't make eye contact
with the monkeys?
- No! Don't eat the cake!
- Now we join these two
in holy marscipony...
- [whimpering]
- To be sweet to one another
as they travel
through the sugary glaze
that is life...
- Oh, Patrick.
I bet you're wondering
what flavor I am.
Chocolate, vanilla,
stinky sock,
or maybe even ice cream.
- Uh!
I can't take it anymore!
I need that cake!
- Patrick, no!
- [laughing maniacally]
Ugh! Oof!
Hey.
Who dares to get
between me and cake?
- It is I, Patrick
from the year 3,000,000.
- Ohh.
- Huh?
- I come from the future
to deliver a dire message.
Patrick Star,
you cannot eat this cake.
- Phew.
- Because I want
to eat the cake!
- What?
- Oh, no, you don't.
[both grunting]
- Aw, come on.
- Hand over the cake or else.
- Or else what?
- Or else I'll punch you in...
[both grunting]
I saw it first!
- I retroactively saw it first
from the future!
[both sobbing]
- There goes our wedding.
Back to Klopnod I go.
- Oh, no!
The bachelor-ification has
already begun.
- It's all ruined.
What are the Klop-Guardians
gonna think?
- Little squid girl.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
- How could you...
- [whimpering]
- Manage to finish
every Klopnodian tradition
in record time?
- Wait, what?
- You even did newest tradition,
the Yekkle Glek,
also known as ze battle
of ze time-traveling children.
- Oh.
[chuckles]
Yeah, well, you know,
that was, uh,
totally on purpose.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
They didn't finish
the last tradition,
the kissing
of the Stoinkping Cake.
- How much time is left?
Oh, no!
It's too late!
- Hmm.
Ah.
I bought you 15 seconds.
- Well, what are ya waiting for?
Kiss that cake already!
[both cheering]
[Patricks grunting]
[all cheering]
[both smooching]
both: Mwah!
Both: Happy anniversary, honey.
Mm-mwah!
- Is it just like you remember?
- Sweetie, when you've survived
the robot apocalypse,
you don't remember a darn thing.
[both grunting]
both: Oof! Whoa!
[dramatic music]
- Ooh.
[both smooching]
[explosion blasts]