Previously, on Pandora.
You're not Professor Osborn.
I'm his teaching
assistant, Xander Duvall.
I feel it incumbent to make
sure you're looked after.
- What's your name?
- Ralen.
I'm Jax. This is Greg,
Thomas and Atria.
How did you convince your master
to let you go to the academy?
Adari masters aren't known for
emancipating their clones.
I killed him.
I've had to call in
more than a few favors
to cover for the fact
that you stole a ship.
I accompanied the students
home on the Earhart.
Tereshkova will leave New
Portland in 36 hours
and return the specimen to Earth.
You going to eat those
or stare at them 29/7?
It's 24/7. You're on Earth now, Jax.
I do not understand.
They don't appear to provide
any nutritional benefit
from my analysis of the ingredients.
It's not about the nutritional value.
It's about the yummy.
Perhaps you heard the old Earth
expression, "When in Rome."
I have not.
Just eat them, because if you
don't, I definitely will.
I second the mouthful.
They do have a pleasing taste.
See? What did I tell you?
What's going on?
Is everything okay?
They're calling us in.
What is it?
What's happened, Jax?
The Tereshkova. She's gone.
What do you mean, gone?
Destroyed.
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.addic7ed.com -
So, what's the deal
with the cyber-tech?
I've had them since I was six
years and four months old.
Your parents must have been loaded
to afford that kind of pricey hardware.
We got by.
You're originally from Earth, right?
My grandparents settled on
Euripides after the migration.
How much of that cyber-wear
do you have under there?
I've heard about subdermal
nanite enhancements
that allow you to pleasure
your partner with...
Tell you what.
All this small talk isn't
really working for me.
And, honestly, you looked a lot hotter
in your profile holo.
Have a nice day.
Loser.
Who's a loser?
Not you if that's what you're
worried about, roomie.
I wasn't.
Did you hear the news?
I was on a date. So lame. What's up?
The Tereshkova was destroyed returning
to Earth from New Portland.
How?
I'm still trying to find
out more information.
Apparently it blew up
near the asteroid belt.
There was a crew of over
150 people on that ship.
That's awful.
Did you know anyone onboard?
You seem really shook up.
Just hits close to home, I guess.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
Do you think you can
log on the datastream
and just see what you can sleuth.
Sure.
Where are you going?
I'm late for a game with
Greg, Atria and Thomas,
I promised I'd be their fourth.
Volleyball, huh?
You never cared about v-ball
until Greg asked you to play.
I thought you weren't at
the academy to meet boys.
I'm not.
I lost the two most important
people in my life.
I'm not looking to care
about anyone else.
Can you just please let me
know what you find out?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Mind's not on the game, is it?
I'm sorry.
I can't stop thinking
about all those people
who perished on the Tereshkova.
And you're wondering if it
had anything to do with us.
Okay, Jax, it didn't.
An EarthCom battle cruiser
is one of the most
sophisticated pieces of
machinery in the universe.
There are a million things
that can possibly go wrong.
How about I help you get
your mind off all this,
otherwise you're going
to drive yourself crazy.
What are you doing tonight?
I thought you had your
med rounds on campus.
Yeah, you're right.
What are you doing tomorrow night?
I don't know.
You tell me.
I'll let you know.
You want to hit the showers?
- Oh!
- Not with you.
Yeah, that-that's not...
I-I didn't mean it like that.
Bye.
_
I am not going to let a
murderer speak on campus.
If you think your Seeker can come here
and there won't be consequences,
you can think again.
He's evil.
A man who preaches nothing
but vile and depraved hate
under the guise of religion.
On Adar, clones aren't
servants, they're slaves.
I spent my whole life
trying to escape that life.
To come here, to the
academy and to Earth.
And now you're just going to let
this serpent-tongued
Mephistopheles speak on campus?
Atria, I understand how you feel.
But this institution
is based on the tenets
of tolerance and mutual understanding.
And, most importantly,
free speech and a sharing
of divergent ideals.
The Seeker's ideals are not divergent.
They're depraved.
The Adari have enslaved generations
of manufactured humans to serve them.
I know.
I was one of them.
Look, his speaking engagement
is not an endorsement
of his views by the school.
Seeker Hubbell was invited by
the Adari Student Council.
Now, our bylaws are very
clear on this point.
You of all people should appreciate
why cloning is outlawed everywhere else
in the Confederacy but in
the Adari territories.
It's not that I'm not
sympathetic to your position.
But we have an obligation
to be open to all voices,
even the ones that we object to.
Not to mention, the Adari were
a vital ally during the war.
They used clones as cannon fodder
and broke their own
non-aggression pact with Zatar
to join Earth.
With friends like that,
who needs enemies?
Atria, please,
look at the big picture.
If there was one person on campus
I thought would understand,
it was you, Professor.
I guess not.
So, what do we really know
about what happened to the
Tereshkova, Professor?
Not nearly as much as we should.
The official investigation
is already underway.
I want you to lead up
the unofficial one.
For me.
What about the specimen that
we discovered on New Portland
that we were transporting?
There's no sign of it
in the debris field.
Someone or something
didn't want that creature
brought back to Earth.
What do you want me to do?
There's an enemy agent on campus
who was onboard the Tereshkova
48 hours before it was destroyed
under suspicious circumstances.
I suggest you begin with him.
You want me to spy on Ralen?
Everyone just wants to pretend
it's unicorns and rainbows
to keep the Adari happy in
case there's another war.
I'm sure that's not true.
I can't believe EarthCom would
sacrifice its values and beliefs
for political expediency.
I am considerably younger than you,
having only been manufactured
less than a decade ago,
but I'm not nearly as naive, Jax.
You're absolutely right, Atria.
I can't change what
happened to the Tereshkova.
But I can make a difference here.
I want you to know you're not alone.
If Seeker Hubbell has a right to speak,
then we have a right to have
our voices heard as well.
Very loudly.
Go back to Adar!
And the maker of all things
looked upon our planet,
and beheld it was corrupt.
And he brought great suffering
to the people of Earth.
But then, praise be.
He offered us a pathway to the stars
to find a new home.
We embarked unto the
stars in our own arks
to new worlds
for those who heard his word.
And I, as his instrument...
Your hate has no place here, Seeker!
I preach only his
divine love, my child.
You enslave an entire
race and call it love?
Hypocritical much?
How can we enslave those
who have no souls?
He has provided them in his grace
to serve only us and his word.
You've got quite the imagination,
I'll give you that.
Go back to Adar!
Go back to Adar! Go back to Adar!
You all right?
Lights.
Three?
It is good to see you again, Nine.
Why do you tremble at my touch?
If the Seeker were to know I was here,
- I would be put to death.
- He won't know.
And you can stay here with
me as long as you wish.
You don't have to go back to Adar.
- I must.
- No, that's what they tell you.
Don't believe it.
Look at me.
For the first time in
my life, I'm happy.
I found a place where I fit in
and where I'm appreciated
for who and what I am.
You do not understand.
I must go back,
because I'm part of the resistance
and I need to return to save our
sisters and brothers on Adar.
And I need your help.
I need your help.
With your contacts,
you can help rally the resistance
to sabotage the cloning factories
and inspire a revolution
against our Adari masters.
If we do it,
we'll be on our own.
EarthCom will not help.
They won't risk alienating the Adari
as long as they believe the
Zatarian threat remains.
Then you must go back to Adar yourself.
It's the only way.
You have to hide me.
If they find me here...
Just getting dressed!
Be out in a minute!
Hold your Zatarian equines!
I'm so sorry about what happened today.
That was so messed up. Is
there anything I can...?
Is there anything I can do?
There is nothing. Thank you.
Do you want to go for a drink, maybe?
Not at this time.
Well, if there's anything you need,
anything at all, just...
Just let me know.
You know we're all here for you, Atria.
I'm here for you.
I understand.
Well, that wasn't very convincing.
We'll have to work on that.
The Adari are so repugnant.
As if we should be
eternally grateful to them
for helping us during the war.
I know I'm not.
Yeah, I don't know if teaching
you sarcasm was the best idea.
Anyway, the Adari acted
completely out of their own
self-interest in joining Earth
during the war.
The Adari are not all the same.
My people traded with
them during the war
before they betrayed our alliance.
You assume they all believe
in the word of the Seeker.
I can promise you they do not.
You seem to know a lot about them.
I became acquainted
with many of the Adari
during our short-lived alliance.
Some I would even consider friends.
Don't tell me you approve of
them using clones as slaves?
I do not.
My people believe all
beings are entitled
to determine their own destiny.
The Adari are untrustworthy,
treacherous and wrong to presume
they can speak for the creator
of all things.
Yeah, maybe we shouldn't
be talking it to you.
Yeah, I imagine it's kind of awkward,
since you were on the losing side.
We did not lose the war, Jax.
We agreed to cease hostilities.
It's not the same thing.
Are you saying you took a time-out?
If you were not my friend,
I would feel as though I
was being interrogated.
Sorry.
What's with Purple-licious?
Hey, Atria.
Ordering some chili cheese fries?
What are chili cheese fries?
My loves.
It is truly blessed to be
home again this very night.
Is it not?
Indeed, my Seeker.
To be amongst our own kind
and away from the infidels
of the otherworlds.
I must cleanse myself of their sin.
Atria, you shall accompany me
to conduct the bathing ritual.
It is my duty and my honor, my Seeker.
Come.
You too, Atria.
Cleanliness is indeed
next to godliness.
Especially in those...
hard-to-reach places.
Got a question for you, Tommy Boy.
You want to know if I think
Atria's been acting strangely.
See, you do have some
telepathic ability after all.
Hardly. You'd have to
be blind not to notice.
Exactly.
That's why I think it's
time we sit down with Atria
and find out what's really going on.
And what about Protocol class?
We'll get the notes later.
You are such a bad
influence on me, Jax.
Good afternoon, Ralen.
I am so dreadfully apologetic that
I have been remiss in meeting with you
ever since you first
arrived at the academy.
I know you are quite a
busy and important man.
Ah, but never so busy that
I should not reach out
to such a brave young cadet
who would seek to
bridge the differences
between our two races by coming
to Earth to study and learn.
E pluribus unum.
"Out of many, one."
But that is not why you invited
me here, is it, Professor?
No.
No, I suppose it is not.
Let us speak plainly.
You suspect me in the destruction
of your war vessel, do you not?
And if I did suspect you of
sabotaging the Tereshkova,
what would you say?
That I have nothing to hide.
Do you, Professor?
And what do you think, Mr. Duvall?
I think we can all agree
that whatever happened
was a terrible tragedy,
no matter the cause.
Most diplomatic.
It is truly an honor
to finally meet you.
Your reputation is, of
course, legendary on Zatar.
I understand you have
become quite friendly
with my niece, Jacqueline.
She is a fascinating young woman.
Indeed she is.
Will there be anything else?
No, not at the moment.
But I have no doubt we
will meet again soon.
Of that I am sure.
Actus non facit reum nisi mens sit rea.
What's it mean?
It's Latin.
"The act does not make one guilty
unless the mind should be guilty."
What do you want me to do?
Stay very close to our
young Zatarian friend.
He's not as smart as he thinks he is.
Atria, we need to talk.
Jaxie!
Okay, Atria, I think you've had enough.
Let's get you to bed. Come on.
Tommy, why don't you say
that like you mean it?
Okay, now I know you've had enough.
- Let's go, come on, come on.
- No, no...
- Oh, oh, oh...
- What is going on
with you, Atria?
Does this have something
to do with Seeker Hubbell?
Pfft! Seek this.
Talk to us. We're worried about you.
Oh, you are just so cute.
Oh, oh! No, no, no.
That's okay, sweetie.
Oh, you're cute too.
Yeah, so I've heard.
Uh... we need to talk, Atria.
I don't want to talk. I just want to...
You know Thomas's abilities.
He's a gifted Telepath,
and I know you hate it
when he reads your mind.
But I think we're going to have
to make an exception this time
for your own sake.
You can't do that.
Can't do what?
You can't read my mind.
Please.
You know I can't...
He won't, as long as you
tell us the truth, okay?
What are you doing, guys?
You know I can't really
read minds like my pop.
I can only sense intense
feelings and emotions.
I know that and you know that.
Don't you find it strange
that she doesn't know that?
Not to mention she doesn't even know
what chili cheese fries are.
But those are your favorite.
Your dinner, my Seeker.
Thank you for this bountiful meal
which you have graced
me with this night.
Oh, one more thing before you go.
I believe you have forgotten something.
Pardon, my Seeker?
To slit my throat.
Isn't that why you're here?
To kill me,
the way you said you killed my son?
After you ran away,
I thought I'd never see you again.
I am a citizen of Earth.
You can't hurt me.
Is that what you think?
You are, and always shall be,
the property of the Adari.
So...
I only have one thing
left to say to you.
Welcome home...
Atria Nine.
She was the one who insisted
on going back to Adar.
To destroy the cloning factories.
She believes she can make a difference.
And you don't?
I do not want to be punished.
You won't. We can protect you.
We can get you sanctuary on
Earth, just like Atria Nine.
You would do that for
me after I lied to you?
If you help us, yeah.
Look, I was scared. I'm sorry.
It was a mistake.
Sorry about what?
I did not know what it
would be like to be free.
My sister gave me that gift,
and I rewarded her with betrayal.
The Seeker knows Atria's
on Adar, doesn't he?
Yes.
That was why he came to Earth.
It was all part of a plan
to lure her back home.
I'm so sorry.
What is he going to do with her?
What he does to all runaway clones.
The Seeker will find out
everything she knows
about the resistance...
and then he'll kill her.
It is so wonderful to have you back.
Your sisters were most cooperative.
They had no choice.
You would have punished them.
I like to think it's because
they're happy in my service.
You were happy for a time as well.
But then you corrupted my son
with your heretical ideas.
Lenar did not need me to
know right from wrong.
He knew it was sick
to keep manufactured humans as slaves.
Believe what you wish,
it does not matter.
I only have one more question for you.
I'll tell you nothing.
You'll kill me either way.
That's true.
But there are many ways to die.
Some less painful than others.
I'm not the scared child
you knew when I left Adar.
I no longer fear you.
You should.
Perhaps you need a reminder.
The most important role
for all clones is to be
obedient to their master.
A lesson you seem to have forgotten.
It is his will.
Look, I can appeal to the
Adari Embassy on Earth
by lodging a formal complaint.
But they consider clones property,
and are unlikely to act.
You're talking politics.
I'm talking a human life.
Your student.
She looks up to you, you know.
Your idealism and your empathy.
You're been such an
inspiration to her and to me.
How can you just turn
your back on her now?
I'm sorry, Jax.
I really got to go.
You know, I would expect
this from my uncle.
Not from you.
I guess humankind hasn't
come as far as we thought.
Jax, what is wrong?
Atria. She went to Adar alone.
I think if something's not done
they're going to execute her.
What is EarthCom going to do about it?
Nothing.
What are you going to do about it?
Nothing. I have to go. I'm sorry.
I find that hard to believe.
I can't involve you in this, Ralen.
You are going to Adar, are you not?
What do you think you can
accomplish there by yourself?
Atria's my friend.
How could I live with myself
if something happened to her?
Hey, I know you.
You're friends with the purple girl.
Yeah.
Listen, Deck Sergeant, we are
really on the clock here.
I need to rent the Earhart
out for training.
Freshman are not
approved for flight time
without the approval of an instructor.
Not to mention, I don't believe you.
Fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice, shame on... you...
I'm going to fail my class
if I don't get some
more hours in orbit.
Well, that is what simulators are for.
There's got to be something
we can do to persuade you.
Look, I got in a lot of trouble
the last time you stole a ship,
so I can't help you, I'm afraid.
Without a teacher's consent,
you are staying grounded.
But they have a teacher's consent.
Oh, Professor Pevney.
Well, my apologies.
They didn't tell me
this was for your class
and they had your authorization.
Yes, well, they do now, Deck Sergeant.
Of course. Powering up the Earhart.
Is there anything else?
You've eaten?
Yes. Why?
- Go have dessert.
- Oh, I'm not...
Getting dessert, sir.
Why?
You know why.
You're with the Adari
resistance, aren't you?
You'll need this.
What is it?
Insurance.
And just remember,
Adar is still the only
planet in the Confederacy
that has the death penalty.
That's a cheery thought.
Good luck.
Atria is lucky to have
friends like you.
So, what's the plan?
I thought you had one.
When I agreed to come along,
I assumed you both knew
what you were doing.
- Hmm.
- So, do you think it's time
to open Professor Pevney's gift basket?
What do you think it is?
I hope it's snacks. I'm starving.
Definitely not snacks.
My son...
your former master.
You know your son is dead.
I know that's what he
wants me to believe.
I know he emancipated you
so you'd feel compelled to protect him,
but I need you to tell
me the truth now.
And why would I do that?
Out of compassion?
I have no soul, remember?
I love him.
Perhaps it's not too late
to make amends to him.
And to you.
Welcome to Adar.
That was rough.
I thought you were some
kind of ace pilot.
Sorry about that.
I've never landed a ship this
big on an alien planet before.
Just ran Sims.
Atria's going to be okay.
We're going to get her out of here.
The Seeker's compound
and cloning factory
are two klicks east of us.
I'm headed to the
compound to find Atria.
You and Pilar should stay here
in case we need to get out fast.
No can do. You'll need a diversion.
What do you say I give you one?
What kind of diversion?
A big one.
Hi, my name is Dr. Regina Lampert
from EarthCom Medical.
I'm here to observe the
Adari cloning procedures.
We don't have your visitation
authorized, Dr. Lampert.
Are you sure? Because I
was personally invited
by Seeker Hubbell himself.
Um, right, Pilar?
Give me a sec, here.
You heard about Atria Nine?
She's being put to death
for disobedience.
Her husk is scheduled
to undergo DNA reconstitution
in the tissue... v-vats.
What the hell are you talking about?
I have no clue.
Excuse me?
Hmm?
Oh.
You are cleared for access.
You may proceed.
Excuse me.
Can I get some help here?
I'm a doctor, not a locksmith.
Are you okay, Jax?
I think so.
I'm in, Pilar.
Planting the charges now.
Great. Now hurry up
before someone sees you.
Or me.
Atria?
Oh, this can't be good.
Thomas! Aah!
Let her go.
No! No!
What are you doing here... again?
Doing what I always do, apparently.
Keeping you out of trouble.
Thanks, but I had it under control.
Yeah, I can see that.
Tom's in the Seeker's compound.
He's going to need some help.
I guess that can be arranged.
We need a distraction.
You'll get your distraction in...
five seconds.
What happens in five seconds?
Boom happens.
What was that?
The cloning factory!
Come on.
Pilar, you got eyes on Thomas?
He's inside the compound.
I've located him in the
Seeker's chambers.
All right.
Let's go save Atria then.
Tom's in here.
On my signal.
Three, two...
This isn't good.
The Seeker has Thomas.
Jax, I dispatched a drone
and have eyes on Atria and Thomas.
I'm sending you their coordinates now.
They're with the Seeker.
- Where?
- On the move.
It appears they're
rendezvousing with a ship
on the perimeter of the compound.
What kind of ship?
A Zatarian ship.
Who the hell is that?
My former master, Lenar.
He's the Seeker's son.
We faked his death so
he could flee Adar
and marry the love of his life.
- A clone?
- Yes.
Me, technically.
You're married?
No, but Atria Six is.
And they're very happy.
Lenar is not like his father.
He's a good and honorable man.
What is Ralen doing here?
Mm-hmm.
He's full of surprises, isn't he?
Who's he with?
I think that's the Seeker's son.
Atria told me she killed him.
Yeah, well, apparently,
he's been miraculously resurrected.
You need to turn your safety off.
I never thought I'd see
you again, my son.
And I hoped I would never
see you again, Father.
You must know how much I
prayed for this day to come.
What are you doing here, Lenar?
Every moment you're on Adar
puts your life in danger.
The Zatarian told me
you were in danger.
I couldn't let anything
happen to my sister-in-law.
What do you really
want from me, Father?
I need you to come home and
support my re-nomination
as Seeker in the Council,
and renounce your marriage
to the abomination
before it can be used by
my opponents against me.
And why would I do that?
Because I will let you
and your friends live.
Or would you really rather
die for real this time?
And what of Zatar?
Would you not make an
enemy of my people
if you killed us all today?
You made an enemy of me when
your people took in my son,
giving him asylum and sheltered
him on your home world.
Lenar asked us for sanctuary.
An offer we could not refuse.
Was it worth losing
the Adari as an ally
in your war against Earth to
help my son flee into exile?
We would make the same
decision again today.
He asked for help.
We were obliged to give it.
You will never understand my people.
Nor you, mine.
Be it a generation or more,
my people shall have their
vengeance against you.
But today, I shall have mine.
Ah!
Don't.
Why not?
Because it's his way, not yours.
The reality is nothing's
going to change on Adar.
After everything we did,
life there will still be the same.
Maybe, maybe not.
But just by you being free,
maybe your story can inspire others
to pick up where you left off.
Yeah, after all, Atria
Three has her own life now
and she's applying to enroll
at the academy next semester,
which is a start.
The Seeker said you weren't human
because you were made in a lab,
but the things that you did today,
all the sacrifices you
made to try to save
your clone brothers and sisters,
that's the most human
thing I could imagine.
And if history's taught us anything,
it's that things take time.
But if we commit and don't give up,
things will get better.
Eventually.
It's hard work.
Speaking of hard work,
I have a lot of homework
to catch up on.
I should go.
Want some help?
Sure.
Guess we'll see you later, gators.
MM-hmm.
Next time, will you please
tell me what you're up to
before you're going to
your life in danger again?
Why, so you can try and stop me?
No.
So I can go with you.
I'm just happy you're back safe, Jax.
Thank God Xander showed up when he did.
I have no idea how he
knew you were on Adar,
but I'm really glad he was there.
You know what, Greg? Can I
catch you a little later?
Why? You got a hot date?
No. There's just something
I got to take care of.
Sure.
Xander!
Jax, what can I do for you?
I've been thinking about something.
I hope it was battle
tactics and strategy,
because I've just graded your paper.
You can do better than a C-plus.
When you showed up to Adar, you
didn't know I was in trouble
because you were spying on me, did you?
Of course not, Jax. Why
would I spy on you?
You knew I was on Adar because
you were spying on Ralen.
You think he sabotaged the
Tereshkova, don't you?
That's what I thought.
I do imagine you must be quite upset.
Your young protégé destroying
a manufacturing facility
worth billions to Parallax.
Cloning is a very lucrative
business for us, you know.
Of course, had I known
of Jax's intentions,
I certainly would have
interceded on your behalf.
I don't care about that.
Parallax will make more
money from the Adari
on re-building their facility anyway.
So why are you here, Regan?
To tell you there's something
far more dangerous to you
than even my father.
And what's that?
Pandora.
Oh, that.
Yes, well, on that we can
most definitely agree.
Does she know what really
happened to the Tereshkova?
No.
And for the moment,
that will need to remain our secret.
You do have a lot of them,
don't you, Professor?
Just make sure you don't
keep them from my father.
We need to know everything
you know about Pandora.
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.addic7ed.com -