Be back for dinner, mommy-o.
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Jax.
Hey, Jax, wait.
Sorry. Aehm.
Welcome to Earth.
You're not Professor Osborn.
You're perceptive, I see.
I'm his teaching
assistant, Xander Duvall.
I was told I'd be meeting Dr.
Osborn, so...
Yeah, he was supposed to.
He wanted to, in fact.
But he's very busy, so
he sent me instead.
You think he'd find the time
to meet the orphaned
niece he's never met.
Yeah, like I said, he's...
Very busy.
I heard you.
I'm not sure we're
completely getting off
on the right foot here, are we?
Well, it appears I'm not the
only one who's perceptive then.
I had a class with your mother...
when I was a freshman.
She was an inspiring teacher.
I'm sorry for your loss.
That's very kind of you.
I suppose we should go
get my duffels then.
You may just be strong
enough to carry all of them.
Interesting he chose to model
his home on the Queen Anne's.
Not what I was expecting.
Yeah? What were you expecting?
Certainly not to find my uncle
aspiring to live in the home
of a Bonanza King.
Even if just a very impressive replica.
Is that you, Mr. Duvall?
It is, Professor.
Uncle.
Jacqueline.
Sorry I was unable to
greet you personally,
but it is most agreeable
to finally meet you
after all these years, sadly
under such unfortunate circumstances.
I appreciate your help, uncle.
It's been a difficult few months
as I'm sure you can imagine.
I presume you've already been
briefed on your dispensation.
If you mean that as my
only living relative,
an I'm now your burden, then yes.
Hardly a burden, my dear.
I'm not an emotional man, but
I loved your mother dearly.
And to her, family was everything.
I feel it incumbent upon me
to make sure that you're looked after.
It's what she would have wanted.
Is there any news on the investigation?
None as of yet,
but I'll see what I can find out.
In the interim, you're aware I
arranged with the chancellor
for you to matriculate this semester
at the Fleet Training Academy.
I appreciate you
interceding on my behalf.
The school year started two weeks ago,
but based on your grades
you should have no problem
playing catch-up.
And if there's anything
else you need...
Quite right. Mr. Duvall can assist you.
He's one of my brightest pupils.
Please feel free to rely on him
for any of your immediate needs.
I certainly will, uncle.
Now as Mr. Duvall said,
the school year has indeed commenced,
and I am already quite
inundated with work,
so if you'll excuse me,
I'll see you both on
Friday for dinner here
promptly at 7:00.
Of course.
Such a warm and sociable man.
Great men like the professor
are often somewhat quirky.
Not the word I would've used.
Anything else I can help you with?
What do you know about my
the death of my parents?
Nothing.
I only T.A. for the professor,
and as you can imagine,
he's pretty tight-lipped.
Of course.
I guess I'll be seeing you around then.
Sooner than you might like.
I'll be seeing you in class.
May I assist you?
Is this Interstellar Protocol?
Stellar Cartography.
Wrong class. Sorry.
Protocol is more than simple etiquette.
It's not about manners or pleasantries.
It's about respecting
customs and traditions
utilizing proper diplomatic formality.
For instance, if I wanted to convey
my profound indignation
over the inability of a cadet to
arrive on time in my class...
how exactly would I do that?
I'm so sorry, I didn't...
To misunderstand the culture
you're communicating with
is one of the worst mistakes
an officer can make
in a first contact situation.
Seemingly incomprehensible acts
can often be better understood
when one examines the situation
from the opposite perspective.
And there are some worlds
in which failure to adhere
to proper protocol
can have the direst of consequences.
Consider yourself lucky
this is not one of them.
Wouldn't you agree, Miss Zhou?
Shral didn't need to
be such a scum weasel.
It's my first day.
I got lost on the way to class.
Are all the professors here so awful?
Actually, most of the
profs are pretty neat.
Except Osborn. That man is a total ass.
He's also my uncle.
Oops.
I guess I shouldn't have said anything.
- I'm so sorry.
- Oh, I agree.
He is a total ass.
I'm Jax. Nice to meet you.
Atria.
So where you headed now, Jax?
Back to the dorm.
I have a ton of assignments
to catch up on.
Well, I'm going to hang
at the Black Hole.
- Want to come with?
- Black Hole?
Center of gravity on campus.
Lounge, bar, hangout.
Place where you can unwind.
And if you ever wanted to
hear some really bad poetry,
it's the place to do that too.
Did I mention it's a great
place to meet hot guys also?
Not on my dance card this semester.
- I have other obligations.
- You say that now.
Oh, that's Tom. He's
also in Shral's class.
You'll like him.
He's not your average joystick jockey.
- Fighter pilot?
- Wannabe.
Hopefully, he'll wise up and
get on a command track.
He's way too smart to be
flying jets in space.
Glad you haven't got many bruises
from that unprovoked
attack in class today.
Ugh. That you can see.
Sumi Starburst for you, Tommy Boy.
Hey, Atria. The usual and...
and the new girl.
- Jax.
- Jax. What can I get you?
Just a shoulder to cry on.
That I can definitely provide.
Let me guess. Osborn.
No. Shral carved her
up and spit her out
real good this morning.
I had him last year.
His bark is worse than his bite.
He's a pretty decent instructor
once you get to know him.
- What year are you?
- Just finished my undergrad.
On the med track now,
looking to get onboard
an exploratory vessel as a CMO.
Ah, a doctor.
Well, not yet.
And with the way this semester's
been going, maybe never.
Well, I love the humility.
Not to mention a man who's
good with his hands.
So, what's your story Jax?
Oh, not much to tell, really.
Yeah, somehow I doubt that.
Her parents were killed
at New Portland.
Didn't you hear?
Yeah, I heard.
Everybody heard.
But just because it's on my mind
doesn't mean it's on my tongue.
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to...
It's fine. It's not any kind of secret.
Old news. Really.
Hello.
Could I get a...?
Come to think of it, I think I
am going to get that drink.
I got this.
- Bartender.
- What can I get you?
He'll have a Blue
Safari, and so will I.
If you wake up with a massive
headache in the morning,
you can blame me.
Why are you talking to me?
Why shouldn't I?
I mean, if you'd prefer, I can
go back and hang with my...
I guess I can't really
call them my friends,
because I just met them, but
the group I'm hanging with.
Are you with the Earth
Intelligence Services?
Not very trusting of the
kindness of strangers, I see.
Come on.
Drinking alone is called alcoholism.
Much better to do it with a crowd.
Go on.
- So, what's your name?
- Ralen.
I'm Jax, this is Greg,
Thomas and Atria.
She's easy to recognize,
because she's the only one
who's a natural purple.
- I see.
- So...
you're the Zatarian
Ambassador's son, huh?
I have that privilege.
What made you decide to
join the Academy, Ralen?
Other than spying on all of you?
That was my attempt at humor.
It can't be easy being
the first Zatarian
to ever attend the
Academy since the war.
I can't imagine it's
any easier for you.
There's not a long history of clones
belonging to the Adari sect
joining the space fleet.
That's true, but that's because
we're considered as property
and our masters won't let us
pursue a formal education.
So how did you convince your master
to let you go the Academy?
Adari masters aren't known for
emancipating their clones.
I killed him.
Ahem. Here.
- Excuse me?
- I could tell
you desperately wanted some
chips, but didn't want to ask.
- Telepath?
- Part.
My mother was a captain in EarthCom.
My pops, telepathic.
In the C.I.S.?
No. Jail.
He got busted in Macau
for cheating at cards.
Wasn't the first time either.
Not what Earth Intelligence had in mind
- when they created Telepaths.
- Yeah.
Wasn't really what I had
in mind for a dad either.
So, what really brings you
to the Academy, Ralen?
I have always thought
the best way to avoid another conflict
between our two respective races
is to understand each other better.
That's why I prevailed upon my father
to have the Earth Ambassador to Zatar
request that my application
to the Academy be accepted.
So, what do you think so far, mate?
Earth preaches a set of
values across the galaxy
about tolerance and diversity,
but I have yet to see the
actions of your people
meet their high-sounding words.
Until today.
Tell you what.
Since we're now apparently the
paragons of human virtue,
allow me to offer you the
chance to join our study group.
You and Jax, of course.
Not easy to make it
at the Academy alone.
We're stronger together than apart.
I will accept your invitation.
We got to go, but we'll see you soon.
We're needed in space.
They a couple?
Not yet.
He has a girlfriend on Vega 5,
which won't last much longer.
For some reason,
147-trillion-mile-distance
relationships never work.
Why? You interested?
Nah.
Not in him.
I like Ralen. What do you think?
We'll see.
I'm having a tough time reading him.
Maybe he just doesn't like you
poking around inside his head.
I know I don't.
Zatarian attack ship closing.
Should I attempt to hail them?
They're heading towards
us and not communicating.
Could be trouble. Weapons hot.
All pulse cannons online.
Prepare to fire on my mark.
But Tom, we don't know
their intentions.
We do now.
Hey.
Let's go again.
Maybe this time a little
bit less chattering,
little bit more blasting, yeah?
Might help.
Hey, Miss Congeniality.
You busy downloading
from the datacore again?
Sorry to interrupt your reboot.
I wish you wouldn't call it that.
You know we call it meditation.
I met some people today.
They invited us to join
their study group.
I said yes for both of us.
Are you sure that is wise?
What do you know of them
and their abilities?
I know I like them.
Not necessarily the best criteria
to evaluate their suitability
as study partners.
Why do you always have
to act so superior?
Because I am superior.
It's not narcissism,
it's an empirical fact.
Right, well, one of them is Zatarian.
Ralen?
- Yeah. You know him?
- I know of him.
- We should be wary.
- Why?
Because he is Zatarian.
We do not know his true
motives for being here.
- I do.
- You do?
Yeah. He said he wants to bring
our races closer together
through mutual understanding.
- And you believe him?
- Why shouldn't I?
- Because he is Zatarian.
- You said that already.
You have to understand,
the Zatarian are violent and warlike.
They're treacherous and
wary of other species.
They're victims of their
basest instincts.
I could say the same thing
about human beings,
and we struggle to
overcome them every day.
So you're saying you're not
going to be in the study group?
I thought you believed in
respect for all races.
Isn't it reasonable to evaluate
this Zatarian on his own merits
and give him a chance
before convicting him
of your own personal prejudice?
I will participate in your study group.
What?
I said I'll participate
in your study group.
Oh, well, I'm glad to hear that.
- Now I got to go.
- Where are you going?
Dinner at my uncle's.
Should be lots of fun.
Tons of laughs You'd love it.
Want to come?
No.
You clean up well.
I could say the same about you.
How was your first day of school?
I'd prefer not to think about it.
I mean, I got raked over the
coals by my prof today.
- Shral?
- Yeah, Shral.
He was a real ass, if
you know what I mean.
No, I mean, hello, Professor Shral.
Mr. Duvall.
Pleasure to see you, as always.
Ah, Miss Zhou.
Mm.
I thought I recognized that voice.
A word of advice.
A good officer needs to get along
with all kind of personality.
Those you like, those you don't.
Other species you can't
even begin to understand.
You'd be wise to remember that.
Enjoy the party.
You're taking perverse glee in
my predicament, aren't you?
Never.
You know, I admire a man
who still has books.
The touch and the feel of paper.
You know, it's tangible.
And as much as we've
gained as a civilization,
I feel we've lost to
life in our digital age.
Ellison Pevney, Miss Zhou.
I knew your parents well.
My condolences.
Professor Pevney, it is an honor, sir.
The pleasure is all mine.
And I am delighted
that you will be in my Earth
History class this semester.
As am I.
Do you mind me asking,
is there any news of your parents?
I keep asking the same
thing repeatedly,
and no one seems to know anything.
Well, surely your uncle can help.
Help with what?
Donovan. We were just
talking about you.
We were talking about the investigation
into the attack on New Portland.
I'm afraid I have no news to report.
I've just learned the
investigation has been closed.
An entire colony was just obliterated.
How can they just close
the investigation?
I wish I had better news.
If EarthCom doesn't find
out what happened, I will.
You realize that's quite
impossible, of course.
We'll see what's impossible.
Anyways, you'll have to excuse me.
It's been a long week,
and I have a lot of
work to catch up on.
Thank you for the gracious invitation.
What was all that about?
She doesn't know, does she?
No.
I don't like it, Donovan. I
think you're making a mistake.
You need to tell her the truth.
For what it's worth, I'm with
Ellison on this one, Professor.
That is your right.
But even if you disagree
with my orders,
I do expect you to follow them.
I just want you to know
that you still have
my father's full support.
And mine, of course.
That is indeed a comfort.
By the way, I understand
you already know the girl.
Not well.
She dated my sister for awhile.
But you knew that already,
didn't you, Professor?
I may have heard something
to that effect.
Don't fence with me, Osborn.
My father won't always
control Parallax.
If he keeps harvesting the
organs of clones he grows
to sustain his frail body,
he may just live forever.
You should try it.
We'll see.
One day Humpty Dumpty may not be able
to put himself back together again.
I think it's time you run
back to lo and report.
Your father is not
renowned for his patience.
Neither am I.
So I advise you to tread carefully.
The company may be mine
sooner than you think.
I wonder what your sister,
Odessa, would say about that.
I doubt she'll be in a
position to say anything.
And if you don't watch
your tongue with me,
neither will you.
Forget it! Let's go!
Prior to this,
World War I had been mistakenly
and over-optimistically called
"the war to end all wars."
But two decades later,
the continent would again find itself
on the brink of conflict
in the Second World War,
as you can see.
Enter.
You missed the study group.
I came to see if you were all right.
I'm fine.
Human behavior remains a
bit of an enigma to me,
but that was clearly a lie.
I guess it is.
I've just...
I've been thinking a lot
about my parents lately.
They were killed in an attack.
New Portland colony?
You heard about that?
My father is the Zatarian Ambassador.
There's not much in the
sector I don't know about.
Of course.
One of the reasons I
agreed to come here
was I thought I might be
able to find out more
about what happened to my parents.
And now it's been three months,
and I don't know any more today
than the day they were murdered.
And then I find out they closed
the investigation entirely.
So now, I may never find out
what really happened to them.
And no one really seems to care
about them or me.
I care.
And I'm not the only one.
We are your friends, Jax.
I am your friend.
Well, I appreciate that.
But unless you have a ship
with EM-FTL capabilities,
I'm not sure there's much you can do.
I do.
Do what?
I might have access to a ship
with light speed capabilities.
I think I may have just
found my new best friend.
Are you sure this is legal?
We are students matriculated
at the Academy.
And this ship is
property of the Academy.
Are you saying this ship
doesn't belong to you?
Let's not split hairs,
as you humans say.
Excuse me?
It's an old model training vessel.
They won't miss it.
School is not back in session
for several more days.
So how do we get to it?
They're not just going to
let us fly it out of here.
I've already made arrangements.
Happy birthday!
I can understand if you don't
want to tell me how old you are,
but it can't be a day over 30.
Oh.
Well, it's not my birthday.
It's not?
But I have a delivery order
right here for William Rogers.
I'm Elias Wilson.
Oh. There must be some kind of mistake.
But you're the flight chief, right?
I am.
What are you doing here?
Well, rumor has it you were
going on a little trip,
and I love to travel.
Look, I appreciate the sentiment,
but I don't think it's a good
idea if you try and tag along.
I don't know how long
we're going to be there,
or what we're going to find.
Well, sounds like we don't
have any more time to waste
talking about it then.
I sure wouldn't mind trying some
of this tasty-looking cake.
It's a long night, and I
can't leave my station.
Oh, I can't.
But I can give you something sweet,
because you're so nice.
What are you doing?
Did you just kiss that man?
Well, of course. It's
his birthday, kind of.
Is that true? Is it your birthday?
Well, no, not really.
Then why are you kissing my girlfriend?
I...
Nice work.
Thank you.
Now I'm really hungry.
That cake looked so yummy.
I just hope we're not making a mistake.
I mean, we could get expelled for this.
What have we gotten ourselves into?
No idea.
BUT I DO KNOW REMEMBER ONE THING
MY SISTERS USED TO TELL ME:
Be a voice, not an echo.
You know, for years, I lived
as a slave among the Adari
because I wasn't considered
a real human being.
No one spoke for me.
So I'll tell you, Tom,
I'll never turn my back on
someone who needs my help.
Ever.
You're amazing, you know that?
Stars can't shine without darkness.
How far to planetfall?
At present speed, 16 hours, 24 minutes.
Okay. Anyone got anything
to pass the time?
I do love my classical.
♪ It's poetry in motion ♪
♪ She turned her tender eyes to me ♪
♪ She blinded me with science ♪
♪ And failed me in geometry, yeah ♪
Scans?
I'm detecting an EarthCom vessel
in orbit around the planet.
Registry, ECOM-19.
It's the battle cruiser Tereshkova.
That's strange. Osborn said the
investigation had been closed.
Apparently not completely.
Can we get any closer
without being detected?
I can try bringing her down from
a parallel orbit on the deck
and below the ionosphere.
This ship is small enough it may
not read on their scanners.
- Do it.
- Aye, aye, cap.
I can also deactivate
the transponder codes,
which will make it less likely
they'll read us as well.
Yeah, but if they do, without
our transponder codes,
they may open fire thinking
we're one of the marauders
who attacked the planet.
There is that too.
Jax, I'm detecting life-forms.
I think it's time we join them.
Put her down near the colony
where she won't be seen.
I'm heading to the surface to
see what's really going on.
- Ralen, you up for a walk?
- I am.
Greg, stay here with the ship.
We'll let you know as
soon as we know more.
I didn't travel thousands
of light years
to let you go down there alone.
Besides, it might actually hurt
my feelings if I found out
you only brought me along for
my charm and good looks.
Well, I'd never want
to hurt your feelings.
The encampment where we
lived isn't far from here.
So, what are we looking for, exactly?
- A reason.
- A reason?
A reason for the attack.
And what if there wasn't one?
There's always a reason.
Seemingly incomprehensible
acts can often be understood
when examined from the
opposite perspective.
Or so I've been told.
- What is that?
- I don't know.
But I know what it's not.
The C.I.S. hasn't remotely
closed their investigation.
So either Professor
Osborn was misinformed...
Or was lying.
I'm going down there. Stay here.
Yeah, we're not letting you go alone.
This I need to do myself.
The Cronin?
They're a long way from home.
What do you make of that?
I do not know.
But Cronin rarely travel this
far from their mother world
unless they have a very good reason.
We need to go tell Jax.
Jax does not need or want our help.
We must be patient.
I wouldn't presume to understand Jax.
And you do?
Because you wish to
be intimate with her.
I only want to help her find out
what happened to her parents.
Of course.
Clearly, I misread your motives.
You got me.
Next time I hang out with her,
I'm taking her somewhere
romantic, like Euphoria 7.
Ah, the pleasure planet.
So you've heard of it then.
Yes.
We should have annihilated
it during the war.
You shouldn't be here.
What the hell are you doing here?
I could ask you the same question.
- This was my home.
- Not anymore.
Everything I know was stolen from me.
I deserve to know why.
Look, you could get
in a lot of trouble.
I've had to call...
I've had to call in
more than a few favors
to cover for the fact
that you stole a ship.
And even if you don't care,
think of your friends.
You have to return to the Academy, now.
You never answered my question.
What are you doing here, Xander?
I'm here to keep you
from getting expelled.
Nice try. Try again.
Well, you're just going
to have to trust me.
- Why in the worlds would I?
- I wish I had a reason,
but sometimes you just have
to have a little faith.
Well, I'm afraid that's in
short supply these days.
- This mean anything to you?
- Should it?
They're images recovered from
your mother's workstation
at the dig site.
"The obstacle is the path."
What does that mean?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you absolutely sure
that's what it says?
Aren't you?
- How do you know?
- I don't know.
I guess my mother must
have said something.
We've had hundreds of
xenolinguistic experts
and cryptologists,
and hundreds of thousands
of hours on the datastream
trying to decode that image,
and none of them have
been able to crack it.
Are you absolutely sure
that's what it says?
Yes.
Your mother never showed you that.
Of course she did.
How else would I know what it says?
No. She didn't.
Those were the images she
was working on decoding
when the colony was attacked
and she was killed.
What's really going on here, Xander?
I can't tell you.
But I can tell you that what
your parents discovered
may well be a threat
to our entire galaxy.
I need to see what's inside this cave.
No. You need to go.
Not until I see it for myself.
We're detecting some
sort of immense power.
Energy signatures off the charts.
You've never been here
before, I presume?
Can't say that I have.
There's something else you should see.
Your parents never told
you about any of this?
To be honest, I always found
their work pretty dull.
I guess I was wrong.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
There's something on the
other side of that portal.
- The obstacle is the path.
- Stand by.
I need further instructions
from Earth before proceeding.
Good thing I don't.
One thing's for sure, we're
not in Kansas anymore.
What?
Never mind.
Any idea where we are?
I wish I knew.
Commander Duvall,
are you there?
Do you copy?
We're okay.
Hold your positions. Await
further instructions.
It seems to have created some
sort of stable wormhole,
between where we were and where we are.
Why?
You tell me. You opened it.
Dr. Slavin?
Dr. Slavin, report.
Report!
Something's not right.
We need to leave, now.
I'm staying. This may
have something to do
with what happened to my parents.
This time I'm not taking
no for an answer.
Stay down.
Jax!
You okay?
Is it dead?
Just stunned.
For now.
Not going to say anything, are you?
Of course not.
So how about I tell you who you are.
You're some sort of
intergalactic secret agent
working for military intelligence.
Not going to tell me if I'm
getting warmer, colder...
- If I could tell you...
- You would.
Got it.
And what about my uncle?
What does he have to do with this?
He sent my parents to New
Portland, didn't he?
Did he know they would be attacked?
What about my friends?
What'll happen to them?
I'll accompany all of you back
to the Academy on the Earhart.
We'll chalk it up to some
sort of hazing prank.
There won't be any disciplinary action.
I like you, Xander.
Against my better judgment, I do.
But you know I am never
going to let this go.
I know.
The worst part is never
getting to say goodbye.
You never really appreciate your
parents until they're gone.
And I think they knew
how much I loved them.
At least, I hope so.
God, I miss them.
Good night, Xander.
Good night, Jax.
Doctor, what do you have for me?
I completed my analysis of its DNA.
Not only does it share
the same nucleobases
as all known terrestrial life,
its genome is practically identical
to that of Homo Sapiens.
Or at least the part of the code
actually endemic to our species.
That said, some of what would
normally be non-coding genes
in humans appears to be active.
And that's its DNA there?
Yes and no.
I don't have time for games, doctor.
No game, Agent Duvall.
It's virtually the same DNA,
but it's not from the specimen.
It's the DNA you took from the girl.
She has the same active sequences.
Are you saying that she's not human?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
_
You're late.
I accompanied the students
home on the Earhart.
The Tereshkova will leave
New Portland in 36 hours
and return the specimen to Earth.
I received your preliminary report.
I believe things may be worse
than we initially feared.
You're wrong about her.
I might very well be,
but we can't afford
to take that chance,
or Pandora could be responsible
for the death of every man,
woman and child in existence.
She's your niece. Her name is Jax.
Call her that. Don't use her code name.
I know you're fond of the girl.
But this Pandora is a lot
like her mythical antecedent.
She was curious too.
And by the time she opened her box,
it was too late to stop
the demons she unleashed
into the world.
And I assure you,
this Pandora's demons
are very, very real.
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.addic7ed.com -