[RALEN] Previously on Pandora...
My telepathic powers
seem to be growing.
We need Jax to reestablish
contact with Cordelia.
[XANDER] This is the latest
in surveillance technology
- from the CIS.
- [JAX] That's going inside me?
You don't want to be with me.
You want to be with Ralen.
My heart was not into it.
That's because it belonged
to Jax, isn't it?
I can't have feelings,
Jax, and still do my job.
It appears Parallax is in possession
of a powerful new weapon.
Whatever it is, it's
too bloody dangerous
to leave in Harlan Fried's hands.
It was you that opened the portal,
just as you will do the same for me.
[XANDER] We must be a pretty
long way from Tiagra.
Are those Zatarian ships?
What are they doing here?
They're preparing for war.
This place is an old Zatari
outpost from the war,
but we were told it was abandoned.
Not from where I'm standing.
I do not have an explanation for this.
We need to get out of here. Right now.
And how in the worlds do we do that?
We go through there!
- Get to the portal.
- No!
What if it takes us
back to where we were?
- Anywhere is better than here!
- Aah!
Jax!
[PANTING]
[XANDER] Ralen!
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[XANDER] Ralen, come on!
- Go, go!
- [JAX] No!
Xander.
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
♪
[XANDER] Start talking!
Now you tell me what you know
about the Zatarian fleet.
I am done asking nicely.
Oh, that was nice?
I know half a dozen
ways to make you talk,
and most of them are deeply unpleasant.
I want answers!
Start talking!
You are not listening.
I do not know why there was a
Zatarian armada in the sky
above the planet.
What are you doing, Xander?
Jax, just relax.
How's your shoulder?
I guess that depends on what I
think I'm seeing right now.
If it is the commander
threatening to torture me,
then your keen powers of observation
appears to be functioning
adequately, Jax.
Jax, you have no idea
what's going on here.
I'm pretty sure I just saw you
trying to intimidate my friend,
who also happens to be your student,
with physical assault.
Multiple times.
Multiple times? How
long have I been out?
A few hours. You're hurt badly, Jax.
You should lie down.
[XANDER] This man is
an enemy combatant.
Jax, you saw the fleet.
The Zatarians are preparing for war.
That is in violation
of every peace accord
they have with the Confederacy.
Yes, and my father must be warned.
I assure you my government
has nothing to do
with this betrayal.
Then who does?
Much like Earth, there are
factions among my kind
who are not happy
about the current state of
interstellar relations.
This fleet poses as much threat
to my race as it does yours.
And you really expect
me to believe that?
I do not care what you believe.
Xander, let him go!
Oh, so I suppose you believe him then?
I don't know what I believe.
But I know we need his help to
get out of wherever we are.
[GRUNTS]
I know you want to see
the good in everyone,
but sometimes you are missing
what is right in front of your face.
Sounds familiar.
How many more of your friends
do we have to lose, Jax,
for this ridiculous obsession?
How many more bad decisions do
you think you can get away with?
Look where we are.
If you had listened to me on Euphoria 7
instead of running back
to Cordelia Fried,
we wouldn't have ended up on Tiagra.
We wouldn't have gone
through the portal.
And we would not be here,
wherever "here" is.
Do not blame Jax, Mr. Duvall.
You are exactly where
your Professor Osborn
wishes you to be.
He sent you to Euphoria 7, did he not?
You are a pawn in a much larger game.
Uncuff him, Xander.
Please.
That will not be necessary.
The portal's vanished.
Please tell me you two have at
least figured out where we are.
I've seen historical holos
of cities like this.
Old Earth tech.
[DIGITIZED BEEPING]
So the portal brought us back in time?
Not quite.
I want to leave you
with a final thought.
Our ancestors fled a dying
Earth for the stars.
The single most important
step in our evolution
as a species.
Now, the lucky ones headed to our
closest celestial neighbors.
But sadly, more than half of our ships
never made it to a planet.
Their crews dying of starvation,
radiation sickness,
or vanishing out there
in the infinite void.
Their bravery paved our future
and helped heal a dying world.
And it's my job to ensure
each and every one of you
are found worthy of that sacrifice.
Class dismissed.
Have you seen Ralen?
Why, was he asking about me?
Jax never came back
from Solstice Break.
Maybe he's seen her.
He may actually be the why.
Ralen told me he liked her,
so I kind of encouraged him
to go after her on Euphoria 7.
So I'm the only one that cares
about grades in the study group.
- And celibacy.
- Not funny.
If they miss enough classes
they'll be expelled.
Well, then we should definitely
try and contact them,
before it's too late.
Keep an eye out for any useful tech.
We need to find a way to send
a message off this planet.
Judging from that ominous-looking ship
looming above us, we may
also may need weapons.
Something about that ship
feels familiar to me.
You ever seen anything like it?
No.
It must have something
to do with that portal
that brought us here.
Either way, it's freaking me out.
Well, it's not sending out any
energy signatures at all.
I think it's derelict.
These were standard
issue in the Ark ships
during the Great Migration.
He's covered in burn marks.
[LOUD BANGING]
What was Ralen doing on Euphoria 7?
I mean, he just turns up in the
middle of an EarthCom black-op?
He's part of a species
that is building an armada
to wipe out the human race.
We don't know that yet.
You can't let personal feelings
get in the way of duty.
I know.
You made that abundantly clear
when you used me as a spy for my uncle.
I'm trying to protect you, Jax.
I don't need you to protect me, okay?
I can protect myself.
And look where that's got you.
Are we really doing this right now?
I know you like him, Jax.
I like him too.
But you cannot ignore the
empirical evidence against him.
I hope I'm wrong.
I really hope you're right.
But we need to be vigilant.
Can we at least agree on that?
[SIGHS]
I think our best hope of
finding any useful tech
to contact Earth is on that ship.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Can you just stop it for
one damn minute, Atria?
- I am begging you.
- Stop what?
I wasn't doing anything.
And you missed another class.
I can't do anything about that.
My head feels like it's
on fire right now.
What is that?
Don't worry about it.
It's not your concern anymore.
Jax and Ralen missed their
return shuttle from Euphoria 7.
Mystery solved.
They slept in.
What I mean is that's all I found.
They've vanished from
the entire data stream.
How is that even possible?
I searched for Xander too.
Ghosted in the same way.
There is no record of
them leaving Euphoria 7,
and there's no record of
them still being there.
We have to tell someone.
[WHISPERING] Go.
[OSBORN] Good evening, cadets.
I do hope for your sake this is worth
disrupting my very busy schedule.
It concerns your niece,
Ralen and your teacher's
assistant, Xander Duvall.
[OSBORN] Interesting.
I assumed it was regarding
the C-minus you received
on your Battle Tactics &
Strategy midterm, Atria.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
[STAMMERS]
The point is,
they haven't reported back
from Winter Solstice Break.
We think they might be
in some kind of trouble.
Students often get into
trouble on Solstice Break.
Your concern is noted,
but not warranted.
They are on assignment for me.
Oh. Doing what, exactly?
[OSBORN] Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I am
required to report
to my first-year cadets.
We'll, uh, let you get back to
that busy schedule now, sir.
We were just worried.
Ralen was with them?
Affirmative.
Ah. Yeah, we think so, sir.
[XANDER] The USS Searcher lost
contact with Earth 150 years ago.
Intended destination: Proxima Centauri.
[JAX] Looks like they never made it.
[BIRD WINGS FLAP]
I think that I can
access the ship's log.
Hoping to find astrogation data.
What about a way to get a
message back to Earth?
[TYPING]
[GROANS]
No, the comms gear's been
completely stripped.
But you guys keep an eye
out for anything else
we may be able to salvage.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[STATIC CRACKLES]
[MONITORS POWERING UP]
[GRANT, OVER MONITOR] We
lost navigational control.
[AUDIO BREAKS UP]
There isn't much on here.
Most of the data's been corrupted.
We lost navigational control
because of a spatial anomaly.
Our star charts are useless.
Ship was heavily damaged,
but we managed to set her down.
We called it Homestead.
Population: 2,012.
Morale is high.
We may be lost, but we
will make this work.
We have no other choice.
No other choice.
Captain Alice Grant, USS
Searcher, commanding.
Major Taylor, front and center.
I wonder what happened to them.
The same thing that's
going to happen to us
if we can't send a message out.
[LAUGHS]
I realize that no one off this planet
may ever see this,
but I would still like to say
that the only reason that
we're all still alive
is because of the courage
and the bravery shown
- by Captain Grant.
- Oh.
So on behalf of the entire
crew and the settlers,
I would like to officially thank her.
Thank you.
- Oh...
- Thank you.
[APPLAUSE]
[GRANT] Year five.
Homestead is strong and growing.
Maybe getting lost was the best thing
that ever happened to us.
Captain Alice Grant, out.
We found a cave under the city.
You are looking at the
first recorded evidence
that we are not alone in the universe.
My geologist believes
that these markings
are over 30,000 years old.
It appears that this pictograph
is of an alien holding up a baby.
A human baby.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
Are you all right, Jax?
They arrived yesterday.
We tried to make peaceful contact,
but they just started slaughtering us.
[INDISTINCT SCREAMING AND SHOUTING]
We're going to try to get
this transmission to Earth,
warn humanity that these
creatures are out there.
God help us.
Move! Move! Move! They're coming!
[GUNFIRE]
[SCREAMS AND ROARS]
We lost navigational control
because of a spatial anomaly.
Those same aliens were on New Portland.
Why were they on this planet?
Why would they kill everyone?
We're not alone.
We need to move.
Commander, I hope that given our
current tactical situation,
you will forgive me a minor subterfuge.
What subterfuge?
I thought you searched him.
I did.
[GRANT] Major Taylor, front and center.
Boys and their toys. What is our plan?
[MARCUS] I realize that
no one off this planet
may ever see this, but
I would like to say
that the only reason that
we're all still alive
is because of the courage
and the bravery shown
by Captain Grant.
[GRANT] They arrived yesterday.
We tried to make peaceful contact,
but they just started
slaughtering us...
[GRUNTS]
slaughtering us, slaughtering us...
[RECORDING SKIPS, REPEATS]
[MARCUS] Shut it off. Please.
Shut it off.
Major Taylor, How are you still alive?
Call me Marcus.
The blue flowers.
The pollen, they halt the aging
process here on the planet.
A literal fountain of youth.
I've lived here on this
planet for over 150 years.
Completely on my own.
Everybody else is dead...
including my captain.
I understand, and I sympathize
with your loss, Major.
But right now, I need you to
tell me everything you know
about the comms array of the Searcher.
Now, do you know where it is?
Yeah, it's in my camp.
But it's useless.
I tried boosting the signal,
but it won't get past the
irradiated ionosphere,
so...
Well, technology's moved on a bit
since you left Earth, Marcus.
Can you take me to it?
Yeah.
But now it's my turn.
How did you guys get here?
We arrived through a portal.
It dropped us in a
cave beneath the city.
How long ago, man?
Approximately 15 Earth hours.
[DISTANT CRASH]
They're here.
Quickly, follow me.
You disturbed their temple.
They're coming for us.
[WHISPERING] Do we trust him?
Right now we don't
have much of a choice.
Grab the bags, grab
anything useful you can.
We're going to need it
for the comms array.
- [CREATURE ROARS]
- Ralen!
- [SNARLS]
- [GRUNTS]
I'll hold them off. You go.
[SCREAMS]
Leave me. I'm wounded.
Come on!
I'll just slow you down. Leave me.
[MARCUS] Come on! Move!
Open the door!
Come on.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[ATRIA'S THOUGHTS] Thomas,
I know you're in pain.
Let me help you.
No, Atria.
No what?
I didn't say anything.
You don't have to.
You read my mind.
I'm reading everyone's minds.
It won't stop.
I can't control my powers.
There's something wrong with me.
Let me take you to the Med-Center.
Maybe they can help.
It's no use.
The pills don't work.
I even went to my quiet place
to try and clear my head.
The old Western town
in the VR simulator?
Even in a sim my powers
are out of control.
I read Hari's mind.
Hari? Who's that?
My horse.
[SIGHS]
You broke my heart.
And it hurts.
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to be
honest with my feelings.
This is all new to me, Tom.
I've never experienced what it's like
being in a real relationship,
or cared about someone
like I care about you.
And I know you know that,
even if it's hard to accept right now.
I love you.
Just not in the way you want me to.
[SIGHS]
I don't...
I don't want to hurt you, or
anybody else. I've got to...
I've got to get as far away
from everyone as I can.
[VOICES WHISPERING]
- [SCREAMS]
- [GLASS BREAKS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[MAN] Whoa! What was that?
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[GASPS]
[MARCUS] If he were human,
I'd say he punctured a lung.
But he's not human, so I'm not sure.
Can you help him?
Yeah. Yeah, I will.
But if he's anything like humans,
he needs to rest right now.
Those aliens that tried to attack us,
we've seen them before.
What do you know about them?
I mean, nothing.
We tried to communicate with them
when we entered their temple, but...
it was useless.
They just wanted to kill us.
All of us.
You were the only survivor?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Marcus.
Those same aliens came to my planet
and took everything that I love.
I was the only one left.
[TYPING]
[COMPUTERS BEEP]
[SIGHS]
You know, I'm sorry about
your friend Ralen.
She looks upset by it.
Maybe Elliot could talk to Jax.
Elliot?
I thought you were the only
survivor of the Ark colony.
I am, but I'm not alone here.
Elliot, Xander.
Xander, Elliot.
Well, say hi to Elliot.
Hi, Elliot.
What's that?
Well, okay, I'll tell Xander,
but he's not going to
like hearing that.
Elliot seems to think we're all
going to die horrible deaths.
Well...
tell Elliot that I'm an optimist,
so not to worry.
I'll let him know.
Yeah.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
You think you'll be able
to get a signal out?
Almost.
But there's only enough
power to send one message.
How's Ralen?
Not good.
[SIGHS]
Look, Jax, maybe that attack
fleet that we both saw
was a big misunderstanding.
Maybe I'm wrong.
You don't think you are, do you?
I think that the most
obvious explanation
is usually the truth.
Sometimes you have to
have a little faith.
[LAUGHS]
One of your better qualities.
So I have some better qualities then?
[LAUGHS]
A few.
You don't care to elaborate, do you?
[SIGNAL CRACKLES]
- Did you get it working?
- Nearly.
I was able to triangulate our position
using some of Major
Taylor's old star charts.
And now soon I'll be able to
send their updates to EarthCom.
Update about what?
The Zatarian fleet that we encountered.
What are you talking about?
We have to tell them where we are.
Jax, you saw that fleet
with your own eyes.
They're preparing to attack Earth.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
Xander, if we use that
message as a warning,
then we're going to be stranded here.
Jax, Intel this specific
could save millions of lives on Earth.
So when I get this system working,
that is the message that
I am going to send.
That is a foolish decision.
There is another option.
Based on the position
of the binary suns,
I believe this planet is closer
to Zatar than it is to Earth.
Our best chance is to contact my people
in hopes of a swift rescue.
[GROANS]
[MARCUS] Come on, get him up.
Come on.
[GROANS]
You're not going to let
him do that, are you?
You already know the answer to that.
Ralen is going to die.
Jax, you know that I would
do whatever it takes
to save Ralen or anybody
else under my command.
But you're still going to send
that message to EarthCom, are you?
That doesn't mean I want him dead.
Those creatures are going
to be coming for us.
We have to be ready.
It must have been tough,
being here alone for so long.
I wasn't alone.
I had Elliot here.
Of course.
How did you do it, Marcus?
How did you survive
against those things?
[SIGHS]
My captain led us into battle.
We gave it to them hard.
Soldiers, civilians
fighting side by side,
giving it everything.
Captain Grant didn't flinch.
[GRANT] Copy that. Major Taylor!
She never gave up.
They just overwhelmed us now.
They were slaughtering us.
[DISTANT SCREAMS]
We were never going to win.
[GRANT, ECHOING] Major
Taylor, where are you?
- And I ran.
- Marcus?
- And I hid.
- Where are you?
I should have stood
and fought with them.
Instead, I just ran away.
I should have fought with them.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
Comms are ready.
[SIGHS]
[RALEN] We should send
a message to Zatar.
They will dispatch a rescue ship.
I'm alerting EarthCom to the fact
that your people are amassing
an armada to destroy the Earth.
I'm afraid I cannot let you do that.
What, and you're going to stop me?
Ralen, you can hardly stand.
I will not let you send that
message, Commander Duvall.
Is that a threat?
Take it as you wish.
I have a sworn duty to the Confederacy
to report vital military intelligence.
Jax.
Jax, what the hell are you doing?
Being impulsive.
Jax, we only had one
message and you sent it.
What did you do?
I sent it to the only
people we can trust.
Someone is trying to contact me.
Who?
I don't know. This feels so weird.
I had to tap into a very
low-tech wavelength
to get the transmission.
What is it?
I'm receiving a simple
text-based hyperspace message
along with a set of coordinates.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh!
It's Jax.
She's with Xander.
And Ralen.
You did it. You found them.
Actually, Jax found us.
For some reason her
message sent through
an ancient information database
known as the World Wide Web.
Never heard of it.
The good news is I know where Jax is.
The bad news is she's
in serious trouble.
We're going to need some help.
[SIGHS]
[SPUTTERS]
Well, well. There's two faces I
wasn't expecting to see again
quite so soon.
And what prompts your visit
at this ungodly hour?
This may sound harsh, Professor,
but you fibbed to us.
We know Jax and Xander are
not on a special assignment
for the Academy.
And what makes you say that?
Because they're stranded
halfway across the galaxy,
and desperately need our help.
And how exactly do you know this?
Jax transmitted a message to me.
I know where they are.
And what was this message?
"Help.
Surrounded by New Portland enemy."
We have to help them, Professor.
And I will.
Give me the coordinates,
and I assure you I will find them.
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
"We don't think so, sir."
This is not a game, cadets.
I need those coordinates now.
And you'll get them...
on one condition.
I've interfaced with the battle
cruiser's computer and nav system.
Entering coordinates.
[PANEL BEEPING]
You have your destination, Captain.
Light speed.
I sent a message to Pilar.
I trust her.
Hopefully help is on the way.
What about sending a
message to EarthCom
about the Zatarian fleet
preparing to strike Earth?
Guess that's on hold for now.
You do not believe me when I say
I know nothing of the intention
of that Zatarian fleet.
You're my friend,
and I know you've never lied to me.
So I'm going to ask you something,
and I need you to tell me the truth.
Why did you follow me to Euphoria 7?
Now is definitely not
the time or the place.
Well, there may not be
another time or place.
Very well.
I was viewing a romantic
comedy transmission on Earth
while you were away.
I enjoyed it quite much, actually.
I wanted us to have the
same happy ending.
[LAUGHS]
You are so weird, Ralen.
Am I?
Yes.
But that's not necessarily a bad thing.
I don't think you understand.
I came to Euphoria 7 to tell you
that I had developed
sentimental feelings for you.
Sentimental feelings?
Romantic feelings.
What are you talking about?
I may be foolish to confess
this to you, but...
I believe I am in love with you, Jax.
[DRUM ROLL]
[LAUGHS]
Okay.
You are hurt way worse than I thought.
Do not do what you always do.
Make a humorous retort
to deflect uncomfortable conversations.
And I presume it is
uncomfortable for you.
It's not uncomfortable, it's
just a little surprising.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Not that I expect you
to answer this, but...
I wish to know if you
perhaps share my feelings.
[DOOR OPENS]
Those creatures, they're
inside the city.
We need to leave now.
We're completely surrounded.
[GUNFIRE]
Here. Shoot anything that moves.
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING]
They're on the roof.
- Stay close.
- What do we do now?
[SNARLING]
[BEEPING]
I'm sorry about your friend Elliot.
I would have done the same for him.
[EXPLOSION]
[MARCUS] Hang on!
[PANTING]
Are you okay?
[EXPLOSION]
[OSBORN, OVER RADIO] This is
Fleet Admiral Donovan Osborn
onboard the EarthCom battle
cruiser Moshe Dayan.
Do you copy?
Sir! Sir! Sir!
Yes! Yes, sir! This
is Commander Duvall.
I am with Jax and Ralen on the surface.
Yes, sir!
[XANDER] Am I glad to hear your voice.
We see your vehicle.
We are making planetfall
and will commence exfil.
[OSBORN] Deploy infiltrators.
[SQUAD LEADER] Infiltrator
Squad One to Squad Two,
get in formation.
[OSBORN] Deploy shuttle.
[SQUAD LEADER] Prepare for exfil.
Protect the shuttle. Dust-off inbound.
Okay, we have eyes on the shuttle.
[GUNFIRE]
[XANDER] The shuttle has landed!
Over there!
[ALL GRUNT]
Everybody out. Now.
I'll lure them away so you
can make it to your ship.
Come on.
The aliens are coming. We need to go!
Marcus, come with us.
No, I ran before.
Everybody I cared about
died 150 years ago.
This time I'm going to do what's right.
I'm going to stay and fight.
Be safe and send Earth my
regards when you get home.
Thank you for giving
me a second chance.
Get out of here.
Go. Go. Go!
Come at me, you ugly bastards! Ah!
[MARCUS] For Elliot!
[SHUTTLE PILOT]
This is shuttle XL4.
We have cleared the planet
and will commence docking.
The first portal took us
to a Zatarian outpost
where the fleet that we'd
been tracking is mustering.
The coornates from my multi-bracelet...
I am aware, Mr. Duvall.
What I now need is a full debrief
on portals you encountered.
How they worked and
where they took you.
We lost Jacqueline's signal
when she made the jump
through the first portal.
What signal?
From the nanotech you injected
into her on Euphoria 7.
You don't think you were
the only one watching.
Why do you think I gave it to you?
You knew that Fried would
use her to open the portal?
You wanted her to do it.
To see what was inside, yes.
Say, if that was the case,
then why didn't you just tell me
when you sent me to Euphoria 7?
You had an extremely
valuable part to play
in our little drama,
and I believed you would
be more convincing
if you didn't know every
detail of the denouement.
And you knew I wouldn't do it
if I knew I was serving
Jax up to Harlan Fried.
Well, that too.
[AIR HISSING]
Hey.
Jax.
Did we make it off the planet?
[LAUGHS]
We did.
That's good to hear.
And I'm glad that you're
here with me as well.
I need to think.
About us?
About a lot of things.
Does that mean you're not interested
in a sentimental relationship with me?
It just means I have to think.
Okay?
Now, get some rest.
- Okay.
Will Ralen be okay?
He will.
And I can't thank you both enough.
If you hadn't gotten my
message and warned my uncle,
we would still be stranded down there.
What are friends for?
Speaking of friends, where's Thomas?
I thought he'd be with you guys.
What is it?
He's not still mad at me, is he?
[MONITORS BEEPING]
[INHALES AND EXHALES SHAKILY]
Quiet... at last.
[ALARM BLARING]
[COMPUTERIZED VOICE] Oxygen
levels critical, 17%.
Oxygen levels critical, 17%.
Oxygen levels critical...