Previously on Pandora...
I may be an empath, but
I... I'm no mind reader.
My dad served in the military, too.
He said EarthCom did some pretty
messed up stuff during the War.
The only reason you came
on in this little adventure
was because I promised you information
about what happened to your parents.
You used me like you always
do to get what you wanted.
You don't care whose lives
you put at risk to do that.
Why do you always have
to act so superior?
Because I am superior.
It's not narcissism.
It's an empirical fact.
♪ You say goodbye ♪
Atria's been bugging me to do a night up
at that new spa up on The Pearl.
I hear it's great.
I hear it's expensive.
Oh, come on, it'll be a fun
trip up the space elevator.
We deserve a night of R & R
with a little zero-g massages,
maybe a facial.
I would very much like to attend also.
Sorry, no C chromosomes allowed.
Girls only, Ralen.
But why don't you and Thomas
plan a boys' night together,
do something fun.
Like throwing chairs.
Is that your idea of fun?
On Zatar, throwing chairs is
considered quite entertaining.
You will never guess what I found out.
You know, that very stud-muffinly
young teacher's assistant
that you don't want to
admit you're so crushing on?
You mean Xander?
- Mmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
He has a birthday tomorrow,
and he doesn't want
anyone to know about it.
Well, then he obviously
told the wrong person.
Was that a joke?
Just an insight I've made from
observing Atria's behavioral patterns.
So in other words, it's a joke.
Well, he didn't tell me.
He told Kossara, and
then Kossara told me.
Why would he tell the bartender
that he's having birthday
if he didn't want anyone to... ?
You're Delaney Pilar, aren't you?
I am. But you may call me Pilar.
I am Jet. I'm in Shral's Interstellar
Protocol class with you.
You know, maybe we could
get together to study
one day.
Well, she's already in a study group.
- Would you like to... ?
- No, thank you, Jet.
Maybe next semester.
Oh, how about dinner this semester?
Ah, sorry, I'm really busy.
But I appreciate the invitation.
You obviously have time for
drinks with your friends,
but you have no problem
blowing me off, huh?
Don't tell me you're with this Zit?
I'm not "with" anyone.
And I'm definitely not
interested in being "with" you.
You know, someone's gonna knock
you off that pedestal one day,
- you smug...
- I suggest you walk away.
Now.
You okay?
When you're as attractive
and smart as I am,
unfortunately, these things happen
more frequently than I'd like.
But I'm fine.
Could I get a Sumi Starburst, please?
What's wrong with that one?
Are you sure you're okay?
Never better.
Like many Sumi customs,
their dining etiquette
is highly ritualized.
They begin each meal
by praising the host
and declaring themselves
unworthy of his or her generosity.
What might the Sumi make
of the old Earth tradition
of touching glasses to make a toast?
Ms. Larson.
As it says in chapter three
of Simak's Guide to
Interstellar Diplomacy,
the Sumi are very sensitive to
gestures of respect and disrespect,
so I think they would appreciate
the honor of someone
making a toast to them.
Then I sincerely hope
you don't pursue a career
in interstellar relations,
or we might find ourselves
in yet another war.
Who would like to explain
Ms. Larson's error?
Ms. Pilar, please enlighten
us with your wisdom.
As it says in chapter four
of the Simak's Guide,
the Sumi are also extremely
sensitive to germs and contamination.
They'd find the gesture
of touching their glass,
or any other eating utensil,
to someone else's to be repulsive.
And possibly an act of
violence and hostility.
Excellent.
War with the Sumi mercifully averted.
Class dismissed.
- Hey...
- I'm used to it.
Some people think I
have an unfair advantage
because of my nanites and
connection to the datastream.
But that only helps with
things like rote memorization,
which the Academy isn't about.
The teachers here expect
analysis and critical thinking.
I have to do that with my own
brain, just like everybody else.
You study harder than anyone I know.
You deserve those straight A's.
Speaking of studying,
I talked to Xander about needing
some extra tutoring from him,
and I've arranged to have him
come to the Black Hole tomorrow
at exactly 1900 hours.
God, I love surprise parties.
And boy, is he gonna be surprised.
Do you think that maybe,
since he didn't tell anybody
it was his birthday, that...
Pilar!
Pilar, can you hear me?
Pilar! Can you hear me?
Pilar, wake up!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Are the doctors going to call
when they know what's wrong?
I hope so.
I'm listed as Pilar's
emergency contact but...
never thought she'd actually need it.
Maybe I should go back to the
medical center and see if she's okay.
No need.
They released you.
Are you okay?
Should you not be getting more tests?
Oh, I already got plenty.
Anyway, the cute doctor
gave me a thorough check up,
including diagnostics of all
of my implants and nanites.
I'm entirely fine.
Other than the fact the doctor
already has a girlfriend.
So, what happened? Why did you collapse?
Just exhaustion and stress, they said.
Apparently it happens
to a lot of freshman.
But you haven't been exhausted
or stressed, have you?
Only... with mid-terms coming up,
I guess I've been
pushing myself too hard.
Maybe we should do that
spa day sooner than later.
Oh, can I?
Still no.
Okay.
Where you going, P?
Wha... ?
Stop looking.
She's hot.
Could you stop staring?
This is not stress. This is
something way more serious.
I think I was sleepwalking.
You don't just suddenly
start sleepwalking.
And yesterday, you
collapsed leaving class.
I think something could be
seriously wrong with you.
The doctors said my BIOS
were completely normal.
Maybe it's not something physical.
I assure you there is
nothing wrong with me.
I am functioning at peak efficiency.
You know, if you're ever
worried about anything,
you can talk to me, right?
I just need to rest and recharge.
I will meditate on the datastream
again before Xander's party.
- I'm worried about you.
- You needn't be.
I am looking forward to the party
tomorrow and watching the two of you
do your "we don't have the hots
for each other" mating dance.
- We don't have...
- Good night, Jax.
Good night, P.
Aah...
What is it?
Are you all right?
No. You woke me up
with all that yelling.
What are you talking about, silly?
You said you really wanted
a strawberry milkshake?
No, I didn't.
Although I was thinking about one.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Ever since me and my pop mind dived,
my telepathic powers seem to be growing.
So, what am I thinking now?
Did you just do what I think you did?
That's telekinesis, not telepathy.
How is that even possible?
You can't tell anyone about this.
Why not?
It's too dangerous.
The ETC did horrible things
to my pop during the war.
If they found out that I inherited
some of his abilities, then...
The war is long over.
The Corps was disbanded years ago.
They're always planning
for the next one.
And I can't put you or any
of our friends in danger.
Isn't that a little paranoid?
EarthCom doesn't do things like that...
do they?
Pilar au naturel. Oh...
Thank you, God.
Is everything all right, Pilar?
Of course. Uh...
See you tonight at the party.
Pilar, where are you?
All right. Xander's gonna be here
in a few minutes. Everybody hide!
Where is Pilar?
Is she not attending?
She'll be here.
She said she wouldn't miss it.
And then, last night, I had this
amazing breakthrough on my paper.
The Battle of Proxima Centauri
has always been considered
a turning point in
the Earth-Zatarian War,
but didn't EarthCom really gain the
advantage after the Siege of 2187?
Well, uh, that's certainly
an... interesting thesis.
You don't agree?
It doesn't matter
whether I agree or not,
as long as you have facts
to back up your arguments.
Oh. Thanks, Xander.
Thank you. That is good advice.
Now, just one more thing...
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
Thanks. Thank you.
Many happy returnings.
Is that not right?
It's close enough.
Well, this is certainly a surprise.
Well, you can thank Atria for that.
She insisted we do
something for your birthday.
Obviously. Thank you. Thank you, Atria.
Happy birthday, Xander.
Oh.
Oh, hug him already!
Sushi?
Yeah.
Great.
You know I really do appreciate this.
I didn't realize how much
I needed a break from work.
Ah... yes, work.
Too bad you can't tell me what that is.
Although, I am sure saving the
galaxy can be quite exhausting.
- Hmm.
You looking for someone who's not me?
Pilar.
She was supposed to be here by now.
I gotta go.
You're leaving already?
Why? Do you want me to stay?
Well, I didn't say that exactly.
Hey, ah...
You're learning.
Anyways, I gotta go check on
Pilar and make sure she's okay.
By the way, you never told me
what you wanted for your birthday.
You never asked.
Well, I'm asking now.
Well, how 'bout I tell
you when you get back?
Deal.
Welcome home, Jax.
Pilar, where... ?
Pilar.
Jax.
I think I'm broken.
I'm broken, Jax.
There's got to be something
wrong with my bio-organic.
It's the only explanation
for what's wrong with me.
Stop that!
What are you talking about?
This isn't stress.
Something in me is malfunctioning.
Something the doctors missed.
There's got to be an
error with my implants
or the core data program that
controls the nanites in my bloodstream
that's affecting my motor functions.
I didn't want to tell anyone
'cause I was afraid
you'd think I was crazy
or just making this whole thing up.
No one who knows you
would ever think that.
We just want to help you.
If there's nothing physically wrong
with me or my implants,
then it must all be in my mind.
Maybe it's not my parts, maybe
I'm the one having a breakdown.
I don't know what's wrong,
but we're gonna figure this out.
Together. Okay?
You've thoroughly analyzed
all of your bio-organics?
What about their source code?
Not yet.
Then let's go through them,
line by line, until we find the glitch.
What if there is no glitch?
What if it's me, Jax? What
if I'm the one who's broken?
No mater what, I will
always be here for you.
You're not alone.
Thanks, Jax.
I've never really understood what
it's like to have a real friend.
I never needed one until today.
Happy birthday, lieutenant.
What?
I said happy birthday, Xander.
It's almost morning, and you haven't
even unwrapped your present yet.
Kossara...
not tonight.
Thank you.
It's been a long night.
We've found nothing.
It's hopeless.
And now I really am exhausted.
Wait... look at this. It's
the code for your dataport.
This one line keeps doing that.
It could have been so easy
for the doctors to miss it
in their diagnostics.
It's not your hardware,
it's your software.
I think we just found the glitch.
I don't think it was a mistake.
It looks like a back door
was programmed into the code
to access the datastream...
and me.
I thought the datastream
was impossible to hack.
Even the Zatarians couldn't
do it during the War.
It is impossible...
without a back door like this.
Who could have put that there?
Most likely, the original
programmer at the company
that manufactured the dataport.
Let me guess.
Parallax.
But why would they want
to hack your implants?
I have no idea.
There's only one reason to
put malicious code in there.
Whoever did that wanted
to be able to control you.
I feel so completely violated, Jax.
What do you say we cut
their strings, Pinocchio?
I don't know.
Once we sever the connection,
whoever's responsible won't
be able to control you anymore.
But if I leave it disconnected,
I won't be able to access
the datastream again.
No.
At least not until we track down
who's been doing this to you.
How do we do that?
I've been on the
datastream my whole life.
I don't even know how
to exist without it.
Do you trust me?
I'm learning to.
I haven't always been as loyal
to my friends as I should have.
But I only want to help you.
I know that.
Good.
'Cause I need you to believe me
when I say we can't do this alone.
We're going to need some help.
It's absolutely inconceivable.
So you don't believe me?
Of course I do, Ms. Pilar.
I just find it unconscionable
that anyone could inflict
this kind of suffering on you.
We have to do something about this.
It appears logical that
Parallax is responsible
for the flaw in the code.
If you can figure out why,
that will help you determine the who.
But... what could anybody want from me?
I wish I could answer that.
What happened at the Black Hole
and then those holograms
of her, that's personal.
Someone has a grudge against Pilar.
Do you know anyone who might
fit that description, Ms. Zhou?
As a matter of fact I do.
Hey, Jet.
We need to talk to you.
About Pilar.
Yeah, sure. I'd love to talk about her,
especially those big, round...
Whoa!
Man, this guy's fast.
Perhaps that's why he
goes by the moniker "Jet".
Do you think?
I'm so sorry.
How clumsy of me.
Ow, you're hurting me, man!
That is my intention.
What do you want?
You tell us, genius.
You're the one with all
the tricked out uber-tech,
so you must have all the answers.
Yeah. Something about Pilar, right?
You are correct, Jax.
He does possess a keen degree
of mental acuity, after all.
What do you want me to say?
I couldn't resist sending out
that holo-nude after she flamed me.
We know you are the one
who hacked her dataport
and forced her to behave in
such an uncharacteristic fashion.
I didn't hack anybody!
You... You can't hack the
datastream. It's impossible.
How did you find out about the
back door in the datastream code?
What back door?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
If you continue to be duplicitous,
I may be forced to apply some
Zatarian methods of persuasion.
We call it the mind ripper.
The English translation
is not entirely accurate,
but I believe you get the point.
I've never tried this on a human before,
but there's a first time for everything.
No, no, no. Look... Look, I'm sorry
I embarrassed your friend, okay?
But I never hacked her. I
don't have that kind of tech.
Really!
- Uh, hello? What is this?
- Ow!
I'm commencing a mind ripper.
Okay, okay, look, it's all fake, okay?
My implants don't actually do
anything. They're just for show.
Speak.
The hacker crowd I run with...
they can afford all
this incredible tech.
Or their parents can, anyway.
My family don't have
the credits to afford it.
So... I fake it.
This...
This is just an ordinary contact lens.
Yeah.
And... And this, this
is a real dataport,
but it isn't connected to anything.
And this tech on my
face is a cheap fake.
Guys, I... I couldn't have
hacked your friend,
or anyone, even if I wanted to.
I think he's telling the truth, Ralen.
If you did not hack Pilar, then who did?
How the hell should I know?
Whoa. No, no, please.
This is your crowd, right?
They're always trying
to one-up each other
with the most difficult hacks.
So if someone was able
to pull off the impossible
and hack the datastream,
they would tell everyone,
would they not?
Tell us who's been extolling
their cybernetic acumen
and technical aptitude.
Uh...
You...
Bragging.
Who's been bragging?
You don't know what these people
would do to me if you cross them.
You should be more worried
about what I'll do to you.
- Come on.
- Wait, stop! Stop!
I can give you the names of some
people I think could have done it.
But I don't know for sure.
How are you supposed to relax
when it's so quiet without
any voices in your head?
The idea is to feel your own body,
listen to your own thoughts.
I don't like my own thoughts.
I keep remembering how
completely helpless I felt that night
at the Black Hole.
And then those holo-nudes
Jet sent to the entire school.
Normally, I could block
it out by flooding my mind
with sounds and images
from the datastream. But...
You've never been off the
datastream this long, have you?
Not since I was six years old.
That's when I first got my implants.
I don't even remember
my life before that.
The datastream has always been there.
I didn't have any brothers or sisters.
Or really any friends.
It was a way to not
feel so alone anymore.
I don't know how you concentrate
with all those sounds and
images in your head all the time.
When I'm on the datastream,
it feels like I'm connected to
something larger than myself.
Do you ever feel that way?
I guess that's why I joined the Academy.
To find that something.
I had it, and I've lost it.
I can't help thinking,
what if I have to keep
off the datastream forever
to keep this from happening again?
That is not going to happen.
Maybe those other students
were right to resent me.
I've spent months convincing everybody
how superior I am because
of my enhancements.
Without them...
I don't know who I am.
You said it yourself...
the datastream can only get you so far.
You've still had to work hard
to succeed at this Academy.
Even without the enhancements,
you are still beautiful
and funny and brilliant and kind...
a true friend.
I know that should be enough.
But this hacker stole something
from me, and I can't just let it go.
None of us are.
I promise.
We should get to class.
I'm not sure I can
face other people today.
Not if they're still talking about...
Fine then. We'll ditch class.
No. You should go.
And leave you alone with all this quiet?
I don't think so.
I'll be okay. You go to class.
The study group needs you.
Without me, they'll need the second
smartest student in the group.
I'll be okay.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Perhaps we are approaching
this incorrectly.
If we can determine how the
interloper took control of Pilar,
that may help us identify
who is responsible.
From what I learned from
talking to Professor Baker
in the engineering department,
they could be anywhere
on the datastream.
They wouldn't even have to be
close to Pilar to mess with her.
Which would explain
Parallax's involvement.
But why choose her?
Shral thinks there might
be a personal connection.
But if that were the case,
wouldn't the hacker want
to watch her every moment?
At least while he's controlling her?
Jet was in the Black
Hole when Pilar walked in.
Jet was also in Professor Shral's
class when Pilar collapsed.
Was that the first incident?
No. It was in the Black Hole,
when she ordered another Sumi Starburst,
even though she had one
she hadn't even touched yet.
So who else was there?
I mean here.
Jet, but I am almost
positive it wasn't him.
There were at least a
dozen other people here.
But I regret to say I...
I don't recall any of them.
I have a plan.
What if we re-integrate
Pilar to the datastream again
and wait for the hacker
to try something.
Only this time, we'll be
there waiting for them.
It sounds dangerous, Jax.
Are you sure Pilar will want to
risk going back on the datastream?
There's only one way for
us to know for certain.
We must ask Pilar.
Welcome home, Jax.
Oh, no.
Pilar is gone.
Like "gone" gone.
I can't believe it.
She didn't even say sayonara.
I don't think she's coming back.
Wassup, Atria?
Why is she here?
Pilar's in trouble.
I know you're upset with
me, and I don't blame you.
But we really don't have time for this.
Pilar has left the Academy.
We need to locate her before something
else unfortunate happens to her.
I'd like to, but what can I do?
You can help us find
out who's responsible.
How's that?
We think it's someone who hangs
out with Jet and his hacker squad.
So if you could just get close
enough to read their minds,
- then maybe we...
- What?
- You told them?
- I had to.
Pilar needs us.
This was supposed to be between
us, Atria. It was private.
I didn't want you to tell
anybody. I told you that.
Please, Tommy.
If you can read minds after
what happened with your father,
then you're the only one
who can help us help Pilar.
I know you don't trust
me after I used you to get
what I wanted with
your father and Tierney,
but this isn't about me.
This is about our friend.
And she needs our help right now.
That's why I need to
take a leave of absence
from the Academy, Dr. Osborn.
Well, frankly, I thought you
had a much brighter future
ahead of you here.
That you might be able to
make command track eventually,
or there could even be a
role for you in the C.I.S.
Apparently, I was mistaken.
I just can't control
what's happening to me.
I need some time to
heal and re-evaluate...
I can assure you you
will have ample time
to re-evaluate your choices in life.
Consider yourself expelled.
Expelled?
- Uh, but I don't want to leave. I just need...
- You're excused.
Good luck with your future endeavors.
- But, sir...
- I said you're excused, Ms. Pilar.
Good day.
Xander?
What's wrong?
I've been expelled.
Surely not.
Can you... ?
Can you talk to the professor?
Ask him to reconsider.
I just need some time.
I understand.
You know, I saw those holo-nudes of you.
You did?
Hey. Don't be embarrassed.
You looked amazing.
It made me wonder if maybe I've been
chasing the wrong girl.
- What?
- Well, you're very beautiful.
You have an amazing body.
Maybe you and I can
spend some time together on The Pearl,
discuss how I can
convince Professor Osborn
to let you back into the Academy, hmm?
Just you and me.
What about Jax? I-I thought
you had feelings for her.
Pretty sure there's enough
of me to go around.
Hey.
No, no.
Jax.
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
You won't believe what's been happening.
What is it? What's happening?
I went to your uncle for help,
- and he wants me to leave school.
- What?
- And then Xander.
- What about Xander?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I'm just glad you're here.
Cool. Well, I'm about to go
to the Black Hole
with Ralen for some drinks.
Do you wanna come?
No, I...
Oh, I think I did something really dumb.
Yeah. Walking into the Black
Hole naked was pretty stupid.
What?
You know that wasn't me.
Come on, Pilar. We all
know what really happened.
You had too much to drink, got wasted,
it's all very walk of shame-y.
What are you talking about? I...
I thought you were my friend.
How can you say that?
You're apparently confused.
See, Atria's my friend.
You're just my roommate.
You said that we were more than that.
I didn't want to be the
one to tell you this,
but I have some friends
going to college on Europa,
and they've all seen your holo-nude.
They can't believe that
you're my roommate.
You're kind of a C-list celebrity now.
I gotta go, Jax.
Bye, Pilar.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, my God.
Ralen!
I think I'm going crazy.
I was about to jump.
I understand.
Would you like me to push you?
Don't worry, Jet.
We're not here to ask you any
more questions about Pilar.
Good. 'Cause you know I
wouldn't tell you nothing anyway.
Neither would my friends
because we don't know
nothing, right, guys?
Of course.
Anyways, we found out who's responsible
and we just thought
you might want to know.
We need to go.
Now.
Did you just tell me to jump?
Why not?
What do you really have to live for?
Unless you want to come
back to Zatar with me.
My father might have special use
for a person with your abilities.
What use?
Don't be naive.
You know why I'm really here.
You know who my father is.
You will be a...
What did they call them
during your Cold War,
a "useful idiot" in the battle to come.
I would never betray the Confederacy.
Why?
It has already betrayed you.
You found out something, did you not?
I did.
Except for Jet, they all
know about the back door.
But only one of them was smart
enough to figure out how to use it.
Who? Who knew?
Locate Sarika Larson.
Go on.
Don't stop now.
Jump!
Pilar.
What are you doing?
I'm going to jump.
Isn't that what you want?
You'll all be happier when I'm gone.
No.
Of course not.
You said I was lying.
That I made it all up.
That wasn't me, Pilar.
You're in a simulation.
None of this is real,
but if you jump, your
brain could think it is,
and you could get seriously hurt.
You need to step down, now!
Wha... ?
What are you talking about?
This can't be another trick, can it?
It is,
but I'm not the one playing it on you.
You're in the VR Simulator at school.
After I left you, you must have
logged back onto the datastream
and got hacked again.
None of this is real.
No, no, no... She... She's lying.
Do it. Jump.
You're broken.
Your friends don't believe you.
You're worthless. Weak.
And deserve everything
that's coming to you.
That's not Ralen. It's Sarika.
Who's Sarika?
How do you not know who Sarika is!
From Shral's class.
She's the one who hacked you.
She's the one who lured you here.
She's jealous of you, and
she wanted to hurt you.
But you are so much stronger than this.
You have always been there
for me when I needed you.
Let me be there for you now.
VR program terminated.
That must have felt good.
You have no idea.
Uh, let me get you another one, Atria.
How did you know I... ?
Why does it have to be like this?
I thought after everything...
I did it for Pilar, Jax.
Not for you.
That's what real friends
do for each other.
I understand.
I have to go. Catch you later, Atria.
Bye, Thomas.
What in the worlds?
Ms. Pilar. Just who I was looking for.
I... I didn't forget
an assignment, did I?
Not at all.
I have news to share that I
thought you'd all like to hear.
By unanimous vote of the
disciplinary committee,
Sarika Larson has been
expelled from the Academy.
And furthermore, on my recommendation,
the civilian authorities
have been alerted
to pursue assault charges against her.
I can't thank you enough
for your help, sir.
Would you like to join us, professor?
Don't mind if I do.
Yeah.
I'm sure you'll be pleased
to hear you received
a perfect score on your
Interstellar Protocol midterm.
An impressive feat, considering you
were under the weather at the time.
And you weren't even back
on the datastream yet.
That was 100 percent Delaney Pilar.
That's wonderful!
Yay you!
The real congratulations
belongs to you guys.
You never gave up on me,
even after I gave up on myself.
Aww.
Ms. Larson?
Do I know you?
Regan Fried.
That was a most
impressive piece of coding.
What do you mean?
Let me be frank.
We gave the information
about the back door flaw
to a select number of candidates.
You're the only one who
exploited it successfully.
How do you know about that?
We created it.
The Parallax Corporation is always
looking for creative thinkers
like yourself.
Would you be interested in a job?
Only if I can get back at Delaney Pilar
and her friends who
ruined my entire life.
I'm sure we can accommodate any
outside interests you may have.
Then you have yourself
a deal, Ms. Fried.
Apparently, we do understand
each other after all.
Professor Shral, I didn't realize
he was expecting you.
Most certainly he is not.
- Right, I'll just tell him...
- Don't even bother.
Oh, Martin, what can I... ?
You knew.
Parallax was using that
girl to hack Delaney Pilar.
Excuse me.
You wanted to use the roommate
to spy on Ms. Zhou for you,
but what you didn't expect
was that she was unreliable
and had her own agenda.
I do not know why you would think that.
I do not work with Parallax, and
I certainly would never condone
the physical or emotional
abuse of one of our students.
But...
if somebody is attempting
to observe Pandora,
we need to find out
who they are and why.
How long do you intend to keep her
in the dark about who she really is?
Until I know the threat she
poses has been neutralized
and where the girl's
allegiances truly lie.
You're playing with fire, Donovan.
If you're not careful,
you're going to burn.
No, Martin.
If we don't put out
this fire, we all burn.