You mustn't make him wait forever.
I love him.
I'd accept him in a trice if it
weren't for Marigold.
You say he'll let you keep her.
- That's not the problem. - What is?
If I stay silent,
there's a lie at the heart of my marriage.
But if I tell him the truth, will I ruin it?
Edith,
you're a grown woman and I can't force you.
But you cannot be married to a man
and leave him out of a secret like this.
It's not possible and you won't be happy.
How happy am I now?
Mrs Patmore, you are the owner of
No. 3, Orchard Lane,
Haughton-le-Skerne.
I am. I'm running it as a
bed-and-breakfast place.
Among your guests, was a certain
Doctor Fletcher and his wife?
Yes, they were my first.
Very courteous and respectable, I must say.
Not as respectable as you think.
Dr Fletcher was a Mr Ian McKidd
- and his 'wife' a Mrs Dorrit.
- What?
Mr Dorrit is now suing Mr McKidd for damages
related to adultery.
You may be called upon to testify.
Oh, my God.
There is some concern Haughton-le-Skerne
will be in the news,
as a site of a house of ill repute.
A house of ill repute?
I'm afraid the rumour mill
has already begun...
but there's a chance that Dorrit
may settle out of court.
- I'll keep you informed.
- Thank you, Sergeant.
Hello. What brings you here?
Oh, Mrs Patmore's the one to ask.
A house of ill repute?
Mama is swanning around the South of France
without a word to any of us.
- I wish Cora -
- I won't hear a word against Cora.
- Mama is being impossible.
- I was going to say,
"I wish Cora wouldn't take it to heart. "
Mama has exhausted my patience this time.
But she did give you Teo.
True. I forgive her everything.
Do you think he will marry Edith?
If he learns about Marigold?
I just don't want her to be hurt.
- Is that it, then?
- Yes, let's go.
Isn't Bertie's employer always in Tangiers?
Can you buy one?
Thank you.
The 6th Marquess of Hexham, 39, has died
on holiday in Tangiers
where he was a frequent visitor.
The cause is given as Malaria.
Lord Hexham was unmarried.
Does this mean Bertie's out of a job?
That depends on the heir.
Poor Edith. It was bad enough
he was an agent.
Now he may not be that.
Don't sound so gleeful about it.
You should have seen her face.
It wasn't very funny for Mrs Patmore.
No. And I'm not laughing, but -
But, you're laughing.
How many classes will you be
taking every week?
Five to start with.
Only afternoons between half-two
and half-four.
What does Mr Carson say?
I haven't asked him yet.
Don't ask him, tell him.
But suppose it doesn't work out?
Suppose I'm no good?
Of course I didn't know they'd invited you.
I would have mentioned it.
Nobody has been as rude to me as your son.
Why in God's name would he
want me at his wedding?
- Well, isn't it a good sign?
- I'm not sure what it's a sign of.
Amelia's influence.
Yes. I think I agree.
She is a very kind and gentle soul.
Is she? Is she, indeed?
Don't you think so?
To be honest, I don't know her.
It was all I could do not to
burst out laughing. Poor thing.
Is it funny? Suppose someone
makes a connection
between Mrs Patmore and her place
at Downton Abbey?
I'm sure they won't.
We should PRAY they don't.
I don't want this story repeated upstairs.
I'm not going to tell them.
Oh, that's the first proper laugh
I've had for ages.
- I couldn't resist telling you.
- Poor Mrs Patmore.
Oh, I know. It's awful for her.
I'm going to have to think of something
serious when I go down.
I had some rather sad news
when we were in Thirsk.
Lord Hexham's died.
- Who's that, M'Lady?
- The owner of Brancaster Castle,
where we all stayed last year.
For the grouse.
Not me, M'Lady. I was... otherwise detained.
Oh, of course you were. I am sorry.
Only it might affect Lady Edith's friend,
Mr Pelham.
He's the agent there. Or was.
He might be out of a job.
How worrying for them.
So my romance might not be the only one
to come to an untimely end.
Have you heard from Mr Talbot?
No. But that's a good thing.
- It means he's accepted my decision.
- Which is what you want?
Which is exactly what I want.
Oh, I just can't get the phrase
out of my head.
It just goes round and round.
A house of ill repute.
Yes, I know what it is, thank you!
Yes, I see.
Ah, Mr Dawes has got some news for you.
Do I want to know?
Read it for yourself.
You passed every paper with high marks.
Oh, Daisy. That's wonderful news.
Poor Mr Pelham.
First that terrible day at the racetrack,
- and then to hear his cousin's died.
- It does seem very hard.
- Did you get hold of him?
- Yes.
He's coming tomorrow, on the first leg
of his trip to Tangiers.
- I've asked him here.
- Good.
- How is he?
- Sad.
He loved his cousin,
and it was all so quick.
The trouble is they've already buried him
and Bertie's not sure what to do.
It's ordinary in hot countries.
It won't mean any disrespect.
No, but, should they leave him there?
Surely the decision is down to the
new Marquess not to Bertie.
Well, that's the thing.
He is the new Marquess... Bertie.
Bertie Pelham is now the Marquess of Hexham?
Yes.
Nonsense. He's having you on.
He'd have told you if he was the heir.
He did tell me. But his cousin
was in his 30s
and they all knew the girl
he was going to marry.
But that's absurd!
If Bertie's a marquess, then Edith -
Edith would outrank us all.
Yes. That's right.
Was he a close relation?
Second cousin, once removed.
Nobody thought it was possible
he would inherit.
Least of all Bertie.
He seemed like a nice young man to me.
And getting nicer by the minute.
With a real love of Brancaster.
Golly gum drops! What a turn-up.
That's dinner.
If we're not too distracted to eat.
So we'll all bow and curtsy to Edith.
- You'll enjoy that, Mary?
- Hardly.
And if Bertie is Lord Hexham
which I still don't believe,
- he won't want to marry her now.
- Careful.
Or people will think you're jealous, dear.
We don't want that.
It's only a try-out, Mr Carson.
Every day you'd leave at two?
And I'd be back by five. So I could
serve dinner and luncheon.
- No lingering over the pudding.
- Mr Barrow is still here -
- Oh, don't we know it.
- But if lunch does go on a bit,
there's still Andrew and Mr Barrow
and you to see to it.
And what makes you think you'll be any good?
I don't know exactly. Perhaps because
I want it so much.
There are plenty of little boys who
want to be famous cricketers.
It's not enough to make them champions.
I just want to try, Mr Carson.
And so you shall.
How terrible. Poor Mrs Patmore.
What an unlikely bawdy house madam.
Mrs Patmore's secret career.
We mustn't joke when Bertie's here.
We'll have long faces, don't worry.
- I had a call from Henry earlier.
- Henry?
Why didn't you say?
- I'm saying now.
- How is he?
Mourning Charlie Rogers.
Missing you.
You're not to ask him to come here.
Suppose he just turns up?
Don't encourage him, Tom. I mean it.
We'd be wretched long term.
And you're not wretched now?
- Mary thinks he'll throw me over.
- I don't see why.
It's surely very encouraging
he's coming here on his way to London.
Unless it's to break with me
so he can start afresh.
He's not bound.
I haven't accepted him.
Have you told him about Marigold?
Not yet.
Make a clean breast of it. Please.
You'll regret it if you don't.
With my luck, I'll regret it either way.
What are you doing?
Making time charts and setting some
tests for comprehension.
Tests? For the village children?
You're not expecting too much?
- Who wants cocoa?
- I think if you expect a lot, you get a lot.
No, thank you, Mrs Patmore.
- Good night.
How are you feeling?
I'm still shaken. I can't deny it.
Is your poor niece managing?
I'm going over to see her tomorrow.
I'll come with you.
A genuine, copper-bottomed
marquess for Edith.
Who'd have thought it?
She hasn't accepted him so
he's not obligated.
He wouldn't be coming here
if he'd changed his mind.
If anyone had told me Mary would
hitch up with a mechanic
and Edith would marry one of the
grandest men in England,
I'd have knocked them down.
Mary has got rid of her mechanic
- and Edith is not married yet.
- I know.
But for poor old Edith
who couldn't make her dolls do
what she wanted,
- it is rather wonderful.
- There's still Marigold.
She hasn't told him yet and she must
if they're to have any chance of happiness.
I beg you, my darling,
please don't let things be spoiled
for her this time.
- That's all I ask.
- All.
I think the wood is right the way it is.
We don't need it any larger.
Mary, let me get him up here.
- There's no point. Nothing's changed.
- You've changed.
It's not as easy as that.
I find him very attractive.
I like him a lot.
'I find him very attractive. '
'I like him a lot. '
What a load of baloney!
If I'm in love with him,
then what's that?
A powerful urge that fades.
Did it fade for you and Matthew?
We weren't married long enough
- but I'm sure it would have done.
- I'm not.
Tom, look I don't mean to pull rank
but with people like us,
we need to marry sensibly.
Especially if we're going to inherit
the family show.
It's a way of life that isn't for everyone
and a bad marriage can poison it.
He's not an orangutan.
He knows how it works.
He wants different things.
What about you and Matthew?
You came from different poles.
Yes, but we were young and free.
- It's difficult the second time.
- Why?
Because you know what's at stake.
It's easier to get it wrong.
- I only see a real opportunity for you
to get it right. - Honestly?
- I'm always honest.
- Are you?
Why would you say that
for heaven's sake?
One word, Marigold.
It wasn't my secret to tell.
So, it is true. Well, I knew it was.
Never mind Marigold.
She won't make you happy.
Henry Talbot will.
Oh, Henry Talbot, Henry Talbot.
You're far more on his side
than you were on mine.
He's the one for you. Trust me
and give him a chance.
No. And if you want to redeem yourself
in my good graces,
you won't give him a chance either.
Where is everybody?
Mary and Tom are agenting
and Edith's gone to meet Bertie's train.
Are we going to talk about it?
Are we going to sit by
and let this young man's family and future
be put at risk from a scandal
we are hiding from him?
I don't think she has to tell everybody
but I agree.
She must tell him. Then it's his choice.
Isn't it up to Edith?
You say that because
after Tony Gillingham had gone,
you thought none of your daughters
would make a marriage worthy of the name.
And now there's a chance and you can't
bring yourself to give it up.
You haven't got children.
You don't understand these things.
No. I haven't had children, Robert,
as you so kindly remind me,
but I hope I do have a sense of decency.
How long are you planning to stay?
Your cold must have cleared up by now.
Don't fight.
Nothing's going to get better
by you two falling out.
Hello, Mr Pelham. I mean...
I'm going to stay Mr Pelham
until the service.
But I wish you'd call me Bertie anyway.
- What sort of service will it be?
- Not a funeral.
I've decided not to disturb him.
I'll fetch his things and
settle his debts and
have a service at home to say goodbye.
That sounds like a very good plan.
- I hope you'll allow me to come.
- I want you to come.
You remember my sister?
Of course. Lady Rosamund.
This must be a strange and
unsettling time for you.
I'll say.
My mother's cock-a-hoop,
but she doesn't appreciate that
I was devoted to Cousin Peter.
I'm sure she does.
Not really. Most people didn't get
the point of him.
He was... so delicate.
But he was as kind to me as
any man has ever been.
Then how pleased he'd be to know
that you're his heir.
That's so nice of you.
Goodness.
I'm afraid you've made me blub.
Let me take you upstairs to unpack.
Luncheon's not for half an hour.
And that's the man you want to
trick into marriage?
I'm going for a walk.
I agree.
But Robert thinks Edith's had
so little luck in her life.
Oh, I sympathise, of course,
but we both know she's making a mistake.
One thing. Don't forget that Mr Pelham
is now the Marquess of Hexham,
when you address him.
I helped him unpack this morning
and he wishes to remain Mr Pelham
until his cousin's funeral, Mr Carson.
He can call himself Mr Pelham
to his heart's content
but he is Lord Hexham nevertheless,
Mr Bates,
and we will refer to him as His Lordship.
Good. Time to get started.
Good news?
Not exactly.
Thank you for your enquiry but
we wish to combine
the roles of butler, chauffeur and valet,
and you seem overqualified.
But please accept our best wishes
for the future.
- What future?
- Don't be silly.
Of course. That's right.
I'm silly, aren't I? Silly old me.
- No wait.
- Let him go.
What was it about Tangiers that your cousin
enjoyed so much?
Who knows? He used to talk of
going down to the beach
and watching the young fishermen
bring in the nets.
How the setting sun would make
the scene magical
until everything was suddenly
plunged into darkness.
Goodness. How lyrical.
He was lyrical. He was an artist.
In his heart, anyway.
I don't think this family can boast
much in the way of artists.
Although we did have an aunt who was
quite good at macrame.
So, are you here to settle things
with Edith before you leave?
Mary, please.
I hope so. I hope we can get
things settled
but I mustn't jump the gun.
You've talked of your mother but
what other family do you have?
That's it. My father's dead,
obviously,
there are no siblings.
It's just me and Mother.
You were joking when you said
she was cock-a-hoop
but she must feel a certain pride.
I wasn't joking but
you can judge for yourselves
when you meet her.
You talk as if we should be scared.
She makes Mr Squeers look like
Florence Nightingale.
Ladies? Can I have a picture?
No, you may not.
He's been there all day.
Well, why didn't you telephone and
warn us? You daft ha'porth!
I'm sorry, Auntie Beryl, I thought
you might not come
and I'm going nearly mad here.
What about the bookings?
Cancelled.
What?! All of them?
One man wanted compensation.
For the ridicule.
I hope you told him what he could
do with it!
I'll give him RIDICULE!
Now, calm down.
There's no harm done so let's go
and have some tea.
This is Mr Molesley.
He will be teaching you history
and English literature.
- Make him welcome, please.
- Good afternoon.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
This term we will explore
the years between the Civil War
of 1642 and...
1642 and the Glorious Revolution...
of 1688.
Almost half a century of change
and social progress.
I hope you will find it as exciting as I do.
Things have changed for you now.
You must know that you're quite free
if you want to be.
I don't.
Look, of course things have changed.
I was in line for a quiet life,
farming, sport, bringing up a
family with my wife.
But now I'm to be one of the
kings of the county -
always on parade, representing the people
who look up to me,
fighting for causes, trying oh so hard
not to be disappointing.
Oh, I think you'll make a
very good job of it.
You couldn't ask for a man with a
sounder moral conscience.
The conscience maybe,
but what about the courage?
Help me. Please.
But can I help? Am I worthy?
The 7th Marquess of Hexham
weds the daughter of the
5th Earl of Grantham?
What could be more suitable?
Mother will be thrilled.
You talk of her a lot.
She has been an important figure
in my life. I admit it.
But I don't agree with her about everything.
Is she very stern?
She certainly believes rank
carries responsibilities.
But so do I.
That's why I need you.
To help me live up to my own expectations.
We ought to go in.
Tea will have started and the children
will be down in a minute.
The husband has been bought off?
Well, he's settled out of court.
And you won't have to be a witness?
So Mr Willis said.
But I've still lost every one
of my bookings.
I'm still a laughing stock.
I did wonder about the whole idea
from the beginning.
You did not!
It's exactly what we're planning to do.
Then clearly we're going to have to be
a lot more careful
than Mrs Patmore, aren't we?
That's the front door, Mr Carson.
I'll go.
Punch is terribly fierce.
I don't think he's a good model
for marriage in later life.
Or relations with the law.
- Take that! And that! And that!
- Ouch, you rascal!
And that's the way to do it!
Very good!
Mr Talbot.
Hello, Mr Talbot. Mary never told me
you were coming.
I didn't know he was.
Well, the thing is, I was driving down
from Durham
and I suddenly realised I'd almost be
passing the gates.
What were you doing in Durham?
Oh, I was doing various car things.
We haven't seen you since that
awful day at Brooklands.
I hope you're coping with it all.
Well, one doesn't have much choice.
Did you know about this?
I might have said if he was
coming from Durham,
then he'd be driving quite close.
Don't think I'm amused.
I dislike my hand being forced.
No-one's forcing anything.
Now you're here, I hope you'll stay
the night at least.
Mary?
Perhaps Mr Talbot is in a hurry to get home.
No, no I'm not.
It's settled then. Carson, will you
please tell Mrs Hughes?
And ask someone to unpack for Mr Talbot.
I'm afraid you've missed tea.
- Oh, don't worry about that.
- I won't.
Hello, Bertie, I heard about your cousin.
I'm so terribly sorry.
Thank you. I'm on my way out there now,
but I wanted to get things settled
before I go.
And are they... settled?
I think so. They will be.
Then I envy you.
I would say Mr Talbot has just
miscalculated rather badly.
.. The struggle between the Monarchy
and Parliament.
Oh, right. That's it for today.
Oh yes, er some of you
may like to examine these time charts
that I've drawn up,
and tomorrow we'll really begin
to make a start.
Would you...?
This is so precisely not the way
to win me over!
Mary, will you just get off your high horse?
Why are you interfering anyway?
Because I love you and want you to be happy.
Well, you've got a bloody odd way
of showing it!
Well, I take it this is me
you're fighting about?
Yes, it is. And you can dig yourself out.
Because I've had enough.
Have you brought a dinner jacket?
Yes.
Well, you were very well equipped
to do your 'car things' in Durham.
How many years do you think
it's taken to find someone
I want to spend the rest of my life with?
Living in my family house?
Working to preserve my estate
and being outranked by your own stepson?
Oh, I'm tougher than I look.
Oh, Henry, please don't make this
harder than it has to be.
Are you mad?
If you're trying to get rid of me,
I'm going to make this as hard
and as horrible as I can!
Well you're being extremely unfair!
I wish I knew what we should do.
I'm attempted to tell him myself.
You think he's strong enough to stand out
against his mother?
Can't we just leave Edith to tell him
or not, as she sees fit?
Tell him what?
That Mr Gregson made Edith his heir.
Some men might not feel
comfortable with that.
Why did you invite Henry to stay,
without asking me first?
Darling, it was half-past five
and the man was in North Yorkshire.
What did you want him to do?
Pitch a tent under a tree?
He must have made a plan for his
journey back from Durham.
I doubt he ever went to Durham.
He came up here to see you.
- Who says so?
- The look in his eyes.
Not one of you thinks it's a good idea!
A professional driver?
With nothing to his name?
- Then give him up.
- I had. I did.
Until Mama invited him
to make himself at home!
You can't expect us to be rude.
The man's only crime is to love you.
Just send him away! As quick as
you can. For all our sakes.
She's right about one thing.
None of us thinks it's a good idea.
No, maybe not. But she's clearly
quite mad about him,
whatever she says.
How was it, Mr Molesley? Teaching?
It was a, quite a challenge.
There's always another day.
I know.
They've got their coffee upstairs so
I'll make a last check.
How are you getting to Tangiers?
Is there a boat that sails direct?
- Actually I'm flying. For the first bit,
anyway. - What?
I know. It does seem rather daring.
I do not envy you.
I don't know. Now the commercial airlines
are starting to operate,
I dare say we'll all be flying
hither and thither before too long.
I rather doubt that.
I must say I do like the way
Bertie makes no bones about it.
He's here to see you.
I know.
The same could be said of me
but I'm not doing as well as he is.
I hope you know what you are doing.
She's quite a handful you know.
- Who's a handful?
- My beloved sister.
Well, she is beloved by me, anyway.
I like Bertie. I do. But when you
see them together...
Meaning?
If Henry were the new Marquess of Hexham,
there wouldn't be a woman in England
who wasn't setting her cap at him.
What about you? Would you
set your cap at him?
Because if that's why you're not,
shame on you.
Oh, stop lecturing me!
Excuse me.
Mary, wait.
Wait!
Look, I made a mistake. I'm sorry.
I thought I could present my arguments
effectively in person,
- clearly I was wrong.
- I can't bear to be manoeuvred.
But you see, I think we love
each other very much.
For some reason,
you're fighting it. I'm not.
My birth is respectable,
so it can't be that,
which forces me to believe that it is
my lack of money and position
that present the problem.
- Aren't you better than that?
- What?
Well, it just seems rather small to me.
Not to marry a man for lack of money
is the same as marrying him because of it.
- Out of my way!
- Am I not right?
No. You push in here, into
my home, uninvited,
in order to call me a grubby,
little gold digger?
You've got a nerve!
Mary!
She loves him but she can't control him.
That's what frightens her.
He's stronger than she is, really.
Or as strong. And she's not used to it.
She's a bit of a bully, your Lady Mary.
She likes her own way.
She is and she does but
there's another side to her. He sees that.
- So you were wrong about him?
- I think I was.
- Why are you smiling?
- Show me a man
that doesn't smile when his wife
admits she's wrong.
Won't you send me to bed happy?
Sounds like an indecent proposal.
I meant, give me your answer.
Let me go to Tangiers with a sense
my tomorrows are beginning.
Please.
I love you, Bertie.
I've been in love before.
I won't pretend that I haven't.
But I really do love you.
Then I'll take that as a yes.
The trouble is, I'm not as simple
as I used to be.
My life is not as simple.
I... just need to be sure
I'm being realistic,
not living in a fool's paradise and
dragging you into it with me.
I'll still take it as a yes.
You're down early.
No, I'm not. Where's Henry?
- He's gone. - What?
He had something in London this evening
and wanted to get back.
I have a mass of letters to write.
- I'm sorry Lord Grantham's left.
- Why particularly?
Because we've got some news
and I was waiting for Mary to join us.
It's not the right moment.
Carson, could we have some more
coffee, please?
Why isn't it the right moment?
Well, Henry's abandoned you.
No, he hasn't. I wanted him to go.
- That's not what it looked like.
- Well, that's how it is.
There's no need for this.
Edith, if your news is good, then we are
very happy for you both.
Aren't we, Mary?
See? I told you.
The one thing Mary can't bear
is when things are going better
for me than for her.
I'm sure that's not true.
You don't know her.
I'm getting married and
you've lost your man.
And you just can't stand it.
- Edith, there is no need for...
- You're wrong.
I'm very happy for you.
And I admire you, Bertie.
Not everyone would accept Edith's past.
- Mary, don't.
- What do you mean?
Well, you must've told him?
You couldn't accept him without telling him?
Tell me what?
About Marigold. Who she really is.
Marigold is my daughter.
Will you excuse me?
I beg your pardon, Your Ladyship,
but Mr Pelham, that is,
Lord Hexham, has asked for a taxi
and Mr Carson has gone out,
so I'm not quite sure...
What? Lord Hexham's leaving?
Obviously, if he wants a taxi.
What's happened? Where's Lady Edith?
Can't she drive him to the station?
Don't bother about it, Mrs Hughes.
- I'll sort it out.
- Very good, M'Lord.
Mrs Hughes, how is Mrs Patmore?
She's still very upset, M'Lady.
But there's nothing to be done.
Is this about her B & B
going down the drain?
Don't be flippant.
Why don't we pay her a visit?
Have tea there and let people see us.
What a good idea!
Why didn't I think of that?
But if it's to be effective, won't we
have to be in the papers?
Well, the local papers. And it wouldn't
be a news story any more
than being photographed at a flower show.
Would Mrs Patmore agree?
I think she'd be bowled over, Your Ladyship.
Then it's settled.
I hope you don't mind my saying
that you seem very suspicious.
Do I? But you must admit, your attitude
is quite a volte-face.
I want Larry's father to be content.
Is that a volte-face?
Yes, but does your fiance
want his Papa to be content
in this way? With me?
Well, you know men.
I'm not sure I do, as it happens.
Tell me about them.
I only meant they dig themselves
into a position,
often before considering all the options.
- And you've considered 'the options'?
- I believe so.
Well, here's another option for you.
I won't rekindle Lord Merton's dreams
unless I'm invited to do so
by Larry Grey, himself.
Is that clear?
I speak for him.
Yes, but you see, I don't want you
to speak for him.
I want to hear him speak for himself.
Oh, I see. The plan is to mix up
His Lordship
or, worse, Her Ladyship,
with a divorce petition and the scene
of an adultery?
But I want to bury that story
and I need a big event to bury it under.
And you have no qualms about dragging
the family we serve
into the mud?
It's their choice, Mr Carson.
They're all grown people, surely?
Well, I've always known that
women were ruthless,
but I didn't think I'd find the proof
in my own wife!
And there's me thinking how kind they were
to come to the rescue.
And so they are. Just tell them yes
and arrange the day.
- He'll miss his train.
- Let him miss it.
He can catch the next one. What happened?
Mary thought Edith had told him
about Marigold.
- How did Mary find out?
- Mary is not stupid.
No. And she's not always kind, either.
Was it really a mistake?
What difference does it make?
I'm not shocked exactly. It isn't that.
I promise you.
You have to protect the honour of your family.
Of course you do.
It isn't even that.
You should have told me the whole story
from the beginning.
You haven't been fair to me.
No. I don't believe I have.
Then why didn't you?
I suppose I thought it might
ruin everything.
You mean you didn't trust me?
I can't have, can I?
Would you have married me in a lie?
I don't think so, but we'll never know now.
No.
You see,
I don't feel I could spend my life
with someone I don't trust.
Who didn't trust me.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
I'm terribly sorry, of course,
but that doesn't mean much, does it?
The truth is, my life was about to be
perfectly wonderful and
now I've thrown it all away.
I'd better go if I'm to catch my train.
Yes, hurry.
I doubt we'll meet again
so I want to say good luck,
and everything else that goes with it.
Good luck to you, too.
I mean that.
Well, you got what you wanted!
Bertie has left for the train
and Edith won't be the next
Marchioness of Hexham!
- Well, that's not what I wanted.
- Isn't it?
I still can't believe she'd never told him.
How was I to know that?
Don't play the innocent with me.
- I didn't mean it.
- Don't lie! Not to me!
You can't stop ruining things!
For Edith, for yourself!
You'd pull in the sky if you could!
Anything to make you feel less
frightened and alone!
You saw Henry when he was here
high-handed, bullying, unapologetic.
Am I expected to lower myself to his level
and be grateful I'm allowed to do so?
Listen to yourself.
'Lower yourself to his level'.
You're not a princess in
The Prisoner of Zenda!
- You don't want to understand me.
- You ruined Edith's life today!
How many lives are you going to wreck
just to smother your misery?
- I refuse to listen!
- You're a coward, Mary.
Like all bullies, you're a coward.
What are you doing up here?
Looking for you to borrow some scissors
but you're going out.
I've left my workbox downstairs
but you're welcome to take them.
Where are you off to?
I said I'd walk with Mr Molesley
to the schoolhouse.
For moral support.
Are you all right, Mr Barrow?
Of course. Why wouldn't I be?
- Going away?
- Do you care?
Look, I wasn't to know you hadn't told him.
It never occurred to me -
Just shut up! I don't know what's happened.
Tom has made you feel bad, or Papa,
or maybe it's just the same old Mary
who wants her cake and hate me to...
- I never meant to.
- Yes, you did!
Who do you think you're talking to?
Mama? Your maid?
I know you!
I know you to be a nasty, jealous,
scheming bitch!
Now listen, you pathetic
You're a bitch!
Not content with ruining your own life,
you're determined to ruin mine!
I have not ruined my life
and if Bertie's put off by that, then -
Don't demean yourself by trying to
justify your venom.
Just go.
And you're wrong, you know.
As you so often are.
Henry's perfect for you.
You're just too stupid and
stuck up to see it!
Still at least he's got away from you.
Which is something to give thanks for,
I suppose!
I beg your pardon, M'Lord but Mrs Patmore
has something to say.
- I wonder if now would be convenient.
- Of course. Bring her in.
How can we help, Mrs Patmore?
Well, that's just it, M'Lord.
I know you're planning to help
by coming over to the cottage for some tea
but should you be mixed up in it?
It's my mess, why should you pay for it?
Indeed.
Carson? Is this what you believe?
It is, Your Ladyship.
I wouldn't like to see
this family dragged into a tawdry,
local brouhaha.
He means me.
Oh, I think we have to show a little more
backbone than that.
- My Lord? - Mrs Patmore has been
loyal to this house
and this house must be loyal to her.
She had made a large investment
in her future.
We can't let it fall away to nothing.
I'll go now, if I may.
We'll see you on Friday.
Are you sure, My Lord?
QUITE sure, thank you, Carson.
You mustn't be nervous.
You don't know what they're like.
I felt like a fraud yesterday.
And all the time I kept wondering,
"What would they say
if they found out that I was a servant
at the big house?"
What would their parents say?
Why not tell them? Then they won't have to
find out, will they?
- Mr Barrow's in a funny mood.
- Why?
He suddenly told me out of the blue
how he hoped
I'd make more of my life than he'd
ever make of his.
I should go back.
- Is something wrong?
- I hope not.
Does Mrs Hughes know you're
on the men's side!
Never mind that. Have you seen Mr Barrow?
Er, he was going in for a bath.
Oh, my God! Come with me!
Hello! Mr Barrow! Are you in there?
Will you open this door?
Get back!
- Oh, my God!
- Fetch Mrs Hughes.
Send Anna for the doctor but tell
no-one else what you've seen.
- I wish I'd gone with them now.
- With who?
- Mr Molesley and Miss Baxter.
- Well, go then.
- I can manage. - I'll be too late, though,
won't I?
Well, you should still go if you want to.
For a walk.
They might have a break when you get there.
Where's Mrs Hughes and Anna?
Mrs Hughes is in her sitting room.
- Are you in a rush?
- Not particularly. Why?
I need you to come with me to the station.
Then you can drive the car home.
- Where are you going?
- Up to London.
I haven't said goodbye to anyone
and I can't bear to look at Mary.
She's unhappy.
- I think she regrets what she did.
- Not as much as I do.
And, for your information,
before I left we had the row
we all knew was coming.
I'm not sorry.
At least I'm just sorry we didn't
have it years ago.
Bertie may come round.
I don't think so. He might have
come round about Marigold.
In fact, I'm sure he would've done.
But I tried to trick him
and he won't come round about that.
Would you like me to talk to him?
No, but I love you for asking.
We should get going.
Anna's gone for Doctor Clarkson.
Now, we should get him into bed
and out of his wet things.
I hope he won't mind if we undress him.
He's past minding if we put him
in a shy and threw coconuts.
Now you take his feet and
we'll take an arm each.
- Should we tell His Lordship?
- Mr Carson's seeing to that.
Right. Here goes.
I hate to think he was so unhappy.
At least it's not gone too far.
Why should you?
.. And maybe one of you
will run the country one day.
How about that?
That's daft, sir.
Only toffs run the country.
No.
No, you see, you must never think that
education is only for special people,
you know, for clever people, for toffs.
- Education is for everyone.
- You would say that, sir.
Yes, I would. But I'm not anyone special.
You're a teacher.
I'm a teacher now. But I'm an
ordinary bloke.
I've spent my life in service,
fetching and carrying.
- You were a servant?
- I was. I am.
And I was glad to get the work.
My mum's in service. She works for
Mr Travis at the vicarage.
Dad's a gardener at Skelton Park.
But I never gave up on learning, do you see?
I read as much as I could
and I taught myself,
and I hope to be able to teach you.
Maybe give you the shortcut
that I never had...
Right.
The Civil War.
Let's start with the Divine Right of Kings.
Did King Charles
really believe that he had a
Divine Right to rule?
Or did he just choose to believe it
because it suited him?
You mean the King was a liar?
Not quite.
Kings are like anyone else.
Anna says Edith's gone to London
and I suppose we all know why.
- Do we have to do this now?
- Yes, I really think -
Carson, what's happened?
Where are the footmen?
That is something I need to
discuss with you, My Lord.
Thomas has cut his wrists?
- Yes, I'm afraid so, My Lord.
- God in Heaven.
Who knows?
Not many and I should like to
keep it that way.
I shall say that he is ill with influenza.
Carson... please don't bother with
serving our tea.
With your permission, My Lady.
How sad. How very sad.
Do you still think dismissing Barrow
was a useful saving, Papa?
That's rather below the belt, even for you.
Look, we've kept him out of the hospital.
Dr Clarkson stitched him up here.
He says Miss Baxter found him in time.
I'll go up in a minute.
I saw Doctor Clarkson leaving when I got back.
What was he doing here?
Mr Barrow has been taken poorly.
He will spend a day or two in bed.
Anna and Miss Baxter will look after him.
How was it, Mr Molesley?
I enjoyed myself today.
The children were generous to me.
The children were spellbound.
- How do you know?
- Because I crept in and listened.
- You never.
- I did. And you're a natural.
So,
are we to lose you to the groves of
academe, Mr Molesley?
Can I teach a little while longer
before I re-order my world, Mr Carson?
I'm glad, though. You're a kind man,
Mr Molesley.
It's about time you were rewarded
for your kindness.
He'll recover, M'Lady. And he hasn't
had to go to hospital.
- Can we keep it quiet? For his sake.
- That's what Mr Carson wants.
What a day.
I ruin Lady Edith's life
and Barrow tries to end his.
- How is Lady Edith?
- She's gone to London.
Which is hardly to be wondered at,
when her only sister has wrecked her
chances of a happy, fulfilling life.
Lord Hexham won't come round?
Lady Edith thinks not.
And I'm sorry.
What about you?
Have you thought any more about Mr Talbot?
Don't you start. You're as bad
as Mr Branson.
Why? What's he done?
He asked Mr Talbot to come here
and he keeps going on and on and on.
But Mr Talbot's not right for me.
He's not. We'd be miserable.
- As long as you're sure that you...
- I am sure!
I apologise.
It's just
nobody can believe that I know my own mind.
Of course, M'Lady.
Right. Can I do anything more for you?
No, thank you.
Good night.
And Anna...
.. I'm sorry.
- You don't know that's the end.
- Yes, I do.
And please don't think badly of him.
It was my own fault.
Well, I liked him.
Me, too.
Your sister hasn't been helpful.
Mary and I are locked into a kind of
lifelong struggle and I don't know,
it's hard for an outsider to understand.
It's hard for me.
Who invented families?
That's what I'd like to know.
What time is Miss Jones coming today?
Five. For tea.
Do we know her real name yet?
She only writes as Cassandra Jones
which is the name on her account.
Perhaps it is her real name, after all.
Well, real or not,
she has quite a following.
So we'd better be pals.
How did you get her to come here?
I'm afraid I forced her.
Look, she wants more money
which is fair enough given
the success of the column,
but I insisted we negotiate in person.
- Why? - I was curious.
Aren't you?
Suppose she sends someone
to impersonate her,
if she's as secretive as all that?
Let's have a sign if we think
it's the real Cassandra.
Say, "Bananas" if you think
she's telling the truth.
All right. Bananas it is.
May we come in?
Hello, Mr Barrow.
Here you are. To make you feel better.
Thank you very much, Master George.
We want you to get better, Barrow.
Truly. And no-one more than Master George.
At least I've got one friend, eh?
Have you been lonely?
If I have, I've only myself to blame.
I've done and said things.
I don't know why, I can't stop myself.
Now I'm paying the price.
Strange. I could say the same.
Mr Carson's told them that you've got...
'Flu. I know.
I beg your pardon, M'Lady.
We're going Barrow
and I hope things improve for you.
I really do.
I'd say the same if it weren't
impertinent, M'Lady.
- Goodbye, Mr Barrow.
- Goodbye, Master George.
- So. Today's the big day.
- Oh, spare me.
- Do you want to take Daisy with you?
- Oh, if I'm allowed.
I mean my niece is good
but she might be dumbstruck with those Lords
and Ladies sitting in my front room.
Come to think of it, how will the village
know that they've been?
Lucy's seen to that.
We've got the man from The Echo
coming at five.
Put up a poster, why don't you?
They're doing something nice, Mr Carson.
Don't spoil it.
Yes. Very nice.
For the public to read about
the cakes and dainties
His Lordship is guzzling as he sits
at the adulterers' table!
I'm sure there've been a few adulterers
sat at the table upstairs.
- That is different.
- Why?
To say nothing of suicidal footman
in the attic!
What are we coming to?
I only thank God that the Dowager
isn't here to witness it.
- I can't believe you came.
- You made it sound so urgent.
Even so, I really appreciate it. Thank you.
- Was everything all right when you
got home? - Well no, not really.
- Spratt has gone away.
- Did you tell him you were coming back?
A good butler should not need to be told.
Now, where are they?
My broken-hearted granddaughters?
It's just Mary. Edith's gone up to London.
I didn't know when I wrote.
All the better.
But how will we get it all there?
They're letting me have a car.
Seeing as I'm giving tea to His Lordship.
You're ready, then?
They've brought the car round.
Andrew, carry that out.
And very, very good luck.
And good luck to us all
in the vain hope that we'll
avoid scandalous gossip.
- You're such an old curmudgeon.
- Don't say you're going off me.
No, because you're my curmudgeon
and that makes all the difference.
Granny. When did you arrive?
Yesterday evening.
I spent the night before in Southampton
and an entire day on trains.
So I've come hot foot.
If you're here to reprimand me
about Edith, please don't.
Tom's already torn me into strips.
- Why did you do it?
- I don't know. She was so...
- Anyway, I'm sorry now.
- You should be.
With Edith, I just say things and
then they can't be unsaid.
Tom believes you're unhappy.
That's why you lash out as you do.
Look, if this is about Henry Talbot,
you should be clear
he hasn't much to offer.
Bertie Hexham is a loss but not Henry.
He's well born, but there's no
money or position.
He's not even a countryman.
Not really. He grew up in London.
- He shoots.
- Yes, he shoots.
Like every social-climbing banker shoots.
Well, let's leave his credentials
to one side for a moment
- and concentrate on what is important.
- Which is?
Tom says that he is in love with you
and that you are in love with him.
- Do you believe him?
- Do you deny it?
For you of all people to talk as if
his qualifications don't matter!
Tony Gillingham had all that I could wish -
birth, money, looks...
.. But he didn't suit you.
- No.
- He wasn't clever enough.
He wasn't strong enough.
Henry Talbot is both.
All right, Granny, it's not his poverty.
But did Tom tell you,
I stood there staring at a car in flames,
wondering if it were him?
I think he's told me everything.
Then you'll know I can't be a
crash widow again. I can't!
I'd live in terror, dreading every race,
every practice, every trial.
- I cannot do it!
- Does he know this?
He'd feel he should give it up
but I don't want that.
He'd resent me.
Oh, can't you find me some Duke?
There must be one spare.
So I can put Edith in her place.
You are the only woman I know
who likes to think herself cold
and selfish and grand.
Most of us spend our lives
trying to hide it.
Oh, Granny please don't
lecture me on sentimental virtues.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
I believe in rules and traditions
and playing our part.
But there is something else.
And what is that, pray?
I believe in love.
I mean, brilliant careers,
rich lives, are seldom led without...
.. Just an element of love.
Oh, Granny. You do surprise me.
Oh, I am glad.
So climbing all those stairs wasn't wasted.
No.
No, I would only say this.
First,
make peace with your sister.
And then make peace with yourself.
Oh, Mary.
- Is Granny coming back for dinner?
- She didn't say so.
She goes without telling us.
And returns without seeing us.
We're in the dog house.
How hard is that to understand?
Now, let's go.
- Sure you don't want to come with us?
- Quite sure.
You don't need me.
You're enough of a headline.
And you certainly don't need me.
- My Lord, I wonder if I might have a word?
- What is it?
With your permission, I'd like to
tell Mr Barrow
that he can stay for the time being
at any rate.
It would take a weight off his mind.
That's a relief. I was going to
suggest the same thing.
Were you, My Lord?
Yes. I feel quite as guilty
as you do, Carson.
I tell you what I blame myself for.
I didn't credit him with feelings.
I thought he was a man without a heart.
And I was wrong.
No man is an island, Carson.
Not even Thomas Barrow.
I ought to be very angry with you.
Summoning Granny to tick me off.
I was amazed she came at my call.
She said your letter was very eloquent.
She was quite persuaded.
So what are you going to do?
As soon as Granny left
I sent Henry a telegram
to get the next train.
- Hopefully he'll be here by tea time.
- What about Edith?
That's a harder task.
I'm ready to say I'm sorry.
But why should she want to forgive me?
I got held up. Is she here yet?
Miss Jones has arrived, yes, Lady Edith.
- Why the mysterious face?
- You better go in.
Edith.
So this, it turns out,
is Miss Cassandra Jones.
- Spratt?
- Good afternoon, Lady Edith.
Bananas!
I don't have to tell you why I'm here.
Either you know everything or
you're not hearing me now.
The truth is...
I love him.
I believe we are right together
but I so very much want to feel
that you're happy for me,
as I'd be happy for you, my darling.
Remember, however much I love him...
I will always love you.
- I often come at this time.
- I don't come often enough.
No, no. It's only a habit.
Actually, I came to ask for his forgiveness,
if that doesn't sound too silly.
I see.
I think that means you want to marry again.
Well, I don't know if you have
his forgiveness...
.. But you don't need to ask for mine.
I'm delighted.
- Anything else I can get you?
- One more mouthful and we'd explode.
Unless there's another of those
delicious scones.
Of course. Lucy, fetch the scones.
- When does the photographer arrive?
- Five o'clock, M'Lady.
I'm afraid some of the village
have caught on
and they're waiting too.
Are you sure you want to do it?
Oh, ye of little faith.
That's it. I'll leave you to it.
You don't have to go, Tom.
Believe me, I've been part of this courtship
for quite long enough.
It's for you to manage from here.
- Well? - Well what?
Mary, the last time I saw you,
you threw me out for saying I loved you.
Now you've whistled and I'm here,
but I don't know why.
Because you were right. Because we are
in love with each other.
I'm not sure why I fought it
but I've stopped fighting it now.
I know I'm not what you were looking for.
Tom and I once talked about
how marriage should be equal.
It has nothing to do with position or money,
simply that a couple should be equal
in both strength and passion.
Should I ring for more tea?
Are you always so cool and collected?
I do hope so.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Only that, your words have made my
heart pound at such a rate
I'm surprised you can't hear it.
I'm hot, I'm cold and can't breathe.
All because of you.
- I must say, you carry it off well.
- Thanks.
I need to know that you're certain.
I am.
I believe I've met my match. I have.
I'm not 20, trembling at the touch
of your hand,
but I know that if I leave you now
I'll never be as happy as we
could've been together.
I'm not 20 either
but I still tremble at the touch
of your hands.
Me, too. I don't know why
I said that, really.
Oh, darling. Thank God for you.
So what do we do now?
Elope to Gretna Green?
Well, I have a confession.
When I came here last
I brought a licence so we could
marry at once.
Doesn't the Archbishop of Canterbury
need to agree?
Not if you can specify the Church.
Well, you still need a bishop.
- My uncle's a bishop.
- Good old England.
Some things never change.
Quite. But the point is,
it's still valid so shall we
get married now?
- Now?
- Well, on Saturday.
You don't want to have a huge society affair
again, do you?
- God, no. I've done that.
- Then will you?
Well, I suppose I've come this far.
Give it a moment, Mr Molesley.
Better give it a moment.
If you're ready, My Lord. My Lady?
- We must have Mrs Patmore.
- Of course.
- Oh, no, no, no. You don't want me.
- I insist.
A picture to mark our gratitude
for a marvellous tea.
Are we ready?
Three, two, one.
And you promise you haven't cheated?
As God is my witness,
I haven't set eyes on her
since yesterday lunch.
- I even had breakfast in my room.
- That was Carson.
He wouldn't take any chances
with Mary's happiness.
Strange. I'll be best man at both
of her weddings.
I hadn't thought of it.
You've been a good friend in this, Tom.
Thank you.
Pay me back by looking after her.
Who's that?
What? I don't believe it!
Why didn't you say to expect you?
Because I wasn't sure until I
got on the train.
How are you feeling?
Fine. Can you not ask me that
for the rest of the day?
- Could you leave us for a moment?
- Of course.
We'll wait for you downstairs.
You know I'm sorry.
I assumed you would be fairly sorry
unless you're actually insane.
Well, I'm not insane but I am sorry,
I don't know why I did it. Not really.
I've told you.
Because you were unhappy so you wanted
me to be unhappy, too.
Now you're happy again, you'll be nicer...
for a while.
If that's what you feel, then why
are you here?
Because, in the end, you're my sister
and one day, only we will remember Sybil...
.. Or Mama or Papa or Matthew
or Michael or Granny or Carson
or any of the others who have
peopled our youth...
.. Until, at last,
our shared memories will mean more
than our mutual dislike.
What do you think he'd have made of it?
I went to his grave to tell him,
which isn't like me.
Matthew loved you and
wanted you to be happy.
I'm sure he'd be very, very pleased.
In fact, I know he would.
You look nice, by the way.
Thank you.
You'd better go in and find a seat.
I'll wait for her here.
Amelia said you called on her.
Yes. I did. We were talking about Larry.
Really? Was it productive?
That rather depends on him.
But surely she was -
The ball is in Larry's court, Lord Merton,
only he can play it.
Those whom God hath joined together
let no man put asunder.
For as much as Henry and Mary
have consented together in Holy Wedlock
and have witnessed the same before
God and this company...
.. And thereto have given and pledged
their troth either to other,
and have declared the same
by giving and receiving of a ring,
and by joining of hands...
.. I pronounce that they be man
and wife together.
In the Name of the Father,
and of the Son, and of the Holy Ghost.
- Amen. - Amen.
Amen.
Congratulations, Henry!
Thank you.
That was a treat, but we'll pay for it now
if we don't get home to serve the breakfast.
Well, Mr Talbot. You have swept me
off my feet.
- I promise you won't be sorry.
- I'd better not be.
There they go, a new couple in a new world.
It seems all our ships are coming into port.
- And Edith?
- Of all my children,
Edith has given me the most surprises.
Yes, surprises of the most mixed variety.
A surprise is a surprise, Mama,
and I'm sure we haven't seen
the last one yet.