[pigs snorting]
-(bird) Whee! [grunts]
[pigs chuckle]
-(Orange) Hey! Hey, bacon-breath, hey!
You got it all wrong.
It's supposed to be green EGGS and ham.
[laughs, pigs snarl]
What? You want some cheese to go with that swine?
Hey, hey little piggies!
You mind if we play a game?
[pigs chuckle]
Sweet! You hear that, guys?
-(all) Yay!
-All right guys, who's going first?
Hey! You should pick me.
-Hey! Join the Little Apple army. Pick me!
-No, you--no, you'd be very smart to pick the Grapefruit.
-Hey, you should pick me, you know.
-Yay! Pick me!
-Um... yeah, I don't really want to go,
so you go ahead and pick somebody else.
-Oh, pick me, I'm the Grapefruit, come on.
I have the biggest muscles.
-No, don't pick them. Pick me!
[all saying "pick me" at once]
-Yeah, that's a great idea.
Pick him, that's awesome, I like that.
-Hey, guess what.
We have the top three favorite Annoying Orange t-shirt designs
that you voted on. Aren't they great?
Check your email to see if you won a free t-shirt or even better,
the ultimate Annoying Orange prize package,
and then tune into my video on October 21st
for a juicy surprise! [laughs]