The Toccoa men, that's the ones
that was there at the very beginning.
They are very close and...
They accept people coming in,
like myself as a replacement...
...but you also had to prove yourself.
Most of them were-- We know were
qualified parachutists. They had to be.
A lot of them were awfully green,
and we knew that. We just--
We hoped we could keep them alive
or they could keep alive.
A lot of them didn't. But...
It was all right,
they eventually blend right in.
I think maybe they were trying to...
...impress the older guys,
maybe people like me or Shifty or...
I don't know why,
but I got right there to where...
...I didn't wanna be friendly
with replacements coming in...
...because, God, I didn't like
seeing them get killed.
I just-- It just tore me up.
Because we were in awe of them. They
were-- They were wearing infantry badges...
...you know, on their uniform.
They had a star on their jump wings. They--
They were like heroes to us, you know.
That's how we looked at them.
And they were good.
Furthermore, they were good.
We had good officers, for the most part,
but we had excellent NCOs.
They looked-- They looked after you.
All right, now, lieutenant,
nice and easy. We still got a shot.
Oh!
Tough break. You're having a tough night.
People have tough nights.
- Sorry, George.
- It's all right.
- Nice shot, sir.
- Thank you, Bull.
- Thank you, lieutenant.
- Heffron, finish me up.
What does he need? What does he need?
- Double seven.
- There he goes.
Hey, there it is!
You're embarrassing the lieutenant here.
Have a drink.
Don't mind if I do, sarge.
Better start winning money soon. I think
your buddies are starting to miss you.
Yeah, they do look kind of sad,
don't they?
They just serious fighting men, that's all.
Well, I think I'm gonna
go introduce myself.
Be careful what you say, now.
It don't take much to set my guys off.
Yeah, you got some
wild-eyed killers right there, Bull.
You know, it's a good thing
we weren't gambling.
Oh, boy, we would've gotten killed.
- You wanna bet?
- What?
- Yeah, a pack of smokes.
- Come on, we'll have another game.
- I don't know much about gambling.
- Pack of smokes.
- Hey, come on.
- First one to hit the bull's-eye?
- Yeah, okay, one shot. One shot.
- Yeah, why not?
- Yeah?
- Make it two.
- Two packs.
- Two packs each.
- All right, two packs.
Here we go, here we go. One shot.
Here we go, Georgie.
Hey, fellas. What do you hear?
What do you say?
Actually, that's Babe's seat.
Private Heffron's.
Is that right? I don't care
if it's fucking Eisenhower's.
- Who are you?
- Private Miller. James Miller.
- I'm in Sergeant Randleman's squad.
- Us too. I'm Les Hashey.
- Tony--
- Garcia. I know who you are.
Old Gonorrhea don't miss nothing.
Lieutenant, are you gonna
shoot lefty all night?
- Hey, come on.
- I'm just curious because he's right-handed.
George. What would I do
without George Luz?
Oh!
- Goodness gracious!
- Two packs, gentlemen.
I know you got them. Pay up.
- So Heffron tell you about Doris yet?
- No.
Well, then I'm gonna educate you.
We're getting ready to get on the plane for
that first frog town we never jumped into.
All of a sudden,
Heffron stops dead in his tracks.
Bing and bang and boom, everybody
banging into each other and everything.
Heffron's just staring up at the nose
of the plane because on it...
...is painted this beautiful pinup.
And written underneath, "Darling Doris."
Doris just happens to be the name
of the skirt who just that day...
...sent Babe one of them letters.
You know the--? The--
Web, what do you call them letters
that the broads send?
- Dear John letter.
- That's it. A "Dear Babe" letter.
Well, anyway, lucky for Babe,
Patton overruns our drop zone.
Mission canceled. In other words, Babe don't
have to risk getting inside old Doris again.
Hey, Bull,
your squad listens up real good.
Yeah, they're being polite,
like whenever Bull opens his mouth.
Johnny, what are you saying?
Bull's boys are just humoring him?
Yeah, like whenever he gives out some of his
folksy wisdom from back down on the farm.
You probably think he's a fucking hayseed.
Ain't that right?
What are you laughing at?
You new boys, you pay attention
to Sergeant Randleman. Got that?
That's the smartest man in the company.
Hey, Mack.
Where'd you get that?
It's the Presidential Distinguished
Unit Citation. For...
- For what the regiment did in Normandy.
- That's right. For what the regiment did.
- You weren't there.
- Hey, hey.
Ease up, Cobb. it's a unit citation.
Shit, Cobb. You didn't fight
in Normandy, neither.
I got hit in the plane
before I got a chance to jump.
Hey, y'all! Listen up!
I got us an announcement to make.
- This here is Carwood Lipton.
- He's already married, Smokey.
This here is Carwood Lipton,
the new Easy Company first sergeant!
As-- As befitting his position, he says
he has to make an announcement.
Well, I hate to break the mood here,
boys, but we're moving out again.
As you can see...
...this is called
Operation Market Garden.
And in terms of airborne divisions involved,
this one's even bigger than Normandy.
We're dropping deep
into occupied Holland.
The Allied objective is to take this road
here between Eindhoven and Arnhem...
...so the two British armored divisions
can move up it toward Arnhem.
Our job is gonna be
to liberate Eindhoven...
...stay there, wait for the tanks.
The entire European advance
has been put on hold...
...to allocate resources for this operation.
It's Montgomery's personal plan,
we'll be under British command.
Yippee.
The good news is, if this works, these tanks
will be over the Rhine and into Germany.
That could end the war,
get us home by Christmas.
It'll be a daytime jump. Intelligence
doesn't expect much opposition.
They think the Krauts in Holland
are mostly kids and old men.
And we should take them by surprise.
In any case, say goodbye to England.
I don't think they're gonna call this one off.
- What are you doing?
- Look at Cobb, man.
Watch and learn, kids.
You wanna live, jump ready to fight.
Someone help me
with this belly strap, will you?
Move it!
- No! Come on.
- Yes, sir.
They let you out of the hospital
like that, boy?
They didn't let me out. I busted out.
I didn't wanna get reassigned
to some other unit.
Yeah? Can you make the jump?
Oh, sure I can, Lip. I just can't sit.
- Welcome back, Popeye.
- Thanks, Bull.
- Popeye went AWOL just in time to jump.
- What's he doing here?
Who, Sobel? Well, he's the newly
appointed regimental S-4.
- Supply officer?
- Yeah, you got it.
Yeah, he picked me up in Aldbourne,
trying to find you guys.
- He know you went AWOL?
- He knows.
He just said I was lucky.
I could sit out this jump if I wanted.
- I said I didn't want to. So he says, "Hop in."
- "Hop in"?
Yeah, I know. I couldn't believe it either.
Anyway, maybe he's gonna
court-martial me later, huh?
Let's get you some gear.
This here would be a nice bivouac position.
Hey, Mal...
...over there.
Son of a bitch.
Malarkey.
- Sergeant Malarkey.
- Sir.
You thought you'd get away with it?
What do you mean, sir?
Sergeant, that motorcycle
is United States Army property.
That may not mean anything to you,
but it means something to me.
Where'd you find it?
- That's him, all right.
- Who is he, sarge?
- He was our first C.O.
- What happened?
He got promoted.
Just tap my leg, sergeant.
- Lieutenant, you'll be in the doorway.
- Yeah, I know. But, look, sergeant...
...you'll be the man behind me.
When the green light comes on,
you can just tap me, all right?
- The green light will be next to you, sir.
- Just do it. That's an order.
Come here. Come here.
Sling it up and down. When you hit
the ground, your knee will hit the butt...
...but the business end will break your jaw.
All right? Lose your reserve.
You won't need it, we're jumping low.
Take your belly band and
wrap it around you. You're fine.
Come on.
- I'm sorry, sergeant.
- Don't be sorry. Grab your rifle, let's go.
Where'd you get that from, Hoobler?
I think I love Holland.
- Where'd you get these?
- That farmhouse over there.
Just sitting out in the open.
I don't know...
...maybe they were expecting us.
Hello, boys.
I made it.
I wonder if they hit anything.
Goodbye, air support.
There's some kind of holdup ahead.
We're going in through this field here.
Move out! Able Company,
let's go! Let's go! Move it! Move it!
You won't be able to shoot as straight
with that thing on.
Okay, hold your fire.
Hey, kid!
- Bull? Bull! Have you seen Captain Winters?
- No, why?
Keep your squad moving!
- Where are all the Germans?
- They could be anywhere.
Keep moving! Keep moving!
Pardon me.
Come on, lady.
- Dick, the clock's ticking.
- Yeah.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, you're very kind.
- Thank you.
- What's up, Welshy?
Snipers.
We've gotta get to these bridges.
All right.
Hashey.
- Ready?
- Okay, everybody, here we go.
Give me a kiss.
Sergeant Talbert, let's move.
We got work to do.
- What did they do?
- They slept with the Germans.
They are lucky. The men who
collaborated are being shot.
Mr. van Kooijk here
is with the Dutch Resistance.
We've been waiting and hoping
for this day for almost five years.
He says he can help us
secure the bridges here.
Yes. Together we can push the
remaining Germans out of Eindhoven.
And that's just the beginning.
- Any idea where they might be?
- Well, we're still working on that right now.
Peers and his friends here
are gathering information as we speak.
His contacts a couple towns down said they
saw the British 2nd and Guards Armored...
...move through half an hour ago.
- They're kids.
- These are reliable reports.
Anything we can do to help you,
we will do. Anything.
Right on time.
Captain.
I'll be happy to show you
the quickest route to the bridges.
I'd be happy to have your help.
Get scouts to the edge of town
in case we're here for the night.
Hey, van Klinken. Webster.
Sleeping outside is for suckers, guys.
Better be good. I was almost asleep.
- Yeah. Yeah, a little bit.
- What were you doing down there?
It's an air-raid shelter. My family has been
in there ever since the first plane flew over.
We're-- We're Americans. Paratroopers.
- The Germans are gone?
- Think so. You see any, you let us know.
- Are you here to stay?
- As long as we have to.
- Yeah, they don't tell us very much.
- Or feed us much.
Please, wait here.
- You see that? I say screw Paris.
- Hey, don't talk about screwing, all right?
They all speak English, they all love us.
What a fantastic country.
Hey, take a look.
Here. Take.
- Here, take.
- Are these olives?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
He never tasted chocolate.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
- Oh, man, you know, I hate eggs!
- Here, sarge, you can have this one!
- Vincent van Gogh was born in Nuenen.
- Yeah? So what?
They sure teach you a lot
of useful stuff at Harvard.
Mellet!
- Hey, get a load of General Patton!
- What the hell's he doing?
- Makes quite a target, don't he?
- You can't be off the tank.
Lieutenant!
Sniper!
Sarge!
Clear the tracks! Move it!
Get behind the tanks!
- Shit!
- Come on! Come on!
Come on, get in the ditch!
Medic up front! Medic up front!
- What should we do?
- Keep down. Stay still.
- Keep moving! Get up! Keep moving!
- Go!
Keep-- Go! Keep moving!
Let's go! Move out!
Up and move! Move! Keep moving!
They shoot at stationary targets! Move!
To the farmhouse! Deploy right!
- Take the right side.
- Right.
Go!
Go on!
Kraut!
- Shit!
- Move! Goddamn it, move!
Go! Come on! Come on!
- What's he saying?
- He said "away, away."
Which either means that the Germans have
gone or he wants us to go. I don't know.
Go! Go!
Ramirez!
Beat it!
All right, fellas, set them up.
Tiger.
Shit.
Heffron! On me!
Stay low.
- You got a can opener, Babe?
- I'm afraid I don't, sarge.
We got a Kraut tank, 100 yards
on the left part of this haystack!
I don't see him.
Put a couple of shells through that
building, you're gonna see him real good.
I can't. My orders are no unnecessary
destruction of property.
I'm telling you, he's right there.
Well, I believe you.
But if I can't see the bugger...
...I can't bloody well shoot him, can I?
Are you staying or going?
He's gonna see you real soon!
What the hell is he doing?
Forward! Tank!
- Fall back!
- Go!
- Fire!
Fire!
Fall back! Fall back!
Take cover! Take cover!
There's a ditch on the other side.
Follow me through.
Van Klinken!
Bull!
Pull back! Pull back!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on, move! Go!
Fire!
Rifle grenade!
Schmidt, MG42, 10 o'clock. Nail them!
Fire!
- We had to leave him.
- It's okay, he--
- He's still alive!
- Who's hurt?
Van Klinken. Other side of that hedge.
Shit!
Okay, ready.
Fall back! Fall back!
Fall back!
Pull back! Pull back!
Alley! Pull back!
Go! Pull back!
Fall back! Go! Go!
- Webster, take over!
- Yeah, where?
We have to get him to the rear!
- What are we gonna do, lieutenant?
- I'm not sure!
Sir, they're about to unflank us!
We gotta get out of here!
Mortar!
Fall back!
--Cut the road!
We have infantry everywhere!
Repeat, armor has cut the road!
We are covered in infantry!
- Fall back!
- We are pulling back!
- Luz, fall back!
- It's a hold-down!
- Hash, where's Randleman?
- I don't know, sergeant.
Get out of here.
Miller!
Come on. Hashey, let's go!
Stay low! Get down!
Medic!
Go get a medic! Keep moving!
Doc.
- Hey, doc.
- Lieutenant.
It's gone right through.
Side to side, both cheeks.
- Malarkey, get him out of here! Go!
- What?
- Just-- Just leave me here for the Germans.
- What? Are you nuts?
- We'll carry you!
- Are you kidding me?
I weigh more than both of
you two guys combined.
Come on!
- What the hell are you doing?!
- Help us!
Get back to the tank!
Germans coming up on the other side!
Keep moving! Keep low!
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
Come on, up you go.
- One bullet, four holes.
- Yup, it's almost a miracle.
Lip, I don't think we know
where the Bull is.
- Keep it moving, sergeant.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go, let's go! Let's go, go!
Keep moving! Keep moving!
Move them out! Let's go!
Hurry it up! Let's go! Let's go!
- How bad?
- I don't know yet.
Nix!
I'm all right! I'm all right.
Am I all right?
- Yeah. Yeah, you feel all right?
- Yeah. Quit looking at me like that.
Captain, we got four dead, 11 injured.
- Okay, let's move them out.
- Oh, and sir, Randleman's missing too.
- Randleman?
- Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go.
- Where's the Bull?
- Don't know.
I never fired a shot the whole time.
- Find anything out?
- About what?
Anything.
What we're doing next?
Nope.
Oh, I did hear one thing.
Lieutenant Brewer's gonna make it.
- What?
- Lieutenant Brewer's gonna make it.
- No, there's no way.
- He's headed back to England.
They'll probably send him home.
How is that possible?
He did turn his head
at the last second...
...when Sergeant Randleman
called out to him.
- Here.
- No.
Just pu-- Fuck!
Just pull it out.
Come on.
- Okay.
- Here.
Go! Go.
Hoob, any news on the Bull yet?
If there ain't no body, then there ain't
nobody fucking dead. Understand me?
I'm gonna look for him.
Not by yourself, you're not.
I'll go with you. Let me get some ammo.
That's okay...
- ...I'll go.
- Me too.
All right.
Go get him.
All right. I mean, what the hell.
I ain't going back up there.
Webster, us or them?
Not us.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
Go, go.
They're bombing Eindhoven.
Yeah?
Come on, Nix.
We'll dig in for the night.
Won't be waving so many orange flags
at us tomorrow.
Where the fuck you been?
- Glad to see you boys.
- Not as glad as us.
Bet you thought we'd given up
on you there, huh, boss?
- Shut up, Cobb.
- What?
I think we should go back now.
Hey, Johnny, look.
Bull!
- Hey, Johnny.
- There you are. You get a little lost?
- Something like that.
- It's good to see you.
You too.
I don't know whether to
slap you, kiss you or salute you.
- I told these scallywags you was okay.
- What, they didn't listen?
These salty bastards, they wanted to
go on a suicide run to drag your ass back.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, I told them don't bother.
Never did like this company none.
- Anybody have a piece of gum?
- Here.
- So they found you.
- Wait, what did you say?
Johnny, don't irrigate me.
"They found you." Now I don't know
who's more stupid, you or the hick.
All right, mount up! Hop up!
Let's move out!
Grab your gear! Let's go!
2nd Platoon, grab your gear! Let's go!
- 1 st Platoon!
- Second squad, fall in now! Cobb, move it!
Dukeman, round them up!
1 st Platoon, grab your gear, let's go.
Van Kooijk says that the Germans are
concentrating their armor up near Veghel.
We may be heading into
some more tanks.
Well, as long as it's
only old men and kids.
Yeah.
I don't like retreating.
First time for everything.
How are the other divisions
faring up North?
I think we're gonna have to find
another way into Germany.