WINTERS: It was more
than 3 years since Lewis Nixon...
...and I decided to join the paratroops.
And more than a year
since we'd first gone to war.
Not knowing what would happen to us.
How long we'd be fighting.
Where we'd end up.
I certainly didn't expect to find
myself in a place like this.
NIXON:
I thought it might be you.
Morning.
I heard reports about
a redheaded Eskimo.
Thought I'd check it out.
Come to join me for a morning swim?
Yeah. You know me so well.
Here. It's from Zielinski.
Oh, great.
What is that?
Ran into the regimental photographer.
Said he had all these
photographs of the 506th...
...going all the way back to Toccoa.
- I traded them for a couple of Lugers.
- That's a bargain.
- What do you think you'll do after this?
- Get some breakfast.
No. After, after.
Well, it's funny you should mention it
because I had a meeting with Col. Sink.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, discussed the possibility
of staying.
In the Army?
Yeah. Yeah, as a career.
What'd you say?
I said I'd think about it.
- What do you think about New Jersey?
- New Jersey?
There's a company in Nixon, New Jersey.
It's called Nixon Nitration Works.
- Sounds picturesque.
- Yeah, well...
...oddly enough, I know the owners.
Probably gonna expect me
to make something of myself.
I thought maybe I'd drag you with me.
Are you offering me a job?
We'll see how you do in your interview,
but a man of your qualifications...
...I think can probably scrape something up
commensurate with your current salary level.
Yeah, I'll think about it.
I... I really appreciate it.
Yeah, just think about it.
Yeah.
WINTERS: Job offers.
Hard to fathom.
And the war wasn't even over.
I was still getting used
to hot showers and morning swims.
We'd entered Bavaria in early May with
the hopes of capturing Berchtesgaden.
This famous town, high in the Alps,
was the Nazi Party's symbolic home.
And all the heads of the Third Reich
had houses there.
Although Hitler was dead,
he had apparently ordered the SS...
...to make it their last stand
from which to mount...
...a guerilla resistance
against the Allied advance.
The first step was blocking the roads.
When are we expecting the engineers
to arrive?
- Half an hour ago.
- So we're stuck here until they do, Nix.
Well, if you're the SS, you're not gonna
let us waltz into Hitler's house.
Probably throw a few rocks
at us yourself.
If you're looking for someone
to find another way up that mountain...
- ...Easy Company is ready and willing.
- Duly noted.
I already recommended you to Col. Sink.
- Terrific. Let's go find out where Hitler lived.
- Ron. We're not sure what's up there.
The colonel doesn't want us
taking any unnecessary risks.
So the French are gonna beat us
to the Eagle's Nest?
SINK: Gents, I just had
a conversation with Gen. LeClerc.
He told me he was first
into Paris and by God...
...he wanted to be first
into Berchtesgaden.
Told him I understood his point.
Now you fire up 2nd Battalion
and outflank that French son of a bitch.
Yes, sir.
I want Easy Company in the lead. Have
the men assemble down on the Autobahn.
Yes, sir.
Eerie.
Not even any natives.
That's because this is the one town
you can't deny being a true Nazi.
- What do you mean?
- NIXON: Well, you have to be to live here.
We need to find some place
we can put the colonel.
How about right there?
NIXON: No, no.
WELSH: Wow.
Kitty would love this.
How many brides get
a wedding present from Hitler?
You wanna take half?
I can't carry all this.
You know, whoever comes in here after us is
just gonna take whatever isn't nailed down.
- Well. Wouldn't want that to happen.
- Heh-heh-heh.
- Nice.
- Don't even think about it.
- Maj. Winters. Sir.
- More.
Permission to climb the mountain, sir?
Eagle's Nest?
- What is this?
- Wait one minute.
Harry, have F Company
put a double guard on the hotel.
Set up roadblocks
on the west side of town.
I want Battalion HQ, seal off
the north side, and prepare for prisoners.
- Sgt. Grant.
- And Harry...
...nobody gets hurt, not now.
And Easy?
Easy will head up the mountain through
the Obersalzburg...
...and take the Eagle's Nest.
MALARKEY: Hi-yo, Silver!
Yeah! Currahee!
WINTERS: The Eagle's Nest was a
surprise birthday present for Hitler...
...built with Nazi party money.
A mountaintop stone retreat
8000 feet up...
...accessible by
a gold-plated elevator.
It was one of the crown jewels
of his empire...
...and the man was afraid of heights.
Here's to him.
- WELSH: Ha-ha-ha.
- NIXON: No, goddamn it, listen.
Hitler, Hitler... No.
Hitler, Himmler, Goering, Goebbels
and the pope walk into a bar...
- Because he drinks too much...
- WELSH: That's how it starts.
Hey, Adolf! Love your Eagle's Nest.
I hope you don't mind.
We made ourselves at home. Love what
you done with the place. Hey, have a drink.
Come on. Just so we can say
we saw you do it.
Listen up.
From Corps, just came in.
Effective immediately.
"All troops stand fast
on present positions."
- Standing fast.
- What does that mean?
Wanna hear it? Mm-hm?
Ready for it? Listen up.
German army's surrendered.
I got a present for you. Come on.
Is it? Yeah?
- NIXON: What is this place?
- WINTERS: Hermann Goering's house.
We discovered it yesterday.
Had it on double guard ever since.
- O'KEEFE: I can vouch for that, sir.
- Oh, anxious to get off duty, O'Keefe?
No, there's just so much
to see and do, sir.
WINTERS: 10,000 bottles of the world's
finest liquor, wine and champagne...
...helped Easy Company mark the day
the war in Europe came to an end.
It's all yours.
Take what you want and then have
each company take a truckload.
We're heading for Austria
in the morning...
...but don't feel you have to leave
anything here for whoever comes here next.
- Austria, sir?
- Happy V-E Day.
Yeah.
V-E Day?
Victory in Europe.
Happy V-E Day.
WINTERS: Instead of an aggressive combat
unit, we became an occupation force.
And no one wanted to leave Berchtesgaden.
Until they saw Austria.
So you reckon they'll make us
run up those or ski down them?
TROOPER:
Hey, how are you? Need a hand there?
MALARKEY: Hi! Hi! He loves you.
Hey, lady, how are you?
I think the war is over!
We'll be comfortable here.
GERMAN COLONEL: I wonder what will
happen to us, to people like you and me...
...when there are finally
no more wars to occupy us?
WINTER:
Have all your men collect the weapons.
Deposit them at the church,
the school and at the airfield.
Very well.
Please accept this as my
formal surrender, major.
It is better than to lay it
on the desk of a clerk.
You may keep your sidearm, colonel.
NARRATOR: Heroic dead of a
combined Army and Marine force...
...mark the grim battlefield
of Okinawa...
...where one of the bloodiest engagements
of the war is being fought.
Thousands of Yanks have been wounded and
thousands have sacrificed their lives...
NIXON: Hey, Sharpe.
...to drive a fanatical foe
from this vital base.
Along the Jap's southern defense line,
the Yanks progress slowly...
...facing one of the fiercest
artillery barrages of the war.
Each small advance is gained by sheer grit
in the face of withering fire...
...from a suicidal enemy being
slowly hammered back into the hills.
The going is brutal
and our casualties are high...
...but Okinawa is the next
big step towards victory over Japan.
A victory that can only be won by
work, war bonds and heroic sacrifice.
- So when are we going?
- We don't have a date yet.
Are we to tell the men right away?
Some of them will have enough
points to go home instead.
Not many, if their only
medal's a Purple Heart.
I think most of us here
will have enough.
And each of us will have to decide
what to do.
I don't know how long we're waiting
here for orders...
...but I want those veterans who are staying,
and all new replacements, ready to fight.
That means rifle ranges.
That means daily close-order drills.
That means troop reviews.
But above all, it means physical training.
Get your NCOs on it.
They're gonna love you.
LIEBGOTT:
What are you crouching down for, Perco?
- Think the deer's gonna shoot back?
- Leave me alone.
How about y'all just shut up.
Let Shifty kill us some dinner.
What's the matter, Bull? You tired of
eating dried-up spuds three times a day?
Hey, you know what, I got an idea.
Why don't we just shoot Bull here...
...and feed the company for a week?
Oh, goddamn it, Shifty.
You let him get away. Army ought
to be glad to be rid of you.
I wish, you know. Seems they want me
to stay around a while.
- You serious?
- How many points you need?
- Fifteen.
- Fifteen?
Jesus Christ, I thought I had it bad.
No Purple Hearts, never was injured.
- SPEIRS: Company!
- ALL: Platoon!
SPEIRS: Attention!
Right shoulder...
...arms!
Order...
At ease.
Gen. Taylor is aware that many veterans,
including Normandy veterans...
...still do not have the 85 points
required to be discharged.
On this, the anniversary of D-Day,
he has authorized a lottery...
...to send one man home in each
company, effective immediately.
For Easy Company, the winner is...
Come on, come on, come on.
...serial number 13066266.
- Sgt. Darrell C. Powers.
- Shifty.
That's how it's done, Shifty.
Congratulations, Shifty.
Sgt. Grant will see to it that 2nd Platoon
takes over at the crossroads checkpoint...
...beginning tonight at 2200 hours.
- So much for our anniversary.
- No shit.
Gen. Taylor has also announced
that the 101st Airborne Division...
...will definitely be redeployed
to the Pacific.
So beginning tomorrow at 0600 hours,
we will begin training to go to war.
Come in.
I don't mean to interrupt you, sir.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
You know, you was...
You was...
Well, it's been a long time.
- WINTERS: You got everything you need?
- POWERS: Yes, sir. I gathered up my loot.
Pistols, mainly. Paperwork's all done.
I even got my back pay in my pocket.
Back home in Virginia...
Well...
I just don't rightly know
how I'm gonna explain all this.
You see, I...
I seen... I seen...
You're a hell of a fine soldier,
Shifty.
There's nothing more to explain.
Thank you, sir.
WINTERS: Two days later,
Shifty Powers was on a truck...
...headed for the rear and a boat home.
Unfortunately, the truck was hit head-on by
a drunken corporal from another regiment.
Shifty had a broken pelvis,
a broken arm and a bad concussion.
He survived, but had to spend the
next few months in a series of hospitals.
I wish I could say that he was
our only casualty in Austria.
I've made up my mind, Nix.
I got the points, I'm going back to Kitty.
Harry, do you really think that Kitty
hasn't run off with some 4-F by now?
Son of a bitch. That's not even funny.
WINTERS: Harry, ignore him.
How am I supposed to tell her I had
the chance to come home to her finally...
...decided not to
so I could go jump on Tokyo?
All right, so don't tell her.
Besides, she's waited for you
for three years, right?
We'll be back to Tokyo and back
in two years, three tops.
It'll probably be over
before you even get there.
Reality is, you're gonna sit here in
Austria for six months, waiting to go...
...and I'm gonna be back
in Wilkes-Barre making babies.
- You didn't tell him?
- No, I couldn't get him to shut up.
What? Tell me what?
- Guts and Glory here applied for a transfer.
- What?
13th Airborne are heading out
for the Pacific right away.
If I'm going,
I wanna get it over with.
- Are you in on this too?
- I can't let him go by himself.
He doesn't know where it is.
You're leaving the men?
They don't need me anymore.
Wounded in Normandy?
Yes, sir. In the leg.
It was a minor flesh wound.
- Company E lost 24 men killed there.
- Yes, sir.
Seventeen of those were in my company
commander's plane. It went down on D-Day.
So you were given command
of the company on D-Day?
That's right.
Fall back to your original positions!
Everyone else maintain
your pace of fire!
In Holland, they bumped you
to Battalion XO.
Yes, sir.
Bastards took your company away.
I fired my last shots there.
For the whole damn war?
Yes, sir.
You got through Bastogne
without having to fire your weapon?
That is correct, sir.
- And you were on the line the whole time?
- Yes, sir.
Can't imagine a tougher test
for a leader.
Having to sit through a siege
like that, under those conditions.
We got through it.
WINTERS:
Come on! Find some cover!
Find some cover! Find a foxhole!
Come on, take cover!
Take cover!
Come on, find some cover!
- CHAPMAN: So why do you want a transfer?
- Sorry, sir?
I said,
why do you want to leave your men?
It's not that, sir. It's just that
if the war was still on in the Pacific...
...and I could do some good
over there...
Looking to have your own division
some day?
No, sir.
- Not gonna make a career of the Army?
- No.
Ye... Well, I don't know, sir.
Because if you think you need more combat
experience to get stars on your helmet...
...let me tell you something, son:
You've done enough.
Thank you, sir.
That's not my objective.
Major, I took this meeting out of respect
for your achievements.
And for the 101st.
If they do go
to the Pacific eventually...
...you should be running
one of the battalions.
Thank you, sir.
And frankly, I think your men have
earned the right to keep you around.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
WINTERS: So I would stay in Austria for
the time being, waiting for orders...
...and trying to watch over soldiers
who had no enemy to fight.
- WEBSTER: Lieb, I fucking hate this.
- LIEBGOTT: Jesus Christ. They fingered him.
He was in the fucking room, Webb. One of
those Polacks who was at the slave camps...
...said this is where the guy lives.
Right here.
- Which camp?
- Whatever camp.
I'm under direct orders
and I'm happy to follow it.
- WEBSTER: Is this a personal thing, Joe?
- LIEBGOTT: What?
- Is this personal to you?
- No, it's a goddamn order.
- Does Maj. Winters know about this?
- Doesn't matter here.
The fuck it doesn't.
What if this guy's just a soldier?
What if he's an officer with no ties to
the SS? What if he's innocent?
You know what? What if he's a fucking
Nazi commandant of a fucking slave camp?
Which one? Which camp?
You don't have any proof.
Were you at Landsberg?
You know I was.
You think he's a soldier like you and me?
A fucking innocent German officer?
Where the hell you been
for the past three years?
LIEBGOTT: What?
Shut up.
Don't fucking lie to me.
See what you did to my fucking people!
That's it.
He's guilty.
- Liebgott says so.
- He probably is.
Goddamn son of a bitch.
Shoot him.
- Shoot him!
- No.
- Officers don't run.
- The war's over. Anybody would run.
WINTERS: Summer in this Alpine paradise
should've been a welcome relief.
Especially now that we were at peace
with the Germans.
Everyone just wanted to go home.
- France. France was the best.
- Really?
Yeah.
Five years. I think I was in every
country, but France was the best.
Italy would be second for me.
Russia is not desirable.
Ukraine, it was okay.
So when do you get out?
The unit is discharged. We leave
when my captain gets transferred.
- It is the end of my second war.
- Jesus!
- I'm going home now, to Mannheim.
- I'll take this one.
Okay.
Hey, Webster. My relief.
- Don't salute the Germans.
- Come on. I sort of get a kick out of it.
Anyway, I got me a new enemy.
The Japs.
Seventy-five points. How about you?
I mean, you're a Toccoa guy, right?
- How many you got?
- Wouldn't you like to know?
Discharged, huh?
- Go ahead, take off. It's my turn.
- Okay. See you back at the farm.
- WEBSTER: Eighty-one.
- JANOVEC: Huh?
I have 81 points.
Well, that's just not good enough.
See about getting you a ride.
Hey. Hey. Where are they going?
Munich. Munchen, Munich.
Wanna go to Munich?
Get in.
Too bad.
JANOVEC: Turn the wheel!
Oh, Jesus.
MEDIC: It's Pvt. Janovec.
He was dead when they brought him in.
Seventy-five points.
- What?
- He was 10 points short.
WINTERS: The enemy had surrendered,
but somehow men were still dying.
Young men who wanted to be home
with their families by now...
...who'd served with distinction
since before Normandy...
...were stuck here
because they didn't have the points.
What they did have plenty of were weapons,
alcohol and too much time on their hands.
GRANT: All of a sudden, from out of
nowhere, a guy jumps out of the hedgerow...
...shoves a trench knife up against his
throat and screams, "Whose side are you on?"
I don't get it.
GRANT: It's D-Day.
It's 2nd Platoon's own Bill Guarnere.
Old Gonorrhea himself.
Just landed in Normandy...
...and wound up
like I don't know what.
"Whose side are you on?"
What a fucking character.
TROOPER: What happened to him?
Got his leg blown off in Bastogne.
Wait here.
You okay, Mac?
You need some help?
They wouldn't give me any gas.
Krauts.
I tried to explain.
This fucking limey wouldn't listen.
I think he was a major.
- Look, private, we got a problem here.
- Do you have any gas?
Why don't you give me your weapon?
Well, I guess I'll just use his jeep.
I don't think he's gonna need it.
Hold on a second, all right?
Jesus!
Sarge! Sgt. Grant!
Sarge!
- Jesus.
- What?
He's not gonna make it.
- You can't operate on him?
- Not me. You'd need a brain surgeon.
And even if you had one,
I don't think there's any hope.
You find the shooter, I want him alive.
Come on, help me.
- ROE: What are you doing?
- We're gonna go find a brain surgeon.
Hey, Lieb. He wants a noncom
guarding each roadblock...
...and at least two men
watching every road out of town.
Bull, Malark, you each take a squad
and one of these witnesses...
...on a house to house search.
- Can we shoot this bastard on sight?
- Try and take him alive.
RANDLEMAN: Where's Grant now?
They took him to a Kraut hospital to see
if they could drum up any good doctors.
Open up.
Come with me.
- Why?
- Get in the jeep.
- Where are we going?
- To the hospital. Get in.
If you're going to shoot me, shoot me.
If you're not, put the gun away.
Get in the jeep, now.
- What happened to him?
- He was shot in the head.
Half-hour ago.
- Come on.
- If you want him to live, you'll help me.
First, by putting that away.
- Let's go.
- Let me drive.
We'll get there faster.
LUZ:
All right, see what we got here.
Jesus. Again, what a hand.
I don't know who's taking
a bigger beating, me or him?
Wanna play a different game?
Same game, just shuffle
them up good, huh?
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm all right.
Wanna go in there and join in?
I should go in there and stop this.
Floyd, let's just play cards,
all right?
- Where is he?
- TALBERT: How's Grant?
- He okay?
- Where is he?!
This him?
That's him.
Replacement. I Company.
Where's the weapon?
What weapon?
When you talk to an officer,
you say "sir."
Have the MPs take care
of this piece of shit.
- Grant's dead?
- SPEIRS: No.
Kraut surgeon says he's gonna make it.
LIEBGOTT: Hey, tough guy, on your
feet. Come on, move.
TROOPER: Get up!
I'm guessing they were Hitler's photo albums,
sir. Sure had a lot of pictures of him in it.
So you looked at them,
but you didn't take them?
- That's right, sir.
- I don't believe you!
I'll be watching you.
You're dismissed.
You better not be lying to me.
- What?
- Sir...
...if it's not gonna put you
in too much of a bind...
...I'd like to resign as
company first sergeant.
If I had my choice,
I miss being back amongst the men.
I'd be happy to go to staff sergeant,
whichever platoon you wanna put me in.
Well, I guess you've earned your right
to demote yourself.
Thank you, sir.
- You wanna take over Sgt. Grant's platoon?
- That would do fine, sir.
All right then, report to It. Peacock.
Let me know if he gives you
any trouble.
Oh, sir, you make your decision yet?
Yeah, I did.
WINTERS:
So, what else is on your mind?
I know Easy Company is gonna need
a commanding officer postwar.
Somebody to hold their hand,
keep them from killing each other.
It better be somebody who knows
what they're doing.
WINTERS:
Yup. I couldn't agree more.
It's absolutely irresponsible to leave them
in the hands of the wrong person.
They're too much of a valuable
resource to the military.
So you've decided to stay in the Army?
Yes, I'm gonna stay with the men.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
WINTERS:
So some of us would stay by choice.
But others were stuck here, unless we
could find excuses to send them away.
So it's an airborne exhibition.
They have one of every Allied combat
plane they've used in the war.
Uh-huh.
I mean, yes, sir.
You'll be like a technical adviser,
make sure they get everything right.
- I understand, sir.
- Sorry it's not a more hospitable location.
No, sir, Paris is just fine, if you need me
to go. Someone has to be there.
We do. We absolutely do.
Your driver will drop you off
at a hotel of your choice...
...and I don't think we'll see you
back here anytime soon.
I won't let you down, sir.
Carwood, yes...
I wanted to say,
as you probably know...
...the Army, when they give a man
a battlefield commission...
...make him an officer, they usually
don't let him stay with the same company.
Yes, sir. I figured this was coming.
Yeah. They're afraid the men
won't show him...
...the proper degree of respect
as they would another officer.
Yeah. It's a good theory, sir.
It's an idiotic theory.
Especially in your case.
Nevertheless, they've given me
the choice as to where to reassign you.
And I thought Battalion Headquarters
might be a good place.
I can think of few better, sir.
Good. Good.
Right now, down at the airfield
there is a German general...
...who is a little PO'd
about having to surrender...
...to Pvt. Babe Heffron
from South Philly.
- Thinks it's beneath his stature.
- Understandable, sir.
Yeah. I thought 2nd It. Carwood Lipton
from West Virginia...
- ...could soothe his ruffled feathers.
- No problem, sir.
Major, is this the type of job
I can expect from now on?
Yeah. Yeah. When we're not
sunning ourselves by the lake.
Lieutenant.
With your permission,
I would like to address my men briefly.
That'll be fine, general.
- Capt. Sobel.
- Maj. Winters.
Capt. Sobel.
We salute the rank, not the man.
WINTERS: Liebgott?
Men, it's been a long war,
it's been a tough war.
You have fought bravely,
proudly, for your country.
You are a special group...
...who found in one another
a bond...
...that exists only in combat...
...among brothers...
...of shared foxholes.
Held each other in dire moments.
Have seen death
and suffered together.
I am proud to have served
with each and every one of you.
You deserve long and happy lives
in peace.
Towel, towel, towel!
Thanks.
Take a look at these two kids.
What the hell happened to them?
New Jersey, huh?
Yeah.
Think about it.
Yeah, I am.
You awake yet?
Awake?
Time to go to bed.
TROOPER 1: Come on, Jimmy.
- TROOPER 2: Nice play.
- TROOPER 3: We got one down.
TROOPER 2: Come on, Pee Wee.
Let's get Webster.
TROOPER 1: Come on, Pee Wee,
let's get him here, baby.
WINTERS: Buck Compton came back to see the
company to let us know he was all right.
He became a prosecutor in Los Angeles.
He convicted Sirhan Sirhan
in the murder of Robert Kennedy...
...and was later appointed
to the California Court of Appeals.
David Webster became a writer
for The Saturday Evening Post...
...and Wall Street Journal,
and later wrote a book about sharks.
In 1961, he went out on the ocean alone,
and was never seen again.
TROOPER 1: Go, go, go! Yeah!
WINTERS: Johnny Martin would return
to his job at the railroad...
...and then start
his own construction company.
He splits his time between Arizona
and a place in Montana.
George Luz became a handyman
in Providence, RI.
And as a testament to his character...
...1600 people attended
his funeral in 1998.
Doc Roe died in Louisiana in 1998.
He'd been a construction contractor.
Frank Perconte returned to Chicago and
worked a postal route as a mailman.
Joe Liebgott returned to San Francisco
and drove his cab.
Bull Randleman was one
of the best soldiers I ever had.
He went into the earth-moving business
in Arkansas. He's still there.
Alton More returned to Wyoming
with a unique souvenir:
Hitler's personal photo albums.
He was killed in a car accident
in 1958.
Floyd Talbert we all
lost touch with in civilian life...
...until he showed up at a reunion
just before his death in 1981.
How we lived our lives after the war
was as varied as each man.
Carwood Lipton became
a glass making executive...
...in charge of factories
all over the world.
He has a nice life in North Carolina.
Harry Welsh, he married Kitty Grogan.
Became an administrator for the
Wilkes-Barre, PA school system.
Ronald Speirs stayed in the Army,
served in Korea.
In 1958, returned to Germany
as governor of Spandau Prison.
He retired a lieutenant colonel.
- WINTERS: Get them round.
- TROOPER 3: All right, Webster.
Easy Company. School circle!
WINTERS: For Easy Company,
it was D-Day plus 434.
A fast man would've had it, Perco.
Listen up. Got some news.
This morning, President Truman received the
unconditional surrender from the Japanese.
War's over.
Regardless of points, medals
or wounds...
...each man in the 101st Airborne
would be going home.
Each of us would be forever connected
by our shared experience.
And each would have to rejoin
the world as best he could.
Lewis Nixon had some tough times
after the war.
He was divorced a couple of times.
Then in 1956 he married a woman named
Grace and everything came together for him.
He spent the rest of his life with her,
traveling the world.
My friend Lew died in 1995.
I took up his job offer and was a personnel
manager at the Nixon Nitration Works...
...until I was called back into service
in 1950 to train officers and rangers.
I chose not to go to Korea.
I'd had enough of war.
I stayed around Hershey, PA,
finally finding a little farm...
...a little peaceful corner of the world,
where I still live today.
And there's not a day that goes by that
I do not think of the men I served with...
...who never got to enjoy the world
without war.
It's a very unusual feeling.
It's a very unusual happening
and it's a very unusual bonding.
We knew that we could depend
on each other.
And so we were a close-knit group.
Just brave.
So brave, it was unbelievable.
And I don't know anybody
that I admire more...
...than Bill Guarnere and Joe Toye.
They were very special.
I'm just one part of the big war.
That's all. One little part.
And I'm proud to be a part of it.
Sometimes it makes me cry.
The real men, the real heroes...
...are the fellows that are still buried over
there and those that come home to be buried.
Seemed like you thought
that you could do just about anything.
And after the war was over
and you came back out...
...you lost a lot of that. Or at least
I did. I lost all that confidence.
You was hoping to stay alive.
That's all.
Henry V was talking to his men.
He said, "From this day...
...to the ending of the world...
...we in it shall be remembered.
We lucky few, we band of brothers.
For he who today
sheds his blood with me...
...shall be my brother."
Do you remember...
...the letter that Mike Ranney wrote me?
You do?
Do you remember how he ended it?
"I cherish the memories...
...of a question my grandson
asked me the other day...
...when he said, 'Grandpa,
were you a hero in the war?'
Grandpa said, 'No...
...but I served in a company
of heroes.'"