We had lost some very good men there.
Toye and Guarnere had lost
their legs there.
Gordon was badly hit.
A number of other people were killed.
It was a difficult situation there.
I don't know the exact amount
of men that got killed in that.
But six, seven of them were
real close friends of mine.
Skip Muck died, and Eugene Roe
came to me...
...about 10 minutes
after he was killed.
He wanted to see
if I wanted to go look at him.
I said, "No. I wouldn't be able
to stand that." So I didn't go look at him.
After Bastogne, we went to Haguenau.
There was another push there.
We wanted to get some idea
what was across the river there...
...what kind of strength they had.
You have a feeling
you're gonna live through the war.
it's starting to ease off.
You can't account for it...
...it's a gut feeling,
but everybody had that feeling.
I believe I might be able
to live through it.
So walk carefully.
Take care of yourself.
The 101st Airborne
had been made famous...
...by what it did
in the Battle of the Bulge.
Newspapers called them
"The Battered Bastards of Bastogne."
They'd been through hell on earth...
...and were now pulling into
the comparative paradise of Haguenau...
...the sounds of the war still
coming from just across the river.
I had missed Bastogne.
All I knew was what I had read and heard
around the replacement depot.
That we had broken the back of the enemy
and the war would soon be over.
Thanks for the lift.
When I was finally able to rejoin
Easy Company...
...they looked nothing like the heroes
who had just helped win the war.
- George Luz!
- Yeah?
It's me. Come on,
I haven't been gone that long.
Jesus. Yes, you have.
Now, look what I've found.
Hey, guys. Sgt. Martin, Sgt. Ran--
What do you want, private?
Sorry, sir. My name's David Webster,
I just got back from the hospital.
Good for you.
- Where's the rest of the guys?
- This is everybody.
Come on, Sgt. Martin,
this can't be everybody.
What about Hoobler, where's he?
You know, Lt. Foley, 2nd Platoon
lost more guys than we did.
They're really short-handed.
Yeah, right. Report to 2nd, Webster.
They'll find a place for you
Next truck up, Webster,
you'll find 2nd. Move.
Hey, guys.
Some lieutenant told me
to report to 2nd.
- Your name's Jackson, right?
- That's right.
Who's leading the platoon?
- Sgt. Malarkey.
- No officers?
- I guess you didn't hear.
- No, what?
They're making Malarkey a lieutenant.
He's on the fast track now.
- Really? That's great.
- Isn't it?
Jackson, help me up, will you?
- So you come from the hospital?
- Yeah.
Must have liked that hospital, because
we left Holland four months ago.
I wasn't there the whole time. There was
rehabilitation, then the replacement depot.
I'm sure you tried to bust out
and help us in Bastogne.
- I don't know how I would've done that.
- That's funny, because Popeye found a way.
So did Alley, back in Holland.
And Guarnere--
Where is Guarnere?
He still platoon sergeant?
- No.
- Let's go.
- He got hit.
- Yeah?
Yeah, Bill got hit.
Blew his whole leg off.
1 st Platoon, moving out!
Spread out. Hold along this line till
I figure out where we're going.
Sarge? Sarge--
What's the matter, Webster?
Nervous in the service?
No, no, I'm fine, sarge.
Why don't you go talk to Capt. Speirs.
Make sure he wants you with us.
Capt. Speirs?
What happened to Capt. Winters?
He's running
the whole battalion now. Go.
Easy Company had a new C.O.
to go along with all the other new faces.
The guys I knew were either gone
or very different from what I remembered.
I was a veteran of D-Day
and Market Garden, and had been...
...with the company since its formation,
but now, because I had missed Bastogne...
...I was treated as a replacement
and felt like I was starting all over again.
- Look who it is. Nice digs, huh, Lip?
- Yeah.
- Sgt. Lipton?
- Look what I found.
- Feeling all right?
- There you go. He's got pneumonia.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What are you sorry about?
He's alive, he's got a couch,
a goddamn blanket. He's snug as a bug.
Sgt. Malarkey said to check with the CO
if I should be in 2nd Platoon.
Have a seat, Webster.
We'll get you situated.
How long have you been sick?
Long enough.
- He wants us to cross.
- Yeah, I bet that water's cold.
Should be able to get you some boats.
Had to be a full moon.
So much for the cover of darkness.
It's gonna leave the patrol exposed.
- Is this the company CP for Easy?
- Yes, sir.
As you were.
Lt. Jones looking for Capt. Speirs.
He's on his way, sir.
Why don't you sit down?
Can you get me coffee?
Want coffee?
- No, thank you.
- All right.
What platoon are you in?
We're about to find that out.
- You got any soap? I need a shave.
- I'll send some down.
- Know what you'll do for this? Right.
- I'm gonna let Speirs handle it.
Capt. Speirs, sir. This is Lt. Jones.
Listen. For chrissake.
Will you go back in the back and sack out?
There's beds back there with fresh sheets.
I will, sir. Just trying
to make myself useful, sir.
Listen up.
Regiment wants patrol for prisoners.
This one comes straight from Col. Sink,
so it's not my idea.
Since the river is the main line of resistance,
we're gonna have to cross it to get to them.
What do we need to do?
There's a three-story building
on the enemy side, up the embankment.
We know it's occupied.
You can have 15 men.
Think very hard about
who you want to lead the patrol.
You'll need a lead scout, a translator.
I've got the entire battalion on covering fire.
- When?
- Tonight. 0100.
- Yes, sir.
- Speirs?
I want this one to be
as foolproof and as safe as possible.
Don't take any chances on this one.
We're too far along for that.
Speirs? I wanna discuss
who might go.
- Who are you?
- Lt. Jones, sir.
Right, our West Pointer.
- Yes, sir.
- When did you graduate?
June 6, sir.
June 6? Of last year?
D-Day, yes, sir.
All right, don't get hurt.
Sir, I'd like to volunteer
for the patrol.
- Speirs, talk to you in an hour.
- Yeah.
Lt. Jones.
We're short on officers.
You think a non-com could lead this?
I can think of a few possibilities.
Martin? Malarkey? Grant?
Honestly, sir,
most of the NCOs could use a rest.
Captain. Request permission to go
on the patrol.
There's your answer.
No. You don't have any experience.
- Report to 2nd Platoon.
- Yes, sir.
Tell...
Tell Heffron, Ramirez
and McClung they're going.
Yes, sir.
Sir, this is Pvt. Webster.
Sir, I'm Pvt. Webster
from 1 st Platoon.
I just got back from the hospital.
Lt. Foley told me to go to 2nd,
but Sgt. Malarkey--
- Fine, 2nd. Take...
- Lt. Jones.
Lieutenant. OP 2.
Come on.
- Are other officers in the platoon?
- No, sir, just Sgt. Malarkey.
They tell me he's getting a battlefield
commission. Maybe he'll be assisting you.
Who's that? Webster?
That's right. How you doing, Sgt. Kiehn?
- Hi, Webster.
- Hi, sarge.
- Look what we scrounged. We got spuds.
- Is OP 2 this way?
Shit! Move! Go!
Shit, they spotted us!
- Is that it?
- I don't know. I think so.
Go! Go! Go!
Come on!
Get over here, get over here!
All clear! All clear!
Okay, okay.
Ready?
- Wait. It was Heffron, McClung and--
- Ramirez. Come on.
- Hey, guys, this taken?
- Go ahead.
Sergeant, this is Lt. Jones,
just assigned to 2nd Platoon.
Platoon Sgt. Malarkey.
Congratulations on
the battlefield commission.
- The what?
- They're making you an officer, no?
Me? No. You must be thinking
of 1 st Sgt. Lipton.
My mistake. So you're
without a platoon leader?
Not anymore, lieutenant.
Right.
So you wanna introduce me to the men?
Well, some are sleeping downstairs.
The rest are right here.
Sergeant, a patrol's being planned
for tonight, 0100. Across the river.
Regiment wants POWs
for interrogation.
What's the situation?
- Hey, Web.
- What?
Come here.
I wanna talk to you a second.
Why?
- You want some coffee?
- No.
- Fifteen.
- Fifteen what?
Looeys since D-Day.
- Any mortars?
- 60s out back.
- He out of high school?
- West Point.
West Point? isn't that where Ike went?
- Yeah. He graduated with his son.
- Shit. So...
What do you know
about this patrol thing?
- Nothing.
- Oh, come on. You gotta know something.
- I don't.
- Bullshit.
You were there, right? At the CP.
This is a prisoner snatch, right?
Hey, Chuck, listen to this.
Come on, Webster. Spill it.
Capt. Speirs is to pick 15 men.
Lt. Jones wants to be one of them.
Let the kid go.
He could use the experience.
Probably could find
14 replacements to help him out.
I take it this was already an outpost
when you arrived?
There were some doggies from
the 79th infantry, but they left in a hurry.
- What's the report on enemy activity?
- Expect some flares, a few mortars at night.
Scattered 88s, snipers during the day.
Yeah, we dodged some mortars
on our way in.
We also got some sort
of rail road gun back there.
Shells about the size of a deuce and a half.
Sounds like a freight train.
They haven't made any attempts...
- ...to cross the river?
- No.
They have roofs over their heads,
just like us.
I don't think anybody wants
to do anything stupid at this point.
Why are you holding out on me?
I know you know.
Just give us the names, Web.
Who?
There are three men here in this room
that they think should be on the patrol.
Who?
If I tell you,
you can't let on that you know.
Your secret's safe, Web.
Who is it?
- Yeah. Heffron.
- Oh, shit!
McClung.
And you.
He want any other guys
from any other platoon?
No. I don't know. Not that I know of.
Look, that's all I know. I'm sorry.
So it's McClung, Heffron and Ramirez?
- I'll tell them, I just need you to--
- Listen up! Got some bad news.
There is a patrol set for tonight.
And so far Speirs wants McClung--
- We know.
- Yeah, we've just fucking heard.
Webster here told us.
Easy White.
Yep. Uh-huh.
Okay. All right. Out.
The PX rations just came in.
Including winter shoepacs.
- Beautiful.
- Yeah, finally, right?
- Now we're in a nice, warm house.
- Also, we got showers.
All right! Let's move! Clear it out!
Incoming!
Come on, come on,
come on, go! Get down, stay low.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm all right.
Showers. Let's go.
- Somebody's been hit!
- Where?
- What's happened?
- Casualty!
- Who is it?
- Bill Kiehn!
I just left him. I was on my way back.
In war, soldiers sometimes
die in the fever pitch of a firefight...
...or by artillery when they're
huddled in a foxhole.
Bill Kiehn, a Toccoa man,
was killed because...
...he was carrying a sack of potatoes
from one building into another.
In the wrong place at the wrong time.
He was dead before Doc Roe
even heard the call for a medic.
Get him out of here, will you?
- Hey, let's go. Let's get out of here.
- Yeah, okay.
- Did you know him well?
- No, not really.
- McClung.
- Thanks.
Malarkey.
Grant, Jackson, Wynn, Liebgott,
Powers and Webster. All right?
2nd Platoon, on me!
All right, I'm leading this patrol.
C.O. wants Grant, Liebgott,
Wynn, Jackson...
...Shifty from 3rd Platoon
and Webster.
- They want anyone from 1 st?
- No.
Is there anyone
they don't want from 2nd?
That list sounds like everybody to me.
It's always 2nd Platoon.
I swear to God, if we were down to
three guys, they'd still want us for it.
I can't believe they're gonna
make Malarkey lead it.
Christ. He only lost his five best friends.
What the fuck's he got to live for?
Has it been a long time since
your last shower, professor?
- Come on.
- Is it hot water or cold?
- Come on. Hurry up, will you?
- All right.
- I guess I don't really need a shower.
- I don't either.
- Lieutenant?
- Yeah?
- You still wanna get your ODs dirty?
- Of course.
I was just thinking.
Sgt. Malarkey's really in no condition
to be on this patrol.
Maybe if you offered,
you could go in his place.
- Being that you are an officer.
- No, they want someone with experience.
The guys they picked
have plenty of that.
Lt. Jones wanted to experience
combat before the war was over.
Don Malarkey had been
on the frontlines...
...every time Easy Company
had seen action since D-Day.
If it was possible for them
to switch places for the patrol...
...it would be
a small moment of justice.
As welcome as a hot shower
and a fresh uniform.
The decision, though,
was not theirs to make.
Goddamn it, Johnny,
you're breaking my heart, I'm telling you.
Come on, George.
Just give me, I don't know, 10, 15 bars.
Juicy Fruit. Happy?
Just got a report of movement.
1 st Sgt. Lipton...
...wants you to lay a few bazooka rounds
into a house across the river.
You'd think we could get
at least one Hershey bar from the...
Come on, Luz,
you're 1 st Platoon at heart.
- Jesus, Cobb, there's not enough.
- Whoa! Hershey bars!
- Jesus Christ.
- Wait your turn, Liebgott.
- Who they for?
- Not you.
- Oh, come on, George. One bar.
- No, there's not enough to go around!
- Is Capt. Speirs here?
- Down by the river, sir.
Hey, bigmouth,
give the kid a Hershey bar.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Look who it is.
What's up, guys?
I like what you did with the place, George.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I did good.
How you feeling?
As long as you keep
your hands off my ass, I'll be fine.
Have a Hershey.
- Thanks.
- He gets a fucking Hershey bar?
He got shot in the ass.
Did I tell you to stick your big ass
out in the wind?
No, but I expect a little sympathy
from you, right?
- I should rub it for you?
- Get the fuck out of here.
Can you believe this guy? Try to get him out
of the fucking war, he comes straight back.
Yeah, well, that's not what I heard.
I heard the Krauts are finished.
Well, just to make sure, we gotta
row across the fucking river tonight...
...grab a few, and ask them in person.
- Are you kidding me?
- Wish I was. Welcome back, Frank.
Jesus. That reminds me, Web.
I need you to run these to OP 2 for me.
Grenade launchers for the night
patrol. Any day now. There you go.
- Hey, you know what? Send these too.
- You been working out?
Hey, hey, hey. Hear what happened
on D Company's patrol last night?
Replacement lieutenant blew
his foot off. Stepped on a Schu-mine.
Fresh in from West Point.
Had to come back empty-handed.
No shit. Maybe he was
a friend of yours, lieutenant.
Hey, Vest, what you got there?
More Hershey bars and Lucky Strikes
for you rear echelon fucks to hoard?
Hey, hey, hey,
Cobb, with the mouth, please.
The kid's just trying
to do his job, all right? Jesus Chri--
You know what, to hell with it. Count them
up, Vest. I gotta go blast this house.
- You happy now?
- Coming, Perco?
Make yourself useful. Watch this shit
for me. Web, come with me.
Sergeant, is Capt. Speirs gonna be
where you're headed?
- Same vicinity, yeah.
- All right. Then I'll join you.
- Where we going?
- To the house I gotta blast.
- Will Capt. Winters be with him?
- Jesus. Look, I don't know. Maybe.
- Then I'm coming too.
- All right. Come on, guys. Please.
I've been here all fucking day.
Give me a bar.
I'm supposed to watch these.
Come on, you don't smoke
cigarettes, damn it. I got a wounded ass.
Did Intelligence give
you the information on the CP?
Third house on the left.
As soon as our men are back in the boats,
I want a quad 50 opening up.
Captain Winters?
About the patrol. I feel that
I should go on the patrol, sir.
I know I could use the experience.
Denied. Anything else?
You're not gonna lead that patrol,
Lieutenant Jones.
Permission to speak, sir.
Go on, lieutenant.
It looks like Sergeant Malarkey
could use a break, sir.
I've discussed it with him...
...and he said that he did not mind
if I took his place on the patrol.
That was nice of him.
- Captain Winters?
- Yes.
I'd really like to be
on that patrol, sir.
If it's true the Krauts
are finished...
I haven't really done anything except
deliver mail and type morning reports.
- Absolutely.
- Thank you, captain.
- He's got a point about Sergeant Malarkey.
- Yeah, a point.
Fine. You can go.
There will be a briefing. CP, 1700.
Yes, sir.
So who do you have in mind leading
this thing, if not Malarkey?
Come on, he can't be leading.
I'm not sure what they decided.
No way. Not on his first day.
Well, do you see any
other officer here?
- What?
- They call you guys too?
So who's in charge of this bullshit?
No, he ain't.
If he ain't, it's you, Chuck.
Or Shifty or Mo.
Well, that would be better.
- Ten-hut!
- Jesus.
At ease.
- Gentlemen.
- Sir.
As you can see, we've assembled 15 of you
for this prisoner snatch tonight, 0100.
Just a couple of points. We've secured
four rubber boats to get you across the river.
Lieutenant Jones here is the ranking
officer. He'll be along as an observer.
Sgt. Martin here will lead the patrol
in Sgt. Malarkey's place.
The whole battalion will be covering
your withdrawal.
We've identified targets,
planned fire.
We hear these whistles, we open up.
So don't blow them until you're
back in the boats with your prisoners.
And if the house turns out
to be empty, sir?
It won't, but in any case, we know it's
an outpost and want it destroyed...
...so you'll have to lay some demo
on a time delay.
Move fast, but carefully.
Put a perimeter around the house.
Once that's in place, get your rifle grenades
in the first-floor window...
...get your assault team in quick.
Good. Understood.
Remember, it's about prisoners.
Don't pop the first thing that moves.
- Clear?
- Yes, sir.
Good.
Picked your assault team?
McClung, Sisk, Cobb, Garcia
and Webster, as translator.
The rest of you guys,
a base of fire with Sergeant Grant.
- You speak German, right, Webster?
- Yeah. A little bit.
Good. That's my team, sir.
- Questions?
- No, sir.
- Good. Good luck.
- Thank you, sir.
- Ten-hut!
- As you were. Carry on!
A little German?
His German's as good as mine.
- Here you go. You need this.
- Thanks.
Can you believe that guy? Webster.
Tries to get out of everything.
Whatever.
- I want four men on each block.
- I was thinking about...
Four men to go in,
four on the left flank...
- Sir? Sir?
- Yes?
- Liebgott and I, we both speak German.
- Yeah?
You said 15. There are 16 of us,
including two translators.
Well, fine. Hey, Liebgott.
You wanna sit this one out?
Yes, sir.
- You wanna supervise 3 squads?
- Thanks, buddy.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
You men going on patrol...
...nothing rattles, nothing shines,
no helmets.
Lieutenant?
Thank you.
You set for tonight?
- I'm ready.
- Those Krauts are gonna catch some hell.
So I hear.
- I'm not personally going in.
- Martin, right?
Martin and McClung. I'm supposed to
stay in the rear and give them cover.
It's the best place to be.
Fifteen men crossing a river...
...to capture prisoners
from a German observation post.
Getting back safely could be successfully
accomplished in as little as 10 minutes.
The same mission could be met
with disaster, and result in nothing more...
...than 15 Americans killed
or wounded in action.
Those of us who had seen combat before
put that out of our minds.
Those who hadn't probably thought of
little else as we waited for darkness.
- Any problems?
- No problems.
It's secured to the tree.
No sign of any AP mines.
Let's go.
Webster, come on.
Keep it steady, keep it steady.
Oh, shit. I can't swim!
Garcia, grab Sisk.
Okay, keep going. Come on,
stay focused. Come on, come on.
Use the rope.
Use the rope. Come on.
Cutters.
Good.
To the side.
Let's go. Come on.
Clear.
Easy there. Clear.
Powers, go! Go, McClung.
McClung, move up.
In twos, up.
Powers, Wynn, secure the left flank.
Lieutenant, take Grant and Heffron, secure
the right perimeter and the crossroads.
Clear? Security out. Go. Move.
Jackson, hold on!
Let's go!
Jackson! Wait!
Put it down!
Keep your hands up
where I can see them!
Keep those Krauts quiet!
Jackson.
Vest, take care of him.
Ramirez, watch Vest.
Let's go, Webster, let's go!
Come on!
- Check them for weapons.
- Cover me!
Keep those men quiet!
McClung, cover him!
Prime and bury the charges!
Shut up, you two!
And pick him up.
McClung, these two are gonna carry
the wounded Kraut. Webster, tell them!
I said, shut up! Ramirez, pick up
Jackson. We're moving out!
Where are you going? You move!
Everybody moves out on my command!
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Shut up, you! Come on!
We all go together!
Let's go! Move! Move out!
Let's go! Move! Move!
Webster, come on!
Powers, fall back! We're moving out!
Keep those prisoners' heads down.
Keep moving!
Wynn, fall back!
We're moving out! Let's go!
We're falling back!
Covering fire!
Heffron, I want you to fall
back now! Let's go!
Move! Get back to the boat!
I'll cover! Go!
Keep those men moving!
Lieutenant, take the whistle!
Let's go!
- Go! Move it, Webster! Let's go!
- Move! Let's go!
Stay low, keep moving!
Keep moving! Fall back
to the boats now! Fall back!
Jesus Christ, come on.
Blow the goddamn whistle!
Okay, get into the boats!
Right now!
Get in the boats, keep moving!
Come on, move!
I'm gonna shoot you,
you fucking Kraut!
Shoot him, we'll have to come
back for more. The boat, now!
You get up, you Kraut piece of shit!
Into the boats!
Quick, get in the boats! Come on!
Let's go! Everyone in the boats!
Let's get these boats in the water!
Start pulling!
You're okay, Jackson!
Keep pulling!
Keep going! Come on!
Come on,
Perconte, let's go!
- Where's the medic?
- We're almost there.
Get Jackson!
Everybody off the boats!
Let's go!
Get cover!
Wounded! We got wounded,
come on!
Get the Krauts back there,
shake them down!
Move! Move!
McClung! McClung!
Get on to the company CP,
let them know what we got.
Shut up!
I can't do this! I can't do this!
Webster, stay with him.
Hey, Shifty, watch Vest!
- I'm going to get a medic. Got this?
- Yeah.
Come on!
Get his legs.
Listen to me. You have to calm down
or we can't help you. Settle down.
He's gonna die!
Jackson, look at me. Don't listen to him.
Look at me, you'll be fine.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Keep still. Be calm, buddy.
Everything's fine.
Goddamn it!
No! You'll jeopardize the battalion!
The battalion needs them.
Stay against the wall!
Watch what you're doing!
We won't get more prisoners
because you killed one!
- Private! Listen to me, private!
- He's gonna fucking die!
Hey, sit down!
Jackson, stay calm. The medic
is coming. They're on their way.
- Where the fuck is the medic?
- The doctor's on his way.
You'll be okay.
All right.
Doc's here. You're okay.
All right, Jackson, take it easy.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Light. I need some light.
Give me some light.
All right, look at the flame.
Look at the flame. Okay, that's good.
All right, let's get him out of here.
Let's get him out of here.
- Help the doc move him.
- I don't wanna die!
- It's okay.
- Let's get him out of here.
- Hey, take it easy.
- I don't wanna die, please help me.
Hey, it's okay. it's all right.
You're all right.
- Jackson?
- God! Oh, my God!
Jackson, you are not gonna die.
I need you to hang on.
Jackson?
Eugene Jackson was 20 years old.
He'd lied about his age when
he joined the Army at 16.
His family, I'm sure, got a telegram
from the War Department...
...saying he died a hero on an important
mission that would help win the war.
In fact, Eugene lost his life on a stretcher
in a dank basement in Haguenau...
...crying out in agony while
his friends looked on helplessly.
He was just one more casualty in a war
that was supposed to be all but over.
Did they put that
in the report on the ADA?
We're working on it.
How long are you keeping the quad 50?
When they want it back,
I'll hand it over.
Keep moving. Go on.
Get up on the truck. Up, up.
Status?
Private Jackson took a grenade
frag rushing the enemy OP.
- It was his own grenade.
- He died of his wounds, sir.
- Any others?
- No, sir.
Well executed. It's not your fault.
Talk to your men.
- Carry on.
- Thanks, sir.
We heard you got two prisoners.
Good work.
Jackson's dead.
Yeah, we heard.
Yeah, well, they want
another patrol tonight.
What are you doing, Cobb?
You leave someone on the bank?
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
It's the third prisoner that was
too far gone to bring back.
Maybe we should put him
out of his misery.
- Fuck his misery.
- I can't listen to it anymore.
- Sir, you want a cigarette?
- Yeah.
- Who's got a light?
- Here. Hang on, sir.
Twenty-two.
What are you looking at, Webster?
Yeah. That's what I thought,
college boy.
Are you drunk, trooper?
- Leave me alone.
- Answer the question.
Yes, sir. I am drunk, sir.
Drunk, sick and tired
of fucking patrols, taking orders--
Hey, Cobb. Shut up.
It's boring, okay?
Taking his side, Johnny?
Yeah, I am.
So he knows we lost a man?
Yeah, he knows. He also knows you picked
up two prisoners who talked.
- About what?
- OB, supply trouble, Hitler's favorite color.
I don't know.
None of it gets us across the river.
What's the point?
Honestly?
Sink's been on the phone all day, bragging
it up. I think he's just showing off now.
I don't know what to tell you.
You gave him a successful patrol,
now he wants two.
Successful.
Sir, the men are mustered. If you
want me to brief them, I'm gonna.
It's the same roster as last night.
Well, mostly.
- Evening, gents.
- Evening, colonel.
At ease.
You all did a damn fine job
on a tough mission last night.
I wish you good luck tonight, because
I'll be expecting more of the same.
- Have you briefed the men?
- Just on our way.
Make damn sure you remind them
how proud I am of what they did.
Yes, sir.
So I'll brief them now, sir?
No. No, I'll do it.
Sarge, they're on their way in.
Ten-hut!
- Martin.
- Sir.
- At ease. This everybody, Grant?
You men did an excellent job
last night.
I'm proud.
I'm proud. I just saw Colonel Sink.
He's proud too.
In fact, he's so proud he wants you to do
another patrol across the river tonight.
Any moment now, the outpost we hit
last night will go up in flames.
- Martin?
- Yes, sir.
Means we'd have to venture farther
into town this time.
Captain Speirs, you have the map, please.
Yeah. Sergeant Grant?
We have enemy movement here and here.
Which means this is our
new house target here.
We recovered all the boats.
So we'll be setting off from the same place
we did last night.
We're not changing the plan any, sir?
No. The plan is the same.
It will be 0200 hours instead of 0100.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, sir.
Okay. Good. Because I want you all
to get a full night's sleep tonight.
Which means in the morning, you will report
to me that you made it across the river...
...into German lines...
...but were unable
to secure any live prisoners.
- Understand?
- Yes, sir.
Good.
Look sharp for tomorrow.
We're moving off the line.
Did I fucking hear that right?
Moving off the line!
It's a whole new way to fight a war.
Don't bother writing this up.
I'll take care of it. I might actually enjoy it.
I think you might be onto something--
Lieutenant Jones.
- Sir.
- Join us at the company CP.
- First Sergeant Lipton?
- Sir.
Your honorable discharge
as an enlisted man...
Just keep them coming, Luz.
...and your battlefield commission
as a second lieutenant.
- What do we have here, boys?
- Hey, pal.
- Congratulations, Carwood.
- Thank you, sir.
- Lip, congratulations.
- Thanks.
Thank you. Welcome back, sir.
- Hey, that's Harry to you. Congratulations.
- Harry, I didn't expect you this soon.
I figured you'd be nursing that scratch
for another month or two.
Did you miss me, Lewis?
Lt. Jones. Regiment has seen fit
to promote you to first lieutenant.
They want you on staff up there.
Don't go far with that.
- Congratulations and good luck.
- Thank you, sir.
Dismissed.
I guess you lost
another platoon leader, huh, Web?
So a second patrol never happened.
Word was Captain Nixon wrote up
a bogus report, and Regiment never got wise.
As we pulled out of Haguenau,
many of us in Easy Company...
...felt that a corner had been turned
and we all might make it home alive.
We'll know more
as soon as we get closer to the line.
Oh, before I forget. Col. Sink's a bit unhappy
with the appearance of your uniform.
He says it's not befitting
to your rank.
Oak leaves.
Congratulations, major.
Gentlemen, we're ready.
I'll drive.
- Sergeant Malarkey.
- Good luck, sir.
- Sergeant Martin.
- Yeah, lieutenant?
- Good work.
- Thanks, sir. Good to have you along.
Here.
I wondered if people back home...
...would ever know what it cost
the soldiers to win this war.
In America, things were
already beginning to look like peacetime.
The standard of living was on the rise,
racetracks and nightclubs were booming.
You couldn't get a hotel room
in Miami Beach, it was so crowded.
How could anyone ever know
of the price paid by soldiers...
...in terror, agony and bloodshed...
...if they'd never been to places like
Normandy, Bastogne or Haguenau?
Subtitles by
SDl Media Group