I never thought I'd get through D-Day,
let alone the next phase or the next phase.
I thought I was gonna
get killed instantly.
I thought one of two things:
a quick death...
...or I'd come through
probably without a scratch.
I think everybody had fear. I think
there's people that can handle fear.
I think I was probably one of them.
I think I was just as scared
as anybody else, except I could think.
It's a feeling you would
not let yourself down...
...and you would not let your comrades
or your unit down.
We all had fear,
but we all had training to know...
...that you try to handle your fear...
...and work to accomplish
what you're supposed to be doing.
Hey, it looks like what's-his-name.
You know, from 1 st Platoon?
- Our 1 st Platoon?
- It sure does.
Blithe.
Hey, Blithe.
Blithe!
Keep moving! Get down!
Thought that was you.
You alone?
You're the first familiar faces I've seen.
I ain't surprised. They dropped us
all over the Contentin Peninsula.
We've been fighting with the 502nd
since we hit the ground.
You?
Oh, I've been...
- ...trying to find Easy.
- Join the club.
Spread out!
Hey, fellas.
- Well, look who decided to show up, Floyd.
- Hey, Luz.
- Thought we'd never find you guys.
- You okay?
- Get a load of this. You like that?
- Yeah, it's the real stuff, eh?
- Yeah, of course.
- You like this?
- Oh, nice. That's a beauty, sarge.
It's a hell of a poncho.
My Luger's gonna put you all
to shame when I get it.
How was your jump?
- Missed the DZ.
- Yeah, that goes without saying.
- I guess so.
- Got any souvenirs to trade?
They're all ticking, unlike their
previous owners. Got anything good?
Not yet.
So have we lost anybody?
Tommy Burgess took one in the face.
Popeye Wynn got pinked in the behind.
- They're gonna be okay.
- That's good.
- You run into Lt. Meehan on your travels?
- No. Why?
Company HQ's still missing.
They think the plane went down.
- They say he's gonna turn up.
- Yeah, I ain't holding my breath.
- Who's in command now?
- Winters for now.
Lt. Welsh is 1 st Platoon.
- Easy Company on the road!
- Let's go! 1 st Platoon!
- Platoon! Move out!
- 1 st Platoon, on your feet!
Let's go, 1 st Platoon!
- Easy's moving out. On your feet.
- Let's go!
- Stand up, let's go! Here we go!
- Today, people!
Listen up! It'll be dark soon. I want
light and noise discipline from here on.
No talking, no smoking and no playing
grab-fanny with the man in front of you, Luz.
- So where we headed to, lieutenant, huh?
- We're taking Carentan.
That sounds like fun.
It's the only place where armor from Omaha
and Utah Beach can link up and head inland.
Until we take Carentan,
they're stuck on the sand.
General Taylor's sending
the whole division.
"Remember, boys...
...give me three days and three nights
of hard fighting...
...and you will be relieved."
Lieutenant. Lieutenant, I'll take point.
Cpl. Hoobler will be lead scout.
- Blithe, glad you could join us.
- Thank you, sir.
1 st Platoon, fall in behind
Fox Company.
You people from 2nd and 3rd Platoons,
follow us. Shake a leg.
"Another thing to remember, boys:
flies spread disease.
So keep yours closed."
Don't wake Jerry.
- Damn it.
- What?
- We lost F Company, sir.
- Again?
- We lost F Company.
- Again? Hey, Blithe, Skinny, guess what.
Perconte, go back
and pass the word to hold up.
Yes, sir.
- Hoobler, take Blithe. Go find F Company.
- Yes, sir. Come on, Blithe.
Shit.
Did you send somebody?
Yeah, I got Hoobler and Blithe
out there now.
Why are we stopped?
This is about officers crapping out
on their training, Nix.
Come on. Let's get this show
on the road.
Damn mosquitoes.
What is it?
Shh.
- Flash.
- Thunder.
- I can hear y'all all the way across the field.
- You F Company?
That's right.
Where y'all been?
Blithe, go back to the lieutenant,
tell him we found F Company.
- I'll figure out where these yokels are at.
- Hey, who y'all calling a yokel?
He's dead, private.
- Did you find Fox Company?
- Yes, sir.
Thought he-- I thought he had me.
Paratrooper?
Division thinks there's a regiment
of them holding Carentan.
- Well, there's one less to worry about.
- Yeah.
That's edelweiss.
That only grows in the Alps
above the tree line.
Which means he climbed
up there to get it.
It's supposed to be the mark
of a true soldier.
I want you to take the 1 st
straight up the middle, hard and fast.
We have to move quickly.
I'll be right behind you
with 2nd and 3rd.
- Go!
- Let's go, 1 st, let's go.
Go, go! Go!
Fire!
- In the ditch! Down! Down!
- Get down! Incoming!
- Goddamn it.
- Where the fuck is everybody?
- Where'd everybody go?
- I have no idea!
Let's go, Easy!
Get those MGs moving, will you?
- Let's get them out of there!
- They're in the open, for Pete's sake!
Go! Go!
Get them going, Buck!
Follow me, Easy!
Move out! Move out, men!
Go!
Move out! Move out!
Get yourselves out of that ditch!
We have men getting killed
out there, Blithe!
Move! You got no cover there! Go!
Go!
Spotter! Upstairs window! Left!
Follow me!
Get yourselves out of those trenches!
In the ditch!
Down, down, down, down!
- Incoming!
- That's an MG42!
- Medic up!
- No! Stay down! He's shot!
Get out of the dirt! Nazi!
There's one in the right upper--
Medic! Pull him back!
Ah, shit!
Sniper! Thattaway! Second floor left!
I need some covering fire. Ready, Luz?
Okay, I'm out.
Guarnere! Clear that sector
on the right!
Hey, up with me!
- Shit!
- Move, Luz! Here! High!
You okay, Shifty?
We gotta take that warehouse!
Shifty!
Hammer those windows.
Let's go! Move! Go! Go!
Tipper, take Liebgott,
start clearing these buildings.
- Right. Come on, Joe, let's go.
- Two to a house.
Second two. Go! Go!
Houses on the right!
Check them and clear them!
Turn left! Bring it up!
Smash it.
Grenade! Luz, come on, Luz.
- Come on!
- Close behind.
Shit!
They got us zeroed! Spread it out!
Spread it out!
- They got us zeroed!
- Go now!
- Get out of the street!
- Get the hell out of there!
They got us zeroed!
Get out of there! Go! Go!
Get the hell out of the street! Move!
Let's go! Go! Go!
- Take cover!
- I need a hand over here!
Medic!
- Move over!
- Through the window!
Come on. Let's get you out of here.
Come on, boy!
Come on.
Move! Move! Move!
Get out of the street! Go! Go!
Lip!
Hey there, buddy.
You're okay, Lip.
Everything's right where it should be.
Come on. Upsy-daisy.
Let's check up front.
Get Tipper up here with the bazooka.
- Check across the front.
- Move on one!
Hello? Anybody there?
Tipper! Tip!
Tipper! Answer me! Tip!
- Joe? That you?
- Looking good, Tip.
Looking real good. Come here, buddy.
You gotta sit down. Come here. Come on.
Easy, easy. There you go.
There you go.
Ah, Jesus.
You hang in there, buddy. Okay,
we're gonna get you fixed up, all right?
Okay. Guys, you wanna give me
a hand here? Come on.
Take the left flank!
Got a bad one.
- Can we move him?
- No.
Padre!
- In the name of the Father, the Son--
- Hey, Malark. You see what I'm seeing?
--Is now and forever shall be,
world without end. Amen.
- Crazy fools, the Irish.
- You should know.
Smokey, the window. Let's go!
- Ho. Morning, sir.
- What's your name, trooper?
Sergeant Farnsworth
from Able Company, 501 st.
I'm here and I'm supposed to tell you...
...that we got it clear from here
all the way to the north of them Krauts, sir.
Well, tell your CO 506 arrived in force
and secured all positions south of you.
Yes, sir, I'll tell him.
Come on, fat boy, let's go!
Lieutenant Winters.
- Yes, sir?
- Is it safe to cross now?
- What's that, sir?
- Is it safe to cross?
- We wanna move the wounded.
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
Come on. Let's get them out of here.
There she is.
Plasma drip.
You're lucky it was a ricochet.
- You just caught a piece of it.
- Stupid.
- What?
- Nothing.
Walking wounded to the rear.
- You gonna be able to stay off it?
- Doesn't look that way.
Well, you gotta try, huh?
What've we got planned, chief?
Well, we expect a counterattack.
Carentan's as important to them
as it is to us.
- Any idea when?
- We're not waiting around to find out.
Battalion wants us to head east toward
high ground, set up a defensive position.
With all the flooded fields, it's the only
direction they can approach from.
Yeah.
- You gonna be all right?
- Ye-- Yeah.
Good.
What's wrong with Blithe?
Well, nothing. Except he can't see.
- He can't see?
- So he says.
Blithe?
It's Lieutenant Winters.
What happened?
I don't know, sir.
Well, things...
They just kind of went black on me.
- What, you can't see?
- Not a thing, sir.
I can't see a thing.
Well, you just take it easy, Blithe.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Get you back to England.
It's gonna be okay.
Sir...
- ...I didn't wanna let anyone down.
- No.
Just take it easy.
It's okay, son.
Sir?
- Yeah? What is it?
- Thank you, sir.
I'm okay.
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm okay. I think I'm okay.
You can see?
God, I don't know what happened.
I think-- I think I'm okay.
All right.
Well, stay here a little while longer
and make sure.
And then you can report
back to your platoon.
Yes, sir.
Now can we get that bandage on?
Yeah.
- Berlin by Christmas, that's how I see it.
- Yeah, you're full of it.
Oh, God. This Kraut cheese
tastes like--
- It stinks.
- Bread's stale too.
- Give me that.
- Yes, sir.
The way we came into town today
and took over?
You know, it don't seem like
Jerry's got too much fight left in him.
Hey, More, don't get hit in the face when
Jerry throws in the sponge, all right?
You mark my words, Mal:
Berlin by Christmas.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
We'll be moving out soon.
Out of town, lieutenant? Already?
That's right.
Don't they know we're just getting
settled here?
Nice, Groucho.
- What?
- Real smart.
You know, you're taking your life
in your own hands. Ain't that right?
I told you. I didn't actually see it.
What, Speirs shooting the prisoners,
or the sergeant in his own platoon?
- Sergeant?
- What? I didn't hear that one.
- Wait, wait. He shot one of his own guys?
- Well, supposedly, the guy was drunk...
...and refused to go on a patrol.
Who knows if it's true?
- Well, I know a guy...
- Hey.
...who said an eyewitness told him
that Speirs hosed those prisoners.
Why? What for?
On D-Day.
Speirs comes across this group of Kraut
prisoners digging a hole or some such...
...under guard and all.
He breaks out a pack of smokes,
passes them out.
He even gives them a light.
Then, all of a sudden,
he swings up his Thompson and:
He hoses them.
I mean, goddamn!
He gives them smokes first?!
You see, that's why
I don't believe he really did it.
- Oh, you don't believe it?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, I heard he didn't do it.
No, no, no, it was him, all right.
But it was more than eight guys.
More like 20.
Hell of a shot.
All except one guy, who he left alone.
Well, all I know, from what I heard...
...he took that last 105 on D-Day
practically by himself.
- Running through MG fire like a maniac.
- Yeah, that I did see.
- On his own?
- Yep.
I don't care if any
of the other stuff's true.
Hey, Albert.
Grab your smokes,
grab your ammo and gear.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Gonna have to take everybody's word for it.
I didn't see any of it.
Let's go! 1 st Platoon! Weapons on me.
We're moving out.
On your feet! Tactical columns!
Flankers out!
Flanks up!
- That means you, Private Blithe.
- Come on, bud. Get up.
You want the bread?
Hey, Luz. How far are we going?
Oh, Jesus Christ, Frank. I don't know.
Until they tell us to stop.
High ground.
There's high ground up ahead.
Yeah. Okay, genius.
Answer me this, then:
Why is Easy Company the only company
who's either at the front of an advance...
...or, like now, exposed
at the far edge of the line?
- To keep you on your toes.
- No, that's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying that
we're never in the middle...
...and we're the fifth of nine
companies of this regiment.
- Able through Item. Think of it.
- See there? You see that--
Incoming!
Contact right! Get in the hedgerow!
See what I mean?!
Bring it around!
Right there! Sergeant More! Stay low!
Luz, get down here with the radio!
Sergeant More! On me!
Go, go, go!
What have they got to sing about?
Flash!
Thunder.
Catchy tune, ain't it?
- Hey, lieutenant. What's the news?
- Same as it was this afternoon.
- They're in their hedgerow, we're in ours.
- Spell me a minute, sir?
You gonna let Blithe get some sack time?
- My back teeth are floating.
- Get back here ASAP, Martin.
You can count on me, sir.
How you doing, Blithe?
I'm okay, sir.
What happened
at the aid station today?
Doc Roe, he called it
hysterical blindness.
No, thank you, sir.
You know what they said in basic:
Dehydration's a soldier's worst enemy.
Here.
Yeah.
It's a game, Blithe. That's all. We're--
Hell, we're just moving the ball
forward one yard at a time.
Nothing but a game.
What is, sir?
This. The whole thing.
No. Thank you, sir.
Just a game.
Harry.
S2 said the Germans only left
a company to defend Carentan.
The rest pulled out sometime last night.
- I knew that town was too easy.
- Yeah.
They regrouped south of town.
May have been on the way to a
counterattack when we ran into them here.
Strength unknown.
They want the town back.
And we're in their way.
If they don't come before then,
we're attacking at first light, 0530.
I'll tell the men to fix bayonets.
Not much of a limp.
- I'll survive.
- How is it?
Hurts.
War is hell.
Smith, wake up.
Come on, Smith. Get up.
It's your watch.
Smith. It's your watch.
Easy, Smith. It's me, Talbert!
Smith! What the hell are you doing?!
That's Talbert!
- I didn't--
- Goddamn!
- Gosh!
- Medic!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
He looked like a Kraut.
- Can you breathe?
- Yeah, I can breathe.
- Look at me. Look at me.
- Yeah, I can breathe!
Okay, I'm just gonna put some sulfur on
the wound, Floyd. You're gonna be fine.
What the hell is that?
Sounds like it's coming
from 3rd Platoon.
Don't you wanna get some sleep?
I don't think-- I don't think I can.
Then go take a look.
Yes, sarge.
- Flash.
- Thunder. Thunder!
Lieutenant Speirs, sir.
Where you going, private?
Check out the noise, sir.
I just came from there.
Everything's under control.
Yes, sir.
Got some nervous privates
in your company.
We do, sir.
Yeah, we do. I can vouch for that.
They just don't see how simple it is.
How simple what is, sir?
Just do what you have to do.
Like you did on D-Day, sir?
Lieutenant...
Sir, when I landed on D-Day,
I found myself in a ditch all by myself.
I fell asleep.
I think it was the airsickness pills
they gave us.
When I woke up,
I didn't really try to find my unit...
...to fight.
I just--
I just kind of stayed put.
What's your name, trooper?
Blithe, sir. Albert Blithe.
You know why you hid
in that ditch, Blithe?
I was scared.
We were all scared.
You hid in that ditch because you think
there's still hope. But, Blithe...
...the only hope you have is to accept
the fact that you're already dead.
And the sooner you accept that...
...the sooner you'll be able to function
as a soldier's supposed to function.
Without mercy. Without compassion.
Without remorse.
All war depends upon it.
Got any smokes?
You want some of this candy shit? No?
- The outpost got ammo.
- Hey, Boyle.
- Here you go, guys.
- We don't know what they've got.
We may be attacking a weaker force,
possibly more paratroopers.
- And you know how they can be.
- Fire and maneuver.
That's the name of the game:
Fire and maneuver.
Dog and Fox companies will be on our
left flank, moving with us. Any questions?
- Let's make them holler.
- It's 9:30 in the evening back home.
- Must be--
- Mortar!
- Incoming! Everybody in the hole!
- Take cover!
Down, down, down, down!
Get that OP in!
Tell them to hold.
I'm checking the lines.
All Easy stations.
Easy 6, hold in position. Over.
Go! Lock and load!
- Easy 6! Easy Red 6!
- Medic!
I've got mortars all across my line.
No sign of infantry yet.
I'm pulling the OP in. Over.
Right stake plus 15. Charge three!
Range, 600.
Load! Fire!
Up and load! Fire!
- Come on!
- Come on! Move it! Move it! Hurry!
Watch for silhouettes on the horizon!
Find your target. Muzzle fire!
- Nail it! Keep low!
- Watch the horizon!
Keep low! Go! Go! Go!
Perconte! Perconte!
Get your men in order! Stay low.
Pour it on them, Perconte! To your left!
Keep going! Keep going!
Keep it up!
I want fire superiority!
Guarnere, keep them pinned down!
Keep firing!
Sergeants, reverse!
Cover the crest of that hill!
No!
Where the hell did they come from?
Okay, pull back!
Holy shit! There goes our left flank!
- Sir, Dog and Fox are pulling back.
- What?
Who gave that order, goddamn it?
Keep firing! Stay low!
Stay low. Keep firing, Perconte!
Come on, Blithe. Stand up!
Get up on your feet, soldier.
Get up, Blithe.
That's right, Blithe. You can do it.
Fire your weapon, Blithe.
Hit those goddamn Germans, Blithe!
Rip it at them, Blithe!
Keep firing! Let them have it!
Keep firing! Don't slack it off!
Let them have it, Blithe!
Pour it on them, Blithe!
The left flank! Watch your left flank!
Fire!
Krauts over there!
Keep the line of fire up here! Move it!
Blaze spray!
Let's go, McGrath! On me!
Shift your fire right!
Down! Down!
Get together!
Come on! You're gonna get me killed,
lieutenant.
I knew you'd get me killed!
- Wait until I tell you, McGrath!
- I can't!
- Hold your fire!
- No, that's too close.
- Bitch! Son of a bitch!
- Too close!
Medic!
Come on!
Now fire, McGrath! Fire!
- Yeah!
- Covering fire!
- Keep firing south!
- Fire!
You hit a home run, huh?
- Smith, I've been hit!
- I got you!
Get me out of here!
Medic!
Randleman!
- You okay? Move it! Move it!
- Yeah.
- Rounds complete!
- Skip! More ammo! Go! Go!
- I'm on my way!
Medic!
Jesus, what was that?
Shermans!
Well, hello, 2nd Armored.
That's right, you sorry asses! Run!
The cavalry! Come on in! The tanks!
Oh, you beautiful babies, you!
Let's go! Pour it on them!
Let them have it! Come on!
- Check it out! Shermans!
- About damn time.
Come on!
Come on.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, buddy, you okay?
Looks like you fellas
had a heck of a fight.
Move forward on the right flank.
We need to know what's in there.
- I don't know who the hell to send.
- Ask for volunteers.
I hate asking for volunteers.
Then pick them.
Need to take a look at that farmhouse.
Who wants to go?
I'll go.
Anybody else?
Martin, Dukeman, you just volunteered.
Hubba-hubba.
I'll be lead.
Blithe's lead scout. Move out.
Harry, what exactly are you doing
with your reserve chute?
You been hauling that thing around
ever since we jumped?
Gonna send it to Kitty
when we get back to England.
Silk. I figure it'll make a good wedding dress,
you know, what with rationing and all.
- Jeez, Harry, I never would have guessed.
- What? That I'm so sentimental?
No, that you think we're gonna
make it back to England.
Okay.
Here we go again. Covering fire!
Covering fire!
Go! Go!
Come on! Hang in there, Blithe.
Come on!
Keep moving! Down!
- Medic up!
- Top window right!
Hang in there.
Medic! We need a medic down here!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Take it easy, Blithe. Take it easy.
Come on, Dukeman. Come on.
Move, move. Coming through.
Give me room.
Get out of my way. I got it.
- What happened?
- Sniper.
All right, Blithe, I got you.
Nice and easy. Nice and easy.
They're pulling us off the front line.
Now?
To a field camp north of Utah Beach.
Hot food and showers.
Then back to England.
- Where's medical supply?
- Third tent on the right.
Harry.
- How's the leg?
- Stiff. Sore.
They want me to take it easy
for a few days.
Yeah, you should.
Talked to Colonel Sink.
Said he appreciated Easy
holding the line.
- Said General Taylor was pleased.
- Yeah.
That's why I came to France,
to please General Taylor.
Yeah.
In grateful acknowledgment of the blood
shed in the service of your country...
...it is my honor to present you
with the Order of the Purple Heart.
Thank you, sir.
How many does that make?
Two? Three?
- You have no shame.
- Hey, I got one hole in my shoulder...
...a second in my calf. Then there's the boil
on my shin that had to be lanced.
And he only gets one.
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
This is great!
Woo-hoo!
- She fancied me, Alton.
- In your dreams, buddy.
- Whoa! Jesus!
- Jesus!
It's good to be alive!
- Jesus Christ, that sure was close.
- No. Missed him by a mile.
Hey, Bull. Hey, Bull, come over here.
Hey, come on. Bull, come over here.
- I got a seat for you.
- Hey, Hoobler.
- Be quiet for the man.
- "The Night of the Bayonet."
The night was filled with dark and cold
When Sgt. Talbert, the story's told
I don't like this.
Pulled on his poncho and headed out
To check the lines
Dressed like a Kraut
Why is everyone in such a hurry
to get back, huh?
- Hospital food don't suit you?
- Get off.
We don't need you anymore, Tab.
Upon a trooper our hero came
Fast asleep, he called his name
"Smith, oh, Smith! Get up! It's time
To take your turn out on the line"
Do you guys have any idea
what he's talking about?
The night of the bayonet.
- Whatever that is.
- But Smith, so very weary
Cracked an eye, all red and bleary
Grabbed his rifle, he did not tarry
Hearing Floyd, but seeing Jerry
- Oh, my God.
- Way to go, Smithy!
"It's me," cried Tab, "Don't do it!"
And yet Smith charged
Tout de suite, with bayonet
- He lunged, he thrust, both high and low
- Oh, come on!
And skewered the boy from Kokomo
I'm heading back to barracks.
- You Heffron?
- Yeah.
- Where you from?
- Who's asking?
- You from Philadelphia?
- South Philly, yeah.
I could tell.
- Seventeenth Street.
- Yeah? Front Street. Hey.
Come here. Sit down.
Hey, you know a guy
named Johnny Waylon?
- Yeah, I know Johnny.
- Used to call him Tar Head.
Yeah, Tar Head. Yeah.
Since you weren't wounded by the enemy
and thus didn't qualify for a Purple Heart...
...we've taken matters
into our own hands.
Tab, this is for you.
- A souvenir.
- That's right.
- Congratulations!
- I could've shot the kid a dozen times.
Yeah, right.
I just didn't think we could
spare a man.
Couple of announcements, men.
First-- Listen up.
First, the training exercise scheduled
for 2200 has been canceled.
Oh, yeah.
Secondly...
...all passes are hereby revoked.
We're heading back to France,
so pack up all your gear.
We will not be returning
to England, boys.
Anyone who has not made out a will,
go to the supply office.
Trucks depart from Membury at 0700.
As you were.
Hello?
Good morning, Mrs. Lamb.
Sorry to bother you so early.
- That's all right, private...?
- Malarkey.
- Come in.
- Actually, it's Sgt. Malarkey now, ma'am.
- I just got promoted.
- Oh, lovely.
I expect you'll be wanting your laundry.
I heard the trucks rumbling by all night.
I guess the Yanks must be
on their way off again.
Yes, ma'am.
Looks like for good this time.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Two shirts, two pairs of trousers,
light starch.
Two bob and tuppence, please.
I can't--
Thank you.
Would you like a cup of tea?
I've got the water boiling.
No. No, thank you.
I'm in a hell of a--
Bit of a hurry.
But thank you anyway.
- Oh, private?
- Yes, ma'am?
Lieutenant Meehan's one of yours,
isn't he?
I hope he hasn't forgotten his laundry.
- I'll take it.
- Thank you.
You couldn't be a dear and help me
with a few others, could you?
Uh, let's see.
Sergeant Evans, Private Moya,
Blowzer...
...Gray, Miller...
...Owen...
...Collins, Elliot...