The numbing shock of war
is behind me now.
Pain has taken its place.
Hurts to move.
Hurts to breathe.
The back of my head throbs
with every step of my horse.
I look at the world through
the hazy lens of fever,
and somehow see it clearer.
Run little rabbit.
What is death?
What is this thing
we all share...
rabbits, birds, horses, trees...
Everyone I love
and everyone who loves me...
even stars die...
And we know absolutely
nothing of it.
State your business
with the fort.
You're boys.
State your business.
Who are you gonna protect?
I guess I'll protect
who needs protecting.
You should spend some time
outside these walls
before you make that statement.
State your business
or be on your way.
Don't touch her!
- What's wrong with her?
We don't need no smallpox.
She got shot.
Get the surgeon.
Follow me.
Come on, baby.
Major, a woman needs help.
- What happened?
- She was shot.
Gonna need to summon
yer staff, Major.
Got two more coming behind...
Head wound and a snake bite.
Well, just list
the ailments, sir.
I'll decide who to summon.
Looks like she's already
been treated.
Just a battle dressing.
Is there a battle
that I'm not I'm unaware of?
Gunfights do not a battle make.
Captain.
Gunfights do not
a battle make, "Captain."
Believe me when I say,
I know the difference, Major.
- This wound is from an arrow.
- Mm-hm.
Swelling in her liver.
I suggest you get her
to Fort Laramie.
Nothing I can do for you here.
I got no porters,
no nurses, no staff at all.
How can you man a fort
without a staff?
There is no fort.
It's been abandoned.
We're meeting engineers
from Pacific Northwest
as they map a path
for the railroad north and east.
No more wagons for this country.
- Who is she to you?
- She's my daughter.
The arrow hit her liver.
Hard enough to recover
from a bullet through the liver,
let alone an arrow.
Those things are filthy
and half the time poisoned.
And even if her liver does heal,
sepsis is in her.
I'm not saying it can't be beat,
but I've never seen it.
Just get her strong enough
to travel, that's all I ask.
- Travel?
She's done traveling.
Laramie is as far as she goes.
If you're lucky.
Best you can hope for
is that she wakes
and you get to say goodbye.
I'll get my bag.
Move!
You ain't no soldiers
but you're manning a fort.
We're with the CY Ranch.
The ranch owns the fort.
CY part of the Wyoming
Stock Grower's Association?
- Part of it.
Mr. Carey founded it.
Don't that figure.
Y'all need rooms
for the night?
We rent 'em.
We're gonna keep moving.
Where'd they go?
We head to Laramie.
All this land is owned
by the boss
of those deputies we killed.
This fort included.
- Go north.
Hit the Bozeman trail.
That'll put us in Montana
for the winter.
You think this place is wild.
Ain't gonna take them long
for those deputies we killed.
This whole country
will be hunting us.
Again.
Your daughter needs a doctor.
What's a doctor
gonna do for her?
You been to war.
I have too.
Three days.
Her liver either heals
or it fails.
And if it heals,
she's got another week maybe.
Yeah.
I gotta talk to my wife.
Walk with me?
John, go check
on your sister, okay?
We can't wait it out here.
Why not?
- Doesn't matter why.
We just can't.
Ain't no doctor can help her.
Nobody can.
And we ain't gonna lay her
to rest here.
We keep heading north.
Where she dies,
that's where we stay.
She'll be with us.
And you can visit her
any time you want.
Oh, I'll be there every day.
Until you put me in the ground
right beside her.
I need everyone
to gather around.
We're gonna head north
from here.
Winter in the Bozeman valley,
then push on to Oregon
in the spring.
- No no no.
We go to Oregon now.
In the springtime.
You promised.
I'm keeping my promise...
I just changed the way
I'm keeping it.
Get ready to leave.
Captain, these folks
need a few days.
Gotta get Josef to the doctor.
- There is no doctor.
Just more of those thieves.
And if we stay around here,
they're gonna hang us.
We are staying.
The trail is easy enough
to follow now.
We will make it to Oregon
without you.
Suit yourself.
- Wait. Wait...
We go with you.
Show me your leg.
You can't drive.
You can't walk.
She can't drive.
How am I supposed
to take you with me?
I'll drive it.
- They're gonna die.
- Then they die.
They're free people now.
That's what they chose.
Ain't my job to tell you
what to drive.
We got a herd of cattle just
sitting in the prairie.
Leave 'em.
What do you want us to do?
What do you want to do?
I hate turning my back
to ya, but...
If we ain't pushing cattle
for you, we ain't much use.
Where are we goin'?
Montana, honey.
Wonder what that'll be like.
It was a hell of a thing
riding with you.
It was a hell
of a thing riding with you.
Colton: Wasn't a day on this
drive I was prettier than you.
You'll always the be one that
got away, Elsa.
Colton, you gotta be pretty
damn good looking
to think the one you never
had got away from you.
Go back to Texas,
you pretty son of a bitch.
Ma'am.
I wondered
what became of them.
Wondered if they staked their
claim in Wyoming
and built sod houses,
bought cattle and tried to
scratch a life from this place.
Or perhaps they fought
the winter and braved their way
to Oregon, laying stakes
in the emerald fields
of the Willamette Valley.
But I'd seen too much
of this world...
knew too much
about the nature of man
to think either would be
their future.
Another future awaited them,
and it lay in the abyss
of unmarked graves
along the Oregon Trail.
She any better today?
She won't take water.
Mm.
Your leg is dying.
And the death is working
its way up.
Now, we can take the leg...
or you can die with it.
Those are your choices.
You know this?
I know it.
You know how to take the leg?
I know how.
Take it.
Okay.
♪ Lullaby and goodnight... ♪
Margaret's been holding
out on us.
She only sings for the kids.
Not for you?
She promised me she'd sing
at my funeral,
but she made me promise
she'd die first, so...
Got horse traded out of my song.
Women will strike some tricky
bargains, won't they.
I've never come out
on the winning end of one yet.
During the war, I got
a telegraph from my wife
that said she was taking
another lover.
And leaving with him on Friday.
It was a Monday when I got
the telegraph.
So, I got my sword real goddam
sharp to slice
that son of a bitch,
and rode two days straight.
When I got there she ran out
of the house and...
tackled me in a hug.
Said she'd read the Rebels
were in Pennsylvania
and she dreamed that I was gonna
die on a battlefield
at Gettysburg.
That dirty, little liar
saved my life.
Josef's leg got's to come off.
We should do it now.
All right.
Thank you.
So we do this now?
Not yet.
Not till you're so drunk
you can't see straight.
Need about half
that bottle in you.
I'm German.
Half this bottle
I'm just hitting my stride
We had these stupid French
running through the streets
of Paris like dogs.
A-le-a-le-a-le...
You know what the hell
he's talking about?
Some battle.
Don't matter.
Sumbitch can drink that whiskey.
Josef: What no one...
understands about a battle
is the noise.
The noise of it...
When they start,
you can hear the man
beside you scream over
the bombs and rifles.
Before long, you can't hear
the bombs over the screams...
Now we're getting somewhere.
Finish that last swig, Josef.
Fuck.
That ain't one
of yer good ones, is it?
I don't have
a good one.
No, no, I'm not ready.
You just lay right there
and take a nap.
We ain't starting nuthin'.
Don't you...
We ain't doing nuthin'.
Just lay back and rest.
Let's give him a few minutes.
Y'all put your knees
on his arms.
Press your hands
into his shoulders, hard.
Thomas,
you might need that.
Which leg you want?
I'm working the saw.
I got the cutting leg.
He's gonna try to kick the life
out of you when he comes to.
I don't think he's coming to.
Well, he's coming to.
Okay
Slow down.
Cut around to the bone
first, yeah?
I'd go right to the saw.
It'll heal better this way.
Okay.
All right, y'all get on him.
Hold on.
Hold him! Hold him!
Oh, my God.
Gotta bury that leg.
He don't need to see a coyote
running through the plains
with his foot tomorrow.
Y'all can get up now.
Are we in Montana?
Almost.
Hm.
- Honey, you need to lay down.
- Mm.
- I'm cold.
Wanna sit by the fire.
There anything to eat?
I can sure make you something
real quick.
I'm sure glad I didn't get
shot in the leg.
Gonna have to hold out
for about fifteen minutes.
I ain't going nowhere.
Fever's broke.
Color's back too.
That's good.
How's the pain.
It's there,
but not like it was.
You want some bacon?
Sure.
Y'all made good time.
Went from prairie to pine trees
in a day.
We left the fort
three days ago.
Oh.
- Slept my way here, I guess.
- Yeah, honey. You sure did.
I'm not sure
what Oregon looks like
but I bet it don't
look like this.
Should have aimed for this place
from the start.
I don't know what Oregon looks
like either, honey,
but this is hard to beat.
The only people who know what
it looks like are already there.
Funny, when you think about it.
All those people from Europe...
Don't speak our language...
Don't know anything
about this place.
Risking their lives
over rumors and dreams.
Rumors and dreams
built this whole world, honey.
Every inch of it.
Wanna know my greatest fear
about dying?
It's being forgotten.
And I can't understand why cuz
I won't be here
to know anyone forgot me.
But the thought is terrifying.
What a silly thing to scare me.
Nobody's gonna
forget you, Elsa.
And you ain't dying.
You should be dead.
But you pay about as much
attention to the rules of nature
as you pay to mine.
You look at me like I'm dying.
I look at you
for what you are...
The most important thing
to me on this planet.
And that comes with
a lot of worry.
Because I can't replace you.
The others were wrong
not to come with us.
You think they'll make it
to Oregon?
I don't think they'll make it
out of Wyoming.
Me neither.
We never spoke of dreams
or death again.
Never spoke
of the Pioneers either.
Because there was no need.
Come on! Let's go!
To survive the frontier,
you must learn to recognize
those who won't.
And be weary
of their doomed decisions.
They are to be avoided at all
costs, because their fear
is tragedy's closest cousin.
And tragedy is contagious
in this place.
- Shea!
- Hold up here.
Get ready.
In the foot locker!
She's hurt.
- I know. Shot.
Lakota arrow.
They been making war?
Somebody made war on them.
They thought it was us.
What do your, uh, doctors say?
We have no doctors.
I'll get you a doctor.
We need to put her in the creek.
It's too cold.
She's got a fever.
Cold is what she needs.
Stop the bleeding.
That was quite the battle, huh?
Was a good one.
You her father?
I can call him.
Call him.
You are her father.
I am.
What do you know of war?
More than I care to.
Mm.
You know that the
Lakota, they dip their arrows
in manure, so a hit is fatal.
And an arrow in the liver
is for certain.
I know what's coming.
I just...
Where we put her in the ground
is where we stay.
And I gotta find
that place fast.
Otherwise I'm living out here
in the sagebrush with you.
I know a place for you.
You go through that pass then
you follow the river south.
I used to hunt that valley
as a boy.
The winters are cruel,
but the summer's are rich
and a man who plans can thrive.
And you look like a man
who plans.
What's the valley called.
I don't know the word in your
language, but it's, uh...
When you die, you go there.
Heaven.
No, there's
another word, it's not...
Paradise.
Yes, Paradise. Good name.
But know this:
that in seven generations
my people will rise up,
and take it back from you.
In seven generations
you can have it.
Mm.
How long's the trip?
Spotted Eagle: Depends
how fast you ride.
But with that wagon,
it will take a week.
And she doesn't have that.
Some day my family
might seek to hunt that valley
and if they do, you remember me.
And you let them.
Your family can hunt
the day I get there
and every day after.
Mm. Good.
Feel better?
You lied.
I'm sorry.
I'm dying.
I know, honey.
Make me a promise.
Anything.
- Let me choose the spot.
Please?
Yeah, honey.
You choose the spot.
They're fine. Ate good.
Went right to sleep.
They haven't spoken since
their father died...
in Texas.
I couldn't get them
to shut up.
They talk to you?
All the time.
Ask about what's this sound
and this animal...
What's Oregon like...
They won't talk to me.
For months.
Guess I'd blame me too.
Ain't blame.
They just don't know
what to say.
After all they seen you
go through.
It's the journey that keeps them
from talking with you.
To them, you're this,
this giant egg...
They're terrified
is gonna break.
They talk to me cuz
they couldn't care less
if I break.
And that's fine.
Guess I don't care
too much myself.
What happens in Oregon?
Don't know a thing
about Oregon.
With us, I mean.
Figure we find
a valley with, uh...
some good water
no people.
Then we stake it out
and make it ours.
And your boys
will talk to you again.
Cuz the journey's over.
I've lost a daughter too.
Time will come
when you blame yourself.
Think it's your fault.
For giving her so much rein.
And maybe it is your fault...
But I'll say this...
I've watched this girl
for the last six months
and she has outlived us all.
I'm 75 years old
and she has out-smiled me,
out-loved me, out-fought me...
She's outlived me.
She's out-lived all of us.
She wants to pick the spot
where she's buried.
She wants to choose it.
Put eyes on it.
These wagons won't make
the trip in time.
My boy can't make the trip
on horseback.
Mm-hm.
And I gave her my word.
I can't let her life end
with me breaking it.
And I have absolutely no idea
how to tell my wife...
I gotta take her daughter
away from her...
To die...
And she can't go.
She'll hear the logic
in it from you.
From me, all she'll hear
is the cruelty in it.
You think you can
do that for me?
Please...
Yeah.
I can do that for ya.
Ma'am?
So, what is my husband
too scared to ask me?
He promised your daughter she
could choose where she dies.
And that's where you
build the ranch.
But it's a week's drive
on a wagon.
She ain't got a week.
Horse can make it in two days.
Still haven't heard
a question.
Well, I really don't know
what the question is, ma'am.
I guess the question is,
are you willing to say goodbye
to her here.
Men are such fucking cowards.
It ain't cowardice, ma'am.
It's a shame that the question's
even being asked.
When do they leave?
Should leave in the morning.
I'm sorry.
Ain't no other way.
I love you.
I love you both.
With all my heart.
I'll see you
in the valley, mama.
See you there.
I hope you prove 'em
all wrong.
Hope you laugh about this
in twenty years.
Laugh at all of us
for doubting you.
Well, if I can't...
I'll come meet you on the beach.
I'll save you a spot.
We'll be right behind you.
Keep 'em close.
Like they were my own.
This way. Here.
Stop.
This is the spot.
Where do you want to go?
Against the tree.
Let's just sit here and...
Rest for a bit.
You want a blanket?
No.
You be the blanket.
What's your first memory?
I was... probably three
I reckon.
My daddy had an apprentice.
And he was banging horse shoes.
I remember the sparks.
He looked up at me
and he smiled...
put his hands over his eyes,
and said "peekaboo I see you,"
then he covered his eyes
with his hands,
and he said
you can't see me."
"Where am I."
I didn't understand the game,
I mean, he was hiding
behind his hands.
And I could see him.
Plain as day.
And I thought he was a fool.
Mine was...
All of these birds...
In the field behind the house.
Right after a rain.
Pecking at the ground.
Pulling out worms.
And I thought...
"How smart. Wait for the rain
to soften the earth."
I just thought that
was so smart.
- You were right, honey.
That was smart.
You birds sure are smart.
Honey...
I understand it now.
Understand what?
I know what it is.
And I'm not scared.
I'm not scared, daddy.
This is it.
Mama! There's a river!
Is it too far?
Ain't nothing too far for us.
You want the river...
I'll stake you a river.
Just look at that, Helen.
Isn't that beautiful...
There is a moment where
your dreams and your memories
merge together,
and form a perfect world.
That is Heaven.
And each Heaven is unique.
It is the world of you.
The land is filled
with all you hold dear
and the sky is your imagination.
My Heaven is filled with good
horses and open plains
and wild cattle
and a man who loves me.
Race ya.
It is always sunrise
in my world...
And there are no storms.
I am the only lighting.
I know death now.
I've seen it.
It had no fangs.
It smiled at me.
And it was beautiful.