[Money for Nothing
by Dire Straits]
♪ MTV... ♪
This place seems confused
by the rules of night and day.
Or perhaps it
simply ignores them,
refusing to cool
when the sun fades.
It's as if God
has not yet decided
what this place should become.
Will it be desert?
Will it be prairie?
Every living thing is armed
with thorns and horns and fangs
as the land wages war on
itself, seeking the answer...
I knew that war.
That war between what
you should become,
and what you could become.
I looked at this place
and saw my unfinished soul.
I looked at this
place and knew, for me...
that war was over.
I know what I am now.
I'm a cowboy.
[music]
It seems the farther
we get from civilization,
the more of its rules
we leave behind.
Its traditions.
Its inhibitions...
The farther west we travel,
the more those rules
and customs become a burden.
[music]
[panting]
- You speak English?
- Sorry. No English.
Alina.
[speaks Italian]
Wife English.
- Oh, um...
- What do you call those?
- Pants.
- In his language.
- Pantaloni.
- Ask him if he has more.
- I know he has more
because I made them.
- Can I trade for some?
- Trade.
- I give you
something and you give...
- I know what trade is.
Why you want my husband's pants?
- Tired of blisters
from the saddle.
- Let's talk trade.
- What do you want?
- What do you have?
- What do you need?
- We need everything.
- It's gold.
- What good is gold
to me out here?
- If everything is what
you need, gold can buy it.
- Oh. I just walk over
to store then.
- There's stores in Abilene.
- Why you have gold?
- Why I have it is none
of your business.
- Then you stole it
and we have no trade.
- Wait.
My father made jewelry
of his money to hide it.
He hid some on me.
- Not yours to hide anymore.
I get you pants.
[chuckles]
There is pants.
Should fit you.
Too small for him.
You have skinny hips.
- You think so?
- I know.
I looking at you.
When you have baby,
its head coming out
looking like eggplant.
- What's eggplant?
[chuckles]
Can you do that to my dress?
[music]
[kissing noises]
What's the matter, never seen
a woman in pants before?
- Naw, I think you're the first.
Hey, cut it out.
[clicks tongue]
- Oh...
[laughs]
It's not the worst
idea you've had.
I don't want to know
where the pants came from.
- I traded for them...
- I said I don't want to know.
[sigh]
Traded what?
Never mind.
I don't want to know.
[clicks tongue]
- [chuckles]
- What time's the meeting?
- Now.
- You want me to come?
- No, stay with the herd.
I saw wolf tracks by the river.
That one of them gypsies?
- Sorta.
- I'll bring you supper.
- Hey, bring me two.
[music]
- River looked
pretty deep to me.
- It's high.
- Maybe we should've crossed
the Red where we was.
Now we're crossing two rivers...
- We're gonna cross twenty
before we're done.
- I didn't see
a decent place to cross here.
- There's one a few miles up.
There's a spot wild cattle use.
Ground pretty rocky.
- How deep?
- It's a swim.
- Your people know how to swim?
- It's illegal
where we are from.
- To swim?
- Where I am from they whip
the bodies of the drowned
before they are buried.
For getting in a river
in the first place.
We don't swim.
- We could get the cattle
across first
then get as many over horseback
as we can,
then the wagons.
- Look, my two cents?
If we run the cattle
over first
they're gonna make
soup out of the bank.
You get a wagon
stuck and you've got
a traffic jam in
the middle of the river.
I seen it,
and you don't want to.
Ferry folks over
then send the wagons.
Then bring the herd.
- How many folks you
need to hold the herd?
- Don't worry about the herd,
I'll get the herd across,
you just keep those
wagons off the bank
or I'm gonna have
a traffic jam too.
- Can you help us
ferry folks across?
- I can do that.
- That means
your wife has to drive a wagon.
- My wife could back a wagon
through the doors of a saloon.
She'll be fine.
- We'll cross in the morning.
- Wait till it warms up.
Let everything get hot
and a little tired.
Animals will be more ready
to get in the river then.
- That's rain over there.
Rain over there
is a higher river here.
- It's high already.
- By the time I get
these misfits moving
it'll be midday, farmer.
Don't you worry about it.
- I ain't no fucking farmer.
- You were.
- I was a captain, too.
I don't call myself
that either...
Captain.
[clears throat]
- Steal some hard tack,
if you don't mind.
- There's some biscuits
in my teepee and some bacon.
- How old's the biscuits?
- They're new enough.
- Thought we was
getting a cook.
- Abilene.
- How bout we kill one
of them beefs
when we get across the river?
- We'll kill a beef when we
have a cook to butcher it.
- This ain't the part of
the trip where we skinny up.
This is the part
where we get fat.
The skinny part's coming.
- We butcher it ourselves,
we'll waste most of it.
Run through
that herd in a month.
Then we ain't skinnying up,
we're starving.
- Hm. Well, have a look
around, Captain.
We're starving already.
[clicks tongue]
- This talking back
is getting contagious.
- You need to have a word
with that farmer.
A word that sticks.
Let me do it,
I'll make sure it sticks.
- By the time we get
to the territories,
we're gonna need all
the fight he's got in him.
They whip the bodies
because it's illegal to swim.
- Illegal to do everything.
Except pay taxes.
[sighs]
Uh... Oregon.
You've seen it?
- I've seen it.
- What was it like?
- It's worth the risk
if that's what you're asking.
- That's what I'm asking.
[music]
- Once we cross the Brazos...
- No turning back.
- Nope.
- It takes a lot
to surprise me, Thomas.
These people, they've never been
allowed to think for themselves.
Now they can hardly
think at all.
The fact they ain't headed
for Galveston
and begging their way on
a boat for home shocks me.
It shocks me, Thomas.
That they haven't quit yet.
- Don't know why
them folks wanna go home.
Their home sounds like hell.
- 'Cause it's the
hell they know.
Most terrifying thing on
this planet is the unknown.
- That's 'cause you ain't never
been whipped, Captain.
Let someone put
a whip to your back
and tell me the unknown
is what scares you.
These folks ain't
never going home.
[music]
[insects]
- Hey...
We'll have to break camp
and cross the river tonight.
- Why tonight?
- It ain't safe
to be behind them.
- You think crossing alone
the river at night is safer?
- These folks are gonna
need help,
we can't help if
we're one of them.
- What about Elsa?
- I'll get her.
- [deep breath]
I'll hook the team.
- ♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ Wake unto me ♪
♪ Starlight and dewdrops
are waiting for thee ♪
♪ Sounds of the rude world ♪
♪ Heard in the day ♪
♪ Lull'd by the moonli... ♪
[rustling]
- Don't stop.
- ♪ Sta... ♪
I can't... I can't.
- Why not?
- I'm shy.
- Since when were you shy?
- Well, with singing I'm shy.
I just...
Worry it won't sound good.
- Cow don't care how it sounds.
Hell, I sing to them all night,
and I ain't shy about it.
- You probably should be.
- [snorts]
[laughs]
Well, you sure ain't shy
about hard timing me.
- No, that comes
pretty easy to me.
- Well...
Somebody gotta sing to 'em.
- ♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ Wake unto me ♪
♪ Starlight and dewdrops
are waiting for thee ♪
♪ Sounds of the rude world ♪
♪ Heard in the day ♪
♪ Lull'd by the moon... ♪
- Guess I'm the
one being forward now.
I'm sorry, I probably should...
- Do it again.
[music]
- You gonna shoot me?
- Thinking about it.
We're moving the wagon
across the river.
- When?
- Now.
- I should stay with the herd.
It takes three to move it.
- Herd ain't going nowhere
with you two swapping supper.
You got a job to do.
Y'all do it.
- Yessir.
Daddy.
You mad?
- You like him?
- I do.
- Then why would I be mad?
I can't treat you
like an adult when it suits me
and a child when I'm worried.
You're one or the other.
Your mother is gonna be
a different story.
- You gonna tell her?
- Hell, no.
I ain't gonna tell her.
You're gonna tell her.
[music]
Y'all hold the herd till every
wagon is across that river.
- Yessir.
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
- He ain't gonna shoot me?
- No, he said I could shoot you.
If you act up.
- Well, acting up
is my only skill.
- No, it ain't.
Do it again.
- [laughs]
- Come here.
[coyote howls]
[horse snorts]
- Oh, no, don't go wasting
your supplies on me, ma'am.
You just...
just keep them children fed.
You fed, too.
- I would have no supplies
if it weren't for you.
- What're you doing?
- Watching.
- Don't do that.
- Why not?
- Marrying a black
man ain't gonna
solve your problems, ma'am.
It's gonna create
a whole bunch of new ones.
- This is free country.
- There's degrees
of free, ma'am.
- What does that mean?
Government can tell me
who to love?
- Your government
says you can't swim.
Can't protect yourself.
Damn right government
can tell you who to love.
And how to love 'em.
They shouldn't.
But they can.
- Then we go
somewhere they can't.
[chuckles]
- Ma'am, you don't want
nuthin' to do with me.
I'm too old.
Too set in my ways.
I don't like talking.
I like sleeping outside
and I like bathing in a river.
That ain't what a woman wants.
- Men have no idea
what women want.
- [chuckles]
Can't argue that.
- Know why?
Because they never ask.
- What do you want?
- I want to watch you eat.
- [grumbles]
Okay.
[music]
[wolf howls]
- Wolf.
- Mm-hmm.
- Even here there are wolves.
[howling]
- Awoo.
[giggles]
[coyote yips]
- What the hell was that?
- I don't know.
- Oregon is not like this?
- Oregon is...
mountains...
and green grass to your hips...
all the way to the ocean.
Where you walk ankle
deep in water.
Oregon is paradise.
- I hope so.
- I promise.
- And then a family?
- And then we make a family.
- Then we have a family.
We start making it tonight.
[coyotes yipping]
[music]
- Looks deep.
- Well, it ain't shallow.
- [sigh]
You take John with you.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Come on, son.
There ain't nothing
on this wagon worth dying for.
If it goes under,
you get clear of these horses.
Let all this mess
go down river.
You swim upriver,
I'll come get you.
- Yep.
- Nervous?
- I'm fine.
- I love you.
- Why'd you say that?
- Because I want you to know it.
- Now I'm nervous.
[music]
Hey! Hey!
[shouting]
- Whoa, that was fun!
Did you have fun, mama?
- Yeah, a real hoot, son.
Close your eyes, son.
Cover his ears.
This is harder than you
said it would be.
- I told you it was gonna take
everything we had and then some.
- You should've explained
what "everything" meant.
[cannon blast]
[wind blows]
[gunfire]
[men shouting]
- No!
That's why
I don't like to sleep.
- Ain't the first time
I seen it.
- Ain't never seen it from you.
You sleep like a goddam baby.
I've never understood it.
- The way I grew up?
Things I seen?
Shit...
Wasn't scared of no nightmare.
Hell, we went to sleep
to escape 'em...
I made coffee.
[music]
[grunts]
- Morning.
- Morning, Captain.
[music]
- What happened
to "Wait till it warms?"
- I didn't mean me.
More current than it looks and
a deep channel in the middle.
Heavy wagons will
get bogged.
- Well...
If they can't cross here
they got no business
going any farther.
- They got no business
going this far.
- One could argue
none of us do.
Guess I'll bring 'em.
- We'll be waiting.
- Will you?
- I said I'll help.
I'll help.
[music]
- There are few things
that focus one
solely on the present.
Terror is one.
Grief another.
But nothing washes
the world away
like the lips of another.
Seems an odd custom,
strangers putting
their mouths together
and exploring each other
with their tongues.
When you think about it,
kissing makes no sense at all.
- Morning.
- Mm. That it is...
It's been morning
for a good bit now.
- Sorry.
- Catching up on your
beauty sleep, I guess.
Lord knows
you don't need much of that.
[music]
Come on.
Let's work.
[music]
You hold the right, all right?
- Okay.
[clicks tongue]
- Come on.
Come on, we're going to
push it to the water.
Come on, cows.
- What a silly thing, kissing.
What a pointless,
purposeless thing.
And I couldn't wait
for another.
- River rose overnight.
- How much?
- Enough.
We need to lighten these wagons.
If it ain't absolutely necessary
it doesn't make the trip.
[speaking German]
- Can we come back for
the things we leave?
- How we gonna do that?
If it's too heavy,
here's where it stays. Let's go.
[speaking German]
- We will get to Oregon
with nothing.
How do we make our
lives with nothing?!
Josef?
[speaking German]
Josef!
[grunting]
- Don't know how his horses drug
this around on dry ground.
It's too heavy.
- Get all this shit
out of there.
- Unpack your wagon.
- Goddammit.
Look at this.
What did I tell
you in Fort Worth?
I said if it is
not absolutely necessary
it does not make the trip.
- It is necessary.
He's a musician.
- No, he's not a musician!
And you're not a carpenter,
and he's not a
fucking blacksmith.
You are pioneers, and that's all
you are until you get there.
You have no home, no job,
no farm.
You have the journey,
that's it.
[speaking German]
- What's he sayin'?
- He says these things,
they can't be replaced.
You are sending him to Oregon
to be a beggar on the streets.
- These are his choices:
he unloads his wagon.
He goes back to Fort Worth,
or I burn his wagon
to the ground. Tell him.
[speaking German]
[sobbing]
- They're gonna hate you.
- At least they'll
be alive to do it.
[music]
- We cross that?
Josef?
We go across that?
- Yes. We go across it.
[music]
[shrieking]
- You're fine, you're fine.
[screaming]
[panting]
- Show me that trench.
- Starts right here.
- You gotta stay
to the right of that spot.
- I know it, Captain.
I passed the word.
Just hope these folks
stay patient.
Cool heads cross rivers.
Hot heads drown.
- Gonna pull wagons.
If someone falls off,
toss them a rope and
pull 'em to the bank.
- Don't let them
reach your horse.
They'll drag you off.
- Why would they drag me off?
- 'Cause when people panic
that's what they do.
- If you come out of the saddle,
that dress'll drown you.
- Oh my God.
I guess we're gonna
get to know each other
a lot better after this day.
[music]
- Looks like they came to their
senses and lightened up.
- A river'll do that to ya.
- Strange they'd just leave it.
- Should've left it in town.
- Once we get to Kansas...
Hell, it looks like a junk yard,
all the things folks
dump at the river bank.
Ovens, bath tubs,
wind mill blades as big
as the wagon it was in.
I swear, folks must think
the way west was paved.
[plunking notes]
- You play?
- I do.
I did.
I guess I don't play anymore.
- Well...
You can play once more.
[plays piano]
[plays "Moonlight Sonata"
by Beethoven]
["Moonlight Sonata" continues]
[crying]
[sobbing]
[panting]
- Don't know any happy ones?
[laughs]
[sniffs]
- Never had much interest
in the happy ones.
[music]
[men shouting]
- Hey, cow.
Hey, cow.
- Get up.
- Yee-hoo!
Whoop, whoop, whoop.
[whistling]
- Get up, cow, get up.
Come on. Come on.
Come on! Hey!
- Hut, hut!
- Woop!
- Get up, cow.
[shouting, whooping]
Hey, cow!
- I had abandoned every
memory of Tennessee,
as though I was born
on this journey.
But I wasn't...
We were leaving a place
and seeking another.
And the journey was
the necessary,
miserable road
between the two.
Somehow I felt immune to
the dangers of this place.
As if the land and
I had struck a deal.
I could pass unharmed
so long as I loved it.
And I did.
I loved everything about it.
But crossing the Brazos
taught me there was no deal.
No matter how much we love it,
the land will
never love us back.
[music]