[Money for Nothing
by Dire Straits]
* MTV... *
[music]
[inhales]
[grunts]
[hooves approaching]
[metal clanking]
[music]
- Captain.
[sigh]
[stammers]
- I know.
I know.
[sobbing]
Elsa: My father won't
speak of the war.
When men ask if he fought,
he says no.
I've seen fellow soldiers call
out his name on the street.
He turns and walks
the other way.
He spent three years
in a Union prison.
When he came home,
my mother said
he weighed ninety-seven pounds.
[music]
- Gonna need a cook.
Or two.
- Why do we need a cook?
- Because your passengers are
feasting like it's Christmas
and somebody needs
to ration their food
because when they run out,
they're coming after my food.
Or your food...
- We're gonna bring
a herd of beef with us.
Food ain't gonna be a problem.
- Yeah, it will.
Add a cook to the list.
You feel like moving some cows?
- Somebody's gotta watch
after these folks.
- If these folks can't survive
six hours sitting by a river,
I'd rather know it now.
[sigh]
- What are you looking at?
- Nuthin'.
- How come I ain't got no hair?
- "Ain't got no"?
Been in Texas six days,
you already forgot how to speak.
- How come?
- You will.
When you're older.
- But how come not now?
- I don't know
"how come not now."
Maybe 'cause it makes
you easier to tickle.
[laughing]
James: Elsa.
Where's your mother?
- Don't know.
- We're going to go
round up some cattle.
Be back in the afternoon.
I want you to stay in camp,
I want you to keep
an eye on your brother,
and don't wander off.
All right.
[music]
- Cool air rises from the ground
and sends a shiver through me.
Then the sun finds my face,
and I am warm.
The world here plays parlor
tricks on your senses...
I do not know what
the word "Texas" means.
But to me it means magic.
- Look, these here cattle,
they're going to Kansas
unless you can
pay Kansas prices.
- What are Kansas prices?
- Hell, you can get
forty dollars a head
for these sons
of bitches up there.
Those New Yorkers
sure do love their steaks.
- We can't pay that.
- Well, I don't blame you.
I wouldn't either.
I tell you what,
I'll put a bee in your bonnet.
There's still wild cattle
down there on the Brazos,
if you got the stones
to go get 'em.
- We got the stones,
we just don't have the men.
- We could saddle up some
of them wagon horses,
stick them Germans on them.
Surely they can hold a line.
- Don't bet on it.
[horse neighs]
- Let's put them in the sell
barn, lot four.
Ain't changed
our mind yet, Captain.
- We're going to round some up.
Can I hire you for that?
- Where you holding 'em?
- Ain't found them to hold them.
- Hm.
You hunting wild cattle?
- I'll give you a dollar apiece
for every one you gather.
- How many you trying
to get together?
- Hundred or so.
- You need ten hands.
And I mean good hands.
- How 'bout three good hands and
twenty who ain't worth a shit.
- If they ain't worth a shit
we ain't gonna get nuthin'
and we ain't gonna get paid.
- I'll pay you
ten dollars apiece
whether we wrangle any or not.
- You're wasting your money.
- Aw, come on, Wade.
You're handy enough
for all of us.
- Yeah, there's still some wild
cattle around Fort Griffith.
That's a pretty
good ride though.
- We're ready when you are.
- Yee-haw. [clicks tongue]
- Yee-haw.
- Come on, boys, y'all
got cattle to sort, let's go.
- We'll be back for them
cattle, don't you worry.
Hya!
[clicks tongue]
[music]
- It seems even trees
are new to this place.
They scatter about in clusters,
like little villages...
And everywhere, treasures.
Everywhere there
is a bounty
just waiting
to be scooped up...
[gasps]
When I looked
out over this land,
I only saw the freedom
it promised.
I knew nothing of the horror
that hides in freedom's shadow.
[gasps]
[groaning, vomiting]
[sighs]
- Let me see 'em
[sigh]
Put them in the pot.
[sighs]
Fools.
- I'm going to go warn him
- Don't bother.
Better they die up here
than do something on
the trail that gets us killed.
Only cure for stupid is
reaching the gates of heaven.
- Funny, I don't recall the word
"stupid" anywhere in the Bible.
[panting]
- Look what
the cat drug to camp.
- Across the river...
People...
Nausea has a number
of them to their knees.
- You were across the river?
Your dress is dry,
so you didn't swim.
Either you learned how to fly
or you rode the back
of one of those Germans.
I don't know which image
is more upsetting.
- There's a sand bar.
And a log.
- Mystery solved then.
They don't even boil it.
Just drink it like
it's from a faucet.
Cholera will run
the lot of them.
- What's my mother doing?
- She's wasting her time.
- I'm done with berries.
Your turn.
Mind the thorns.
[music]
- Don't see any saddle horses.
- I've got a few.
- Got a few saddles, too?
These sons of bitches
are plow drivers.
- We warned you.
- Hell, we're better
off without 'em.
- Can any of 'em ride?
- I got one can ride.
[clicks tongue]
[crying]
- It's the water.
You have to boil it
before you drink it.
[speaks German]
Don't drink it.
[groans]
[cries]
- Go saddle Lightning.
- She's sick.
From the water.
They all are.
- Go saddle Lightning.
[groaning]
You making them tea?
- These poor people
don't know to boil water.
- I'll be gone
'till tomorrow late.
- Be careful.
- Shotgun's under the
buckboard if there's trouble.
- [laughs] I have Claire
if there's trouble.
- Claire usually
makes things worse.
I'm taking Elsa...
- You're what?
- This bunch is short
on riders and we need her.
- I'd object, but it sounds like
you're not asking my permission.
- No, ma'am, I am not.
- How am I supposed
to make her a lady
when you keep treating her
like a man?
- Plenty of ladies
in this world.
Pretty short
on decent men, though.
[clicks tongue]
- How am I supposed
to respond to that?
- Sun'll be fierce.
- [laughs]
It'll blow off.
- Here, tie it down.
- What's that for?
- Not sure.
But I'd sure hate you don't
have it when we find out.
Stay close to me.
[chuckles]
[music]
- They're back early.
- Yep.
Shea: Who are they?
- A stroke of luck
there, Captain.
[clicks tongue]
- Goddamn, Wade.
If there's a better way
to get shot I don't know it,
chargin' in here like a
bunch of fucking bandits.
[chuckles]
- We've seen you shoot, Grady.
I think the bandits are safe.
- Y'all hunting strays?
- Wild ones. Seen any?
- Yeah, some.
Them wild bulls pester them
English cows pretty good.
Must be the way they smell.
All smell the same to me,
but I ain't a bull.
- Your crew's pretty light
to gather wild cattle.
- Could use the help.
We'll pay.
- No need.
We need to clear some out.
Y'all best come on up to camp.
- Come on.
[music]
- Good to see you, Wade.
Almost fucking shot you.
- [laughing]
- Whoo, yeah,
I got you one.
- What you got here?
- I bet you double.
- Woo.
- I'm surprised you got anything
to bet at all after Abilene.
That town is hard
on a cowboy's wallet.
- We stay away from
that son of a bitch.
It'll suck on you like a tick.
- You better bat your eyes...
- Even if we get a herd
to the wagons, we can't hold it.
We can't leave till we've hired
some guns and some hands.
- These Germans gotta learn
to hold their own, Thomas.
Or they won't survive the trip.
None of us will.
- They're barely
surviving the river
and they ain't camped
five miles from town.
- There ain't no one to hire.
- Then we don't go.
- You can stay.
I'm going.
I want to see it one last time.
Before it's settled.
Before it's ruined.
- After you see it, then what?
- Then I don't care.
The world can
open up and eat me.
I don't give a shit.
[sniffs]
- What's that for?
- Well, it's for snakes.
They won't cross it.
- What about you?
- Honey, I'm so far away
from a bath
ain't no snake gonna
curl up next to me.
Ah...
[Elsa laughs]
[clears throat]
- Mm.
[sighs]
- Thank you.
For bringing me.
- Hm. Bringing you ain't a gift.
We need you.
So, thank you.
These cattle are wild.
These bulls will hook you.
Don't get caught up
in the brush with one.
You push the ones
that want to be pushed,
the rest we leave behind.
I need you to hear
me on that.
- Yes.
- I trust you.
- Know what today is?
- [laughs]
I don't know.
Thursday, maybe?
- Eighteen years-ago
on this day,
Lee surrendered to Grant
in the home of Wilmer Mclean
in the village of Appomattox.
A year later, I was born.
It was Monday,
April 9th, 1883,
Monday was my birthday.
- Yeah, Thursday.
I think you're right.
- Hey. Wake up.
We gotta go.
He's already saddled.
I'll follow you.
- I can't see.
- Follow the horse
in front of you
and watch its hooves
sparking off the rocks.
[music]
- We'll ride out
in a line from here.
I'll drop you off as we go.
When I'm set, I'll call out.
The next man in line
does the same.
Drive due west.
When you hit the river don't
cross if you don't see tracks.
It's boggy enough to swallow
horse and rider both.
When you hit the meadow,
wait for the men in
the south to fold north.
Hold your line and we'll
push 'em right into camp.
Stay here.
This is your hole.
The rest follow me.
- What do I do?
- You follow 'em.
[music]
- In the back, hold...
[horse snorting]
[music]
[yipping]
[shouting]
[shouts]
- Come on, buddy.
[snorts]
[kisses]
- Hey.
Ha. Ha!
[music]
[shouting]
[cow lows]
[whooping]
- Push 'em up,
push 'em up!
- Come on!
Get!
[whoops]
- Keep 'em comin'.
- Whoa!
- Come on, cow!
- Come on.
[cow lows]
- They're coming out of
the south with a few more.
We'll marry them here,
then push em on.
Makes you wonder what
the rich folk are doing, huh?
- They ain't doing this.
- No, ma'am, they ain't.
- [laughs]
- I looked to my right
and saw my father,
somehow riding vertically
toward the earth.
Beyond him, cowboys
and cattle pushed toward us,
dust following them
like a cloudy shadow.
The light was soft
and pale and pink,
like God decided to
light this day with candles.
And the whole of Texas
spread out before me.
It was the most magnificent
thing I'd ever seen.
- Well, that went better
than I expected.
- [chuckles]
- You having fun?
- Yeah.
- We got to get someone
at the mouth of that draw,
so they don't leak into it.
Someone else
to push from the rear.
- I'll do it.
Can I do it?
- You can do it.
- [chuckles]
[clicks tongue]
[music]
- All right, boys.
Let's get a moving.
Yip!
- Freedom...
To most, it is an idea.
An abstract thought that
pertains to control.
That's not freedom.
That's independence.
Freedom is riding wild
over untamed land
with no notion
any moment exists
beyond the one you are living.
[playing music]
- They gonna play
music all night?
- It looks that way.
- When do they sleep?
- That is a question
yet to be answered.
But I know when you sleep:
you sleep now.
- Yes, ma'am.
[woman singing]
- Godless noise.
We could be listening
to cicadas and frogs
by the river, but instead
we're listening to this.
- For once, we're in agreement.
But I don't mind the song.
I mean, it's sad...
But I suppose I'd be sad too
if I was a world away
from my home.
- You are a world
away from your home.
I don't know what he expects
to find in these mountains,
or wherever it is
we're headed,
but I'll tell you
what we won't find:
we won't find civilization.
We won't find
a church for prayer
or a house with wood floors
or painted walls,
restaurants or friends
or schools for our children.
We just left it all behind.
- I don't recall anyone forcing
you on the train, Claire.
- Fate forced me.
When it robbed me of a husband
and robbed my child
of a future with him.
What was I to do,
beg on the street?
Don't recall anyone
forcing me...
Who the hell do you
think you are?
- I...
- What is so funny?
- Honestly, Claire...
I don't have the energy
or the interest
to continue this conversation.
- Well.
[scoffs]
He's a dreamer, Margaret.
Always has been.
And they never come true.
- It's coming true, Claire.
- No.
This is not the dream.
This is the nightmare.
You'll see.
[music]
- You drink coffee?
- It's not for me.
- No one else here.
You lied!
- I did, didn't I?
- What kind of a woman
drinks coffee?
- I can't wait to hear
this lecture on womanhood.
This coffee is for him.
After a long night.
Someday, if you're lucky
to find a man
or simply find a man
who is extremely unlucky,
you will learn coffee is a
welcome treat after a hard ride.
Mmm.
[hooves approaching]
- Take it easy,
just a little bit.
- Where's the wagon boss?
- He camps to the south.
- [laughs]
Fucking gypsies.
Gypsies don't travel
with much, I've learned.
But you, uh...
You Irish, y'all usually
travel well stocked.
I'll ask again,
where's your wagon boss?
- You'll be meeting
him soon enough.
- Mm-hmm.
- We have nothing
to offer you, sir. Be gone!
- Be gone, she says.
- What do you want here?
- Last I checked,
ain't nobody owned the river.
Be gone.
Hell.
[panting]
- God dammit.
- Go!
You're not welcome here! Go!
Go!
[gasps]
- You are the devil! I see you!
I see you!
[screaming]
- And to think, all I wanted
to do was water the horses.
Ain't all I want to do now.
[shotgun cocks]
- It'll be the
last thing you do.
- There's a dozen guns
with sixty bullets
between 'em out here.
You've only got two.
- And they're both for you.
[shouting]
[gunshot]
- Aw! Get off me!
[horse grunting]
[grunts]
[gunshots]
[shouting]
- John?
John?
[gunfire, screaming]
[screaming]
- No! No!
No, no!
[screaming in German]
John! John!
- Mama?
- John!
Oh my God, oh my God!
[music]
[sobs]
[cries]
- Hey. That's a girl.
- Yep.
Dress sort of gave it away.
- Pretty handy.
- She got around good.
- Not awful to look at either.
- Hard to tell with
that hat hanging over her head
like elephant ears.
- Hey.
[clicks tongue]
[whistling]
- Come on.
- Hey.
Thirsty?
There you go.
Careful.
Would you take off your hat?
Wanna get a better look at you.
- Why get a better look?
- Well.
There's a fair chance
you're too pretty for me.
If you are, I'd rather know
now so I don't waste my time.
- Maybe you're
too pretty for me.
[laughs]
- Well, shoot.
I mean, if me being pretty
is the problem,
then we ain't got a problem.
Shoot.
Yep.
Too pretty for me.
Dang it.
[laughing]
- And just like that,
horror steps from the shadows.
And our freedom was gone...
[music]
- We're gonna ride
into town with Josef
and meet the Marshal.
I'd like you with us.
- Somebody needs to be here
in case they come back.
- Cowboys are here.
They've done dealt with
their share of bandits.
[music]
- I'm so sorry.
- What are you sorry about?
You didn't shoot her.
- I'm still sorry.
- Are you?
[scoffs]
- Yes.
- You don't know
what that word means.
But you're going to learn.
All of you are going to learn.
- Going after them?
- Yeah.
- They were rough
and they were rude,
and they were looking for it...
But I can't say
they started it.
- It don't matter
who started it.
- I'm just saying...
Not sure there's justice in it.
- I believe in you,
and I believe in that boy,
and I believe in our daughter.
And that's all.
Justice don't factor into it.
You know that gun
that's in your saddle bag?
- Yes, sir?
- You sleep with it.
[music]
[cocks rifle]
Sheriff: You think they
came to town?
Shea: Where else would they go?
- Well, if they're here they'll
be at the White Elephant.
You're the only one
without a badge.
- Will a badge
make me shoot better?
- Doubtful.
But it'll keep a rope off your
neck if things go sideways.
Raise your right hand.
- Ain't I gotta swear
to something?
- You just did.
- What about me?
- What did you say?
- Me. What about me?
- You just keep your trap shut
'til I tell you to open it.
[music]
[piano playing]
Come on, keep up.
Come here.
[indistinct chatter]
You see any of 'em,
you point 'em out, all right?
All right, any more?
That back table.
Yeah, I know this crew.
Clyde Barker!
What of this business
on the Trinity?
- We were just watering horses
and these immigrants--
[scream]
- Is there any more?
Don't just sit there
shaking, are there any more?
- I ain't armed.
Them immigrants took my guns.
- I can see that.
If you want to
dance with the girls?
Dance with the girls.
If you want to drink at the bar?
Drink at the bar.
But if anybody here
fancy himself a gunman...
You're in the wrong town.
There's only one killer
in Fort Worth and that's me.
[indistinct chatter]
- We're gonna head north
first thing in the morning.
- They ain't ready.
- They'd better get ready.
Because everybody in this town
is gonna be looking for us,
and if they find us
they're gonna hang us
from a fucking tree.
- God damnit.
[music]
- Did you find them?
- We found them.
- And?
- We murdered them.
[sighs]
- Keep 20 feet between you.
At water you wait to cross
until the wagon
in front of you has crossed.
Do not let your children
ride on the buckboard,
they will fall off.
Hold your children
and mind your animals.
- I figure we'll
see you up to the Red.
Ain't got nuthin better to do.
Besides, there's a
few widows among them now.
- You change your minds as well?
- Well, it's the chivalrous
thing to do.
- Earn your keep.
This ain't no travelling
fucking carnival.
- We know what this
is better than you do.
- We know what we're
getting into, Captain.
And we earn our keep.
[music]
- It's time.
- No.
Don't touch me.
- Go help them hold the cattle.
Let me talk with her.
You don't want to go?
- Where are you going, James?
What do you think is waiting
for you out there?
Eden?
Eden is a garden.
There are no gardens here.
- You plant gardens.
You build them.
- No, gardeners plant
gardens, James.
We are not gardeners.
- You'll die here.
- You say that
like it's a warning.
What do I have left
to live for, James?
I have had seven children...
[music]
and they have all ended up
just like this one.
In the dirt I kneel beside.
I am done kneeling.
I am ready to lay down.
- Well, I can't just
leave you here.
- Well, it's a free
country, remember?
It is not your decision to make.
It is mine. And I have made it.
- Goodbye, Claire.
- God damn you, James.
God damn you and your dreams.
[music]
[sobbing]
- Move 'em, Thomas!
[music]
- Let's go.
- You let her stay?
- I didn't let her do anything.
That choice ain't mine.
Don't look back.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'll catch up.
- Stay in the wagon, son.
[music]
- Figure I'd stick around.
Make sure you don't
drown in a river.
- Thought I was too pretty
for you.
- You are, but I'm pretty
short on common sense, so...
- I've painted a picture
of my husband in my mind...
And he don't look like you.
- Well, I'm a cowboy, ma'am.
We don't look
like nobody's husband.
But we're the ones
you think about
when your husband ain't around.
[laughing]
- Come on.
[chuckles]
[sobs]
[crying]
- No way to stop her?
- For what?
I've dug my share alone.
- So have I, and wouldn't
wish it on anybody.
I admire her courage.
- It wasn't courage.
- Yes, it was.
[music]
Elsa: What began as a journey
had become a retreat.
Into the unknown.
We were backing into the abyss,
so worried our
sins would follow us,
we didn't bother
watching where we walked.
And behind us was a cliff.
[music]