I told you not to teach her.
I didn't teach her nuthin'.
This was
our third day here.
The longest we'd stayed
in one place
since the journey started.
One trait all animals
share, people included:
no matter where we are
or where we wish to be,
if we're there
longer than a day,
we try to make a home of it.
But the Plains
are not for home building,
not enough resources.
No shelter...
The Plains are for
the vagabonds, wanderers,
and cowboys.
Their home is a saddle.
The sky is their roof.
The ground is their bed.
What they lack
in material comfort
is regained in the knowledge
that they are always home.
To them the journey
is the destination.
Should they find gold
at the end of the rainbow,
they would leave
it there and seek another,
choosing freedom
over the burden of the pot.
I haven't thought
once of Oregon.
No dreams of the ocean
or snow covered mountains.
I only dream of the journey.
That is all.
No gold for me.
Just the rainbow.
You ready?
Yes sir.
Well, joined up
with some mustangs, I see.
Mustangs are tricky to herd.
This is your world, Sam.
What do you think?
I think we run
the trick out of them.
Carve out that stallion
and get him caught.
They'll follow us
to camp like sheep.
Get up against it
on the other side!
Push in on it.
Whoop at him to keep him moving.
Whoop at him?
Girl's starting
to ride like a Comanche.
That is a compliment, James.
Hup!
Hey!
Come on!
Ya! Hyah!
Hup!
Hyup! Hyup!
Ya! Hyup!
Now you know
how to steal horses.
Hm. Could come
in handy some day.
If you stick with me it will.
Ow... Damn.
Yeah, ha ha.
He says you ride too good
for white man pants.
He's right.
Thigh tore out.
You have another dress.
I'd rather wear a bean sack
than be choked
by a damned dress.
It should be double stitched.
Let me see it.
I hear things are bad
around Laramie.
Yep.
Well, the Arapaho and the Lakota
are pretty fed up
with the thieves
and the government's lies
taking matters
in their own hands.
Who can blame 'em?
They won't be
your worry, though.
The winter is your worry,
and with all those folks afoot,
winter's when you're
passing through.
Well... It's too much.
I think I ought
to take them to Denver.
Denver would be wise.
Let's tend to the horses.
Where they go ain't up to you.
You even ask
them what they want?
Want ain't got
nuthin to do with it.
They won't survive.
Then they don't survive.
That's their choice.
It ain't yours.
You're going anyway.
I don't know where I'm going.
But I ain't going to Denver.
And I sure as hell
ain't going back.
Do you want to go to Denver?
I haven't factored
what I want into this once.
There is a map
in your father's mind,
and no one's gonna stop him
from following it.
No sense in trying.
He said to trust him.
I'm trusting him.
Do you trust him?
Know why he lets you
run wild, don't you?
'Cause he trusts me, too.
'Cause he knows dresses
is your future.
No matter where we go,
you're wearing dresses.
And raising babies,
and sweating over a garden,
and swallowing every dream
you've ever had,
because that's all the world
wants from you.
He may find some place where
we can hold the world off
for a while, but it'll
find us there too,
and bring all their rules
with it.
Indians!
Put your rifles down!
Put 'em down!
Now that's not very friendly.
We don't know they're friends.
If they weren't our friends,
we'd already be dead.
We asked them to come.
They're here to trade.
No matter which way
we go we need provisions.
Wait. Wait!
Are we going
somewhere different?
She will help you
with rip in pants.
They're fixed.
Thank you.
Mm-hm.
Good.
What's that?
That's not for sale.
What is it?
From the Spanish.
You know, they tried
to take our land too.
I ain't taking nuthin',
I'm just passing through.
Our land cannot be taken.
White man thinks he took it.
White man is like the wolf.
He kills everything
until only the wolves are left,
then the wolves kill each other.
Then there is nothing.
And the land is free again.
That sounds about right.
Come up from the west
now heading north.
Got a good look
at the Comanche camp,
decided easy pickins
weren't so easy.
I'll follow 'em.
You get those people out
of here, Shea.
No matter where you take 'em.
Thank you.
Come across any
barbed wire yet?
Never heard of it.
It's twisted steel wire
with little barbs woven into it.
Sharp as a knife's tip.
It is the one fence cattle
will not push through.
They're going to carve this
country into little rectangles.
Then fence them off.
And just like that,
two of our great
pleasures are gone.
Next time I see you
I hope it's in a saloon
and not a gunfight.
If you see me in a saloon,
I followed a cattle thief in it,
a there will damn sure
be a gunfight,
or a hanging, one of the two.
Church picnic then, maybe.
When we meet again,
it will be on a trail,
if there's one left.
I think this is my
last trail, Charlie.
Well, then, I guess
this is adios.
Adios, my friend.
Ow.
They must be tight.
They will stretch.
What is she saying?
I ask why you wear clothes
like a horseman.
She says you are one.
But you are a white woman,
so I don't understand.
No more rip.
He already pay.
Thank you.
Got her some chaps.
It's official.
You're all cowboy now.
I have no home.
Which is to say,
my home is everywhere.
I need you to translate.
We've got eight wagons
to make the trip.
To accommodate your belongings,
only the very young
and old can ride in the wagons.
The rest of you must walk
or sit a horse.
And if you don't
know how to ride,
this ain't the place to learn.
If we're lucky,
and we haven't been yet,
we'll reach Fort Laramie
in October.
That means crossing
South Pass in the snow
or staying
the winter at the fort.
Neither are safe.
Another option is...
We head to Denver.
We can be there in six weeks.
There's a lot of good land
in those valleys.
It's a good place to call home.
No Oregon?
When was this decided?
It wasn't.
Not by me.
We ain't stopping.
The land in Denver is free?
It is not.
Then we are maids and miners
the same we were at home.
But you're alive.
If you want to push on,
we'll push on in the spring.
I'm heading north.
Anyone wants to ride
with me is welcome.
A good remuda of horses
and plenty of beef,
and I can't think of a better
place to learn to ride.
You come with me, I ain't
gonna baby you like he did.
You're gonna work
and you're gonna keep up,
'cause I ain't crossing
the mountains in the snow
and I ain't winterin'
at no fort.
You're gonna
get 'em all killed.
Well, people die
in Denver, too.
It's their choice.
The question is:
what are you going to do
when they make it?
What's it gonna be?
We go with you.
We head out in the morning.
Come ready.
I don't want to leave.
You want to stay.
I don't need to see mountains.
Mountains are worth seeing.
You saying I should go?
I'm saying mountains
are worth seeing.
But you don't need wagons
to see them.
I can take you.
It's settled.
You'll take me then.
Where are you going?
I must offer
your father something.
For what?
For you.
Buffalo.
Everywhere you go,
a blessing follows.
You know how to steal horses.
Now I teach you to hunt..
Lightning with the Yellow Hair.
Up to his shoulders!
Shoot behind his ears!
Hoh...
Eat.
Bite into it.
His strength is your strength.
Lightning with the Yellow Hair.
Horse thief and hunter.
What have you done?
I killed a buffalo.
You packed up?
No, Captain.
Better get to it.
Ain't gonna do it.
I promised I'd see her to Oregon
and that's what I'm gonna do.
Well, free country.
It's gonna be hard enough
with you,
but we ain't got
no chance without you.
I ain't ever
asked you for nothing
but I'm asking you now.
Don't leave us, Captain.
Where you going?
What happened to you.
I killed a buffalo.
We ate its heart
to keep its strength.
Where you going?
Oregon, honey.
With you.
I'm not going to Oregon.
I'm staying here.
What time we pull out?
First light.
No more crack
of 9 am for this outfit.
New sheriff in town ain't
gonna take it anymore, huh.
Not if we're
gonna beat winter.
Let's talk
about your daughter.
Uh oh, she's mine again.
What did she do?
Ran off with that
Comanche boy, killed a buffalo.
Mm-hmm. Came back, her
face covered in blood
'cause I guess they ate half
of it in the field.
Go ahead and laugh.
She is feral.
You always talked
about how you'd raise our boys
to be men
and you started with her.
When we get back
to any form of civilization
I'm gonna have to undo
all of that.
Do you really want to?
Oh, please.
James...
Let me deal with one
dreamer at a time.
You're a dreamer, too.
You wouldn't be with me
if you weren't.
I'm a believer, honey.
There's a difference.
Fair enough.
What is this?
It's for you.
Why is it for me?
Whatcha doin'?
I'm trading these things.
Got no use for 'em anymore.
Elsa.
Stay in here.
You don't want to see this.
Are you aware
of what he's asking?
I'm aware.
Take the horse, daddy.
Young lady,
I will not allow this.
You're not allowing it?
I'm eighteen years old.
I'm allowing it.
You think being
18 makes you a woman?
Law thinks it does.
Don't just stand there.
Stop him.
Shoot him.
Do something!
I understood
my mother's worry.
My choices make no sense
in her world,
where customs and prejudice
rule, where law cannot reach.
There will be customs and
prejudice here too, I'm sure.
But they were born
of this world and belong in it.
To import the traditions
of the place you fled,
the place that failed you,
is to condemn the place you
seek with the same failures.
We saw your daughter.
Cookie thought you might want
a swig or two of this.
I guess she's gonna
fall in love with every man
she meets till
one of them sticks.
Hell, I don't know.
After a night or two
without you,
I bet she'll point that
fast horse north
and catch us
before we leave Kansas.
You don't know my daughter.
So, no Denver for you.
These folks don't
trust me anymore.
And I don't
trust them for making
a right choice for themselves.
Can't lead people I don't trust.
But you trust them.
They came a long way.
I trust their desire
to see it through.
I'm gonna trust you.
I think I can live with that.
But you're gonna
have to lead 'em.
I'll guide 'em and I'll
protect 'em, but you lead them.
I can do that.
I'm gonna leave that with you.
Hell, no.
I'm liable to crawl in
the son of a bitch
trying to figure out
what to do with that girl.
It's looking like you might
have to trust her too, James.
I barely recognize you.
Barely recognize me either.
And I'm happier for it.
What's the worst that
could happen to me, mama?
Mark my words,
you will get hurt.
How many dead lovers
have you laid against?
I've been plenty hurt.
Don't talk to me about love.
You barely understand
the concept.
I worked a sharecropper
farm for three years,
pregnant with you, while your
father lay rotting
in a war prison.
And how old were you then?
Seventeen.
Somehow you knew
love at my age,
but I don't
understand the concept.
It's different.
It's not different.
It's exactly the same.
Here's the difference.
You are my child.
When you fall down, and you will
it is my duty to pick you up.
I can't do that if
I don't know where you are,
and if I don't know
what you've become.
It's not your duty
anymore, mother.
I love you.
But I'm a woman.
I pick myself up.
I'll ride with you to Oregon,
then I know where to come if I
ever need a place to start over.
Or maybe I'll just visit,
bring your grandchildren.
So, um...
Is there...
Some form of ceremony?
No ceremony.
All I ask, have a ceremony.
Say vows before God...
so this at least has a chance.
He saved my life.
Twice.
Saved your husband's life too.
I don't need to ask
God's permission to love him.
God sent him.
How you doing there?
He goes where he wants.
Not where I say.
Horse goes where you look.
You're looking at his head.
He don't know how to go there.
Look up at the cattle.
There you go.
What if I want to look at you?
You can look anywhere you want
now, he knows where he's going.
You just say he goes
where I look,
now you're saying
I can look anywhere.
'Cause he knows
where he's going.
You make no sense.
Pretty good way to travel, huh?
I'm terrified.
Now that you
got the steering figured,
it's time you find yer seat.
How do I find my seat?
Ah!
Stop speaking German.
We're American now.
Is it okay?
The horse?
Your turn next.
No, no, not me.
Yes, you.
You will be a cowboy.
You be the cowboy.
I drive the wagon.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You got to keep your
feet off his flanks.
That's like tickling
you under the arm.
You're gonna run
from the tickle.
So will he.
They're learning.
Yeah, I'm watching the lesson.
And it is skunk ugly.
There's good water up here.
Good place to rest.
Good place to break
that stallion.
What the hell's water got
to do with breaking a horse?
I'll show you
when we get there.
Come on.
Come on. Hup, hup, hup.
Lightning
with the Yellow Hair.
You think you can catch me?
You're going to cook it?
Naw, I'm gonna
make sandals out of it.
You expect us to eat that?
Don't they got
deer where you're from?
Pigs.
Pigs?
A pig is one of the
nastiest animals on this planet.
You are what you eat
and a pig will eat anything.
Like a raccoon.
What does deer eat?
Grass.
What does deer taste like?
It tastes like this place.
And the grass and the dirt
and the water from the creek
over there all mixed together.
You eat dirt?
So do you.
Every meal.
If you really want me to
bake yer biscuit,
think about this: one
day yer gonna be dirt.
Dirt? When will
they be dirt?
Depends on when they
go in the ground, ma'am.
Don't it?
Hey, not telling them don't
mean it ain't true.
Whoa, whoa.
He's broke now.
Naw, he's a couple weeks
from being broke.
He's broke. Run him.
If you want him to give you
his heart, you must run him.
This place is beautiful.
That's where she gets it from.
Where who gets what?
Your sister.
What did she get?
Her spirit.
What's a spirit?
The thing that drives you.
What drives me?
I don't know yet, honey.
What drives Elsa?
Hmmm... The wind.
Ya!
Strong.
Fast...
A good horse for war,
that one.
Where will she live?
My land is with Quanah Parker.
South of the Wichita Mountains.
I will build her a house
if that's what she wants, but...
I think she would rather
chase bandits with me.
She would.
But she's young.
The young change their minds.
What if she changes
her mind about you?
Then I will bring
her back to you.
How will you find me?
White men think the world
is so big
because you fight against it
when you travel.
We move with it.
Like the wolf.
It is small to us.
I will find you.
No chance you'd
want to come to Oregon?
I fought too hard
for what land we have left.
Doubt the fighting's over.
I marry your daughter, but
I still belong to the people
and the people belong
to this land.
We don't dare leave it.
Maybe some day you find
land to belong to,
and you'll know what I mean.
I could make her go with us.
How you gonna do that?
If you tie her to
the back of the wagon
she'll just chew
through that damn rope.
She said she'd ride
with us to Oregon
then come back to him
in the spring.
Let's just hope she falls
in love in Oregon.
With the pattern
she's established
she'll fall in love
again by Nebraska.
It's not funny.
You're the one laughing.
You think our daughter
is the only one out here
falling in love?
I bet there's emigrant
kids fooling around
behind every bush
along this creek.
Ours just doesn't hide it.
If she loves something
she will hold its hand
in front of the whole world.
She gets that from you.
She gets racing up
that hill from me.
But the way she loves...
she gets that from you.
That's why it scares you so bad.
You're not scared?
My fear is selfish.
I just want to be with her.
Yeah.
Know her children
when she has 'em.
But I...
can't alter the course
of her life
just because of how bad
I'm gonna miss her.
She'll change her mind.
How do you say "I love you?"
Kah-Muk-Kun-Tun Nuh.
Kah...
Kah-Mah-Kun-Tun Nuh.
Pretty good.
How do you say my name?
Lightning with
the Yellow Hair...
Teach me more.
Eere.
Huku.
Tsunipuh.
Mura.
At least we have
a path to follow.
How far to Fort Caspar?
Couple a weeks.
We just might pull this off.
We meet here
when the flowers bloom.
When do the flowers bloom?
In your new home it's April.
Here it is June.
I'll meet you here in June.
Sam!
I love you!
I felt their
eyes move over me.
Felt their pity
and disapproval...
And it meant nothing to me.
The only thing that mattered
was riding away,
just as I was riding
away from him.
As I pondered
the new journey before me,
making it back to him.
They watched the tears run
my cheeks and I let them.
I didn't turn my face
or wipe them away.
Tears we can't control,
sobs and weeps
are little surrenders,
and I will surrender
nothing to the pain.
Tears may flow,
but I will not weep.
I am the wife of a warrior now.
Which is to say, I am a warrior.
And warriors don't cry.
We're wasting time.