♪ ♪
Oh, I think you better stay
home from school, sweetie.
I'm not at school?
No, honey. And you should stay home.
Yes, Miss Hoover.
I put some books beside the bed.
Will you test me on them later?
Of course.
And I won't even give you any warning.
I'd like that.
(GRUNTS)
Mm!
(READING):_
HOMER (READING):_
Aw. Ooh!
"Born near Florence,
Italy, in the year 1452,
"Leonardo da Vinci displayed a genius
unmatched in human history."
- _
- Extra, extra!
- Renaissance begins today!
If you're gonna torture someone,
do it quick!
LISA: "As a child,
Lisanardo's gifts were evident"
Hey, sonny boy,
I want you to be just
as talented as her.
I made an Uffizi
on the floor of the Farnese.
Yeah, yeah. That's, uh, that's great.
Lisanardo, did you finish
that drawing of the suspect yet?
Wow.
Gee. That talented kid
is gonna make you a lot of money.
- (CASH REGISTER DINGS)
- We're rich!
Like Marge's tomato sauce.
- (GRUNTS) Not until dinner.
- Oh!
While we're celebrating
Saint Christopher,
he help people who get
lost telling stories
find their way back to the point.
He was canonized by
Gregory the Inconvenient,
who shot him out of the cannon.
This was before they
discovered gunpowder,
so they pulled the cannon
to a cliff and pointed down.
- But then he stayed in.
- _
They had to give him an eviction notice.
LISA: "Florence, at the time,
was at the start of the Renaissance."
- _
- Hey, you can never be too careful.
Aw, don't worry.
Those Dark Ages ain't never coming back.
We got frescoes, we got spinach
and this delicious new
thing called a pizza.
I'm the original Ray.
Well, I am-a Famous Ray.
Basta!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTING)
What about me, Little-a Caesar?
Pizza! Pizza!
Ouchie! Ouchie!
Et tu, Noidus?
LISA:
"Young Lisanardo was soon an apprentice
"to the most famous artist in Florence,
- _
- Andrea del Verrocchio."
- Whoever paints the sweetest cherub
will have the honor of having
my name signed on their work.
That's what great artists do.
Excellent, Barticelli.
Very nice, Dolphatello.
Ralphael, what is this?
My foot hands are brushes.
(LAUGHING)
VEROCCHIO: Jesus.
Your little angels are so
much better than my Jesus.
- Is that wrong?
- (SIGHS) No.
Your genius has shown me
what a failure I am.
I will never paint again.
- _
- (CACOPHONOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
At least there are no geniuses in here.
(PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
What? We can't all be great.
Right, Mediocroto?
Si. On every paper, I get a C.
We don't want you in our class.
You're too much better than us.
Yeah, your gifts come from heaven above.
Uh, that's not true.
♪ ♪
Here's some more talent.
Not a good time.
♪ My gifts came down
from God above ♪
♪ But talent doesn't
bring you love ♪
♪ Although my brilliant
genius shone ♪
♪ My last supper was all alone ♪
♪ In 1470. ♪
(CRYING)
If you can't beat 'em, kill 'em.
Use your genius to
invent weapons of war,
just like I'm gonna
invent the Charleston.
- ♪ ♪
- (SCATS)
Ow, my appendages!
I'll show them all.
I'll show them all in a secret diary
that no one will decipher for 400 years.
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
(SNORES)
(YAWNS)
Oh, what to invent? What to invent?
Portable siege engines.
Flamethrowing mirrors.
A waterpowered stabbing wheel.
Hmm. With these, we could kill
the most evil people in the world:
slightly different Christians.
- MAN: Ow!
- This is your true masterpiece.
Why did you kill us?
Scusi.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ooh.
I'm going to kill you all.
It's my only pathway to pope.
Cardinals suck.
Go, Cubs!
"Lisanardo had learned
"that using her intellect
for war was blasphemy
"but using it for art would
make it endure forever.
- She escaped to France and retired in happiness."
- _
I'll be out in a sec.
Keep the engine running.
(GRUNTING)
Lisanardo, I have many questions.
Why are you hitting yourself?
A nerd says what? And how is it possible
that I am rubber and you are glue,
et cetera, et cetera?
I will answer all questions
just as soon as I finish
my masterpiece, my king.
♪ Mona Lisa, Mona Lisa ♪
♪ Men have named you ♪
♪ You're so like the lady
with the mystic smile. ♪
Well, if this doesn't get
Ron Howard to direct,
- I don't know what will.
- _
Real humble, Lis,
making yourself into Leonardo da Vinci.
Shouldn't you be in school?
Eh, it was art, which I hate.
Well, if you hate
the formal study of art,
you're just like another
artist I'd like to discuss
who also had trouble with the Academy.
You must have a fever,
because that segue was sweaty.
_
Unimaginative and boring. A.
Milhouse, this has nothing
I haven't seen before.
A-plus.
Bart, you've really made me think.
How dare you? F-minus.
(GRUMBLES)
_
(KIDS LAUGH)
(LAUGHS) Oh, a single entendre,
the most complicated joke there is.
Class, settle, please,
because today we have a special treat:
a visit from Paris'
leading Bacchus model.
Sorry I'm late. As a supermodel,
I have to be eating
and drinking all day.
(BURPS)
You prefer robe open or robe off?
Uh, just cover your privates
with this walnut shell.
Whoa, so roomy.
Mm-hmm...
Gah! That looks nothing like him.
And it shouldn't.
We're making the art that we feel
because we can't compete with a camera,
especially modern compact cameras.
Please hold still for 17 hours.
Since you refuse
to paint the still life,
you'll become the still life.
Foie gras!
_
("ORPHEUS IN THE UNDERWORLD:
CAN CAN" PLAYING)
This epoque just gets beller and beller.
Who is that kid?
I am Toulouse-Moetrec,
the chronicler of the demimonde.
(CHUCKLES)
I keep liquor in my cane.
Not very efficient. Really not.
ROOSTER: Coq au vin, au vin!
This is the greatest
thing I've ever seen,
and I have seen, like, five things!
You, my friend. You are a genius!
Maybe we should stop slavishly
following the teacher
and use our own minds
to slavishly follow Bart.
To the easels.
All right,
time to do my first self-portrait.
Time to look in a mirror
for the first time in my life.
I can only assume that I am beautiful.
All right, here we go.
Looking now.
(SCREAMS)
(CHUCKLES): Oh, don't worry, sir.
You won't see anything here
that'll encourage debate,
provoke thought or be out of
place in a dentist's office.
Ah, well, I'm sure this will have
a definite je ne sais quoi?!
Ugh! Oh!
The emperor is coming here
to look at this artwork today.
His Majesty will feed
us to the guillotine!
That hasn't been used in years.
No one even remembers how to work it.
Pull up, let go. How hard can that be?
(GROANS)
Mon cher, le superintendent,
which of our works will you be
entering into the royal Salon?
None. You are all refusés.
What about our student loans?
Oh, they'll be refunded.
We are not barbarians.
I mean, uh, come on.
Oh, if only we could get our
art in front of the emperor.
Monarchs love challenges
to the established order.
No, no. But there is one thing
the emperor loves more than anything.
- France?
- No, he hates France.
But he loves cheese.
Look who he appointed mayor of Toulon.
♪ ♪
_
- Hmm.
- Do we have a winner?
Keep your pants on, Moulin Huge.
There are 44 more galleries
of mediocre art to judge.
What is that cheese doing?
Oh, you know French cheese. Very runny.
I warned them not to
make cheese into wheels.
Cubes were fine.
I get motion sickness,
and I'm lactose intolerant.
Hurry. He's biting his way in!
What the...
Aw, once again,
I have just cheese that is not cheese.
Your Majesty, if you'll take a seat,
we'll show you something really special,
a transformation of art
from a rote copying of nature
into the experiences, ideas,
and mind of the artist.
You had me at "take a seat."
I don't know art,
but I know what I like.
And I like eating and
not looking at art.
I hereby award you the Royal Medallion.
(CHUCKLES) Congratulations
on your discerning eye,
Your Majesty. I love this pupil.
Is this not the student that you
expelled from the royal salon?
Well, I... Uh, that is, I, uh...
Just pretend I'm not here.
Uh, sir, is your tongue
sticking out because you're dead
or because you're mad at me?
Uh, little of both.
Yeah. (EXHALES)
("LA MARSEILLAISE" PLAYING)
_
Oh, sure, Maggie. That's easy.
Renaissance artists love to
put babies in their paintings,
especially baby angels.
Let's just not think about
why there were so many babies
in heaven, shall we?
("RIDE OF THE VALKYRIES" PLAYING)
Hey!
_
Damn it!
So, telling stories about art, huh?
Do they have one about a fat guy
whose wife is too good for him?
Stupid fat guy.
Bet he doesn't even
know what's going on.
Well, Dad, have you ever heard
of Diego Rivera and Frida Kahlo?
(SCOFFS) Lisa, I haven't even heard
of Jackson Pollock and Lee Krasner.
Well, Diego and Frida
were married in 1929.
- ♪ ♪
- _
I now pronounce you esposo and esposa.
You may now beso quite mucho.
Mwah!
(CHEERING)
Spanish for "Best wishes!"
Spanish for "Congratulations!"
Spanish for "¡Muy bueno!"
Amigos, familia,
and El Barto.
♪ Barto, El Barto ♪
♪ The fox so cunning and free. ♪
The mysterious El Barto.
Do you know nobleman Don Bartholomew?
He lives in that house you
come out of every night.
¡Ay, caramba!
Gosh, quite the swordsman.
Slashed my shirt,
did not even nick me.
Move along, folks!
It's gonna take me a while to bleed out.
(GROANS, CHUCKLES) That's clever...
a "B." (EXHALES)
I know I speak for my wife, Frida Kahlo,
when I say I couldn't
imagine life without you.
But I also speak for my wife,
Frida Kahlo,
when I say we leave
for New York tomorrow!
You never asked me!
Don't worry. As a woman,
you will be treated with
much more respect in America.
_
Diego, I know you are a socialist,
whilst I am a lion of capitalism.
Yes, we hate the capitalists.
Right now,
a young socialist is being born
who will take them down.
Mr. Bernie Sanders.
I hope he's quick about it.
Getting a cootie shot should
not cost your lunch money.
And if you don't listen to me,
listen to the Bernie Babies.
What? Everybody's got goons.
I disavow that and welcome it.
Señor Rockefeller,
what is it you are
looking for from Diego?
Frida, please! I'm so sorry.
My wife does not understand
these discussions.
I understand that he
is paying you $21,000
for a mural for his
new Rockefeller Center
with the theme "man at the crossroads."
$21,000.
Do you know what that
is in today's money?
$21,000.
(WHOOPS)
This entire area will be your canvas.
(GASPS) I will need very tiny brushes,
a magnifying glass
and a huge bottle of tequila.
No worm.
A snake.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) You
drive a hard bargain,
but this is just a model.
The real Rockefeller Center
will be 66 stories high.
And every Christmas,
we will kill and decorate a giant tree
as a warning to the other trees.
(GRUMBLES)
Oh, Frida. Let us celebrate our triumph
with some snuggle-issimo.
- No.
- (GASPS) What's wrong, my dear?
Is your unibrow hurting?
You are selling out, my love.
_
I am not selling out!
I am doing this mural
for the little guy!
People like him!
Why are you washing windows at night?
Who said I was washing windows?
As for you, squander your gift,
spit on your talent.
- I am glad we are in agreement.
- (HUFFS)
But what will I do while
you work on your mural?
Paint a happy self-portrait,
smiling ear to ear,
not a care in the world.
That's not who I am, Diego!
I love you, too.
Going to the bar!
Paint. Paint your misery.
Also, leave. Leave your husband.
Which one of you is the angel?
- We both are.
That's how mad you're feeling.
Oh.
Back to Heaven!
_
Buenas noches, darling.
What a crazy night I had.
Now we got to get our
stories straight about Zeppo.
It was an accident, okay?
(HONKS)
Ah...
Starting a new painting?
Yes. I am painting my feelings.
Oh! Oh!
Wow. So strong, so brave,
so true to herself.
- Mm...
- (GROANS)
My darling,
I am not half the artist you are.
Diego, what are you saying?
I am saying I've underestimated
you all this time.
You are a genius!
From now on, I will show my awe of you
by sleeping with other women.
Starting an hour ago.
And I will sleep with other
women starting two hours ago.
I'm so glad I don't hear what you say.
But I will do something I have
not done in our entire marriage:
what you want.
Well, actions speak louder than words.
No. Unless the action is the
demolition of a big building,
words are usually louder.
Everything is a fight.
I completely disagree.
But just wait till you see what I do.
You'll be pleased with what I do not do,
and you will love what I do do.
Good night!
(GRUMBLES)
Welcome to Rockefeller Center,
a temple of capitalism.
To find a taller building,
you'd have to walk a full seven blocks.
(CHUCKLES): Long blocks.
With people bumping you.
Enough already.
While the art is still deco, okay?
For you, my darling.
Man at the Crossroads.
Rich people. Yes, excellent.
The cosmos. Yes, makes sense.
A worker.
Well, I suppose it couldn't be helped.
Fascist army.
Always welcome in any lobby.
Hmm. Who's that fellow?
With the beard and the Bolshevik smile.
That is the founder
of Soviet Russia, Lenin.
But-but-but he's a communist.
Oh, he just attended
a couple of meetings.
I can't have a communist
in my colossus of capitalism.
Paint over it.
No!
Then you will lose your commission,
and I won't let you be
the model for Atlas.
Hmm...
I don't care.
There is one person
I want to be proud of me,
no matter what.
(GASPS) Oh, my darling.
Release the hounds.
(BARKING IN DISTANCE)
They're on the 66th floor, sir.
They should be here in about 25 minutes.
(BARKING CONTINUES)
But-but-but why is it
just sitting there?
I, uh... I think they may be eating
the elevator operator, sir.
Let us leave, my darling,
with our scruples intact.
Push the owner's button.
- But...
- I said push it.
Aah!
Ironically, in time,
Frida became more famous than Diego,
an icon for brilliant
female artists everywhere.
This is really, really good.
If I play my cards right,
I will direct a Rick and Morty.
♪ ♪
All right, now it's time for
the story of Vincent van Moe.
(CHUCKLES) ♪ Bar-ry, bar-ry night ♪
♪ Squeeze your bar
rag clean and dry ♪
♪ For the last time,
say there's no Wi-Fi ♪
♪ With eyes that know
the darkness of my soul ♪
(CRIES)
♪ Serving them the dregs ♪
♪ Something's growing ♪
♪ On my eggs ♪
♪ Add tap water to the kegs ♪
♪ And search the bushes
for my missing ear ♪
♪ Now the show is done ♪
♪ Except the part ♪
♪ Where the chick goes "Shh!" ♪
♪ But no one ever obeys her ♪
♪ 'Cause, really,
what's she shushing for? ♪
This one ain't so great.
♪ I will not listen ♪
♪ She's not the boss of me ♪
♪ And she will never be. ♪
(CRYING)
End the credits!
Shh!
- synced and corrected by sot26 -
www.addic7ed.com