D'oh!
_
♪ Gather round, me buckos ♪
♪ A story I will tell ♪
♪ Of a woman named Lily ♪
♪ Who cast quite a spell ♪
♪ It started back in Britain ♪
♪ It started in a pub... ♪
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTING)
- She's mine.
- It's my birthday.
She's mine.
(BAGPIPES HONKING)
I can't be the cause of this.
- I'm leaving.
- MAN: Your fault!
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
♪ We were fighting over Lily
using knife, fork and club. ♪
That's all I got.
The rest will be spoken word.
(GUITAR PLAYS MELODY)
Lily gets why we're here.
Life is supposed to be fun.
I loved her. We all loved her.
The way gophers love that sweet,
sweet poison.
Every man wanted her for the
greatest reason there is.
Lily could make life fun.
♪ ♪
Now everyone,
hold hands with a stranger.
- Oh, pleased to meet you.
- (OVERLAPPING GREETINGS)
MAN: How delightful.
- ♪ ♪
- _
Lily! (GIGGLING)
- MAN: Good one, Lily.
- (LAUGHTER, APPLAUSE)
(CLOCK CHIMING)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- (CHEERING)
MAN: Thanks, Lily!
Pub's back open!
But like The Beatles and balmy weather,
she was too hot for England to handle.
I find you far too alluring
for the average Englishman
and banish you to Britain's
penal colony, America.
This is your captain speaking.
- Will you date me?
- Sorry. No.
Uh, okay. I'm experiencing
some emotional turbulence.
My life is pathetic.
Going back and forth, back and forth.
(CRYING): I don't want to live anymore.
WILLIE: Even the most glamorous
movie stars of Hollywood bored her.
Oh, farewell, Leo. You're a lovely boy,
but my heart isn't some CGI
bear for you to conquer.
But I've completely
opened myself up to you.
I even admitted I play the
same guy in every role.
Marry me!
Oh, maybe I should go back to England.
No. Give this country a chance.
Don't judge us by Hollywood.
All right, but I'm leaving now, dear.
You'll have to content yourself
with generic supermodels, I'm afraid.
Nothing ever works out for me.
- WILLIE: She needed to get away.
- _
Somewhere. Anywhere.
- So she threw a dart.
- _
Hmm, what's next?
♪ ♪
_
WILLIE: So she headed to Springfield,
little knowing that its men
had the lowest testosterone,
not counting the Columbia
University football team.
Lily wanted peace,
but the best-laid plans...
(BABBLES)
Can't understand me? Too bad.
- I'm your narrator.
- _
Do not tell me...
(BABBLING)
Hmm.
The only thing worse
than when you guys yap
is you sitting here
all quiet and sullen.
I ain't sullen, I'm lachrymose.
Oh, why did I give him that
stupid word-a-day calendar?
Hmm. Impulsinicity?
Uh, excuse me, there, lady,
but, uh, this is a man's bar.
And I'd like a man's drink.
Bourbon, neat, in a dirty glass.
You got it. Whoa.
Just got to look up what "neat" means.
I just don't understand.
Understand what?
What's a pub without a song?
♪ At the pub at the crossroads,
there's whiskey and beer... ♪
There are songs about drinking?
♪ There's brandy,
strong cognac that's aging for years ♪
♪ But for killing the thirst
and for easing the gout ♪
♪ There's nothing at all
beats a pint of good stout ♪
♪ Pint of good stout. ♪
Oh, what's that I hear you asking?
Where are the Simpsons?
Haven't you heard enough
about the bloody Simpsons
to last a thousand lifetimes?
Well, I guess not.
So, Homer is about to receive
an unpleasant surprise.
What a great day.
I've never been so happy.
Nothing can ruin it. Nothing.
What? Where you going?
On our vacation, remember?
My aunt's letting us use
her home at the Vineyard
for three weeks, rent-free.
How come I'm not coming?
Well, that was her one condition.
D'oh!
Aw, I'm gonna miss you all so much.
Well, at least I'll have the dog.
Sorry, Dad.
We put the pets with Mr. Flanders
because, well,
we knew he'd take care of them.
(WHISTLING)
- Come to papa.
- (BARKING, MEOWING)
(GRUNTS) Good, good.
Make-believe you love him.
- Flanders, I love you!
- D'oh!
We're staying at my Aunt
Edith's house at Hyannibunkport.
It's south of Squibagansett,
east of Codtucket,
next to Little Crabkill Bog.
Those are great names.
You'll never want to leave.
I'm gonna keep you in my
sight as long as I can.
- ♪
♪
- (THUNDER RUMBLES)
(HORN HONKING)
We love you! Stop following!
(FADING): Okay.
(HORN HONKS)
(BUZZING)
♪ ...drink it up,
then throw me out the door ♪
♪ I've traveled in England ♪
♪ I've traveled in France ♪
♪ At a hint of good music,
I'll sing or I'll dance ♪
♪ So hear me, then, mister,
and pour me one more... ♪
Gentlemen...
♪ If I can't drink it up,
then throw me out the door. ♪
(LAUGHTER)
You have to seize life
and relish every minute.
Eliminate all sorrow.
Open a bloody window.
♪ Hallelujah. ♪
Okay, okay, that's enough of that.
(SATANIC MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Hallelujah. ♪
- ♪ Ha... ♪
- (SATANIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Hey, Lily, you like suspenders?
'Cause I got them.
Well, I hope you don't mind
if I give them a wee snap.
- (LAUGHS SOFTLY)
- Ooh! Intimacy.
Lily, you've transformed this
dump into a joint. Bless you.
(CRYING)
(MOANS SADLY)
- ♪ ♪
- (GASPS)
(SIGHS)
Who are you?
- Homer Simpson.
- You know, Homer,
I've never met a man who didn't
offer me his chair or his beer.
- You have now.
- So, tell me,
what's wrong with you?
Mm, it's personal.
Tell me. Maybe I can lighten your load.
- My family left me for three weeks.
- No.
The dog and cat are with Flanders.
Oh!
I'm alone. I don't know what to do.
You have to have a good
time for their sake,
because if you don't,
they'll feel guilty
and never forgive you.
And you'll never forgive them,
because they're causing you the misery.
And you'll all be
buried in dirty laundry
with squealing kids for
the rest of your days.
Wow. Wow.
You're the smartest woman
I've ever met in my life.
Except one.
Shut the window!
But then everything smells like you.
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
- Take that.
(PHONE RINGING)
_
- _
- ♪ Anticipation ♪
♪ Anticipation is making me late... ♪
Welcome to our tour of the Vineyard.
This is where Steven
Spielberg shot Jaws.
That's the end of our tour.
Now, my aunt's house
is only eight miles away.
But we just have to
make it before sundown.
_
Uh, Mom,
I think you've gone off the road.
Whoa, watch out for that deer!
(GASPS)
- That was close.
- (SHOUTS) More deer!
(THUDDING, TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIGHS) We're here.
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
- (GROANS)
- (LAUGHTER)
- CARL: Your turn, Lily.
(CLICKING, BEEPING)
- (FANFARE PLAYS)
- _
(MOANS)
I miss them. I miss them.
It's been so long. No one to comfort me.
Put your mobile away,
because I'm gonna sing in German.
♪ Vor der Kaserne ♪
♪ Vor dem grossen Tor ♪
♪ Stand eine Laterne ♪
♪ Und steht sie noch davor... ♪
This is like that beautiful
scene in Sound of Music
when all the Nazis sang good night.
♪ Wie einst Lili Marleen ♪
♪ Wie einst ♪
♪ Lili Marleen. ♪
If you're done singing,
can we turn up the game?
(GASPS, CRIES)
- (CRYING)
- What's wrong, lady?
We miss you inside.
A good bloke who never had a break,
and now has a broken spirit.
He's lost and lonely,
and really doesn't give a fig about me.
- I'm in love.
- I love him, too.
(BOTH SIGH)
Okay. The sun is shining.
(EXHALES) I can finally read my book.
- _
- (SEABIRD CHIRPING)
Hello, nature. Time to meet your death.
♪ ♪
(GASPS) Bart, those are tick bites!
You'll get Lyme disease.
Why didn't somebody warn me?
_
- (MARGE GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
_
Get me a priest.
Mom, I always liked you.
Oh, honey, try to relax.
Watch Itchy & Scratchy!
I am itchy and scratchy.
Meanwhile, Homer little dreamed that...
Willie! Do you think it would
kill you to rake and talk?
Would you rather I tell the story
about what's under
these leaves and dirt?
- _
- (SKINNER GROANS)
Oh. No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Carry on.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Getting back, Lily continued to light up
all the men's lives, except Homer's.
BOTH: Lily!
Gentlemen.
I made you all picnic lunches.
- Yeah!
- Wow!
- It's British food.
- BOTH: Oh...
Post-1990 British food.
BOTH: Yes!
♪ ♪
Smithers, that woman has captivated me,
which, if memory serves,
is an early state of physical arousal.
Sir, we've been through this before
with several women and
one very shapely tree.
I feel a tingle I haven't felt
since they took the
cocaine out of Coca-Cola.
I must woo her.
And Simpson's my way in.
Have him ask her on a date on my boat
which will actually be a date with me.
But, sir,
why not have me ask her directly?
(LAUGHS) As if I could trust you
to keep your hands off a lady.
(FORCED CHUCKLE)
How well you know me, sir.
♪ ♪
HOMER: Uh-oh.
Very good, Maggie!
Now we can cook them. Num-num!
(HORN BLARES)
Who are all those people?
It's the weekenders from Falmouth.
(HORN BLARES)
It's almost here.
And raise the prices...
...now!
Clam strips and beer!
MAN: Black Dog mousepads!
- MAN 2: Over here!
- MAN 3: T-shirts!
MAN 4: CDs by James Taylor's brother!
- Hyah!
ALL: Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
That's it! We're going home.
Everyone was innocently
falling into Burns's trap.
And trouble brewed as Lily
offered a perverse prayer.
- ♪
♪
- (SEABIRD SCREECHING)
(BELL DINGS)
LILY: Forgive me, Lord.
I must have Homer.
Please let me win him, even briefly.
It would be like having
a lover and a child
at the same time.
Hey, Lily. How you doin'?
Homer! I'm so glad you
asked me to meet you here.
Thanks, I'm glad you feel that way.
But there's something I didn't tell you.
Uh... you're on a date with my boss.
That's my boat.
♪ ♪
My name is Montgomery Burns.
I'm the richest and therefore
most attractive man in town.
Okay, see ya.
Wait, wait, wait, Mr. Burns!
Surely a venerable
gentleman such as yourself
would know that I need a chaperone.
Of course. Simpson, join us.
Smithers, cue my weapon of woo.
♪ ♪
I know a shortcut.
HOMER: Why am I staring at her?
I'll make my eyes look
at something else.
Oh, my God.
I'm smiling back.
I hope you enjoyed your dinner.
(CHUCKLES)
And just wait till we get to dessert.
You make me feel like I'm having dinner
with a James Bond villain.
(CHUCKLES)
She gets me.
Now, wink for me, Smithers.
(CHUCKLING)
(SIGHS) What am I doing here?
HOMER: What have I done
to this wonderful woman?
How can I make it up to her?
I'm sorry.
Why did you bring me here?
Fear of unemployment.
Um, let's just stay through dessert.
Look at me! I'm Gypsy Rose Lee!
You and me and my
cardiologist make three!
Sorry, I have to leave right now.
Oh. But why?
I just spilled a glass
of wine on myself.
Also, this bottle.
Homer, let's go.
Whoa.
That was awful.
There's some people that make you feel
being lonely isn't so bad.
And there are people that make you
never want to be lonely again.
(LAUGHS) I hear ya.
And I almost understand ya.
Thank God you were there to save me.
That's what I'm best at:
saving people from
things I get them into.
(GIGGLES) You've got a little cake
on the corner of your mouth.
Oh, I do? Where?
- Just here.
- There?
- Just there.
- Oh... Where?
- Right there?
- Just... You're missing it.
- There?
- Just to the...
- Oh, just let me do it.
- Okay.
You can stop now.
Uh... I meant go slow.
Uh, wait a minute, wait.
While you're there,
could you get the upper lip?
(LAUGHS SOFTLY) Oh, my God,
what am I going to do with you?
Please, nothing.
I'm taking you home now.
♪ ♪
Well, aren't you going to walk me in?
(WHIMPERS)
Look, Lily.
You're the most... Um...
Finish that thought.
You're the most anything of any woman
I've ever known except for my wife.
Who I loved... I mean love!
I said "love!"
- Oh, that's beautiful.
- Thank you.
But give me one damn
proper kiss goodbye.
No.
♪ ♪
(HOMER WHIMPERING)
(MOANING)
No. No!
This is good,
but is it worth burning in hell forever?
We'll see each other in our dreams,
whether you like it or not.
You stay out of my dreams!
All my stuff's in there!
Gotta stay awake.
If I dream of Lily, it's all over.
Gotta stay awake. Gotta stay awake.
Must not dream.
Oh, no.
(SNORES)
♪ ♪
(GIGGLES)
You've got a little cake on
the corner of your mouth.
- Homer? Homer?
- (MUTTERS) She's here.
She's here and God help me,
- I'm glad.
- Homer.
- Marge!
- Surprise!
We came back early.
Oh, thank God. Oh, thank God!
I'll never let you go a...
(PHONE VIBRATES)
Who's calling you so late?
Telemarketer.
Gotta take it.
Those people are so sensitive.
- Hello?
- (FALSETTO): Wrong number!
- Homer?
- Damn it!
- I need to see you now, Homer.
- (WHIMPERS)
You know the address.
Lovers Lane, just off Fidelity Avenue.
Listen. I have to tell you right now
I can never see you again.
Can you tell me in person?
Great idea.
Keep me on the line.
I'll guide you here.
Ooh...
You realize nothing's gonna happen.
Of course.
♪ I promise you
chocolate and kisses ♪
♪ Martinis with lemon drops... ♪
♪ ♪
No, feet! No!
(SIGHS)
♪ I just woke up ♪
♪ And made you pork chops... ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
- ♪ La, la, la ♪
- MARGE: ♪ La, la, la ♪
- LILY: ♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la... ♪
Pork chops!
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la. ♪
You're home.
Yes, I am.
And I'll never leave you.
There might be frequent interruptions.
I may stop at Moe's,
I may be watching the hot dogs spin
at the movie theater,
or I may be picking a flower for you...
but I will never, ever leave you.
Aw, Homie.
(SOBBING)
ANNOUNCER: Now boarding,
non-stop Springfield to London.
Sorry, lady.
How was America, dear?
There's nothing there for me.
It's big, full of fried food,
and heartbreaking...
and that's just one man.
There'll never be another like him.
_
Buy you a drink, sweetheart?
No.
- Fancy a drink?
- No, thank you.
Would you get... No.
No. No thanks.
- Get off.
- BRITISH MAN: Buy you a corndog?
(GASPS) Yes! But first, are you married?
And would you shave off the mustache?
Yes, and immediately.
♪ ♪
_
- synced and corrected by sot26 -
www.addic7ed.com
Shh!