Kota.
In the area of education this city
has created an identity for itself..
..nationally as well as internationally.
And right from the start,
Maheshwari classes..
..has been carrying the banner
of success on this path to victory.
Within a span of 30 years
Maheshwari classes has
embarked upon a mission..
..that envisions the
whole world of education..
..with services from standard
eighth till university.
In this pursuit Maheshwari classes
has to give credit to its team..
..teaching methodology
and student-centric approach.
We are now catering to
the need of the students..
..throughout their academic cycle..
..till their step into
their professional life.
The complete educational hub.
The journey of thousand
miles begins with a single step.
The credit for having come this
far after starting with one classroom..
..goes only to our students.
Gyan Mittal.
All India Rank one JEE Advanced,
listen to his own words
All the credit for my success
goes to Maheshwari classes.
It is the best coaching for IIT JEE.
Year after year the
best results come from here.
Not only in JEE, but also in NEET,
Olympiad, KVPY, NTSE and other exams.
Maheshwari classes,
We will make a change together.
Kota.
In the area of education this
city has made a name for itself..
..nationally as well as internationally.
And right from the start,
Maheshwari classes..
..has been carrying the banner
of success on this path to victory.
Within a span of 30 years
Maheshwari classes has embarked..
It's not as though we were unaware, sir.
We even sought admissions
for coaching in April..
..but that was in Itarsi. Local.
Vaibhav was doing very
well even over there.
He was amongst the top three..
..but when the All India
test series took place in November..
..that's when our eyes opened.
Sir, Vaibhav's friend
Piyush is your student.
He lagged behind Vaibhav in school.
You can confirm from him.
Even he shot ahead of Vaibhav...
Sir, Vaibhav is a
very hardworking student.
He even studies a lot but
Itarsi lacks the facilities of Kota.
Only one small institute exists there.
Only 'Success' and 'Ace' are small.
Goel-classes has 400 students this year.
Yes, sir. My Vaibhav
was attending Goel classes.
He was attending Goel?
- Yes.
Then he must be pretty
weak in chemistry.
He won't be able to cover it alone.
No, sir. The boy is smart.
He scored 90 percent in high school.
Trust me sir, he will be able to follow.
- No. He won't.
Pan India more than 7 lakh students score
90 percent in 10th grade.
More than 2 lakhs in CBSE alone.
And how many seats do they have in IIT?
5273 only.
If only the students with over 90
percent appear for IIT..
..even then 99 percent of those
won't make it.
Sir, the Minister forwarded this letter.
He even called me.
That's why I am
refusing in person.
Look, I won't make tall promises
but it would be beneficial to Vaibhav..
..to join us when the
12th grade batches start in April.
With all the others.
Jai Shree Krishna
Could you talk to Piyush?
We should have taken
admissions back then only.
Both of you would have been together.
Anyways, if not here then maybe
somewhere else.
But nowadays this
is the number one.
You better focus on driving
Smartass.
Where in Talwandi? 'Prodigy?'
How long have you been in Kota, brother?
Son, I've been in Kota since
the time it used to be a city, not a factory.
Back then coaching classes
did not have any uniforms..
..and this environment was confined
to a small locality of 'Vigyan Nagar.
What an apt name! Ain't it, sir?
Yes, some Agarwal classes used to be there.
Some? There was a time
when Mr.Agarwal used to rule, sir.
There may be many dons today,
but he is the only true Godfather.
This Jurassic park was established by him.
His name may not be Corleone
but he is Godfather to all.
He is called the
Stephen Hawkins of Kota.
Not Hawkins. Hawking.
Huh?
- Hawking. King.
Yes, yes. He is the king.
His own children
may not have made it to IIT..
..but he has got thousands
of others through.
Though he couldn't walk by himself but
has helped lakhs run their household.
Sir, its because of him every
other house in the city has a PG..
..and a mess at every corner.
And it has to be.
As every year more than 2 lakh
students come here.
Toss a stone blindly..
..it's bound to hit a student.
Hey! But don't toss one.
This is not a city, sir.
But rather a very big hostel.
Here the battle is not whether
an institute could post the solutions or not
But instead,
which institute did it first.
Everyone here is crazy, sir.
Everywhere there is discourse..
..about which institute
charged fees from the topper..
..which institute really educated him..
..and which one simply bought off his rank.
Which teacher was poached by whom?
Which faculty quit to
start on his own?
And who in turn
is quitting his institute?
Study a little!
Focus on your driving, brother.
It is a kind of 'Big Boss' running here.
Do you watch Big boss?
- Yes, I do.
Nobody watches it here.
This is the only city in India..
..where Nokia dominates Samsung.
If I must add, sir..
..all the students who come here
may not get selected..
..but a student
who doesn't get selected from here..
..was never meant to be.
Get your work done.
I'll wait.
Yes. It's done, sir.
Sure?
We will get it done, sir.
Be confident. My brother-in-law
started this institute with just one room.
And look at it today.
that's all impressive
but will he be able to manage on his own?
Why not? He scored 90 percent
in the boards. That is not a joke.
The boy is sharp .
But I heard IIT has only 5273 seats. So..
But sir, you only need one.
Vaibhav.
Just because he is willing to enroll..
..doesn't necessarily mean that you
have to accept.
Better stay at home and prepare this year..
..and aim for
Maheshwari in 12th grade.
Dad, even if I have to take admission
in Maheshwari for the 12th grade..
..let me study in here only.
I can't do it at home.
Enroll him and hand him the material.
Which batch?
- IIT JEE A10.
A10?
How many batches do you have in all?
- Only ten, sir.
We don't have too many batches.
Teach less but teach well!!
Dad, Piyush was telling me that
lower batches don't get any attention.
Says who?
Do we give attention or not?
- We do, sir.
I myself was in A7.
- He was in A7.
Sir, charge the entire fees if you wish
but please ensure a better batch.
Look, sir.
Entire fees for 2 years will be charged anyways.
..but he will still be in batch A10.
It's brother-in-law's policy.
But this batch won't be permanent.
Reshuffling tests will
take place after two months..
..and you will do well in it.
That's it. Batch changed.
This is your material.
Uniforms are not in stock.
You will get it by day after tomorrow.
And you have a choice of three schools.
You can enroll yourself in any.
Which of these is a good school?
How does it matter?
He doesn't have to attend.
We have a tie-up with all three.
Okay. I'll go and put this away.
- Yes.
Hello.
Yes, Piyush.
Yes. Finally you found
the time to call me.
This is Vaibhav.
Yes.
This is my Kota number. Save it.
Yes. Today.
No, not in Maheshwari. Prodigy.
Why thank God?
Are you crazy?
It's a good thing they
teach so much at Maheshwari.
Yes.
The lady who kept me as PG is nice.
She is very nice.
She told me I'm
like her son Bunty.
Oh, never mind that. Let's meet.
Once studies begin I won't
be able to come to Vigyan Nagar.
Shall I come?
Oh, I see.
Tomorrow then?
Ok. Let me know if you don't have
extra classes tomorrow. Will meet.
Hello?
May I come in?
I am Meena. Prodigy. A5.
You've seen the storeroom downstairs?
- Yes.
That's my room.
- I see.
You left the RO turned
on downstairs. What..?
Yes.
There was no water,
so I guess I left it turned on. Sorry.
Remove the plug after you use it.
Else aunty gets very upset.
Oh!
Is aunty very strict?
She spoke to me very
sweetly this morning.
She is bound to speak nicely
in front of parents.
She should have the guts to speak nicely
once they've left. Right?
I have a two way socket.
You can have it.
Socket. Why?
When your roommate comes
he will fight every night..
..for phone charging.
There is only one plug.
No, I will stay here by myself.
All alone?
Ya.
The rent will be quite a bit.
Why didn't you go to Maheshwari
if you have the resources?
It is not so easy to
get admission in Maheshwari.
Isn't it? I got admitted.
In Maheshwari?
- Yes.
Then why...
The fee here is far lower
and also they teach in Hindi.
Also,  Jeetu Bhaiya is here.
Jeetu Bhaiya?
How come you don't know Jeetu Bhaiya?
By which route did you come?
His hoardings are all over the place.
He is the best teacher
of physics in Kota..
..and number three at Unacademy.
Unacademy?
It is India's biggest education ape.
Ape?
You don't know ape?
Then how will you make it through to IIT?
You know the tiny boxes in mobiles.
If you send something..
Oh! App.
Yes. Ape.  Jeetu Bhaiya has uploaded
the entire syllabus of JEE on it.
You can study anytime you wish.
Even teachers learn from it.
Frankly, just that Jeetu Bhaiya
isn't contesting the elections..
..else he would have been
the best candidate.
So you are Jeetu Bhaiya's fan?
- Absolutely.
That man is deserving of fans.
He solves papers on International
physics to the clock.
All the best physics teachers in India..
..send their problem books to him to review.
His salary is more
than 10 to the power of 7.
Yet he is cheerful,
affable and light-hearted.
Just a minute. Just a minute.
Water did not come out of the RO.
Then how did you drink?
This is Uday's room.
He is from Udaipur but
he told aunty he is from Patna.
Why?
That I don't know.
Didn't you ask?
Why would I ask!
It's not a syllabus question.
'One said and the other agreed.
Nanak says both are wise.'
Feel free to keep fruits, veggies,
yogurt, water, anything in it.
He has made it a public fridge.
Isn't Uday over here?
He mostly stays at Laxmi PG,
with lady Shivangi.
Very nice lady.
She's Uday's friend but
has more affection for me.
Uday studies with her all day long.
He studies so much he
doesn't even attend classes.
I too want to study that much.
Meena.
You were inside?
Call your mother a lady. I am a girl.
Hi.
- Hi. I'm...
Vaibhav. From Itarsi.
Joined Prodigy.
You are like a son to aunty, right?
Voices from the corridor
are audible here.
Even the sounds from here
are audible downstairs.
I am Shivangi. Uday's girlfriend
but have told aunty that I am his cousin.
The fridge may be public, I'm not.
So do come, fetch water and leave.
There is no need for small talk..
..unless you have doubts
in physics and chemistry.
And that too only if Meena
is unable to clear it.
Doubt solving expert. The standard
rate is two puffs for 30 minutes..
..and three puffs for one hour.
Only physics and chemistry?
You must be weak in math.
I was strongest in math.
It's bio that I was weak in..
..but I am doing medical
because dad is an IITian.
Your dad is an IITian?
Even dads are IITians?
That's great!
And he wants you to get into medicine.
There should be variety in the family.
Correct.
IITian thinks correctly.
- Variety my foot!
Dad is an IITian,
that's why he knows the truth about IIT.
He can't send his only daughter
amidst the lusting engineers..
..who are brimming with testosterone.
He won't be able to endure the meiosis.
I wore your bermudas. I hope it is okay.
My clothes are in the wash.
It is okay. I shall wear yours someday.
Actually, they will suit you.
The mess starts at 7:30.
Go early to eat..
..else cheese will be gone
leaving only spinach in the curry.
Let's go together.
No, no. I am fasting.
I have to sleep early.
I have classes at 6 AM.
I'll have Poha n Jalebi early morning.
Class?
So early?
But my time-table..
Jeetu Bhaiya runs
faster than the time-table.
You will have it too.
Which batch were you alloted?
- A10.
And you accepted it? A10.
Yes. Deepak sir said
it won't be a problem.
Why?
Why? What's wrong with A10?
Wrong? Sir, leave aside JEE advance..
..they don't even prepare
one well for MAINS exams.
No extra classes.
No doubt session. No DPP.
Also time gets wasted.
Who provided you all these insights?
Look, you came very late as it is.
We admitted you.
Now you feel the batch is wrong.
Change the batch.
It's not what you think.
It's your first day. Be positive.
Just start studying.
The batch makes no difference.
Sir, if it makes no difference
then transfer me.
To any other batch.
And sir, if I am worthy of A10..
..then I shall end up there
after the reshuffling.
No. No. Not possible.
It's a rule. We don't give special
treatment to anyone in Prodigy classes.
Be it a student or faculty.
But, sir, A10..
- Jeetu sir.
How are you, sir?
How are you?
- Good. Good, sir. Please sit.
Brother-in-law was
missing you yesterday.
Jeetu never comes over.
He even called you.
Sister prepared baked chickpea fluffs.
That's precisely why I didn't come over.
Your sister is a very bad cook
Moreover it's awkward to tell her.
This is absolute truth, Deepak.
This indeed is true.
You go to your class, son.
This is the entrance test
paper for the physics faculty.
You asked for it.
That's wonderful, sir!
Wonderful! The paper is very good, sir.
Then clear my payment, sir.
Payment?
- I took so many extra classes last month.
I messaged you.
Hasn't it been cleared as yet?
Will get it cleared, sir.
Yes, it's up to you.
If I don't get paid by Friday..
..I'll just switch off the
phone and leave.
Sir..
There are 58 countries
that offer visa on arrival.
I could be in any of them
Then keep looking for me.
Take me along if you go, sir.
If you leave because of me,
brother-in-law will kill me anyways.
Brother-in-law won't let you leave.
He still wants to start
up Prodigy International school..
..Engineering college and Universities.
And he will need someone over
there who can cut people's salaries.
Sir.
- Say hello.
Yes.
- Sir.
- Sir, I need to talk to you.
Why are you troubling sir?
Sir, it's nothing.
Just a second, Deepak.
Sir, my name is Vaibhav Pandey.
I enrolled in the 11th
grade batch yesterday.
Sir, he is a late admission.
Now he wants to upgrade his batch.
No, sir. He won't let
me tell you the whole story.
Listen. Vaibhav Pandey?
- Yes, sir.
Do you enjoy begging?
First of all. Stop begging.
If you want something
work hard and snatch it.
The batch you have now is your truth.
A test will take place in two months.
Make an effort and you will improve.
But all the others got
batches through entrance exam.
I didn't even get to take that
That is also a truth.
Sir, I definitely deserve
a better batch than this.
Why later? Give me a test now.
I am willing to sit for it.
Ask me questions, sir.
Okay.
Here are fifty questions.
You've until tomorrow. Solve these.
The batch you earn after this will be final.
What happened?
Why are you getting involved
in this matter, sir?
Even your time will be wasted.
- Thank you, sir.
Now seeing him other kids will
also demand the same.
How many kids will you test?
Not everybody demands.
Only he did.
We shall see.
Don't forget the payment.
Yes. Your payment will..
I'm not getting this, buddy.
After finishing the puffs
you say you aren't getting it.
Seeing the figure I
felt I will be able to do it.
What kind of a question is this?
How hard does one blow into the bubble maker
to make a stable bubble?
This hasn't been taught.
You really can't do it, bro?
God!
Even Piyush isn't answering my call.
What should I do? I am trapped.
Shivangi too has gone.
Why did you agree to this paper
when you hadn't studied mechanics?
I had to be heroic over there.
I can't solve three
questions in four hours.
And I will be humiliated
if I take this with me.
Let's go then.
Where?
I had the puffs.
So the questions will be solved..
..whether I solve them
or someone else does.
Come.
I have to prepare for my own
Board exams and I have little time.
What are you studying for?
- Reshuffling.
You still have two months to go.
- Exactly.
How will this get done so soon?
I too am in 11th grade. We
haven't been taught all of this as yet.
You can ask me anything
from before this.
They taught us in the 11th grade.
But I've forgotten everything.
You can ask me anything
that comes after that.
"No sorrow, no cannabis or your rum."
"My world is made up of friends."
The first is B.
The second is A. The third is C.
So soon, brother? Please write
the solution as well, brother. Please.
You said Jeetu sir set the paper.
- Yes.
This is too easy. Don't waste my time.
I told you, didn't I? Students
of A1 are very selfish.
This is too easy?
"No sorrow, no cannabis or your rum."
"My world is made up of friends."
"I had read it in books.
Now it is written on the walls."
"My world is made up of friends."
Sure, bro. Show me.
Which question do you want me to solve?
Just show me the questions.
Not the options.
It's just that every
question has a journey..
..which we have to take
ourselves without a map.
Brother, solve the third one.
I wasted two years to do this.
I won't make the mistake
in the drop year.
We are only asking you to solve
one question. It will take ten minutes.
If I take ten minutes to
solve ten questions for others..
..then it will take me one month
of the year to clear other's doubts.
It's a 'do' or 'die' situation for me.
And I want to do 'do'.
Please leave. Please leave.
NOW!!
Check it. The answer is 8.
But bro all the options are in
sin theta and cos theta.
Oh, yeah? Show me another question.
Yes, this appears familiar.
I think I can solve it.
- Then do it, buddy.
I've been cramming non-stop
for two days.
If I don't speak to my girl today
she'll break up with me.
Please understand.
Really, bae. Is that what he said?
What happened after that?
Come back tomorrow.
I'll solve it for you tomorrow.
Come during the day tomorrow.
Ya! Got it. Root 3/4. Check it.
The three options are in form of graph.
And what about the fourth?
- None of the above.
Then that must be it.
You see? I solved it, didn't I?
Your girlfriend betrayed you,
didn't she?
It happens.
No. I never had a girlfriend.
Your parents must be getting divorced?
Right? No?
Or you must be gay.
Wow, bro! You are gay.
My first gay friend.
- What nonsense are you speaking?
Then what is the reason?
What's the reason that a fragile
and helpless boy like you..
..left his home, school and
all else mid semester to come to Kota?
You are not a genius. That much is obvious.
Meena, he isn't telling
but this guy has a dark past.
Uday.
Can't you find a
better time for ragging?
We can't solve one question.
If you can tell us something
about mechanics then tell us..
..or else remain quiet for two minutes.
I don't know about mechanics
but the answer to the third one is C.
That's plain guesswork.
I am not guessing.
I have seen this question.
Yes, it appears familiar to me as well..
..but I've forgotten how it is done.
It is okay.
If anyone explains a little to me once..
We got ourselves embarrassed just now.
You want to go again?
I thought people come
to Kota and become geniuses.
Jackasses!
Idea!
Kids, we will solve
a tricky question today..
..and if you don't use
the trick in this question..
..it will be difficult
for you to solve this question.
As you can see a block and
spring system has been used here.
Here I have projected the back block..
..towards the front block with V0 velocity.
- This is the one.
The spring with the natural ability.
Go a little forward.
A little forward. A little forward.
Now you have to solve
this with center of mass.
If you solve this with center of mass..
- Yes, this is the answer.
We were fooled by the change
of language of the question.
We took the frame of reference
of ground when we had to take center of mass.
You see, Meena.
I'm not like you. You forget.
My lectures can be revised
anywhere and at any time.
Yes. Alright.
What?
If one problem is
from Resnick Halliday..
..then all the others too
can be from some book or the other.
Don't start reading the text.
Look out for the figure first.
If you find the figure, then
read the question. It will save time.
I found the bubble one!
Surface tension equated with..
- Read it later. Just copy it now.
Bring more books.
These are bad times.
We have to sneak out for studies.
God save us from IIT.
"What good is a life with no friends?"
I've been shot.Help me..
-- Revive me.
Kill him. Kill him.
He's hiding in the bushes.
Come help me.
How do I come?
Please come now.
"My world is made up of friends."
"It is made up of your
love and your worship."
"My world is made up of friends."
"I have met several thousand
but I have only four good friends."
"This is everyone's path.
This is everyone's calling."
"What good is a life with no friends?"
"Don't get lost. Don't get separated."
"Don't get lost again."
Take them. Take them all.
These books are of no use.
The one for whom
I wanted to crack IIT..
..she eloped with a commerce guy.
We only need the solution.
Old edition?
It will do. It will do. It will do.
Bye. Bye. Bye, bro.
"No sorrow, no cannabis or your rum."
"My world is made up of friends."
"I had read it in books.
Now it is written on the walls."
"My world is made up of friends."
YOU have the keys!!
Oh yeah!!
"I had read it in books.
Now it is written on the walls."
"My world is made up of friends."
Enough already.
You will surely get a better
batch than A10 with this much.
This is copied.
Let me solve a few myself.
Hey, bro. Don't tell  Jeetu Bhaiya
that you copied all these.
You will waste the
whole night's efforts..
..just for a couple of questions.
I am going to bed now.
How much longer will you remain awake?
It's almost done. Only a little longer.
Good luck.
- Yes, bro. Thank you.
Bye.
- Yes.
You did all of these?
Yes, sir. It took me all night.
How did you do this one?
The third one?
Sir, Instead of ground we had
to use center of mass as the frame of reference.
Then it got done.
Correct.
This one?
Sir, the first part
in this one was very easy.
In the second part the
movement of inertia was changed.
Then it got done.
This one?
In this one had to blow air into
a bubble. Then the surface tension..
You must have doubled it.
- Doubled. Yes, sir.
Then you must have equated it.
- Yes, sir.
It's correct.
Your method is correct.
- Thank you, sir.
But the answer is wrong.
Classic calculation mistake.
Coincidentally Sharma sir's
solution has the same mistake.
In the last edition.
Page number 98, problem number 17.
I mailed him.
He will correct it in the next edition.
Do you know why you couldn't
solve the remaining 8 questions?
Because those 8 questions
were framed by me.
The solutions for the other
questions are in one book or another.
Those you have solved.
You couldn't complete
these by yourself in one night.
Who was with you?
I'm asking you for the last time. Did you solve these?
No, sir.
I had only solved NCERT so far.
Didn't you know this yesterday?
Yesterday you were acting like Kejriwal.
Give me one opportunity, sir.
Give me a chance. I will do it.
What happened?
Sorry, sir.
Do you know for whom quota,
coaching, material..
..DPP, sheets and ready
reckoner are designed for?
For the students.
- For rankers.
It's not for us?
We only copy. What do we have? Fees.
The rankers get facilities from
fees charged to students like you..
..and people like me make an earning.
Guys like you come to Kota.
Playing pokemon in 9th grade..
..and PUBG in 10th grade and
Kota in 11th grade.
Why? We will answer when Mr.
Sharma asks.
You are preparing for IIT and NEET in Kota.
It looks cool. It's a fad.
You read the ads in newspapers
and see the hoardings..
..that state 100 percent
selection guaranteed.
We claim the same.
100 percent selection guaranteed.
You see that and you come here.
There is no guarantee.
I am not reprimanding you.
I am opening your eyes. Sit.
Sit.
You came to Kota, didn't you? Why?
To study, sir.
You could have studied at home.
What will Kota do?
Think. Think. This will take time.
Kota provides an environment.
Since there are students everywhere..
..there is competition and focus.
So we ought to get selected.
And what if you don't?
Sir, even if one is not
selected it doesn't matter.
One has to study
for the 12th grade, sir.
It gets done from here.
There is no loss, sir.
There is. There is a loss.
That's what people don't understand.
Children leave Kota in 2 years..
..but Kota doesn't leave
the children for years.
What does Kota do?
It isolates you from the world.
Then it doesn't matter in
life which government crashed..
..who got married to
whom and who won the IPL.
None of it matters in life.
Parents, siblings, friends and
relatives. Everything is left behind.
And you are left here alone.
What is left? IIT.
You keep harping about IIT over here.
When you desire something
so much at your tender age..
..there are only two outcomes.
If you get in then you have peace.
You're chilled.
And if you don't get in you wind
up being jealous, rancour and self-doubt.
One loses confidence, brother.
Then a person deems himself
a bigger loser than the world does.
After that no matter how
good a college you get into..
..you don't like it
because it is not IIT.
Seven years. 4 years of
graduation and 3 years of working.
It takes 7 years to
come out of this trauma.
Do you know the
punishment for fraud in India?
7 years. So henceforth
stop all this fraud.
This is not your school where
you impress someone to get more marks.
Here you and I have to get
together to help you get selected.
You won't achieve that in this manner.
By copying and cramming.
What they show in the films is wrong.
People getting selected by cramming.
It's not the Chaturs who go to IIT.
Only Ranchos do.
You have seen 3 Idiots, haven't you?
Don't be afraid of the batch.
This is your truth. Accept it.
Yes, sir.
It is also true that you
brushed up entire Mechanics in one night.
So, you are certainly a fighter student.
And that is all a teacher wants.
You joined late
hence you are lagging behind.
..but you are not alone.
We will fight right up till the last moment
and crack IIT.
Okay?
Say yes or no.
Yes, sir.
Go.
Give this to the receptionist.
She will leave anytime.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
How do I solve the
remaining eight questions?
Come. The repeater batch has
the same topic going on.
Come on.