I'm hungry.
Mooovie Monday!
The only cure I know
for the Monday blues is...
Varsity Blues.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Take a seat down there.
Second from the end.
All right,
everybody here?
Yes.
Popcorn, anyone?
Yes, please!
Thank you.
Anyone else?
No.
Movie Monday started
with training videos.
But we went through those
pretty fast.
Then we watched
a medical video.
Since then, it's been
half hour installments
of various movies.
With the exception of
an episode of Entourage,
which Michael made us watch
six times.
Entourage!
Kevin, would you like to do
the scenes from last week?
Yes.
Why him?
Don't whine.
Get the windows.
Previously on
Varsity Blues...
Okay, Billy Bob
got a head injury,
but coach made him play.
So then Lance,
he gets sacked.
And he's out for the year.
Hello?
Not everyone approves
of movie Monday.
I won't say who.
I don't approve.
I don't.
Hello?
Let's go after
that title now.
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Hi, Jan!
Hope you brought
the Milk Duds.
How would a movie
increase productivity,
Michael?
How, on earth,
would it do that?
People work faster after.
Magically.
No.
They have to,
to make up for the time...
watching the movie.
No.
Do I need to hire
a babysitter for you...
Kitchen.
Some little 14-year-old girl
whose job it is...
Michael is going to
get us all fired.
You sat back and let him
play that dumb movie
and now Jan is peeved off.
And we're all
going to lose our jobs.
That's not going to happen.
You know she has it
out for him now.
That's not his fault.
He had to
follow his heart.
Ever since Michael
dumped Jan for Carol,
Jan's been bitching out
on him.
Reject a woman and she will
never let it go.
One of the many defects
of their kind.
Also, weak arms.
Dwight, you should be
running this office.
Michael would never let me.
It's not
up to Michael.
It's Jan's call.
Talk to her.
I could never do that.
Fine, sit back
and do nothing
and let us all
get fired.
I know that patience
and loyalty are good
and virtuous traits.
But sometimes I just think
you need to grow a pair.
At  the Stanford branch,
they all play
this World War II video game
called Call of Duty.
And they're all
really into it.
I'm told it started
as a team building exercise.
Unfortunately,
I really suck at it.
Oh.
We didn't play
many video games in Scranton.
Instead
we'd do stuff like...
Uh, Pam and I would sometimes
hum the same
high pitched note.
And try to get Dwight
to make an appointme
with an ear doctor.
And Pam called it...
Pretendonitis.
Hey, Kelly,
my stuff just got here.
Kelly really likes
to online shop.
So I felt like I wanted
some new clothes.
I mean, I just...
I wanted to...
I felt like it was time
to maybe, um...
just get new clothes.
Okay.
I love it.
Really?
I don't know.
Now, you haven't even
tried it on yet.
Try it on.
Not at work.
I'll try it on--
Fashion show!
Fashion show at lunch!
No.
Fashion show!
Fashion show at lunch!
Why did you do that?
I'm just killing Germans
any way I can.
We're on the German team.
Shoot the British.
Wait, are we
playing teams?
Yeah.
Wah!
Gah!
Hello?
Is this Jan?
Who is this?
This is Dwight Schrute.
I am calling about
an extremely sensitive matter.
You should talk to Michael
and he'll talk to me
and that way we don't have
to speak to each other.
It's about Michael.
What about him?
I can't talk here.
It's too sensitive.
It's not about
a surprise party, is it?
No, but we should discuss that
another time.
Look, I'm already an hour
outside of Scranton, Dwight.
I am not coming back.
Pull over at exit 40.
There is
a Liz Claiborne outlet.
I  know you
like that store.
Go inside and shop
until I can meet you.
How do you know
I like that store?
Many of your blouses
are Claibornes.
How do you know that?
It's part of my job.
No, it's not.
It's officially not.
Noted.
* Mm mm mm *
I'm going to the dentist.
Okay.
I have to have
an emergency crown put in.
Ouchy.
Yes.
It's a new dentist.
He's far.
I might be gone
three hours.
Three hours, wow.
Have fun.
Did you get anything good?
Yeah.
New blouse?
Halter top?
Camisole?
Teddy?
I could save the branch.
Really.
If you let me run it.
Okay.
Okay, I can run it?
What would you do differently?
Mostly get rid of waste.
Which is half
the people there.
And clean house.
Right here.
It's all for me.
Thank you.
Dwight, you just feel strongly
to speak with me this way
behind Michael's back.
And turn on so many
of your co-workers.
The decision to turn on Michael
was difficult.
But once I did it,
I didn't look back.
And mostly I feel that
Michael would approve.
It's really what's best
for the branch.
And I could care less
about my co-workers.
So, here we are.
It's all on the table.
I want the branch.
And I await your decision.
Oh, by the way...
There's a new Ann Taylor
outlet store near here.
I know you like
their earrings.
Where is it?
Michael.
Hi.
I've had a very interesting
conversation
with one of
your employees.
Oh, that's nice.
No, it wasn't.
Dwight  just told me
that he thinks
he can run the branch
better than you.
What?
Mm-hmm.
You were at the dentist?
You can't have people
undermining you.
Get control of your branch
immediately.
Okay.
What was Dwight thinking?
That he could turn Jan
against me?
She's my ex-lover...ishh.
Wow.
It's so sexy.
You look so hot.
It's really something.
It's too much.
What?
I'm gonna return it.
No, you have to keep it today.
Just see how you feel.
Hey.
Hi.
You look nice.
Thanks.
Isn't  that, like,
your third soda today?
Yeah, I think we can be
a big help to your company.
Okay,  see you next week.
Bye.
Again?
Scared?
Call of Duty!
Andy, Jim, can I see you
in the conference room
for a minute?
Now?
Yes, now.
Put the game on hold,
everyone.
This is not working, okay?
We are getting slaughtered
out there.
It's the new guy.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I don't know...
what we're talking about.
See what I mean?
We just need a strategy, okay?
We're gonna set up a trap
in the gun room.
All right, Jim,
are you using the MP-40
or the 44?
Um, sniper rifle?
Snipe--
What?
Are you playing for
the other team?
You don't snipe
in Carrington, okay?
Saboteur!
I'm gonna kill you for real.
The game is over.
I'm really
going to shoot you.
Hey, Dwight...
Hey.
You want an m&m?
No, thanks, I'm stuffed.
No, seriously.
You should have an m&m.
They're really good.
Okay.
Good, huh?
So good.
Hey, I thought you weren't
supposed to eat anything
for a couple of hours
after you've had
a crown put in.
They have this new kind of
quick drying bonding.
So...
Sounds like a good dentist.
Oh, yeah.
What's his name?
Crentist.
Your dentist's name
is Crentist.
Yeah
Huh.
Sounds a lot like dentist.
Maybe that's why
he became a dentist.
Let me see your teeth.
Let me see 'em.
Ohh.
You should floss.
I know.
Well then.
I'm glad you're okay.
Business is like
a jungle.
And I am like a tiger.
And Dwight is like
a monkey...
that stabs a tiger
in the back with a stick.
Does the tiger
fire the monkey?
transfer the monkey
to another branch?
Pun.
There is no way
of knowing what goes on
inside the tiger's head.
We don't have
the technology.
Dwight, can I talk to you
for a second?
Wow, this is tough!
Brrrrr!
What?
Oh.
Aaaarg!
What is it?
Well...
I just got off the phone
with Jan.
And, um...
She demoted me.
No.
Yeah.
You know what the craziest
part of this is?
She demoted me
to your job.
And she said that you
should be expecting
a call later from corporate.
And that, um...
I guess that means
that you are going to be
acting manager
of Dunder-Mifflin Scranton.
I can't believe this news.
That...wow.
Yeah.
I told her I didn't know
whether you'd wanna do it.
Because you've always been
so loyal to me.
You've been my most
trusted ally.
You said that?
Yep, I did.
I did.
But I think...
you should do it.
Well...
Gosh, if you think
I should.
Then I will.
Perfect.
Well, we're settled.
All right.
Well, then you are now
acting manager
of Dunder-Mifflin
Scranton branch.
And I am assistant
regional manager.
Assistant to
the regional manager.
Thank you, Michael,
for staying on.
I really appreciate it.
Hey, hey.
I can't imagine this place
without you.
Can you?
That's so nice.
Well, um...
I guess we should
go tell the troops.
Yeah, when I'm ready, Mike.
Okay, let's do it.
Hey. Hi, hello.
Everybody, I have
some good news.
And I have
some bad news.
I am being replaced
as your leader by Dwight.
You're kidding.
You might think
that I am kidding
and I understand that.
Congratulations, Dwight.
Thank you, Angela.
But why Dwight?
Because Dwight never lies.
How does that qualify him
to run a branch?
Because that's all it takes.
Okay, Dwight,
would you like to
say a few words
to everybody about loyalty?
Thank you, Michael.
I just wanna say
to the few of you
who will remain
under my employ,
that I intend to lead you
into the black
with ferocity.
Michael, what will you do?
Oh, I'll be fine.
Do you have any savings?
No, no, I don't.
Michael, you might
lose your condo.
I won't.
I have this
little vacuum cleaner
that's broken.
If Dwight doesn't
work out,
maybe that could be manager.
Maybe I'll quit.
It's really happening.
Yes.
We can
make a difference here.
I will make
a difference here.
You alone?
'Cause I thought together...
Oh, please,
don't be naive.
You can be in charge
of the women.
Look how cute he is.
And he's trying to shoot
with a smoke grenade.
I'm sorry, what are you
whispering back there?
Nothing, just concentrate
on turning around.
I'm trying.
I just...
Just tap S then D.
Oh.
Any last words? No?
What?
Wow.
Psychopath.
What?
I'm just looking.
Please go back
to your desk.
In a minute.
Well, I remember why I dress
the way I do at work.
But I'm gonna
keep the clothes.
I  mean, it'll just be cool
to have some after work clothes
other than pajamas.
Well, I guess it's time...
that I turn over the keys
to the famous Sebring.
No, thank you.
It's a corporate lease,
Dwight.
You've earned it.
No, thanks.
What?
Not my style.
But you said
you liked it.
You've always admired it.
That was before.
I'm thinking about
getting something German.
Something with
decent gas mileage.
Plus the convertible
is a ridiculous choice
for this climate.
Take it back.
No.
That's my car.
What did you--
That's my car!
Yes.
I know, Dwight.
I know.
I know. I know.
You know what?
Jan called me
about your little meeting!
No.
I know what you did.
I made the whole thing up,
Dwight.
The Sebring's cool.
Oh, do you?
Do you like the Sebring?
How dare you!
How dare you, Dwight?
Don't fire me.
Please.
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't fire you
right here on the spot.
I have excellent
sales numbers!
Not good enough!
I'll do anything!
Anything!
I'll do your laundry
for a month!
For a year! Michael!
I have a laundry machine.
I'm sorry.
I'll do anything.
Please.
I don't know if I can trust you anymore.
You can't. You can't.
But I promise I'll never
betray you again.
What can I do, Michael?
What can I do?
You can get up.
Get up.
And you can
hug it out, bitch.
Hug it out, bitch.
That is what men
say to each other
after a fight.
They hug it out.
And in doing so,
they just let it go.
And walk away.
Then they're done.
Not a good idea to say that
to a woman, however...
I have found.
Doesn't translate.
Yep, we huged it out.
But, it turns out I was a little hangry.
So I felt I needed to punish
him jusl a little bit more.
And I make him do my laundry for a year.