[CLATTERING]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
♪ ♪
_
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
CARLO: Yeah, I started
the hostility log thing
- this week.
- PETER: How's that working out?
CARLO: Oh, yeah, good. Yeah. Um...
Had a bit of a situation
Wednesday with somebody.
Yeah, it was just-just some
guy eyeballing me at the pub.
But I was getting pretty pissed,
and I used the stop technique,
you know, we spoke about. So, yeah.
It's... I'm-I'm getting
pretty good at it,
- so that's good.
- PETER: Great.
Um... Ray, how have you been?
Yeah, good, mate.
- PETER: Yeah?
- Yep.
Is there anything you
want to talk about?
Nah, I'm good.
PETER: Are you sure?
- Nothing at all?
- [RAY CHUCKLES]
I beat my, uh, girlfriend's
brother up over Christmas.
[INHALES DEEPLY] Okay.
[COUGHS] Um...
What happened?
I went round to her parents' place,
and, um...
Yeah, we did the whole,
uh, Secret Santa thing.
Me daughter got this unicorn candle,
which she was pretty chuffed about,
and, uh, me girlfriend's
brother decided he wanted it,
and when it was his turn,
he, uh, took it off her.
So you assaulted him?
Well, he was being a dickhead, so,
- you know.
- PETER: So you assaulted him?
Eh, pretty much.
And how did your girlfriend
feel about this?
Well, she's not my
girlfriend anymore, so...
VINCE: Shit.
- Sorry, mate.
- Mm.
PETER: I mean, uh, you know,
without wanting to state the obvious,
can you see how violence
is perhaps not the best way
for you to resolve your disputes?
No, I think it generally is.
But, you know, just don't do it
in front of your girlfriend, you know?
[ALL CHUCKLE]
PETER: Uh, what's great about it?
I mean, it doesn't seem to have worked
- for you this time.
- RAY: Yeah, well, sometimes it does,
sometimes it doesn't, you know?
PETER: Can you give me one example
of violence ever working?
World War II.
- World War II.
- RAY: Mm-hmm.
We didn't beat the Nazis
just by talking to them.
We used violence.
PETER: Okay, sure.
So every now and then,
violence is necessary as a last resort.
But for you,
uh, with your girlfriend's brother,
I mean, would you call that an
example of violence working?
Yeah, look, I shouldn't
have done what I did.
You know, I'm not making excuses.
But I don't think you can say
that all violence is bad. I mean,
I think there's good
violence and bad violence.
What's good violence?
World War II.
Thanks, Vince.
Um...
- Yeah.
- Uh, all right,
maybe it's about time.
Maybe we should leave it there.
Thank you, everyone. Thank you.
[GRUNTS]
- [RAY HUMMING A TUNE]
- NARRATOR [ON TV]: German forces
had already moved in
and now occupied the
abbey ruins in force.
Here you go, mate.
You can have the fatty bit.
- Mate, you didn't even chew that.
- Meanwhile, in the town below,
the 28th Maori battalion
had led a successful attack on
the casino railway station,
only to then become trapped and
cut off from their support
across the river.
- [MACHINE GUNS FIRING]
- [BULLETS WHIZZING]
- ♪
♪
- MAN: Cheers, love.
[MAN WOLF WHISTLES]
♪ You're bad ♪
♪ Like poison honey... ♪
Hey.
How you doing?
- Good. What's news?
- Not much.
News with you?
Nothing. You okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
♪ You're a naughty, naughty girl ♪
♪ And I love it ♪
♪ Naughty, naughty, naughty, naughty. ♪
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[SNIFFS]
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SNIFFS]
♪ ♪
[ROCK MUSIC RINGTONE PLAYING]
- Hello?
- VINNIE: Ray.
It's Vinnie.
How you going, mate?
I'm good my friend. How are you?
- Yeah, good mate. What's news?
- Oh, you know,
same old shit in here, mate.
But listen, I thought I'd
check in and see if you want
to catch up for a beer or sometime.
Yeah, sounds good, mate.
Yeah.
I'm pretty-pretty busy this week. Um...
what about next weekend?
Sure, weekend. Oh, fuck.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck. No, I got to go see my folks.
They got a farm up there in Dorrigo.
So, yeah, I'll be away all weekend.
Oh, okay. What about-what about
the weekend after that, then?
Weekend after. Sounds great.
Let's shoot for that, eh?
Yeah, mate, I'll keep it free.
All right. You take care
of yourself, brother.
Yeah, same, mate. Talk to you soon.
- All right, mate.
- See you, mate.
You just gonna leave that
there are you, love?
Excuse me?
Well, your dog just took a shit.
- Are you gonna clean it up, or...
- So?
You're just gonna leave
it for somebody else
- to stand in, are you?
- Well, if it bothers you so much
why don't you pick it up?
Why don't you fucking pick it up?
Oh, okay. Yeah.
FREDDY: Nah, it's been good. I mean,
- it's still early days, but...
- RAY: Mm.
Fuck, last night,
we're lying in bed and she says to me,
"Who have you had the best
sex of your life with?"
And I'm lying there thinking,
"Fuck, how do I answer this?"
- Mm.
- You know?
Because she's not the bird
I've had the hottest sex with,
but I can't tell her the
best sex I ever had
was with some 52-year-old hooker
- in an alley, you know?
- Mm.
So I have to say something, and fast...
- ... so I say... "You!"
Uh, but because I took a
second to answer, she's like,
"Why'd you have to
think about it?" I said,
"I don't know, the question
kind of took me by surprise."
[SIGHS]
I tell you, mate, women
can ask questions
that scare the shit out of you.
Mm, mm, true.
- So who is this dude, anyway?
- Who?
- This guy.
- Oh, Simon Gillespie.
You know the Gillespies.
- The mining family?
- Yeah.
Oh, okay.
And what's his problem?
He's been having some lady trouble.
Oh, okay.
Hey. Uh, Simon's here.
- Do you want to see him now?
- Yeah, yeah.
Bring him in. Thanks, Mandy.
- You're good.
- Oh, thanks, Mandy.
- FREDDY: G'day, mate. [CHUCKLES]
- SIMON: Hey, Freddy.
FREDDY: Well, there's a familiar face.
- How are you?
- Good to see you.
[CHUCKLES] Good to see you too.
- It's been way too long.
- Yes. Yeah.
Uh, Simon, this is Ray.
- SIMON: Hi, Ray.
- How you going, mate?
- Uh... yeah. Yeah, thanks.
- Uh, take a seat.
Um, right. Why don't you, uh,
- tell Ray your story, mate?
- Straight down to business, right?
- Yes. Yeah.
- Okay, well, uh,
I was seeing this young lady
for about a year or so.
It was-it was, you know, it was
nothing too serious, I guess,
from my perspective anyway.
And so, I, uh, stopped seeing
her a few weeks ago, and...
and now she's threatening
to tell my wife.
And, uh, she's threatening,
if I don't pay her a shitload of cash,
she's gonna talk.
- And how much is she asking for?
- SIMON: Uh, two million.
- Ooh, shit.
- SIMON: Yeah, yeah.
[CHUCKLES]: The fucking...
And I told her
I don't have that kind of money.
She won't listen to reason, all right?
And she-she also said she's
gonna go to the press
and tell them all sorts
of shit about me,
- and none of that's true, okay?
- RAY: Mm.
'Cause with my public profile,
I-I just... I can't have that.
- Right?
- No.
So, she's just, like, being, um,
just totally off her head, you know?
So what do you want me to do, mate?
Uh, well, you-you know.
No, I don't.
SIMON: Well, I want...
I want you to take care of her.
- RAY: Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
Yeah. So... what you reckon?
Yeah, I'll have a think about it.
- Have a think about it?
- SIMON: Uh, okay.
So... next...
next week or a few days, or...
- Yeah, a couple of days.
- SIMON: Oh. Great. Great.
♪ ♪
FREDDY: Now this one here,
I've got a bet each way,
'cause that... that means
if it comes first I'll
win a lot of money.
If it comes second or third,
I'll win a little bit of money.
If it doesn't win at all,
I don't get anything,
but that never happens to me,
unless I'm having a bad week.
But that's... Oh, this...
this race here... race six...
- How are ya? How's it going?
- MANDY: Good, good.
- Yeah.
- When are we gonna see you
on-you on the dance floor, eh?
- Aw, that's not really my job.
- You're not gonna jump up?
- What if we-what if we pay extra?
- No.
- I'm not into it.
- Come on.
Can't pay me enough. I'm gonna get you
- some water, though.
- And some vodka.
Come on, bring-bring back some drinks.
Fuck off. What was that?
- MANDY: Shit.
- [GUYS LAUGHING]
Oi, hey... [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
- Piece of shit!
- Okay. Okay, love.
What the fuck? [GRUNTS]
RAY: Get 'em out.
[MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
MANDY: Ugh.
[SIGHS]
Thanks.
- Pretty handy with that tray.
- [CHUCKLES]
Mate, I know you're going through
some shit at the moment,
but fuck.
♪ I just can't do that ♪
♪ Give me drinks ♪
♪ I'm too fast, trouble. ♪
- Tell you who was a good fighter.
- Mm?
Durán. Roberto Durán.
Yeah. Yeah, hands of stone, mate.
- Durán, yeah.
- Yeah.
I, um, I read where Mayweather
said that Durán was his, uh,
number two on his all-time list.
Mm. Who was his number one?
Mayweather.
Mayweather was number one on
his own greatest of all-time list?
[LAUGHS]: Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
What a wanker. Jesus Christ.
He had a perfect record, though.
- What'd he have, 50?
- 50. 50 from 50.
- 50 from 50. Yeah.
- Yeah. Yep.
He had 27 KOs,
five... over five weight classes.
- Yeah.
- '96 bronze medal at the Olympics.
Oh, yeah?
What are you on?
34 bucks an hour, I think.
And what else you on?
Just a bit of goey.
Ice?
Just had a little bit, mate.
Just feeling a bit shithouse
since me and Zo split up,
so... you know, pickup.
Get off that shit, mate.
- It'll be all right, Ray.
- No, it won't be
fucking all right, mate.
Fucking get off it.
What, are you the boss of me now, mate?
Mate...
I vouched for you to get you the job.
Yeah, I know, and I appreciate it.
Well, you know...
don't make me look bad, all right?
I won't.
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
What's going on with you and Simon?
What?
Well, he said you're
trying to blackmail him.
[SCOFFS]: What?
I'm not trying to blackmail him.
So why's he saying that you are, then?
Oh. I don't know. I mean,
- I-I don't know.
- He said you're asking
for two million bucks to
keep your mouth shut.
[SIGHS]
Look, I... I asked him
for $1,000 a month,
till the baby turn... till she turns 18.
Oh, my...
Did he...
[ENGINE STOPS]
- Nice house, mate.
- Jesus Christ.
Oh, you scared the shit out of me.
- How'd you know where I live?
- Hey, listen, mate,
I talked to Fiona, and I got her down
- to 250 grand.
- You...
- you spoke to her?
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- You can afford 250, yeah?
- Uh, y...
Yeah, look, listen, um...
- thanks, yeah?
- Yeah.
But don't worry about it.
- I'll-I'll deal with that. Yeah.
- Oh. Okay.
I think you should pay the money, mate.
W... [SCOFFS]
Why would I want to do that?
'Cause I know she's pregnant.
Ah. Uh... look, I, w-w... Look, w...
Okay, um...
Listen, the thing is...
she's batshit crazy.
- She-She's...
- Let me stop you there, mate, okay?
Pay the money.
48 hours, okay?
What?
- You heard what I said.
- Wh-Wh...
what happens if I don't?
[CHUCKLES]
You really want to find out?
All right.
[GATE OPENS, CLOSES]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER IN DISTANCE]
- [MUSIC PLAYING INSIDE]
Here you go, mate.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What's going on?
Alex wants to know
what's taking so long.
Well, if he's not happy, mate,
he can have his money back
and find somebody else to do the job.
- I didn't say he wasn't happy.
- Mm.
He just wants to know
what the holdup is.
Yeah, well, Vinnie's got
good security, mate,
and he's not easy to get to, so,
- you know...
- [TIRES SCREECH IN DISTANCE]
Anyway, his parents have got a farm...
and he's going up there this weekend,
so I'm gonna try to get him there, so...
Just get it done.
♪ ♪
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --