[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
How you going?
Hello.
Uh, my daughter Brittany
goes to school with...
your daughter Taylor.
[STAMMERS] Yeah. Yeah.
And, um, apparently,
uh, Taylor's been...
bullying my daughter,
saying stuff to her, putting
stuff up on the Internet
- and... That kind of stuff.
- My daughter wouldn't do that, so...
Okay.
Well, can you talk to her and find out?
'Cause I don't think my
daughter's gonna lie about it.
How did you get my address?
Look, love, I'm not
here to cause problems.
- I'm just here...
- Don't call me "love," mate.
Okay. All right.
What?
Do you think you scare me or
something, coming around here?
I'm not trying to scare you.
I'm gonna go inside now.
And I'm gonna call my brother.
Oh?
He's a cop.
Mm. Scary.
You gonna go now, or...
Don't be a dickhead.
[CHUCKLES]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
MAN: There's not much I can do for me.
[MUSICAL SCORE PLAYS ON LAPTOP]
You lose independence.
Nancy loses hers.
I think she's hanging it tough.
[BIRDS CHIRPING OUTSIDE]
[LID CLACKS]
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
[EXHALES]
[URINATING]
[URINATING STOPS]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
Fuck!
[STRAINS]
♪ Maria ♪
♪ Gratia plena ♪
♪ Gratia ♪
♪ Plena. ♪
Give me five minutes.
♪ ♪
[MUTTERING]
You want coffee?
You got any decaf?
Decaf? Serious?
I can't drink caffeine anymore.
Why not?
Makes me sweat too much.
So, you got any?
No, we only got real coffee, mate.
You counting it?
- [SCOFFS]
- [CHUCKLES]
Could've miscounted.
Yeah. Yeah, I could've.
So, what's with the no socks?
It's called fashion, mate.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's not something
you'd know too much about.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Right.
So, this guy wants to talk to
you about a piece of work.
- Mm.
- It's all very hush-hush.
- Eh.
- Do you want to meet with him?
- Who is he?
- I don't know.
One of his guys came in last
night and spoke to me about it.
Says it's a big job.
Lot of money.
And he just wants to meet with me?
Yeah.
Set it up.
All right.
[ENGINE STOPS]
- How you going?
- Alex.
Ray. Good to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Ray. This is Kev.
- Kev, how are you, mate?
- How are you?
You come well-recommended.
What can I do for you?
Heard of a guy called Vinny Williams?
Yeah.
Prez of the, uh, Dead Birds.
Yeah. You know him?
Yeah, I met him once or twice.
Through a mate of mine.
Huh.
Still interested?
It's gonna cost you.
Name your price.
Why do you want him whacked?
Does it matter?
Yeah.
I'm his VP.
Personality clash, huh?
Yeah, yeah. Something like that.
How much?
250.
Done.
- 100 up front.
- Sure.
[ZIPS]
You cancel the job,
I keep the cash, okay?
'Course.
Thank you. See you when the job's done.
- Catch you later.
- Yeah. Good to meet you, man.
- Cheers.
- ALEX: Let's go.
[KNOCKING]
[KEY RATTLING IN LOCK]
Brucey?
Bruce!
BRUCE: In the dunny.
RAY: Shit, mate. What happened?
I just thought I'd have a lie-down.
How long you been in here for?
Not long.
RAY: All right.
Now give me your hand. Ah, fuck.
Can you get that hand out of there?
- Can you get that hand out?
- [GRUNTS]
- Right.
- Okay.
Chuck that up there, mate.
Can you get a hand on that?
- [GRUNTS]
- Huh?
Okay, so what I'm gonna do,
I'm just gonna pull you up.
- [GRUNTS]
- Watch your head.
[STRAINS]
Aw, shit.
[GROANS]
All right.
All right, let me get under your arms.
- All right, count of three.
- [GRUNTS]
All right. One... two...
- three!
- [GROANS]
- You all right?
- I'm all right.
- All right.
[RAY EXHALES]
[MUTTERS] We'll have to get you a carer.
I'm not having a fucking carer.
Fair enough.
Well, you can't live here, mate.
You could have died.
So?
What, you given up, have you?
I've had enough. [EXHALES]
Why don't you come live with me?
I want to live here.
I know you want to live here, mate,
but you can't live here anymore.
I'll put you in the garage.
- [GROANS]
- I'll put a bed in there,
bloody TV, whatever you need, mate.
Britt'll be there.
All right, she'd love it if
you're there all the time.
[GRUNTS]
What do you reckon?
I'll think about it.
Okay, that's good, that's good enough.
All right.
- You want a cuppa?
- Meh.
Yeah.
- There's no milk.
- [REFRIGERATOR DOOR OPENS]
Oh, for fuck's sake.
GARY: Th-That's the official
story, but, you know...
RAY: Yeah, but I think...
I think there was a guy behind
- the fence on the knoll.
- No, but that doesn't make any sense.
See, I don't think there was anyone
on the grassy knoll behind the fence.
I think the shooter was in the pergola.
RAY: Where's the pergola?
Well, the pergola's on the grassy
knoll, but it's-it's up near...
more up north towards
the depository... it's
the big white building,
- the-the concrete one.
- Mm.
Yeah. And, uh... And this ch...
and there's a photo...
there's two blokes,
that are hiding in the
pergola, and I reckon
that's where the head shots come from.
And when the limo comes
around the corner,
- where does it stop?
- Mm?
Where does it stop, eh?
In front of the pergola.
Well, the limo didn't stop.
How do you know it doesn't stop?
Well, you look at the film, it doesn't.
It slows down but it doesn't stop.
- On the Zapruder film?
- Yeah.
Oh. [STAMMERS]
Well, that's bullshit because
the film's doctored, so...
- The Zapruder film is doctored?
- Yeah, of course. Yeah.
- Who doctored the Zapruder film?
- Everyone knows
the Zapruder film's doctored...
- it went missing for years.
- I didn't...
And-And then it came back.
It resurfaced, like,
eight to 12 years later.
- Now we're telling more fantasies.
- The frames are missing.
Yeah. That's right. Well, frames
are missing, and... Yeah.
It just-it just doesn't make any sense.
- It's fucking bullshit.
- Mm.
So, yeah.
You okay, babe?
[WHISPERS]: I want to go home.
- Huh?
- Hey, what made you...
why did you shave it off?
Your beard. Why'd you shave it off?
Well, because, uh, Tat
gets pash rash, so...
- got to keep her happy.
- Oh.
- Very nice of you.
- GARY: Yeah. You like it?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- You like it?
I do. Uh, it's... Yeah, no, I do.
- Actually, I do.
- Yeah?
- It's good.
- Yeah, all right.
Okay. There you go.
Yeah, you look like an '80s porn star.
- Really?
- [SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
What?
Babe? You all right?
Have you told Ally about you-know-what?
What?
Your pee-pee movies.
Okay.
- Pee-pee movies?
- [SHORT CHUCKLE]
- Oh... yeah.
- [LAUGHING]: What the fuck's going on?
- RAY: Nothing.
- Babe, time and a place.
- Nothing? Bullshit. Nothing.
- Nothing's going on.
- Come on, what? Spill.
Come on, Ray.
Well, you tell her.
- [CHUCKLES]
- TATIANA: Last year,
Ray left a DVD at our house.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah.
TATIANA: Yes. And I found it.
- Oh... Okay, what was the DVD?
- [THUMP]
- Ow! Gary.
- What?
Golden Shower Power.
Oh, right, okay.
So we are... we're talking pornos?
- Yes.
- Yeah, okay.
Golden showers?
- Mm.
- It's when people...
- piss on each other?
- Yes.
- Apparently. Yeah.
- Okay.
ALLY: [CHUCKLES] Wow. Wow, okay.
This is like a whole side of you
that I have never
seen before. [CHUCKLES]
- There's a lot you don't know.
- I know, clearly.
Um...
so are you-are you the-the
pisser or the pissee?
Oh, either's fine.
ALLY: So you like the
taste of piss, or...
RAY: Oh, I don't mind it.
- Mm. Okay.
- Mm.
I need to go to toilet now,
so do you want me to wait?
I was gonna go, but do
you want me to wait
'til we get home, or...
Yeah. Yeah, it'd be good if you wait.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- You guys have got it sorted out.
- RAY: Mm.
- ALLY: [LAUGHING]: Mm.
- Right. Right, you want another drink?
I want to go home.
- You want another drink?
- Yes, please.
You want another drink?
Yeah? Get another one.
Where's the, uh...
It was his DVD, all right?
She found it,
and he tells her...
'cause he's, you know,
I don't know, he panicked or whatever...
he tells her, "It's Ray's."
And then he comes to me and says,
"Man, I need you to
come 'round to my house
and apologize."
Right? Which I did.
And say...
you know, it's my DVD.
[CHUCKLES] Why would you leave a porno
- at somebody else's house?
- That's what I said to him.
Why the fuck would I...
Like, not only why would I
leave it at your house,
but why the fuck would I
bring a porno into your...
Like, who comes into somebody's house
- and you bring a porno with you?
- [LAUGHING]
You know that I mean?
And then you leave it,
and, y-you know what I mean?
- And you go.
- I know. I don't...
- It doesn't make any fucking sense.
- No.
BRITTANY: Dad,
why don't you like sandwiches?
Uh...
I like toasted sandwiches.
Just don't like the
raw ones, that's all.
Why?
Uh... I don't know. [MUTTERS]
Why do you like them?
- Because they're yummy.
- Mm.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Who's that?
Don't know.
- Who is it?
- Go to your room.
- Why?
- Go to your room, please.
MALE OFFICER: Afternoon, sir.
Are you Ray Shoesmith?
I don't answer questions.
Can I help you?
We're looking for a Ray Shoesmith.
Does he live here?
I don't answer questions.
Okay. Is there somebody here
who can answer questions?
I don't answer questions.
Okay. I don't really know how
to respond to that, sir.
We just spoke to a woman by
the name of Petra Jenkins.
She says you threatened her
and tried to menace her.
- Did she?
- Yeah.
You got anything you
want to say about that?
I don't answer questions.
Would you mind telling us why?
Okay.
See ya.
We'll come back later.
Okay.
FEMALE OFFICER: Friendly chap.
MALE OFFICER: That's just weird.
[ENGINE STARTS]
- What?
- Nothing.
ALLY: If something happened to me...
like, if I was in...
I don't know... like an
accident or something,
and I was in a wheelchair...
would you look after me?
Yeah.
What if I was, like, a quadriplegic?
Is that the ones that
can use their arms,
but they can't use their legs?
No, that's a paraplegic.
Quadriplegics can't use
their arms or their legs.
So, what, you'd just be
lying in bed all day?
Pretty much.
I'd probably put a pillow over your head
and put you out of your misery.
Serious?
Well, why would you
want to live like that?
What if I wanted to live?
Hmm.
So how would we have sex?
Well, quadriplegics can't
feel anything down there.
Yeah, but we could still
have sex, though, right?
So you'd still want to have sex with me
even if I couldn't feel anything?
Why wouldn't I want
to have sex with you?
Sure.
- Knock yourself out.
- [CHUCKLES]
Just don't complain I'm a dead root.
But you're a dead root
anyway and I don't complain.
- Thanks very much.
- [CHUCKLES]
What are you doing?
You'll see.
[RAY SIGHS]
Aw, is that for me?
No, it's for the dude on
the park bench over there.
There is no dude over
there on the park bench.
Yes, there is.
It's my imaginary boyfriend.
He said he'd look after me
if I was a quadriplegic.
Yeah, well, I said I'd look after you.
Oh, good.
Just wanted to make sure we were
gonna have sex, that's all.
[LAUGHS]
- [GLOVES THUMPING]
- ["YOUNGBLOODS" BY ILLY PLAYS]
♪ We doin' it big while we here
for the ones that aren't ♪
♪ A lot of people tell you
what you're meant to do ♪
♪ But only one can decide
what's best for you: you ♪
♪ Me? I'm just trying to
get the message through ♪
♪ It goes like, save the
drama, spend your youth. ♪
- [SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Hey. You Taylor?
Yeah.
I've heard that you've been
bullying my friend Brittany.
What?
You bother Brittany again,
and I'm gonna rip your head off.
Got it?
- Yes.
- It's all right? All right.
Do you need me to stretch
my lips or... ? [MUMBLES]
- No, it's okay.
- Okay? [MUMBLES]
Do you need me to stop talking?
- Yes.
- Yeah, okay.
Okay.
They're very glittery.
Am I holding still enough for you?
- Yes.
- Yeah? All right.
- Okay. You want to see?
- Yes.
Okay.
[GASPS] Oh.
[LAUGHING]: Oh, that's beautiful.
Wow, I really like what you've
done here. This is good.
- Thanks.
- This is good, yeah.
Wow. Thank you.
They'll love this at work.
Yeah, she's all right now.
She was pretty upset, but...
I don't think she's gonna
have any more problems.
Were you bullied at school?
Mm-hmm.
Bad?
Pretty bad.
Were you beaten up?
Mm-hmm.
Well, what was this...
all through school?
Um... probably up until about...
halfway through grade six.
- Well, it stopped?
- Mm-hmm.
Why did it stop?
Fought back.
What happened?
Oh, there was this little prick,
and he'd been bullying
me for about two years.
And, um...
... this one day, you know,
we were playing downball,
and he just started getting
stuck into me, and,
you know, and I started crying,
and... and he just kept following me,
just kept saying shit to me,
- just wouldn't leave it alone, you know?
- Mm.
And I just grabbed him and threw
him up against a wall, and...
... just beat the absolute
fuck out of him.
And he stopped?
He sure did.
It's always better to give than receive.
Is it?
Fuck yeah.
Why do you say that?
Well, you got to fight back, you know?
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
Otherwise, people will
walk all over you.
You know?
I mean, that's the thing.
Look, I wasn't looking for
trouble as a kid. You know?
But I learned there's people
in this world who will
take and take till there's
nothing left of you.
I used to get angry about it.
Well, I... I used to
get angry at myself,
'cause I couldn't do nothing about it.
- You know what I mean?
- Mm.
Like, I felt...
I felt like I was weak.
You know what I mean?
Um...
I can remember...
I took a razor blade out of
the, um, the bathroom cupboard.
I went down to the swings
at the end of the street.
And I'm sitting there and
I'm thinking, you know,
"I'm gonna top meself." You know?
"I've had enough."
'Cause I was getting hit at home,
I was getting hit at school, you know?
And, um...
But I couldn't do it, you know?
And then, I felt like,
"Geez, you weak bastard,
you can't, you know, you
can't even kill yourself."
You know what I mean?
And I thought,
"Is it 'cause I don't want to die
or is it 'cause I'm just
afraid to cut myself?"
So I took the razor blade
and I cut me hand up.
Anyway.
♪ I was sitting ♪
♪ In my Corolla ♪
♪ Talking to you ♪
♪ While my friends ♪
♪ Drank inside ♪
♪ There was a silence ♪
♪ Weak telephone reception ♪
♪ Doesn't compliment ♪
♪ A dark ♪
♪ State of mind ♪
♪ You know it's bad. ♪