[PANTING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- Good work, bro.
- Cool, man.
- Good sesh, man.
- All right.
I'll catch you at your next fight.
Yeah.
Hey, Ray.
Yeah, man?
Hey, um, you want to help
me out with the kids?
- Yeah. All right. Yeah. Yeah.
- Appreciate it, man.
- Which ones?
- Just take that group.
- I've got these guys.
- Yeah. All right.
All right. Let's do it.
RAY: All right, so what we'll do is,
we're just gonna do some
light sparring, uh...
Don't try to knock each
other over, right?
So, you guys go together.
- Yeah.
- All right?
And just keep it nice and friendly,
and we'll do a bit of this,
do a bit of that. All right.
Let's see what you got.
Okay. Okay.
All right. All right,
I'm gonna throw a few.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Ooh, okay. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. There you go.
- Pretty good, pretty good. Yeah.
- Thanks.
So, how long you been doing this for?
- About a month.
- Is that all?
I used to do jiujitsu
for a couple of years
- before this, though.
- Oh, okay.
Well, do you want to see
if you can get a takedown?
- Sure.
- Cool. Well...
Huh?
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHS]
You okay, old man?
Yep.
Should've tapped.
No shit.
[GROANS]
JOHN: All right, let's go.
Back to work, guys.
Back to the gym, back
to the ring. Let's do it.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[COUGHS]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER TV]
- [ALLY LAUGHS]
[RAY CHUCKLES]
Feel my leg.
- Why?
- Just feel it.
[COUGHS]
- Hmm?
- They feel fat.
- Do you think they feel fat?
- Not really.
- Not really?
- Mm.
Why didn't you say "no"?
'Cause when you say "not really,"
it kind of sounds like they are fat.
MAN [OVER TV]: Three
million dollars! Do I hear...
[CHUCKLES] Don't get shitty.
Do I hear 125?
- 126?
- Don't get shitty.
I'm not shitty.
[PASSES GAS]
Are you all right?
[RAY PASSES GAS]
Yep.
Do you mind not farting in my face?
I didn't fart in your face.
Yeah, come on, don't. It's disgusting.
You should be happy I
fart in front of you.
Why should I be happy?
Well, I only fart in front of
people I'm comfortable with.
Just 'cause you feel
comfortable doing something
doesn't mean that you should do it.
So, if I... if I felt comfortable
taking a shit on your chest,
does it mean I should do it?
[OVER TV]: Oh! Ah, sold...
Do you want to take a shit on my chest?
- Maybe.
- Yeah?
Well?
Go for it.
Don't tempt me, pal.
I'm daring you.
All right.
[CHUCKLES] Huh?
- [GRUNTING]: I'll do it.
- Do it. Yeah, really?
But you got to take
your pants off first,
'cause you're just gonna end
up shitting in your pants.
- [LAUGHING]
- Huh?
You're an idiot. [GRUNTS]
- Where are you going?
- I got to have a wee.
RAY: You weed half an hour ago.
Thanks for keeping score.
- MAN [OVER TV]: So, what's your name, sir?
- CONTESTANT: Kevin.
I haven't peed for hours.
ALLY: Good for you.
It's not a competition.
Yeah, it is.
All right. Give us a kiss.
I don't want to go to school today.
Why not?
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
If there's something going
wrong, you can tell me.
Come on. What's wrong?
There's a girl at school, and
she's mean to me all the time.
What's she doing?
She calls me names and stuff.
Have you told your teacher about it?
No.
Do you want me to talk to her about it?
No, I'll tell her.
Okay.
Well, yeah, if you have
any problems, darling,
you just talk to your teacher,
'cause that's what
she's there for, okay?
- Okay.
- Uh-huh.
Mwah. Love you.
Bye. Love you.
RAY: Have a good day.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Mm.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING, SHOUTING]
VINCE: So, my girlfriend wanted
to go out with her friends,
like, have a girls' night out,
go clubbing, and, um...
Well, I don't really like
her going out without me.
So, yeah, we just started
fighting about it.
And why don't you like her
going out without you?
Oh, well...
I just don't.
Do you not trust her?
I mean, has she ever... has
she ever cheated on you?
No.
No, no. It's nothing like that.
I mean, not that I know of.
I guess the thing is, like...
Well, yeah.
Yeah, actually, I guess
I don't trust her.
And why do you think that is?
VINCE: Well, she's, like,
like, really fucking sexy,
you know. Like...
when she goes out, she wears these tiny
little fucking outfits, and,
you know, they don't leave
a whole lot to the imagination, so...
Here, look.
I'll show you.
- This is her.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- She's a fucking stunner, man.
- Yeah.
[CARLO COUGHS]
Let's have a look.
Oh, holy shit, mate.
If my missus looked like that,
I'd never let her leave the house.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Okay. Thank-thank you, Carlo.
VINCE: So, when me and
her go out together,
guys will just come up
and start hitting on her
while I'm standing there.
You know, like, that's,
like... the last guy
I bashed was because of that.
Uh, this fucking bloke just comes up
and starts hitting on her right
in front of me, you know?
- And she loves the attention, so...
- Right, so...
RAY: Can I ask you something?
VINCE: Yeah.
How many blokes has she slept with?
- Ray...
- VINCE: It's all right.
Like, 30, 40.
No wonder you don't trust her, man.
I mean, shit, if she's slept
with that many blokes,
what's to stop her from
sleeping with a few more?
- You know what I mean?
- Exactly.
- Ray, that's enough.
- RAY: I mean, you know,
she goes there, she gets drunk.
Before you know it,
- she's fucking somebody else.
- PETER: Ray.
How about you keep your
misogyny to yourself?
- My what?
- Your misogyny.
- What's that?
- Um...
A-According to the dictionary,
a misogynist is a person
who despises women.
I don't despise women.
Well, from what I'm hearing here,
it sounds like you don't
think very highly of them.
I got a girlfriend. I got a daughter.
Hey, what are you saying?
Like, I hate 'em or something, or... ?
Plenty of history's great misogynists
have had daughters and girlfriends, Ray.
Like who?
Like... plenty.
Name one.
I think we should, um, move on.
Uh...
Hugo.
HUGO: I managed to drive to
work today without incident.
PETER: That's terrific.
RAY: Britt?
What are you doing? You gonna
come have some tea or what?
What you doing?
What's the matter?
Who put that up there?
- Who did that?
- BRITTANY: Taylor.
- [SETS DOWN PHONE]
- [SIGHS]
Dad, why does she hate me so much?
Look, not everybody is
gonna like you, darling.
- Okay?
- Okay.
And you can't make
people like you, okay?
But you can make them fear you.
I don't want people to be scared of me.
Well, I'm not saying that, you know,
you should make everybody scared of you.
But, um, if people don't respect you,
that's when you make 'em fear you.
So, if people respect me,
I don't need to scare them?
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
But if people... see, if
people don't respect you,
and you still treat them with respect,
then you're a doormat,
if you understand what I mean.
- What does that mean?
- Well, you know, like a doormat.
A doormat is a person who lets
other people walk all over 'em.
- Okay?
- Okay.
And that's not the kind
of person you want to be.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna take care of this
problem for you, okay?
- Okay.
- This Taylor...
Look at me, darling. Look at me.
She's not gonna bother you again, okay?
All right? I promise you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Now, you want to come have some tea?
What are we having?
- Pizza.
- Johan's?
Mm-hmm.
With the bacon?
Of course.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
[CROWD CHEERING, BOOING]
Excuse me, guys.
Thank you. Thank you.
Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry, guys.
- Is that another goal?
- Yeah.
What's up with all the
fucking hand passing, man?
It's like a game of hot potato.
[LAUGHS]
These blokes need to harden up.
Every time they get the
ball, they shit themselves.
- Mm.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
_
GARY: Oh, shit.
Mate, I need a favor.
- What?
- I need you to come
around my place and put a
password on my computer.
Why?
'Cause I'm watching too
much fucking porn, man.
Every day, I'm jerking off.
Twice a day sometimes.
Fucking serious.
Why don't you pick the password?
'Cause if I know the password,
I'll just unblock it.
Well, if you ask me, I'm
not gonna tell you.
I know. That's the whole point of it.
[CROWD CHEERING]
That's it. Just score another goal.
Get on to it!
- Well, don't get shitty.
- I won't.
You will. You'll get shitty.
If I don't tell you
what the password is, you'll get shitty.
- No, I won't.
- Yes, you will.
Yeah, all right. Maybe I will,
but no matter what,
just don't tell me, all right?
- And save my marriage, for God's sake.
- [LAUGHS]
[CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
What's up?
[CROWD CHEERING]
Have you got an address?
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
MAN: Who's there?
Freddy sent me over.
Freddy sent you?
Yep.
- MAN 2: Who is it, man?
- MAN 1: I don't fucking know.
Why?
You want to let me in, mate, or what?
- MAN 2: What's he want?
- I don't know.
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
After you.
H-How you doing?
Hey, good, man. How you doing?
- Good.
- Excellent.
Yeah.
So, Freddy's been trying to call you.
Ah, yeah. No...
I mean, we've run out of credit, eh.
Sorry, man.
Uh-huh.
Sorry.
So, you're supposed to do a
job for him or something?
Oh.
Yeah, yeah, job-job's done.
- D-Do you want to see?
- MAN 2: Ah, yeah.
- Yeah? Yeah, come...
- Yeah, come through.
Just come this way, then.
[GRUNTS]
So, uh, we were gonna dump him
in the hills, but it got light,
like, the sun came up, so
we brought him back here.
But as soon as it gets dark,
we're gonna go get rid of him.
How hot's the car?
- What do you mean?
- Well, when did you steal it?
Oh, it's my car.
It's our car. It's our car.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yello?
RAY [OVER PHONE]: What
do you think you're doing?
What?
You're using these
idiots to do hits now?
No, mate. I just thought
I would give them a go
and see how they went.
Oh, okay. Well, I'll tell
you how they went, mate.
They've grabbed this guy,
they've killed him... whoever he was...
and now they've got him
in the boot of their car
in their garage
because they didn't feel like
getting rid of the body just yet.
Yeah, all right, settle...
settle down, will you, mate?
Don't fucking tell me to settle down.
- He hung up on me.
- Aw.
[CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING]
Yello?
Funny. Look, I'm sorry, mate, okay?
I-I didn't think you'd mind
me using them on this one.
I mean, they charge a
quarter what you do.
All right? And, I mean,
I'm having a bad week this week.
Mate, you've been having a bad
week for the last 20 years.
- Yeah, I know. I know.
- Well, do something about it.
- Well, like what?
- I don't know. Not my problem.
- So, what do you want to do?
- I don't know. You tell me.
I can't read it from here.
What do you think?
Well, they're drug-fucked, mate.
If they get pinched,
they're gonna roll on you.
Yeah, okay, well, dig a hole,
put the dead guy in, and, uh...
and put the other two in with him.
All right.
How much is this gonna cost me?
90.
90?!
Yeah. 30 each, mate.
I'd charge anybody else 40 each.
Yeah. Okay, and I appreciate that,
but, look, it's not like you
got to do a lot of work here.
You know? I mean, one
of them's dead already.
Yeah, but I still got to bury him.
Sure, but you're charging me
like you got to kill him.
All right.
Ten to get rid of the dead guy,
30 each for the other two.
- 70.
- Okay,
and I appreciate the
discount there, mate,
but-but the other two guys...
I mean, you know, it's
not like you got to dig
three holes, you know.
Y-You're only gonna put 'em
all in the one hole, so...
Yeah, but I got to dig
a much bigger hole.
Well, get them to dig it.
Why don't you come down here,
yeah, and you can dig it?
I'm not gonna...
Why would I...
Fucking slimy little prick.
Hung up on me again.
[CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING]
- Hello?
- 60.
65, take it or leave it.
[SIGHS]
Yeah. Deal.
I don't want to wait six
months for my money, either.
Yeah, I know. You'll-you'll
have the money next week.
You know the thing that
shits me about you?
There's only one thing?
You haggle over every cent
you got to pay me, right?
And then you get into the
casino, you blow 100 grand
- like it's nothing.
- Yeah, I know, I know.
Yeah, you know.
All right. Bye.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SIGHS]
[LIGHTER CLICKING]
[INHALING]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
I'm gonna get a car.
Oh, just use ours, mate.
Can't use yours.
- Why not? Why not?
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [DOOR SHUTS]
- I don't know, man.
[PARKING BRAKE SETS]
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
- Lift him up.
- I am, man. Wait.
RICK: Got him?
- Ooh!
- RICK: You fucking idiot.
WAZ: Shut up, man.
You want to take the head?!
[RICK GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- WAZ: Ah, man. This stinks.
- Fuck.
♪ ♪
WAZ: How do you get on with the ex?
RAY: Oh, not too bad.
She's remarried, but...
[CLEARS THROAT] ... yeah, we get on.
[SNIFFS]
I've got a... I-I got a daughter.
- Eh?
- Yeah.
How old is she?
She's, um...
- she's six, eh.
- Mm.
Ava.
- Beautiful.
- Yeah.
- She gets that-that from her mum, eh?
- Mm.
You see her?
WAZ: Nah. Not-not anymore, really.
How come?
Uh, the ex won't let me, man.
- Yeah.
That's cool, man. Like...
I know I'm a fuck-up.
Just need to get off the drugs, man.
WAZ: Yeah.
Tell me about it, bro. Fuck.
I tell you, man, these...
these last 24 hours, I just...
I'm not cut out for this shit. I...
This is not me. No. No offense, eh.
Eh, it's not for everybody, mate, so...
So are you, like, you from
Sydney originally, or...
Nah. Country boy.
What brought you up here?
You know, work, mainly, but, uh...
Eh, I wouldn't mind
getting back to the...
back to the country one day,
but I got my daughter here
- and me brother, so...
- Oh.
- I got a bro as well, man.
- Mm.
- He's, uh, he's back in Perth.
- Yeah.
He's a fucking muso, man.
He's killing it, eh, like...
You heard of the band More or Less?
- No.
- Yeah.
We started it together, man,
- like, me and him.
- Mm.
We used to write songs
together and shit.
Fucking, like, playing gigs.
Fucking...
Do-do you, like, play any
musical instruments?
Nah.
Tried to learn how to play the drums
- when I was a kid, but...
- [CHUCKLES]
That's what I am, eh.
Yeah, I'm a drummer.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, man.
Yeah, I-I'll fucking teach you. Hey.
Yeah. Well, I don't
have a drum kit, so...
Yeah. I-I don't either, man.
But if you buy one, then
I'll-I'll teach you how...
- I wouldn't charge.
- Mm.
It'd just be... We'd have,
like, fucking drum sessions.
[RADIO KNOB CLICKS]
♪ No less than the trees and the stars ♪
♪ You have a right to be here ♪
♪ And whether or not ♪
♪ It is clear to you ♪
- ♪ No doubt... ♪
- Put it out.
- Fuck off.
- ♪ The universe is unfolding... ♪
RICK: Shit!
- Sorry about that.
- Fucking motherfucker.
All right, good one, buddy.
RICK: Yeah, well, what are
you gonna do about it?
- Put the fucking gun away.
- Yeah, shut the fuck up.
- Rick!
- Go on, what'd you say?
- Just chill out, man.
- No,
shut the fuck up! I'm the
fucking boss here, okay?
WAZ: Okay, okay, chill!
- No, you're not the boss of me, okay?
- Rick, okay...
What the fuck?!
♪ For the world is full of trickery ♪
♪ But let this not blind you ♪
♪ To what virtue there is ♪
♪ Many persons strive for high ideals ♪
♪ And everywhere life
is full of heroism ♪
♪ Be yourself ♪
♪ Especially do not feign affection ♪
♪ Neither be cynical about love... ♪
[GASPING]
Hey.
♪ Take kindly the council of the years ♪
♪ Gracefully surrendering
the things of youth ♪
♪ Nurture strength of spirit ♪
♪ To shield you in sudden misfortune ♪
♪ But do not distress
yourself with imaginings ♪
♪ Many fears are born of
fatigue and loneliness ♪
♪ Beyond a wholesome discipline ♪
♪ Be gentle with yourself ♪
- ♪ You are a child... ♪
- ♪ You are a child ♪
- ♪ Of the universe ♪
♪ No less than the trees and the stars ♪
♪ You have a right... ♪
[COUGHS]
[SPITS]
- ♪ It is clear to you ♪
♪ No doubt the universe is unfolding ♪
♪ No doubt the universe ♪
- ♪ Is unfolding... ♪
- ♪ As it should ♪
♪ As it should ♪
♪ Therefore, be at peace with God ♪
♪ Whatever you conceive him to be ♪
♪ And whatever your
labors and aspirations ♪
♪ In the noisy confusion of life ♪
♪ Keep peace with your soul ♪
♪ With all its sham,
drudgery and broken dreams ♪
♪ It is still a beautiful world ♪
♪ Be careful ♪
♪ Strive to be happy ♪
♪ You are a child ♪
♪ Of the universe ♪
♪ No less than the trees and the stars ♪
♪ You have a right to be here ♪
♪ You are a child ♪
♪ Of the universe ♪
♪ No less than the trees and the stars ♪
♪ You have a right to be here ♪
♪ You are a child ♪
♪ Of the universe ♪
♪ No less than the trees and the stars ♪
♪ You have a right... ♪