[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
Dad?
Dad.
[WHISPERING]: Dad.
Can I sleep with you?
[GROANS] What's wrong?
Monsters.
All right.
[SIGHS]
You know what I used to do
when I was scared of monsters?
What?
I used to give them names.
Really?
I used to make friends with them
and talk to them and all
that kind of stuff.
Why don't you try that?
Okay.
But don't give them, like...
don't give them scary names,
give them funny names.
Like what?
Well, I used to have one that
used to live under my bed.
I used to call him Gus.
- That's funny.
- Mm-hmm.
See, and if it's funny,
then you're not gonna be so
scared of them, you know?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
You get some sleep, eh?
Hmm?
[SIGHS]
You gonna stay under there
all night, are you?
- BRITTANY: Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Night-night.
- Good night.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
RAY: What's that?
FREDDY: You never had basmati?
- No.
- That's Indian rice.
It's, uh, it's really long grain.
You got to try it.
Where do you get that from?
Oh, just at the n... Fuck!
- Jesus.
- Kill the fucking thing, will ya?
- Fucking relax, mate. Jeez.
- Kill it!
I don't come cheap, mate, so, uh...
Yo... You fucking smart-ass.
I'll give you 50 bucks.
- Just kill it.
- [CHUCKLING] They're harmless.
Mate, I just had a double
heart attack here, okay?
So I don't really think you can
say that they're harmless.
They can't hurt you.
Well, it's hurting me right
now, psychologically.
I nearly had a bloody heart attack.
[CHUCKLES] You know what you need to do?
- You need to kill it.
- No.
What you need to do...
- is face your fears.
- Oh, yeah, fuck that shit.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
- Come here.
- Ray, Ray, no! Hey! Ray!
I'm not... No! Hey! I'm not... Don't!
I'm not messing around, dude.
Dude, when have you ever heard
of a huntsman ever
fucking hurting anybody?
Yeah, I don't... Well,
I'm sure they hurt people.
Probably kill people, too.
- Oh, they kill people, do they?
- Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Yeah. Well, you imagine some old lady,
she's at home, right? She looks up,
there's a massive huntsman, right?
She has a heart attack. She dies.
A week later, they find her.
The fucking huntsman's gone.
The paramedics come in. They say,
"Oh, heart attack. Natural causes."
But it wasn't natural causes, was it?
- It was a dirty, great hairy fucking huntsman.
- [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, y-you think it's funny.
They're probably responsible
for killing more old
people in this country,
- and we don't even know about it.
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Freddy, Kim is here to see you.
- FREDDY: Okay.
- Thanks, love. I'll be right out.
- Okay.
[SIGHS]
- [EXHALES]
- [RAY GROANS]
Just kill it, will you?
I don't kill bugs, mate.
Oh, you don't kill bugs,
you just kill people?
I got to draw the line somewhere.
Uh, you all right?
[EXHALES] No, I'm not all right.
[PANTING]
Shield me from it or
something, will you?
- Don't let it fucking jump.
- Okay. Okay.
Oh, look at the size of it.
- Come on.
- That thing'd eat ya.
- [YELLS]
- Don't! You mongrel bastard.
[CHUCKLES]
So, uh, why don't you tell
Ray your story, mate?
Okay, uh...
my daughter, uh, Jenny...
she went missing in '95.
And, uh... we never, um... The cops...
We nev-we never found out
what happened to her.
Uh, so, um...
The cops, uh, were looking
at this one guy, uh,
- as a suspect.
- Mm.
And one of the cops that I was...
had most of the dealings with...
um, he was convinced that this guy, um,
a guy called Dennis Miller...
... uh, he was convinced
that he knew something, you know?
And he was involved,
but the cops couldn't get enough, uh,
hard evidence to charge him, you know.
And this guy, Miller,
he was a convicted...
He was convicted of,
uh... fiddling with kids.
And he did some, uh,
some time in jail. And, uh...
With the wife and me, all these years...
it's been hard, mate. Um,
just the not knowing
what happened to Jenny.
And the thing is, uh, I got, uh...
uh, liver cancer, and I
don't have that long,
so I just need someone,
uh, to go and talk to this guy.
And, uh, I just want to know
what happened to my Jenny.
And, um, I don't want to, uh...
I don't want my wife not knowing,
and I don't-I don't want to
leave this world not knowing.
And I'd love to be able to
tell my wife what happened.
And, uh, look, it might be
asking too much, but, um...
You see, we-we...
we never got to bury her.
We never got to close the book.
If you could, uh, find out
what he did with her,
like, her remains...
Just so... we can just visit her.
RAY: How old was she?
Thirteen.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
Smells good.
Can I help you?
I hope so.
You normally just go walking
into people's houses?
What'd you do with Jenny Greer?
You better get out of here,
or I'll call the cops.
[RAY CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I'm serious.
Look, t... I don't want
any trouble, okay?
Oh, I don't want any trouble, mate.
I don't know this Jenny...
whatever you said her name was.
- Greer.
- Okay, Greer.
Uh-huh.
Take those.
Put 'em on.
What-what...
- Put 'em on.
- Okay.
So, Jenny's dad...
wants to know what happened to her.
I don't know.
He doesn't want the cops involved,
so you're not gonna get into trouble.
He just wants to know what
happened to her, right?
And he wants her remains.
So you tell me what I want to know,
and I'll get the fuck out of here,
and you'll never see me again, okay?
Swear to God, I don't know anything.
[RAY SIGHS]
I-I've got money.
[CHUCKLING]
I don't want your money.
I swear to God, I don't
know where she is.
Yeah, you said that.
What are you gonna do?
[FAUCET TURNS OFF]
Whatever it takes, mate. Come on.
- Come on. All right?
- No! [GRUNTING]
Ow! [GRUNTS]
[WHIMPERING]
[INSECTS TRILLING]
[GASPS, GRUNTS]
[COUGHING]
[PANTING]
[COUGHS]
It's pretty good, mate.
What's the herb you got in there?
- Basil.
- Basil?
Lovely.
- [PANTING]
- All right.
You seem like an okay
sort of a bloke, mate.
And I don't want to hurt you.
So just tell me what I want to know,
and I'll get out of your hair.
[GRUNTS]
I really would-would
like to help you, but...
... y-you got the wrong guy, mate.
I mean, I... I know with my...
I know I did some bad
things in the past, but...
I swear, I-I didn't do...
I don't know this Jenny.
I tried to be nice, mate, all right?
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHING]
You want some more, mate?
Where do you want it?
The Otford railway tunnel!
[CRYING]
Otford.
That's where she is.
Where in the tunnel?
I don't know, exactly, but...
... that's where I put it.
It?
Her.
That's where I put her, I mean.
I swear to God.
You believe in God, do you?
♪
RAY: Right here, left.
[INSECTS TRILLING]
Look ahead.
You look at me again,
I'll put one in your head.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[STRAINS]
[PANTS]
Help me get this out the way.
[GRUNTS]
Okay. You help me get this out?
[PANTING]
[ANIMALS HOOTING, CHITTERING, SQUAWKING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Oh...
[GROANING SOFTLY]
[TAKES DEEP BREATH]
Is he in there?
[SQUAWKING IN DISTANCE]
[WATER DRIPPING]
Do you know the pain that you've caused?
I'm sorry.
[WHIMPERS]
[PANTING QUIETLY]
[BIRDS SQUAWKING, CHIRPING]
Thank you.
♪ An old cowpoke went riding out ♪
♪ One dark and windy day ♪
♪ Upon a ridge he rested ♪
♪ As he went along his way ♪
♪ When all at once a mighty herd ♪
♪ Of red-eyed cows he saw ♪
♪ A-plowin' through the ragged skies ♪
♪ And up a cloudy draw ♪
♪ Yippee-ai-ay ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
♪ Yippee-ai-yo ♪
♪ The ghost herd ♪
♪ In the sky ♪
♪ Their brands were still on fire ♪
♪ And their hooves were made of steel ♪
♪ Their horns were black and shiny ♪
♪ And their hot breath he could feel ♪
♪ A bolt of fear went through him ♪
♪ As they thundered through the sky ♪
♪ For he saw the riders comin' hard ♪
♪ And he heard their mournful cry ♪
♪ Yippee-ai-ay ♪
♪ Yippee-ay-yo. ♪