Uh, so my name's Ray.
I'm, uh, Brittany's dad.
UM... [CHUCKLES]: I work
in the security industry.
So, basically, I work in a club.
And, um...
you know, my job is to kind of make sure
that people behave themselves
while they're in the... in the club.
Yeah, love?
Are you a bouncer?
Uh... Mm.
Yeah, there's a bit
more to it than that,
but, yeah, basically, um,
yeah, I'm a bouncer. Yeah, man?
You're pretty small for a bouncer.
Yeah, I guess, but, um,
it's not the size of the
dog in the fight, mate.
What does that mean?
Well, it's not the size
of the dog in the fight,
it's the size of the fight in the dog.
I don't get it.
Um...
Well, in a fight, what matters
is how much heart you've got.
That's kind of what decides a fight.
- Yeah, man?
- Do you think you could beat
my dad in a fight?
Well, I've never met
him, but, um, I'd...
I'd say...
- probably not.
- What about Conor McGregor?
Uh, uh, definitely,
definitely couldn't beat
Conor McGregor. Yeah, love?
Is your job dangerous?
Um...
No. Not really, no.
I wouldn't say it was. Yeah, mate?
Have you ever killed anybody?
Uh, once.
Really? What happened?
Uh, this kid was asking
me too many questions.
I'm just kidding, mate.
I'm just kidding.
[CHUCKLING]
Uh, okay, man.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
What, no socks went out of
fashion, did they, mate?
Your mate beat the shit
out of old Stan last night.
Dirk?
Yeah.
What happened?
Stan was getting flirty with Giselle.
You know, nothing out of the usual.
- Mm.
- Your mate comes in
like a bull at a gate,
starts getting rough.
Stan said something...
I don't know what.
Next second, old Stan's
laying on the ground,
getting his head stomped on.
Is he all right?
No, he's not all right.
I had to get Mandy to
take him to the hospital.
Now, I know he's your mate
and all, but he's got to go.
Mm.
[CHILD SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
DIRK: Hello?
It's me.
Hi, mate.
How you doing?
Eh. [CHUCKLES]
Feeling all right?
Yes, pretty much. [SNIFFS]
Not a bad joint.
Yeah, it's...
[GROANS]
... all I can bloody afford, isn't it?
You want a drink or something, mate?
A sandwich? Some pharmaceuticals?
Nah, I'm good.
[GRUNTS, EXHALES]
So you beat the shit
out of old Stan, eh?
- Yeah.
- Ooh.
He was getting pretty
handsy with, um, Giselle.
Mm.
- As usual.
- [CHUCKLES]
Dirty old bugger.
Well...
Got to fire you.
Oh, mate.
I'll leave you to it, all right?
Ray.
Yeah?
I don't want your money, mate.
[EXHALES]
KATE: Do you think...
how do I put this... do you think
there is a difference
in the act of killing
between when you were in the Army
and-and what you do now?
Does-does it feel any different?
No.
No difference at all?
No, killing's killing. Mm.
You know, you get medals in the Army
for when you kill people, but, you know,
I don't get those
anymore, but, you know...
Yeah. I can't imagine
hit men get medals.
Nah. We get paid better though, so...
Yeah? No one tells you what to do now.
Yeah. You know, if I want
to do a job, I do it.
If I don't want to do a job, I don't.
You know, I can say no.
- Yes or no.
- Mm.
Do you ever feel sorry
for any of your victims?
Not really, no.
- [SNIFFS]
- Never?
Why would I?
Well, what about their families?
What about 'em?
Well, doesn't it ever bother you...
you know, the pain that you're causing
the loved ones that are
left behind, grieving for...
for the person that
you've just murdered?
You know, I killed people when
I was in the Army, you know?
Nobody, you know...
They had families, so...
Yeah, sure, but I think...
you know, I think the
difference is choice.
When you're in the Army,
you-you don't have a choice.
But here, you-you do.
You've got a choice.
- You don't actually have to do this job.
- No, no, no,
- no, no, no, no, no.
- You could... I mean, you could choose
- to do something different.
- No, no, no, no.
I chose to join the Army.
You know, I could say, like,
somebody put a gun to my head
and said you got to join
the army or, you know...
I had a choice. That's-that's
what I decided to do.
I was gonna go over there
and fucking kill people,
- so...
- Yeah, okay.
You got no problem with that.
- Okay.
- As soon as I come back here
and I start doing the same thing,
suddenly you're all, fucking,
I don't know, "high
and mighty" about it.
Like, you know...
like I should feel bad
about it or something.
- Should I feel bad about it?
- Uh,
I'm-I'm just asking a question.
Yeah, you're asking some questions.
Yeah. It's the questions you're asking,
- you know what I mean?
- Well, okay, well, so,
what about... what about your daughter?
I mean, you-you know,
from what you've told me,
you really love her.
I'm sure she loves you.
Surely she'd be really,
you know, devastated
if something happened to you.
- Hey, my friend.
- Hi.
Get that one and a pack
of John Kelsey's, friend.
Money, champ.
Thanks, mate.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Could've just had one of these, prez.
No, I don't smoke that.
What's wrong with them?
It's all the chemicals,
mate. It tastes like shit.
[RAY COUGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
Oi.
[CHUCKLES]
What, are you stalking me, mate?
- Hey? How are you?
- Hey, good.
What you doing... What the fuck?! Jesus.
[GRUNTING]
Get him!
Hold him, hold him, hold him.
- Got him.
- Hold him.
- VINNIE: Kev!
- I got him.
- [THUDDING]
- VINNIE: Kev!
RAY: I got him. Got him.
VINNIE: Kev!
I got you.
RAY: Good? Let's get out of here.
Let's go, mate.
- VINNIE: Kev!
- [ENGINE STARTS]
So who's paying you?
Your VP.
Alex?
Mm-hmm.
[SIGHS] Jesus. Fuck.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS] Uh, you got a smoke?
Quit.
You quit?
Good for you, mate.
I got some rollies in me pocket.
You good I get 'em out?
Hey, go for it.
[VINNIE SIGHS]
They paying you all right?
Yeah.
Mind me asking how much?
- $250.
- Fuck.
Jesus. Yeah, well, you're good.
I'll give you that.
I never saw it coming.
Nothing personal.
Yeah, I know.
I'm surprised I've fucking lived
this long, to tell you the truth.
Mm.
I'm guessing if I was
to try and buy you out,
you'd just pocket the
cash and kill me anyway.
Still got to get your $250.
- Mm-hmm.
- [CHUCKLES]
It was weird, but...
I mean, I'd never shot
any bloke before that.
And it's not like it is
in the movies, right?
- It's different.
- Mm.
And this fellow, I remember,
his legs went all sort of wobbly
and sat down on the floor.
He just looked real fucking tired,
you know. Just real tired.
He looked up at me, you know.
He sort of looked me right in the eye.
Just said, "Fuck, mate."
Then he just...
[EXHALES]
That was it.
Lights went out of his eyes.
20 years, and that bloke still
comes to me in my dreams.
Every time I see him, he just...
looks at me with this look, you know.
That same look.
Doesn't say anything, just...
just looks at me.
Scares the shit out of me.
You don't get that?
Blokes you've knocked come
to you in your dreams?
Sometimes.
Doesn't bother you?
[CHUCKLES]
Bothers the shit out of me.
Not enough to make you
want to quit, though.
[CHUCKLES]
Every job's got its downside, man.
♪ ♪
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
Come on, mate.
Right, eh? [GRUNTS]
Let him go, man.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- [SIGHS]
- [GROANS] Keep an eye out.
Cool.
[PLANE APPROACHING IN DISTANCE]
[EXHALES]
Top spot.
Yeah.
I'll see you in your dreams.
[SIGHS]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[WATER DRAINING]
[PHONE BUZZING, RINGTONE PLAYING]
[GROANS]
[BUZZING, RINGTONE CONTINUE]
Yeah?
[SNIFFS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
Ooh.
So what happened?
I was asleep upstairs, woke up.
Saw a light, uh, spinning around.
- Mm.
- Got up, went to the money room.
Got clocked as soon as I
walked in the fucking door.
Did you get a look at him?
Nah. It was too fucking dark.
What about the CCTV?
Yeah, I got about 30
seconds of the prick.
- Mm.
- He got in back here.
- Yeah.
- Knew what he was doing.
How much did he get?
FREDDY: The night's takings.
It's Dirk.
Fucking little...
I give the guy a job.
I treat him like a fucking...
Shit.
I know he's your mate and
all, but I want him gone.
- What do you mean, gone?
- I mean gone-gone.
I'm not gonna whack him.
Yeah, well, I'll find somebody who will.
[ALARM CHIRPS]
[GRUNTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
- [SNORING]
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [SNORTS]
- [PAGES TURNING]
Oh!
Bloody hell, Ray.
- Wakey, wakey.
- [SIGHS, SNIFFLES]
What's going on?
Need a favor.
What?
Need some backup.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
[ENGINE STOPS]
[GROANS]
Mm.
Smoke, Ray?
Nah, I quit.
- What?
- Mm.
When?
About a month ago.
Cold turkey?
Yeah, I started cold turkey, but...
I was just getting too fucking
angry all of a sudden.
- [LAUGHS]
- I had to get on the fucking patches.
- That work?
- Yeah, they do.
You start off...
Like, you start off with
the strong... ones.
- Mm.
- And then, like, you have them
for a week, and then you go to the next,
- you know, less strong...
- Yeah.
- ... less strong week by week.
And, yeah... eventually...
you know, got off 'em.
- Wow.
- You thinking of quitting,
- are you?
- No. God, no.
[SIGHS]
It's fresh.
It's romantic.
What's going on, Ray?
[RAY SIGHS]
You got to leave town, mate.
[LAUGHING]: What?
I know you ripped Freddy off.
You got to go, mate.
You got to go today, and
you can't ever come back.
- Yeah. Nah, fuck that.
- [SHORT CHUCKLE]
You got to go.
Or what?
Are you gonna shoot me?
Do it.
You remember when I killed
that kid in Uyghur prov?
Mm.
That was it for me.
It's like...
... my life had promise,
you know?
Had a... spark.
Then, after that, just...
[SCOFFS]
Mate, pick a spot.
Anywhere. All right?
Anywhere you want to go,
- you know?
- Mm.
I'll drive you, all right?
I'll set you up.
You know, get you on your feet.
Okay.
[WAVES CRASHING]
Hey, sorry about all
that shit with Freddy.
Forget it.
Come on.
Nah.
I got to go.
Sorry.
[THUD]
♪ ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
♪ If you miss ♪
♪ The train I'm on ♪
♪ You will know ♪
♪ That I am gone ♪
♪ You can hear ♪
♪ The whistle blow ♪
♪ A hundred miles... ♪
♪ A hundred miles ♪
♪ You can hear ♪
♪ The whistle blow ♪
♪ A hundred miles... ♪
♪ Lord, I'm one ♪
- ♪ Lord, I'm two ♪
- ♪ Lord, I'm three. ♪
- ♪ Lord. ♪