So when'd you see him last? [SNIFFLES]
Last week.
Did he, uh, tell you I got
him a job at the club?
Yeah, he mentioned that.
How are you for money?
Yeah, we're okay.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Yeah, we'll be okay, but thanks.
Mm.
Jesus.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
I mean...
I haven't mentioned
anything to Maddy yet.
[WHISPERING]: You're not gonna tell her
that he, um... you know?
- She's seven.
- Okay. Mm.
Fair enough.
I'll just say it was an accident.
Mm-hmm.
Aye.
What a fucking dickhead.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
[HUMMING A TUNE]
- All right.
- What you want to see?
Uh, what do you guys want to see?
- That.
- Yeah. That looks good.
"Winnie's Big Break."
- Yeah. Want to watch that one?
- What about Outlanding?
- No.
- That's a documentary.
- No, it's a movie.
- No, it... Look.
"Based on a true story."
Yeah, it doesn't mean
it's a doco, though.
- Yeah.
- No, it just means
it's based on a true story.
No. We want to watch that one.
- Winnie's Big Break?
- Yeah.
That's boring.
No, that's way lamer. Look at it...
- No, that's lame.
- No. Who wants to see
Winnie's Big Break?
- Outvoted.
- I don't care.
♪
Shh.
What?
- Stop.
- What?
- [MUSIC PLAYING]
- [INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA]
[HUMMING A TUNE]
I'm bored.
Me too.
- Help me find some socks, then.
- BRITTANY: Socks?
- Boring.
- Socks are important.
Why?
Well, they stop your feet from smelling.
Your feet stink anyway.
Yeah, Uncle Ray, your feet stink.
- Do they?
- They pong.
Yeah.
You pong.
BRITTANY: That doesn't
even make any sense.
Well, you don't make any sense.
Can we go and look at the bikes, Dad?
Yeah!
- Where's the bikes?
- Over there.
Please?
All right.
But don't go anywhere else.
- Hey, Maddy?
- Yeah?
Pick something out for your birthday.
- Okay.
- Can I get something, Dad?
Is it your birthday?
- No.
- Well?
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA]
Can I get this, Dad?
No.
- Please?
- No. Put it back.
You never buy me anything.
I buy you stuff all the time.
- So buy me this.
- No.
Why?
'Cause if I do buy you
everything you want,
you're gonna grow up
to be a spoiled brat.
I don't even know what that is.
A spoiled brat is a person who
gets everything they want
and they're weak and whingy and whiny.
Is that what you want
to be when you grow up?
- No.
- Come on, put it back.
Where's Maddy?
Um, I don't know.
She rode off somewhere.
- Rode off where?
- Uh, around there.
I want to look over here.
No, you stay with me, please.
Is that the bike she was on?
I think so.
Maddy.
[SINGSONGY]: Maddy.
[SIGHS] For fuck's sake.
[KIDS LAUGHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- How you going, love?
- Hello.
- Lost me daughter.
- Oh, what's her name?
- Maddy.
- Okay, I'll get on the PA.
All right.
Maddy, can you please
come to the front counter?
- You stay here.
- Maddy to the front counter, please?
- How'd you go, love?
- Uh, nothing yet.
- Where did you lose her?
- Uh, just down on the left.
Uh, in the swimming...
Have you checked the changing rooms?
Whereabouts are they?
I'll show you. Come.
This way. I like your sneakers.
BRITTANY: Thanks.
Okay, you take that side
- and I'll take this side.
- Yeah.
Have you got CCTV cameras, have you?
Yeah.
You monitor those, do you?
Yeah, in the back.
All right, can we go and have a...
- look at them?
- Sure. Come with me.
Come on.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER IN DISTANCE]
- [LAUGHS]
- Wayne?
And how's this, right?
- He never got the feature.
- Wayne?
- And then...
- Wayne.
... and then kicked him out. [LAUGHS]
Wa...
- What the fuck?
- Last ten minutes, mate.
I want to see your footage. Okay?
- Where were we, love?
- Uh, the water sports section.
RAY: Water sports section,
- last ten minutes.
- Why?
Wayne, please. His kid's missing.
RAY: Keep going.
WAYNE: Well, that's ten minutes.
Okay. I'll let you know, mate.
Keep going.
Okay, stop it there. All right?
Zoom in on the guy.
Okay.
Should I call the police?
- Nah.
- Jesus Christ.
Okay.
COMMENTATOR [ON TV]:
Blueboy going very well.
- [RINGTONE PLAYING]
- Roppinghoe in contention
as they run towards the home turn!
It's Roppinghoe, Blueboy...
Raymondo.
Need you to listen, mate, all right?
Dirk's kid's been grabbed, okay,
from a shopping center.
I got a photo of the guy.
I'm gonna send that to you now, okay?
Yeah, okay, mate. What do you need?
You reckon you can get a
list of all the sex offenders
around the Marrickville area?
Yeah, yeah. I got a cop
I can reach out to.
I'll get that ASAP and get
it to you. Anything else?
Uh, look, anything you can do, mate.
- Yep.
- Um, I really need your help.
- Okay?
- Yep, I'm on it.
Just wait.
[DIALING]
[ROCK PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
Mm.
- _
- Fuck.
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[MUTTERS]
Yeah, mate?
Mate, I need your help.
Mate of mine's kid's been grabbed
from a shopping center in Marrickville.
- What?
- Yeah, she got grabbed.
Somebody grabbed her. Okay?
I got a photo of the guy.
All right? I'm gonna send
that to you now, all right?
- Okay.
- Great, mate. Okay.
And, uh, I need you to get out there,
try to track this prick down, all right?
Yeah, don't worry, I'm on it.
Okay. Thanks, mate.
[GRUNTS]
Put your belt on, Britt.
[PHONE WHOOSHES]
- Seat belt, please.
- I want Mom.
Look, we're gonna find Maddy, all right?
Please, put your belt on, okay?
Come on, come on.
- JACINTA: Hey. Hey. Shh...
- [CRYING]: Mom.
Shh. It's okay.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
- Whoa, Gaz. Hey, please.
- How you going? Hey.
- Please, please. Sit.
What do you know?
So I put word out,
- spoke to some people.
- Mm.
One of my associates knows this guy
who told story about this fellow
who he was buying weed from.
He said when they went to do deal,
this guy, he says,
"Do you want to see my toys?"
- Toys?
- Toys.
Fucking hell.
You got a name for this guy?
Pidgy.
- Pidgy.
- Pidgy, like pigeon.
- Pidgy. Right.
- Hmm.
Where is she?
What?
Oh! [GRUNTING]
Where is she?
Pidgy?
Yeah. Who are you?
I'm a friend of Hasan's.
I just need some information.
All right. Come in.
- RAY: Five...
- MAN: I swear to God, mate,
- ... four...
- I haven't... I don't know.
- ... three...
- I haven't done anything.
- Please, mate, please!
- ... two...
- ... one.
- No, please stop! I don't know anything.
Please.
Where were you this morning?
- Where were you this morning?!
- I haven't left.
- I haven't left the house.
- GARY: Did you buy some weed
off a bloke a couple
of months ago who said
he had some "toys"
he wanted to sell you?
Mate, you just need to be
honest with me now. All right?
If you're straight with me, then
we got nothing to worry about.
But if you're not, then we
got a fucking problem, okay?
Who's this bloke with the "toys"?
Who's this guy?
- Who is it?
- Don't know! I don-I don't know.
I've never seen that guy before.
I swear to God. I'm
sorry, I don't know him.
- I'm sorry.
- PIDGY: Yeah, I bought
a couple of kilos off a bloke in Enmore.
- Okay.
- Been buying off him
for a couple months.
One day, he says, do I
want to buy some toys?
And I said, "Yeah, sure," but...
I didn't know.
I thought he must be talking
about guns or something.
Anyway, we go down in his basement.
There's a concealed room that's
behind a cupboard, right?
Big old lock on the door.
We open it, we go in...
There's these kids,
just there.
_
- [TOILET FLUSHING]
- Babe.
MICHELE: Yeah?
Where's all the dunny paper?
Are we out?
Well there's none in the bathroom.
Must be out, then.
Well, there was, like,
ten rolls in there last week.
Yeah?
So, like, that's a roll a day.
What are you, like, shitting
ten times a day or something?
No.
Hey, look, I'm not having a go at you.
I'm just trying to understand
why you need so much of it.
Okay. Here's how it goes.
- I pee, I wipe, okay?
- Yeah?
Okay, then I use my intimate wipes.
Your intimate wipes?
Yes. Then I grab some more toilet paper
and I wipe again.
Why do you wipe again?
Because my intimate wipes are wet.
I can't be walking around
all wet down there,
- can I?
- Okay. So how much...
Like, when you grab the
toilet paper to dry yourself,
how many squares are we talking?
I don't go by squares. I scrunch.
All right, well, why don't
you just take one square,
- or fold... One, like, tw...
- Because I'll get pee
on my hands, that's why I scrunch.
You don't want me touching you
with pee on my hands, do you?
Well, don't you wash
your hands afterwards?
Yes, I do wash my hands.
I'm sorry... can you not afford
one roll of toilet paper a day?
Hey, I can buy a truckload
- of the stuff.
- Then why are you being such a dick?
I'm not being a dick. I'm just, like...
- [KNOCKING]
- [SIGHS]
- Hey, mate.
- Need to talk to ya.
What about?
Want to talk to your son-in-law.
- Nasir? About what?
- Dirk's kid.
- Yeah.
Mate, I can tell you right now,
- he's got nothing to do with that.
- Let's go, mate.
- What?
- Let's go. Come on.
- Go where?
- Come on. We're going, mate.
Ray. Ray. I've got shit to do.
- I don't give a fuck. Let's go.
- He's an accountant.
[ENGINE IDLING]
[HORN HONKS]
- [HORN HONKS]
- Jesus Christ, Ray!
[FREDDY SIGHS]
Now, mate, this is family here,
so just take it easy, okay?
Let me do the talking, okay?
Okay?
Relax.
Thank you. Appreciate it.
- Hi, love.
- Hey, Da...
- Dad...
- Ray. Ray, Ray.
Ray, Ray! Ray...
- [GUNSHOT]
- Ray, Jesus Christ, Ray!
- What are you doing?
- Everybody down!
What are you... Ray, please, please,
- think about this.
- SOPHIA [CRYING]: Dad!
Think about this.
- Where's the kid?
- What?
FREDDY: Ray. Ray. Ray, Ray, Ray.
Don't!
Where's the kid?
- Jesus Christ, Ray!
- Shut the fuck up.
- Please... please don't do this, Ray.
- Shut up!
- I want to help you.
- Which kid?
- Ray...
One more time, pal. You don't tell me
what I want to know... right...
I'm gonna spread your granny's brains
- all over the fucking carpet.
- Ray, don't!
- No, Ray.
- Wait, wait! No! What kid?
Shoot me!
- Shoot me.
- [SOPHIA PANTING]
Ray.
- Ray, please.
- Look, I'm sorry.
Look, I'm... I'm-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what I said.
I was angry, that's-that's it.
My brother was a hothead.
I know. I just...
I just miss him.
Listen to what he's saying.
Please, Ray. Please.
Please.
- Please, Ray.
- [GRANDMOTHER WHIMPERING]
Oh, God.
- [NASIR SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
- [GRANDMOTHER CRYING]
- [CAR REVS]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
Fuckin' hell, Freddy!
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I didn't know. You all right,
darling? I'm so sorry.
I am so sorry.
[PHONE DINGS]
_
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[TRUCK PASSES BY]
- Pidgy.
- Hi.
- You must be Gary.
- Tim?
Yeah. Come on in.
[PIDGY GRUNTS SOFTLY]
So...
how much you after?
How much you got?
Four.
- Four?
- But I can get heaps more.
Okay. It's good stuff?
- [SHORT CHUCKLE]
- No, Gar, it's always good.
Yeah?
- Would you like to try it?
- No, no.
Pidgy vouches.
Okay.
You winning, mate?
- [LAUGHING]: No, he's shit.
- Huh?
Uh, don't worry about it.
It's all right.
- GARY: All good?
- Yeah.
Pidge, you want to do that,
- I'll get the cash? Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Ten?
- Ten.
Ten.
Oh, fuck.
- Oh.
- GARY: So, um...
... what else you got?
All sorts of shit.
Guns?
Right this way.
Okay.
All right. Just got this...
shotty for two grand.
Oh, yeah. 870.
- Yeah. Nice.
- [GRUNTS]
I can do this Glock...
for four.
And everyone wants one of those.
Yeah. Nice.
Yeah, look, I don't need any now,
but good to know where I can get 'em.
Righto.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Can I get you some pills?
No, no, I'm all good.
How about some coke?
No, mate, no.
- Speed?
- No.
- All good, mate.
- Uppers?
- [CHUCKLES]: No.
- Downers?
- No, all good.
- [CHUCKLES]
Bloody hell. You're a one-stop shop.
Got everything, mate.
What do you got down here? Hmm?
Kitchen sinks?
- [LAUGHS]
- Hey?
TIM: Well, it was a pleasure
doing business with you.
Get on the ground.
What?
Get on the fucking ground.
What's your problem?
- [GRUNTS]
- [WOMAN GASPS]
Pidgy.
Tie 'em up. Get over there. Move it.
- Get the fuck over there!
- [TIM GRUNTS]
Where's the key to the
door with the lock on it?
- [PIDGY SHOUTS]
- What are you talking about?
Uh, don't shoot.
- The key to the toy room.
- PIDGY: Look at me. Tie it.
[PIDGY GRUNTS]
[TIM WHIMPERS]
Tie him up, Pidge.
[GRUNTING]
PIDGY: Hands!
GARY: The fuck you looking at?
[PIDGY PANTING, SIGHS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
♪
Maddy?
You Maddy? Yeah?
You know who I am?
Your Uncle Ray sent me.
He asked me to take you
home to your mum, okay?
You want to go home? Yeah?
Okay, okay, come on. Let's go. Come on.
Come on. Just go this way.
Go out this way.
Just jump in the back here.
There you go.
Righto, Maddy, you wait here. All right?
And I'll be back and I'll take
you back to see your mommy.
Okay? All right. Yeah. Okay.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Righto, Pidge.
Piss off.
Get up. Get up.
- WOMAN: Y-Yeah. Yeah.
- Get up, get up.
Fucking pusher cunt. Get up.
Move it.
Down. Go.
[WOMAN BREATHING SHAKILY]
The fuck you doing standing around?
Get in, get in, get in.
Get in.
Hey, listen...
just so you know,
we didn't do anything to her,
man. We just sell 'em.
[GRUNTS]
[PHONE DINGS]
_
How you goin', Maddy... you all right?
[INDICATOR CLICKING]
Oh...
Oh, darling. Oh, my God. Oh, God.
Mm.
Oh, my God, darling. [SNIFFLES]
Inside. Out of the car.
- All good?
- Thank you.
You're okay. [SNIFFLES]
♪
[ALL WHIMPERING]
[SCREAMS]
♪ Looka yonder ♪
♪ A big black cloud come ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
♪ Yonder on the horizon ♪
♪ Stopped at the mighty river ♪
♪ Sucked the damn thing dry ♪