- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Huh?
Rats!
Hey, is there someone in the restaurant?
Oh, yeah.
Aw, he looks scared.
Can we keep him? Can we keep him?
No.
We'll name him Bob Number One.
And, Dad, you can just
go by Bob Number Two,
or maybe no name at all.
Wait. Why would I be Bob
Number Two or no name?
- I am Bob.
- Well, yeah, but this is Bob,
so now we're, like, Bob and Bob.
- I don't like it.
- You can't just name a guy Bob.
Yeah, you can. Somebody did it to you.
- That's true.
- Bob Number Two is
throwing out some major 'tude right now.
- Isn't he, though?
- Yeah, lose the 'tude.
It is kind of nice to have
someone in the restaurant.
- Yeah.
- What's he doing?
If he's robbing us,
I feel sorry for him.
No. Don't say that. We're fun to rob.
Maybe he's just looking
for the bathroom.
You're overthinking it, bro!
Just go anywhere! I'll clean it up!
No way.
♪ In Heaven! ♪
Where is everybody?
Didn't we just build a whole
new mixed-use complex
for the baby boomers?
Ugh.
_
I'm just following the
admissions criteria.
Can't we just tweak them a bit?
It's easier to get in to
Upper West Side preschools.
All we're getting up here
are little old ladies
and Promise Keepers.
Have you accepted the Lord?
I'm here, dimwit.
Frankly, those guys weird me out.
We have interesting people.
Look, Tracy Morgan's here.
Tracy, what are you doing here?
- You're all better.
- Nobody tells me these things!
- You gonna stop that?
- Eh, it'll stop on its own.
We've got to get more people in here.
Ned Flanders is about to
talk about that very topic.
_
Do the people my daddy
shoots go to Heaven?
They do if they haven't
done anything wrong.
So, a lot of them, yes.
Come on, kids, think about it.
Why do people get into Heaven?
Clayton Kersh...
_
Well, nobody said Sunday
school kids were geniuses.
Kids, there's only one way into Heaven.
Never stray from the
path of righteousness.
Easy for you to say.
With a mustache like that,
you're an obvious narc.
The truth is, this mustache is a memento
of the awful sinner I used to be.
I was raised with no religion.
Our house was a den of bebop.
Neddy, you're coloring inside the lines.
Rules are for fools, man!
That's right, baby.
Be free! Be free!
Go off the page. Write on the wall.
Color a cloud purple.
Jack and Jill are on the pill, man!
Godless and Maudeless,
each job I took became more depraved.
Finally, I became one of
the most iniquitous men
that ever blew a wrapper off a straw:
door-to-door salesmen.
Now, here's how I move
these Karpet Kings.
I make my pitch, then I start
crying, bawling like a baby.
The trick is I'm secretly
clinically depressed.
Haven't thought of that.
Not bad.
Slices of pie all around, Mabel!
So, rookie, your first day.
What do they have you
pushing, water beds?
Well, I am reaching for the stars
with Vertebreaker trampolines!
- What's so funny?
- They got you slingin' springs!
The kid's a hop jockey.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
I know someone who sold
two of those tot tossers.
In his whole career!
What those door-to-door ding-dongs
didn't count on was a little
extracurricular activity
during Apollo 14.
Whee!
Over.
- Whee!
- Over.
America caught bounce fever.
Trampolines were just what
people were looking for
to forget the long quagmire
that was Gunsmoke.
_
Before I knew it, I was
the king of springs.
But after spring comes the fall.
Mabel! A slice of pie
for all my friends!
Better yet, leave the tin.
- Well!
- Well, how about that!
Big man, are ya? Real big man.
Well, big man, I got a headline for ya.
They just found out those
things are a death trap.
Oh, sure, there's broken
bones, concussions,
the occasional kid who goes
up and never comes down,
but I wouldn't call them a death trap.
I mean electrocution, smart guy.
Those little angel makers
you've been slingin'
generate static electricity
with every bounce.
The mats are made of birthday
balloon rubber and cat hair.
If you get to 500 bounces,
zappo! French-fried kid.
I've put innocent lives in danger.
And my sales pitch strongly
implied that wouldn't happen.
Eh, that's the game we're in.
If you don't like death, get
out of children's toys.
_
I've got to stop him!
401... 402...
Wow! I knew he could bounce,
but I had no idea he could count.
412... 413...
Oh, the brake pedal won't go down!
Why did I get these
super shag floor mats?
Why?!
_
495...
496...
497... 498...
499...
- Jesus.
- 'Sup?
Lord? Why am I here?
Uh, Ned Flanders, you
have been a sinner,
but you have taken the first
step on the road to redemption,
and if you accept the word
of the Lord... that's me...
I shall return you to Earth to
carry forth my word of hope.
And, uh, like that.
Jimi Hendrix is here for
your guitar lesson.
Hey, man. You been
practicing what I told you?
Uh, yeah, uh, I meant to,
but, uh, I lost the pick in the hole.
- Of the guitar?
- Oh. I wish.
I don't care, baby. Jimi
gets paid either way.
_
Praise the Lord, I am reborn!
It's a miracle! He
recovered without help!
In retrospect, I should have tried CPR.
Well, I'm a believer.
Come on, fellas, let's
go spread the good word.
God is alive!
Anyone need a vacuum?
God gave me a second chance,
and as a sign of his mercy,
he permanently scarred
my beautiful, beautiful philtrum.
Whoa!
And that's why I'm wearing this
mustache till I'm just ash.
It wasn't till God seriously deformed me
that I fully understood his love.
So, Ned Flanders gets into Heaven.
It'll be interesting to see
which wife he goes with.
Eh, either way, it'll be tough sledding.
Well you know Lord, if you
want more people here,
there's a category
you're not considering.
People who bring their dogs on planes
and say they're therapy pets?
I can hear you.
Oh, and nice to meet you, finally.
So, you made me in your image.
Well, it's like looking in a mirror.
- Not!
- Who did that?
- It wasn't me.
- Oh, you traitor!
Actually, I'm talking about people
who don't believe in God
but are still righteous.
- I'm talking about atheists, Lord.
- Atheists?
I refuse to believe they exist.
Well, they do. Maybe they
deserve a place here, too.
I'd like to talk about someone
who should be in Heaven:
my grandmother.
My grandmother's 36, and she's
got eight grandchildren.
Strong woman.
My grandmother was an atheist.
I'll just flip this.
Her name was Genevieve.
- _
- She lived in occupied France
in the darkest days of World War Two.
And she no longer believed in God.
♪ He's in the afterlife,
punishing heavily ♪
♪ He's the boogie woogie
Christian God of John 3:16 ♪
♪ A root, a toot, just
don't eat his fruit ♪
♪ He was born in a barn ♪
♪ He loved religion. ♪
How could a god allow
this awful war to happen?
I stopped a thousand wars
that would've been worse.
Nobody ever talks about that.
Perhaps her mélancolie
came from her marriage
to the village's most
notorious Nazi collaborator.
Bonjour, bonjour, Commandant!
And may I say, you put
the "ja" in "jawohl!"
Ah, my dear wife. I'm
just here collaborating,
mixing in a little treason.
You know, stuff that'll look really bad
in a documentary if we lose.
Now, with business booming,
you can no longer deny your husband
the sweet fruits of marriage.
Mmm, oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm hooked. Mmm.
Oh, yeah. Oh. Oh, yeah.
Kissing with your eyes
closed never goes awry.
Ever.
Why did I marry the model
for the town gargoyle? Ugh!
Quiet.
Qui est là? Qui! Qui!
We're U.S. paratroops.
We've been roaming the countryside
disguised as French farmers.
You must leave now. My
husband is a collaborator.
Well, I've got a screenplay
I've been looking for
someone to help me write.
Not that kind.
If he just gets something on
the page, that's progress.
Germans.
We're cooked. Worse than the
Cubs in the '32 Series.
I'm not a sports guy.
Do you have an art metaphor?
We'll be chopped up worse
than a Picasso nude!
Now my alarm is palpable!
What are you gonna do,
help us or turn us in?
Because I don't believe
there is a God above,
we must make our own Heaven down below.
Ah!
Hurry now!
- Do we get tips?
- Not in Europe.
Damn it. Now I know what
we're fighting for.
Quoi?!
Ooh-la-la! Dinner is served.
What an odd accent.
Are you really French?
Stinking customers!
You can't ask me personal questions.
Ah, you are French.
American fool. They'll
see right through you.
You don't know the first thing
about world-class dinner service.
Now listen here. I know we
may not look like much,
but when a fish knife needs
to be placed just so,
they're the mugs you want.
I am your, um, uh...
How do you say "sommelier" in French?
Café Meaux. Meaux speaking.
I'd like to speak to Monsieur Pants,
- first name Pierre.
- Un moment.
Pierre Pants? Pierre Pants?!
Oh, come on, anyone in
this joint Pee Your Pants?
Heil humor!
Laughing is for Germans only.
Ow!
Now, precisely what part
of France are you from?
Eh... Normandy beach.
You know, where the invasion's coming.
We must warn our Panzers!
We got to stop 'em, but how?
Don't ask me. I believe in
nothing, except my country.
♪ Allons enfants de la patrie ♪
♪ Le jour de gloire est arrivé ♪
♪ Contre nous de la tyrannie ♪
♪ L'étendard sanglant est levé ♪
♪ Ils viennent jusque dans nos bras ♪
♪ Egorger nos fils, nos compagnes... ♪
Come with me, fraulein,
and everything will be Nietzsche keen.
You can drink our beer,
you can take our gold,
you can take my wife.
No, you can't!
Oh. Well, the marriage counselor said
we should try to find a
common interest, so, uh...
_
Oh, Meaux, I am so sorry
I ever made you kiss a fish.
That was a fish?
But this isn't.
Mmm.
There's more in the bedroom.
We have a bedroom?
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
So, it goes to show atheists
can do great things, too.
All right, I agree.
We will open Heaven to
the deserving atheists.
And if you let them in,
there are a few mistakes
I'd recommend getting rid of.
Christopher Columbus.
Hey, what are you two talking about?
Nothing. What are you doing here?
I was looking for a quicker
route to the bathroom,
and I got lost.
- Oh, it's him.
- Hey, dudes.
Who wants to rub my belly?
Now, why don't you consider
other faiths for your Heaven?
Like, oh... I don't know...
the way of the Buddha?
I say no shirt, no shoes, no salvation.
I say we have Lisa Simpson.
Well, there is redemption,
and there are good works.
But there is another path.
A path to enlightenment
without ego or possessions.
I don't know. Jesus is pretty fond
of that plus sign he's
always carrying around.
Let me share the Buddhist path to Heaven
with an enlightened tale I call
"The Princess Not
Affiliated With Disney."
Unless we are now owned by Disney.
In the sixth century B.C.,
or zero in the Buddhist calendar...
Oh, you have your own calendar.
What's today, the fifth of Bibbity-boo?
... zero in the Buddhist calendar,
lived the spoiled Princess Siddmartha.
Siddmartha, sweetie,
look what we got you.
Oh. A pony.
50 ponies!
Oh. Somehow 50 ponies
- seem less than one.
- Oh.
The princess wondered, if
nothing was denied her,
why was she not satisfied?
Why couldn't she be
happy like her brother
with his stupid multiplayer games?
Brother, do you not grow
weary of this opulence?
Sometimes, but there's
always the decadence.
There must be a middle path
between opulence and decadence.
Flatulence?
No.
Please, somebody, think
of the elephants!
Princess Siddmartha, hmm,
perhaps the stars hold the
answer to your questions.
Why don't you take a look?
Meh.
Those children have nothing,
but they're enjoying themselves.
Maybe all these riches have blinded me
to what really matters:
goats' heads. Hmm.
That's mine.
_
♪ I live a life of great excess ♪
♪ And yet I find no happiness ♪
♪ There's more to life
than this, I hope ♪
♪ Than golden tubs and fragrant soap ♪
♪ All kinds of stuff, and yet I mope ♪
♪ I want less ♪
♪ Don't want to grab life by the horns ♪
♪ Don't want to grab that brass ring ♪
♪ Hear me shout and hear me sing ♪
♪ All I want is just one thing ♪
♪ I want less, I want less ♪
♪ Less, less, less ♪
♪ I want more of ♪
♪ Less... ♪
Less.
Oops.
Disguised as a poor boy,
Siddmartha sought out
the most learned
scholars in the kingdom.
But she soon learned
Kathmandu U, like Budhanilkantha Tech,
was just another party school.
_
Excuse me.
You're wasting your lives, man.
It's the year zero.
How much is there to learn?
Come on, girl. Let's find inner peace.
I will sit under this Bodhi Tree
because I am void of ideas.
So, Siddmartha sat and
sat and sat and sat,
willing to wait forever and a day
until she found enlightenment.
_
♪ Om... ♪
Namaste!
Even though she strayed from
our faith, I'm proud of Lisa.
That Buddhist kid's a
really good person.
What? I'm just sayin'.
Mm, if we've learned anything
from these three
tangentially-related stories,
it's that there are
many paths to Heaven.
Maybe we should let everybody in.
Great idea.
I decree that all with
good souls are welcome
in Heaven now and forever.
How did I get here?
Well, you see, you were
Smithers' plus one.
I demand to get in on my own merits.
I'll talk to him.
Don't be scared, boys.
That's just angels bowling.
Oh, I'm sorry about that.
- Oh, we consider it a blessing.
- Kiss-up.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --