AT THE WILLARD HOTEL
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
THE POET JULIA WARD HOWE
AWOKE FROM
A SPECTACULAR DREAM.
THAT DAY, SHE HAD HEARD
ANEW ENGLAND REGIMENT
SINGING ON PARADE...
AND HAD FALLEN ASLEEP
WITH THE SONG
JOHN BROWN'S BODY
RINGING IN HER HEAD.
NOW, IN THE DARK,
SHE GOT UP
AND SCRIBBLED OUT THE WORDS
WITH A PENCIL STUB.
SHE SOLD HER POEM
TO THE ATLANTIC MONTHLY
FOR $4.00.
IT BECAME THE ANTHEM
OF THE UNION.
BY 1862, RUSSIA
HAD EMANCIPATED THE SERFS.
IN FRANCE, VICTOR HUGO
PUBLISHED LES MISERABLES,
AND JEAN BERNARD FOUCAULT
MEASURED THE SPEED OF LIGHT.
IN AMERICA,
THE UNITED STATES
PASSED THE FIRST
NATIONAL INCOME TAX
TO PAY FOR WAR.
THE GATLING GUN
WAS INVENTED,
AND WAR ITSELF
WAS CHANGING.
THE SHOCKING CASUALTIES
OF BULL RUN
AND WILSON'S CREEK
WERE DWARFED
BY BATTLE AFTER BATTLE.
AND NOW THERE WERE
NEW QUESTIONS--
WOULD THE NORTH'S STRENGTH
BE OFFSET
BY INCOMPETENCE
AND LOW MORALE?
WOULD ENGLAND SIDE
WITH COTTON AND THE SOUTH?
WHO WOULD CONTROL
THE MISSISSIPPI?
FOR A YEAR,
THE NATION, NOW TWO NATIONS,
HAD TORN ITSELF APART.
FROM A BLOODLESS DUEL
OVER A MAN-MADE ISLAND
IN CHARLESTON HARBOR,
THE WAR HAD SPREAD ALONG
A THOUSAND-MILE LINE
FROM MANASSAS, VIRGINIA,
TO SHANGHAI, MISSOURI,
AND BEYOND.
AS 1862 BEGAN,
OVER A MILLION MEN
WERE MASSING FOR WAR.
IN A FIERCE STRUGGLE
FOR TENNESSEE,
THE PEOPLE OF CLARKSVILLE
ON THE CUMBERLAND
FOUND THEMSELVES PRISONERS
IN THEIR OWN HOMES.
FAR NORTH OF ANY FIGHTING,
THE PEOPLE OF DEER ISLE, MAINE,
SUFFERED, TOO--
WITH SAD NEWS
FROM PLACES MOST OF THEM
HAD NEVER HEARD OF.
BY THE END OF THE WAR,
THE LITTLE TOWN
OF WINCHESTER, VIRGINIA,
HAD CHANGED HANDS 72 TIMES.
SAM WATKINS,
A CON FEDERATE PRIVATE,
WOULD SEE
HIS FIRST BIG BATTLE
IN APRIL ON THE BANKS
OF THE TENNESSEE.
ELISHA HUNT RHODES,
A CLERK FROM PROVIDENCE,
RHODE ISLAND,
WOULD CELEBRATE
HIS 20th BIRTHDAY
IN A UNION CAMP.
UNION GENERAL GEORGE McCLELLAN,
THE IDOL OF HIS TROOPS,
WOULD FASHION A MIGHTY ARMY
AND LEAD IT SOUTH
TOWARDS RICHMOND,
WHERE ROBERT E. LEE
WAS WAITING.
"THE STRUGGLE OF TODAY,"
LINCOLN TOLD CONGRESS,
"IS NOT ALTOGETHER
FOR TODAY.
IT IS
FOR A VAST FUTURE, ALSO."
NOW, IN THIS,
ITS SECOND YEAR,
THE WAR WAS
BECOMING A STRUGGLE
OVER THE FUTURE
OF FREEDOM.
IT REALLY IS
ONE OF THOSE, UM...
ONE OF THOSE
WATERSHED THINGS.
IT WAS A HUGE CHASM
BETWEEN THE BEGINNING
AND THE END OF THE WAR.
THE NATION
HAD COME FACE TO FACE
WITH, A DREADFUL TRAGEDY,
AND WE REACTED THE WAY
A FAMILY WOULD DO
WITH A DREADFUL TRAGEDY.
IT WAS ALMOST
INCONCEIVABLE
THAT ANYTHING THAT
HORRENDOUS COULD HAPPEN.
YOU MUST REMEMBER THAT
CASUALTIES IN CIVIL WAR BATTLES
WERE SO FAR BEYOND ANYTHING
WE CAN IMAGINE NOW.
IF WE HAD 10% CASUALTIES
IN A BATTLE TODAY,
IT WOULD BE LOOKED ON
AS A BLOODBATH.
THEY HAD 30%
IN SEVERAL BATTLES,
AND ONE AFTER ANOTHER,
YOU SEE.
"THIS AFTERNOON, SEEING THE
GENERAL ALONE IN THE OFFICE,
"I STEPPED UP TO HIM
AND SAID,
"GENERAL, I WANT
TO GO HOME.
"WANT TO GO HOME? AND FOR WHAT?
HE REPLIED.
"AS I COULD NOT
THINK OF AN EXCUSE,
"I BLURTED OUT, I WANT
TO SEE MY MOTHER.
"IS SHE SICK?
HE ASKED.
"NO, I REPLIED,
I HOPE NOT.
"HE THEN ASKED ME HOW
LONG SINCE I LEFT HOME
"AND IF I WAS
EVER AWAY
"FOR SO LONG A TIME
BEFORE.
"I TOLD HIM
"I HAD BEEN
IN THE SERVICE 7 MONTHS
"AND NEVER HAD BEEN
AWAY FROM HOME ALONE BEFORE.
"WELL,
SAID THE GENERAL,
"YOU HAVE BEEN
A GOOD BOY,
AND YOU SHALL HAVE A
FURLOUGH FOR 10 DAYS."
ELISHA HUNT RHODES.
"I ALWAYS SHOT AT PRIVATES.
"IT WAS THEY THAT DID
THE SHOOTING AND KILLING,
"AND IF I COULD KILL
OR WOUND A PRIVATE,
"WHY, MY CHANCES
WERE SO MUCH THE BETTER.
I ALWAYS LOOKED ON OFFICERS
AS HARMLESS PERSONAGES."
SAM WATKINS.
THE COMMANDER OF
SAM WATKINS' COMPANY "H"
WAS CAPTAIN
WILLIAM R. JOHNSTON.
HIS IMMEDIATE SUPERIOR
WAS COLONEL GEORGE MANEY
OF THE 1st TENNESSEE.
FROM THERE, THE CONFEDERATE
CHAIN OF COMMAND
ASCENDED THROUGH
COLONEL WILLIAM H. STEPHENS
OF THE 2nd BRIGADE
TO GENERAL
BENJAMIN CHEATHAM,
COMMANDER OF THE 2nd DIVISION
OF GENERAL LEONIDAS POLK'S
1st ARMY CORPS,
THEN TO GENERAL
ALBERT SIDNEY JOHNSTON,
COMMANDER OF THE ARMY
OF THE MISSISSIPPI,
ABOVE THAT, TO WAR SECRETARY
GEORGE W. RANDOLPH...
FINALLY,
TO JEFFERSON DAVIS,
PRESIDENT OF THE CONFEDERATE
STATES OF AMERICA.
FOR ONE UNION SOLDIER,
THE CHAIN OF COMMAND DESCENDED
FROM PRESIDENT LINCOLN,
SECRETARY OF WAR
SIMON CAMERON,
AND GENERAL McCLELLAN,
COMMANDER OF THE ARMY
OF THE POTOMAC,
TO GENERAL ERASMUS KEYES,
COMMANDER OF THE UNION
4th CORPS,
GENERAL DARIUS N. COUCH
OF "COUCH'S BRIGADE,"
TO COLONEL FRANK WHEATON,
COMMANDER OF THE 2nd
RHODE ISLAND VOLUNTEERS,
AND FINALLY TO PRIVATE
ELISHA HUNT RHODES.
"JANUARY 31, 1862.
"MUD, MUD, MUD.
"I'M THINKING OF STARTING
A STEAMBOAT LINE
"TO RUN
ON PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE
"BETWEEN OUR OFFICE
AND THE CAPITOL.
WILL THE MUD NEVER DRY
SO THE ARMY CAN MOVE?"
"OF ALL DETESTABLE PLACES,
"WASHINGTON
IS THE FIRST.
"CROWD, HEAT,
BAD QUARTERS,
"BAD FARE,
BAD SMELLS,
"MOSQUITOES,
AND A PLAGUE OF FLIES
"TRANSCENDING EVERYTHING
WITHIN MY EXPERIENCE.
"BEELZEBUB
SURELY REIGNS HERE,
AND WILLARD'S HOTEL
IS HIS TEMPLE."
GEORGE TEMPLETON
STRONG.
THROUGHOUT LINCOLN'S
PRESIDENCY--
AND THIS IS TRUE
OF MOST PRESIDENTS--
HE WAS FAIRLY RUN CRAZY
BY OFFICE SEEKERS,
ESPECIALLY AT THE START,
WHEN HIS CAMPAIGN MANAGERS
HAD PROMISED JOBS
TO A GREAT MANY PEOPLE
WHO CAME TO COLLECT THEM.
AND ONE MAN SAW HIM
ONE DAY,
AND HE LOOKED
PARTICULARLY WORRIED.
THE MAN SAID, "WHAT'S
THE MATTER, MR. PRESIDENT?"
AND LINCOLN SAID, "THERE'S
TOO MANY PIGS FOR THE TITS."
ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S
PROBLEMS WERE NOT CONFINED
TO FIGHTING REBELS ALONE.
THE PRESIDENT'S
UNWIELDY CABINET
INCLUDED FORMER
CONSERVATIVE WHIGS,
FREESOIL WHIGS,
AND UNION DEMOCRATS.
4 HAD BEEN HIS RIVALS
FOR THE REPUBLICAN
PRESIDENTIAL NOMINATION.
NEARLY ALL
WERE PRIVATELY SURE
THEY COULD DO A BETTER JOB
THAN THEIR CHIEF.
SECRETARY OF STATE
WILLIAM H. SEWARD
HOPED TO REPLACE LINCOLN.
SECRETARY OF THE TREASURY
SALMON P. CHASE
WANTED TO REPLACE SEWARD.
MARY TODD TOLD HER HUSBAND
TO GET RID OF BOTH
OF THEM.
INSTEAD, LINCOLN FIRED
WAR SECRETARY SIMON P. CAMERON,
A PENNSYLVANIA BOSS
SO CORRUPT, SAID LINCOLN,
THAT THE ONLY THING
HE WOULDN'T STEAL
WAS A RED-HOT STOVE.
THE NEW SECRETARY OF WAR
WAS EDWIN M. STANTON,
AN ABLE, RUTHLESS
WAR DEMOCRAT FROM OHIO
WHO WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT HE BELIEVED TO BE
LINCOLN'S
"PAINFUL IMBECILITY."
ON ONE THING,
THE CABINET WAS AGREED.
GENERAL GEORGE McCLELLAN
WAS NOT MOVING FAST ENOUGH
AGAINST THE CON FEDERATES.
"THE ARMY," SECRETARY OF WAR
STANTON SAID,
"HAS GOT TO FIGHT
OR RUN AWAY.
"THE CHAMPAGNE AND OYSTERS
ON THE POTOMAC
MUST BE STOPPED."
"DEAR ELLEN,
"I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW DISGUSTED I AM BECOMING
"WITH THESE
WRETCHED POLITICIANS.
"THEY ARE A MOST
DESPICABLE SET OF MEN.
"SEWARD IS A MEDDLING, OFFICIOUS,
INCOMPETENT LITTLE PUPPY.
"THE PRESIDENT
IS NOTHING MORE
THAN A WELL-MEANING
BABOON."
GEORGE McCLELLAN.
THE PRESIDENT
PORED OVER MILITARY BOOKS,
ASKED OFFICERS FOR ADVICE,
AND IN EXASPERATION
SUGGESTED THAT
"IF GENERAL MCCLELLAN
"DOES NOT WANT
TO USE THE ARMY,
I WOULD LIKE TO BORROW IT
FOR A TIME."
FINALLY, HE ORDERED McCLELLAN
TO MOVE
ON MANASSAS JUNCTION,
AND THEN PROCEED OVERLAND
TO TAKE RICHMOND,
BUT MCCLELLAN
WOULD NOT MOVE
AND TOOK TO HIS BED
WITH A FEVER.
MCCLELLAN
DID NOT WANT TO FIGHT
THE VAST CONFEDERATE ARMY
HE HAD CONVINCED HIMSELF
NOW OCCUPIED
NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
INSTEAD, HE PROPOSED
TO FLOAT HIS ARMY
TO FORTRESS MONROE
AT THE TIP
OF THE FINGER OF LAND
BETWEEN THE JAMES
AND YORK RIVERS,
THEN RACE UP
THE PENINSULA
TO SEIZE
THE CON FEDERATE CAPITAL.
IMPATIENT FOR ANY ACTION,
LINCOLN AGREED.
MCCLELLAN WOULD MOVE
IN MID MARCH.
IT HAD BEEN 8 MONTHS
SINCE THE NORTHERN ARMY
HAD CRAWLED BACK
INTO WASHINGTON
AFTER BULL RUN.
"FEBRUARY 9, 1862.
"DEAR MR. PRESIDENT,
"GENERAL McCLELLAN HAS ALMOST
RUINED YOUR ADMINISTRATION
"AND THE COUNTRY.
"HE IS A DO-NOTHING.
"HE IS THINKING
OF THE PRESIDENCY IN '64.
"HE IS PLACATING
THE REBELS--
"THAT'S WHAT
AILS HIM.
DEPEND UPON IT."
JOSEPH MEDILL.
"WHAT SHALL I DO?
"THE PEOPLE
ARE IMPATIENT.
"CHASE HAS NO MONEY
"AND TELLS ME
HE CAN RAISE NO MORE.
"THE GENERAL OF THE ARMY,
MCCLELLAN,
"HAS TYPHOID FEVER.
"THE BOTTOM
IS OUT OF THE TUB.
WHAT SHALL I DO?"
"WASHINGTON.
"DEAR ELLEN,
"I WENT TO THE WHITE HOUSE
SHORTLY AFTER TEA,
"WHERE I FOUND
THE ORIGINAL GORILLA,
"ABOUT AS
INTELLIGENT AS EVER.
WHAT A SPECIMEN TO BE AT THE
HEAD OF OUR AFFAIRS NOW."
GEORGE McCLELLAN.
IN THE MIDST
OF ALL HIS TROUBLES,
THE PRESIDENT DELIGHTED
IN HIS SONS.
THE OLDEST, ROBERT,
WAS AWAY AT HARVARD,
BUT WILLIE, 11,
AND 8-YEAR-OLD THOMAS,
KNOWN AS TAD,
HAD THE RUN
OF THE WHITE HOUSE.
WILLIE WAS STUDIOUS,
LIKED TO COMPOSE VERSE
AND MEMORIZE
RAILROAD TIMETABLES.
HE HAD RAISED
A BOYS' BATTALION
FROM AMONG
HIS SCHOOLMATES
AND INVADED CABINET MEETINGS
WITH HIS "TROOPS."
IN FEBRUARY,
HE DEVELOPED WHAT THE DOCTOR
CALLED "BILIOUS FEVER."
HIS PARENTS SAT UP
NIGHT AFTER NIGHT
TO NURSE HIM.
ON FEBRUARY 20,
WILLIE DIED.
FOR 3 MONTHS,
MARY LINCOLN VEERED
BETWEEN LOUD WEEPING
AND SILENT DEPRESSION
AND SOUGHT TO COMMUNICATE
WITH HER DEAD CHILD
THROUGH SPIRITUALISTS.
"IF I HAD NOT FELT
"THE SPUR OF NECESSITY
URGING ME TO CHEER MR. LINCOLN,
"WHOSE GRIEF
WAS AS GREAT AS MY OWN,
I COULD NEVER
HAVE SMILED AGAIN."
THE WAR LEFT LINCOLN
LITTLE TIME TO MOURN.
HE WAS SOON BACK WORKING
18 HOURS A DAY.
"AS SHE CAME PLOWING
THROUGH THE WATER,
"SHE LOOKED LIKE A HUGE
HALF-SUBMERGED CROCODILE.
"AT HER PROW,
I COULD SEE THE IRON RAM
PROJECTING STRAIGHT FORWARD."
THE CONFEDERACY
HAD BEGUN THE WAR
WITH NO NAVY WHATSOEVER,
BUT BY THE FALL OF 1861,
CONFEDERATE ENGINEERS
WERE BOLTING IRON PLATES
TO THE HULL OF
THE STEAM FRIGATE MERRIMACK,
BUILDING A WARSHIP
MORE POWERFUL
THAN ANYTHING
THE UNION HAD.
NEWS OF THE MONSTER
QUICKLY REACHED THE NORTH.
SECRETARY OF WAR STANTON
FEARED SHE WOULD STEAM
UP THE POTOMAC
AND SHELL THE WHITE HOUSE.
THERE WAS PROBABLY
ONLY ONE MAN IN AMERICA
WHO COULD STOP
THE MERRIMACK,
AND HE WAS MAD
AT THE NAVY.
THE SWEDISH-BORN INVENTOR
JOHN ERICSSON
WAS PROUD, VAIN,
AND CRANKY,
AND FELT HE HAD BEEN
CHEATED OUT OF PAYMENT
FOR SERVICES TO
THE GOVERNMENT YEARS BEFORE,
BUT WHEN SECRETARY
OF THE NAVY GIDEON WELLES
BEGGED HIM TO DO SOMETHING
TO STOP THE MERRIMACK,
ERICSSON CAME UP WITH
AN EXTRAORDINARY DESIGN.
HIS SHIP
WOULD HAVE ONLY TWO GUNS
TO THE MERRIMACK'S 10,
BUT THEY WOULD BE MOUNTED
ON A REVOLVING TURRET,
AND THOUGH HIS VESSEL WOULD
BE MADE ENTIRELY OF IRON,
ERICSSON ASSURED EVERYBODY
THAT "THE SEA
SHALL RIDE OVER HER,
AND SHE SHALL LIVE IN IT
LIKE A DUCK."
PROFESSIONAL NAVY MEN
DISMISSED THE PLAN,
BUT LINCOLN
OVERRULED THEM,
AND JUST 100 DAYS LATER,
ON JANUARY 30, 1862,
ERICSSON'S SHIP SLID
INTO MANHATTAN'S EAST RIVER.
HE CALLED HER THE MONITOR,
AND THERE HAD NEVER BEEN
ANYTHING LIKE HER.
THE SINGLE VESSEL CONTAINED
47 PATENTABLE INVENTIONS.
"WE RAN FIRST
TO THE NEW YORK SIDE
"AND THEN TO BROOKLYN,
"AND SO BACK AND FORTH
ACROSS THE RIVER,
"LIKE A DRUNKEN MAN
ON A SIDEWALK.
WE FOUND SHE WOULD NOT ANSWER
HER RUDDER AT ALL."
ONCE AT SEA,
WATER SPILLED IN,
VENTILATORS FAILED,
THE SHIP FILLED WITH GAS,
HER CREW BEGAN TO FAINT,
BUT THE MONITOR
KEPT LIMPING SOUTH.
400 MILES AWAY,
OFF THE COAST OF VIRGINIA,
THE MERRIMACK WAS WAITING.
SATURDAY, MARCH 8,
WAS WASH DAY
FOR THE UNION FLEET
IN HAMPTON ROADS, VIRGINIA.
LAUNDRY WAS DRYING
ON THE RIGGING
OF THE UNION WARSHIPS
WHEN THE CONFEDERATE
MERRIMACK
HEADED STRAIGHT
FOR THE U.S.S. CUMBERLAND.
THE CUMBERLAND
OPENED FIRE,
BUT THE SHOTS
BOUNCED HARMLESSLY
OFF THE MERRIMACK'S SIDE.
THE CONFEDERATE SHIP
RAMMED THE CUMBERLAND,
THEN STOOD IN SO CLOSE,
THEIR MUZZLES
ALMOST TOUCHED.
THE CUMBERLAND
SANK IN SHALLOW WATER.
THE MERRIMACK WENT ON
TO SET
THE U.S.S. CONGRESS AFIRE,
DROVE THE U.S.S. MINNESOTA
AGROUND,
THEN DREW BACK
FOR THE NIGHT.
FOR ONE DAY,
THE CONFEDERATE NAVY
RULED THE SEA.
AT 1:00 THAT MORNING,
THE CREW
OF THE BATTERED MINNESOTA
SAW A STRANGE-LOOKING SHIP
DRAW UP ALONGSIDE THEM
IN THE DARKNESS.
"CLOSE ALONGSIDE
THE MINNESOTA,
"THERE WAS A CRAFT
SUCH AS THE EYES OF A SEAMAN
"NEVER LOOKED UPON BEFORE--
"AN IMMENSE SHINGLE
FLOATING ON THE WATER
"WITH A GIGANTIC CHEESE BOX
RISING FROM ITS CENTER.
"NO SAILS, NO WHEELS,
NO SMOKESTACK, NO GUNS.
WHAT COULD IT BE?"
THE MONITOR HAD ARRIVED.
THE NEXT MORNING,
THE EPIC BATTLE
OF IRONCLADS BEGAN.
HULL TO HULL, THE TWO SHIPS
HAMMERED AWAY AT EACH OTHER,
SO CLOSE,
THEY COLLIDED 5 TIMES
AS THE MEN INSIDE,
HALF-BLIND WITH SMOKE,
LOADED AND FIRED.
AFTER 4½ HOURS,
THE MERRIMACK DREW OFF.
IT WAS HER ONLY FIGHT.
TWO MONTHS LATER,
RATHER THAN SURRENDER
THEIR SHIP,
THE CONFEDERATES
BLEW HER UP
WHEN THEY WERE FORCED
OUT OF NORFOLK.
BOTH SIDES SET TO WORK
BUILDING MORE IRONCLADS
WHILE EUROPE WATCHED
IN WORRIED FASCINATION.
FROM THE MOMENT
THE TWO SHIPS
OPENED FIRE
THAT SUNDAY MORNING,
EVERY OTHER NAVY ON EARTH
WAS OBSOLETE.
"GENERAL GRANT HABITUALLY
WEARS AN EXPRESSION
"AS IF HE HAD DETERMINED
TO DRIVE HIS HEAD
THROUGH A BRICK WALL
AND WAS ABOUT TO DO IT."
THE YEAR 1862
WOULD INTRODUCE TWO GREAT
FORCES INTO THE WAR--
UNSPEAKABLE SLAUGHTER
AND ULYSSES S. GRANT.
WHILE MCCLELLAN
HESITATED IN WASHINGTON,
GRANT, BACK IN THE FIELD
AFTER MONTHS OF DESK DUTY,
WON TWO CRUCIAL VICTORIES
OUT WEST.
LAUNCHING SIMULTANEOUS ATTACKS
BY LAND AND WATER,
HE TOOK FIRST FORT HENRY
ON THE TENNESSEE RIVER,
THEN FORT DONELSON
ON THE CUMBERLAND,
WHERE HE ISSUED AN ULTIMATUM
TO THE CONFEDERATE COMMANDER--
"NO TERMS
EXCEPT UNCONDITIONAL
AND IMMEDIATE SURRENDER."
THE TENNESSEE
AND CUMBERLAND RIVERS
WERE NOW IN UNION HANDS.
THE CONFEDERATES HAD BEEN
DRIVEN FROM KENTUCKY.
DOZENS OF SOUTHERN TOWNS
WERE NOW OCCUPIED
BY UNION TROOPS.
IN LESS THAN A YEAR,
GRANT HAD GONE FROM CLERK
TO UNION HERO.
NEWS STORIES DESCRIBED HIM
COOLLY SMOKING UNDER FIRE,
AND ADMIRERS SHIPPED HIM
BARRELS OF CIGARS.
A DELIGHTED NORTHERN PUBLIC
NOW THOUGHT THEY KNEW
WHAT THE INITIALS
IN HIS NAME STOOD FOR.
THEY CALLED HIM
"UNCONDITIONAL SURRENDER"
GRANT.
BUT BEFORE GRANT'S MEN
MARCHED INTO FORT DONELSON,
CONFEDERATE GENERAL
NATHAN BEDFORD FORREST
SLIPPED OUT OF IT
WITH 1,000 MEN.
"I DID NOT COME HERE
FOR THE PURPOSE
OF SURRENDERING MY COMMAND,"
HE SAID,
AND LED HIS TROOPS 75 MILES
THROUGH THE SNOW TO SAFETY.
GRANT AND THE UNION ARMY
WOULD MEET
BEDFORD FORREST AGAIN.
AFTER THE CONFEDERATE DEFEAT
AT FORT DONELSON,
THE FEMALE ACADEMY
AND STEWART COLLEGE
AT NEARBY
CLARKSVILLE, TENNESSEE,
WERE CONVERTED
TO HOSPITALS.
"SUNDAY THE NEWS CAME.
"SUCH PANIC-STRICKEN PEOPLE
WERE NEVER BEFORE SEEN.
"THE WOUNDED
WERE BEING BROUGHT UP.
"THE CITIZENS WERE RUNNING.
"THERE WERE ALREADY
TWO HOSPITALS HERE
"WHICH WERE FILLED
WITH THE SICK,
"AND THEY, POOR FELLAS, WERE
CRAWLING OUT FROM EVERY PIECE--
"WALKING,
GOING ON HORSEBACK,
IN WAGONS."
NANNIE HASKINS.
THE UNION ARMY
WAS RIGHT BEHIND THE WOUNDED.
THEY MET NO RESISTANCE.
A WHITE FLAG FLEW
ABOVE TINY FORT DEFIANCE
WEST OF TOWN,
AND MAYOR SMITH CAME OUT
TO INFORM
THE UNION COMMANDER
THAT THE CONFEDERATE ARMY
HAD RETREATED TO NASHVILLE.
FARMER JOHN BARKER
WROTE IN HIS DIARY
THAT THERE WERE NOTHING
BUT LINCOLNITES
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTY.
AN UN EASY FEDERAL OCCUPATION
OF CLARKSVILLE BEGAN.
EARLY IN THE WAR, SOME--
UM, A UNION SQUAD CLOSED IN
ON A SINGLE
RAGGED CONFEDERATE,
AND HE OBVIOUSLY
DIDN'T OWN ANY SLAVES.
HE COULDN'T HAVE MUCH INTEREST
IN--IN THE CONSTITUTION
OR ANYTHING ELSE.
THEY SAID, "WHAT ARE YOU FIGHTING
FOR, ANYHOW?" THEY ASKED HIM.
AND HE SAID,
"I'M FIGHTING
BECAUSE YOU'RE
DOWN HERE,"
WHICH IS A PRETTY
SATISFACTORY ANSWER.
ON APRIL 4,
GEORGE MCCLELLAN AT LAST
BEGAN TO MOVE
FOR RICHMOND--
121,500 MEN,
14,592 HORSES AND MULES,
1,150 WAGONS,
44 BATTERIES
OF ARTILLERY,
AMBULANCES,
PONTOON BRIDGES,
TONS OF PROVISIONS,
TENTS, TELEGRAPH WIRE.
IT TOOK 400 BOATS
3 WEEKS TO LAND IT ALL
AT FORTRESS MONROE
ON THE VIRGINIA COAST.
"THE WHOLE REGION SEEMS
"LITERALLY FILLED
WITH SOLDIERY.
"ONE OF
THE FINEST ARMIES
"EVER MARSHALLED
ON THE GLOBE
"NOW WAKES UP THESE LONG,
STAGNANT FIELDS AND WOODS.
"GENERAL McCLELLAN IS HERE
AND COMMANDS
IN PERSON."
REVEREND
A.M. STEWART.
"I AM TO WATCH OVER YOU
"AS A PARENT
OVER HIS CHILDREN,
"AND YOU KNOW THAT
YOUR GENERAL LOVES YOU
"FROM THE DEPTHS
OF HIS HEART.
"IT SHALL BE MY CARE
TO GAIN SUCCESS WITH THE
LEAST POSSIBLE LOSS."
BUT AT YORKTOWN,
LESS THAN 20 MILES AWAY,
THE CON FEDERATES WAITED,
VASTLY OUTNUMBERED
BUT DETERMINED
TO DEFEND THEIR HOMES
AND HURL BACK
THE INVADERS.
FOR THE NORTH,
IT WAS SLOW GOING.
ROADS SAID TO BE
BONE DRY WERE BOGS.
UNION OFFICERS,
FORCED TO RELY
ON STORE-BOUGHT MAPS,
LOST THEIR WAY.
FINALLY, ON APRIL 5,
THE ADVANCE GUARD
REACHED YORKTOWN,
WHERE THE CONFEDERATES
HAD TAKEN OVER THE BUILDING
USED BY LORD CORNWALLIS
AS HEADQUARTERS
DURING
THE REVOLUTIONARY WAR.
THERE WERE JUST 11,000
SOUTHERN TROOPS DUG IN--
NOT EVEN 1/10
OF McCLELLAN'S FORCE...
BUT THE CON FEDERATE
COMMANDER
WAS JOHN BANKHEAD MAGRUDER,
A SHOWY VIRGINIAN
WHO LOVED AMATEUR THEATRICALS.
HE NOW OUTDID
EVEN HIMSELF.
TO FOOL MCCLELLAN
INTO BELIEVING
THAT HIS SMALL FORCE
WAS ENORMOUS,
MAGRUDER KEPT UP
A SPORADIC,
WIDELY SCATTERED
ARTILLERY BARRAGE
AND PARADED ONE BATTALION
IN AND OUT OF A CLEARING
IN AN ENDLESS CIRCLE
UNTIL IT SEEMED, TO UNION
OBSERVERS, A MIGHTY HOST.
CORPORAL EDMUND PATTERSON,
9th ALABAMA.
"THIS MORNING,
WE WERE CALLED OUT
"BY THE LONG ROLL,
AND HAVE BEEN TRAVELING
"MOST OF THE DAY,
"SEEMING WITH NO OTHER VIEW THAN
TO SHOW OURSELVES TO THE ENEMY
"AT AS MANY DIFFERENT POINTS
OF THE LINE AS POSSIBLE.
I'M PRETTY TIRED."
"IT SEEMS CLEAR
THAT I SHALL HAVE
THE WHOLE FORCE
OF THE ENEMY ON MY HANDS,"
MCCLELLAN
TELEGRAPHED LINCOLN,
"PROBABLY NOT LESS
THAN 100,000 MEN,
AND POSSIBLY MORE."
MCCLELLAN CALLED
FOR REINFORCEMENTS.
GENERAL JOSEPH E. JOHNSTON,
THE OVERALL
CONFEDERATE COMMANDER,
COULD NOT BELIEVE
HIS LUCK.
"NOBODY BUT McCLELLAN," HE SAID,
"COULD HAVE HESITATED
TO ATTACK."
"ONCE MORE,
LET ME TELL YOU,
"IT IS
INDISPENSABLE TO YOU
"THAT YOU
STRIKE A BLOW.
"I HAVE NEVER WRITTEN
TO YOU OR SPOKEN TO YOU
"IN GREATER KINDNESS
THAN NOW,
"NOR WITH FULLER PURPOSE
TO SUSTAIN YOU,
BUT YOU MUST ACT."
"THE PRESIDENT
VERY COOLLY TELEGRAPHED ME
"THAT HE THOUGHT I HAD BETTER
BREAK THE ENEMY'S LINES AT ONCE.
"I WAS MUCH
TEMPTED TO REPLY
THAT HE HAD BETTER COME
AND DO IT HIMSELF."
GEORGE McCLELLAN.
"I DON'T SEE THE SENSE
"OF PILING UP EARTH
TO KEEP US APART.
"IF WE DON'T GET AT
EACH OTHER SOMETIME,
"WHEN WILL
THE WAR END?
"MY PLAN WOULD BE
TO QUIT DITCHING
AND GO TO FIGHTING."
BUT McCLELLAN CHOSE TO DIG IN.
AS HE SETTLED IN
FOR A SIEGE OF YORKTOWN,
UNION GENERAL PHIL KEARNY
TOOK TO CALLING
HIS COMMANDER
"THE VIRGINIA CREEPER."
DURING
THE PENINSULA CAMPAIGN,
McCLELLAN'S WORKING HIS WAY
UP THE YORK JAMES PENINSULA,
AND HE CAME TO A STREAM.
AND HE AND HIS STAFF
WERE SITTING THERE WONDERING
HOW DEEP IT WAS,
IF THEY HAD TO MARCH ACROSS IT.
AND CUSTER, WHO WAS
A JUNIOR OFFICER ON HIS STAFF--
JUST GRADUATED FROM WEST
POINT, A CAPTAIN, I THINK--
RODE OUT INTO MIDSTREAM,
SAT ON HIS HORSE, AND
TURNED AROUND IN THE SADDLE
AND SAID TO McCLELLAN, "THIS
IS HOW DEEP IT IS, GENERAL."
"A MAN'S CONCEIT DWINDLES
"WHEN HE CRAWLS
INTO AN UNTEASLED SHIRT,
"TROUSERS TOO SHORT
AND BAGGY BEHIND,
"COAT TOO LONG
AT BOTH ENDS,
"AND A CAP AS SHAPELESS
AS A FEEDBAG.
"A PHOTOGRAPH
OF ANY ONE OF THEM,
"COVERED WITH YELLOW DUST
OR MOSAICS OF MUD,
"COULD ORNAMENT ANY
MANTEL, NORTH OR SOUTH,
AS A TRUE PICTURE
OF OUR BOY"
NORTH AND SOUTH,
THE AVERAGE SOLDIER
WAS 5'8" TALL
AND WEIGHED 143 POUNDS.
HIS CHANCE OF DYING
IN COMBAT WAS 1 IN 65;
OF BEING WOUNDED,
1 IN 10.
1 IN 13
WOULD DIE OF DISEASE.
THE AVERAGE AGE
OF A SOLDIER WAS 25.
THE MINIMUM AGE
FOR ENLISTMENT WAS 18,
BUT RECRUITING OFFICERS
WERE NOT PARTICULAR.
DRUMMER BOYS
AS YOUNG AS 9 SIGNED ON.
THERE WERE MORE THAN 100,000
SOLDIERS IN THE UNION ARMY
WHO WERE NOT YET
15 YEARS OLD.
WILLIAM BLACK WAS
NOT YET 12 WHEN HE ENLISTED.
SHOT IN THE LEFT ARM
DURING BATTLE,
HE WAS THOUGHT TO BE
THE YOUNGEST COMBAT SOLDIER
WOUNDED IN THE WAR.
"ALMOST EVERY KNOWN
TRADE, PROFESSION,
"OR CALLING HAS
ITS REPRESENTATIVES
"IN OUR REGIMENT--
"TAILORS, CARPENTERS,
MASONS, AND PLASTERERS,
"MOULDERS
AND GLASSBLOWERS,
"PUDDLERS AND ROLLERS,
"MACHINISTS
AND ARCHITECTS,
"PRINTERS, BOOKBINDERS
AND PUBLISHERS,
"GENTLEMEN OF LEISURE,
"POLITICIANS, MERCHANTS,
"LEGISLATORS, JUDGES,
"LAWYERS,
DOCTORS, PREACHERS.
"SOME MALICIOUS FELLOW
MIGHT ASK THE PRIVILEGE
"OF COMPLETING
THE CATALOGUE BY NAMING
"JAILBIRDS, IDLERS,
LOAFERS, DRUNKARDS,
"AND GAMBLERS...
BUT WE BEG HIS PARDON
AND REFUSE THE LICENSE."
"ALL THE APPLIANCES
OF HOME LIFE
"WHICH ARE POSSIBLE
ARE BEING INTRODUCED
"INTO OUR ENCAMPMENT--
"A WEEKLY NEWSPAPER,
"A PHOTOGRAPHIC
ESTABLISHMENT,
"A TEMPERANCE LEAGUE,
"AND A CHRISTIAN
ASSOCIATION.
"WE HAVE A POST OFFICE,
LETTER BOX,
"POSTMASTER,
AND MAIL CARRIER.
"OUR BOYS WRITE
VASTLY MORE LETTERS
"THAN THEY RECEIVE.
"YOU CAN HARDLY IMAGINE
THE EAGERNESS
"WITH WHICH THE MAILMAN
IS LOOKED FOR,
"THE DELIGHT ON THE
RECEPTION OF A LETTER,
"THE SADNESS,
SOMETIMES EVEN TO TEARS,
"WITH WHICH THOSE
WHO ARE DISAPPOINTED
TURN AWAY."
REVEREND
A.M. STEWART.
FOR THE ENLISTED MAN,
ARMY LIFE MEANT
PERIODS OF TEDIUM
PUNCTUATED BY MOMENTS
OF EXTREME TERROR.
IT ALSO MEANT
LONG ABSENCES
FROM FAMILY AND HOME.
"JULY 1862.
TUPELO, MISSISSIPPI.
"DEAR SISTERS,
"I WOULD BE
THE GLADDEST PERSON IN THE WORLD
"TO SEE YOU AND TALK
WITH YOU AWHILE,
"FOR I SEE NOBODY HERE
BUT MEN,
"AND THEY APPEAR TO BE
VERY SORRY COMPANY.
"I THINK THAT I COULD
ENJOY MYSELF AT HOME
BETTER THAN ANYWHERE
ELSE IN THE WORLD."
BENJAMIN STUBBS.
FOR THOSE OFFICERS
WHO TOOK THEIR FAMILIES
WITH THEM TO CAMP,
LIFE WAS SOMEWHAT BETTER.
"THERE HAS BEEN
A GREAT BATTLE INDEED
"IN THE SOUTHWEST,
"A CONFLICT OF TWO DAYS,
"CLOSELY FOUGHT
AND WITH VARYING FORTUNE
"AND BY GREAT ARMIES.
"IT SEEMS
ENTITLED TO A PLACE
AMONG THE FIRST-CLASS
BATTLES OF HISTORY."
GEORGE TEMPLETON STRONG.
IT WAS FOUGHT
IN EARLY APRIL.
THE TREES
WERE LEAFED OUT,
AND THE ROADS WERE
MEANDERING COWPATHS.
NOBODY KNEW NORTH FROM
SOUTH, EAST FROM WEST.
THEY HAD NEVER BEEN IN
COMBAT BEFORE, MOST OF THEM,
ESPECIALLY
ON THE SOUTHERN SIDE.
SO IT WAS JUST A DISORGANIZED,
MURDEROUS FISTFIGHT“
100,000 MEN SLAMMING
AWAY AT EACH OTHER.
IN EARLY APRIL,
AS MCCLELLAN CONTINUED
TO SIT IN FRONT
OF YORKTOWN,
42,000 UNION TROOPS UNDER
GENERAL ULYSSES S. GRANT
WERE ENCAMPED ON THE WEST SIDE
OF THE TENNESSEE RIVER
NEAR PITTSBURG LANDING.
GRANT'S INVASION
OF TENNESSEE
HAD PRACTICALLY
CUT THE STATE IN TWO,
AND NOW HE WAS WAITING
FOR DON CARLOS BUELL'S
ARMY OF THE OHIO
TO JOIN HIM.
THEIR COMBINED FORCES
WERE THEN TO PLUNGE
INTO THE HEART
OF MISSISSIPPI,
BUT BUELL WAS LATE,
AND AT CORINTH, MISSISSIPPI,
22 MILES AWAY,
THE COMMANDER OF THE WESTERN
DEPARTMENT OF THE CONFEDERATE ARMY,
ALBERT SIDNEY JOHNSTON,
SAW NO REASON TO WAIT.
THEIR ARMIES WERE STILL
EVENLY MATCHED,
AND HE WOULD ATTACK
AND END GRANT'S INVASION.
"TONIGHT WE WILL WATER OUR
HORSES IN THE TENNESSEE,"
JOHNSTON TOLD
HIS STAFF OFFICERS
ON THE MORNING
OF APRIL 6.
THE CONFEDERATES QUIETLY
MOVED TOWARD THE UNION LINES.
"IT WAS A MOST
BEAUTIFUL MORNING.
"IT REALLY SEEMED LIKE SUNDAY
IN THE COUNTRY AT HOME.
"THE BOYS WERE SCATTERED
AROUND CAMP,
"POLISHING AND BRIGHTENING
THEIR MUSKETS
"AND BRUSHING UP
AND CLEANING
THEIR SHOES, JACKETS,
AND TROUSERS FOR INSPECTION."
PRIVATE
LEANDER STILWELL.
AT THE HEAD
OF ONE UNION DIVISION
WAS WILLIAM TECUMSEH SHERMAN,
WHO HAD SHAKEN OFF
THE MELANCHOLY
THAT HAD SENT HIM HOME
THE PREVIOUS YEAR.
HIS OHIOANS
WERE ENCAMPED ON A HILL
NOT FAR FROM A LITTLE
LOG-BUILT METHODIST CHURCH
CALLED SHILOH
WHEN THE 6th MISSISSIPPI
ATTACKED.
"I SAW MEN IN GRAY
AND BROWN CLOTHES
"RUNNING
THROUGH THE CAMP.
"AND I SAW
SOMETHING ELSE, TOO,
"SOMETHING I HAD
NEVER SEEN BEFORE--
"A GAUDY SORT OF THING
WITH RED BARS...
A REBEL FLAG."
"WE WERE
CROWDING THEM.
"ONE MORE CHARGE, AND THEIR
LINES WAVER AND BREAK.
"THEY RETREAT
IN WILD CONFUSION.
"WE WERE JUBILANT,
"AND THE OFFICERS
COULD NOT CURB THEIR MEN
TO KEEP THEM IN LINE."
SAM WATKINS.
THE BATTLE EXTENDED
ALONG A 3-MILE FRONT.
THE WORST FIGHTING
WAS IN THE CENTER,
WHERE THE REBELS CAME
ON AND ON
LIKE "MADDENED DEMONS,"
A UNION SOLDIER SAID.
THE GENERALS DIDN'T
KNOW THEIR JOBS.
THE SOLDIERS DIDN'T
IT WAS JUST PURE DETERMINATION
TO STAND AND FIGHT
AND NOT RETREAT,
AND THE BLOODINESS OF IT
WAS JUST ASTOUNDING TO EVERYONE.
IT ALSO CORRECTED A SOUTHERN
MISCONCEPTION WHICH HAD SAID,
"ONE GOOD
SOUTHERN SOLDIER
IS WORTH 10
YANKEE HIRELINGS."
THEY FOUND OUT THAT WASN'T
TRUE BY A LONG SHOT.
IN A PEACH ORCHARD,
THE FEDERALS LAY FLAT
BENEATH
THE BLOSSOMING TREES,
FIRING AS THE REBELS CAME,
SOFT PINK PETALS
RAINING DOWN
ON THE LIVING
AND THE DEAD.
BY LATE MORNING, THOUSANDS
OF UNTRIED FEDERAL TROOPS
HAD SEEN ENOUGH.
MOST DID NOT STOP RUNNING UNTIL
THEY REACHED THE RIVER,
WHERE ALMOST 5,000 MEN
COWERED BENEATH THE BLUFF.
"WE ARE SWEEPING THE FIELD,"
GENERAL JOHNSTON TOLD
HIS SECOND IN COMMAND,
BEAUREGARD,
"AND I THINK WE SHALL
PRESS THEM TO THE RIVER."
GRANT'S BACK
WAS TO THE TENNESSEE.
THERE WAS NO SIGN OF BUELL
AND NOWHERE ELSE TO GO,
BUT A THIN FEDERAL LINE
HELD IN THE CENTER,
ILLINOIS AND IOWA
FARM BOYS MOSTLY,
PRONE ALONG
A SUNKEN ROAD.
THEIR COMMANDER,
BENJAMIN PRENTISS,
UNDERSTOOD
THE DEADLY SERIOUSNESS
OF GRANT'S ORDER
TO "MAINTAIN THAT POSITION
AT ALL COSTS."
THE CONFEDERATES LAUNCHED
A DOZEN MASSIVE ASSAULTS
AGAINST WHAT BECAME KNOWN
AS THE HORNET'S NEST.
ALBERT SIDNEY JOHNSTON
HIMSELF LED THE LAST CHARGE.
HE CAME OUT OF IT WITH,
BITS OF HIS CLOTHING NICKED ALL UP.
ONE BOOT SOLE
WAS SHOT IN HALF,
AND HE FLAPPED HIS--
ON--ON HORSEBACK THERE,
AND SAID, "THEY DIDN'T
TRIP ME UP THAT TIME."
AND VERY SOON AFTER THAT, THEY
SAW HIM REEL IN THE SADDLE
AND REALIZED HE WAS HURT,
AND THEN SOMEONE SAID,
"GENERAL, ARE YOU WOUNDED?"
AND HE SAID, "YES,
AND I FEAR SERIOUSLY,"
AND HE WAS SHOT
BEHIND THE KNEE--
IN THE FEMORAL ARTERY,
I SUPPOSE-
AND BLED TO DEATH.
THEY SAW BLOOD
COMING OUT OF HIS BOOT,
AND HE COULD HAVE BEEN EASILY
SAVED WITH A TOURNIQUET,
BUT HE HAD SENT
HIS--HIS SURGEON OFF
TO TAKE CARE OF SOME
FEDERAL PRISONERS.
"ADVANCING
A LITTLE FURTHER,
"WE SAW GENERAL
ALBERT SIDNEY JOHNSTON
"SURROUNDED
BY HIS STAFF.
"WE SAW SOME
LITTLE COMMOTION
"AMONG THOSE WHO
SURROUNDED HIM,
"BUT WE DID NOT KNOW AT THE
TIME THAT HE WAS DEAD.
THE FACT WAS KEPT
FROM THE TROOPS."
SAM WATKINS.
THE COMMAND
OF THE WESTERN ARMY
NOW PASSED
TO GENERAL BEAUREGARD.
ALBERT SIDNEY JOHNSTON
WAS LOOKED ON BY MANY PEOPLE
AT THE TIME OF SHILOH,
AND ESPECIALLY BEFORE
SHILOH WHILE HE WAS
HOLDING THAT LINE
UP IN KENTUCKY,
AS THE SOUTH'S
NUMBER-ONE FIELD SOLDIER.
JEFFERSON DAVIS
VIEWED HIM AS THAT,
AND WHEN HE LOST
ALBERT SIDNEY JOHNSTON,
HE SAID, "I REALIZED OUR STRONGEST
PILLAR HAD BEEN BROKEN."
MEANWHILE,
THE CENTER OF THE UNION LINE
BENT BACK ON ITSELF
BUT WOULD NOT BREAK.
CONFEDERATES
TRAIN ED 62 CANNON
AT POINT-BLANK RANGE
AND OPENED FIRE.
THE HORNET'S NEST
EXPLODED IN A HAIL
OF SPLINTERED TREES
AND SHATTERED MEN.
AT 5:30, PRENTISS
AND THE 2,200 SURVIVORS
OF HIS DIVISION SURRENDERED.
THEY HAD HELD UP
THE SOUTHERN ADVANCE
FOR NEARLY 6 HOURS,
AND IT WAS GROWING DARK.
BEAUREGARD WIRED
JEFFERSON DAVIS
THAT HE HAD WON
A COMPLETE VICTORY.
"I HAD GENERAL GRANT
JUST WHERE I WANTED HIM,"
HE SAID, "AND COULD FINISH
HIM UP IN THE MORNING."
EVERYWHERE, WOUNDED MEN
LAY IN AGONY.
NEITHER ARMY HAD YET
DEVISED A SYSTEM
FOR GATHERING OR CARING
FOR THEM ON THE FIELD.
SCORES OF WOUNDED
COLLAPSED AND DIED
DRINKING FROM A MUD HOLE
NEAR THE PEACH ORCHARD,
STAINING THE WATER RED.
IT BEGAN TO RAIN,
AND FLASHES OF LIGHTNING
SHOWED HOGS FEEDING
ON THE UNGATHERED DEAD.
"SOME CRIED
FOR WATER,
"OTHERS FOR SOMEONE TO
COME AND HELP THEM.
"I CAN HEAR THOSE POOR
FELLOWS CRYING FOR WATER.
"GOD HEARD THEM,
FOR THE HEAVENS OPENED
AND THE RAIN CAME."
GRANT SPENT THAT NIGHT
BENEATH A TREE
RATHER THAN LISTEN TO THE
SCREAMS OF THE WOUNDED MEN
IN HIS HEADQUARTERS.
IT WAS THERE THAT
SHERMAN FOUND HIM.
"WELL, GRANT," HE SAID,
"WE'VE HAD THE DEVIL'S
OWN DAY, HAVEN'T WE?"
"YES," SAID GRANT.
"LICK 'EM TOMORROW, THOUGH."
"NEVER TO ME
WAS THE SIGHT
"OF REINFORCING
LEGIONS SO WELCOME
"AS ON THAT SUNDAY
EVENING
"WHEN BUELL'S
ADVANCE COLUMN DEPLOYED
ON THE BLUFFS OF
PITTSBURG LANDING."
DURING THE NIGHT,
BUELL'S ARMY FINALLY ARRIVED.
THE UNION MEN MARCHED ASHORE
AS A BAND PLAYED DIXIE.
AT DAWN, THE UNION FORCE,
NOW 70,000 STRONG,
DROVE INTO
BEAUREGARD'S 30,000.
THE CONFEDERATES FELL BACK,
COUNTERATTACKED,
FELL BACK AGAIN,
AND BEGAN TO WITHDRAW.
THE UNION HELD THE FIELD.
COVERING
THE CON FEDERATE RETREAT
WAS NATHAN BEDFORD FORREST,
WHO NOW TURNED TO LEAD
ONE LAST CAVALRY CHARGE
HEADLONG INTO THE PURSUING
NORTHERN ARMY.
AND HE LANDED SQUARE IN THE
MAIN BODY OF THE UNION TROOPS.
HE WAS SURROUNDED BY-- ONE
GRAY UNIFORM IN A SEA OF BLUE,
AND, THEY BEGAN
TO HOLLER,
"KILL HIM.
KILL THE GODDAMN REBEL.
KNOCK HIM
OFF HIS HORSE,"
AND ONE SOLDIER DID,
STICK HIS, RIFLE OUT
INTO FORREST'S SIDE
AND PULLED THE TRIGGER
AND LIFTED FORREST
CLEAR OF THE SADDLE
WITH THE IMPACT
OF THE BULLET,
AND FORREST, MEANTIME,
WAS SLASHING WITH HIS SABER.
HIS HORSE WAS KICKING
AND TURNING,
AND FORREST SAWED
HIM AROUND
AND GOT HIM CLEAR
AND TOOK OFF,
AND THEY WERE
SHOOTING AFTER HIM,
SO HE REACHED DOWN
AND GRABBED ONE UNION SOLDIER
AND SWUNG HIM
UP BEHIND HIM
ON THE CRUPPER OF THE HORSE
TO USE AS A SHIELD,
AND WHEN HE GOT
OUT OF RANGE,
HE THREW THE MAN OFF
AND RODE BACK
TO JOIN HIS COMMAND.
THAT WAS THE LAST SHOT FIRED
IN THE BATTLE OF SHILOH.
THE GROUND, GRANT
SAID, WAS SO COVERED WITH DEAD
THAT IT WOULD HAVE BEEN POSSIBLE
TO WALK ACROSS THE CLEARING
IN ANY DIRECTION,
STEPPING ON DEAD BODIES
WITHOUT A FOOT
TOUCHING THE GROUND.
"WHEN THE GRAVE
WAS READY,
"WE PLACED THE BODIES
THEREIN, TWO DEEP.
"ALL THE MONUMENT REARED
TO THOSE BRAVE MEN WAS A BOARD
"UPON WHICH I CUT
WITH MY POCKET KNIFE
THE WORDS 125 REBELS."
2,477 MEN
WERE KILLED AT SHILOH.
THERE WERE 23,000
CASUALTIES OVERALL--
MORE THAN ALL
THE AMERICAN CASUALTIES
IN ALL PREVIOUS
AMERICAN WARS COMBINED...
AND IT WAS ONLY
THE BEGINNING.
SHILOH HAD THE SAME
NUMBER OF CASUALTIES
AS WATERLOO,
AND YET, WHEN
IT WAS FOUGHT,
THERE WERE ANOTHER
20 WATERLOOS TO FOLLOW,
AND GRANT, SHORTLY
BEFORE SHILOH, SAID,
"I CONSIDER THIS WAR
PRACTICALLY OVER.
THEY'RE READY
TO GIVE UP,"
AND THE DAY AFTER
SHILOH, HE SAID,
"I SAW THAT IT WAS GOING TO
HAVE TO BE A WAR OF CONQUEST
IF WE WERE TO WIN."
SHILOH DID THAT,
AND IT SOBERED THE NATION
UP SOMETHING AWFUL,
THE REALIZATION
THAT THEY HAD
AVERY BLOODY AFFAIR
ON THEIR HANDS,
AND IT CALLED FOR
A HUGE REASSESSMENT
OF WHAT THIS THING
WAS GOING TO BE.
YEARS AFTERWARD,
A UNION VETERAN SAID,
THE MOST A SOLDIER
COULD SAY OF ANY FIGHT WAS,
"I WAS WORSE SCARED
THAN I WAS AT SHILOH."
"SHILOH"
IS A HEBREW WORD
MEANING
"PLACE OF PEACE."
"APRIL 11, 1862.
"I FIRMLY BELIEVE THAT
BEFORE MANY CENTURIES MORE,
"SCIENCE WILL BE
THE MASTER OF MAN.
"THE ENGINES
HE WILL HAVE INVENTED
"WILL BE BEYOND
HIS STRENGTH TO CONTROL.
"SOMEDAY, SCIENCE SHALL HAVE
THE EXISTENCE OF MANKIND
"IN ITS POWER,
"AND THE HUMAN RACE
COMMIT SUICIDE
BY BLOWING UP THE WORLD."
HEN RY ADAMS.
THE ARMIES THAT U.S.
GRANT AND GEORGE McCLELLAN LED
WERE THE BEST-EQUIPPED
IN HISTORY.
THE PRODUCTIVE CAPACITY
AND TECHNICAL INGENUITY
OF THE NORTH WERE NOW
FOCUSED ON WEAPONS...
AND THE CIVIL WAR
WOULD SEE
THE FIRST
RAILROAD ARTILLERY,
THE FIRST LAND MINES
AND TELESCOPIC SIGHTS,
THE FIRST
MILITARY TELEGRAPHS.
IN 1862 ALONE,
240 PATENTS WERE ISSUED
FOR MILITARY WEAPONS.
LINCOLN WAS FASCINATED
BY NEW WEAPONRY.
HE PERSONALLY TESTED
NEW RIFLES
AND ORDERED UP
10 UNION REPEATING GUNS,
FORERUNNERS
OF THE MACHINE GUN,
BUT HE PASSED UP
A SCHEME
TO MANUFACTURE
CANOE-SHAPED FOOTWEAR
FOR WALKING ON WATER,
AND TACTFULLY DECLINED
A HERD OF WAR ELEPHANTS
OFFERED BY
THE KING OF SIAM.
THEY HAD
MANY CRAZY IDEAS,
ALONG WITH
SOME GOOD ONES.
THERE WAS ONE PLAN
TO USE TWO CANNON,
EACH WITH A CANNONBALL
AND THE TWO CANNONBALLS
CONNECTED BY A CHAIN.
AND YOU VVOULD FIRE THE TWO
CANNONS AT THE SAME TIME,
AND THE BALLS
WOULD GO OUT,
AND THE CHAIN
BETWEEN THEM
VVOULD JUST CUT A SWATH THROUGH
EVERYTHING IN THE WAY.
THE TROUBLE WAS,
ONE CANNON, OF COURSE,
WENT OFF BEFORE
THE OTHER ONE DID
WITH THE RESULT THAT THE
BALL WENT AROUND IN A CIRCLE
FROM THE OTHER CANNON.
THE MOST IMPORTANT
INNOVATION OF THE WHOLE WAR
WAS THE RIFLED MUSKET,
ALONG WITH
A FRENCH REFINEMENT--
CAPTAIN CLAUDE MINIE'S
NEW BULLET,
AN INCH-LONG LEAD SLUG
THAT EXPANDED INTO
THE BARREL'S RIFLED GROOVES
AND SPUN
AS IT LEFT THE MUZZLE.
THE MINIE BALL COULD KILL
AT HALF A MILE
AND WAS ACCURATE
AT 250 YARDS--
5 TIMES AS FAR
AS ANY OTHER ONE-MAN WEAPON.
THE AGE OF THE BAYONET
CHARGE HAD ENDED,
THOUGH MOST OFFICERS
DID NOT YET KNOW IT
WHEN THE WAR BEGAN,
AND SOME HAD STILL
NOT LEARNED IT
WHEN THE WAR WAS OVER.
IT WAS BRUTAL STUFF.
THE REASON FOR THE HIGH CASUALTIES
IS REALLY QUITE SIMPLE--
THE WEAPONS WERE WAY
AHEAD OF THE TACTICS.
THE RIFLE ITSELF,
IT THREW A .53 CALIBER
SOFT LEAD BULLET
AT A LOW
MUZZLE VELOCITY,
AND WHEN IT HIT--
THE REASON THERE WERE
SO MANY AMPUTATIONS,
IF YOU GOT HIT HERE,
IT DIDN'T CLIP YOUR BONE
THE WAY THE MODERN
STEEL-JACKETED BULLET DOES.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANY BONE
FROM HERE TO HERE.
THEY HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO TAKE YOUR ARM OFF,
AND YOU'LL SEE PICTURES
OF THE DEAD ON THE BATTLEFIELD
WITH THEIR CLOTHES
IN DISARRAY
AS IF SOMEONE HAD BEEN
GOING--RIFLING THEIR BODIES.
THAT WAS THE MEN THEMSELVES
TEARING THEIR CLOTHES UP
TO SEE WHERE
THE WOUND WAS,
AND THEY KNEW
PERFECTLY WELL
IF THEY WERE
GUT SHOT, THEY'D DIE.
"APRIL 25, 1862,
"PITTSBURG LANDING,
TENNESSEE.
"DEAR JULIA...
"I'M NO LONGER BOSS.
"GENERAL HALLECK
IS HERE,
"AND I'M TRULY
GLAD OF IT.
"I HOPE THE PAPERS
WILL LET ME ALONE
"IN THE FUTURE.
"IF THE PAPERS ONLY KNEW
HOW LITTLE AMBITION I HAVE
"OUTSIDE OF PUTTING
DOWN THIS REBELLION
"AND GETTING BACK
ONCE MORE
"TO LIVE QUIETLY
AND UNOBTRUSIVELY
"WITH MY FAMILY,
I THINK THEY WOULD
SAY FEWER FALSEHOODS."
ULYSSES S. GRANT.
ULYSSES S. GRANT'S REWARD
FOR THE COSTLY
UNION VICTORY AT SHILOH
WAS TO BE REMOVED
FROM FIELD COMMAND.
GRANT'S SUPERIOR WAS
GENERAL HENRY WAGER HALLECK,
A CALCULATING
ADMINISTRATOR
WHO WAS JEALOUS
OF GRANT'S SUCCESS
AND ANXIOUS TO GET RID
OF HIS CHIEF RIVAL.
AFTER THE BATTLE
OF FORT DONELSON,
HE SPREAD RUMORS
GRANT WAS DRINKING.
AFTER THE FEARFUL
LOSSES AT SHILOH,
HE HAD GRANT REASSIGNED.
GRANT DECIDED TO QUIT,
BUT HIS FRIEND
WILLIAM TECUMSEH SHERMAN
TALKED HIM OUT OF IT.
"YOU COULD NOT BE QUIET
AT HOME FOR A WEEK,"
HE SAID, "WHEN ARMIES
ARE MOVING."
GRANT AND SHERMAN
WERE BOTH OHIO BOYS
AND WEST POINTERS
WHO WERE FOND OF CIGARS,
SCORN ED
POMP AND POLITICS,
AND HAD FARED POORLY
IN CIVILIAN LIFE.
GRANT ENJOYED SHERMAN'S
RAPID-FIRE BRILLIANCE
AND WAS GRATEFUL
FOR THE DISPATCH
WITH WHICH HE CARRIED OUT
EVERY ORDER.
SHERMAN ADMIRED
HIS FRIEND'S COOL TEMPER,
HIS STEADINESS
IN THE MIDST OF CRISIS,
AND WHAT HE CALLED GRANT'S
"SIMPLE FAITH IN SUCCESS."
THEY TRUSTED EACH OTHER.
"I'M A DAMNED SIGHT
SMARTER THAN GRANT.
"I KNOW MORE ABOUT ORGANIZATION,
SUPPLY, AND ADMINISTRATION,
"AND ABOUT EVERYTHING ELSE
THAN HE DOES.
"BUT I'LL TELL YOU
WHERE HE BEATS ME
"AND WHERE HE BEATS
THE WORLD--
"HE DON'T CARE A DAMN FOR WHAT
THE ENEMY DOES OUT OF HIS SIGHT,
BUT IT SCARES ME
LIKE HELL."
WILLIAM TECUMSEH SHERMAN.
"ANY ATTEMPT NOW
"TO SEPARATE
THE FREEDOM OF THE SLAVE
"FROM THE VICTORY
OF THE GOVERNMENT,
"ANY ATTEMPT TO SECURE
PEACE TO THE WHITES
"WHILE LEAVING
THE BLACKS IN CHAINS,
"WILL BE LABOR LOST.
"THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
"AND THE GOVERNMENT
AT WASHINGTON
"MAY REFUSE TO
RECOGNIZE IT FOR A TIME,
"BUT THE INEXORABLE
LOGIC OF EVENTS
"WILL FORCE IT UPON THEM
IN THE END--
"THAT THE WAR NOW
BEING WAGED IN THIS LAND
IS A WAR FOR
AND AGAINST SLAVERY."
FREDERICK DOUGLASS.
LETTER BY LETTER,
SPEECH BY SPEECH,
MONTH AFTER MONTH,
FREDERICK DOUGLASS
TIRELESSLY LOBBIED
THE GOVERNMENT
IN WASHINGTON,
URGING LINCOLN
TO EMANCIPATE THE SLAVES...
BUT THE PRESIDENT
STILL INSISTED
THE WAR WAS BEING FOUGHT
FOR UNION
AND PUBLICLY AVOIDED DOUGLASS
AND THE DEBATE.
"OUR SOUTHERN FRIEND
TELLS US
"THE NORTH IS FIGHTING
FOR NEGROES.
"OUR UNION FRIEND SAYS
"THEY'RE NOT FIGHTING
TO FREE THE NEGROES,
"BUT FOR THE UNION.
"VERY WELL.
"LET THE WHITES FIGHT
FOR WHAT THEY WANT;
"WE NEGROES FIGHT
FOR WHAT WE WANT.
"LIBERTY
MUST TAKE THE DAY,
"NOTHING SHORTER.
"WE CARE NOTHING
ABOUT THE UNION.
"WE HAVE BEEN
IN IT SLAVES
OVER 250 YEARS."
"WHATEVER NATION
GETS THE CONTROL
"OF THE OHIO, MISSISSIPPI,
AND MISSOURI RIVERS
WILL CONTROL
THE CONTINENT."
WILLIAM TECUMSEH SHERMAN.
OUT WEST, UNION NAVAL
STRATEGY WAS STRAIGHTFORWARD"
SEIZE CONTROL
OF THE MISSISSIPPI
AND CUT
THE CONFEDERACY IN TWO.
ON APRIL 7,
UNION GUNBOATS
AND 2,000 TROOPS
TOOK THE CONFEDERATE FORTRESS
AT ISLAND NUMBER 10
NEAR NEW MADRID, MISSOURI,
LEAVING THE RIVER OPEN
AS FAR SOUTH AS MEMPHIS.
TWO MONTHS LATER,
MEMPHIS FELL.
ON THE NIGHT OF APRIL 24,
A 60-YEAR-OLD FLAG OFFICER,
DAVID G. FARRAGUT,
STARTED NORTH
UP THE MISSISSIPPI,
INTENT ON CAPTURING
NEW ORLEANS.
BUT FIRST, HE HAD
TO GET BY THE HEAVY GUNS
AT FORTS JACKSON
AND ST. PHILLIPS,
70 MILES BELOW THE CITY.
WHEN THE MOON ROSE,
THE CONFEDERATES OPENED FIRE
AND SENT BLAZING RAFTS
DRIFTING INTO THE UNION FLEET.
THE FIRST VESSEL
WAS HIT 42 TIMES.
FARRAGUT'S OWN FLAGSHIP
WAS SET ON FIRE,
BUT SOMEHOW THE ENTIRE FLEET
MADE IT PAST THE FORTS.
NEW ORLEANS SURRENDERED
THE NEXT DAY.
FARRAGUT HAD
THE AMERICAN FLAG RAISED
OVER CITY HALL.
"NEW ORLEANS GONE--
"AND WITH IT,
THE CONFEDERACY?
"ARE WE NOT CUT IN TWO?
THAT MISSISSIPPI
RUINS US, IF LOST."
MARY CHESNUT.
"TUPELO, MISSISSIPPI.
"I DON'T KNOW HOW THE WAR
WILL BE DECIDED
"IF ENGLAND AND FRANCE
DON'T INTERFERE
"AND STOP THE WAR.
"AND IF THE CONFEDERACY
"HAS TO GAIN HER
INDEPENDENCE BY FIGHTING,
"I AM AFRAID SHE WILL
HAVE TO GIVE IT UP,
"FOR THERE ARE
SO FEW PROVISIONS
IN THIS PORTION
OF THE CONFEDERACY."
JAMES JACKSON.
IN THE FOLLOWING MONTHS,
FARRAGUT'S FLEET
GAINED CONTROL
OF THE SOUTHERN MISSISSIPPI
AS FAR NORTH
AS BATON ROUGE AND NATCHEZ,
BUT THE NORTH DID NOT
POSSESS THE WHOLE RIVER.
THE CON FEDERATE STRONGHOLD
AT VICKSBURG STILL HELD.
"REPUBLICS--
EVERYBODY JAWING,
"EVERYBODY PUTTING
THEIR MOUTHS IN,
"NOTHING SACRED,
"ALL CONFUSION
OF BABBLE.
"REPUBLICS
CAN'T CARRY ON WAR.
HURRAH FOR A STRONG
ONE-MAN GOVERNMENT."
MARY CHESNUT.
FROM THE SOUTHERN
WHITE HOUSE IN RICHMOND,
JEFFERSON DAVIS STRUGGLED
TO KEEP THE WAR EFFORT
ON TRACK.
SOUTHERN INDUSTRY GREW,
DRIVEN BY NECESSITY,
AND THE CON FEDERATE
GOVERNMENT,
FOUNDED ON THE PRINCIPLE
OF DECENTRALIZATION,
FOUND ITSELF
CONTROLLING EVERYTHING...
FROM THE FORGING OF CANNON
AT THE BIG TREDEGAR
IRON WORKS IN RICHMOND
TO THE DAILY OUTPUT
OF THE WOMEN
WHO SPUN CLOTH
FOR UNIFORMS
IN THEIR PARLORS.
IN CHARLESTON,
MARY CHESNUT'S CIRCLE
KNIT SOCKS
FOR STONEWALL JACKSON'S
ENTIRE BRIGADE.
WOMEN WOVE BOOTS
FROM PALMETTO FRONDS,
AND SAVED THEIR URINE
FROM WHICH TO DISTILL
NITER FOR GUNPOWDER.
SOUTHERNERS GREW POPPIES
TO YIELD OPIUM,
AND MADE COFFEE
FROM CORN AND PEAS,
HYPODERMIC NEEDLES
FROM THORNS,
ROPE FROM SPANISH MOSS...
BUT THE CON FEDERATE ARMY
WAS SHRINKING.
THE TERM OF ENLISTMENT
FOR THE EARLIEST VOLUNTEERS
WAS UP IN THE SPRING.
MOST MEN
PLANNED TO GO HOME.
IN APRIL, AT THE INSISTENCE
OF JEFFERSON DAVIS,
THE CON FEDERATE CONGRESS
PASSED TWO LAWS.
ONE EXTENDED ALL ENLISTMENTS
FOR THE DURATION.
THE OTHER REQUIRED
ALL ABLE-BODIED WHITE MEN
BETWEEN 18 AND 35
TO SERVE FOR 3 YEARS.
IT WAS THE FIRST NATIONAL
DRAFT IN AMERICAN HISTORY.
"THE CONSCRIPTION ACT,
AT ONE FELL SWOOP,
"STRIKES DOWN THE
SOVEREIGNTY OF THE STATES,
"TRAMPLES UPON
THE CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS
"AND PERSONAL LIBERTY
OF THE CITIZENS,
AND ARMS THE PRESIDENT
WITH IMPERIAL POWERS."
GOVERNOR JOSEPH E. BROWN
OF GEORGIA.
"MRS. DAVIS
IS BEING UTTERLY UPSET.
"SHE IS BEGINNING
"TO HEAR THE CARPING
AND FAULTFINDING
"TO WHICH THE PRESIDENT
IS SUBJECTED.
"THERE MUST
BE AN OPPOSITION
"IN A FREE COUNTRY,
BUT IT IS
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE."
MARY CHESNUT.
VETERANS WERE
ESPECIALLY RESENTFUL
BECAUSE POTENTIAL DRAFTEES
WHO OWNED 20 SLAVES OR MORE
COULD BE EXEMPTED.
"A LAW WAS MADE
ALLOWING EVERY PERSON
"WHO OWNED 20 NEGROES
TO GO HOME.
"IT GAVE US THE BLUES.
"WE WANTED 20 NEGROES.
"THERE WAS
RAISED THE HOWL
“OF RICH MAN'S WAR,
POOR MAN'S FIGHT!
"FROM THIS TIME ON
TILL THE END OF THE WAR,
"A SOLDIER WAS SIMPLY
A MACHINE, A CONSCRIPT.
"ALL OUR PRIDE
AND VALOR HAD GONE,
"AND WE WERE SICK OF WAR
AND CURSED
THE SOUTHERN CONFEDERACY."
SAM WATKINS.
NEARLY HALF THE SOUTHERNERS
ELIGIBLE FOR THE NEW DRAFT
FAILED TO SIGN UP.
"APRIL 21.
"16 DAYS HAVE NOW BEEN
SPENT IN THIS PLACE.
"OUR GRAND ARMY
HAS AGAIN COME TO A HALT.
"UNDER THE DRY PINE LEAVES
WHERE WE ENCAMP,
"A GREAT SECESH ARMY
OF WOOD TICKS HAVE WINTERED.
"FEW ARE SO HAPPY
AS NOT TO FIND
"HALF A DOZEN OF THESE
VILLAINOUS BLOODSUCKERS
STICKING IN HIS FLESH
EVERY MORNING."
CHAPLAIN
A.M. STEWART.
"THE FIRING
FROM THE CONFEDERATE LINES
"WAS OF LITTLE CONSEQUENCE,
"NOT AMOUNTING TO OVER 10 OR
12 ARTILLERY SHOTS EACH DAY,
"A NUMBER OF THESE BEING
DIRECTED AT THE HUGE BALLOON
WHICH WENT UP DAILY FROM GENERAL
FITZ JOHN'S HEADQUARTERS."
"WHEN ABOUT
100 FEET ABOVE THE GROUND,
"THE ROPE BROKE,
"AND THE GENERAL
SAILED OFF TOWARD RICHMOND
"AT A GREATER SPEED
"THAN THE ARMY
OF THE POTOMAC IS MOVING.
"HE HAD
SUFFICIENT CALMNESS
"TO PULL THE VALVE ROPE,
AND GRADUALLY DESCENDED
ABOUT 3 MILES FROM CAMP."
ON THE PENINSULA,
GENERAL GEORGE McCLELLAN'S
HUGE ARMY
SAT IN FRONT OF THE SMALLER
REBEL FORCE AT YORKTOWN
FOR ALMOST A MONTH.
IT RAINED 2
OUT OF EVERY 3 DAYS.
HUNDREDS FELL ILL.
"I FEEL THAT THE FATE
OF A NATION DEPENDS ON ME,
"AND THAT I HAVE
NOT ONE SINGLE FRIEND
AT THE SEAT
OF GOVERNMENT."
GEORGE McCLELLAN.
McCLELLAN HAD MOVED
MORE THAN 90 FEDERAL GUNS
TO YORKTOWN BY MAY 3,
SOME SO MASSIVE
THAT IT TOOK 100 HORSES
TO HAUL THEM UP
ALONG HASTILY CONSTRUCTED
TIMBER HIGHWAYS
CALLED "COR-DU-ROI" ROADS.
MCCLELLAN
FINALLY DECIDED TO ACT
AND CAREFULLY PLANNED
A MASSIVE BOMBARDMENT
FOR MAY 5,
BUT ON THE NIGHT OF THE 3rd,
GENERAL MAGRUDER'S
CONFEDERATE BATTERIES
SUDDENLY INTENSIFIED
THEIR FIRE.
MCCLELLAN BRACED
FOR AN ATTACK,
BUT THE NEXT MORNING,
THE CONFEDERATES HAD VANISHED.
DISBELIEVING
FEDERAL TROOPS
EDGED INTO THE DESERTED
SOUTHERN CAMPS.
MAGRUDER HAD PACKED UP
HIS SHOW AND MOVED ON,
BUT McCLELLAN DECLARED IT
A UNION VICTORY.
"THE SUCCESS
IS BRILLIANT,
"AND YOU MAY REST ASSURED
"THAT ITS EFFECTS WILL BE
OF THE GREATEST IMPORTANCE.
"THERE SHALL
BE NO DELAY
IN FOLLOWING UP
THE REBELS."
THE UNION MEN
NOW CAUTIOUSLY
FOLLOWED THE REBEL ARMY WEST
TOWARDS RICHMOND.
"MAY 20.
"RICHMOND IS
JUST 9 MILES OFF.
"THE NEGROES ARE
DELIGHTED TO SEE US,
"BUT THE WHITES LOOK
AS IF THEY WOULD
LIKE TO KILL US."
ELISHA HUNT RHODES.
FROM McCLELLAN'S LINES,
YOU COULD HEAR THE BELLS
OF RICHMOND TOLLING.
YOU COULD HEAR
THE CHURCH BELLS IN
THE PUBLIC CLOCK STRIKING,
HE WAS THAT CLOSE.
A WORRIED
JEFFERSON DAVIS NOW PREPARED
FOR A SIEGE OF RICHMOND,
RELYING MORE AND MORE
ON THE ADVICE
OF HIS CLOSE MILITARY
ADVISOR ROBERT E. LEE.
WHEN DAVIS ASKED
WHERE LEE THOUGHT
THE SOUTH'S NEXT DEFENSIVE
LINE SHOULD BE DRAWN
ONCE RICHMOND FELL,
LEE SAID,
"RICHMOND MUST NOT FALL.
IT SHALL NOT BE GIVEN UP."
STILL, GEORGE MCCLELLAN
REFUSED TO ATTACK.
THOUGH HIS ARMY STILL
OUTNUMBERED THE REBELS,
HE REMAINED CONVINCED
THE OPPOSITE WAS TRUE.
ONE OBSERVER NOTED
THAT MCCLELLAN
HAD A PARTICULAR FACULTY
FOR "REALIZING
HALLUCINATIONS."
HE DEMANDED
ANOTHER 40,000 MEN.
"IF HE HAD
A MILLION MEN,
"HE WOULD SWEAR
THE ENEMY HAD TWO MILLIONS,
"AND THEN HE WOULD
SIT DOWN IN THE MUD
AND YELL FOR 3."
EDWIN M. STANTON.
WITH THE YEAR HALF GONE,
THE UNION'S GRAND STRATEGY
HAD STALLED.
THE WESTERN CAMPAIGN
BEGUN BY U.S. GRANT
HAD GROUND TO A HALT
IN NORTH MISSISSIPPI,
AND McCLELLAN'S MIGHTY FORCES
WERE PARALYZED
IN FRONT OF RICHMOND.
THERE WAS WORSE TO COME.
THE KILLING THAT WOULD
SOON BREAK OUT IN VIRGINIA
WOULD CONTINUE ALL YEAR
AND COME TO A CLIMAX
ALONG A TINY CREEK
IN WESTERN MARYLAND
CALLED THE ANTIETAM.
"WE TALK OF
THE IRREPRESSIBLE CONFLICT
"AND PRACTICALLY
GIVE THE LIE TO OUR TALK.
"WE WAGE WAR AGAINST
SLAVEHOLDING REBELS
"AND YET PROTECT
AND AUGMENT THE MOTIVE
"WHICH HAS MOVED THE
SLAVEHOLDERS TO REBELLION.
"WE STRIKE
AT THE EFFECT
"AND LEAVE
THE CAUSE UNHARMED.
"FIRE WILL NOT
BURN IT OUT OF US,
"WATER CANNOT
WASH IT OUT OF US,
"THAT THIS WAR
WITH THE SLAVEHOLDERS
"CAN NEVER BE BROUGHT
TO A DESIRABLE TERMINATION
"UNTIL SLAVERY,
"THE GUILTY CAUSE OF
ALL OUR NATIONAL TROUBLES,
HAS BEEN TOTALLY
AND FOREVER ABOLISHED."
FREDERICK DOUGLASS.
SamSerial.com
https://telegram.me/samserial