Thanks, mate.
Stand by.
Rehearsal, nice and quiet, please.
Are we still waiting on anyone?
Bob Hawke,
if you win the election next week,
which all the polls predict,
one of your first public acts
as prime minister
will be to welcome Prince Charles
and the Princess of Wales
and young Prince William.
Does that prospect
fill you with enthusiasm?
I don't, uh, regard it
as the most important thing
I'll have to do
in the first month in office.
But, yes, they are coming.
I've had the opportunity
of meeting Charles
on a number of occasions. I find him…
a nice young bloke.
Is he the sort of man
you'd like to be the king of Australia?
Look, I don't think we'll be
talking about, uh, kings or monarchy
here in Australia much longer.
We're past that now, aren't we?
We're a bit more mature.
Hear, hear.
You know my position on this.
It's no secret.
I respect and admire the Queen enormously.
The desire is simply
to have a head of state
that embodies and represents
Australia's values and traditions,
a head of state that looks like us,
sounds like us, thinks like us.
As opposed to?
Well, one of them. A pom.
You know, an unelected non-Australian
who lives on the other side of the world
and, for all their good intentions,
is a different breed.
You wouldn't put a pig in charge
of a herd of prime beef cattle…
…even if it looked good
in a twinset and pearls.
Your Majesty.
The results
of the Australian general election.
Oh, good news or bad?
Mr. Hawke by a landslide.
- Oh dear. The one who wants us out?
- Afraid so.
The rough, tough
former trade union negotiator
and the proud holder
of the world record for beer drinking.
A yard of ale in a sconce pot
in 11 seconds.
I don't know what that is.
It sounds very impressive.
- Well, it's a lot of beer, very quickly.
- Ah.
Teetotal now, I believe, ma'am.
Oh, a great relief to everyone,
I should imagine.
Especially Mrs. Hawke.
Is there a Mrs. Hawke?
Yes, there is. Hazel.
Ah, Hazel. Strange, I think,
to name a child after a tree.
- Especially a northern hemisphere tree.
- Yes.
I suppose
it does put the pressure on them, rather.
On who, ma'am?
The Prince and Princess of Wales
and their forthcoming tour.
Do you think they'll be all right?
One shouldn't listen to gossip,
but I had lunch
with Princess Margaret the other day.
There's growing concern among those
who chatter at Kensington Palace…
- I thought we didn't listen to chatter.
- I listen to nothing else.
…about the Princess of Wales.
She's struggling to cope, apparently.
Wretched in the marriage.
And…
if rumors are to be believed,
she's, uh… doing things to herself.
What things?
People do the strangest things
when they're unhappy.
I heard she was insisting
on taking the baby with them on the tour.
- What for?
- As a stabilizing influence.
Since when has a baby ever been
a stabilizing influence on anything?
We never took the children anywhere.
When we went to Australia in 1954,
we left them at home for five months.
Hmm.
And do you suppose
that might have had consequences?
On what? The tour was a triumph.
I should probably ask Charles and Diana
to come and see me.
This tour is too important.
Does anyone know
the story of the Russian bear hunter?
I'm afraid
I've already told Mrs. Parker Bowles.
- Perhaps she could help me tell it.
- All right, sir.
A bear hunter
goes deep into the Siberian woods.
Suddenly, he sees…
…an enormous bear.
The hunter raises his gun,
and, bang, he shoots.
The bear disappears from view.
"Got him!" he thinks.
But then he feels a tap on the shoulder.
He looks up to see the bear, who says…
"No one takes a shot at me
and gets away with it!"
"You have a choice."
"Either I can tear you to pieces
and devour you now, or…"
"…or you can drop your trousers,
bend over,
and let me have my way with you."
The hunter pulls down his trousers,
and the bear does his worst.
Afterwards,
the hunter hobbles into town…
- …somewhat bow-legged.
- Yes!
And he buys a much bigger gun
and goes back into the woods.
And it isn't long
before he sees the bear again.
He raises his gun, bang, fires.
- But when the smoke clears…
- …the bear's nowhere to be seen.
"Got him," the hunter thinks.
But a moment later,
he feels another tap on his shoulder,
and the bear says…
"You know what to do."
Now, after the bear's done his worst,
the hunter heads back in town again
and buys an even bigger gun.
- A bazooka.
- Yes!
He goes back into the woods,
he sees the bear,
he takes aim and fires.
Boom!
But when the smoke clears…
the hunter looks up
to see the bear standing over him,
and the bear says…
"You're not in this for the hunting,
are you?"
I wanted to wish you both luck
and asked Sir Sonny to join us today
to stress again
the importance of the trip.
Thank you, ma'am.
As you know,
Australia is one of the most important
and influential members
of the Commonwealth.
If they were to strike out
and assert their independence,
the worry is
other countries could fall like dominoes.
You're too young to remember,
but we also toured Australia
and New Zealand in 1954.
Yes.
- It was long and hot and arduous.
- Yes.
- But we worked together.
- As a team.
And in the end, I think…
it wasn't only a success politically.
It…
brought us very close.
Yes.
And as husband and wife,
we would wish the same for you.
Mmm.
Aw, there.
It's all right. Mummy's here.
He's teething. Have you got the drops?
- He'll be all right on the plane.
- Diana.
Just glance over your shoulder.
Then on
to Ayers Rock on the 23rd.
Uh, Sydney on the 28th,
before Brisbane, Tasmania and Canberra
for an audience
with the prime minister and his wife.
Then the tour moves to New Zealand.
It's an awful lot of moving around.
A baby needs stability.
And… perhaps for that reason,
the baby was never intended
to be part of the trip.
I always made it perfectly clear.
No baby, no me.
And everyone accepted that
and has worked very hard
to change plans that were set in stone.
And now,
instead of being separated for six weeks,
it's just… How long?
- The first two weeks.
- What?
- When the tour is at its most arduous.
- Where will William be then?
Woomargama.
- Where?
- It's a sheep station in New South Wales.
Whose idea was this?
- Mine, ma'am.
- Do you have children?
- No, ma'am.
- Why does that not come as a surprise?
- Diana.
- Come with me.
- Ma'am.
- Please.
What do you see?
His Royal Highness
Prince William.
That's a title. You can't see a title.
Very well. I see… a baby boy.
Asleep or awake?
- Awake.
- Loud or quiet?
- Quiet.
- Angry or calm?
- Calm.
- Ugly or beautiful?
It's just a question,
nothing to be frightened of.
- Is the child ugly?
- No.
Then can we agree
that this child is the opposite of ugly?
Can we say he's a beautiful child?
I'm busy, ma'am. What is your point?
My point is that
this child is not just beautiful.
This child is perfect in every single way.
So why should you expect me,
as his mother,
to be without him for one second,
let alone two weeks?
Because you married
the Prince of Wales, ma'am.
And that is an act of service
to the Crown and to the country,
which you signed up to willingly
and with open eyes,
and you are the Princess of Wales.
Then the greatest act of service
that I can give to the Crown as princess
is not to be some meek little wife
following the great prince around
like some smiling doll,
but to be a living,
breathing, present mother,
bringing up this child in the hopes
that the boy that will one day become king
still has a vestige of humanity in him.
God knows he's not going to be getting it
from any of his courtiers.
Mummy's here.
Uh…
- New Zealand.
- Yes, New Zealand.
Welcome to Alice Springs.
More than a month's rain in a week.
Hello there. Charles, lovely name.
Very good. Nice to meet you.
Hello there. Lovely to meet you.
- He's not very happy.
- I will mind him.
- Diana.
- Are you all right with him?
Diana! Come on.
We have to go.
I understand before we arrived,
you received
about a month's worth of rain in a week.
Of course, in Britain,
we call that summer.
But seriously, my wife and I,
we couldn't be more delighted to be here.
Question for the princess.
What part of the tour
are you most looking forward to?
Oh gosh. Um…
There's so many.
We're going
to a glamorous ball in Sydney.
And, um…
The Royal Botanical Gardens…
We're going to visit
the Royal Botanical Gardens in Sydney.
Oh God!
And I think we're going
on a pleasure cruise on… some river.
Um…
And then we're going to visit Ayers Dock.
- Rock. Rock!
- Ayers Rock.
- She really say that?
- Blimey!
Honestly.
What about the cost of the trip
at a time when Australia is
experiencing extreme weather, you know,
and the money could be spent
on the victims?
I'm afraid
that's not really my department.
She's good with glamorous balls.
Ayers Rock, or "Ayers Dock" …
Apparently, there are protests planned
for their visit to Canberra.
A growing backlash
about the expense of the trip.
Maybe now's the moment.
1788, the First Fleet landed
at Sydney Cove.
Two long centuries of subjugation
by Mother Crown,
and we are still unable
to cut the apron strings
and stand on our own two feet.
Why?
Because there has never been
the tipping point
where we finally say, "Enough."
But, uh…
five'll get you ten
it'll be this jug-eared bonehead
that pushes us all over the edge.
And Australia gets to be free…
once and for all.
That's all for now.
- Thank you all very much.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
An hospitable Perth,
fresh, alert, scrubbed by the sun.
City of Australia's tomorrow.
Into Queensland,
named for another great queen
four generations back.
To Brisbane, friendly, easygoing Brisbane.
What's this?
Australia, 1954.
I wanted to remind myself.
Huh.
One of your greatest hits.
Yes, I think so.
How hot it was!
Do you remember?
Yes, one could hardly sleep at night.
No.
Look at the size of those crowds.
Head of the Commonwealth,
defender of the faith.
Sydney,
over a million people turned out.
- To see the beautiful new Queen.
- Mmm.
Now she's old and dumpy,
they want rid of her.
Not old and dumpy. Experienced and mature.
Which is why you should have gone yourself
instead of sending out the B-team.
This was always designed
to be Charles's tour.
As Prince of Wales,
he has to start sometime.
Then send him
to the Bahamas or Seychelles,
not Australia and New Zealand.
Some countries are too important
to send out the understudy.
…a living symbol
of the unity of Crown and people.
And a nation waits.
- Your Royal Highness, over here.
- Towards the cameras, please.
Maybe just get in closer together
if possible.
- Princess Diana, over this way.
- That's great. Thank you.
- Can we get some big smiles, please?
- Can we get waves for the Australians?
- Lady Di!
- Diana!
Are you going up to the top today?
Charles.
Charles!
I can't.
The heat.
I feel dizzy.
You all right?
- I think I need to go and sit down.
- Can you pull yourself together?
Do you need some water?
Are you feeling all right, Diana?
- Is it the heat?
- Are you all right, Princess?
It was at this point
the princess seemed to struggle.
The English rose wilting in the heat,
perhaps.
It's pathetic.
She's pathetic.
It's so critical
we get this tour absolutely right,
and yet she's so weak and fragile.
One can't rely on her
for the simplest thing.
Letting the side down wherever she goes.
How will I get through the next six weeks
without you?
By ringing me every day.
Letting me cheer you up.
You're going to be brilliant.
God, I miss you, my darling,
your adulthood.
If Diana had one ounce
of the strength of character
that you seem to display at every turn,
perhaps we'd rescue...
- Change the plan!
- Ma'am...
- God, now what?
- I won't go on like this.
- You understand? I mean it!
- It never ends.
I'll call you back.
We'd have to reorganize police,
schools, couriers, military...
Well, I don't care about any of that!
It's intolerable.
What's intolerable?
Well, I don't expect you to understand.
I just need him to let me go
wherever it is they've taken my son.
Woomargama?
It's on the other side of the country.
I explained to Her Royal Highness
we are five days into an important tour
which has been years in the planning.
We can't change things around willy-nilly.
- And I told him...
- He has a name.
If people expect me to continue
with this tour for another minute,
then I need to see my son first.
Our son.
- Hello.
- Your Royal Highness.
William?
William.
William!
Thank you so much. Has he been all right?
- He's been great.
- Hi, darling!
Hello! How are you?
Yes.
Oh, I missed you so much.
Yes. Hello!
You want to go to Daddy?
- Prince William, over here.
- Do we have a crown somewhere?
Who does he look like more?
What are his favorite toys?
Is he more Spencer or Windsor?
- William!
- Come on.
Not bad for a future king.
Oh, that's lovely. King and heir.
- Little performer.
- What about a spare?
Come to Daddy.
He's doing quite well.
There you are. Close your eyes.
Gone down?
Yes, finally.
Exhausted after his performance.
The star.
Crashing and bashing into everything.
The basher.
A mini tornado.
Will you eat? They made…
somewhat unimaginatively
for a sheep station, shepherd's pie.
I'm not hungry.
What?
I wanted to talk to you.
I've had some thoughts.
About?
Us.
Well, I have some things
I'd like to discuss too.
Would you like to go first?
- It'd make a nice change.
- What does that mean?
- It means you always go first.
- What poppycock.
You're the Prince of Wales.
You're born to go first.
Are you even remotely aware
of how bad things have got for me?
I'm not blind.
I can see how unhappy you are.
How thin you've become.
You don't know the half of it.
I know more than you think.
People talk. The staff. And I was…
very saddened…
horrified by what I learned.
So, what do you want from me?
To be heard.
And I'm listening.
No, more than that.
To be understood, appreciated.
I don't need endless flattery.
No one wants that.
But I am trying my hardest to please you,
to live up to your standards,
and I don't think
you have the faintest idea
of what it's like to feel this way.
- To be constantly overlooked, ignored...
- Don't have the faintest idea?
I know what being overlooked feels like.
I've spent my whole life being unthanked,
unappreciated, uncared for.
And if I've been cold or distant with you,
perhaps it's because I don't feel
truly understood by you.
I sometimes think
you see me as an old man.
Or worse,
a gargoyle above the church door.
Gray, made of stone,
unemotional, but I'm not.
You think I don't crave
the occasional "Well done," or…
"Aren't you clever?"
Or even just a thank-you.
I need encouragement
and the occasional pat on the back too.
Does that explain
why you keep going to her?
I'm not going to say her name.
I'm worried if I do, I might spit.
Camilla. What's she got to do with it?
That's what I keep asking myself.
What's she got to do with anything?
But, obviously,
she's got a lot to do with everything
because you can't leave her alone.
She and her husband are close friends,
not just of mine, but the whole family's.
Remember I found your bracelet,
the one with your nicknames
engraved on it, Fred and Gladys?
It was harmless fun.
Three days before our wedding,
you gave that to her.
And on our actual honeymoon,
you wore the cuff links that she gave you,
with the interlocking initials,
the two Cs,
interwoven
and obscenely entwined like lovers.
And on the same honeymoon, a photograph
of her falls out of your diary.
Later in the year,
I find your love letters.
Page after page
with a passion I'm not getting from you!
'Cause you show no interest in me!
You refuse to come to Highgrove,
where I'm happiest.
Yes, because she is there!
And not just her, but the gardens
and the polo and the hunts,
and the boring old philosophers
and father substitutes
who patronize me and ignore me,
but love her, presumably.
Which is why the two of you
are perfect for each other.
- So, where do I fit in?
- You fit in because you're my wife.
And…
because…
I love you.
I…
- I...
- I do.
Gosh.
So…
how are we going to solve it?
Well…
Well, I suppose…
I suppose we've got to learn
to give it to each other
on a more regular basis.
The encouragement, I mean.
- Well, and the other thing.
- Well, yes, that too.
'Cause I still think you're gorgeous.
- Cleverest, handsomest man in every room.
- Do you really?
Pathetic,
but I do need that sometimes.
And you look gorgeous too.
Your beauty, your radiance is
a great shining, spectacular miracle.
When I see the light in people's faces
when they look at you, it makes me realize
that I'm the luckiest man in the world,
we're the luckiest family in the world.
It makes me want
to ring the Queen and say,
"Can you hear that? Listen to that!"
"It's 100 decibels louder
than anything you ever got."
"Chew on that! Choke on that!"
I think this might be the most important
conversation we've ever had.
- Yes.
- And the solution is so simple.
Any time either of us feels
we're not getting what we need,
we simply need to give that very thing
to the other.
- If you learned anything from today...
- We both need the same as each other.
To be encouraged.
To be supported.
And to be…
appreciated.
To be loved.
Yes.
A toast.
To a fresh start.
A new beginning.
Happy Easter, my darling.
Well done, brave boy.
What does he want?
Give him a kiss.
- What have I got here?
- What's that?
The first leg
of the royal tour has come to an end.
The prince and princess have seen
a slice of the Northern Territory…
The royal couple emerged.
2,000 well-wishers there to greet them.
But the more formal welcome
came from the governor-general
and the prime minister.
Welcome to sunny Perth.
We're absolutely delighted to be here.
Thank you so much.
Hours before
they were to arrive in the city,
tens of thousands of people
began lining the streets from the airport.
By now,
the pace was really beginning to pick up,
and so too was the public's reaction.
More than 5,500 people
queued patiently
to take up the best possible position
around the ropes cordoning off…
Here, the reception
the royal couple were getting was growing…
There was a frenzy
of waving hands and flags
as the prince and princess appeared,
holding hands
in the back of their Rolls-Royce.
The crowds were desperate
to get a glimpse of the perfect couple.
The Prince and Princess of Wales…
Even overseas reporters,
who've seen it all before,
seemed a little taken aback
by the sheer scale
and excitement of the welcome…
We've gotta get a good spot.
Please welcome
the heir to the throne
and Australia's future king,
His Royal Highness the Prince of Wales.
Thank you, Sir James.
In case you've been living in a cave,
perhaps I should introduce you
to a most remarkable woman and mother
who I am proud to call my wife.
Lady Di!
I love you, Diana!
Diana, I love you!
I love you so much! I love you!
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off of you ♪
♪ You'd be like Heaven to touch ♪
♪ I wanna hold you so much ♪
♪ At long last, love has arrived ♪
♪ And I thank God I'm alive ♪
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off of you ♪
- Let's give them a show, shall we?
- Go on, then.
♪ I love you, baby ♪
♪ And if it's quite alright
I need you, baby ♪
♪ To warm a lonely night ♪
♪ I love you, baby ♪
♪ Trust in me when I say ♪
♪ Oh, pretty baby ♪
♪ Don't bring me down, I pray ♪
♪ Now that I've found you, stay ♪
♪ And let me love you, baby ♪
♪ Let me love you ♪
It was marvelous. Did you see it?
You had two left feet.
Good morning,
Your Royal Highness.
Thank you.
A phone call
from Mrs. Parker Bowles.
Would you like to return it?
No.
No, I wouldn't.
Thank you, Edward. That will be all.
- You had fun together at the ball.
- We did.
I could've danced all night.
So, has that been the highlight?
Well, that's hard to say. Um…
We greatly enjoyed seeing Sydney Harbor,
and Charles tried bodysurfing
on Bondi Beach.
But, um, I suppose the greatest highlight
has been, well…
Well, meeting all of you,
the people of Australia.
You've made us feel so welcome,
so at home.
Well, perhaps
because you've been so refreshing.
You're not what we expect from royalty.
That's because
I don't think of myself as royalty.
No. First and foremost,
I'm a wife and a mother.
That's what's most important to me.
She really is a wonderful mother.
And how's William getting along?
He's having a magical time here.
So, he likes Australia?
Well, let's put it like this.
His favorite cuddly toy
used to be a whale.
But since coming here,
it's been firmly supplanted by a koala.
More than 10,000 people were waiting
to catch sight of the prince and princess.
The princess was overwhelmed
with posies and small gifts from…
Prime Minister's Office.
No, he's very busy at the moment
and cannot comment.
Mr. Hawke will not be answering
any questions about this at present.
- Hello!
- Look up, Diana!
- This way!
- Up here!
Diana!
- There she is!
- I love you!
Look over there.
She's just there.
Lady Di!
Why don't I take one of you?
That's more interesting.
There you go. Ready? Smile.
Cheese!
Okay!
Smile, ma'am, this way.
- Charles!
- Hello!
- She's gorgeous. You're lucky to have her.
- Thank you.
- What do you think of Brisbane?
- Glorious.
- Diana, come back to Brisbane again soon.
- Oh, like a boomerang. Just watch me.
Oh, please do.
- I love your dress.
- I like yours!
- Would you like to swap?
- Oh, I wish! You're so beautiful.
- Diana!
- Oh, look at your uniforms.
They're so sweet.
Diana!
Stay back, please.
Finally,
the prince and princess arrived,
and pandemonium broke loose.
There's a problem no one foresaw.
Huge crowds wherever they go.
Some even bigger, I'm told,
than you got, back in the 18th century,
or whenever you went.
1954.
And I very much doubt it.
Along with raves in all the newspapers
for Diana's beauty.
And charm.
And, most of all, her motherhood.
I heard she'd been hysterical,
clinging to the poor baby
like a life raft.
Evidently, that clinging is
what the Australians have responded to.
What a natural mother she is.
How physical.
And caring.
Why is all this a problem?
You and I both know
how much Charles craves reassurance,
and attention, and praise.
This tour of Australia and New Zealand
was supposed to be his grand debut,
his moment in the sun as future king.
Just saying.
But there was little doubt
who most people really wanted to see.
Hello. Thank you.
Hello. Thanks for coming.
Thank you. Hello, everyone.
Where's Princess Di?
She's busy working, I'm afraid.
You'll have to put up with me.
Aww…
Oh, we only really came
to see Lady Di.
Will you go for a swim, ma'am?
I don't think so.
Which one do you fancy
giving you the kiss of life?
Let's hope it doesn't come to that!
How about it, boys? Any volunteers?
- I think you've got some admirers.
- Can we get you guys in closer?
- No worries.
- Just remember, no touching, no looking.
Who? Me or them?
Picked up nicely there
by His Royal Highness, and off it goes.
Number five is trying to cut him off.
Prince Charles here, the Prince of Wales,
playing on a borrowed pony called Apollo.
We want Di!
A strong hit from number two there.
And here comes Prince Charles,
swooping from his position at the back.
Is everybody ready?
- We want Di!
- Get set. Go!
Taking a shot…
All right, Charles?
Are those for me?
That is so kind of you. Thank you.
- Are you a real princess?
- Why don't you poke me and find out?
Did that work?
As they move
from Queensland to Tasmania,
the royal tour is
going from strength to strength.
And whilst it's been a great
personal victory for Prince Charles,
no one can deny
it's the Princess of Wales
who's truly captured
the heart of a nation.
Well, she's not stuffy
like the rest of the royals.
You get a sense
of her being a real person.
- Yes.
- You've gotta love her, haven't you?
Do you love Charles
as much as you love Diana?
Yeah. She loves him.
He must have something!
What do you think
of the princess?
- She's amazing.
- She's just like us.
Do you think
you could have a cup of tea with her?
Absolutely. She's really down to earth.
That's why I love her.
- Lady Diana, over here!
- Your Royal Highness, this way, please!
Lovely to meet you.
- Hello. Lovely to meet you.
- Good evening, Mr. Premier.
Lovely to see you again. Mrs. Gray.
Thank you.
Diana, this way, please!
It's a great pleasure
to be able to come to Tasmania
to receive such an enthusiastic
and heartwarming welcome.
The last time I was here
was two years ago, in 1981,
shortly before we were married,
and at that time,
everybody was saying, "Good luck,"
and, "Hope everything goes well,"
and, "How lucky you are
to be engaged to such a lovely lady."
And, my goodness,
I am lucky enough to be married to her.
That's the thing about ladies.
You never quite know what they get up to
when your back's turned.
It's the final straw. Pulling faces,
horsing around
while I'm trying to do my job.
I was blushing!
Blushing at your compliments.
People were laughing at me,
laughing in my face,
at the end of a week in which
half of Australia's also been booing me!
I don't deserve this.
This is supposed to be my tour.
My tour as Prince of Wales
to shore up a key country
in the Commonwealth
at a very delicate moment politically.
- And thanks to you...
- People have shown up!
Thanks to me, people are interested!
No! Thanks to you,
people are laughing in my face!
Booing the heir to the throne,
booing the Crown.
Oh, come on! Oh, don't do this.
Please!
Open the door.
Charles?
We still have ten days in New Zealand
to get through.
- Welcome, Your Royal Highness.
- Prime Minister.
Given our different perspectives,
our different views
on the… appropriate governance
of this nation,
I never thought I'd find myself
commiserating with you, but…
Let's face it.
She's made us both look like chumps.
I… don't understand.
Terra nullius.
That's what your ancestor
King George III called us
when the Brits first arrived.
"Nobody's country."
Well,
by God,
we were somebody's country then,
and… we're our own country now.
When you arrived, I thought…
your visit might inspire Australia
to finally…
throw off the shackles
and stand on her own two feet,
and… no offense,
but if it'd just been you, you know,
I might've got my wishes!
But then, you know…
she comes along.
The perfect wife, the perfect princess,
and the whole place goes nuts.
It's the power of fairy tales.
That superstar may have just set back
the cause of republicanism in Australia
for the foreseeable future.
- Lady Di!
- Love you!
Bye, Princess Diana!
Sir.
Highgrove.
Kensington Palace.
It's the Princess of Wales.
I was hoping the Queen might see me.
Welcome back.
Thank you, Mama.
- You said I should always call you that.
- Of course.
Please.
- Thank you, Nigel.
- Ma'am.
I've come because…
Well, I don't know who to turn to anymore.
I'm struggling.
Struggling?
My dear, you've just had a triumph.
I don't consider it a triumph
if at the end of it,
my husband and I are wretchedly unhappy.
Look at these pictures of you both
everywhere.
Are you really telling me
that's unhappiness?
Well, not in that moment, no.
In that moment, it's… perfect happiness.
But then behind closed doors,
it's a different story.
He resents me,
resents the attention I get.
And why is that?
I don't know.
I was hoping you could tell me.
He's your son.
Because I've been a terrible mother?
Is that what you've come here to tell me?
- No.
- The Duke of Edinburgh a terrible father?
- Of course not.
- I struggle to understand Charles too.
I think that's no secret.
But us sitting here
sticking knives into him
isn't helpful either.
Is it also possible there is a part of you
that is enjoying your own success
too much?
What is "too much"?
A smile? A moment's happiness?
Overstepping the mark is too much.
I think we do all know when
we've played to the gallery excessively.
We know.
All right.
Yes.
It does feel good sometimes to be cheered.
It can be a comfort.
Since I've joined this family,
it's not been easy.
I've been given no help, no support,
just thrown in the deep end,
and I think that people out there
can sense that I've suffered,
that I'm undervalued, ignored...
I think it's a mistake to assume
that people feel sympathy for us at all.
And I think
it's a mistake to assume they don't.
You've seen how the crowds responded to me
in Australia, here too.
- Instead of resenting me for it...
- I assure you, no one resents you.
Charles resents me.
Anne resents me. And is it possible
that you resent me too?
All I want is to play for the team.
You're the Princess of Wales.
- So of course you're part of the team.
- Then show me.
This whole thing,
it starts and stops with you.
You're the captain of the team.
If you show me love,
approval, and acceptance,
everyone else will follow.
I think
we've gone as far as we can for now.
- We can continue another time.
- Don't dismiss me, please.
Don't push me away.
- What?
- Mama…
That's all I want.
It's all any of us want from you.
Is it too much to ask?
A hug?
Yes.
What kind of hug?
A tight, rather desperate hug.
- I feel sick.
- Yes.
But is it possible that she has a point?
We are rather a tough bunch
in this family.
We don't give out much praise
or love or thanks.
Mmm.
Perhaps Diana is best placed to...
- Hug everyone else too.
- To connect with the modern world.
And isn't that how the Crown survives
and stays relevant?
By changing with the times.
Mmm.
Diana…
…is an immature little girl
who, in time, will give up her struggles,
give up her fight, and bend,
as Philip did.
As they all do.
And when she bends, she will fit.
And if she doesn't bend, what then?
She will break.
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off of you ♪
♪ You'd be like Heaven to touch ♪
♪ I wanna hold you so much ♪
♪ At long last, love has arrived ♪
♪ And I thank God I'm alive ♪
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off of you ♪
♪ I love you, baby ♪
♪ And if it's quite alright
I need you, baby ♪
♪ To warm a lonely night ♪
♪ I love you, baby ♪
♪ Trust in me when I say ♪
♪ Oh, pretty baby ♪
♪ Don't bring me down, I pray
Oh, pretty baby ♪
♪ Now that I've found you, stay ♪
♪ And let me love you, baby ♪
♪ Let me love you ♪