…of his party.
Mr. Heseltine says Britain
should reach for the levers of power
if only to prevent
others pulling them first.
One dead in an Ulster gun battle
between soldiers and terrorists.
Police make arrests over ballot rigging
in the transport union.
Confusion over plastic clingfilm…
Thank you, dear.
…government's cancer warning.
And animals to the slaughter.
How the RSPCA hopes
to stop live animal exports.
Michael Heseltine was speaking
to a conference in Hamburg.
Mr. Heseltine is now
on his way back to London
to be in the Commons this afternoon.
There, Sir Geoffrey Howe
is expected to spell out in detail
the reasons for his resignation.
Is there anything
Sir Geoffrey is likely to say
that could influence Mr. Heseltine
on whether to throw his hat in the ring?
Well,
Sir Geoffrey is an extremely cautious man.
I suspect
that his speech will be carefully written,
and I just wonder
whether it will be sufficiently in code
not really to damage the prime minister.
Sir Geoffrey has very deep personal
and ideological differences
with the prime minister.
I think he will spell them out,
but whether he will spell them out
in clear, set terms
that amount to an assault
on her leadership,
I think we have to wait and see for that.
I remind the House
that a resignation statement
is heard in silence
and without interruption.
Sir Geoffrey Howe.
Hear, hear.
Mr. Speaker, sir,
"I find, to my astonishment,
that a quarter of a century has passed
since I last spoke
from one of these backbenches."
"Mr. Speaker, I believe
that both the chancellor and the governor
are cricketing enthusiasts."
"So I hope that there is
no monopoly of cricketing metaphors."
"Increasingly,
those of us close to the prime minister
feel like opening batsmen
being sent to the crease,
only to find
the moment the first balls are bowled
that our bats have been broken
before the game by the team captain."
Order!
Order.
"The point… The point, Mr. Speaker,
was perhaps more sharply put
by a British businessman,
trading in Brussels and elsewhere,
who wrote to me last week."
'People throughout Europe, ' he said,
'see our prime minister's finger-wagging
and hear her passionate 'No, no, no'
much more clearly than the content
of the carefully worded formal texts.'"
"'It is too easy, ' he went on,
'for them to believe
that we all share her attitudes.'"
"'For why else, ' he asked,
'has she been our prime minister
for so long?'"
"'This is, '
my correspondent concluded,
'a desperately serious situation
for our country.'"
And sadly, Mr. Speaker, I have to agree.
"The conflict of loyalty,
of loyalty to my right honorable friend
the prime minister,
and, after all, in two decades together,
that instinct of loyalty
is still very real…
and of loyalty to what I perceive to be
the true interests of the nation,
that conflict of loyalty
has become all too great."
"I no longer believe it possible
to resolve that conflict
from within this government."
"That is why I have resigned."
"In doing so,
I have done what I believe to be right
for my party and my country."
"The time has come for others
to consider their own response
to the tragic conflict of loyalties
with which I have myself wrestled…
for perhaps too long."
Hear, hear.
Lilibet?
- Uh, the Queen?
- In the drawing room, Your Royal Highness.
Right.
She has resumed
her affair with Major Hewitt
with flagrant disregard for the agreement
we made in our meeting with you.
A meeting in which it is now clear
she brazenly lied to your face.
So I hope you agree
it leaves me no option
but to start a formal separation.
Oh, Charles!
I'm wretchedly unhappy,
yet there is someone else out there
who would make me perfectly happy.
- Quick, switch on the television.
- Why?
It's the Ides of March.
It's Julius Caesar,
or should I say Julia Caesar?
We're in the middle
of an important conversation.
- Shh.
- …her style of government.
He says her nightmare image of Europe
risks the future of the nation.
Can Sir Geoffrey's peroration,
where he said the time has come
for others to consider their response,
be read in any other way
than a clear invitation to open a contest
for the leadership?
That is one of the implications.
Some people would go further than that.
They would say he is urging people
to vote against Mrs. Thatcher…
…Thatcher is facing
the most serious threat
to her 11 years in power…
…first time in 15 years…
Geoffrey Howe,
Mrs. Thatcher's longest-serving colleague
throughout her years in power,
turned on her in the Commons today
and accused her
of risking the nation's future.
He was explaining for the first time
why he resigned as deputy prime minister
12 days ago.
…refusal to keep in step
with the European community.
…a coded diplomatic speech.
Instead,
years of resentment and frustration
were compressed
into a bitter attack on Mrs. Thatcher
and her attitude to Europe.
He called on Conservative MPs
to consider what he described
as their conflict of loyalties…
Howe delivered
a stinging indictment…
There is great bitterness
on the prime minister's side,
and they hope there will be some reaction
in her favor. It's down to Conservative…
Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher
faces a challenge
that could cost her her job.
…MPs, ministers, and peers
are still trying to assess
what one described
as an incitement to mutiny
and another said was an act of treachery.
William!
Run!
Oh, Ivo's got it! Ivo's got it!
Go, Ivo! Go, Ivo!
- Ivo!
- Move it!
Yes, well done!
Well done, Ivo!
Oh, he's brilliant, isn't he? Yes!
Did you see that? Yes!
Well done, boys!
Bye, my darling.
Not long until the holidays.
Hmm?
Love you.
- Well done today.
- Thank you.
And we'll see you at Christmas.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Is that it?
We're not going to talk again, ever?
Since every time we do talk,
it ends in an argument,
I'd say silence was preferable.
What's this I hear
about a trip to New York?
Oh, don't look so surprised.
The government requested it.
Everyone knows I'm going.
No one knew you were going on your own.
What an ugly, avaricious piece
of self-advancement that is.
I'd sooner be doing it
with my husband by my side.
Doing what?
The past few months, you've barely been
in a fit state psychologically
to go to the hairdresser,
much less represent the Crown.
Although I gather you still found time
to see… certain other people.
I think
this conversation's gone as far as it can.
You were the one who insisted on talking.
I always said silence was preferable.
- Mrs. Thatcher?
- Prime Minister?
One crisis rising above
all the others today, Your Majesty.
Yes.
An inconvenience
one would dearly like to avoid,
given the significant challenges
this country already faces.
The crisis in the Gulf.
Oh, that crisis?
Well, that is
the predominant challenge facing us.
I thought you might be
referring to matters closer to home.
There are one or two
minor domestic matters,
some changes
to the fishing license conditions,
but nothing I would want
to waste your valuable time with.
You don't think
we should briefly discuss… that speech?
Which speech?
The resignation speech
made by Sir Geoffrey Howe
that's caused such a stir.
Why would we want to discuss that?
Because a great deal of fuss
is being made of it.
Oh, poor Geoffrey.
I'd offered him
the position of deputy prime minister,
and he seems to have taken it
rather the wrong way.
In the newspapers, his speech is seen
as a direct challenge to your authority.
I think that all depends
on which newspapers you're reading.
Not just newspapers. Television too.
Or watching.
And as sovereign, I must ask you…
do you expect a leadership challenge?
- The prime minister came to see me today.
- Ah, yes.
To discuss
the crisis in the Gulf.
What?
Not the fact
that she'd just been knifed in the back
by one of her longest-standing allies?
No, I asked her about that.
- Did you really?
- Yes.
You're brave.
What did she say?
She said the situation was unfortunate…
…but it amounts to little more
than petty rivalries and resentments…
…played out
at the level of the schoolyard.
I shall see them off in no time.
And, really,
we should not dignify an insignificant…
…internal party squabble
with any more of our precious time.
Well…
Sir Geoffrey's attack makes this,
the criticism of Mrs. Thatcher,
much more lethal.
I think she's in deep trouble,
not that she will be beaten
in the first ballot by Michael Heseltine,
but more probably that
there will be enough votes against her
and enough abstentions
to damage her seriously.
One person said to me
that he thought it possible,
if she were badly enough damaged,
that members of the Cabinet
would go to the chief whip
and say that
she ought to consider her future.
It's premature to say that yet,
but undoubtedly
there's a rather stronger tide
running against Mrs. Thatcher tonight
than there has ever been before.
Powell.
Yes.
Yeah.
I see.
Thank you.
How many?
- We're four short.
- Oh.
Not enough to stop it
going to a second ballot.
Oh, it's betrayal of the very worst kind.
They owe their political lives to me.
- It's despicable.
- Oh, those little men!
And you want me
to get on my knees to them?
Never.
Have them brought in to me.
One by one.
First item on the agenda
is Her Royal Highness's forthcoming…
solo visit to New York.
Looking at the itinerary,
our concern would be
that it seems to be challenging.
Several appointments each day.
- It's just four days, Edward.
- In multiple locations.
We all know the toll
a schedule of engagements can take,
and I'm sure no one here would wish to see
the Princess of Wales overstretched.
Certainly not at a risk to her own health.
The Princess of Wales's health
is exemplary.
Mental health.
Not to mention the amount of time
she'd be separated from her children
and the distress that might cause her.
The Princess of Wales
is well aware of what's required of her
and is very much
looking forward to the trip.
I have only one question.
Will you support me?
Of course.
You will always have
my unconditional support.
I am with you.
You can always count on me.
The problem is…
…the numbers are against you…
…and your inability
to unite the party behind you…
…over Europe…
…over the economy…
…over taxation…
Perhaps if your methods
were less confrontational…
…and if you'd consulted with Cabinet
rather than ruling by decree…
…your rejection
of core Conservative values,
of moderation…
…compassion…
…and your total disregard
for the center ground…
…leaves you vulnerable.
Exposed. Isolated.
I shall always defend you, Margaret.
Always.
But…
…as your friend…
…as an ally…
…I think I speak for the majority
when I say…
…the time might have come
for some new blood.
…and that it would be
in everyone's best interests
if you were to… stand down.
Bastards.
The bloody lot of them.
Murderers.
So…
…is that it?
Is that the end?
No.
I still have one card to play.
Britain will send more troops to the Gulf.
The defence secretary Tom King
has said Britain…
President Bush called
to tell me he thought it barbaric.
Chancellor Kohl said it was inhumane.
Mikhail Gorbachev reminded me
that ten years ago,
it was Britain
holding democratic elections
whilst Russia staged cabinet coups.
Now it's the other way round.
What they all agree on
is that getting rid of me
is an act of national self-harm,
which is why I've come to you, ma'am,
that together we may act
in the national self-interest.
How might I help?
By dissolving Parliament.
What?
We are on the brink of war.
What kind of signal
does that give to our enemies,
to Saddam,
if we were to change leadership now?
It would make us look
hopelessly weak and divided.
I agree it's not ideal.
Have you consulted Cabinet on this matter?
I have not, ma'am.
Surely that would be
the normal course of action?
With all due respect,
the decision to dissolve Parliament
is in the gift
of the prime minister alone.
It is entirely within my power
to do this if I see fit.
You are correct.
Technically,
it is within your power to request this.
But we must all ask ourselves
when to exercise those things
that are within our power and when not to.
Your first instinct as a person,
I think, is often to act.
To exercise power.
Well,
that is what people want in a leader.
To show conviction and strength.
To lead.
I'm merely asking the question.
Whether it is correct to exercise a power
simply because it is yours to use.
Power is nothing without authority.
And at this moment,
your Cabinet is against you.
Your party is against you.
And if the polls are to be believed,
if you were
to call a general election today,
you would not win.
Which suggests the country is against you.
Perhaps the time has come
for you to try doing nothing for once.
The difference is…
you have power…
in doing nothing.
I…
will have nothing.
You will have your dignity.
There is no dignity in the wilderness.
Then might I suggest
you don't think of it as that.
Think of it as an opportunity
to pursue other passions.
I have other loves.
My husband, my children…
But this job is my only true passion.
And to have it taken from me…
stolen from me so cruelly…
What hurts the most
is that we had come so far.
And now to have
the opportunity to finish the job
snatched away at the very last…
I'm in hell!
And he just hates me.
And wants me to fail.
He tells everyone I'm mad.
They treat me like I'm mad.
And I'm starting to feel mad.
Why did I agree to this trip?
I'm going to fall flat on my face.
All right?
I think so.
Lovely to meet you. Hello.
Lovely to meet you.
Princess Diana, one quick…
Over here, please, Lady Di!
I love you, Diana!
Diana! Diana!
Thank you so much.
That's so kind. Thank you.
- Your Royal Highness.
- Hello.
We're so thrilled to have you with us.
This is Linda Correa.
Lovely to meet you, miss.
They told us there was a waiting list
for public housing…
A modest hospital
on the wrong side of Harlem
very few American politicians
have ever even thought to visit,
but today this is the final stop
on Princess Diana's
whirlwind tour of New York.
Your Royal Highness.
We established
the pediatric AIDS unit two years ago
to deal with the rising problem
of infants suffering with the disease.
Hello.
Many of the children had been abandoned
or have parents who are addicts
or sick with the virus.
They desperately need foster parents,
but people are too afraid to take them.
Why?
Because of the stigma.
The fear of the disease.
Chants of
"We want the princess" were heard
in New York's Harlem neighborhood today.
A triumphant end to a trip
which has seen the princess fly solo
for the first time,
hitting new heights
without her husband, Prince Charles.
We love her. She's beautiful. She's warm.
She's perfect. They don't want her there,
we would love to have her here.
The way she hugged that boy
in the hospital nearly broke my heart.
Prince Charles is a lucky man.
Princess Di, thank you
for bringing love and vitality
to the Lower East Side!
She knows how to make people feel good,
and that is a God-given talent.
Am I right?
Yeah!
If you care about me as much
as you say you do, sir, you will let go
of these ideas
of breaking it off with Diana.
Why?
Don't you want us to be free, to…
live our life in the open?
I do.
But I want to be humiliated
and attacked even less.
That's what'll happen if you put me
in a popularity contest against her.
I will lose.
- Oh…
- I'm an old woman.
I'm a married woman.
Nowhere near as pretty,
nowhere near as radiant.
Someone who looks like me
has no place in a fairy tale.
That's all people want, is a fairy tale.
If they knew the truth
about our feelings for one another,
they'd have their fairy tale.
No!
To be the protagonist of a fairy tale,
you must first be wronged.
A victim.
Which, if we were to become public,
we would make her.
In the narrative laws
of fairy tales versus reality…
the fairy tale always prevails.
She will… always defeat me
in the court of public opinion.
What is all this, my darling?
What's got into you today?
It's reality, sir.
She's the Princess of Wales.
She's a future queen,
the mother to a future king.
- And I'm just...
- My one… true love.
A mistress.
Mistress to the Prince of Wales, just like
my great-grandmother Alice Keppel
was the mistress to the Prince of Wales,
your great-great-grandfather.
And he loved her till the end.
Leave this with me.
Number 10 is a house
and a home as well as an office,
and as Margaret Thatcher left it
after so long,
there was applause to be heard,
and, I'm told, a tear or two shed
among the unseen staff.
Mrs. Thatcher's own voice
had an emotional edge to it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are leaving Downing Street
for the last time
after 11 and a half wonderful years.
It was the end of an era
dominated by this woman
whose name has become a political byword.
Eleven years of Thatcherism.
She recovered quickly for one last wave.
But then
the Iron Lady's composure almost broke.
Watch her face as she reaches her car.
Friends say that she is deeply shocked
by the seeming injustice of it all.
Three election victories
and a clear, though insufficient,
majority in the first ballot
rewarded, as she sees it, with the sack.
Mrs. Thatcher, of course,
has a new home now in Dulwich…
Martin? Could you ask the prime...
Could you ask Mrs. Thatcher
to come and see me?
When I ascended the throne…
I was just a girl.
Twenty-five years old.
And I was surrounded
by stuffy, rather patronizing
gray-haired men everywhere
telling me what to do.
And I wanted to say…
the way you dealt with all your stuffy,
rather patronizing gray-haired men
throughout your time in office
and saw them all off…
Well, they've had their revenge now.
I was shocked by the way
in which you were forced to leave office.
And I wanted to offer my sympathy.
Not just as Queen to prime minister…
but woman to woman.
Throughout the time we worked together,
people tended to focus
on our many differences.
Which was lazy and misleading, I think.
And overlooked the many things
we do have in common.
Our generation.
Our Christianity.
Our work ethic.
Our sense of duty.
But above all…
our devotion to this country
that we both love.
So with that in mind…
The Order of Merit…
is not awarded by some faceless committee.
It comes at the personal discretion
of the sovereign
and is in recognition
of exceptionally meritorious service.
It is limited to just 24 recipients,
no matter their background.
You could be the daughter of a duke.
Or a greengrocer.
What matters… is your accomplishments.
And nobody can deny…
that this is a very different country now
to the one inherited
by our first woman prime minister.
Now, it's normally handed over in the box.
But if you would allow me…
Congratulations.
It's kind of you to come.
Why would you say that?
I think
even my sternest critics would concede
that my first solo trip
has not been a disaster,
that I didn't fall
totally flat on my face.
So I can only imagine, hope,
that you've come here to apologize,
to eat your words,
and congratulate me.
Your… capacity for self-delusion…
never ceases to amaze me.
We're all glad
you're back where you belong
without too much damage done.
You have two sons that need you.
Our sons have easily survived
me being away four days.
I'm not sure
one can say the same for the rest of us.
The exquisite selfishness of your motives
and the…
the calculated vulgarity of the antics…
knowing full well
the headlines they would get.
"Antics"?
Grandstanding like that.
You think we couldn't do that too?
Theatrically hug the wretched
and the dispossessed
and cover ourselves in glory
on the front pages?
I doubt it.
You barely find it in yourselves
to hug your own.
I hug who I want to.
I hug who I love.
Particularly when they are affected
by the selfishness of others
and need cheering up.
- Who are you referring to?
- Camilla.
Why would I care about her?
Because I care about her!
Morning, noon, and night,
I care about her!
And you hurt her.
And if you hurt her…
you hurt me.
Camilla is who I want.
That is where my loyalties lie.
- That is who my priority is.
- Not the mother of your children?
- Don't bring the boys into this.
- All right. Not the woman you married!
I refuse to be blamed any longer
for this grotesque misalliance!
I wash my hands of it!
If you have a complaint…
about…
not being loved…
or appreciated in this marriage…
I suggest you take it up
with the people who arranged it.
- ♪ I really can't stay ♪
- ♪ But, baby, it's cold outside ♪
- ♪ I've got to go away ♪
- ♪ This evening has been ♪
- ♪ Been hoping that you'd drop in ♪
♪ So very nice ♪
♪ I'll hold your hands
They're just like ice ♪
- ♪ My mother will start to worry ♪
- ♪ Beautiful, what's your hurry? ♪
- ♪ And father will be pacing the floor ♪
- ♪ Listen to the fireplace roar ♪
- ♪ So really I'd better scurry ♪
- ♪Beautiful, please don't hurry ♪
- ♪ Well, maybe just a half a drink more ♪
- ♪ Put some records on while I pour ♪
- ♪ The neighbors might think ♪
- ♪ But, baby, it's bad out there ♪
- ♪ Say, what's in this drink? ♪
- ♪ No cabs to be had out there ♪
- ♪ I wish I knew how ♪
- ♪ Your eyes are like starlight now ♪
♪ To break the spell ♪
♪ I'll take your hat
Your hair looks swell ♪
- ♪ I ought to say no, no, no, sir ♪
- ♪ Mind if I move in closer ♪
- ♪ At least I'm gonna say that I tried ♪
- ♪ What's the sense of hurting my pride? ♪
- ♪ I really can't stay ♪
- ♪ Oh, baby, don't hold out, baby ♪
♪ Ah, but it's cold outside… ♪
Sir…
♪ But, baby, it's cold outside ♪
- ♪ The answer is no ♪
- ♪ But, baby, it's cold outside ♪
- ♪ This welcome has been ♪
- ♪ How lucky that you dropped in ♪
♪ So nice and warm ♪
♪ Look out the window at that storm ♪
- ♪ My sister will be suspicious ♪
- ♪ Gosh, your lips look delicious ♪
♪ My brother will be there at the door ♪
- ♪ Waves upon a tropical shore ♪
- ♪ My maiden aunt's mind is vicious ♪
♪ Gosh, your lips are delicious… ♪
He is learning. He is.
He's doing much better.
She tells jokes,
but she starts with the punchline,
which sounds funnier than the joke.
There you are.
Mama.
Well, I'm sure no one told you,
but I made a request through my office
for us to find a moment
to speak together, in private.
I hope you're not wanting to talk here.
No, not here.
Or now. The dogs need feeding.
- The dogs.
- Yes, the dogs.
We'll have to find another time.
Who's hungry?
Are you all hungry?
Who'll tell me about their day?
Hello! Have you had a lovely day?
Have you had fun?
- What are you doing here?
- I hope you don't mind.
- I thought we might find a moment alone.
- Honestly, both of you!
Both of us?
You and your wife
ambushing me everywhere I go
with anxious looks, wanting to talk.
I do want to talk, Mummy.
We need to talk.
Fine. Let's talk.
Might I request
we do it like privy counsellors?
On our feet to keep it brief.
It's the marriage.
I had a horrible idea
we were going in this direction.
I have done my best.
My very best, and I am suffering!
No, you are not suffering. We're suffering
having to put up with this!
Let me make something clear.
When people look at you and Diana,
they see two privileged young people
who, through good fortune,
ended up with everything
one could dream of in life.
No one, not a single breathing,
living soul anywhere,
sees cause for suffering.
- They would if they knew.
- Knew what?
They know that you betray your wife
and make no attempt to hide it.
They know that thanks to you,
she has psychological problems
and eats or doesn't eat
or whatever it is she does or doesn't do.
They know you're a spoiled, immature man,
endlessly complaining unnecessarily,
married to a spoiled, immature woman,
endlessly complaining unnecessarily.
And we are all heartily sick of it.
All anyone wants is for the pair of you
to pull yourselves together,
stop making spectacles of yourselves,
and make this marriage
and your enormously privileged
positions in life work.
And if I want to separate?
You will not separate or divorce
or let the side down in any way.
- And if one day you expect to be king...
- I do.
Then might I suggest
you start to behave like one.
- Rabbit, right in the head.
- No!
Have you seen Diana?
Come.
Hello?
Ah.
Oh, please, no.
I, uh, I came to see if you're all right.
Do you know, I… I don't think
I've ever seen inside this room.
We can be a rough bunch in this family.
And I'm sure, on occasion,
to a sensitive creature like you,
it must feel like…
Well, let me ask. What does it feel like?
A cold, frozen tundra.
Right.
Like that, then.
An icy, dark,
loveless cave…
with no light…
no hope… anywhere.
Not even the faintest crack.
I see.
He will come around.
He will.
Eventually.
When he realizes that…
he can never have the other one.
Would it help you to realize
we all think he's quite mad?
That might have reassured me once.
But I worry we're past that point now.
Sir.
And if he…
If this family can't give me the love
and security that I feel I deserve,
then I believe I have no option
but to break away, officially…
and find it myself.
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Why not?
Let's just say
I can't see it ending well for you.
I hope that isn't a threat, sir.
No, not now. Out!
Although we are both outsiders
who married in,
you and I are quite different.
Yes.
I can see that now.
You're right to call me an outsider.
I was an outsider the day that I met the…
the 13-year-old princess
who would one day become my wife.
And after all these years…
I still am.
We all are.
Everyone…
in this system…
is a lost…
lonely…
irrelevant outsider…
apart from the one person,
the only person,
that matters.
She is the oxygen we all breathe.
The essence of all our duty.
Your problem, if I may say…
is you seem to be confused
about who that person is.
Come!
Just to say, Your Royal Highnesses,
the photographer is ready.
Thank you.
Everyone,
we're going to do the photograph.
Don't you think the Queen
would be best suited in the middle?
Charles is pushing in.
You stay outside.
No squabbling, please.
Quiet. Quiet.
Ah, yes.
The merriest of Christmas smiles!
Yes.
Three, two, one…
Done. Did anyone blink?