- EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU LESLIE KNOPE?
- YES.
- WE ARE PART OF A GROUP
THAT TRIES TO IDENTIFY
POTENTIAL CANDIDATES
FOR POLITICAL OFFICE
HERE IN TOWN.
ARE YOU THEORETICALLY INTERESTED
IN RUNNING FOR OFFICE?
- ABSO-TOOT-LY I AM.
VERY SORRY THAT I JUST USED
THAT WORD.
- BEFORE WE GO ANY FURTHER,
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME
IS THERE A SCANDAL OUT THERE?
IS THERE ANYTHING AT ALL YOU
NEED TO TELL US ABOUT YOUR LIFE?
- NOPE.
- WHO WERE THE SUITS?
- THEY WANT ME TO RUN
FOR OFFICE.
- OH, MY GOD!
LESLIE, YEA!
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
YEA.
- YEA!
- WAIT, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN
ABOUT YOU AND BEN?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK
IT'S GONNA BE REALLY BAD.
- UH-OH. YOU JUST WANNA GO BACK
TO SAYING "YEA"?
- YES, PLEASE.
- OKAY, YEA.
- YEA. YEA.
- KNOPE, FOLLOW ME.
- JUST ONE SECOND.
- NOW!
- RON, HEY!
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
RON! RON, RON, RON, RON, RON!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- MY EX-WIFE TAMMY IS BACK.
- YEAH, I SAW HER
IN THE COURTYARD.
- NO, MY OTHER EX-WIFE TAMMY.
TAMMY ONE.
I HAVE ACCRUED 228
PERSONAL DAYS.
STARTING RIGHT NOW,
I'M USING ALL OF THEM.
[grunt]
WHILE I'M GONE,
YOU'RE IN CHARGE.
- AH!
[metal clanging]
- ALSO, I KEEP A SIZABLE SUPPLY
OF GROUND CHUCK IN MY DESK.
REMOVE IT OR IT WILL BEGIN
TO SMELL.
GODSPEED.
- HI, RON.
- MOVE!
- WHOA!
AH, GEEZ.
[triumphant music]
*
- WARNING! HIGH LEVELS
OF SWAGGER COMING THROUGH.
TOMMY HAVERFORD BACK
IN THE PARKS DEPARTMENT.
ENTERTAINMENT720 HOCKEY JERSEY,
ANYBODY?
BRANDED MOUSE PAD?
ENTERTAINMENT720 IS JUST
A LITTLE MULTI-NATIONAL
ENTERTAINMENT COMPANY
THAT I STARTED WITH MY BOY
JEAN-RALPHIO.
WHAT EXACTLY DO WE DO?
LET'S JUST SAY IT'S TOO HARD
TO EXPLAIN.
DONNA, YOU LOOK AMAZING.
HOW ARE THE KIDS?
- I DON'T HAVE KIDS.
- WOW.
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN?
- THREE WEEKS.
- [sigh]
- SO DID YOU GET A CHANCE
TO LOOK
AT MY SAMPLE POSITION PAPERS?
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT MY STANCE
ON EGYPTIAN DEBT RELIEF?
- UH, WELL, IT PROBABLY WON'T
COME UP
IN A LOCAL CITY COUNCIL
ELECTION.
BUT YOUR THOROUGHNESS,
AS ALWAYS, IS IMPRESSIVE.
- THANK YOU.
- NOW, WE HAVE THREE MONTHS.
I THINK WE SHOULD START
TALKING STRATEGY.
- MY STRATEGY IS TO WIN.
I'VE BEEN DREAMING ABOUT RUNNING
FOR PUBLIC OFFICE MY WHOLE LIFE.
WHILE OTHER GIRLS WERE PLAYING
WITH BARBIES,
I WAS PLAYING WITH A
GERALDINE FERRARO ACTION FIGURE
THAT I MADE MYSELF FROM
A PICTURE OF HER THAT I GLUED
ONTO A POPSICLE STICK.
- SEE YOU NEXT WEEK?
- OKAY, I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO IT.
HEY! WHAT--
- WHO WAS THAT?
- UH...
LADY--JUST LADIES.
MEETING FOR THE LADIES'
YACHT CLUB.
ANCHORS AWAY, LADIES.
- WHAT?
- JUST DON'T--
- LADIES' YACHT CLUB?
- I CANNOT BELIEVE YOU HAVEN'T
TOLD HIM YET.
- AFTER I TELL HIM,
I'M RUNNING FOR OFFICE,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO BREAK UP.
- WHY CAN'T YOU JUST KEEP
SNEAKING AROUND?
- ANN, YOU BEAUTIFUL, NAIVE,
SOPHISTICATED, NEWBORN BABY.
- WHAT?
- BEFORE, IF PEOPLE FOUND OUT,
WE WOULD MAYBE LOSE OUR JOBS.
NOW, IF PEOPLE FIND OUT,
IT'S GONNA BE A MAJOR SCANDAL.
MY CAMPAIGN WILL BE OVER
BEFORE IT BEGINS.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- I HAVE A PLAN.
AND IT'S REALLY GOOD.
I'M GONNA POSTPONE TELLING HIM
UNTIL YOU FIGURE OUT
WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO.
SO GET CRACKIN'.
- HOW IS THIS ON ME?
[cell phone chimes]
- FINE! I'LL DO IT.
GOD, WHO KEEPS EMAILING ME?
A PENIS.
- WHAT?
[cell phone chimes]
OH, MY GOD.
OH--
IT'S EMAILING ME TOO.
- WHOEVER THIS IS SENT IT
TO EVERY WOMAN
IN THE ENTIRE GOVERNMENT.
- OH, MY GOD.
HE'S GONNA BE SO EMBARRASSED.
I MEAN, THAT'S A CRAZY ACCIDENT.
- NO, ANDY, HE DID IT
ON PURPOSE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT? RESPECT.
THAT'S A BALLER MOVE.
PUN INTENDED.
- EXCUSE ME.
- CHRIS, JERRY'S MAKING US LOOK
AT DIRTY PICTURES
ON HIS COMPUTER.
- IT IS EXACTLY BECAUSE OF
THAT LEWD PHOTO
THAT I AM HERE.
BEN AND I ARE LAUNCHING A FULL
INVESTIGATION.
AND I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
TO ALL THE WOMEN...
AND JERRY.
IF I COULD GO BACK IN TIME,
AND CUT YOUR EYEBALLS OUT,
I WOULD.
- WOW, THAT IS SO SWEET.
- THANK YOU.
- WE ARE GETTING A LOT OF MEDIA
REQUESTS ABOUT THIS.
SO LESLIE, CAN YOU DO
PERD HAPLEY?
- HO! SHE CAN DO PERD HAPLEY.
- HI-OH!
- SERIOUSLY,
CAN YOU DO HIS TV SHOW?
- OH, YEAH.
- ANDREW MY MAN-DREW,
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- I'M ABOUT TO DO AN EXPERIMENT
WHERE I HUCK THIS AT THE WALL
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
BUT THAT CAN WAIT.
SHOE SHINE?
- ANDY, I'M GONNA BE HONEST.
I CAME HERE TODAY
TO TALK TO YOU.
NOW LOOK, YOU'RE ENTHUSIASTIC.
YOU'RE HARD-WORKING.
YOU CAN LIFT HEAVY THINGS.
I THINK THERE MIGHT BE A PLACE
FOR YOU
OVER AT ENTERTAINMENT720.
- OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S MY COMPANY!
- I DON'T KNOW, TOM.
I MEAN, I'M JUST NOW GETTING
REALLY GOOD AT SHOE SHINING.
AND I MEAN, I'M STILL
PRETTY BAD AT IT.
- LET ME ASK YOU THIS.
ARE YOU LIVING YOUR DREAMS?
- I DON'T KNOW, TOM.
- WELL, I'M LIVING MINE.
AND IF YOU WANNA LIVE YOURS,
HERE'S MY CARD.
- IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO READ.
- BLACK PRINT, BLACK BACKGROUND.
IT'S THE COOLEST POSSIBLE
COLOR SCHEME.
- YEAH.
- IT'S ALSO A STRONG MAGNET.
SO DON'T PUT IT IN YOUR WALLET.
IT WILL ERASE YOUR CREDIT CARDS,
GUARANTEED.
- DESTROY MY CREDIT CARDS.
DEBT AND EVERYTHING?
- MR. MAYOR, I PROMISE YOU
THAT WE WILL FIND THE OWNER
OF THAT WEINER
AND WE WILL PUNISH HIM.
GOOD-BYE.
ANN PERKINS!
- HEY.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHO TO COME TO
WITH THIS,
BUT THAT PICTURE, UH--THERE'S
SOMETHING VERY DISTURBING
ABOUT THE TESTICLES.
- I'VE ALWAYS FELT
THE SAME WAY MYSELF.
THE TESTICLES ARE LIKE
THE EARS OF THE GENITAL SYSTEM.
THEY SERVE A VERY
IMPORTANT FUNCTION,
BUT THEY'RE NOT THAT GREAT
TO LOOK AT.
- OKAY, WOW.
NO, I WAS SPEAKING MEDICALLY.
THEY'RE ENLARGED.
I THINK THAT MAYBE THAT GUY
IS SICK WITH SOMETHING--
PERHAPS, A HERNIA, OR MUMPS.
- ANN PERKINS!
YOU REALLY KNOW YOUR TESTES.
- THANK YOU?
- FOR A FEMALE PERSPECTIVE
ON THIS SCANDAL,
WE TURN TO A WOMAN,
LESLIE KNOPE.
I'M ABOUT TO ASK YOU A QUESTION
RIGHT NOW
AND THAT QUESTION IS THIS.
THE LEWD PHOTO--
JUST HOW BIG A DEAL IS IT?
- WELL, FRANKLY, PERD,
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- [laughing heartily]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
BUT IT HAD THE CADENCE
OF A JOKE.
- WHEN MEN IN GOVERNMENT
BEHAVE THIS WAY,
THEY BETRAY THE PUBLIC'S TRUST.
MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR MORE WOMEN
TO BE IN CHARGE.
- THERE YOU HAVE IT,
WHERE "IT" IS THE THING
LESLIE KNOPE JUST SAID
ABOUT THIS SITUATION.
PERD HAP--
- HOW WAS THAT?
WAS THAT OKAY?
- AMAZING.
THAT SOUND BITE IS GOLD.
- YOU'RE GONNA GET GREAT
FEEDBACK ON THIS,
AND WE THINK
WE CAN CAPITALIZE.
YOU'RE GONNA ANNOUNCE
YOUR CANDIDACY ON FRIDAY.
- FRIDAY.
IN THREE MONTHS.
- NO, THIS FRIDAY.
IS THAT OKAY?
- NO, YEAH.
YES, IT IS GREAT.
OKAY, WE'LL DO THAT THEN
NOW SOON.
AND, UM, I JUST HAVE SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN POSTPONING FOR A WHILE
THAT I NEED TO DO,
BUT I'LL DO IT NOW.
- GREAT.
YEA.
- I KNOW IT. HA HA.
OKAY.
- BEN? I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
- THAT WAS MY BROTHER.
HE JUST HAD A BABY GIRL.
- OH, MY GOD, THAT'S HORRIBLE.
OR GOOD--FULL DISCLOSURE.
I DIDN'T LISTEN TO WHAT
YOU JUST SAID.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING--
- OKAY, WELL, BEFORE YOU
SAY ANYTHING,
LET ME JUST SHOW YOU
WHAT I GOT AT DOUG'S DONUTS.
IT'S AN L-SHAPED ECLAIR!
THE "L" IS FOR LESLIE...
FOR YOUR NAME.
[knocking]
- HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
- BAD, REALLY BAD.
- OH, GOD.
HOW DID THE BREAKUP GO?
- WELL, I STARTED CRYING
BECAUSE HE GAVE ME AN ECLAIR.
AND THEN WE MADE OUT
AND SPENT THE NIGHT TOGETHER.
BUT THIS MORNING IN THE COLD
LIGHT OF DAY,
I COOKED BREAKFAST
AND WE MADE OUT SOME MORE.
- WOW, YOU OPPOSITE-OF-BROKE-UP
WITH HIM.
- HE GAVE ME AN ECLAIR, ANN!
- JOE, I'VE DETERMINED THAT
THE LEWD PICTURE WAS SENT BY YOU
BECAUSE YOU SENT IT FROM YOUR
PERSONAL EMAIL ADDRESS,
STINKMASTER69@ALUMNI.
SARAHLAWRENCECOLLEGE.EDU.
REALLY?
SARAH LAWRENCE?
- YEAH. I WANTED A SMALL
COLLEGE EXPERIENCE.
- YOU ALSO BRAGGED ABOUT IT
TO MANY OF YOUR CO-WORKERS.
- THERE'S AN OLD SEWAGE
DEPARTMENT SAYING.
"IF YOU'VE GOT A NICE
DRAINPIPE,
THERE'S NO REASON TO HIDE IT."
- I DOUBT THAT'S A SAYING.
WE ARE TERMINATING YOU
EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY.
- IS THIS
BECAUSE YOU'RE JEALOUS?
- NO.
IT'S BECAUSE YOU BROKE THE LAW.
- THE LAW OF HAVING
AN AMAZING PACKAGE.
- BEFORE WE HAVE HIM
FORCIBLY REMOVED,
YOU SHOULD KNOW THIS, THAT
ONE OF OUR FEMALE EMPLOYEES,
A NURSE, EXAMINED THE PHOTO
YOU SENT HER--
- I BET SHE DID.
- AND YOU HAVE THE MUMPS.
YOU MIGHT WANNA GET
THAT CHECKED.
- SWEET.
SOMEONE'S GOT MUMPS
ON HIS LUMPS.
UP HIGH.
ANYONE?
- RON ISN'T HERE.
HIS EX-WIFE TAMMY CAME,
AND HE GOT SCARED AND RAN AWAY.
WELL, AS ACTING MANAGER
OF THE PARKS DEPARTMENT,
I DECLARE THAT EVERYTHING
YOU ARE SAYING IS STUPID.
I LOVE YOU.
- HEY, SO TOM OFFERED ME A JOB
AGAIN.
AS MY MANAGER,
WHAT DO YOU THINK I SHOULD DO?
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?
- I THINK IT'D BE KINDA COOL
TO WORK FOR TOM.
- SO TAKE IT.
- BUT WORKING AT A START-UP
CAN BE KIND OF RISKY.
- SO DON'T TAKE IT.
- BUT TOM TOLD ME TO FOLLOW
MY DREAMS.
- SO TAKE IT.
- BUT THIS ISN'T MY DREAM.
- SO DON'T TAKE IT.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- ME NEITHER.
- YOU GIVE SUCH GOOD ADVICE.
BABE, I LOVE YOU.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
[cell phone chimes]
- ANN PERKINS!
- HEY. DID YOU MAYBE TELL PEOPLE
THAT I DIAGNOSED THAT GUY WITH
MUMPS BASED ON HIS PORN PHOTO?
- I DID!
I WAS SO PROUD OF YOU.
- OKAY, BECAUSE NOW I HAVE
EVERYONE IN CITY HALL
SENDING ME PICTURES
OF THEIR JUNK,
ASKING ME IF THEY HAVE MUMPS.
- OH, MY GOD.
YOUR INBOX IS LITERALLY FILLED
WITH PENISES.
- MM-HMM.
- I AM SO SORRY.
[cell phone chimes]
- OH, LOOK.
ED MILLER FROM PAYROLL.
- BEFORE I DO THIS,
IS THERE ANY POSSIBLE WAY THAT
WE COULD STILL KEEP DATING?
[cell phone chimes]
- WE'VE ATTACKED THIS
FROM ALL ANGLES.
EITHER YOU DON'T RUN
FOR OFFICE--
- WHICH IS OUT OF THE QUESTION.
- OR YOU BREAK UP WITH HIM
AND AVOID A POTENTIAL SCANDAL.
[cell phone chimes]
- DO YOU NEED TO GET THAT?
- NO, IT'S JUST PENISES.
LESLIE, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO BREAK UP WITH HIM EITHER.
THERE'S JUST NO OTHER WAY.
- YEAH.
- JUST BE DIRECT AND HONEST.
- OKAY.
HMM.
IT'S THE ENTIRE SANITATION
DEPARTMENT FOR MUNCIE.
OOH.
- WOULD YOU LIKE ANY WINE
TO START?
- YES, AND I'M GONNA BE DIRECT
AND HONEST WITH YOU.
I WOULD LIKE A GLASS OF RED WINE
AND I'LL TAKE
THE CHEAPEST ONE YOU HAVE
BECAUSE I CAN'T TELL
THE DIFFERENCE.
- I'LL HAVE THE SAME.
- GREAT.
- OKAY. HERE'S THE DEAL.
- OKAY.
- I REALLY, REALLY LIKE YOU.
- I LIKE YOU TOO.
AND I THINK I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY.
- I HIGHLY DOUBT THAT.
- I THINK I DO.
- OH, I DON'T.
- AND, UM...
I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
- NO. WHAT IS THIS?
IS THIS JEWELRY?
- IT'S NOT, JUST OPEN IT.
- NO.
OH, I NEED TO GO TO...
ANOTHER PLACE.
I'M GONNA GO TO THE BATHROOM--
THE WHIZ PALACE,
AS WE LIKE TO CALL IT HERE--
AND I'M GOING TO BE BACK
AND I'M NOT GONNA SPLIT.
I'M HERE FOR YOU BECAUSE
WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT STUFF.
OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT.
- WAIT--
RON.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- RUNNING AWAY
FROM MY PROBLEMS.
- COME ON IN.
[door slams]
- OKAY, SO HERE'S
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- I DIDN'T ASK.
- FRIDAY, I'M SUPPOSED
TO ANNOUNCE THAT I'M RUNNING
FOR CITY COUNCIL,
AND I HAVEN'T TOLD BEN YET.
I KNOW I SAID THAT WE BROKE UP,
BUT WE COULDN'T.
WE'RE STILL DATING.
BUT NOW I HAVE TO BREAK UP
WITH HIM FOR REAL,
BUT I DON'T WANNA BREAK UP
WITH HIM
BECAUSE HE'S SO CUTE.
HE'S SO NICE.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA STAY HERE,
THERE ARE THREE RULES
YOU NEED TO FOLLOW.
ONE, NO TALK ABOUT TAMMY ONE.
TWO, NO TALK ABOUT BEN.
THREE, NO TALK.
- I DIDN'T EVEN ASK YOU
LAST NIGHT.
WHAT IS GOING ON
WITH TAMMY ONE?
- YOU JUST VIOLATED RULES
NUMBER ONE AND THREE.
YOU LOSE YOUR COFFEE
PRIVILEGES.
- OH.
- OH, YOU CHOOSE, KNOPE--
HUNTING, FISHING, OR DRINKING?
- I'D REALLY LOVE TO SHOOT
A GUN RIGHT NOW.
- FISHING IT IS.
- AND SO EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY,
ALL MALE EMPLOYEES
MUST STOP SENDING EXPLICIT
PHOTOS TO MS. PERKINS.
- IF I MAY, WHAT IF BASED
ON EMPIRICAL EVIDENCE,
I TRULY BELIEVE THERE'S A GRAVE
AND IMMEDIATE MEDICAL EMERGENCY?
WERE THAT THE CASE,
COULD I THEN SHOW YOU MY DONG?
- NO.
- THAT WOULD BE HARASSMENT.
- FAIR ENOUGH.
NOW COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
SCENARIO.
LET'S SAY I'VE BEEN WATCHING
A LOT OF WOMEN'S GOLF
AND I'VE HAD SOME WINE--
- HOW ABOUT THIS?
I'M GONNA GET A MALE DOCTOR TO
COME IN AND DO SOME SCREENINGS.
- PERFECT.
JUST AS A BACKUP,
I'M SENDING YOU SOME PHOTOS.
- THAT WILL NOT BE NECESSARY.
- THAT'S ME.
[cell phone chimes]
- BRAND-NEW DAY,
BRAND-NEW MERCH.
I GOT YOU GUYS SOME AWESOME
ENTERTAINMENT720 STUFF.
DONNA, THIS IS FOR YOU.
ENTERTAINMENT720 UMBRELLA.
ENTERTAINMENT720 FLY SWATTERS.
RUBIK'S CUBE WITH MY FACE ON IT.
* BREATH MINTS
FIREPLACE BELLOWS.
AND...DRUM ROLL PLEASE.
[drum roll sound]
DRUM ROLL SOUND EFFECT
KEY CHAIN.
- SHOULDN'T YOU BE WORKING
AT YOUR NEW COMPANY, TOM?
- I AM WORKING, APRIL.
I'M MAKING HIGH-LEVEL
NETWORK CONTACTS.
YOU THINK BETHENNY FRANKEL
SITS BEHIND A DESK ALL DAY?
SHE MAKES $100 MILLION A YEAR.
HOW MUCH YOU MAKE A YEAR?
- $101 MILLION.
- WELL, I, FOR ONE,
AM HAPPY TO SEE TOM.
- THANKS, JERRY!
HERE. HAVE AN UMBRELLA
AND SOME BREATH STRIPS.
- WHOA.
- ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH CHITCHAT,
EVERYONE.
PLEASE GET BACK TO WORK.
- YOU'RE NOT OUR BOSS.
- WHAT'D YOU JUST SAY TO ME?
- MA'AM.
- SO...DID YOU GET A CHANCE
TO THINK ABOUT MY OFFER?
- YEAH, I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID.
I WANNA DO MY DREAMS,
BUT I JUST DON'T THINK MY DREAM
IS WORKING FOR A COMPANY THAT
PUTS LOGOS ON STUFF.
- THAT'S NOT
WHAT MY COMPANY DOES.
ALTHOUGH, MAYBE WE'LL START.
- HEY, WHAT YOU THINK?
- DONNA...THAT LOOKS GREAT.
- I COULD DO WITHOUT THIS ONE.
- [grunts]
- SO RUNNING FOR OFFICE.
NOW I'M GONNA HAVE TO FIND
A REPLACEMENT FOR YOU.
- I MIGHT NOT WIN.
- YOU'LL WIN.
- I MIGHT NOT RUN.
- YOU SHOULD.
WHAT'S OUR PLAN HERE, KNOPE?
- I FIGURE WE BUILD A FIRE,
ROAST THE FISH WE SHOT,
AND MAKE S'MORES.
- I DON'T HAVE THE MATERIAL
FOR S'MORES.
- I DO.
I ALWAYS CARRY EMERGENCY
S'MORE RATIONS IN MY CAR.
GIVEN YOUR HUNTING ABILITIES
AND MY CHOCOLATE SUPPLY,
I FIGURE WE COULD STAY UP HERE
FOR TWO...THREE YEARS.
- YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS 12,
MY BROTHER SHOT ME IN
THE PINKY TOE WITH A NAIL GUN.
GRANTED, IT WAS
A HILARIOUS PRANK,
AND WE ALL HAD A GOOD LAUGH.
- THAT'S AWFUL.
- BUT I AVOIDED GOING
TO THE DOCTOR.
I HATE PAPERWORK.
AFTER A FEW WEEKS,
THE TOE JUST KINDA FELL OFF.
- YOU ONLY HAVE NINE TOES?
- I HAVE THE TOES I HAVE.
LET'S JUST LEAVE IT AT THAT.
THE POINT IS THE DOCTOR SAID
IF I HAD COME IN RIGHT AWAY,
THEY MIGHT'VE SAVED THE TOE.
YOU CAN'T RUN AWAY
FROM YOUR PROBLEMS.
- ESPECIALLY IF YOU ONLY HAVE
NINE TOES.
SORRY.
THAT WAS UNCALLED FOR.
- I'M RON SWANSON.
AND YOU'RE LESLIE [bleep] KNOPE.
YOU WITH ME?
- WELL, WHAT IS YOUR DREAM?
- IT'S TO BE THE BIGGEST ROCK
STAR ON THE PLANET OBVIOUSLY.
BUT THAT COULD TAKE ANOTHER
3-5 YEARS.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
SHOE SHINING HAS BEEN A...
BEEN A PRETTY WILD RIDE.
BUT IS IT POSSIBLE THERE'S
SOMETHING MORE OUT THERE FOR ME?
- ANDY, THERE'S TONS OF STUFF
YOU CAN DO.
I'LL HELP YOU FIGURE IT OUT.
- REALLY?
- YES.
ONE YEAR FROM NOW, YOU,
ANDY DWYER, WILL NO LONGER BE
A SHOE SHINIST.
- KYLE, BEAT IT.
I WANNA MAKE OUT
WITH MY WIFE NOW.
- BUT YOU'VE ONLY DONE HALF
OF ONE OF MY SHOES.
- HERE.
NOW I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
SCRAM, KID.
- [grunts, laughs]
- HELLO.
- HEY, RON! WELCOME--
- STOP.
FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS.
I PROMISED LESLIE
I'D HIRE HER A NEW ASSISTANT
SO THE DEPARTMENT DOESN'T
COMPLETELY SHUT DOWN
WHILE SHE RUNS FOR OFFICE.
- YOU'RE RUNNING FOR OFFICE?
- YEAH, CITY COUNCIL.
- LESLIE, THAT IS GREAT.
- THANK YOU.
- WILL YOU PLEDGE RIGHT NOW
NOT TO RAISE TAXES?
- I THINK THAT'S PREMATURE.
- NO PLEDGE, NO VOTE.
- THE POINT IS
SHE NEEDS AN ASSISTANT.
START ASKING AROUND--
- HIRE ANDY.
ANDY CAN DO IT.
- SURE, YEAH.
- DONE.
ANDY, YOU ARE NOW LESLIE'S
ASSISTANT.
- HONEY.
- NO--
- LESLIE, I'M GONNA WORK
MY ASS OFF FOR YOU.
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU ASK ME.
I WILL PROVE MYSELF.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
TO PAY ME.
- NO, HONEY, NO.
- TOMORROW, THERE WILL BE
A 300-PAGE ORIENTATION BOOKLET
AS WELL AS A DOZEN
HOMEMADE COOKIES
IN THE SHAPE OF YOUR FACE.
BUT TODAY...
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
I HAVE TO DO.
- IF ANY OF YOU NEED
ANYTHING AT ALL, TOO BAD.
DEAL WITH YOUR PROBLEMS
YOURSELVES LIKE ADULTS.
I'LL BE IN MY OFFICE,
WAITING FOR TAMMY ONE.
- YOU WANT ME TO FIND HER?
- THERE'S NO NEED.
SHE'LL FIND ME.
SHE HAS THE TRACKING ABILITY
AND BODY ODOR OF A BLOODHOUND.
- OKAY, SO NOW YOU'RE SURE THAT
EVERYTHING IS OKAY, YOU KNOW,
DOWN THERE?
- YOU'RE PERFECTLY HEALTHY.
THAT MAN HAS THE LARGEST PENIS
I HAVE EVER SEEN.
I ACTUALLY DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF HE HAS MUMPS.
FORGOT TO LOOK.
I WAS DISTRACTED BY THE LARGEST
PENIS I HAVE EVER SEEN.
- I KNOW I'VE BEEN ACTING
REALLY WEIRD LATELY,
AND, UM, I REALLY LIKE YOU.
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO SAY
IS GONNA CONTRADICT THE IDEA
THAT I REALLY LIKE YOU,
BUT THAT WON'T CHANGE--
- SO JUST OPEN THE BOX.
- PLEASE STOP BRINGING OUT
THE BOX, OKAY?
- LESLIE--
- YOU'RE BEING REALLY NICE,
AND WHAT I'M ABOUT TO SAY
IS GONNA MAKE YOU HATE ME.
- OKAY, THEN I'LL JUST OPEN
THE BOX FOR YOU.
- WOW.
YOU KNEW?
- I FIGURED IT OUT A WHILE AGO.
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD'VE TOLD YOU I KNEW.
BUT I JUST--I WANTED THIS
TO LAST AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
WE HAVE TO BREAK UP.
- WHY?
WHY DO WE HAVE TO BREAK UP?
- WELL, LESLIE, EVERYTHING
YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED,
YOU HAVE EARNED
AND YOU HAVE WORKED FOR.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE TO THINK
THAT YOU GOT WHERE YOU ARE TODAY
BY SLEEPING WITH YOUR BOSS.
- BUT I REALLY LIKE SLEEPING
WITH MY BOSS.
- YEAH...YEAH.
OKAY, LOOK. I'M GONNA MAKE THIS
REAL EASY FOR YOU.
UM, IT'S NOT YOU, IT'S ME.
I'M NOT READY FOR A COMMITMENT.
I JUST DON'T LIKE YOU ANYMORE.
I KNOW IT'S HARD TO HEAR THAT,
BUT...
YOU'RE BORING, AND FRANKLY
YOU DISGUST ME.
ECHH!
- HOW DID YOU FIGURE IT OUT?
- LESLIE, THERE WAS A DUDE
IN THE LADIES' YACHT CLUB.
- YEAH, BUT I COVERED THAT
PRETTY WELL.
- ALSO, YOU'VE BEEN MAKING
CAMPAIGN SPEECHES IN YOUR SLEEP.
GRANTED, YOU ALWAYS DO THAT,
BUT THEY GOT REALLY SPECIFIC
AND MOVING.
- DID I HAVE A GOOD
OPENING LINE?
- IT WAS SIMPLE,
BUT I LIKED IT.
- FRIENDS, HONORED GUESTS,
PAWNEEANS.
I AM LESLIE KNOPE, AND
I AM RUNNING FOR CITY COUNCIL.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
- HELLO, TAMMY.
- RONALD.
- THAT'S ENOUGH SMALL TALK.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- YOU REMEMBER WHAT I DO
FOR A LIVING, I TRUST?
- YES.
YOU RUIN PEOPLE'S LIVES.
- YOU'RE BEING AUDITED,
RONALD.
- I DON'T CARE.
- THEN WHY IS YOUR MUSTACHE
TREMBLING?
I'M HERE AS A FRIEND.
CALL IT NOSTALGIA.
OR PERHAPS GUILT
FOR ALL THE TIMES
I TRIED TO SMOTHER YOU
IN YOUR SLEEP.
- I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
- WRONG. YOU DO.
BUT AS YOU'RE SO FOND OF SAYING,
IT'S A FREE COUNTRY.
GOOD LUCK.
I HOPE YOU DON'T GO TO JAIL.
SIT UP STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE NOT DOING YOUR BREASTS
ANY FAVORS.
- THANK YOU.
- HI.
YOUR BREASTS LOOK AMAZING.