- OKAY, GUYS.
THE BATTLE ROYALE IS COMING UP.
EVERY DEPARTMENT IN ONE ROOM,
ARGUING FOR MORE MONEY.
BUDGETARY THUNDERDOME!
SO, UH, MAKE LISTS OF WHY
OTHER DEPARTMENTS SUCK,
AND I'M GONNA GO
GET THE SECRET WEAPON.
OUR SECRET WEAPON IN THIS
BUDGETARY BATTLE?
RON.
EVERY TIME ANOTHER DEPARTMENT
ASKS FOR MORE MONEY,
HE JUST STARES THEM DOWN
UNTIL THEY BACK OFF
AND/OR WET THEMSELVES.
HEY, WHO'S READY TO GET--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- TAMMY ONE SHOWED UP.
I'M BEING AUDITED BY THE IRS.
- NO!
YOUR WORST NIGHTMARE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
SCREW THIS.
FIRST OF ALL,
INCOME TAX IS ILLEGAL.
SECOND, TAMMY IS
A PSYCHOLOGICAL MASTERMIND.
THIS IS JUST ANOTHER WAY FOR HER
TO PUT HER HAND UP MY KEISTER
AND CONTROL ME LIKE A PUPPET.
I'D RATHER BE LOCKED UP.
- RON, THIS IS
A FEDERAL TAX AUDIT.
YOU COULD GO TO JAIL.
JAIL, RON.
RON, JAIL.
JAIL, RON, JAIL.
YOU COULD GO TO JAIL.
JAIL, JAIL, JAIL.
- ARE YOU BROKEN?
- ANDY, APRIL!
- WHAT'S UP, BOSS?
- STOP YELLING
AND BEING ANNOYING.
- GRAB YOUR CALCULATORS.
SETTLE IN.
OPERATION RESCUE RON
IS STARTING.
DON'T WORRY.
I WILL THINK OF A BETTER NAME
FOR IT BY TOMORROW.
- HERE YOU GO.
- CALCULATOR.
[triumphant music]
*
- HEY...
- HEY, MAN.
- BEN.
- HEY, THANKS
FOR TEXTING ME TO HANG OUT.
I'VE REALLY FELT
LIKE WE'VE DEVELOPED
A COOL FRIENDSHIP, AND--
ANYWAY, IT WAS JUST NICE
TO HAVE THAT VALIDATED.
- YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
LOOK, WE GOT SOME DOCUMENTS
OVER AT ENTERTAINMENT720
THAT SEEM REALLY COMPLICATED.
AND I THOUGHT, MAYBE YOU COULD
TAKE A LOOK AT THEM
BECAUSE NERD STUFF PROBABLY
REALLY EXCITES YOU,
BECAUSE YOU'RE A NERD.
- NO, OF COURSE.
YEAH, NO, I JUST--
PUT ON MY STAR WARS PAJAMAS
AND SIT IN MY MOM'S BASEMENT
AND PORE OVER SOME SPREADSHEETS.
SOUNDS GREAT.
YEAH.
W-W-WHAT'D YOU GOT?
- SOMETHING CALLED
"BREAK EVEN ANALYSIS TABLES."
- OH, BREAK EVENS?
THOSE ARE REALLY FUN.
YEAH, SURE.
I'LL TAKE A LOOK.
- LET'S HIT IT.
- WHAT YOU--
RIGHT NOW?
UH--I HAVE WORK.
- AND I THOUGHT I HAD A FRIEND.
- ALL RIGHT.
- IT'S ALMOST TOO EASY.
- I CAN HEAR YOU.
- [laughs]
I KNOW YOU CAN,
BEN.
THAT'S HOW EASY IT IS.
- SO WE NEED TO FIND PROOF
OF EVERY TAX DEDUCTION
I'VE TAKEN
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
- RON, MOST OF THESE
AREN'T EVEN RECEIPTS.
THIS ONE SAYS,
"I BOUGHT SUPPLIES. 2007".
- YOU WON'T FIND ANY
BANK STATEMENTS EITHER.
I'VE HEAVILY INVESTED IN GOLD
WHICH I'VE BURIED
IN SEVERAL DIFFERENT LOCATIONS
AROUND PAWNEE.
OR HAVE I?
- WHAT'S THIS?
SOME KIND OF LAME DRUG DEAL?
- THAT IS
A GENTLEMAN'S AGREEMENT.
I MADE THAT MAN
A DINING ROOM TABLE
IN EXCHANGE FOR 60 FEET
OF COPPER PIPE
AND A HALF PIG.
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE SOME
ACTUAL RECEIPTS HERE.
SAME AMOUNT, EVERY MONTH.
140 BUCKS.
WHAT'S THIS?
- EVERY 30 DAYS,
I BUY SHOTGUN SHELLS
AND CIGARETTES
AND SEND THEM HOME TO MY MOM.
- [laughs]
- THAT'S SO SWEET.
YOUR MOM SOUNDS KICKASS.
- MY FIRST EX-WIFE'S NAME
IS TAMMY.
MY SECOND EX-WIFE'S NAME
MY MOM'S NAME IS TAMARA.
SHE GOES BY TAMMY.
- YOU CAN PREVENT
ADULT-ONSET DIABETES
BY GETTING AN ANNUAL CHECK-UP,
EXERCISING,
PRAYING...
- OKAY.
[clears throat]
- WHO IS THAT GUY?
- THAT IS WALT MORPHLING.
HE WAS THE DIRECTOR
OF PUBLIC HEALTH,
BUT HE HAD TO RETIRE AT 46
BECAUSE HE HAD DIABETES.
- THAT IS SAD, BUT ALSO,
IN THIS TOWN,
UNDERSTANDABLE.
- I WOULD LIKE
TO SHOOT A NEW PSA
AND I THINK IT'D BE GOOD
TO GET SOMEONE
WHO'S HEALTHY AND TELEGENIC,
AND I THOUGHT THAT
YOU WOULD BE PERFECT.
- ANN PERKINS.
I AM FLATTERED.
AND I WILL DO IT.
IS THERE A SCRIPT YET?
- UH, NO, BECAUSE YOU JUST
APPROVED THE IDEA, LIKE,
THREE SECONDS AGO.
- I WOULD LIKE YOU
TO WRITE ME A SCRIPT
AND GET IT TO ME IN AN HOUR.
AND WE SHOULD START THINKING
ABOUT WARDROBE.
CASUAL?
FORMAL? SEMI-FORMAL?
SPORTY?
SCARY?
POSH? BABY?
THOSE ARE THE SPICE GIRLS.
I JUST GOT CAUGHT UP
IN MY OWN THOUGHTS.
I'M VERY EXCITED ABOUT THIS.
- IN TERMS OF SHIRTS,
I CAN WEAR WHITE...
- WELCOME TO PARADISE,
MY MAN.
YOU CAN CHILL
OVER THERE BY THE BAR.
WE ALSO GOT BASKETBALL
AT ANY TIME YOU WANT.
THERE'S ROY HIBBERT
AND DETLEF SCHREMPF.
- OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S AN ACTUAL NBA PLAYER.
HE PLAYS FOR THE PACERS.
- NBA'S ON STRIKE,
SO WE GOT HIM FOR ONLY, LIKE,
75% OF HIS ORIGINAL NBA SALARY.
WHAT UP, ROY?
- IS THIS ALL YOU WANT ME TO DO?
PLAY ONE ON ONE WITH DETLEF?
- YES.
AND KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
JEAN-RALPHIO!
- TAKE ME THERE.
[shouting]
- BUMP!
[laughs]
- WHO ARE YOU?
- UH--
- THIS IS BEN.
HE'S HERE TO HELP US
WITH THE PAPERWORK.
- BEN?
IS THAT YOUR REAL NAME?
- YES.
- OH, YOU COULD DO BETTER
THAN THAT.
I'MA HELP YOU OUT RIGHT NOW.
YOUR NAME IS ANGELO.
ANGELO, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING OUT.
GET A THICKER TIE.
IT LOOKS WEIRD ON YOU.
MAKES YOUR HEAD
LOOK LIKE A FISH.
SECONDLY,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
THE PAPERWORK IS,
BUT WHEN YOU FIND IT,
CAN YOU TAKE CARE OF IT FOR US?
WE DON'T HAVE ANY PENS
'CAUSE WE'RE AFRAID
IT'S GONNA LEAK IN OUR SHIRTS.
LASTLY, I HATE THE NAME,
ANGELO.
I'MA SWITCH IT UP FOR YOU,
RIGHT NOW.
YOUR NEW NICKNAME IS...
JELL-O SHOT.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT,
J-SHOT?
DO YOU HAVE QUESTIONS?
- YEAH. WHERE ARE WE?
- ALL RIGHT, BEN.
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING,
ONE OF THESE MODELS THAT
WE PAY TO HANG AROUND HERE
WILL GRAB IT FOR YOU.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE'RE GONNA
BE PLAYING VIDEO GAMES,
TWEETING OUR HIGH SCORES.
- HIT IT!
- UM, HI.
ARE YOU THE RECEPTIONIST?
- I GUESS.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
- IF YOU DON'T MIND ME ASKING,
HOW MUCH ARE THEY PAYING YOU?
- $100,000 A YEAR.
WITH FULL MEDICAL.
- I MEAN, I WOULD GUESS
THEY'LL BE BANKRUPT
BY THE END OF...
THIS SENTENCE.
NO, THANK YOU.
- IS THIS TRUE?
YOU ONLY SPENT $40 ON CLOTHES
IN THE PAST 5 YEARS?
- IT SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
- HOW DID YOU MEET TAMMY ONE?
- TECHNICALLY, I'VE KNOWN HER
SINCE I WAS BORN.
SHE WAS A CANDY STRIPER
AT THE HOSPITAL.
SHE HELPED DELIVER ME.
all: OH, MY GOD.
- I GREW UP
IN A VERY SMALL TOWN.
600 PEOPLE.
EVERYBODY KNEW EVERYBODY ELSE.
WE FIRST TOOK UP TOGETHER
WHEN I WAS 15.
- AWESOME.
- OH, MY GOD.
- IT WAS A LITTLE SCANDALOUS,
BUT EVERYONE FEARED HER,
SO THEY KEPT THEIR MOUTHS SHUT.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW HER,
BUT SHE'S MY HERO.
- NO, SHE'S NO HERO, APRIL.
SHE'S A HELLACIOUS NIGHTMARE.
SHE DID, HOWEVER,
TEACH ME EVERYTHING I KNOW.
SUNDAY SCHOOL, SEX.
SHE WAS MY MATH TEACHER
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL
AND MY BABYSITTER,
AND SHE TAUGHT DRIVER'S ED.
I--
- HELLO.
I DON'T BELIEVE WE'VE MET.
I AM LESLIE KNOPE, DEPUTY--
- I DON'T THINK
IT WILL BE NECESSARY
FOR YOU TO SPEAK AGAIN
WHILE I'M HERE.
- WHY DO I ONLY DATE BRUNETTES?
YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES YOU EAT CHICKEN
AND YOU GET FOOD POISONING
AND THEN, EVEN THE SIGHT
OF CHICKEN MAKES YOU SICK?
TAMMY ONE IS MY BLONDE CHICKEN.
- GOOD GOD, RONALD.
THIS IS A MUCH BIGGER MESS
THAN I IMAGINED.
YOU'LL TAKE A WEEK OFF
FROM WORK.
WE'LL DO A COMPLETE OVERHAUL
OF YOUR FINANCES.
I'LL NEED ACCESS
TO ALL YOUR ACCOUNTS,
AND YOUR HOME.
- IS THAT NECESSARY?
- OH, OH.
WE'RE PLAYING A GAME WHERE
EVERYONE SAYS SOMETHING STUPID?
- [laughs]
- YOU.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- TIM.
TIM BUCKENOWSKI.
- REALLY?
- NO.
ANDY DWYER.
- ANDY...
YOU'RE GOING TO COLLECT
ALL OF THIS,
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO PUT IT IN MY CAR.
- WHAT--
- MS. KNOPE.
- YES?
- YOU'RE GOING TO GO TO PAYROLL
AND GET COPIES OF RONALD'S
WORKPLACE EXPENSE REPORTS.
- OH, I--I'M JUST WONDERING
HOW LONG THAT'S GOING TO TAKE,
BECAUSE RON AND I HAVE A VERY
IMPORTANT MEETING TOGETHER.
IT'S CALLED THE BATTLE ROYALE.
IT'S SUPER FUN.
WELL...
- YOU AND RON
HAVE A BIG MEETING, HUH?
- I'M SURE RON WILL REMEMBER
THE MEETING FONDLY
WHILE HE MAKES TOILET WINE
IN A FEDERAL PRISON
IN TERRE HAUTE.
- I'LL--I'LL HEAD DOWN
TO PAYROLL.
- [clears throat]
NOW.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING ANY YOUNGER.
- YES, MA'AM.
- SHE'S THE COLD, DISTANT MOTHER
I NEVER HAD.
I LOVE HER.
- [whistling]
GOOD MORNING, EVERYONE.
- GOOD MORNING, SIR.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- RON?
YOUR MOUSTACHE FELL OFF.
- [laughs]
LESLIE, YOU GOOFBALL.
[laughs]
TAMMY POINTED OUT THAT
MY FACE LOOKED BETTER
WITHOUT ANY HAIR ON IT.
AND IT COLLECT
A LOT OF FOOD CRUMBS,
WHICH IS VERY UNSANITARY.
HEY, JER.
HUMP DAY, AM I RIGHT, BUDDY?
[snaps fingers]
- WHAT?
- WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHERE'S TAMMY ONE?
- SHE MOVED IN WITH ME.
SHE'S REALLY HELPING ME OUT.
YESTERDAY, SHE CONVERTED
MY BANK ACCOUNT
INTO A JOINT BANK ACCOUNT
WITH HER.
- OH.
THAT'S GREAT.
AND HOW IS THAT GONNA HELP?
- NOT SURE.
WHEN SHE EXPLAINS IT,
IT MAKES TOTAL SENSE.
IT IS SO NICE
HAVING HER AROUND.
HERE'S SOMETHING NEAT.
TAMMY'S GOT ME
TAKING BABY ASPIRIN
TO LOWER
MY RISK OF HEART DISEASE.
SCIENCE IS A MIRACLE.
ANY-WHO,
BACK TO THE OLD GRINDSTONE.
THESE EMAILS AREN'T GONNA
SEND THEMSELVES.
[laughs]
- DIABETES CAN'T BE CURED.
BUT IT CAN BE PREVENTED.
MAKE A CHOICE.
MAKE A CHANGE.
AND TOGETHER,
WE CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ANY NOTES?
- GREAT.
JUST AS GOOD,
IF NOT EXACTLY THE SAME
AS THE LAST ONE.
IN THAT LAST ONE,
I LEFT A NANOSECOND
OF A PAUSE BETWEEN THE WORDS,
"TOGETHER" AND "WE."
IT FELT MUCH BETTER.
BUT I'D LOVE TO TRY ANOTHER ONE.
- I REALLY THINK WE'VE GOT IT.
- ANN.
THIS IS IMPORTANT TO ME
BECAUSE IT'S IMPORTANT TO YOU.
I MEAN, YOU SPENT
A LOT OF TIME AND ENERGY
ON WRITING THIS.
- NOT REALLY.
- SO, IT NEEDS TO BE PERFECT.
SO, LET'S DO 1 MORE,
THEN 5 MORE,
THEN 20 IN A ROW.
- HEY,
LOOK WHO IT IS.
- HEY, HEY.
- TOM.
JEAN-RALPHIO.
PROFESSIONAL BASKETBALL PLAYERS.
- 'SUP,
JELL-O SHOT.
- CAN I ASK YOU GUYS
A QUESTION?
HOW EXACTLY
ARE YOU MAKING MONEY?
- WANNA KNOW
HOW WE MAKE MONEY?
- DO YOU WANNA KNOW
- BY LITERALLY
PRINTING OUT OUR MONEY.
- WE BOUGHT A PRINTING PRESS.
THIS PRINTS BILLS WITH OUR FACES
AND THE E720 LOGO ON THEM.
- AND PROMOTE THE COMPANY
BY GOING TO CLUBS
AND TOSSING THE BILLS
IN THE AIR AND SCREAMING,
"FREE MONEY!"
- YOU CAN'T JUST PRINT
YOUR OWN MONEY.
THIS HAS TO STOP,
RIGHT NOW.
[rap music]
- AWW!
- WHAT'S THE DEAL,
BABY?
ONE SECOND, YOU HIT
THE PARTY SWITCH,
AND THE NEXT SECOND,
YOU'RE ALL BUSINESS?
- I NEED TO SEE
ALL OF YOUR BOOKS.
- YOU GOT IT, BABY.
BABY!
GET HIM THE BOOKS.
- AWW, SNAPPLE.
ARE WE CALLING
EVERYBODY "BABY" NOW?
'CAUSE HONESTLY,
I LOVE THAT.
- ARE WE SAYING "SNAPPLE"
ANYTIME WE THINK
SOMETHING'S DOPE?
'CAUSE I LOVE THAT, BABY.
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE?
[whistles]
JELL-O SHOT!
[rap music plays]
- UH-OH!
HIBBERT, HIBBERT.
all: HUP, JELL-O SHOT!
JELL-O SHOT!
- THANK YOU.
- WE'RE HERE TO SERVE YOU,
FRIEND.
I HOPE THE REST OF YOUR DAY
IS COOL BEANS.
- RON,
WHAT IS THIS MEMO
YOU SENT TO ME?
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO THE BATTLE ROYALE?
- I HAVE DECIDED
NOT TO ATTEND THIS YEAR.
- OKAY, FIRST OF ALL,
IT'S DISTURBING
THAT YOU WROTE A MEMO,
AT ALL.
BUT YOU LOVE ARGUING AGAINST
GOVERNMENT SPENDING.
WHY DO YOU NOT WANNA
DO IT NOW?
- LESLIE, PLEASE.
THE GOVERNMENT KNOWS
WHAT IT'S DOING.
I'M CONFIDENT THAT I'LL--
OUCHIE.
- YOU AND I ARE GOING TO LUNCH.
WE HAVE TO TALK.
- LET ME JUST CALL TAMMY FIRST
AND GET PERMISSION.
- OH, COME ON.
- TAMMY,
I WAS WONDERING IF I COULD
GO TO LUNCH WITH LESLIE?
TERRIFIC.
BYE.
SHE SAYS I CAN'T GO.
- YOU'RE GOING TO LUNCH WITH ME.
I SAY YOU CAN GO.
- OH, GOSH.
I'M REALLY IN A PICKLE NOW.
- OH, MY GOD.
WHEN RON FALLS FOR TAMMY TWO,
HE TURNS
INTO A DEMONIC SEX MANIAC.
BUT THIS?
NEUTERED WIMP?
THIS IS WORSE.
OPERATION GOLDEN DOVE
IS IN TROUBLE.
RON, THERE ARE SOME THINGS
I WANT TO SPEAK TO YOU ABOUT
BUT I'M NOT QUITE SURE
HOW TO PHRASE THEM.
- JUST BLURT THEM
RIGHT OUT, LESLIE.
ANYTHING YOU SAY WILL STAY
BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
RIGHT, MY LOVE?
- STOP FIDGETING.
- SORRY.
- I WAS HOPING TO SPEAK
WITH RON ALONE.
- HE WANTS ME HERE.
HE INVITED ME.
NA-NA-NA-NA-NA.
- DON'T WORRY, LESLIE.
TAMMY'S TOTALLY COOL.
- HUH, OKAY.
THEN I'LL SAY IT TO HER.
YOU'RE EVIL,
AND YOU NEED TO GO.
[both chuckle]
- LESLIE, YOU ARE A PANIC.
TAMMY,
MAY I USE THE RESTROOM?
- REMEMBER TO WASH YOUR HANDS.
- OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S CUT THE CRAP.
IS THIS AUDIT EVEN REAL?
- IN A SENSE, YES.
BUT IN ANOTHER, TRUER SENSE, NO,
IT IS NOT.
I WANT RONALD BACK,
BUT I HAD TO LEARN
ABOUT HIS FINANCES,
TO MAKE SURE MY FUTURE
WAS PROTECTED.
I'M IMPRESSED.
HE'S ACQUIRED
QUITE A BIT OF GOLD.
- YOU GOLD DIGGER.
YOU'RE LITERALLY A GOLD DIGGER.
- THE THING I LOVE ABOUT TAMMY
IS SHE CALLS ME ON MY CRAP.
EVERY GUY NEEDS THAT.
- OKAY, IF YOU WANT
THIS COMPANY TO SURVIVE,
YOU IMMEDIATELY NEED TO
DOWNSIZE.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T NEED
THIS AIRPLANE HANGAR.
- UM, I THINK WE DO.
- AND TWO, YOU HAVE TO KEEP
DETAILED FINANCIAL RECORDS.
- THANK YOU!
I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO TELL THEM THAT!
- WASTE OF TIME.
THEY WOULDN'T KNOW
A NON-EMPLOYEE TAX-REPORTABLE
EXPENDITURE REQUEST
IF IT BIT THEM IN THE ASS.
- HEY GUYS, WHICH TWO PEOPLE
HERE STARTED THEIR OWN COMPANY?
'CAUSE I'M PRETTY SURE
IT WASN'T YOU TWO BOZOS.
- HEY!
- LOOK, YOU GUYS CAN SWAGGER
AROUND ALL YOU WANT,
BUT BUSINESSES NEED REVENUE,
OKAY?
UNLESS YOU START WORKING
ON AN ACTUAL PLAN,
YOU'RE DEAD IN A MONTH.
THAT'S A FACT.
- BEN,
THANKS FOR YOUR TIME.
BUT WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
AS FAR AS BUSINESS DECISIONS GO,
I THINK WE KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
DON'T FORGET TO GRAB A FREE iPad
ON YOUR WAY OUT.
- HE DIDN'T EVEN HAVE ONE.
- DIABETES!
FIGHT IT!
NOT QUITE, BUT I LIKE THE
ENERGY--ARE WE STILL ROLLING?
- YUP.
- DIABETES!
- OKAY, LET'S--CAN WE TAKE
A BREAK?
- I THINK THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
I THINK WE ALMOST HAVE IT,
AND I AM VERY EXCITED
AT THAT PROSPECT.
I'LL CANCEL MY FOUR O'CLOCK
AND MY FIVE O'CLOCK
AND MY SIX O'CLOCK APPOINTMENTS.
- I CANNOT BELIEVE
I DATED HIM.
FOR A LONG TIME.
AND HE BROKE UP WITH ME!
- FAT EQUALS SPLAT!
AS IN, "YOU'RE DEAD!"
IS THERE SOMETHING THERE?
NO--NO.
THAT--THAT SUCKED.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING THERE.
I'M FEELING IT--
LET'S GO RIGHT AWAY!
IT'S MAGIC TIME!
FROM THE TOP, EVERYBODY.
- THERE'S NO ONE ELSE HERE.
- BASICALLY, WE'RE BEING
ATTACKED BY GODZILLA.
AND TO BEAT GODZILLA,
WE NEED MOTHRA.
NO OFFENSE.
- NONE TAKEN.
I'M VERY FLATTERED.
- WHO'S THIS?
WHO'S THIS TALL DRINK OF WATER?
- ANDY.
- HEY, ANDY.
HOW'S IT HANGING?
- LISTEN, WE NEED YOU TO BREAK
RON FROM HER SPELL.
CAN'T YOU JUST MOVE
YOUR BUTT AROUND,
OR WEAR A DRESS
MADE OUT OF MEAT?
- WELL I COULD DO
ALL THOSE THINGS AND HAVE,
BUT THAT BITCH IS CRAZY.
WHEN RON LEFT HER
AND WE GOT TOGETHER,
SHE THREW ACID ON MY FOOT.
- EWW!
- COULD WE TAKE A PEEK AT IT?
- LISTEN, TAMMY ONE WAS
MY SUNDAY SCHOOL TEACHER, TOO.
SHE CAN PINPOINT
YOUR WEAKNESSES,
AND THEN DESTROY YOU
WITH JUST ONE WORD.
AND A JAR OF ACID.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I THINK I HAVE AN IDEA
THAT COULD SAVE RON.
- ANDY, DON'T JOKE AROUND.
- I HAVE IDEAS, TOO.
- YOU WERE RIGHT
TO COME GET ME.
MY SON RONNIE ALWAYS HAD
A WEAKNESS FOR THOSE LADIES.
- OH, WOW.
IS THIS RON?
- YUP.
AT THE AGE OF FIVE.
HE'S STANDING NEXT
TO THE FIRST CHAIR
HE EVER BUILT.
- OH, MY GOD!
THERE'S A ROOM
FULL OF JUST GUNS.
- WHY DO YOU HAVE SO MANY GUNS?
- THIS IS AMERICA, ISN'T IT?
- YES.
- THEN I DON'T HAVE TO ANSWER
STUPID QUESTIONS
WHILE STANDING
ON MY OWN PROPERTY.
LET'S GO.
[whistles]
- OKAY. WELL,
IT'S DEFINITELY RON'S MOM.
- TAMMY.
- RONNIE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WELCOME
TO THE BATTLE ROYALE.
RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT NOW.
OPERATION SOARING FALCON
IS IN ITS FINAL STAGES.
- IT'S TIME TO SETTLE THIS.
- AH.
AN OLD-FASHIONED
PRAIRIE DRINK-OFF.
- WHAT'S IN THAT JUG?
IT SMELLS LIKE JET FUEL.
- THAT'S SWANSON FAMILY
MASH LIQUOR.
MADE FROM THE FINEST CORN
EVER GROWN ON AMERICAN SOIL.
ITS ONLY LEGAL USE
IS TO STRIP VARNISH
OFF OF SPEEDBOATS.
- IF YOU WIN,
HE'S ALL YOURS.
AND IF I WIN, I BRING HIM
BACK TO THE FARM
FOR GOOD.
- WAIT, WHAT?
THAT WASN'T THE DEAL.
- POUR IT.
I'M THIRSTY.
- POUR ME ONE, TOO,
THEN.
LET ME IN HERE.
I'M GONNA JOIN YOU AND IF I WIN,
RON STAYS HERE WITH US.
- LESLIE, NO,
DON'T DRINK THAT.
WE USE IT TO BURN WARTS
OFF OF THE MULES!
- POISON!
UGH!
I MADE A MISTAKE.
- HOW WERE WE TOGETHER
FOR FIVE MONTHS?
- WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S POSSIBLE
YOU CAN JUST DATE A GUY
BECAUSE OF WHERE YOU ARE
IN YOUR LIFE EMOTIONALLY.
- YEAH, I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT,
JOHN.
- ANN PERKINS,
I HATE TO SAY THIS,
BUT I HAVE A STAIN ON MY SHIRT.
WHICH MEANS THAT EVERYTHING
WE SHOT SO FAR IS UNUSABLE,
BUT LET'S USE THIS
AS AN OPPORTUNITY
TO REVISIT THE SCRIPT.
DELIVERY GUY.
- HEY.
- DIABETES!
- HAD ENOUGH?
- OF THIS WATERED-DOWN
BABY FORMULA?
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
- NOT MEVEN CLARSE.
MARVIN CLODS.
GLENN CLOSE.
- LESLIE, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THIS...
- SHH!
GO TO BED, JIMMY.
WRAH!
I CAN'T FEEL MY FACE.
MY FACE IS NUMB.
[hissing]
WHAT IS THAT?
- AND TOGETHER,
WE CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
THAT'S IT.
I THINK WE GOT IT.
DO YOU THINK WE GOT IT?
- YES! YEAH, WE HAVE IT.
WE HAD IT SEVEN HOURS AGO.
- OH, ANN, I--I KNOW THAT
I CAN BE INTENSE,
BUT I'M ONLY TRYING TO BE
THE BEST ME THAT I CAN BE.
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR THIS OPPORTUNITY
AND YOUR PATIENCE,
AND YOUR INTELLIGENCE,
AND YOUR INSIGHT.
YOU REALLY ARE
AN AMAZING HUMAN BEING.
- THANK YOU.
- OH, RIGHT--
THAT'S WHY I DATED HIM.
- HEY.
- I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE.
WE BROUGHT IN FIVE ACCOUNTANTS
TO LOOK AT E720
AND THEY ALL SAID
THE SAME THING YOU DID.
IF WE DON'T START
MAKING CHANGES,
WE'RE GONNA LOSE THE COMPANY.
- OKAY. WELL,
FIRST THING YOU NEED TO DO:
GET RID OF FOUR
OF THOSE ACCOUNTANTS.
YOU DON'T NEED FIVE ACCOUNTANTS.
- AGAIN, GOOD ADVICE.
HERE.
- YOU REALLY--YOU NEED TO STOP
GIVING THESE AWAY LIKE CANDY.
- I BOUGHT THAT ONE PERSONALLY.
AS A THANK-YOU.
IT'S A iPad.
- * EVERYBODY PRANCE, NOW!
* PRANCE, PRANCE, PRANCE,
PRANCE, PRANCE, PRANCE *
- SHE'S HAD ENOUGH.
CALL IT OFF.
- THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
SHE'S OUT.
- WAIT.
I'M SUBBING IN.
- APRIL, NO--THAT STUFF
WILL MELT
THE SHELL OFF A GARDEN SNAIL.
- WHATEVER.
I'M PUERTO RICAN.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
[sputters]
[bleep], OH, MY GOD!
- OKAY.
THIS ENDS NOW.
- AH.
- MOM, YOU'RE GOING
BACK TO THE FARM.
AND YOU,
YOU'RE GOING BACK TO HELL.
- FINE.
I GOT WHAT I CAME FOR ANYWAY.
I FOUND YOUR UNDERGROUND SAFE.
I STOLE HALF YOUR GOLD.
- THAT'S DECOY GOLD.
YOU THINK I'D LEAVE MY GOLD
IN A LOCKED SAFE
BURIED UNDERGROUND,
WHERE ANYONE COULD FIND IT?
YOU DON'T KNOW ME AT ALL.
- YES, I DO.
I KNEW YOU THE MINUTE
YOU WERE BORN.
AND I INTEND TO BE THERE
THE MINUTE YOU DIE.
- RON,
YOUR FAMILY'S WEIRD.
- LITERALLY, THERE'S A--
SOMEONE READING A MAGAZINE
AND SOMEONE
APPLYING NAIL POLISH.
WHAT'S THAT--WHAT IS SHE DOING?
SHE'S JUST PLAYING WITH AN iPad.
TOM TOLD ME THAT CHAIR
WAS $27,000.
THAT CHAIR THAT HAS A ROOF.
THE--THERE'S SOMEONE OVER THERE
IN A DEEP SLEEP.
SHE'S PROBABLY BEING PAID
UPWARDS OF $100,000 A YEAR.
THERE'S THIS VIDEO OF A BOAT.
LOOK AT THAT THING.
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH THAT THING?