Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Lee.Ee,
don doesn't think
there's a problem.
Lee, those restrictions
aren't going to affect
lucky strike.
Besides, Lee, your lawyers
came up with them.
"no more smoking teenagers"...
we complied a year ago.
"no more famous athletes"
And we have to stop using
certain angles.
Low angles, wide lenses...
Anything that
makes the smoker
appear superhuman.
- Why is this empty?
- Because you drank it all.
- He can't hear you.
- There's kind of a loophole
Because even
without athletes you
can still use sports.
Bowling, for example,
seems a natural fit.
Bowling is a sport, Lee.
Well, how about
horse-racing?
Lee. Lee,
the jockey smokes
the cigarette.
Did either of you ladies
bring any ice with you?
We're sorting out
the focus group for pond's
And I haven't
gotten the hypothesis...
- In writing anyway.
- He said "don."
We'll do our best.
- Peggy, write it up.
- You haven't okayed
the brief.
I liked your idea.
I liked it a lot.
The mirror one
or the cleansing one?
What's the mirror one?
Well, I think
it's about the ritual,
The multiple applications,
indulgence.
"pond's is
the only cold cream
that allows me"
To stare at myself
in the mirror
for 20 minutes
"And feel good
and not vain."
That's very good.
So we're talking
about girls 18 to 25.
Can I grab a few
from around here?
Yeah, help yourself.
See, I would
never buy a sailboat.
I don't want
to do things myself.
For that price,
that boat should
have a motor.
A what?
- One of those too.
- Anything else?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask
don about that?
I have to go to
the little boys' room.
I'm sorry, Lee,
can you go through that
one more time?
That's the lucky strike call?
Why wasn't I told?
Be happy.
I saved you an ass-ache.
So what's so bad
he couldn't tell me?
Cal Rutledge from
Chesebrough-pond's
Has a wild hair
about Clearasil.
He thinks they're in conflict.
Pimple cream and cold cream?
- That's a rather
broad definition.
- Does it matter?
Look, Pete, we're
going to have to resign
the Clearasil account.
- Why?
- Lane.
It can't be up for debate.
Clearasil is worth
$1.25 million in billings
- And pond's over two.
- No.
Do you know what it took
to get my father-in-law
To join this new firm
to begin with?
15% of $750,000
Is near $113,000.
Roger, I don't expect him
to understand this,
But do you have any idea
of what I've had to do
to keep that account?
The personal toll I've paid?
I do, but you've
been good to him...
Remember that...
saleswise.
- Mr. Sterling.
- I don't believe this.
- Roger.
- Throw yourself
on the grenade.
Protect the agency.
You're a partner now.
This evening if you can.
Over half this agency is
dedicated to your needs,
But if you want to get
into the line-by-line
Of the costs we've billed for,
I'll have lane Pryce
at the foot of your bed
in 20 minutes.
Oh my God,
there's some kind of fire.
Right down by radio city.
Roger, we should go.
Sorry, Lee.
We gotta go.
Okay, bye-bye.
Should I type all this up?
Yes, and remind me
to remind Caroline
to tell lane
That lucky strike noticed
that they're being billed
For all the work we do
for everybody else
at this agency.
You know what?
I don't want that on paper.
- Who is that?
- A dear friend.
Is that the letter
from California?
Yes.
- I hate this office.
- You wanted to be
close to Roger.
Make yourself at home,
why don't you?
Did you see Sunday's paper?
If this is about
the Playtex ad they keep
complaining about,
I've been told
the printer swapped
paper stocks.
And I don't care
if she looks like
a Puerto Rican.
Puerto Rican girls
buy brassieres.
Not that they need to.
I saw this one on the subway
In one of those striped
Jean Seberg shirts,
Red rag in her hair, nipples...
I'm not in the mood.
What do you want?
- Cosgrove's getting married.
- So?
He took us
to the opera last month...
Great seats and now I know why.
- It turns out her father
shits gold ingots.
- What does he do?
C.F.O. Of corning.
My father-in-law's
a bus driver.
The only place he can
take me is to the moon.
Ken's the competition.
Why are you going to
the opera with him?
Geyer is twice our size,
And we're friends, aren't we?
Friends.
Why are you always
looking for a job?
What?
Look, Pete.
There's a group of us,
we're all coming up together.
You don't think
Kenny's a comer?
You know he has
mountain dew?
That's Pepsi.
We're having
lunch tomorrow.
Tag along.
- He always asks about you.
- Of course he does.
Worst case, Kenny'll brag
too much and you can steal
a client from him.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
That looks like bad news.
Oh, it's not mine.
I'm Joyce.
I work at "life"...
assistant photo editor.
Peggy Olson,
Sterling Cooper
draper Pryce...
copywriter.
Really?
"life" magazine...
I love your photos.
Well, you'll never see these.
I have to admit I'd be shocked.
He's my friend
and my boss hates nudes.
Who hates nudes?
That's a beautiful one.
I'm going to the mailroom.
Peggy, right? 37th floor?
Tom, you're 15 minutes early.
So are you.
Sit down.
We can eat anytime
or not at all.
Excuse me.
Dewar's on the rocks.
What's so important?
Well, Tom,
How are you feeling?
Couldn't be better.
I hope you know
I've always done my best
to make you happy.
I do.
And there's no reason,
as far as I'm concerned,
That there should be any
change in the way that we
deal with each other.
Tom, I...
This is very hard
for me to say.
I honestly don't know how
you're going to take this
And it's been
very hard to separate
Our business relationship
from the rest of our life,
But they should be separate.
You are some kind
of high wasp, all right.
- Look, I can't keep this up.
- Keep what up?
- I heard.
- You know?
You crazy kid.
What are you talking about?
Jeannie was with Trudy
at the doctor.
Congratulations!
What?
Oh, shit.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
It was Monday,
for crying out loud.
Why hasn't she told you?
I don't know.
Well, it may be her news,
but it is good news.
You can't tell her that
I told you. You can't.
I'm going to be a father?
Can you believe it?
- I'm going to be
a father.
- Yeah.
I feel like my heart's
going to burst.
Champagne right here.
Bring a bottle.
We're going to tie one on.
If it's a boy, it's $1,000;
A girl, $500.
I'll do what I can do.
You really can't tell Trudy.
I don't know how I let
the cat out of the bag.
I thought you knew
what I was talking about.
What did you think
I was talking about?
- What?
- Why did you
have to see me?
I just wanted to...
We're putting
new creative
on clearasil.
Oh fine. Who cares?
May you know
this feeling many times.
Mmm. I only had the one
And I love her to death,
but I wish we'd had more.
Jeannie had
her uterus removed...
Some kind of a cyst
or something.
Trudy.
I'm sick, Peter.
I'm so sick about this.
Daddy just called me
from a pay phone drunk
and in tears.
I know what you think.
I just wanted to wait till
our anniversary to tell you.
I don't care, Trudy.
I don't care how I heard.
Oh, Peter.
How did this happen?
What did the doctor say?
He said I was
going to have a baby.
I want to pick you up
and spin you around,
But I don't want
to damage anything in there.
I'm so happy you're happy.
I don't know.
It feels much different
than I expected.
How would you know
what this feels like?
Come, get off your feet.
- How are you feeling?
- Oh.
Tell me you'll
forgive my father.
They already think
you hate them
And, honestly, it's my fault.
I don't hate them.
I shouldn't have taken
my mother to the doctor...
not that doctor.
It's just I thought
something was going on,
And I was so prepared
to be disappointed
Or that, God forbid,
something was really wrong.
Trudy, I had to talk to him
Because the agency has
to drop clearasil.
- Why?
- There's another product
that's similar
- And we can't...
- a conflict.
Peter, I'm familiar
with the term.
You use it all the time.
I invited him there
And his good news
trumped my bad news.
And the funny thing is,
that was the moment
to tell him.
I was so bowled over.
We did it.
Why don't you
let my father
hear this from me?
He's already so guilty,
he'll never feel
the knife go in.
I can't let you do that.
But I'm the one
who talked him into returning
to the agency to begin with.
- We needed him.
- And now you don't.
He'll be fine.
Tomorrow night.
Yankee pot roast.
Let's go. Caroline will
be watching your desk.
Why don't you have to do this?
You don't have to do this.
You're getting paid.
We're old and we're married.
They don't want us.
But I use pond's.
I do.
Come on.
Girls, find your places.
Megan, help me
with the curtains.
No matter how late
I come, I'm always
waiting for someone.
I had to wait
until the girls left
the ladies' room to change.
You could've
used my office,
but I don't have one.
- This isn't right.
- I thought you wanted "Faye,"
not "Dr. Miller."
Yes, but I told
someone to leave
the "e" off of "Faye."
I like to be able to correct
it in front of the girls.
It makes them trust me.
Because your name
is spelled wrong?
Because I'm obviously
not that important.
I don't need it.
- I have to warn you...
there's lots of perfume.
- There always is.
Why, everyone has
a nifty name tag.
Very well then.
I suppose I'll work
in Mr. Sterling's office.
He won't be coming.
As I said, my name is Faye.
I don't have a name tag.
I guess they forgot about me.
Well, they got mine wrong.
I'm dotty.
I mean I'm not a dotty person.
That's my name.
Hello, dotty.
So there's no reason
to be anxious.
We have to enjoy the fact
that we're all getting paid
not to work for a little bit.
But don't worry,
that's our little secret.
And I'd like you
to think that this is
Just a bunch
of your friends,
As if maybe
this is a sorority
Or a bridal shower...
With tea.
Or just a bunch
of us celebrating, say,
Allison's birthday
at my apartment.
You shouldn't be surprised,
Looking around the room,
That we're here to talk about
Beauty.
What are the things we all do
To keep ourselves beautiful
Or simply to enhance it?
Please pass a Danish.
You don't have
to raise your hand.
Anyone?
I can say it.
I have a routine.
I brush my hair 100 times
Just like I did
when I was a little girl,
But of course
only the night before
I have it set.
- Very cute.
- Can you imagine?
Your financial future's
in the hands
Of a roomful
of 22-year-old girls.
Not mine.
Okay.
Sometimes I watch my weight.
No one's hungry?
I'd like a Danish.
I don't use pond's if
that's what you're asking.
Mmm, that's okay.
I'm of French extraction
and my mother has
beautiful skin.
She never washes her face.
She's not dirty.
She uses water,
but nothing else.
And you do what she does?
What does she do?
She stands at the sink
and she runs the water
Until it's just
the perfect temperature...
not too hot.
And she splashes it on her face
And she pats her cheeks
with her fingertips.
And she looks at herself?
Yes, she does.
She's amazing.
I sit at my vanity
And I have this night cream...
My boyfriend laughed at me.
What was so funny about it?
It was just,
you know, one time.
At Christmas eve
we were staying up late
And we were
playing house, I guess.
You shouldn't
do things for them.
They don't appreciate it.
You don't think
they appreciate
you being beautiful?
We broke up a year ago.
Actually, I don't know
what he noticed,
But it wasn't me, I guess.
It's worse when
they notice, sometimes.
Allison, please continue.
It... it's nothing.
- Are you in there?
- Yes.
I asked your girl to
inform me of your arrival.
She's in that group.
Did you speak with Tom?
I'm sorry.
It didn't happen.
The opportunity passed.
Well, then we shall
endeavor to recreate it.
Perhaps lunch today?
I'm afraid Roger has
already informed pond's
That this was attended to.
That's sloppy.
I have a lunch,
but I'm seeing him tonight.
Damn it.
Lane.
I just found out
I'm going to be a father.
Well now, that should
take the sting out
of all of this.
I suppose.
Uh, I apologize.
That's the very best news.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
And I just kept thinking
"why does he stare
at other girls?"
Well, men do that, but...
But does he look
at me that way?
And we're not married,
so who am I?
How the hell did
this get so sad so fast?
- Shh!
I know I'm speaking
For everyone here.
You can't think
it has anything to do
With how
you look, dotty.
You can only do your best
With what God gave you.
What about makeup?
I feel like
it doesn't matter
what I see.
It matters what he sees.
I feel like
I gave him everything
- And I got nothing.
I could see
she was gonna crack.
Allison?
Are you
all right, dear?
- It's okay.
She'll be all right.
- Should I...
If she wanted
to be around us,
she would've stayed.
Sarah, what do you do
that makes you feel good
about the way you look?
I feel kind
of responsible.
Do you mind?
Is there any
kind of ritual?
I think my strategy was right.
They just want to get married
And they'll buy
anything that'll help.
- Are you all right?
- Oh, it's you.
Come with me.
People cry in these things
all the time... grown men.
I was in a bunch when I
first started working here.
I'd say half the time
somebody cries.
Really?
I think it just
feels good to talk.
I can't even say anything
Because I know
he's right out there,
Right through the glass.
Who?
I don't know how you stand it.
The way he turns on
the charm one minute
And then yanks it away.
How can you even talk to him?
Don?
Would you stop it?
I realize you must've
gone through everything
I've gone through.
But now I know.
It's just... he's a drunk.
And they get away
with murder because
they forget everything.
I don't know what you think.
Forget it.
Your problem is not my problem.
- Fine.
- And honestly,
you should get over it.
please leave me alone.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
- Did she go home?
- No, she's fine.
Nothing else good happened.
- Bye now.
- Bye-bye.
That went very well.
You can stop the tape.
Is she okay
- Who?
- Yeah, she's fine.
All right. Let's talk
preliminary results.
Is it all right
if we put this back
the way it goes?
- We can go to my office.
- Let's go in there.
That's big big news.
If you need any baby crap,
Jen and I have a closetful.
- Hello, fellas.
- Good to see you, Kenny.
- Pete.
- How are you, Ken?
- Mr. Crane.
- Over here, Gil.
There's a phone call for you.
I've gotta get this.
Those goniffs at c.B.S.
Are screwing me again.
- Those what?
- Order for me...
Caesar salad, no dressing.
- Ah.
- You want to take a look?
Sure.
Listen. I've got to
get this out of the way.
But I would appreciate it
for the future
If you would not
say shitty things
about me behind my back.
What?
Come on. Are you gonna
deny it and make it worse?
I don't know
what you've heard,
but it's not true.
You didn't call me
an all-American idiot
Who fell into everything?
Whom did I supposedly
say this to?
Does it matter?
Well, I'd like
to defend myself.
I heard that you told
your wife that I was
driving the tractor
- When the accident happened.
- What?
I don't think so.
What I probably said was
that you were involved...
We all were...
and that it was
your account.
And crane told me
yesterday you said
I was marrying for money.
I didn't say that.
He did.
Well, he's like that
and everybody who knows
him knows that.
But when you say it...
and especially when it
gets back to my fiancee...
Trudy knows her,
you know... some garden club.
I was unaware of that.
Look. You know what?
I apologize...
mea culpa.
That's textbook Harry.
You know what?
He's buying lunch.
I don't really care.
I'm just glad to be
out of the office.
Mmm, it is nice,
especially without
having to listen
To some client yammering
about how dirty the city is.
- Huh.
- How's it going?
I've been
floating along laterally,
But I don't know
that it's a love affair.
- It's better than McCann.
- What was that like?
Are you kidding me?
It's the worst agency
I've ever seen.
The worst.
My mother was
a nurse at the state
hospital in Vermont
And that was the last time
I saw so many retarded people
in one building.
So you're getting married.
Congratulations.
It's all that
really matters, right?
Actually, I have
a bit of news of my own.
Trudy is with child.
Good for you.
I'll be honest...
I can't wait.
It's very good so far.
Hmm. A new family,
a new agency...
It has to be exciting.
Well, you know,
wherever you do this job,
You're doing this job.
I know you're all slaves
to draper over there,
But I'd rather be
a slave to creative
than some old fart.
Whoever pours
the last drink gets
all the credit
And you're spinning
your wheels half the time.
Right now we're
chasing mountain dew.
Supposedly we're going
to turn it into Pepsi,
But the only reason
Pepsi would do it
Is to make b.B.D.O. Sweat.
This whole idea that we'd get
the bigger company is a joke.
We'd just end up with
a bunch of little pieces.
Well, the grass is
always greener.
Oh, who am I kidding?
Look how lucky we are.
Another Campbell...
That's just what
the world needs.
- Can I come in?
- It's your office.
Glad to see
you're feeling better.
If you don't feel
like working...
What?
I'm very embarrassed.
People cry in those groups
all the time, Allison.
That's not what
I'm embarrassed about.
This actually happened.
I know.
We made a mistake
And I feel like it's awkward
And it's better
for both of us
if I move on.
I don't think
that's necessary.
We're both adults.
No, I really would
feel better about it.
A friend of mine told me
about a job at a magazine
And I thought that
might be interesting,
working for a woman.
Anyway, I...
I would appreciate it
if you could write me
a recommendation.
Absolutely.
What would probably
be even better
Is if you type up
whatever you want
and I'll sign it.
- What?
- You've been sparkling
in your duties.
Just put it on my stationery,
put whatever you want
and I'll sign it.
I don't say this easily,
But you're not a good person.
Allison, hold on.
What's going on?
I'm gonna need a new secretary.
And this cleaned up.
Would you be open
to Allison returning
in a couple of days?
If that's what she wants.
Really?
No.
There's a Joyce Ramsey
to see you at reception.
So at this point you've
read everything out here?
I don't even like magazines,
But I brought in
a book and they told me
it didn't look right.
Hi.
Do you want
to come back
and see my office?
Another time.
Listen, my friend
the photographer,
Mr. Reject,
he's having a...
I don't even know
what to call it...
downtown.
Are you inviting me?
- Are you afraid
of the subway?
- Of course not.
Thanks, sweetheart.
Washington market,
Unless you have to work
or have plans that are
more interesting.
It starts at 9:00.
I'll be there at 10:00.
She's kind of pretentious.
I know.
darling, we're
so excited.
Is that you, Peter?
I'm gonna keep
my mouth shut from now on.
Well, hello there.
How are you feeling?
A little behind.
Why don't you let me fix
my father and you a drink
And you can show my mother
what we have planned
for the maid's room.
I'll make the drinks.
I don't care.
No, why don't you show
your mother the maid's room?
I don't know
that I'm an expert.
Oh, okay.
Come along, mother.
We're a couple
of lucky ducks,
aren't we?
We are. Tom, let me
ask you something.
- What are you having?
- In a minute. Listen...
Oh, I know what
you're gonna say.
You need a bigger
apartment. I get it.
Every time you jump
to conclusions, Tom,
you make me respect you less.
- What?
- Look.
You gave us clearasil
and we're extremely
grateful,
But there's only
so much business
it's going to do.
Yeah, well, that's kind
of in your hands, isn't it?
I'm done auditioning.
You gave us this
under a certain pretext.
I've done well by you.
And the idea was
If we do well by this account,
You'll give us a shot
at the big one,
Because right now
I have bigger business
than clearasil.
Are you mad at me?
No. Clearasil was
conflicted out by
a bigger company
And I'm trying to build
a business here.
Well, what do you want?
Do you want the cough syrup?
I want all of it. I want
the formula 44 mixture,
The cough drops,
the inhaler, Vaporub.
Who's doing a better job
for you than I have?
Well, you've given me
something to think about.
Really?
I think it's pretty simple.
What can I get you?
Trudy, do we have any ice?
You son of a bitch.
Tom, you have
to come see this.
Joyce!
- I made it.
- You look so elegant.
Okay.
Peggy works
in the same building.
Sharon was one
of Davey's models.
What did your mother say?
Oh, she doesn't know.
- What is that?
- He screws around
with movies too.
He's not as good at it.
I can't believe
how big this place is.
I think it was a sweatshop.
Is there beer or something?
I thought I saw
someone with a beer.
Jesus.
I thought I needed
a lot of attention.
Listen, I'm already high,
But this is easier
than finding a beer.
If you'd like?
I'd love it.
Hey!
I'm hungry.
I have a boyfriend.
He doesn't own your vagina.
No, but he's renting it.
This film is
more interesting
than I thought.
It's rhythmic.
Yeah.
I thought I was gonna
get to meet him.
Abe!
Where the hell's Kellogg?
Hey. Abe.
- Are you with Joyce?
- Are you?
- I'm Peggy.
- Peggy's a writer.
So am I.
What do you write?
I'm a copywriter.
But what do you write?
That is writing.
You're not working
on something else?
Davey Kellogg,
this is Peggy Olson.
- She wanted to meet you.
- I'm catholic.
So do you like it?
I don't think I'm supposed to.
I love your nudes.
We're looking for
photographers.
I'm glad I was here
to see this.
- Who's "we"?
- I work at sterling
Cooper draper Pryce...
- Advertising.
- Why would I ever do that?
So you can get paid
to practice your art.
Art in advertising?
Why would anyone
do that after Warhol?
Sorry, for somebody
to sell their soul,
- They've got to have one.
- It's a raid!
- It's the N.Y.P.D.!
This way.
Wait wait.
This is the N.Y.P.D.! Stop!
- Nobody move!
you know, I've been
arrested before.
for what?
I was writing about
this boycott in Harlem
And they wouldn't leave,
so I didn't leave.
Oh. Did you
go to jail?
No.
My sister came and got me.
I feel like I should kiss you.
Come on.
They chased everybody
down the fire escape.
- Are they beating people?
- They took the film.
I should see this.
It could be a story.
- How can I find you?
- I know where she is.
Nice to see you,
miss Blankenship.
I look forward
to hearing that every day.
There's coffee
and a roll on your desk
And Mr. Sterling would
like to see you.
Roger, he's here.
Could you get the others?
Blankenship? Boy.
Hello?
Could you fetch Campbell
And Pryce, lane...
misters.
What did you do
to make them take her
out of mothballs?
She was working
in Cooper's apartment.
Allison found
a better opportunity.
Do you know he works
without pants?
Morning, don.
- Don.
- Morning.
I'd like to say
in front of this
informal partners' meeting
That I am in the midst
of signing Vicks chemical...
The entire cough line.
It bills at around $6 million
- And they love television.
- It's truly spectacular news.
Congratulations.
How'd you swing that?
I guess as
the president would say,
I turned chickenshit
into chicken salad.
I thought I'd kick
clearasil over to geyer.
Anyone but Chaough.
We're taking Philip Coakmeyer
and Tom Vogel to luncheon today.
Don't worry,
we already checked it
with your, uh, girl.
- Keep it up.
- Thank you, don.
Please reschedule
Dr. Miller.
They're not really
pornography, per Se.
They're just nudes.
They're like
renaissance paintings.
The party sounds fun.
We had nude models
in school.
You know right away whoever
has the best drawing
is going to get her.
Did you know Malcolm x
was shot last Sunday?
Yes, Peggy.
Did you know who he was?
You ever read the stuff
between the ads?
A few of us are sending
a bottle of champagne
to the Campbells.
I'll sign the card.
- I was hoping
for a contribution.
- No thank you.
- Trudy's pregnant?
- Mm-hmm.
I can't believe
that guy's married
to her.
I would get her so pregnant.
Hello.
Congratulations.
Yes.
A $6-million account should
shut lane up for a while.
No, I mean about the baby.
Yes. I guess
that's news.
I just wanted
to let you know
how happy I am for you...
Both.
Thank you.
Dr. Miller
is here to see you.
It's a she.
Send her in.
- What do you want?
- Nothing. I moved
the meeting.
Oh, your secretary
said you needed to
see me immediately.
We're still working things out.
Well, I've done everything
but finish the report.
How'd we do?
Well, it turns out
the hypothesis was rejected.
I'd recommend
a strategy that links
Pond's cold cream
to matrimony...
A veiled promise.
Hello, 1925.
I'm not gonna do that,
So what are we gonna
tell the client?
I can't change the truth.
How do you know
that's the truth?
A new idea is something
they don't know yet,
So of course it's not gonna
come up as an option.
Put my campaign
on TV for a year,
Then hold your group again,
maybe it'll show up.
Well, I tried everything.
I said "routine."
I tried "ritual."
All they care about
is a husband.
You were there.
I'll show you
the transcripts.
You can't tell how people
are going to behave
Based on how they have behaved.
Why are you being so hostile?
You think I've never had
this argument before?
Because you go in there
and you stick your finger
in people's brains
And they just start talking...
blah blah blah...
just to be heard.
And you know what?
Not only does it have
Nothing to do with what I do,
but it's nobody's business
Well, you're the client.
That's right.
- Hello.
- It's Joyce.
Lunch,
five minutes.
Um, sure.
- Meet you in the lobby?
- No, my friends want
to see Megan.
Pete, you remember
Phil Coakmeyer.
- A pleasure
to see you again.
- Shall we?
We're just waiting on don.
Hi.
- You want to join us?
- I can't.
- Did you get pears?
Did you get pears?
We'll discuss it inside.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com