We're making you Head of Accounts.
- Previously on Mad Men.
- Spectacular.
- Excuse me.
- You're now Head of Accounts.
You've been engaged from 2 months
and you're not making wedding plans.
I had your baby and I gave it away.
I don't know
why I pick the wrong boys.
My father has a stroke.
Lord knows Don could afford to build him
a house in his backyard if he wanted to.
Stop calling other people money.
- He's leaving me.
- I want you to be my wife.
It's business going on
and I'm not invited.
Synchro: Hutch
Mad Men S03E02
- Love Among The Ruins -
Is there more? I love her.
I saw Susan Watson
do it on Broadway.
She was great,
but she didn't have that.
It's not going to be her, but they want
that scene frame for frame, as they say.
So something about how desperate
she is for a Pepsi?
It's for Pepsi, but it's not for Pepsi.
It's called Patio,
and it's a dieter's kind of Pepsi
to help women reduce.
It's Pepsi's diet-rite cola,
and there's claims
that their lawyers went over...
Calories, et cetera,
if we do it right, we land Patio.
And if we land Patio,
I'll be at lunch with Pepsi.
I think Pete Campbell
just broke a sweat.
I'm coming to casting.
We're going right to casting?
You don't have to
if you don't want to.
I understand why you like this,
but it's not for you.
I'm the one who would
be buying Patio.
You're not fat anymore.
Thank you.
Let's assume we can't talk them
out of the name
and let's assume we can get
a girl who can match
Ann Margret's ability
to be 25 and act 14.
Is that what she's doing?
Is it just a knock-off?
Are we allowed
to make fun of it, at least?
She's fun and sexy.
Don't be a prude.
Would you say that to me?
It's sexy, and it's what they want.
Clients don't always
know what's best.
When we land them, you can
start talking to them that way.
Pick it up.
Bobby, back away from the stove.
We're out of Melba toast.
Jesus, Betts, have some oatmeal.
That baby's gonna weigh a pound.
Carla must have had some,
because I would have
thrown the box away.
Are we gonna collect the whole set?
I thought you didn't mind
her doing the legwork.
You didn't need
a decorator last time.
I'd like to feel like
I'm paying for something.
These are $3 a piece, you know.
And I can't really judge
by a picture.
I'm late.
We should really spend
a day in Tarrytown.
It'd be so easy.
- No.
- Those stores smell bad.
We are going to Tarrytown...
And you're going to stare at
some antique chair for so long
the buttons are
gonna seem interesting,
and then we'll go to carvel.
See you tonight.
What are you doing?
I hope you received the package showing
our campaign to ease the way
for the Ravenswood
nuclear power facility.
Kinsey was responsible for that.
Almost a year and nary
a peep of opposition.
It was very impressive.
I've told Paul
that you're facing an onslaught
of negative public opinion
in your attempt to demolish the
Pennsylvania railroad station this year
and replace it with the new
Madison Square Garden.
We should've torn the damn thing down
during the newspaper strike.
No one would have noticed.
Now let's take a look at
the landscape, as it were.
"Save Penn station."
"Rape on 34th street."
"Stop fascism!"
"How to kill a city."
"Architects' inhumanity to architects
surpasses understanding."
"The new design is also ambitious,
pedestrian and dull."
Ada Louise Huxtable is
as green as that folder.
People know that she's an angry
woman with a big mouth.
Who writes for
"The New York Times."
I don't care if she wrote
for the 10 commandments.
She's trying to sell papers
doing what they always do...
Making people miserable.
My great-great-grandfather, Silustagman,
would have turned his boat around
if he had known that this city would
one day be filled with crybabies.
So what's your best weapon
against lunatics?
15 stories,
vaulted ceilings, pink milford
granite columns...
I don't think it's crazy to be attached
to a beaux-arts masterpiece
through which Teddy Roosevelt
came and went.
I've met the opposition.
I know crazy.
Do you know where the greatest
roman ruins are?
They're in Greece, Spain,
because the romans tore
theirs all down.
They took apart the Coliseum
to build their outhouses.
This is the Coliseum.
Have you seen the plans?
In "The New York Times."
- Do you have a problem, buddy?
- He's looking for an angle.
You know those snide ad men
you see in the movies?
Right here.
I've got a mailbox full
of death threats from beatniks
like him who'd rather
live in a teepee.
This is the greatest city in the world.
If you don't like it, leave.
We'll let you know.
You have no problems with an atom plant
on the east river, but this bothers you?
It's Penn station.
This city has no memory.
Out with the old, in with the new
who says that's a good idea?
I'm going to have
to talk to Don about this.
Don't do that.
Look.
Now they'll trust me more
when I help them.
Do you ever listen to yourself?
I hate you. You know that.
Other than Wilma Flintstone,
I haven't seen anyone carry so well.
It's smoke and mirrors.
I've busted plenty of seams.
It makes me optimistic.
Greg has made it perfectly clear
that come July 1
and he's chief resident,
I'd better watch out.
Hello, Mrs. Draper.
Can you get Mrs. Draper
a glass of water?
Why don't you tell me first
how long I'm going to be here?
What's so urgent?
London Bridge falling down?
In a manner of speaking.
I appreciate you stopping by.
Didn't you just call us
to your office?
Yes. I thought it best
if I told you in person.
I just heard from London. We've been
sacked by Campbell soup, Great Britain.
I don't want to have to walk down here
every time we lose an account.
This is an advertising agency.
I'll wear out the carpet.
It's not so much
the account we lost
as the account we failed to gain.
So now B.B.D.O. has
all of Campbell's soup?
Why didn't we have
a meeting with them?
Perhaps I should drag Burt Peterson
in and fire him again?
Obviously Don would've
loved the shot.
How did this slip
through the cracks?
I don't usually set meetings,
I attend them.
If this is where we wanted to end up,
we all did everything perfectly.
You ever get three sheets to the wind
and try that thing on?
Mrs. Pryce is here.
Nothing to fret about as long as
there's new business.
Five minutes?
It's definitely side to side.
Is that a boy or a girl?
I'll call my mother.
Look.
Princess Grace just
swallowed a basketball.
- How are you, Roger?
- It's not hard to adjust to happiness.
Shall we?
Good night, Mrs. Harris.
I'm in a foul mood.
Chateau Fafite Rothschild'49.
I'm very impressed
that you have this.
Not bad at that.
- Where are you living?
- We have a finished flat in sutt place.
Three bedrooms, spectacular view
of the river.
And we're near the U.N.,
so there's plenty of africans.
Like the Bordeaux grape,
may we all get better with time.
This is delicious.
Rebecca was curious if you knew
anything about schools.
In the city,
I'm a little out of touch.
How long have you been together?
- 10 years.
- Nine years.
15 for us.
Do you miss London?
God, yes.
But what we lost in London
we gained in insects.
J. Walter Thompson is
opening an office in Caracas.
I don't know if the ladies want
to talk about that.
No, of course not.
The cookie.
Brilliant.
Look, I didn't want to be there
any more than you did.
It was just the cherry
on top of my sundae.
What?
Tell me now and not three seconds
after I've dozed off.
I've been trying to get
my father on the phone.
Of course I called william and,
again, something's wrong.
Another stroke?
Gloria left him.
- Can you blame her?
- Yes, I can blame her.
She came into his life,
he suddenly takes ill
and she abandons him.
Maybe she realized
he's a son of a bitch.
Don, I'm worried about him.
He doesn't sound right,
and I can't take a car trip now.
I think William and Judy should
bring him up this weekend.
Great, more antiques.
It's spring break.
It'll be nice for the kids.
Those girls are a nightmare.
They'll leave
by Saturday at the latest.
Why did you even bother asking me?
She's really kicking.
Mr. Sterling, your family is here.
Send them in.
If it isn't fall bride.
- Where's Brooks?
- He'll be along.
- Would anyone like anything? Coffee...
- It's 10:30.
Sherry if you have it.
I told Brooks to come late.
I don't want him to be embarrassed.
By what, that I'm paying
for anything?
You just tell him...
That's the way it's done.
No, Roger, it's about Jane.
What about her?
It was her idea
to take you to Dior.
Why haven't you returned her calls?
You're hurting her feelings.
I know what you think.
You think it's so uncomfortable that
I won't even bring it up.
You're being very dramatic for a girl
who didn't want a wedding at all.
Do you want me to say it?
Do I have to say it?
Say what exactly?
I suggested to Margaret
a compromise.
You and Jane host your own table
and I'll be at the Hargroves'.
So you get T in-laws
and I get Siberia.
Are you worried about an odd number?
Because I'll get your mother a date.
- I have a date.
- Who?
- Bruce Pike.
- What does that old Saddlebag want?
I didn't want to go
to her wedding, but I did.
The least she can do
is not come to mine.
- Not come?
- That's why I suggested a compromise.
You're not even giving
Jane a chance.
Seeing her on my wedding day
is gonna ruin it.
She's young enough to be my sister.
How does it look?
- Sweetheart.
- Brooks! Thank God.
Mom.
- How are you, sir?
- Not great, Brooks.
Not great.
- Can I get you something?
- No.
That's okay. I'll have yours.
We're not married
anymore, you know.
I like the silver and the bells.
Go with the bells.
November 23rd.
I'll tell Jane.
Mr. Pryce is here to see you.
Send him in.
Your wife is charming.
She lifted Rebecca's
spirits inestimably.
I'm glad to hear it.
They really hit it off.
I hate to send you
into the Lion's den,
but I think it best
you take the gentleman
from Madison Square Garden
to a nice lunch today.
Peter and Paul rubbed him
very much the wrong way.
I told you before
Roger's the lion tamer.
Roger will join as well.
It will help if you tell me
who these people are.
All I could secure
was Edgar Raffit,
vice president
of Madison Square Garden,
and he's irate.
What does he want?
A Cyrano De Bergerac to make
New York fall in love with him.
- Today?
- Do you have plans?
Have Campbell send over the folder.
Wild indians.
They've been cooped up
since woodbridge.
I fixed some lunch.
Cold roast chicken
or I have cold cuts.
We went to Pat's steaks.
I got you a half.
- Have you all already eaten?
- No, we waited.
I even got Gloria
a chicken parmesan.
Great.
We'll mail it to her.
She's in Boca Raton.
She's not coming back.
He understands completely.
He's just playing it up.
- How was the drive, daddy?
- In the Lincoln?
You should take your Coumadin
with your sandwich.
So I said to them,
"it's so crowded in here
"I feel like I'm on the subway."
I've never seen anyone
like you on the train.
My husband won't let me.
It's a figure of speech.
Have a seat and I'll let Mr. Pryce
know that you're here.
Sorry about that. I got tied up.
What else do you have to do today?
- What else do you have to do all week?
- I barely made it here.
Ginger presses the buzzer,
says "your family's here."
Sounds silly.
Gibson, up.
Like that's gonna help.
To my knees, Don.
They're bringing me to my knees.
Sorry to hear that.
I made my bed,
I should lie in it, right?
Your words, not mine.
Like it's not hard enough losing
my little girl to that kid.
I've got her mother pouring
poison in her ear.
There's a land grab going on.
I blame Mona.
All of a sudden, I could give
two craps about that wedding.
All I want to do is win.
Gentlemen.
A pleasure to meet you.
Roger Sterling.
- Ed Raffit.
- Our creative Director Don Draper.
Have a seat, please.
Let's get you fixed up.
- I only have a minute.
- Edgar, please.
Eat our sweetmeats, drink our wine.
I understand one of our copywriters
took a yetta wallenda-
Sized misstep.
The girl, the tightrope walker.
They got her off the sidewalk
with a hose last week.
The point is we completely
understand your problem.
All we want to know
is how we can help.
You're supposed to tell me.
I've done all I can. Don?
In the interest of time,
you want to demolish Penn station
and New York hates it.
Not all of New York,
a vocal minority.
Can they stop it?
I think all the hubbub is making
it unpleasant for...
But they can't stop it, can they?
Why do you people insist on making us
sound like villains?
Your concern over public opinion
shows a guilty conscience.
Now what good is that serving you
if what is to be done
is already underway?
Leave those.
Bring a couple of iceberg wedges,
bleu cheese, bacon.
So let's say I don'thave
a guilty conscience.
Good.
And let's also say that change
is neither good or bad,
it simply is.
It can be greeted
with terror or joy...
A tantrum that says
"I want it the way it was"
or a dance that says
"look. It's something new."
Would you draw the line at 50%?
I'm not drawing a line at all.
P.R. people understand this,
but they can never execute it.
If you don't like
what is being said,
change the conversation.
What is that conversation?
I was in California.
Everything is new and it's clean.
The people are filled with hope.
New York city is in decay.
Madison Square Garden
is the beginning
of a new city on the hill.
- Just like that?
- It's true, isn't it?
If I were to come to you,
I don't want
that kid on my account...
The communist, the radical.
I will handle it personally.
Grandpa Gene is gonna watch
his program now.
I just want to catch
the end of the game.
Move.
Daddy seems well.
He has an appetite.
He eats constantly.
When I found out Gloria was gone,
I was hoping he ate her.
How could you not know about that?
I went by, but he lied to me.
Then finally, when I let myself in,
he went bananas.
He's ashamed.
- Judy can get through to him.
- He's down in the dumps,
but he seems very clear-headed.
That's not true, Judy,
and you know it.
He's angry and he's in and out.
There is this place...
The Parker home.
It's midway between us
in New Brunswick.
And what happens there?
He lives there.
It's got everything, plus doctors.
It's expensive,
but I thought maybe
we could sell our house.
That would give him
enough to live on.
That's very generous.
Do you think he belongs in a home?
- Betty, I know I don't get a vote.
- Neither does Don.
All you care about is the house.
You want to walk in there,
see daddy on the bottom of the stairs
and have his last words
be "take the house."
Fine, Betts.
What's the solution?
Those homes are for people who don't
have families.
He's a lonely old man
and he's not well.
He's your father.
Thanks for
the ritzy accommodations.
You're an army man, gene.
Drop your socks and grab something.
Lights out at 8:15.
I'm impressed.
I wish you would hang
your coat up downstairs.
It's covered with soot.
How bad is he?
He's not the problem.
What am I saying?
He's the whole problem...
That and William's
never-ending bullshit.
What now?
He wants to put him
in an old folks home.
I understand it's not ideal,
but it is the next logical step.
Don, he just wants the house.
He keeps nailing himself
to the cross.
For all I know, Judy's pushing him.
Cut it out.
What do you want to do?
How can he talk that way to me
in the condition I'm in?
- Do you want anything?
- Just throw it on the chair
and stay here.
Be careful.
I'm fine.
It's so funny... How she is.
My father and
her fought constantly.
She never remembers that part.
Family is important to her.
I care about family.
You know, Don had nobody
at their wedding.
Nobody at all.
Why can't we just move in with him?
I'll take care of him.
It's bad enough to work for him.
I'm a 30-year-old man.
I don't want to have somebody tell me
I have the wrong tie on.
Raffit is sending over
every piece of paper
they have on the new garden.
He wants you to see
these new drawings.
Apparently they're
right out of "Metropolis."
- Did he talk about television?
- I have a meeting on the books.
He talked a lot about radio...
And Kinsey.
You're gonna have to keep
a low profile on this,
but it doesn't mean
you're not working.
Mr. Pryce is here to see you.
I didn't realize you were
in the middle of something.
Did you come to treat us to
a little new-business lunch?
May I speak with you
in private, Don?
- Can I get you anything?
- No, thank you.
Bad news, I'm afraid.
I just got off
the phone with London.
There's a problem
with Madison Square Garden.
- Did their check bounce already?
- Unfortunately, there's a conflict.
Did you tell them it's a stadium
in the middle of New York city?
- It's one of a kind.
- They know exactly what it is...
A project...
And they told us to turn it down.
- I'm confused.
- It's a question of economics.
Servicing Madison Square Garden
will requirean account man,
at least two copywriters,
two artists, an ombudsman
to city hall... All against
200,000 in billings.
- That's for right now.
- Precisely.
From what I understand,
groundbreaking is two years away.
Madison Square Garden is
our way into the world's fair,
the largest trade show in history.
Plus there's the garden itself...
Hotels, concerts, sports.
- This could mean 30 years of business.
- They're not interested.
I'm sorry.
You told me to go out
and get this account.
I did. I did my job.
And now you're telling me
it's all for nothing
because you forgot to check
with your boss first?
- Who's running this place?
- I know this is difficult.
I take full responsibility.
Why the hell did you buy us
in the first place?
I don't know.
Tell Mr. Campbell
Madison Square Garden is dead.
- Do you have a second?
- Can it wait?
Sal sent up the storyboards.
What is this?
It's Patio,
the diet drink for Pepsi.
Yes. Everyone wants a drink
that sounds like a floor.
- This is chinese.
- It's all one shot,
like the beginning
of "bye bye birdie."
- I haven't seen it.
- Well, this is an Ann Margret type.
Fine.
You really haven't seen it?
You see everything.
We have a few versions of a song,
and the boys are very excited
about finding this girl.
I'm sure.
Don't you find her voice shrill?
Just throw yourself at the camera.
It's pure.
It makes your heart hurt.
No one seems to care
that it speaks to men,
not the people
that drink diet drinks.
What do the geniuses at Patio want?
Maybe we should be talking about how
this is better than coffee or dexedrine.
It's not about
making women feel fat.
This is
"Look how happy
I am that I drink Patio."
"I'm young, excited
and desperate for a man."
I don't mind fantasies,
but shouldn't it be a female one?
I know you understand
how this works.
Men want her.
Women want to be her.
- Even if that's true...
- It is.
I'm sorry if
that makes you uncomfortable.
You know if we were
making a movie or a play,
we'd be embarrassed
to do this. It's phony.
You're not an artist, Peggy.
You solve problems.
Leave some tools in your toolbox.
Could you hold that?
- Heading home?
- Yes.
Let me ask you something.
You're a young girl.
Excuse me?
You're the only one around here
who doesn't have that
stupid look on her face.
What does that mean?
What would your father have to do
for you to not want him
at your wedding?
My father passed away.
It's so crowded in here.
I feel like I'm on the subway.
Where's your drink?
Don't worry about this.
It's under control.
Hey, where's mom?
She's upstairs.
I'm going out
for a bucket of chicken.
What's the matter?
- I'm a horrible daughter.
- No, you're not.
William says these are the options:
we put him in a home
or they move in with him
and Judy is his nurse.
- Judy.
- William says?
He's probably right.
I'll go get
the chicken in a minute.
Can I speak to you a minute?
- What year is this from?
- I don't care.
Look, Don,
we're all upset.
One thing I've learned
from this... don't get old.
- About your father.
- It's a real jackpot.
He always said he didn't want
to be a burden,
and yet here we are.
This is what's going to happen.
You're going to explain
to your sister and your wife
that we have reached
an understanding.
You are going to support
your father financially
and I am going to take him
into my house.
His house will remain untouched.
I appreciate the advice, Don.
I'll take it under consideration.
You're gonna tell your sister
that this is what you want.
We'll pretend that you did
the right thing on your own.
- He's my father!
- And he's in my home.
I want you to leave tonight
and I want you to leave the Lincoln.
- I can't have him here without a car.
- Are you kidding me?
How are we supposed to get home?
New York Central...
broadway limited from Penn station.
It leaves in two hours.
You want him?
You got him.
Dad, we have to talk.
I could eat.
Daddy, William has
something to say.
All of us...
We've been trying to figure out
a way we can help you live better.
I'd be doing all right
if people left me alone.
Daddy...
Don and I want you
to live here with us.
Honey, I'm not that blue.
Just for a while.
I think you need a little vacation.
So the animals are running the zoo?
We're not selling the house,
and you're gonna have your car.
The plans, the plans,
the plans you make.
You know you want
to get out of town.
You'll be with the kids.
Betty is a better cook.
You always say that.
Well, I should've been
the first to go.
Daddy, don't talk like that.
We should go pack.
Girls, start getting
your things together.
It's nice, right?
It's called a Stinger.
- I don't know what's in it.
- It's delicious.
I'm graduating from
Brooklyn college next month.
What are you studying?
- What?
- What are you studying?
Do you want one?
I'm afraid you're
gonna bite my hand.
I'm sorry.
I just need to eat.
My mom says I'm still growing.
I've got to work on my manners.
I started pre-law,
but switched to engineering...
- More jobs.
- Really?
Those are so different.
You've gotta figure if we're all gonna
be replaced by machines,
might as well be a guy
that makes them, right?
Or you could just become a robot.
Are you in school?
I work at an ad agency,
Manhattan.
I don't know how you girls
do all that typing.
And I work for a jerk.
We're hitting the road.
You got cab fare?
What are you talking about?
I live around the corner.
That's right. He does.
Do you have,
you know...
What?
... a trojan?
I can't.
Jeez.
It's getting pretty late.
There are other things we could do.
Did you hear that?
The heat is on. We've gotta
get rid of this stuff.
You got anything else around,
go flush it.
You're leaving?
I have to work tomorrow.
- You want to get breakfast?
- It's the middle of the night.
Where do you work again?
Madison Avenue.
Well, you know, I hang out
at that place a lot.
It's the bottom one.
Thanks.
This was fun.
Parents, friends and family,
I'd like to welcome
you all to field day.
I hope you can appreciate
how hard the children
have prepared
in all kinds of weather.
"The tradition of the maypole
dates back over 500 years,"
"and is celebrated
all over the world."
"We erected our maypole
for ossining's"
"sesquicentennial."
"We dance around the pole"
"in a timeless celebration"
"of the renewal of springtime."
Okay, ribbons up.
Daddy!
- Did you see me dance?
- I did.
You were great.
Cindy's dad wants
to take our picture.
Say "cheese!"
- How was your morning, Mr. Draper?
- Fine.
- Do you want to talk about Pampers?
- What you got?