- Previously on This Is Us...
- (whispering): Hello?
RON : Hey, Kevin, uh,
it's Ron Howard calling.
Um, I'm prepping a movie
right now that I'm gonna direct.
You would be perfect.
I would?
Can you do that?
- JACK : What are you doing?
- RANDALL : If I can find people
who roll their tongue,
they could be my birth parents.
You know we have
to tell the girls, right?
We're gonna foster a kid, bring
another child into the home.
They need to know about it.
What if we get a kid
that has serious issues
that we're not prepared for?
I'm worried.
I have been drunk
for weeks.
And I need to get a handle on it
before I can walk back into that house.
If you have a problem,
we will fix it together.
You know, you never really talk
about your dad's death.
(crying)
KATE : We-we have to find Kev.
He needs to hear it from me.
JACK : It's been three weeks now.
And, um...
I finally feel like
I'm tackling this thing for real.
So that's good.
I know I'm supposed to talk
more to you guys,
um, really bare my soul.
(laughs softly)
Feels like you get extra
credit around here for...
for crying. (Chuckles)
Um...
I-I promised my wife
that we would talk more,
this time.
But, um...
I'm finding that harder to do.
(insects chirping)
Hmm.
REBECCA : Hi.
Are you coming up soon?
Yeah, I'm...
I'm almost done, just doing my steps.
Okay.
- Well, I'll see you up here.
- Okay.
JACK : I know that men,
we're supposed to talk
about their issues nowadays.
You know, the strong
silent type is out, and...
and guys like that sensitive kid
on My So-Called Life are in.
(chuckles)
At least, that's what
my daughter taught me.
Um...
But I've gone this way
for a very long time.
REBECCA : Hey.
Sleep, baby. You need to go to bed.
I will.
- Is everything okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Good night.
JACK : I've got two sons, though.
(typing)
Still young.
So I-I hope they don't end up
cavemen like me.
You know, I hope that if
something's-something's
weighing them down,
I hope that they don't
keep it bottled up.
(exhales)
♪
synced and corrected by susinz
^.^.^.^.COLORED by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com
Mm. Something smells good.
Marinara?
It's been three weeks, Beth.
Three weeks since we've
been approved to foster.
Oh, damn. Bolognese.
I love it when you cook your feelings.
I just don't understand
what's taking so long.
Right? We got a bedroom set up.
Got the girls on board.
Look at this place.
There's two staircases,
kitchen island the size of Maui.
Yeah, 'cause kids in need love them
some big old kitchen islands.
- Don't... mm...
- (phone ringing)
- Mm. Do not get excited.
- Hold on.
Okay, the last time you got
excited, it was Vanity Fair
calling to see if we wanted
to renew our subscription.
- I know. I didn't...
- And the time before that,
it was the wrong number
looking for "Johnny."
I know. We should get
rid of the landline.
So I'm gonna answer this phone, okay?
But I am sure it is not an agent
- calling with a kid for us.
- (whispers): Oh, my God.
- Answer the phone, woman.
- (chuckles)
Hello?
Yeah, this is she.
Okay.
(drawer opens)
(drawer closes, pen clicks)
Okay. Uh-huh.
Yeah. Great.
(laughs) All right, I'll see you soon.
Bye-bye.
- (pen clatters)
- Well?
Her name is Deja.
- As in "déjà..."
- Vu, yeah. She's 12 years old,
and she's been in and out of
foster care a bunch of times,
and her mom just got arrested,
so they moved her out of her home.
What about the dad?
They said we'll get
the case file in a couple days.
- And?
- And she's on her way over.
Wow.
This is it. It's happening, Beth.
I know, baby.
I really think that being a
foster parent was my calling.
Like that call was my calling calling.
- Randall...
- To honor my parents' legacy,
to honor William's life!
I know, it's very moving.
- But I want you to breathe...
- Mm-mm. Tess! Annie!
- (claps hands) Family meeting!
- ...breathe through it.
- KATE : This is so cool.
- KEVIN : I know.
KATE : Everybody looks, like,
busy and important.
Everybody on The Manny
just looked pasty and sad.
Well, that's comedy writers
for you, you know?
They don't get enough sun, so...
Anyway, thank you so much for coming
and hanging out with me today.
You know it means a lot to me, right?
Are you kidding?
I can't believe Sylvester
Stallone is in your movie.
I can't believe it, either. I know.
It's unbelievable.
So, so first up today,
we have this, like,
super emotional scene, right?
Right before we go
into battle, where I deliver
this epic monologue about how
every single thing in my life
has led up to this very moment.
Which is crazy, because
everything in your life
has led you to this moment.
I know. Right? And then,
tonight, we have this,
just, unbelievable
action sequence, right,
where I get to go in there and
save Sylvester Stallone's life?
Can you imagine?
I'm on a movie set, saving
Sylvester Stallone's life?
(Sylvester Stallone impression):
Every champion was once
a contender who refused
to give up. You...
SYLVESTER STALLONE : Not so bad.
- (laughs)
- Oh.
Oh, Lord. Ah, Mr. Stallone,
how are you?
- How are you?
- Kevin Pearson here. Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- KEVIN : Uh, AKA Lieutenant Booker.
- Mm.
- Please don't kick me off your set
for doing a horrendous
Rocky impression.
I think I'll let it slide.
Anyway, it's good to meet you,
- Kevin.
- Hey, good to meet you, too. I... oh!
- Uh, my sister Kate.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Pleasure. Pleasure to meet you.
- She's happy to meet you, too. Say hi.
- (chuckles)
- Hi.
- Sylvester Stallone.
- No. "Sly." Sly is good.
- Okay. Sly.
- Mm-hmm.
- (Kate giggles)
- Is... I'm starving.
I'm gonna go check out
the, uh, frittata situation
so I'll catch up with you guys later.
- KEVIN : All right.
- Nice to meet you, Kate.
Okay. You, too.
- Enjoy your frittata.
- Bye.
(Kevin chuckles)
(laughs)
- What just happened?
- I don't know.
Um, Sylvester Stallone knows my name.
You name has never sounded cooler.
Oh, my God, I wish Dad was here.
Ugh!
- Stallone was his hero.
- I know.
God, he would've been
- so proud of you, Kev.
- Right.
I mean, to see this set,
and all you've accomplished.
What you've gone through.
Yeah, but I mean, he-he can't
see it, though. Right?
So, uh...
Check that out. All right?
You know what we should do?
- Mm-mm.
- We should take a selfie in the tank.
Send it to Randall?
He'll get a kick out of that.
- Come on.
- All right.
KATE : He was like,
"Oh, call me Sly." What?
- Morning, everyone.
- Morning. -Morning.
REBECCA : Can I make you some breakfast?
No, I'm good.
I'm gonna get something along the way.
Okay.
Bye.
- KATE : Bye, Dad.
- KEVIN : See you.
Hmm.
KEVIN : Hey, Randall. Who do you think's
hotter, Brandy or Mariah Carey?
They're both really hot.
How are you playing
"Who's Hotter" right now?
Our family's falling apart.
Mom and Dad are barely talking.
Oh, my God, Kate. They're fine, okay?
Hey, Randall. Come on.
Would you tell her they're fine?
They're fine.
I got to run a... quick little errand.
I'll-I'll see you guys after school.
An errand?
I'm sorry, are you Mom?
(Kate chuckles)
Uh, I put an ad in the paper
looking for my birth parents.
Yeah.
This woman wrote back.
She says she's my mom.
Meeting her at Schenley Park.
Give me that.
KATE : Hi, Headless Soldier Number Two.
Are you following me?
- Mm-mm.
- (laughs)
Explain something to me.
Why do they always have to put melon
and fruit and things in the water
like, you know, like, there's, like,
swamp animals in there.
I remember when water... ready for this?
- Was just water. What happened?
- (laughs)
- I know, tell me about it.
- (laughs): I know.
- Anyway.
- Yeah.
Sylvester Stallone?
I don't want to take up
much of your time,
I just want to tell you that...
(exhales) ...you were our
dad's favorite actor.
- Oh, thank you.
- I mean, we watched
all your movies, like, a thousand times.
- Really? I appreciate that.
- Yeah. And seriously,
- I know Rocky by heart.
- So does Kevin.
And we would watch it
when we had a cold,
- when my dad had a cold, even...
- Really? You know what?
Why don't you bring your father
down to the set sometime?
Since he's such a fan and everything,
we'll take a picture.
It'd be my pleasure.
Oh, no, um...
Our dad actually died
when we were in high school.
- I'm s...
- So.
(exhales sharply)
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, thanks.
You know, you just
made my dad feel good.
You could help him forget
a 102 degree fever,
or a bad day at work.
I just, you know,
I just want to thank you
for making my dad feel good.
Thank you for telling me that.
You're welcome.
I really appreciate this.
- Very sweet.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Ah.
(chuckles)
- Hey.
- Hmm.
You don't really know
all of Rocky by heart, do you?
- You questioning me?
- (chuckles)
(singing "Gonna Fly Now" by Bill Conti)
"November 25th, 1975, Philadelphia."
- We pan down from the Jesus mural.
- Oh, come on.
- This is unbelievable. Yeah?
- Right? When you're,
- when you're in the ring.
- Yeah. I'm impressed.
- Okay.
- Okay. You're...
- Don't question me.
- "Yo, Adrian."
You're the new Adrian.
Oh, my God.
So, now I have Amber
Monday through Friday.
Miguel has her on the weekends.
And we bought Amber a car
so she would hate us less.
But, um, it's not working.
(chuckles)
I'm sure she's just
- adjusting, still.
- Mm...
So how have you and Jack been?
I mean, since your fight.
- We're fine.
- Yeah?
Yeah. I mean, we mumble "hello"
to each other in the morning,
and we, uh, kiss each other
good night before bed.
Mm.
When was the last time you had sex?
It's been a while.
- Becca...
- What?
- Have sex with Jack.
- (scoffs)
- It's not that simple.
- You're wrong.
I am telling you, if you let
so much time go by
that the answer to that question
is "It's been a while..."
That was the beginning
of the end for me and Miguel.
(sighs)
I mean, I guess I could plan...
- a night away from the kids.
- Yeah.
But the whole romantic
date night thing,
that's always been Jack's department.
SHELLY : So now it's your department.
Come on, just think of something.
Think of somewhere special to take him.
Do something. Put on a pretty dress.
Slap a big carefree smile on your face
and just sweep your
husband off his feet.
What's all this?
I'm Jack Pearsoning you.
That's a term I made up for when you
sweep someone off their feet.
Come on, get in the car.
That is so pretty, Annie.
She's gonna love it.
Okay, people, let's get
our game faces on.
Remember what we learned?
When she gets here, we'll
give her a tour of the house,
repeat our names a lot
so that she learns them,
keep asking if she has any questions.
It was on all the foster parents blogs.
How do you spell "Deja"?
D-E-J-A. I hope.
- (doorbell rings)
- RANDALL : Ah.
- (exhales) Here we go.
- Alright.
Hey there. Come in, please.
- LINDA : Hi, guys.
- BETH : Hi.
This is Deja.
RANDALL : Hi, Deja.
It's really nice to meet you.
I'm Randall.
I'm Beth.
We're so happy to have you here.
This is Tess and Annie.
- TESS : Hi.
- ANNIE : Hi.
Hi.
ANNIE : I made this for you.
(audio drops very low):
This is our snack drawer.
You can help yourself
to anything you want.
And the white board over there
is where we make our grocery lists.
So if you ever have
any special requests,
just put 'em down right there.
I want to go to bed.
Bed.
No, bed we can do.
I'm gonna leave you guys
to get to know each other.
Bye, Deja.
I'll walk you out.
Sorry, Linda? Is that it?
Are you just leaving?
'Cause I don't think she's okay.
That is correct.
- She is most definitely not okay.
- Okay.
She just got yanked out of her family,
plopped down with a bunch of strangers.
So, what do we do?
In most of the blogs I read,
the kids were a bit more responsive.
Well, I'd tell you, the...
the first night
is the hardest part, but I'd be lying.
You and your family,
you're doing a great thing.
Just be patient,
have zero expectations and...
don't try to predict
how a single day will turn out.
It's not exactly your temperament, huh?
- I'm working on it.
- (laughs)
Okay, you've got my number
if there's an emergency.
I'll reach out tomorrow
when we get her full file
- from Child Services.
- Okay. Thank you.
(exhales)
(indistinct conversation)
Whatever happens out there,
I will fight like hell
I will protect my men,
and I guarantee you,
by nightfall, I'll have you
back in your bunk
writing those dirty letters
that your wife likes so much.
You got my word on that.
Boom!
That's the one.
KATE : You really don't think
I'm too old?
No way.
I don't know if anyone
believes I, you know,
can make a living
at being a singer, so...
No, it really doesn't matter
what other people think.
Seriously. No.
I'll tell you what people didn't think.
They didn't think I could write Rocky
in three days... it happened.
I'll tell you something else, they
didn't think I could act in it.
Guess what, it happened.
Sometimes, people can be real idiots.
- Real idiots. Real.
- I'm telling you,
- it's, like, contagious.
- (laughs)
- Yo, yo. Guys.
- KATE : Hey.
- How are we?
- You got a great sister here.
Yes, I do. Thank you for noticing.
We like here a lot.
We're gonna keep her.
- KATE : Thank God.
- All right, guys, we are lit
- and ready for you on set, gentlemen.
- KEVIN : All right.
- Okay, great.
- Knock 'em dead.
- Will do.
- See you around.
- Okay.
- Here we go.
My sister didn't ask you
to sign anything, did she?
I had to beg her to leave her
Rambo figurines at home.
(chuckles)
We were just talking about her singing.
Yeah.
Yeah, she mentioned
your father a little bit.
He'd be really proud of you.
Look at this.
I keep hearing that, yeah.
Nah, it's got to be tough
not having him here.
- I get it.
- Yeah.
It was a long time ago,
you know, for me, so...
It's a funny thing,
when you think about it... time.
Your sister sings a couple
of bars of Rocky,
and for a split second
I can smell the ring again.
And then she tells me that
when you were little kids,
you watched a lot of my movies,
and I'm thinking for a
moment about my kids,
when they were little... the messy hair,
the matching pajamas
and all that stuff...
and I swear to you, I can see it all
so very clearly I could just
reach out...
...touch it.
In my experience, Kevin,
there's no such a thing
as "a long time ago."
There's only memories
that mean something
and memories that don't.
Right.
Let's do one for your father.
- Okay?
- Okay, you guys want to run the lines,
- or you want to just roll?
- Let's roll. Good?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
SLATE GUY : Scene 58, take one.
RON : And action.
Sir, first of all, I want to thank you
for everything.
And I want you to know...
I'm sorry, uh, I need a line, please.
WOMAN : "I want to thank you for
everything you've done for me.
And, sir, whatever happens..."
Got it. Okay. Thank you.
- Could we... Sorry.
- That's all right.
KEVIN : Sorry, Ron.
Could we get back into it?
Yeah, yeah, no problem. Just keep going.
RON : And action.
First of all, thank you, sir,
- Mm.
- ...for everything.
Uh...
Guys, can we... It's not, uh...
I can see all the, uh,
the movement back there.
- Sorry.
- (sighs)
- Nah, I heard it, too.
- Yeah.
Yeah, no problem. Just go from the top.
- Thank you.
- RON : Here we go... still rolling.
What's the word?
- The first word.
- "I."
"I wanted to thank you..."
Just the first word's all I needed.
Thank you, though,
for all the rest of them.
- All right.
- Sorry, guys.
I got you a new toothbrush.
The bathroom's just
down the hall to the left.
- (whispering indistinctly)
- Hi.
How we doing in here?
Can we give her back?
No, baby, we can't give her back.
Why would you want to do that?
She didn't like my painting.
(sighs) I don't think that's true.
I think she's just shy.
She barely talks.
Tess, put yourself in Deja's shoes.
- It's a brand-new house...
- DEJA (in distance): Hey. Hey!
- ...brand-new family.
- DEJA : Why do you have these?
- Those are mine.
- ...putting away your clothes...
You said this was my room.
- It is your room...
- No!
- Give 'em back, you bitch!
- Hey. Wait a minute.
Whoa, whoa, what's the matter?
BETH : Hey...
Hold on. We're okay.
Right? We're okay. Everybody's okay.
No, everything is... yeah.
WOMAN : Is it you?
Who posted the ad?
I couldn't remember which
park I said to meet at.
I see how you're looking at me.
Your dad just had really dark skin.
You said in your ad that, um,
you didn't need money, so I thought,
"Well, my boy's doing well."
Uh, if you don't need money,
then you have money, right?
You have money?
Where you going?
Wait.
- Randall, what...
- It's not her. Let's go.
KATE : Randall, wha...
Randall.
I see what you're doing now.
We came here for one
of our first dates.
REBECCA : One of our best dates.
JACK : So that explains
the Chevelle, the burgers,
but no concert tonight.
No concert that night, either.
Yeah, 'cause it got rained out.
Uh-huh. So we stayed in the car.
And we listened to Billy on the radio.
- Yeah.
♪ I never asked for much before ♪
♪ Not before ♪
♪ Things are changed, I need more... ♪
So, should we eat our burgers?
I was thinking that maybe we...
we could eat our burgers later.
Oh.
Okay. Okay.
(closing bag)
Yeah, that's... that's good, too.
♪ I never thought that she would say ♪
♪ Say good-bye ♪
♪ But she did ♪
♪ And now I want to die ♪
♪ I want to die ♪
♪ I never thought that I would need ♪
♪ Need a friend ♪
♪ Oh, but I did... ♪
(whispering): Ba-Babe, babe, hey.
Maybe we can just, we just wait.
Just-just wait for just...
just, ba-baby, just slow-slow down.
- Maybe just... slow down a bit.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. There's just been
a lot going on lately, you know?
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- No, I...
Yeah, this was a really, um...
this was silly
- to plan our thing like this.
- No, it...
Oh, I...
(Rebecca sighs)
She calmed down.
I told her we'd all talk
about it in the morning
after we got some rest.
Tess and Annie are a little freaked out,
so they're gonna sleep
in the same room tonight,
but I turned on the baby monitor
so we can hear if anything is going on.
Really?
You didn't even get out the baby monitor
- the first night William was here.
- Oh, I didn't?
I can't believe I thought
I was gonna win this girl over
by repeating our names
and giving her a tour.
It's pretty stupid.
Not stupid.
Hopeful.
Every time someone's told me
something was gonna be really hard,
it hasn't been that hard.
SATs, biz school, New
York City Marathon,
I study or I train... (sucks teeth)
...it's not that hard.
I think this might finally be the thing
that's as hard as everyone says it is.
It's only been three hours.
Everybody said there's gonna be
lots of high and lows.
RANDALL : Right.
Did you see the way she flinched, Beth?
- I mean, somebody must've really...
- Yeah.
(quietly): Yeah.
Hey.
Oh, that was so good.
Off to a rocky start, no pun intended,
but gosh, once you got going,
it was awesome.
Kate, why would you tell Sylvester
Stallone about our dad?
I just wanted to thank him.
Yeah, okay, because, you know
what, him bringing up to me
two seconds before the scene
started really threw me.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Well, I... I'm sorry.
It kind of seems that
it throws you no matter
who brings him up or when.
What are you talking...
that's not true.
- That's not true at all.
- Come on, Kev.
- You-you never talk about it.
- Well, you know what,
so, 'cause I don't want
to wallow in sadness about it,
- I have a problem?
- Okay, there is a difference
between wallowing and actually having
a normal conversation about it.
- Mm-hmm.
- There is.
- Okay.
- And, you know what, when I went to my
- weight-loss camp and
- I, you know what,
- I saw a therapist...
- here's the thing about that, though,
- And she asked me about Dad's death...
- right now, I don't have time
for that. I got an action scene
that's coming up and I don't have time
- to talk about this right...
- And I couldn't talk about it.
I couldn't talk about it.
And you know what she told me?
She told me that if I don't
learn to face my grief,
that it would be like
taking in a deep breath
and holding that breath
for the rest of my life.
That's great.
No, that-that, I mean,
that's-that's great.
I just, I... (laughs)
(exhales)
There's nothing for me
to let out, Kate.
I don't... there's not.
- I think that...
- Our dad died and it's very sad, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- It's very sad,
but I don't need therapy because of it.
- You might.
- And I don't need to go
to some-some exercise class
and scream my head off about it.
And here's what I really don't want.
I don't need to be talking
to Sylvester Stallone about it
two seconds before the biggest
scene of my entire career.
I'm sorry... I am.
Yeah, well, you know,
I-I-I don't, I'm not like you.
We're different people.
I don't need to walk around
and be sad and damaged
just because you are.
- Okay, wait. Hold on a sec...
- (door slams)
(sighs)
Sorry.
It's fine.
You know, it's a lot
harder than I thought.
AA...
talking to you.
It's just all harder.
Yeah.
I can tell.
Well...
You know, my life
before I met you, Bec...
it wasn't great.
I just kind of tried
to get away, you know?
Get away from my neighborhood.
Get away from my father.
Just get away from everything.
But now they say that
if I want to fix myself,
I've got to sit in that.
I've got, I've got to sit
in all the ugly, horrible years.
And they say that
on the other side of it,
there's relief.
That's what they say.
But I feel like I'm...
holding on... by a thread.
I love the night
that you planned for us.
But it's been awhile since we...
And I didn't want the
first time again to...
I didn't want to feel
like I was feeling.
(Jack sighs)
Baby, you are the
strongest person I know.
- I don't know.
- But I do.
I know.
Okay.
(sighs)
Where are you going?
I'm gonna get back in the car
'cause I miss talking to you...
and I'm not ready to stop yet.
(chuckles)
What do you want?
So, um, who's in charge here?
Your mom and dad, like,
who makes all the rules?
They both do, but...
- (both) Mom.
- Okay.
Um, what happens if you break the rules?
She has us talk about it
for, like, a million years
and sometimes you might lose
iPad privileges.
What's losing iPad privileges?
ANNIE : It means you can't use
your iPad for a while.
You guys have your own iPads?
- Yeah.
(scoffs)
This house is crazy.
ANNIE : If you open that door,
the alarm will go off.
Oh.
Where are you going?
Well, I'm having trouble sleeping.
First night in a new place, I guess.
Where I'm from, there's lots
of noise in the streets.
It's so quiet here.
- You're scared?
- No, I'm not scared.
It's just...
Do you know how to turn off the alarm
so I can leave without
waking everyone up?
Yeah, the code is my birthday,
but you should stay.
Oh, I don't think so, sweetheart.
I came by today to meet
your mother and you kiddos
and see your house.
Your dad seems like the best...
work friend a guy could ask for.
But I been sleeping in my apartment,
doing things my way for a long time.
What if I'm bad at...
I just don't want to let
any one of you down.
Once I went to sleep over
at my friend Lucy's house,
and I got scared and my parents
had to pick me up.
Later, I was sad I went home
because I probably would've
had fun if I had stayed.
Is that right?
So, maybe if you stay
here, you'll have fun.
And if you go home, you'll be sad.
You think so?
Okay, then.
Hey, can you show me how to turn
on the lights in the bathroom?
Yeah. You just walk in
and wave your hands.
- (chuckles)
- (giggles)
This house is crazy.
You can sleep in the reading
chair if you're scared.
- I'm not scared.
- ANNIE : Okay.
Okay, fine.
DEJA (over monitor): Just because
the bed in my room sucks.
It's too squishy.
- (indistinct chatter)
- KEVIN : Got it.
MAN :
Here we go.
Start to roll.
You like what you see?
RON : Yeah, yeah. Sure. Okay, now,
Sly's down there,
pinned under that Jeep.
You and your unit are gonna save him.
Remember now,
he's like a father to you.
And he's gonna die on your watch
- if you don't save him.
- Right.
- Lot of pressure, Ron.
- All right.
- Get ready.
- Thank you. All right.
♪ Covered in blood... ♪
RON : Pyro!
- ♪ You had the sense ♪
- Action!
♪ To stay calm and contained ♪
♪ There's no sense in crying my blues ♪
♪ For my brain ♪
♪ Leaving me standing outside ♪
♪ Show me a sign ♪
♪ Something that's shining ♪
♪ Like the tears in your eyes ♪
♪ You can surprise me ♪
♪ Because I want to be ♪
♪ The one the one you return to ♪
♪ You just believe ♪
♪ You're not alone in the world... ♪
(shouting)
- RON : Cut!
- Damn it.
- Ah!
- RON : Kevin, are you good?
(Kevin groans)
- MAN : Cut there, cut there.
- RON : Stay put!
- (laughs)
- This is your wheelhouse.
- No way. You let Shelly...?
- (laughs)
Advi... she gives horrible advice.
Do you remember the time
when-when she convinced you
to get a crew cut?
It was not a crew cut,
it was a pixie cut,
and I think I looked very chic,
thank you.
Well, I thought I was
married to Peter Pan.
(both laugh)
That's true, Peter Pan...
JACK : Yeah.
(insects chirping)
Becca, I...
(sighs)
I borrowed money from my
dad to buy our house.
(Jack sighs)
I was embarrassed that-that I...
couldn't provide for us without him.
Oh, Jack.
And there's...
there's a lot of other stuff, too.
Uh, that I buried away.
And I'll tell you...
eventually, just...
I'm working on it.
- Is that okay?
- Yes.
Yeah.
Of course.
I'm ready when you are.
- RANDALL : Have a good day, man.
- Thank you.
(door closes)
They just sent over Deja's file.
BETH : And?
Her mom's in big trouble.
(exhales)
- (knocking on door)
- Hey.
- KEVIN : We, uh,
just wanted to see how you were doing.
Yeah, you didn't say much
on the bus ride home.
Oh, I'm fine.
So, Deja.
I'm sorry I called you a bitch.
Thank you.
And those are not my cigarettes.
They're my mom's.
I wanted to have them to give
to her when she picks me up.
- Deja...
- Hey.
(quietly): I got it.
You know what I thought of, the
first time I heard your name?
I thought of the expression "déjà vu."
Because you remind me
a little of myself.
When I was your age.
KATE : Can I ask you something?
Why now?
Why did you suddenly try to find them?
RANDALL : These are my parents.
Jack and Rebecca.
They adopted me the day I was born.
This is my birth father.
William.
I met him for the first time last year.
My whole childhood, I felt split inside.
There are these people
that I lived with,
and then there were my birth parents,
who I had never met.
But I thought about them all the time.
RANDALL : It's like, a...
a-a ringing in my ears, and, uh...
It quiets down sometimes, but...
I-It can quiet down so much,
I almost forget it's there,
but then, there are some times
where it's so loud,
I just feel alone.
But, I mean, that doesn't
have anything to do
- with you guys.
- We know.
It's okay.
But here's the thing.
My life turned out pretty great.
And it's not just my big house,
or my super-fine wife, all right?
I've got this big,
amazing extended family.
amazing, beautiful life.
And if I'm seeing me in you,
if seeing you is giving me that
sweet, sweet déjà vu feeling,
I think that means it's gonna
happen for you, too.
Okay?
Okay.
RANDALL : Okay.
Deja?
Your mom might not be
coming back for a while.
What do you mean? Yes, she will.
No, this is what happens.
She gets busted, she gets taken away,
- then she comes back for me.
- I...
I know that's how it usually happens,
but since this time
was a lot more serious,
she might be going to jail for a while.
(glass shatters)
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't...
(car door closes)
We got to get you out of this car.
We're liable to stay here all night.
Cops are gonna pull us
over for-for squatting.
(Rebecca chuckles)
- (car door closes)
- Hey.
Well, looks like someone got
to enjoy the burgers tonight.
- Do you think he's a stray?
- I don't know.
Hey. Come here, pooch.
- Hey. Hi.
- ♪ How could it all fall ♪
♪ In one day? ♪
- Hey, bud.
- How you doing?
Look at this guy. (Laughs)
♪ Were we too sure of the sun? ♪
(phone beeps)
(line ringing)
♪ If you need to... ♪
- KATE (over phone): Hey.
- Hey.
(Kevin exhales)
Twin-fight.
- Yeah.
- Twin-make up?
Sure.
♪ If you need to, keep time on me... ♪
I'm sorry, Kate.
I'm an idiot. I...
I don't think you're sad and damaged.
I don't know why I said that.
The truth is,
I am insanely proud of you,
and everything you've
accomplished over the past year,
the-the weight loss and the therapy.
Meeting a guy who can burp the alphabet.
- (laughs softly)
- That's pretty cool.
Well, thank you.
Hey, um, I'm sorry
if I threw you off earlier.
How'd the big scene go?
I... you know, good. It's...
♪ If you need to... ♪
I fell, you know.
Banged up my leg pretty bad.
KATE : Did you hurt your knee?
- Yeah. A little...
- Your bad knee?
Yeah, you know...
You got to keep an eye on that, Kev.
- It's fine.
- Are you kidding me?
- Why is it that I'm the actor...
- "It's fine"?
...and you're the one
that's so dramatic all the time?
- It's fine.
- (groans) Okay.
- Bye.
- Wait. I, uh...
♪ I'll keep time on you... ♪
Kate, it's really hard for me with Dad.
KATE : Okay.
Well, maybe one day.
♪ Keep time on me... ♪
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe one day.
♪ How could it all fall in one day? ♪
I got to go. I...
I got to pack up and...
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Okay... Kev?
- Talk to you later?
- Oh, okay.
- All right.
- Bye.
(phone clicks)
(sniffles)
♪ If you need to ♪
♪ Keep time on me. ♪
(sniffles)
KATE : He's just like you.
synced and corrected by susinz
^.^.^.^.COLORED by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com