Previously on This Is Us...
Beth, I want to adopt a baby.
I realize I didn't come
to New York to be in a hit play.
I came to New York to win back my girl.
- (phone buzzes)
- Hello. Hey, Kevin, it's Ron Howard.
I'm prepping a movie right now
that I'm gonna direct.
It shoots in Los Angeles.
You would be perfect.
KATE: I know what I want to do.
- I want to sing.
- Hmm.
- Whoa! What the hell was that?
- Sorry.
Don't punish her because
I crossed the line.
- Hey, Bec?
- What'd you say?
(groans)
- Hey, hey, come on. Come on.
- (groaning)
Jack!
I think you should go stay
with Miguel for a while.
♪
WILLIAM: Things not
said, advice not given,
envelopes unstamped,
regrets enveloping me.
(typing)
Is it easier there? I wonder.
I ponder, I guess... Yes.
(Rebecca sighs)
I guess, yes.
(horn toots)
♪
What's Mom doing back?
WILLIAM: Do you think of
me as I do of you, my son?
My son.
My... son.
- You're a cutie, aren't you?
- (giggling)
Oh, you're the cutest baby
in the world.
Yes, you are.
- Oh, my goodness.
- (baby coos)
- WOMAN: Randall?
- Yes.
We've really got to get
our day going, Randall.
- Oh, of course. Sorry.
- (baby fussing)
No. All this talk about adoption
is giving me baby fever, right?
♪ I got baby fever ♪
♪ He got baby fever... ♪
Okay, that's gonna have
to do it for today, buddy.
- Yeah, you're right. Sorry.
- (woman laughs)
Happy birthday, Randall.
Thanks, guys.
It's gonna be a great year.
WILLIAM: The things you'll
do, I'll never know.
The pain.
The secrets.
♪
Mom, where's Dad?
- What's wrong?
- Nothing's wrong.
Everything's fine. We're gonna sit down
and explain everything to you guys.
WILLIAM: Oh, to be given a chance,
a start, the restart,
the fresh start.
(imitates roaring crowd)
The crowd goes wild!
You are gonna crush
this audition, babe.
- You're gonna crush it.
- Oh, you think?
Oh, man. All right.
- (imitating trumpet fanfare)
- (laughing)
That is so sweet.
Happy birthday to you.
Oh...
You ready?
- Make a wish.
- Okay.
Aah!
- Ow, ow, ow, no, no.
- Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
WILLIAM: Will love come for
you, as it did for me?
Find you, wreck you,
save you, change you?
Sophie got carried away.
Baby, I love you,
and I wanted to bring you
to the perfect place
and I wanted to say the perfect thing.
But I can't say the perfect thing
because you are the perfect thing.
So... what do you say?
Will you marry me?
HOWARD: And cut.
Very nice, very nice, Kevin.
I could feel the tennis ball welling up.
Really? So, when we film Emma's side,
we just... plop her
down in there like that?
Well, it's a little more complex
than just plopping,
but, uh, yeah.
Huh, I mean, technology, huh?
It's crazy.
Yeah, it is, and you know what
else is kind of crazy, Kevin?
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
WILLIAM: And if life breaks for you
the way it would not break for me,
if love hunts you,
finds you, captures you,
will you hold it tight...
nurture it, protect it?
Let's go. Come on.
I hope you will.
I hope you can.
What the hell is going on?
This father's advice is not required,
it has no call,
so instead I'll share some
from another.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- Hi, Dad.
It's better to have loved and lost
than to never have loved at all.
Your mom and I want to talk to you.
Subs & corrections by susinz.
Synced by kOoL tHuG
*www.addic7ed.com*
Uh, your father and I thought
that it was important to
be honest with you guys
about what's going on.
Ben... from the band,
was pretty inappropriate,
and your father came to surprise me,
and he got upset,
and I left the tour.
We had a pretty difficult night.
And now we're just
taking a moment to...
- catch our breath.
- Yeah.
- Catch your breath.
- Yes.
What does that mean?
Are you getting a divorce?
- No, no, no.
- Of course not.
- We...
- No, no, we're just taking
- a couple of days for ourselves.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna go stay at Miguel's house.
- Yes.
Okay?
- Well, I'll go with Dad.
- Kate, stop.
- But, Dad...
- Stop.
- Well, this is...
- No, this is insane!
- Bug...
- No. Are you...
Go ahead.
Would you give your mom
and I a sec, buddy?
(sighs) "Buddy."
♪
(sighs)
They're gonna be fine.
We'll be fine.
- Bec...
- Mm-mm. No, not yet.
I need to stop feeling so...
disappointed.
I need to feel something else first.
But we'll talk soon.
And some freshly squeezed
orange juice, and voilà.
Eat up, monsters.
- Daddy?
- Yeah, baby?
Happy birthday!
TESS: Happy birthday!
- Hey-yo!
- Thank you, girls.
(sighs)
- ANNIE: Daddy?
- Yeah, baby?
How come Mommy goes to work now,
and you stay home and are the girl?
Annie, who...
It is incredibly old-fashioned
and upsetting that you just said that.
It is perfectly normal
for a mommy to go to work
and a daddy to stay at home.
Women can do anything.
Look at Hillary Clinton.
Hmm?
She lost.
Yeah, but she almost won.
Just eat your breakfast.
BETH: Mmm. Smells good.
(gasps)
They're eating.
Who, Stacey Dash
and Omarosa over there?
Yeah, they're chowing down.
- It good?
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
You ready for this afternoon?
Yep.
It's gonna be the best
birthday gift ever.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm gonna go take a shower.
- Okay.
(phone rings)
- Hey.
- Babe, hey.
You're not on a plane.
Why are you not on a plane?
It's-it's my mom.
She had a really bad morning,
and I just, I couldn't leave her.
Of course not. No.
How about now, though?
She good? She good now?
She has MS, Kevin.
She's never good.
I'm... I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm just...
I'm tired and I'm sad,
and I'm gonna miss your birthday.
- It's fine.
- No, it's not.
I wanted to be with you.
I wanted to be in L.A.,
and I wanted to see Kardashians.
Well, I was gonna take you to the
place where they get their smoothies.
Oh, stop. You're killing me.
Did I ruin your birthday?
No, of course not.
It's not ruined.
The crew got me this cake.
A cake with my face on it.
Kind of cool.
Well, I should get back to her.
I'm so sorry, Kevin.
Well, listen, the Kardashians
aren't going anywhere.
- Promise?
- I promise. They're like gremlins.
By next week, there'll be,
like, a bazillion more of 'em.
(laughs)
Okay.
I love you.
Yeah, I... yeah, I c... I can't.
- Ready.
- KATE: Okay.
If you don't think this looks good,
you have to tell me.
Now, the perfect situation
for any man to be in.
Okay, you can look.
Schwing.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
They might not even ask you to sing.
I'm serious.
If that outfit has
anything to say about it,
you are absolutely going to be
the new lead female singer
of Yelp's 17th best
reviewed wedding band
in Southern California.
- Well, I am down two sizes.
- I know. And it shows.
You think you're so cute.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- And you are.
You actually look like
a young Bruce Willis.
Don't do that.
You cannot tell a man
who went bald at 25
that he looks like a
young Bruce Willis.
- It's too much.
- No.
Do you know what the...
sexiest thing about you is?
Yeah, my calves.
- Mm-mm.
- Oh.
The sexiest thing about you
is how sexy you make me feel.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, I see.
- Oh.
- (chuckles)
- Kate?
- Oh, no!
- Hey.
- Hey. Birthday girl.
Birthday boy. Where's Sophie?
Canceled. Mom.
- M.S.?
- Yeah.
- You? Want to talk?
- Disappointed. No.
BOTH: Happy birthday.
I love it when you guys
talk twin in front of me.
Hey, Kevbo.
- Yep?
- Since Sophie is bailing,
does that mean... that we're gonna have
to cancel the double date tonight?
- (laughs)
- No.
- You... It's still our birthdays, Toby.
- It's still our birthday.
My God, give me a break.
By the way, you're
gonna love this place.
It's, like, the number
one joint in town, okay?
I had to pull strings like frickin'
Geppetto just to get in there.
- That's a Pinocchio reference.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Geppetto was a woodworker.
Wasn't a...
Never mind.
Let's take a look
- at the outfit. I want to see.
- Yes. What do you think?
- It's great. I mean, you look...
- Yeah?
Yeah, you're beautiful.
The only thing is, are
you trying too hard?
- It's just a question I had.
- No.
I don't know. You don't want to be
the girl in the room
that's trying too hard.
- Yeah.
- Uh, we like the outfit, so...
Okay, I have a backup.
- What? I wanted... I wanted...
- Come help me, please.
KEVIN: I'll be right back. Gonna
help her with this real quick.
So glad I gave you that extra key
in case of emergencies, Kev.
The key was for emergencies!
And the she says she's too
disappointed to talk.
She says, "Soon.
We'll talk soon."
And then she just...
leaves.
Oof.
"Oof."
That's what I get?
You're supposed to be
a guy who says things,
and-and I get "Oof."
(chuckles)
You make each other better.
You're gonna be fine.
Yeah, she's gonna call.
- 'Course.
- Today.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, that phone is gonna ring,
and I'm gonna be home before tonight.
We've got some things
to work on, yeah, sure,
of course, but... it's okay.
Hey, no sheets.
Look... sheets are for long-term guests.
I'm not a long-term guest.
Okay.
Hey, look, I'm gonna
pop into the office,
get a jump on the week.
Why don't you come?
It'll take your mind off things.
Nah, I just want to be alone.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
It's all yours, man.
Hey. Thanks.
For saying the thing.
Sorry about the "Oof."
(chuckles softly)
She's gonna call.
(sighs)
(food crunching quietly)
So... how was the party? Hmmm?
(food crunching)
- (dishes clack loudly)
- What the hell?
- We're gonna go to the movies.
- KATE: I don't want to...
We're gonna go to the movies.
We're gonna go see
the one with Tom Hanks
at the dollar theater,
and we're gonna...
give ourselves over to Tom Hanks
and he's gonna make us feel
so much better about the
mind-blowingly upsetting crap
that's going on in our heads.
Yeah? Great.
It's gonna be fun.
WOMAN: Now, obviously, what
makes private adoption unique
is that you are paired
with an expectant mother
who has already committed
- to put her newborn up for adoption.
- That's perfect.
I was a newborn myself
when my parents found me.
It's perfect. Right?
It's common in these situations
for one spouse to be the dragger
and one to be the drag-ee.
It's important to communicate,
because... fair warning...
this process will really
get up in your business.
"Get up in there."
That's what she said.
- Uh...
- Fingerprints, background checks.
We'll be interviewing
both your daughters
to get a sense of their feelings.
We haven't told the girls yet,
but they're gonna love it.
- A little brother...
- Or little sister.
Or brother. Hey, is that
something we can request?
I mean, I love me some
headstrong sisters,
but they run pretty deep in my
house, if you know what I'm saying.
He wants a boy.
He wants to adopt a little boy,
because he was a little boy
when he was adopted.
Yeah. I mean, I guess that's part of it.
He wants to honor
his two fathers by replicating
the exact same situation he had.
Well, I don't know if I
would put it that...
Hey, Mary, let me ask you.
You have any kids
laying around that were
left at a fire station?
'Cause that might really
scratch my husband's itch.
- (door opens, closes)
- (clears throat)
Well, as you can see, we're not
afraid of honest, open communication.
RANDALL: Are you fake smoking?
Yes.
(exhales)
Do you not want to adopt?
- Does it matter what I want?
- Hey.
We only ever talk
about what you want, Randall.
You want to adopt.
You want to honor your fathers.
I know this has been
a weird year for you,
and I am trying to be supportive,
but this is becoming, like...
a weird pattern.
Okay, I hear you.
We're partners, in everything.
But 37 years ago, my parents chose me,
and that's why I'm here
with you right now.
This isn't going away for me, Beth.
You need to get your head around it.
Hey... Beth.
No. I'm not throwing down with
you in an adoption parking lot.
- Can we just go...
- Uh-huh.
♪ I've been caught ♪
♪ In fire ♪
♪ I stayed down the other night ♪
♪ I've been caught ♪
♪ In fire ♪
♪ I stayed down ♪
♪ Without knowing what the truth is ♪
♪ I've been caught... ♪
WOMAN: All right, guys,
there's a lot of you.
We're gonna be here into the night.
It may seem like overkill, but this is
a big opportunity.
Make sure you sign the
sheet, and we'll call you.
- ♪ Caught in fire. ♪
- Make it quick
- and make it count.
- ♪ I stayed down ♪
♪ Without knowing what the truth is ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Fire ♪
(movie playing indistinctly)
(indistinct chatter, laughter)
REBECCA (in distance): I have no life.
- I am a freakin' ghost!
JACK: Oh, you know? That is...
- No, no, no, no.
- Admit to me
that you hated the fact that
I had something happening for myself.
JACK: I hated that you lied about
working with your ex-boyfriend.
No, that's total BS, Jack.
You hated the fact
- that I was singing again.
- I was fine with it!
- No, you didn't want me to
have a career. - Career?
You are a 40-year-old woman
singing covers in pubs!
That is not a career, Rebecca!
That is ridiculous!
- Want some?
- Sure.
Thank you.
I think Randall's finally
gonna make his move.
What's wrong?
Are you kidding me?
Mmm.
Could I have some, too?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- Mommy.
Ooh. Happy birthday.
- Right there.
- Mmm.
Beth's struggling with the adoption.
I thought that she was on board.
- Yeah, I did, too.
- Oh.
How did you guys decide?
With me.
There was nothing to decide...
the moment we saw you...
You knew.
That's a hell of a story, Ma.
One of my favorites.
I know you guys didn't have
a perfect marriage.
You'd just lost a child,
and you both just wanted me?
Right away? Just like that?
(sighs)
It's complicated.
That's something people say
when they don't want to tell the truth.
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ La, la-la-la ♪
♪ Ah, ah... ♪
That little guy, right there.
He wound up here.
Exact same place, exact same day.
(muted crying of babies)
Just... look at him, Bec.
Placed right there, right next to ours.
Can't you just feel it?
You know, can't you just... see it?
REBECCA: I said no.
But your father was so sure.
I was tired and I was grievin,
and he just kept pushing me.
(whispers): He was so determined
that you were meant to be.
Meant to be ours.
Sometimes, in marriage,
someone has to be the one
to push to make the big moves.
And oftentimes in our marriage,
yes, it was your father.
(Rebecca sighs)
Our marriage wasn't perfect, it's true.
But none are.
And your father wasn't perfect, either.
But he was pretty damn close.
As close as they come.
He pushed... a stranger on me.
And that stranger became my child.
And that child became my life.
He became you.
(sighs)
Road tripping to Memphis
like teenagers.
You're gonna be the
death of me, old man.
I can get a bit bullheaded
when I want something bad.
Don't think that I ever
thanked you for taking me in.
Oh, you definitely did not.
You know he brought you home
without even asking me?
First you.
Then his brother.
He wanted something and then he just...
went ahead and did it.
Bullheaded.
Like father, like son.
Well, I'll take that compliment.
Take that compliment any day.
Didn't turn out so bad, though, huh?
Things that he pushed on you?
No, you're all right, old man.
Could have done without
the Manny in my basement
- for a year, but you're all right.
- (laughing)
So you like my spot, huh?
Yeah, I do.
I like to come here.
Reminds me of home.
Reminds me of me.
A little less fancy
than your neighborhood.
A little less white.
(chuckling): Yeah, there's that, too.
(coughing)
TOBY: Come on, you've got
to give me something.
Did any of the other girls sing Sinead?
What did they say when you were done?
Come on, I have been
on the edge of my seat all day.
I don't know, it was just
regular audition stuff.
- Wow.
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
(soothing instrumental music playing)
Um, excuse me.
Is this the, uh...
is this the hottest restaurant in town?
I bought the whole place out.
It's a birthday dinner.
- Come on.
- This is nice.
- It's cool, right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, wait,
do you want your sister
to sit across from you, next to you,
or just straight in your lap?
Across from me is fine.
- Sorry.
- Sit down.
That gentleman right there,
that is Aito.
He is a genius.
He's from Top Chef, or Iron Chef,
or Amazing Race.
You are a TV star, Aito!
The guy loves me.
- Oh, wow, look at that.
- Thank you.
Oh, there's a... a wine for every fish.
- (Kevin laughs)
- Okay, I'd like to make a toast.
- Yep.
- To the birthday girl.
- And the birthday boy.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
I would just like to say
that I am very proud of you.
So, cheers.
You know what, Tobe?
I actually didn't go
to the audition... I bailed
before I even got in the room.
What? Why, after all
that hard work?
I know. Believe me, I felt
the same way when she told me earlier.
- When she...
- But... yeah.
But let me tell you, you don't know
what it's like being in those rooms
Man, it's horrible. You know how
many times I've walked into a room
and I wanted to bail when I saw
James Marsden ready to read?
Wow. Really?
You told...
Okay, wow. Um...
Toby... Toby.
- Hey.
(sighs)
Went to see my mom.
Okay.
You know she didn't want
to adopt me at first?
My father pushed.
I love my parents.
I loved them together.
But I don't want to be them.
My mother said there's no such thing
as a perfect marriage.
But on that, I have to
disagree with my mother.
I didn't think that was allowed.
Today I'm allowing it.
Because we're perfect, Beth.
And I know this, you see,
because I'm a perfectionist.
So that's kind of my bag, you know?
Been chasing after it my entire life.
Perfection.
And I fail... and I
fail, and I fail and...
the failure leads to self-doubt
and self-loathing, and it's all...
And all this other crap I got
muddled up inside here.
But when it comes to you and me...
baby, there ain't nothing muddled there.
We are perfect together.
We are perfectly imperfect.
And I didn't even know that was a thing.
You see, we don't follow
one another, Beth.
We don't push our own
plans on each other.
We adjust our plans together.
And if I can't adjust to you, then...
...then I have to figure out
another way to do this.
I'll volunteer somewhere,
I'll... Yes, ma'am?
Can I take you somewhere?
Where?
I want to adjust your perfect plan.
Is it "perfectly imperfect"?
- Right?
- Yeah.
I like that.
(Randall chuckles)
- We open at 8:00.
- I was just...
You know, my wife, she sang
here a few months back.
Rebecca Pearson?
She sang with a jazz band?
Brunette. She's a knockout.
Good for her. We open at 8:00.
The thing is, she's not
with the band anymore.
She's going solo, and I
thought maybe you'd...
you'd like to book her for a solo gig,
considering how well she did
the first time around.
Is this for real?
Are you for real right now?
Look, come on, I could pay you.
I'll pay you to give her a monthly gig.
You know, just... once a month.
- You know, something that...
- Hey, hey, hey, pal...
you're embarrassing
yourself and your wife.
We're booked months in advance,
we don't do solo acts,
I've got nothing for you.
♪ You've been down ♪
Okay, thanks. Thanks for the trouble.
♪ My dark stairs ♪
♪ I'll tell you now ♪
♪ That you matter ♪
♪ Tell you, darling ♪
♪ That I still care. ♪
(sighs)
- Dude, just...
- Come on, hey, listen, man.
She didn't want to disappoint you.
Do you understand? And, hey, listen,
I know I overdid it with the dinner.
My fault, okay, but I was trying
to take her mind off of the audition.
That is not your job, Kevin.
That's the point, it's
not your job, okay?
I-I... She's going to be my wife.
I'm supposed to be her person.
Not you. All right?
I'm the one who's supposed
to cheer her up,
to buy her birthday dinner.
Then buy the dinner!
- Split the dinner with me.
- I can't...
I can't afford this crap!
Okay? And I hate that you pay for
meals while we're out, every time.
What is that? You're
not her father, Kev.
And you're not her husband.
Okay, stop right there. Do not tell me
how to take care of my sister.
I've been taking care of her
for a really long time.
Yeah, and how well is that
working out for her?
Just fine, thank you vey much.
Yeah? She doesn't need to be
coddled. She needs to be pushed.
Stop it! Both of you.
I'm a 37-year-old woman.
And I shouldn't need
to be pushed or coddled.
Not by a man, not by a husband,
not by a brother, not by anyone.
I don't even know what
you're saying right now.
- Just...
- Ugh...
Where are you going?
Back to the audition
to wipe the floor with those bitches.
That's where I'm going.
And don't follow me.
Well, you heard her, so...
Don't do it.
- Don't...
- I'm...
Don't, do...
Man, she's my ride.
You have to give me a ride.
Come on, get in the car. Get...
How do you... I don't even...
You reach under the thing, and you...
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I had it bound for you.
This was his favorite spot.
I've been coming here almost every day,
trying to figure out how I can
give you what you want.
Trying to wrap my head around it.
And I know you have
this notion in your mind,
this notion of a perfect little newborn
that we could shape
and mold from scratch,
like Play-Doh, but...
Randall, if we're really gonna do this,
I think this is the way.
Your parents did
something wonderful for you.
And because of that,
you had a wonderful life.
But things could have been
very different for you.
That could have been you.
If you really want
to do this, if you really want
to risk our perfectly imperfect
life for something,
let's go all the way.
Let's take in an older kid
who no one else in the
whole damn world is gonna help.
Oh, sorry we're all done.
You have to let me audition.
I can do any song on your list.
I was here before, but I lost
my nerve, and I'm a singer.
Well, I used to be more of one
when I was kid, but...
Fine. Which song?
- "Nothing Compares 2 U."
- Let's go.
All right, guys,
one more: "Nothing Compares 2 U."
Uh, I was also thinking
- that I could just...
- Two, three,
four.
(music begins playing)
(microphone distortion)
♪ It's been seven hours and 15 days ♪
♪ Since you took your love away ♪
♪ I go out... ♪
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay.
- Talk to you tomorrow?
- Mm-hmm.
(quietly): No.
No.
You will not dismiss me like that.
And you will not dismiss me
because I don't look
like that girl up there.
I know I'm not what you imagined,
but I will not walk out
of this room and allow you
to just give this gig
to a lesser singer
because she's a size two.
Because I've been living
versions of that story
my entire life, and I
can't do it anymore.
And I won't do it anymore.
Amber.
"Nothing Compares 2 U."
Two, three, four.
♪ It's been seven hours and 15 days ♪
♪ Since you took your love away ♪
♪ Since you been gone ♪
♪ I can do whatever I want. ♪
That's enough, thanks.
That's Amber.
She's our backup singer.
She was our lead singer,
but we demoted her because
she wasn't good enough.
Your pitch is good, but
your range is limited
and your falsetto blows;
You're out of practice, right?
You can't waltz in here
and compete with girls
who have been honing their
craft at open mic nights
since they were 16 years old.
I-I don't care what dress size you wear.
It's... you're not good enough, honey.
Toby, she was the one
that told me my father had died.
Uh, 17 years old, she had to be
the one to tell me that.
She's not just my sister, Toby.
I'm not just her brother, we...
We've walked side-by-side
through an entire life together,
and these things
that we've experienced are...
you know.
I'm not that good an actor.
Uh, I'm not, I'm not-I'm not
really that good at anything,
to be honest with you.
Uh, I'm always the guy in
the room trying the hardest.
(clears throat)
Being her brother, I...
I never had to try to be good at that,
you know? So...
I can't just cut the cord that quickly
'cause she met this amazing guy.
I know.
I do need you to stretch
it a little bit.
I know.
(door opens)
Yeah.
That did not go well.
- Oh.
- No, no, no, it's okay,
because it wasn't about
my weight or my age,
it was about my lack of ability.
Which is fantastic.
'Cause I can do this.
I know I can do this.
Just gonna have to work my way up.
Hmm.
Well.
But, ooh, I need a drink.
Does anyone want a nightcap?
I... I'm-I got an early call.
So I'm gonna bail on the drink.
Okay.
- Happy birthday.
And, uh, I'll let you take it from here.
Drink?
WILLIAM: And now, an addendum
to my earlier advice,
if I'm so lucky
as to still have your ear.
I loved you, I lost you.
And I advise you, 'twas better
than to never having had loved at all.
(both laugh)
WILLIAM:
But now, with more years,
with more time, more perspective,
I see things in a slightly new way.
So here, my good son,
is a father's advice,
updated and recalled.
It's better to have
loved and lost, surely...
(speaking indistinctly)
...but try not to lose it at all.
Jack?
- (knocking continues) Hey, Jack?
Hi.
So, I was trying to remember
myself tonight, Jack.
The person I used to be.
And then I started remembering you, too.
And I'm not the only one
who gave up on my dreams, Jack.
We both did, right?
And we, we realized
an even bigger dream,
an even more massive dream.
And I'm... I'm still really upset,
and I don't think I'm ready
to talk about any of that yet.
But...
I shouldn't have let you leave.
And not just because of all of
the beautiful things you said,
I shouldn't have let you leave
because that's not what we do.
That's not who we are, that's not us.
I know that, that's not us.
I know that I'm not deeply unhappy,
and I'm not unfulfilled,
and you're not an alcoholic,
and you're not your father.
And even when I watch Tom Hanks,
I sit there and I think to myself,
"He's not so great."
And who does that?
Who watches Tom Hanks and thinks,
"You know what? I'm married to
a man that's better than that."
Bec, you don't know everything about me.
- Yes, I do.
- No.
- I know everything about you.
- Rebecca, you don't know...
I'm drunk right now.
I have been drunk all day.
I have been drunk for weeks.
And I thought I had it under
control, like the first time, but...
I have a problem, Rebecca.
And I've hidden it from you
for a very long time.
And I've-I've hidden it from our kids.
And I need to get a handle on it
before I can walk back into that house.
And I'm sorry,
baby, I...
...I am very embarrassed.
And I am very sorry.
But I need to fix this on my own.
(Jack inhales, exhales)
(Jack breathing)
(knocking on door)
Get in the car.
Get in the car, Jack.
You are my husband, and I am your wife,
and if you have a problem,
we will fix it together.
I just need you to get in the car.
So we can go home.
(sniffles)
- (quietly): Come on.
Come on, baby.
Okay.
(whispering): I need
you to get in the car.
- (crying)
- I need you to get in the car.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Jack, look at me.
♪ Is it getting better? ♪
A few months from now,
everything will be back to normal.
♪ Or do I feel the same? ♪
♪ Will it make it easier on me, now ♪
♪ I've got someone to blame? ♪
(sobbing)
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ To drag the past out ♪
♪ Into the light ♪
♪ We're one ♪
♪ But we're not the same ♪
MIGUEL: I'm gonna get some pillows.
♪ We get to carry each other ♪
♪ Carry each other... ♪
- We... we...
We have to find Kev.
♪ One ♪
He needs to hear it from me.
(sobbing)
♪
♪ One... ♪
(crying)
(singer vocalizing)
(screams)
No...
(singer continues vocalizing)
Subs & corrections by susinz.
Synced by kOoL tHuG
*www.addic7ed.com*
How did you stop before Jack?
It was not easy.
I'm not going to overreact to
everything she says this time.
You wanted to adopt and now
you're Randalling out on me.
Ok stop making my name a thing.
♪ tell me are you out there listening ♪
♪ Do you hear me calling out for you ♪