Our dad died, and it's very sad, okay?
- Previously on This is Us...
- KATE: Come on, Kev.
You never talk about it.
Well, you know, 'cause I don't want
to wallow in sadness about it,
- I have a problem?
- Okay, there's a difference between
wallowing and actually having
a normal conversation about it.
I wasn't good at football, Toby.
I was great.
Listen, I was just hoping we could get
one more refill on the prescription.
I-I don't know
why it's that big of a deal.
Kevin, you're-you're spiraling.
What's going on? This isn't you.
When I dream of our future together,
Sophie, it's a nightmare.
- Okay.
- Okay, who's gonna do it?
- Who's gonna be the first one to walk?
- Who's gonna do it?
- We know you want to.
- Come on. We know you want to so bad.
REBECCA: Come on, guys.
- (GASPS) Number One is up. He's up!
- Kevin's up!
- Come on.
- Come on! Come here. Come here, boy.
- Look at that, Kevin
Pearson, first one born,
first one to walk. He's on his feet.
Look at him come down the track.
- Ladies and gentlemen!
- Yes, buddy!
- He's walking. There he goes!
- Look at those steps!
-(CLAPPING)
Yeah! You did it!
JACK: Number One. Number One.
Is there nothing Number One can't do?
("WHERE DO THE CHILDREN PLAY?"
BY CAT STEVENS PLAYING)
♪ Well, I think it's fine ♪
♪ Building jumbo planes ♪
♪ Or taking a ride ♪
♪ On a cosmic train ♪
♪ Switch on summer ♪
♪ From a slot machine ♪
♪ Yes, get what you want to
if you want ♪
♪ 'Cause you can get anything ♪
♪ I know we've come a long way ♪
♪ We're changing day to day ♪
♪ But tell me ♪
♪ Where do the children play...? ♪
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
Hello, again, everyone, and
welcome to another great matchup
- on Sunday Night Football.
- (KNOCKING)
MAID: Mr. Pearson? Housekeeping!
- You in there?
- (KNOCKING)
...in four nights, when
we go to Washington
for the big Thanksgiving night game.
- MAID: Mr. Pearson?
- Al, people can eat all day long
- You there?
- and then get ready for the big ga...
Do you need service, sir?
Maybe some clean towels?
The "Do not disturb" sign's
been up all week.
Yet here we are, huh?
Disturbing.
I'm... Come on, I'm messing
around with you, uh... Martina.
Like Navratilova, right?
The tennis player.
Yeah? You play tennis?
I don't play either.
She was great, though, huh?
She was great. Not much of a looker,
but she had a great backhand.
Maybe it was a forehand...
Remember.
So, do you want some towels?
Uh... No, you know what,
I'm all set on towels.
But since you're here, Martina,
and we're already
mid-disturb, come on in.
We could use a refill
on all things alcohol-related.
(CHUCKLES)
- (PHONE RINGING)
- (GROANS)
Maybe I should change your sheets, too.
Yeah, no, go nuts. (GROANS)
Kate, how many times
do I have to tell you?
You don't have to call me every
15 seconds. I am fine, okay?
Mr. Pearson? Hi. This is Kelly,
the homecoming coordinator
from McKinley High.
We spoke last month.
- Right. Yeah, now is not a good time.
- Oh, my God.
I've never talked to a
celebrity on the phone before.
Except for Ryan Seacrest
that time I phoned in
and won Zayn Malik tickets.
(QUIETLY): Get it together,
Kelly. (CLEARS THROAT)
I'm, uh, just confirming you are
all set for tomorrow night?
Uh... tomorrow night...
Alumni Honors Ceremony. Go, Lions!
That's not tomorrow, though.
That-That's in, like...
that's in, like, two weeks. That's...
that's-that's the 20th.
Uh-huh, yeah, t-tomorrow is the 20th.
Martina, what day is tomorrow?
Tomorrow's the 20th.
Tomor...
Excuse me, Martina, wha...
I'm on the phone with, uh...
What do they call you?
Oh, sorry. Kelly.
Mr. Pearson, are you not coming?
Because everyone here is really excited
about giving you this honor.
Old high school wants to honor me.
- Should I go?
- Is it outside this room?
If it's outside, you should go.
I mean, I was gonna go back east
for Thanksgiving anyway.
Sorry, are-are you still
talking to me or...?
- Martina.
- Yeah?
No, I was answering, uh...
Kelly.
(SIGHS) You guys want
to honor Kevin Pearson?
Let's honor him.
(QUIETLY): Maybe bathe him, too.
♪
REBECCA: Jack! Fuse!
JACK: Yeah! I'm working on it!
Could you work a little faster?!
Hey, Ivy League, you think
you could help me figure out
which one of these
is for the first floor?
I'm not Ivy League yet.
Killing me.
Sorry to have interrupted
your evening, my liege.
- How's your Harvard application coming?
- Almost done.
- REBECCA: Oh, thank God.
- JACK: Fixed it!
Good job, babe!
Wait, wait, is that what you're wearing?
- Mm-hmm. -The coach from Pitt
is gonna be here any second.
You should really stop borrowing
shirts from Sophie, Kevin.
I don't really think
the coach is gonna care
what shirt I'm wearing.
KATE: Whatever, Crop Top.
Ew! What is that flavor?
It's orange zest. I panicked
and added it last minute.
Can you please go put on
a collared shirt
and a nice pair of pants?
You think we can, like,
move Dad's AA stuff?
Yes, we can do that.
- It's been, like, six months.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it takes as long as it takes.
- Change.
- Well, it's just so lame...
- JACK: So I think
the power's gonna hold.
You ready to wow this
coach, college boy?
God, it's just Pitt, you know?
I didn't even really want
to meet with the guy.
Yeah. We know.
Go put on a collared shirt, though,
and some pants with a fly.
- It's just Pitt.
- Now.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪
- Welcome to Pittsburgh, Kevin.
- Thank you.
We are obsessed with The Manny.
Is the beard for a movie or...?
- Yeah.
- Can we get a picture?
(CHUCKLING)
That's gonna be a good one.
Are you, uh, visiting or coming home?
Uh... just...
Neither.
Both. I don't... I don't...
I don't know.
Well, let me know
if you need anything, uh,
water or a phone charger.
Running a little low on painkillers.
Hook me up with some of those?
I-I... don't really, um...
I'm joking, man. Come
on, give me a break.
You should've seen your face.
It was classic.
Hey-ey, uh, make a left...
make a left right here.
- The high school's actually...
- Yeah, no, no. Quick detour.
Okay. No problem.
Stop, stop, stop. Right here.
♪
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
...right past Mom. Pump fake to you.
Okay? Number One, it's coming to you.
Leap into the driveway by the street.
Okay? Right. This one's coming
to you, Number One.
One, two. One, two.
Okay, okay!
Ho-ho! Okay, go 42!
Go 42!
Set!
- Hut, hut!
- One, 1,000, two, 1,000, three!
You're not supposed to blitz!
- I'm running! Go, go, go! You got it!
- (REBECCA LAUGHING)
You got it! Oh, get it, get it, get it!
♪
- He got it! He got it!
- (SQUEALS)
Hey.
Can I help you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
(CAR DOOR OPENS, SHUTS)
Kate, can you clean his
pee anywhere else?
A college coach is gonna
be sitting on that couch.
Okay, well, I'm not
getting it on anything.
And, uh, speaking of college,
have you made your list yet?
Your guidance counselor
said to make a list
of your top five schools,
'cause you don't want to put
- all your eggs...
- In one basket.
- JACK: He's here!
- Okay! Okay, okay.
- I'm out. (GRUNTS)
- (DOORBELL RINGS)
- Hey, knock 'em dead.
- Train your dog.
Make that list!
Yeah.
- Coach Waltering.
- Jack, how are you?
How are you? Come on in, please.
This is my wife Rebecca.
So nice to meet you.
- Thank you for coming over, Coach.
- Of course.
- Very nice to meet you as well.
- Hey.
And there he is!
Kevin Pearson, superstar.
How you doing? Coach Waltering.
♪
Sophie?
Kevin.
You're back.
Mr. Pearson.
Mr. Pearson, you're early.
We are beyond stoked to have you.
My Snapchat is legit blowing up.
Do you mind?
- (CAMERA CLICKS)
- Now, the Honors Ceremony
won't start for a couple of hours,
but we've got, like,
a greenroom set up for you.
You probably think it's super
lame, us doing a greenroom.
I know you've been in real greenrooms.
But, uh, we got La Croix water
and Wi-Fi.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Just, uh...
You look so much like somebody
I knew when I went here.
Oh. Someone pretty, I hope.
I'm gonna go...
- go walk the halls for a bit here.
- Yeah.
Well, I will just,
uh, see you later, then.
Hey, is the beard for a movie, or...?
It's probably for a movie.
♪ Have you heard
about the lonesome loser? ♪
♪ Beaten by the Queen
of Hearts every time ♪
♪ Have you heard about
the lonesome loser? ♪
♪ He's a loser, but he
still keeps on tryin'... ♪
Now, I'm here to tell you, kid,
that with that arm
and my guidance,
you could be on your way
to joining the great tradition
of Pennsylvania-grown
quarterbacks: Joe Montana...
- He went to Notre Dame.
- Kevin.
What?
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
What kid doesn't want to play QB
for the Irish, right?
♪ Have you heard about
the lonesome loser? ♪
♪ Beaten by the Queen
of Hearts every time ♪
♪ Have you heard about
the lonesome loser? ♪
♪ He's a loser, but he
still keeps on tryin'... ♪
You will be taking a lot
of snaps next year.
Well, am I gonna start?
♪ Oh-oh, oh, oh... ♪
Excuse me, Coach, our son seems
to have forgotten his manners.
Well, Kevin, you might not start,
but you may very well finish.
Now, let's talk
about the players drafted
to the NFL from our program...
♪ Have you heard about
the lonesome loser? ♪
♪ Beaten by the Queen
of Hearts every time ♪
♪ Have you heard about
the lonesome loser? ♪
♪ He's a loser, but he
still keeps on tryin' ♪
♪ Oh-oh, oh... ♪
(JACK SIGHS)
Get out of my sight.
- Okay.
- Get...
back here.
Okay.
That man...
He takes time out of his day,
he comes to our home,
he sits at our table,
and he offers you, a C-plus student
- at best...
- You invited him, not me.
...a full ride to a good college!
- We can do better.
- Kevin, that is not the point.
Do you have... any idea
how lucky you are to get
an opportunity like that?
It's not luck. It's talent.
(REBECCA SCOFFS)
JACK: Okay.
You get your ass downstairs,
and you write him an apology letter.
- Now.
- Why?
Because you've been apologizing
to the world lately?
- Kevin, it's part of his 12 Steps.
- 12 Steps.
I know that.
Do you have something
you want to say to me?
Do you... have something...
Nope.
Go do what your dad says.
It was embarrassing
to watch you behave just like you did.
I know the feeling well.
(CROWD CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
Can I get you something to drink?
What do you have?
There's red, and there's white,
- and there's water...
- Red is great. Thank you.
- Hey. Kevin Pearson.
- Oh.
- Yeah, hi. Good.
- Oh, you're just...
Hi. Hi. Just...
Good God.
Oh.
Guess you don't need a name tag.
- Sorry.
- Everyone knows you're Kevin Pearson.
- Yeah.
- Me? Well, I need a name tag.
- (KEVIN SNIFFLES)
- Lived here my whole life,
face still hasn't lost
its baby weight, and God knows
I haven't changed my hair
since I was 16,
- but I still need a name tag.
- Oh.
We went to school together.
- This school.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh...
You can use the name tag.
- (SCOFFS) Charlotte Everby...
- Everly.
- Wow. Okay. Everly.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
I wa... I was supposed to get
my hands on-on one of those.
- She-she... -Oh, please,
you can have a sip of mine.
- Oh.
- Uh, it's awful.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Uh, grapes crushed by real Italian feet.
- Mm.
- Mm-hmm.
Boy, that is gross.
- (LAUGHS)
- That is really foot-forward.
It is totally foot-forward. (LAUGHS)
Oh, God, did I have a mad crush
on you back then.
I mean, you were... everything.
You made us want to come to school.
- Us?
- The nerds.
And the girls. The gays.
Basically, everyone.
Um, heard that you
and Sophie got divorced?
Uh, yeah. We did. But we...
- but we got back together.
- Oh.
And then I managed to
screw that up, too.
- Hmm.
- (RINGTONE PLAYS)
My sister Kate. You remember Kate?
I remember you two
being inseparable. How is she?
Good. She's, uh... pregnant.
No. No, no, no.
I wasn't supposed to, uh,
tell that to anyone.
So... you know,
don't tell anyone, or her,
- that I told you.
- So I shouldn't tweet it?
You should not tweet it, no.
Yeah, so wha-what do you, uh...?
Do you have kids here?
- Are you a parent here, or...?
- Uh, fellow honoree.
- Oh.
- For my work as a plastic surgeon.
- Butts or boobs?
- Burn victims mostly.
- Right.
- Yeah. Skin grafts and such.
- And twice a year, I go
to developing countries
with Operation Smile,
- so that kids with cleft palates...
- Mmm.
- Oh, um...
- Thank you.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Someone's a little nervous
about his speech.
- Yeah.
- (KEVIN SIGHS LOUDLY)
- Uh...
- I got to give a speech?
Now, I know you think this is
a man who needs no introduction
but there's someone here
who begs to differ.
Coming out of retirement
to present Kevin
with his Distinguished Alum Award,
his former football coach,
Duffy "The Duff" Collins.
- (APPLAUSE)
- MEN (CHANTING): Duff! Duff!
Duff! Duff! Duff!
Duff! Duff! Duff! Duff!
MAN: Hey, Duff!
Well, thank you for that.
I, uh... I had the pleasure
of coaching Kevin
for four yea... well,
three and a half years.
And in my career, I never saw a
kid with so much natural talent,
confidence or charisma.
But he caught some tough breaks
and suffered some losses.
And that's when he really
showed himself to be a star.
(CHEERS, APPLAUSE)
He fought through the adversity
and the heartache.
JACK: And he found success
on another path.
He is,
for all you kids out there,
a living, breathing example
of outer and inner strength.
This kid is tough as hell.
Kevin, I know
this little award
may not be much to you...
But for me, who knew you when,
who knew your father...
(VOICE BREAKING): you coming
back here to get this award...
(CLEARS THROAT) We are all very proud.
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
Uh...
well, thank you.
You're a... good man.
But what you said was wrong.
- (LAUGHTER)
- I'm-I'm...
It's not, uh, funny.
I'm serious, guys. Uh,
I'm not strong.
At all. Uh...
- KELLY: We love you, Kevin!
- WOMAN: Love you, Kevin!
- (CHEERING)
- But, uh...
Stop, don't. Don't do that. Don't.
Don't-don't... don't love me.
You, uh, you guys want
to love someone, love Paul here.
A newspaper man in...
let's face it... a dying medium.
Or Dr. Everly, a woman who...
...who helps messed up kids
go out and face the world.
The truth is, I...
I'm not worthy of this award.
Or any honor, for that matter.
So...
Uh...
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
(WHOOPING)
Can't sleep either, huh?
Um, just hungry,
and we don't have anything good to eat.
Listen, I wanted to talk to you.
Your brother,
he wants to tour this college on Friday,
and it's in D.C.
I'm-I'm probably gonna miss
your football game.
It's fine.
What happened earlier tonight...
how mad I got?
My fuse has been very short lately
with everything that I'm dealing with.
I shouldn't have yelled at you.
It wasn't right.
Okay.
What's going on with you, Kev?
Nothing, Dad. I just, uh...
I got to go write that letter.
Yeah, I...
Look...
Look, it's all just...
You know, it was just
really steep tonight, Charlie.
Yeah... No, I've... I've said it,
uh, said it about a hundred times.
Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. I'll do it right now.
Thanks for being there.
(SIGHS)
God, grant me the serenity
to accept the things I cannot change,
the courage to change the things I can,
and the wisdom to know the difference.
All right, so, we're gonna see
you guys after Kev's game?
- Yes.
- Dad, come on.
It's a four-hour drive.
I don't want to get there late
and make a bad impression.
Randall, you're a math prodigy
with insane SAT scores
and perfect grades.
Any college would be lucky
to have a giant dork like you.
Thanks, LL Cool K.
So, you guys out?
Yeah. Sorry we're missing your game.
Next campus tour's a month away.
That's fine, man. I've got enough fans
in the stands cheering me on.
- (SCOFFS) -That's a nice
attitude adjustment, Kev.
I'm glad that talk really sunk in.
- See you later.
- Mmm. Okay.
Travel safe. I love you.
Love you, too, Mom.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
Amazing speech, man.
Can we get a picture for the yearbook?
And, uh, one for me.
WOMAN: Great job. Great speech.
MAN: Awesome job, Kevin. So ins...
WOMAN 2: Amazing.
(PHONE BUZZING)
Great job.
Hey. You want to walk?
They retired my jersey.
Do you know that?
- Yeah.
- You know what it was, the number?
One.
Well, you couldn't ask
for a better number.
Didn't ask for it. Just got it.
I was, uh, first born in my family,
so it was, like... (SNIFFS)
already my nickname.
You know, I was branded at birth.
(SIGHS)
Very first one to learn how to walk.
I was, I was, I was always, you know,
- first one picked in any sports team.
- (CHUCKLES)
I was the first boy
to kiss a girl in school.
Number One.
First grown man to get drunk
in a high school quad?
That was Jim Kalotchnik.
Oh, the janitor.
(CHUCKLING): That's right.
I always thought that his legs
were different lengths,
- but I guess, looking back...
- He was drunk.
- He was friggin' drunk. (LAUGHS)
- Yeah.
(SIGHS)
I feel like I could be standing
completely naked out here.
You know, all anyone would ever see
is me in that number one jersey.
Well...
...that's not all that I would see.
Please don't do that.
(INHALES)
(GRUNTS) See you, Charlotte.
What up, gridiron, huh?
Has it been 20 years or so?
(CROWD CHEERING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
ANNOUNCER (OVER P.A.): Another
first down for number one.
(SNIFFS, GROANS)
All right.
Pearson lines up under center.
Two rushing touchdowns
already tonight.
What can this kid not do?
He can't go four hours
without a Vicodin,
that's what he can't do.
But everybody loves him anyway.
"Wow!
Pearson!"
- Blue 42!
- Blue 42, set, hut-hut.
The ball is hiked.
Pearson drops back. He looks left.
He pump fakes.
He rolls to his right. He tucks
the ball. He's in traffic.
(WHOOSHES) Shucks a defender.
He looks downfield.
He's got a man open. Wide open.
He sees his entire future.
Notre Dame.
Heisman Trophy.
First-round draft pick.
Rookie of the Year. Super Bowl MVP.
He sees his dad in the stands.
As he holds the Super Bowl
trophy, his dad's proud of him...
like, "tears down his
eyes" proud of him.
He says, "That's my son."
"That's my son."
Pearson's about ready
to release. He cocks back.
- Boom! He's down, folks.
- (CROWD GASPS)
Ladies and gentlemen, Pearson's down,
and he's not getting up.
His knee is wrecked.
He's not coming back
from this one, folks.
It is over for Kevin Pearson.
- Kate, go call your father.
- Yeah.
Find a phone, page him. Go, go, go.
- Kate, Kate, go.
- Okay, yeah.
KEVIN: Will he get up?
He will.
Ladies and gentlemen, he will.
He'll get up.
Kevin Pearson will walk again,
just in time to bury his beloved father.
That'll keep him down.
For good this time, right?
Nope.
Nope, he's-he's up again.
He's up again, and he's... (SNIFFS)
He's marrying a terrific girl.
He's off to Hollywood, and it's a...
it's a happy ending for Kevin Pearson.
Oh, whoa. Wait, nope. Hold on, now.
He cheats on the girl.
Yes, that's right. He loses her.
And how's he punished?
(LAUGHS): Well, he... he gets a sitcom,
and he makes millions,
ladies and gentlemen.
(IMITATES CROWD CHEERING)
The crowd goes wild.
What will he do
with his lucky second chance?
Ladies and gentlemen, he'll blow it.
That's what he'll do. He blows it all.
Surely the universe has to
punish him this time, right?
Wrong. He gets the girl back.
- Now he's got the girl back,
- and-and it's a movie this time.
And then pop!
Oh.
There it goes, the same knee.
Bam, he's down again.
And he tries so hard to be strong,
and he needs painkillers
to get through it.
And even when he tries to tell people
how pathetic he is, it...
They just...
They don't hear it.
They just cheer.
KELLY: Hey.
Just the Manny I've been looking for.
You want to party?
(SNIFFS)
Uh, I couldn't believe it
when you walked back
into that reception tonight.
I was sure you'd left your phone
or something.
And then you pointed at me
and said, "Let's get out of here."
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- Yeah, no, I was there.
It was, like, 20 years of fantasy energy
just going, pow, pow, pow, pow!
All right, cool.
You were nice to me in high school.
I mean, you never knew my name,
but we'd pass in the halls,
and you'd always smile.
Say hi.
And once, at one of Hannah
Brubaker's summer parties,
you saw Mikey Doyle
getting a little handsy with me,
and you pulled him away.
I did that?
I thought to myself, "Now, that
is a good guy."
It's weird, the things you remember.
Anyway, babble, babble.
"Charlotte, stop talking,
please." (LAUGHS)
Whoa. Are you okay?
- Your sweat glands are in overdrive.
- Yeah, know why?
I think it's just, uh...
I think it may be...
If you could crack a
window or something?
- Yeah. I'm on it.
- It's hot in here.
(GROANS)
CHARLOTTE: I still don't get
why you wanted to come here.
Your room at The Riverview's
probably super nice.
Actually, will you excuse me
for a second?
Oh, mi baño es su baño.
Yeah. (LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
CHARLOTTE: You okay in there?
Yeah.
(INHALES AND EXHALES DEEPLY)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
You know, I feel like it's
like a blood sugar thing
or something happening
with me, 'cause I,
I haven't eaten since
the airplane, you know?
So, I was, I was wondering, uh,
maybe you could whip us up
- a snack or something.
- Say no more.
One bedspread picnic coming right up.
Ah, that'd be great. (SNIFFS)
CHARLOTTE: Yodels and cheese okay?
I haven't gone shopping in a while.
Yeah. That's fine.
- Kevin?
- (DOOR CLOSES)
♪ Well, I've been out walking ♪
♪ I don't do too much talking ♪
♪ These days ♪
He's having an MRI done; it's his knee.
♪ These days, I seem to think a lot ♪
♪ About the things that I forgot to do ♪
♪ And all the times ♪
♪ I had the chance to... ♪
Hey, how are you? How's it going?
- Name and birthday?
- Tony Tisdale. 12-10-69.
Doctors' handwriting sure
gets worse every year.
More like Jimmy Fallon up there.
I didn't know Jimmy Fallon worked here.
It's like a late night talk
show or something, right?
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
♪ And I had a lover ♪
♪ It's so hard to risk another ♪
♪ These days ♪
♪ Now if I seem to be afraid ♪
♪ To live the life ♪
My pendant. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
♪ Well, it's just
that I've been losing ♪
♪ So long ♪
How you feeling, champ?
He came around the end, and...
(LAUGHING): I didn't even see him.
I know.
All right.
Just say it.
How long do I have the cast on?
- Am I gonna make the playoffs?
- Well...
The thing is, Kev, you...
- Look, if anyone can beat the odds...
- Dad, just say it.
The kind of break you have,
the doctor called it catastrophic.
He thinks you'll be able
to run again, thank God,
but...
the physical demands of the game...
he-he doesn't think
that your knee can...
bear that kind of stress.
(CHUCKLES) Like soon?
(SIGHS)
I know it's a difficult thing to hear.
He's wrong. (LAUGHS)
- I can come back from this.
- Kevin.
Yeah, you know what, maybe I
don't go to Notre Dame. (LAUGHS)
I'll go to Pitt, I don't care.
I wrote Coach Waltering that
nice letter, like you said, Dad.
- It was really nice.
- I know. I believe you.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I've been awful to you.
- And I can do better.
- Kev, hey.
I need you to listen to me, bud.
I would take this on for you.
Okay? I would take on this
and anything else if I could.
And I know that you've had this dream
for a very long time,
and God knows you have
such a beautiful talent,
but I know, in my gut,
it is not the only one that you have.
(EXHALES, BREATHES HEAVILY)
Hey. I got this
at a very hopeless time in my life.
Someone very special gave it
to me back in Vietnam.
It's a Buddhist symbol of purpose.
I was feeling very lost when I got that.
But I put it on, and I moved forward.
And you know when I was wearing it?
The day you were born.
The moment you came out, my Number One.
And when I held you,
for the first time,
right here in this hospital,
it hit me like a bolt of lightning.
- You were my purpose, Kevin.
- (KEVIN CRYING)
And I swear to you, son,
I swear to you,
you will find yours.
- Okay?
- (KEVIN SNIFFLES)
Okay.
Charlotte?
Hey, Charlotte. It's me.
Charlotte, it's Kevin!
I left my dad's necklace.
I need to come in
for a few seconds to look for it, okay?
Charlotte!
- Kevin.
- Charlotte!
Are you out of your mind?
Coming back here, you bastard?
That necklace belonged
to my father, okay?
And I... I just need to come in
for a second and look for it.
- Screw you.
- Just hold on.
That necklace, it's the only thing
I have left in my life from my dad.
(CRYING): It's the only thing I
have, and I know it's up there.
It's a... it's-it's a wh...
it's a wheel pendant
on a little chain.
It's on your bedroom floor.
It's from where you tore
my shirt off. I know...
Would you announce that
to more of my neighbors?
Just go look for it. Please, please.
I don't have your damn necklace.
- Now leave me alone.
- Please, listen to me.
I understand you're upset
that I left, okay?
It had nothing to do with you,
all right?
(CRYING): I'm in pain out here!
Look, I'm in pain here, okay?
Can't you see I'm in pain?
(SOBBING): I just need it to stop.
I just need somebody to help me.
♪
I just need help, please.
I just need somebody to please help me.
- Hey.
Thanks for taking my call.
Yeah, man.
I didn't know you were already in town.
That beard for a movie?
Randall, I need to tell you something.
It's okay.
I already know.
Kate lost the baby.
(PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
♪
JACK: Number One has done it!
- Number One has done it!
- REBECCA: Yes! (LAUGHS)
JACK: And now the crowd,
the crowd moves its attention
to the filly!
- Oh, come on, sweetheart.
- REBECCA: Come on, sweetheart.
- Come on, Number Two.
REBECCA: Come on...
Just like your brother, baby.
Come on, come on.
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*