Previously on This Is Us...
So is it still there?
It's still there.
Congratulations. You're
officially six weeks along.
Is it always like this?
DEJA: It gets worse when
there's a lot going on.
One of the things that helps me
when I'm feeling stressed, though,
- is running.
- She told you what I said?
STANLEY: Let's all raise a glass
to my unemployed
28-year-old son.
JACK: My life, before I met
you, Bec, it wasn't great.
I just tried to get away
from my father.
I've been working my ass off,
and I am finally on the brink
of something special,
and I will be damned
if I let this stupid knee
destroy another one of my dreams.
- (kids shouting)
- Stop!
- Stop it, it's mine!
- Why can't you get it?
It's mine!
- You're gonna keep the boys safe?
- Oh, yeah. I will.
- BEC: You have moisturizer for Randall?
- JACK: Check.
BEC: And remember,
Kevin's afraid of bears.
- (chuckles) So am I.
- Okay.
Uh, the number for
the campground's by...
By the phone in the kitchen.
- I told you that already.
- Three times.
- Okay.
- You really think that this trip
is gonna help the boys get along better?
I do.
- BEC: Because Kevin can be so...
- Yep.
And Randall is just
only trying to help.
I know, baby. It's gonna be great.
Look, camping's all about teamwork.
Do you remember how the
Steelers were a wreck
at the start of the '79 season?
You're gonna Chuck Noll the boys?
(whispers)
I'm gonna Chuck Noll the boys.
- Okay. Good luck.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna tell Mom or Dad!
- Stop!
- Go get 'em, Coach.
- Oh! (howls)
Oh, do you guys hear that?
Do you know that sound?
That is the call of the wild.
- Hey, Kate!
- JACK: Come on, hop in the car.
Your brothers are leaving.
Come say good-bye.
Randall, put that up front for me.
Thank you. Kev, here.
We are gonna have the
best girl's day ever.
- We are?
- Yeah.
Can you say movies and manicures?
I think the first thing we'll want to do
- is set up the tent when we get there.
- Ugh!
- Backseat.
- I'm already up here, Dad.
- Get in the backseat with your brother.
- (sighs)
- (engine starts)
- (car door closes)
JACK: Hey, and no Game Boy.
KEVIN: What?
Come on. There is no
Mario out in the wild.
(horn honks)
- BEC: Bye, guys. Good luck!
- KATE: Bye.
(Rebecca and Kate talking indistinctly)
♪
(knock on door)
(whispers): Hey.
You kept my daughters up
way too late last night.
Can't even get them out
of bed this morning.
Oh, my gosh.
Well, come on, dude.
I get, I get, like, what?
One night with my nieces before
I got to go to Sophie's,
- so sue me, okay?
- Okay.
But by the way, uh,
they kept me up, all right?
- Really?
- Annie's basically obsessed with me.
She keeps asking me questions
about Ron Howard and Sly Stallone.
I don't believe my daughter
asked you about Ron Howard.
- Listen, um...
- Yeah.
I need to borrow a tie
for Sophie's hospital
gala thing tonight.
- Yeah.
- And make it something sharp, too,
because they're actually
auctioning a date off
with yours truly to raise
money for the charity.
- Told me that.
- I tell you that?
- Told me that, like, four times.
- You jealous?
No black man will ever be
jealous of being auctioned.
Hashtag "AmericanHistory."
Uh, question for you.
Um, what do you think of Deja?
- I think Deja's lovely, adorable.
- Yeah.
You know, in, like, a surly,
nonverbal kind of way.
Well, she's only been here for a month,
so just tread lightly.
- What does that even mean?
- It means...
- It's my middle name, Tread Lightly.
- Just...
Oh, and don't say
anything about her hair.
Alright.
Want two?
Morning. How are you?
What is that?
Beth, you sure you don't want
to go to this gala tonight?
Gonna be fun.
Oh, man, you know I
love me a good Ke-vent.
But, uh, it's a little last
minute to get a babysitter.
Well, first of all, it's a Sophie-vent.
Uh, can I come?
To the gala?
Yeah. Of course. I mean, uh...
I would have to take you.
Kevin will be busy.
Is that, um, is that cool with you, Kev?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
The more the merrier. It's a great idea.
Cool.
Ow.
Um... sorry. Can you
excuse me one second?
What's up?
You really think she's ready to go
to some swanky Manhattan charity ball?
She said she wanted to go.
She actually seemed excited
about wanting to do something, Beth.
- We can't just ignore that.
- What you're ignoring
is the fact that she is
crushing on Kevin.
I'm gonna pretend like
I didn't hear that.
- Hey, hey.
- She's a 12-year-old girl,
and for better or for worse,
not that I think it...
- Just please don't say it.
- But your brother is
- smokin' hot.
- Don't even think it.
Oh, my God. This is disgusting.
I think it might be
too much for her, babe.
It's all those fancy people,
and it's way past her bedtime.
- She doesn't know...
- This is my opportunity
to connect with her.
And I don't care if Kevin...
Lord have mercy on my soul...
is the reason that she wants to go.
Trust me, it'll be fine.
And I get... No, I understand why.
But why doesn't it match
what Howard has?
It should be a fairly easy thing to say.
All right, just make it match.
Just make the work match.
- Hey! How you doing?
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah.
- In your office?
In my office.
All right, come on.
Oh. (scoffs)
Oh, you thought that I wanted to...?
Uh, yeah.
You said, "Can I talk
to you in your office."
That's how it always starts.
In the pornography that I don't watch.
I'm pregnant.
Excuse me?
I'm eight weeks pregnant.
(clears throat) Um...
S... Uh, so what
you're telling me is...?
We're... pregnant.
Well, that is...
the greatest thing I have
ever heard in my whole life.
- Oh, my God.
- (laughs)
(Toby laughs)
- Oh, that's wonderful!
- I'm glad you're happy.
Oh, I'm not happy. I'm ecstatic!
I'm-I'm aquiver!
I'm gonna put on my happy
song and I'm gonna be all...
No, no. Don't.
Right? 'Cause...
this might not happen. In fact,
it probably won't happen.
- What?
- I'm 37.
I'm having a geriatric pregnancy.
- Geriatric?
- Geriatric.
It's literally what it's called.
And because of my weight, you know?
And because, well, bad things
just seem to happen to me.
- I don't...
- Okay, I get it.
I do. I do. You don't
want to jinx things.
Not about jinxing.
(scoff) This is about hope.
It's about hoping that the
little lima bean inside of me...
turns into a grape.
And that the grape turns into a walnut,
and the walnut turns into an apricot.
And the days and the weeks
and months of hoping...
that it doesn't turn disastrous.
And your hoping is only gonna
make my hoping harder.
Okay? So I'm gonna ask you...
No, I'm gonna tell you.
Please keep...
whatever hopes and dreams that you have
about being a dad to yourself.
And never ever tell anyone
about them, including me.
Especially me.
Until the baby's living
outside of my body.
Okay.
BEC: Hey, Bug.
Are you ready?
I can't decide between
Honey, I Shrunk the Kids
or Turner & Hooch.
Huh. Well, we can't go see
both movies and get a manicure.
- (whispers): Or can we?
- (giggles)
- (phone ringing)
- Hey, baby, go grab a sweater, okay?
It's cold in the movies.
Pearsons.
WOMAN: May I speak with
Jack Pearson, please?
I'm sorry. He's not here.
Can I take a message?
Tell him that his father,
Stanley Pearson, is close to passing.
(phone ringing)
MAN (recorded): You've
reached the Willow Creek
Campground Ranger Station.
Please leave a message.
(beep)
BEC: Hi. Uh, I am leaving
this message for Jack Pearson.
Uh, he and my two sons are staying
at the Willow Creek Campground.
I need him to call me as soon as he can.
The nursing home where
his father Stanley is at
just called and said that he's ill.
Jack, if you're listening,
I need you to call me back.
How do you want me to handle this?
♪
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
STANLEY: Jack, enough!
(woman singing jazz music over radio)
Now, what we're after is rainbow trout.
What we'll probably catch are bass,
but what we don't want...
- Are catfish.
- And carp.
No carp.
You thirsty?
- JACK: Nope.
- STANLEY: I am.
(engine turns off)
- Be right back.
- Okay.
(doorbells jingle)
(hammer clinking)
KEVIN: It's my turn to hammer.
RANDALL: Wait, I haven't
hammered it yet.
Hey, guys! Guys!
Less arguing, more tent-building.
- Okay.
- (sighs) Grab that string.
Oh, I get it.
This goes up like this.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about right there.
- Teamwork, huh?
- It's up! This is awesome!
We have so much...
- (Randall shouts)
- (Kevin laughs)
Ugh, Dad!
Can you help me, please?!
KEVIN: Help, help! The sky is falling!
- JACK: Okay.
- Ah, it's funny.
- Come on out.
- Did you have fun in there?
Get over here.
Over here. Right now.
Do you think that's funny?
If I said yes, would you be mad?
He's your brother, Kevin.
You should be able
to depend on each other
more than anyone else, more than
anyone else in the world.
Look at me.
You will be good to your brother.
Now rebuild that tent.
When you're done,
you're gonna sit inside it.
- For how long?
- Until I tell you you can come out.
♪
KEVIN: Hey, uh... this is
Kevin Pearson calling,
uh, leaving a message for Dr. Lu.
I realize it's the weekend.
Sorry about that.
Um, but I am in New York right now,
and I ran out of my prescription
for, uh, for my Vicodin again.
It's no big deal. Uh, I realize
we've gone through
all of the, uh, the refills.
So, you know, uh, hit me back
when you get a chance.
Thank you very much.
Who you talking to?
Uh, it was Kate. She had a...
universal remote problem.
Okay, so this is option number two.
Well, hello.
Hello. I love option number two.
You don't think it's too... flowery?
Too flowery? Is that...
Can you possibly be too flowery?
No, it's great. I love it. Huge fan.
Really?
Starting a little early.
It's just beer.
It's the weekend. We wrapped a movie,
and I'm-I'm, uh, I'm celebrating that.
- I'm relaxing a little bit.
- Okay, well, just,
you know, try to pace yourself
'cause we have a long
night of schmoozing.
Tell me about it.
I'm sorry, Soph.
I'm just, you know, tired.
- Little tired.
- Yeah.
I'm happy to be here with you, though.
- Yeah. Me, too.
- Yeah.
(Kevin sighs)
Wasn't there, like, a-a third option
you were gonna show me?
I think it's too booby.
It's too booby?
- Let's go with that one.
- (laughs)
Does she like the dress you got her?
- She looks fantastic.
- Hey, don't say anything
about the way she looks.
I wasn't gonna tell her...
And no jokes, okay?
You're a terrible joke teller.
That's hurtful and untrue.
- I'm very funny.
- Man, just be cool.
I'm Randall "Cool" Pearson.
Oh, no.
That's my middle name. Yeah.
You ready?
Okay.
Have a nice time.
See you later.
- Hey.
- Huh?
Cool means normal.
- All right?
- No, it doesn't.
Cool means cool. (clicks tongue)
You see that Michaels over there?
Used to be a Kohl's.
Right.
Ah, and that Dunkin' Donuts
by the light.
That used to be a Dairy Queen.
Man, I used to love me a Blizzard.
You down with DQ?
(singsongy): The DQ Blizzard.
♪
Hi, uh, I spoke to someone on the phone.
I'm here for Stanley Pearson.
I'm his daughter-in-law,
Rebecca Pearson.
♪
(whispers): Hi.
I'm Rebecca.
Jack's wife.
Um...
the nursing home called me.
And Jack wasn't home, so, um, here I am.
Is there anything that I can do for you?
Okay, well, um...
It was nice to have finally met you.
I'm sorry that it's under
these circumstances.
I know you and Jack
had a pretty difficult relationship.
Um, that's a vast understatement.
You sure there's nothing that I can do?
Is that my granddaughter?
Excuse me.
- (whispers): Is that my grandpa?
- Kate.
♪
He's coming back.
(video game music playing)
I said no Game Boy. Turn it off, now.
- Why are you so hard on him?
- I'm not.
Yes, you are, Kev,
and I want you to tell me why.
- (sighs) He's annoying.
- No, he's not annoying.
He... He's just trying to show
you how much he loves you.
You know, it...
it would be so easy
for you to be nice to him.
But it takes you more energy
and causes more trouble,
you being mean to him like you are.
So why... why can't you
just be nice to him?
I don't know.
That's not a good enough answer, Kevin.
I want you to tell me why.
- I don't know!
- Is it because
he gets special attention sometimes?
You know, 'cause all you kids,
you need something different.
At different moments,
you need something different
- all the t...
- I don't know! Stop!
You said I had to sit in here.
You didn't say we had to talk about it.
I don't want to talk about it.
Okay.
We'll talk about it later.
(video game music playing)
- (gentle jazz music playing)
- (lively chatter)
When I walked to the classroom
of my new school
and saw all those new faces, I thought,
"Whoa. None of these
kids looks like me."
I felt like I am in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Beam me up, Scotty.
That's a Star Trek reference.
You know Star Trek?
"These are the voyages
of the starship Enterprise."
Oh, there's your brother.
KEVIN: I'm starting to get
really uncomfortable here,
and, uh... you know,
if I could get that refill,
that would be... that would be great.
Um, it's no big deal,
but call me back, please.
All right.
Hey! Look at you.
- You clean up nice, don't you?
- RANDALL: Hey.
- Good to see you.
- Don't talk about her hair.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- All right. Uh, oh.
- Hey.
- This is, uh, this is Sophie.
- Good to see you.
Sophie's my girlfriend.
SOPHIE: Hi!
I love your dress.
I like your hair, by the way.
It's very, very...
sort of Halle Berry in Swordfish.
Thanks.
Um, I like The Manny.
You do?
Do you watch The Manny?
What's your favorite episode?
Which one's your favorite?
"Iron Manny"?
"The Thin Manny"? "Manny Get Your Gun"?
- I'm gonna grab a drink.
- "Of Mice and Mannys"?
"Manny-Pedi"?
- (laughs)
- I thought you were a fan.
♪
Hey, kiddo.
I'm sorry this is so boring.
I just want to wait a little bit longer
and see if your dad calls back.
You think Dad's gonna look
like that when he's old?
Better not.
I don't want to get old like that.
I don't want my hair to fall out.
You do have really,
really beautiful hair.
You know that? (chuckles)
You want to guess how much hair
you had when you were born?
Like, almost none.
- Ew!
- (laughs) Not ew.
What about Kevin and Randall?
- Eggheads.
- (laughs)
All three of you
were just big old eggheads.
- Totally bald. (chuckles)
- (laughs)
But that's how it works.
Everything changes all the time.
And when you're a mom,
you get a front row seat
to the best show in town:
watching your kids grow up.
Give me that egghead.
It's underneath
all this hair somewhere, right?
(both laugh)
WOMAN: I'm at
this cocktail party, right?
And they're serving
these mini pizzas
with Gorgonzola and pear,
which is just my favorite thing
in the whole world, you know?
And I just panic. Bolt.
And I-I'm standing out by the valet,
and this guy is smoking a cigarette,
and I-I just, like, ask him for one.
And he turns out to be
really nice and super cute.
(chuckles) His name is Terrence,
and we've kind of
been seeing each other.
But that's not the point.
The point is...
I've started smoking.
Vaping, actually.
You're vaping?
That was the point?
It's, like, a gateway thing.
Oh. Okay.
So, to review:
you exit a cocktail party
serving delicious mini pizzas,
you smoke one cigarette,
you meet a guy... a nice guy
whose name is Terrence...
And now you're dating.
And now you're whining about vaping?
- Vaping?!
- Seriously?
You're snapping at me? Again?
I am. Again.
Do you know why no one's defending you?
Because you don't have a problem!
The people that come here have problems.
Real problems with real issues.
What do you come here for, anyway?
So you can feel better about yourself
'cause you're not
as screwed up as we are?
Screw you, Madison.
(scoffs)
(scoffs mockingly)
Would anyone else like to share?
MADISON: Screw you, Kate!
Screw you and your terrible attitude,
and that is not an easy
thing for me to say
because confrontation makes me cry!
Why do you hate me?
Because you're annoying
and you shouldn't be here.
Well, I think you're annoying.
The way that you and your fiancé
come here every week
and smile and giggle at each other
when some of us don't have
anyone to do that with.
You have the guy that you vape with.
His name is Terrence!
And he probably won't last,
because, you know what,
nobody I date ever does.
Do you think it's because
you're annoying?
Oh, my God! You suck!
(sighs)
(engine starts)
- (car beeps)
- (crash)
- (shouts)
- Oh, my God.
- (panting)
- (car door opens, closes)
(Madison groans)
Are you insane?!
- (crying)
- Oh, my God, are you actually hurt?
I don't... I don't...
I don't know. I-I...
I don't think so.
Kate, it was just a little tap.
- Are you serious?
- No, but I'm pregnant.
(sniffles)
I just freaked out for a second.
(shuddering breath)
But, um... but I'm...
uh, I'm fine.
(chuckles): Kate.
Oh, my God, you're pregnant?
Yeah. I know, I know. It's hard, um...
- it's hard to believe, but...
- Kate.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Oh. (chuckles)
That's amazing! I'm so happy for you!
- (chuckles) Thanks.
- Oh, my God.
Yeah, but don't tell anyone,
because it's still real...
really early stages, okay?
(mouthing)
(squeals, laughs)
(chuckles, sniffles)
You may know him as
television's very own Manny,
But the next item on our auction agenda
is a whole lot more than that.
He's starring in Ron Howard's
new World War II epic,
Hill 400, that just finished shooting.
- Oh, no, you d...
- (gasps)
Sorry, you don't...
you don't eat that part.
You don't eat that part.
I'm sorry. I just didn't want
you to choke... that's all.
You okay?
I have to go to the bathroom.
So, without further ado,
may I introduce to you the one,
the only, Kevin Pearson.
(applause)
Uh, thank you for hitting me
back on a weekend.
I really appreciate it.
Listen, I was just... I was hoping
we could get one more, uh...
one more refill on the prescription.
(applause continues)
Kevin Pearson, ladies and gentlemen.
Right. No, I-I understand
you've already refilled
the prescription one more time
than you should have,
but I-I don't know why
it's that big of a deal.
(applause continues)
Kevin Pearson!
Well, I don't have a doctor out here.
All right, look, you know what,
here's the thing though.
If you can't help a guy
when he's in pain, right...
Which I obviously am...
Then you're kind of useless.
And-and, I'm sorry, I find it ridiculous
that you're treating me this way.
You know what, take my
headshot off the wall, okay?
It's-it's a doctor's
office, not a diner.
Hello? Hello?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
- (birds chirping)
- (grunts)
Here you go, bud.
Kevin's fine.
I bet he's hungry.
I know that you love
your brother, Randall,
and you want him to
love you, and he does.
- Yeah, right.
- He does.
I promise you.
But, look, sometimes...
sometimes you got to...
give people some space,
let them come to you.
Just got to be patient.
But I don't like patience.
Nobody likes patience.
Hey, Kev.
Randall.
What are we doing?
RANDALL: Deja's in there.
Is she okay? Is she...
- is she sick?
- Of me, I think.
But she likes you.
No. No, no, no.
She likes that I was the Manny.
- No. Kev, bro, she likes you.
- (sighs)
You're good with her.
You're good with people.
I come on too strong.
That's why I'm standing
out here, trying to...
stop myself from barging
into the women's room
to make her talk to me.
Madam.
How are we?
I should not go in there.
No. No, you should not go in there.
- But I'm going to.
- I know.
I'm definitely going to.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- (sighs)
- You know why?
- Hmm?
- 'Cause you care too much.
Yeah.
You always have.
You just...
- You feel too much.
- Yeah.
- And I... I mean, I... (chuckles)
- Hmm.
- I try not to feel anything at all.
- No, that's not true.
It is true. It's true, Randall.
Hey, you okay?
(chuckles softly)
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going in.
- Hey, Randall. You know, there...
- Hmm?
There could be a woman...
(whispers) pooping in there.
I know.
Man coming in.
- (birds chirping)
- (horn honks)
(engine turns off)
Jack Pearson?
Yeah, I'm Jack.
Got your wife on the radio.
- She's patched through to the phone.
- (static crackling)
Did she say what's wrong?
No, she's been trying to reach
you all day. Just push to talk.
(static crackling)
Bec? Bec, what's wrong?
Yeah, every-everybody's fine.
Everything's okay.
Um, I just, uh...
The nursing home where
your dad is at called.
My dad?
And I couldn't get ahold
of you, so I came.
You're not mad at me, are you?
Wait, y-you're at
my father's nursing home?
Wh-What's wrong with him?
He's old.
I think it's, uh, cirrhosis.
But he's...
dying, Jack.
I mean, I don't think that
he really has much time left.
Do you... want to come back?
No, uh, I'm gonna stay
here with the boys.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I mean, is there anything
that you want me to... tell him?
No.
No, that man's been dead
to me for a long time.
How are... how are the boys doing?
Well, baby steps, but...
we'll get there.
You are a miracle.
You know that, Jack?
Coming from your dad
and being the dad that you are,
you are a freaking miracle.
Yeah, well, takes one to know one, Bec.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Bye.
♪
Hey, babe?
Yeah?
Uh, so, I got good and bad news.
Uh-oh. Always bad news first.
(sighs) I banged up the car.
What? Are you all right?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
It was just a fender bender.
(exhales) Okay.
And the good news?
The person I got in the
accident with was Madison.
- Did you kill her?
- No.
Oh. I thought you said it was good news.
But I did tell her
that we were pregnant.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
And?
And it actually felt
good saying it out loud.
Really?
- And I want you to come with me.
- Okay, where are we going?
- Just come with me.
- Okay, where we going?
- Don't ask questions.
- I'm right behind you.
- I'm not gonna ask any questions.
- Okay.
Where are we going?
(smooth jazz music playing)
Ah, sorry about that. Mwah.
How are you? So, what, uh...
what'd I miss?
Huh?
You see that nice lady over there?
- KEVIN: Uh-huh.
- She bought you.
14 grand.
(sighs)
Oh. (stammers) Like, I missed it?
That you did.
- Oh, wow.
- Where the hell were you, Kevin?
Uh, I was in the...
Ron called, you know?
Something about dailies and
we need to reshoot a few things,
I guess, or he thinks maybe
we do, maybe we don't...
You embarrassed me.
You embarrassed me
in front of my friends
and coworkers.
You're not gonna say anything?
I don't know what you want me
to say though, you know? I...
I'm sorry.
Why? Why did you choose to get drunk?
- Tonight. My night.
- Okay, calm down.
This wasn't like somebody, you know...
Like, it wasn't a choice.
I didn't plan it.
Really? Somebody just
put a gun to your head
and told you to drink a dozen bourbons?
Okay. All right. Look, here we go.
Pile on, Sophie. The...
- Jump in, the water's warm.
- Oh, no.
Don't you do that. Don't you
make me the nagging girlfriend
- when you were a jerk. That...
- Okay. All right. No, no. Okay.
(whispers): I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
You're right. I'm-I'm just...
I'm, you know...
You're what?
You're what, Kevin?
You've been weird ever since
you got back to New York.
- Have I? Okay.
- Yeah.
You know, I-I never should have agreed
to come here tonight, okay?
I didn't want to let you down,
that's the truth, but I am...
I'm exhausted, you know?
Now, look, I-I'm gonna...
I-I got to get...
I probably just need some air,
so I'm gonna go, you know...
I'll meet you back at your place, okay?
♪
DEJA: You gonna stand out there forever?
Yep.
You can't grab me like that.
The second-to-last home was the worst.
I was always in trouble there.
We all were.
It was because of the magazines.
Foster mom, Alice,
she had these subscriptions
to all the beauty magazines...
Glamour, Vogue, Cosmo.
I think her boyfriend knew
that we thought it was funny,
'cause she was ugly.
(chuckles softly)
She was butt-ugly.
That's why he used them on us.
The magazines.
Because they didn't bruise much.
That's why I don't like being grabbed.
♪
(door unlocks)
- Okay.
So you can tell anyone in here.
And then we'll never come here again.
- Anyone in here?
- Yeah.
Okay, do I have to speak in code?
Uh, 'cause I don't think
they're gonna get it.
No. Go crazy. Use the "P" word.
- Bold move. I like it.
- Mm.
Um, I think that's my dude.
Just-just wait right here, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
Uh, excuse me, my good man.
Do you think that you could play
just one song for me
- on your house system?
- Uh...
Just, uh, hear me out. Um...
You see that beautiful woman over there?
She is pregnant with my child.
Well, congrats, man. That's awesome.
Thanks. So, what do you say?
(exhales)
- One song. Great.
- Just this once.
Okay, it's my happy song,
and it's all cued up.
Uh, he's just gonna
charge it a little for me.
Those batteries, they go... (whooshes)
So he's just gonna charge it.
("Only Wanna Be With You" by
Hootie & the Blowfish playing)
- Toby?
- What?
- Tobias?
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I... had to.
♪ You and me, we come from
different worlds... ♪
How's it going? We're pregnant.
Hi there. We're having a baby.
♪ When I look at other girls ♪
♪ Sometimes you're crazy ♪
♪ And you wonder why ♪
♪ I'm such a baby 'cause
the Dolphins make me cry ♪
♪ Well, there's nothing I can do ♪
♪ I've been looking for
a girl like you... ♪
(Kate shrieks)
(laughing)
All right, we can go now.
♪ You look at me, you got
nothing left to say. ♪
(video game music playing)
(music stops)
(sighs)
♪
Are these cold yet?
You guys have one of those for me?
Here.
(grunts) Hand me that bag.
You better spin that one.
(chuckles) Ooh! Ooh!
Jack's not coming.
("Ballad of the Dying Man"
by Father John Misty playing)
Just so you know,
your son is a great father
and provider and husband.
You think you screwed
him up, but you didn't.
- You only made him stronger.
- (howling)
(all howling)
♪ Naturally the dying man
wonders to himself... ♪
(howling continues)
♪ Had his commentary been more lucid ♪
- ♪ Than anybody else?
- (horn honks)
♪ And had he successfully beaten ♪
♪ Back the rising tide... ♪
- Hi!
(laughs): I missed you.
Hey, bud.
- It was so awesome.
- Yeah?
- Gonna get you!
- (kids chattering playfully)
(Rebecca laughs)
♪ Lord, just a little more ♪
♪ Time ♪
♪ Oh, in ♪
♪ No time at all ♪
♪ This'll be the distant ♪
♪ Past... ♪