Previously on This Is Us...
Let's do one for your father.
(groans)
A handyman with triplets.
He's a construction foreman,
and he does very well for himself.
Not well enough.
He cannot support three children.
What if we get a kid
that has serious issues
that we're not prepared for?
- Those are mine.
- I'm putting your clothes in this.
- Give them back, you bitch!
- Hey.
- RANDALL: Whoa, whoa. Beth?
- (Deja screams)
We're okay. Everybody's okay.
No, everything is... It... Yeah.
♪
JACK: Five minutes, people.
We still got to get
to the grocery store
before it really starts coming down.
(gasps) How about Broadcast News?
You're always trying to get me
to watch Broadcast News.
Has it worked yet?
- Huh.
- (sighs)
- Road House?
- Ooh.
I do like me some Patrick Swayze.
And I'm vetoing Road House.
Hey, Randall. You find anything yet?
No. If we really get snowed in,
I'm gonna focus
on my Rube Goldberg machine.
The science fair
is only three weeks away.
Enough with the science fair, Randall!
- Hey, Kev, cool it.
- KATE: I picked mine.
It's about a baby who can talk.
John Travolta. Yes, please.
- What is it with you today?
- What?
No! Someone already rented
all three of The Karate Kid!
Oh, no. How is my boy gonna survive
this tragedy of titanic proportions?
(grunts)
- Stop making fun of me.
- What's up with you?
I just want to go home.
- Yeah.
- There's no movies,
- and it's really hot in here.
- What is wrong with you?
Hey, Jack?
He's burning up.
Mom, I don't have time to talk
about Mrs. Korzen's
daughter's new Pontiac.
I just need to know
if I had chicken pox as a kid.
- I'm so itchy, Dad. I'm gonna die.
- I promise you,
kiddo, in the history of chicken pox,
no one's ever died.
- Well, ac...
- REBECCA: Okay.
Yeah. I have sick kids. Mm-hmm.
Mom, I got to go. Okay, bye.
I had them when I was three.
And my mother is exhausting.
Good. Since you both had it,
you don't need to worry
about getting sick again.
Which is a relief, because
it's much worse as an adult.
Now, Randall doesn't have a fever
or any symptoms yet like Kevin and Kate.
I have a pretty strong immune system.
That's an excellent thing, sir.
But I always recommend
that siblings try and
get it all together.
One fell swoop and knock it out.
Are you people insane?
And then Grandpa Williams
started flying the helicopter.
Then we got cotton candy ice cream,
- and I woke up.
- (chuckles)
That is definitely a wild dream.
What about you, Deja?
Remember any of your dreams?
Yeah, me neither, usually.
Okay. You get to go, mamacita.
- Thank you.
- You got it.
Um...
I could do your hair,
too, Deja, if you want.
Picked up some new barrettes.
Fun jewel tones.
The girls will vouch for me.
I never pull too hard.
- I'd give you a B-plus.
- Yeah.
(chuckles) No, I'm good.
Okay.
All right, little mamas,
why don't you get your things
ready for school?
Here you go.
See you in a bit.
I don't know what to do.
I've changed Annie's hairstyle
four times this week
just to make hair care look cool.
As cute as those Afro puffs were,
Deja's not taking the hint.
It's been two weeks.
She has to wash that hair.
Well, she's testing her boundaries.
Trying to push us away.
We knew this might happen.
- Scalp is stinking up the kitchen.
- (sighs)
I think we have to have a real
sit-down talk about this.
Look, she already
doesn't like it here, Beth.
You think telling her,
"Hey, we all had a little chat
and agreed your hair is funky,"
is gonna make her feel welcome?
Yeah, 'cause that's the
way I would say it.
Come on, Randall.
It's a hygiene issue.
We have to address it.
I know, but I...
Look, for nine years,
you got to be the lead parent...
"Lead parent"?
While I've been
sitting in that office,
talking about weather patterns.
But now you're working full-time
and looking damn fine
- in those suede heels, might I add.
- I know.
I know you do.
Look, Annie scrapes her knee,
and she still goes to you first
for the boo-boo kiss.
Are we seriously having a
conversation right now
about the order of
Annie's boo-boo kisses?
May I take the lead here? Please?
I just want her to feel
like she fits in first
before we say something
that may alienate her even more.
And who knows?
Maybe when she's more
comfortable with us,
she may want to wash it herself.
All right.
She better get comfortable quick,
'cause your girl is getting ripe.
(Randall sighs)
♪
MAN (over TV): Let them burn.
Keeping those abs nice and tight.
TOBY: If you want
to eat the muffin, kid,
- eat the muffin.
- I don't want to.
Well, I didn't make it
to be a TV hood ornament.
That right there is
the healthiest poppy seed muffin
you will ever eat.
I made it with whole wheat,
unsweetened almond milk
and grape-seed oil.
It is so healthy, in fact,
it hardly qualifies as a muffin.
Quit trying to get
me to eat the muffin.
All right.
Well, then, stop staring at it
for a second and look at me.
You have been kicking toned ass
the last couple weeks.
- Thank you.
- But it feels... obsessive.
You've already thrown away half
of the stuff in our kitchen.
It wasn't organic.
You go to weight group every single day.
Last night, I think you were
treadmilling in your sleep.
And, you know, we haven't really been...
connecting.
(sighs)
- We had sex two days ago.
- I know, and you were checking
your Fitbit calorie burn the whole time.
All right. I'm sorry.
(sighs) It's just that
this is the first big event
that I've been paid to sing at,
and it needs to go amazing,
- and I got to fit in that dress.
- I know, and you're gonna.
And you're gonna look
amazing in that dress.
All the 13-year-old boys
at the bat mitzvah
are gonna be shvitzing
for you in that dress.
Cute. So, can you
turn the video back on?
- Uh...
- I have 15 minutes left in the workout.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(clears throat)
MAN (on TV): Work those
heels, delts here.
Hey-hey, Kevin.
- Brian, hey. How are you?
- Hey.
Yeah, I'm good.
Hey, can I see you a second?
Yeah, you kidding me?
I always have time for you,
my all-time favorite producer.
Just don't tell Dean I said that
'cause he gets a little...
- jealous.
- Yeah. Can I see your leg?
Can you lift up your pant leg?
(laughs)
Uh, higher.
- Really?
- Higher.
Usually you have to buy a guy dinner
- before you...
- (laughs) Yeah. No.
Seriously.
All right.
- Kevin. Oh, my God.
- I know.
Listen, it-it... This looks
a lot worse than it actually is.
You know, I got
a little banged up in that scene
I did with Stallone, but I'm-I'm fine.
Why do you think we have
- a medic on the set?
- No, I know.
- I didn't want to slow down production.
- There's a reason.
- You know, 'cause... See?
- Uh, hey.
Can you find Delaney
for me right away...
- No. Brian.
- So I can go over today's schedule?
Brian, I'm the king of powering
through things like this.
K-Kevin, I wasn't asking.
I wasn't asking.
Ow. They really hurt, Dad.
Yeah, I know you're suffering, pal,
but your sister, she's
got the same thing,
and she's handling it like a champ.
- So?
- So, I-I'm thinking you'll feel better
if you toughen up a bit.
I'm gonna go ahead and run you guys
an oatmeal bath here in a bit,
- all right?
- Randall, what are you doing?
Yeah, what are you wearing, bud?
It's 20 degrees out.
I'm exposing myself to chicken
pox like Dr. Grader said.
- I need to get it and get it over with
- (doorbell rings)
- before the science fair.
- No, you're gonna get frostbite
or pneumonia, all right?
So just go upstairs
and put your jams on.
- (sighs)
- Mom?
Oh, you sounded so
- overwhelmed on the phone.
- What? Hi.
I thought, she needs an extra hand
to help with those sick kids.
Thank God I made it in before
it started really coming down.
- Aw, you poor things.
- (sighs)
- Hi, Jack.
- Hi.
Would you mind getting my stuff
- out of the car?
- (Rebecca sighs)
You know, and you might
need to salt that walkway
while you're out there, 'cause
I almost slipped, broke my neck.
- (mouthing)
- Oh, for God's sakes.
It's the middle of winter.
Where are Randall's clothes?
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
So, what are we looking at here, Dr Lo?
You have a large tear in your meniscus.
It's likely it was slightly damaged
when you fractured your
knee, which was...
Uh, I fractured my knee
about 20 years ago.
It's been pretty fine since then.
Until two weeks ago.
I'm assuming you've been in
quite a bit of pain since then.
Yeah, I tried taking painkillers
for a few days,
but I didn't like the
way it made me feel.
And rather than coming to see me
to get the knee looked at,
- you decided to...
- Tough it out. Yeah.
Uh, look, here's the thing.
We're almost done with the movie, okay?
So I really need to get
back to work next week
so that I can finish my
last three scenes, so...
...how do I do that?
How do we make that happen?
Well, we can do a simple
arthroscopic surgery
to remove the tear.
Three small incisions,
in and out in an hour.
Many patients walk the same day.
♪
KEVIN: I itch everywhere, Grandma.
I even have chicken pox
in a place I can't talk about.
(chuckles): Aw.
You poor angel. Look at you.
You must feel awful.
Would presents from Grandma
make everyone feel better?
- Hmm.
- (chuckles)
Here we go.
Hey, what is she doing here?
Did you invite her?
No, I'm not a masochist, Jack.
I did not invite her.
Two minutes in,
and she's already commenting
on what a mess the house is.
I mean, we have ten-year-old triplets.
I don't know what she was expecting.
What are we gonna do?
Well, we can't put her in a car
and send her back to Connecticut.
- It's... No. No. We can't.
- Really?
- It's snowing like crazy outside.
- (sighs, groans)
Look, we're-we're just
gonna have to get through it.
- (groans)
- Just don't let her bait you.
I don't let her bait me.
- Well, I beg to differ, Bunny.
- (exasperated grunt)
I hate when she calls me Bunny.
I don't even like bunnies.
Where does that come from?
Says the woman that cannot be baited.
Ha.
Okay, look, hey, hey.
What if a third set of hands
is actually gonna be
helpful with the kids?
(laughs) You're really
cute when you're dumb.
Yeah?
- Don't leave me alone with her.
- I know.
- Come on.
- Remember when you wanted
- to put that in the wedding vows?
- Yeah.
JANET: Here you go.
Little Mermaid?
- Thanks, Grandma!
- Yeah.
I think it's a little too small.
You can use it as your goal dress.
REBECCA: Mom.
Sweetheart, no, no.
We'll return it for the right size.
'Cause I'm sure that
Grandma kept the receipt.
(quietly): Yeah.
And I think that you should try out
for your school team;
I think you'd be a natural.
It's the third basketball
that she's given him.
- You realize that?
- I know.
I don't really play, Grandma, but...
I guess I could try if
you really want me to.
Well, everyone should have something
that they're really good at.
RANDALL: You're gonna
love bowling, Deja.
Now, we are a family
that falls on two sides
of the lane bumper debate.
I say, hey, they make us all better.
Beth would disagree with that,
- but Beth ain't here, now, is she?
- (laughs)
Hey, let's take our shoes off
so we'll be ready to give
them to the cashier.
I'm not giving somebody my shoes.
But we have to rent
bowling shoes, Deja.
It's okay... They'll give you yours back
as soon as we're done.
Why would I want to wear
somebody else's gross shoes?
- No, no, don't worry.
- Daddy,
- I don't want to rent shoes, either.
- Annie, please, not now.
- Dad, come on, it's our turn to go.
- Yeah, w...
Okay, hey, uh...
how about I ask them if you
can bowl in your socks?
- I'm not wearing socks.
- You're not...
GIRL: Bet her feet are
nastier than her hair.
What did you say?
- Nothing.
- No, I heard you.
- I wasn't talking to you.
- If you got something to say,
you could say it to my face.
Okay. Fine.
Your hair's nasty.
RANDALL: Whoa, hey. Deja.
- Stop.
- Hey, don't touch her.
I'm sorry about that, man.
She shouldn't have done that.
- No, what the hell is your problem?
- Come on, girls.
- Let's go.
- No, no, no, you don't just walk away.
She needs to apologize.
Excuse me, sir, would
you back up, please?
Are you all right, Maya?
- Hmm? She hit you hard?
- She didn't hit her.
Okay? Your daughter was
being a frickin' bully.
Don't blame my daughter because
you can't control yours.
Bro, I think you need
to watch your tone.
- Did you not hear me?
- No, brah, I heard you.
You really need to back up right now.
Look, if your daughter can't
keep her hands to herself...
I'm not his daughter.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
♪
SOPHIE (over phone): Honey,
I'm so sorry I can't be there
to help nurse you through your recovery.
Yeah, no, you and me
both; We could live out
- a very specific fantasy of mine.
- Dude, she's a nurse.
- You can live out that fantasy anytime.
- Lucky me.
Maybe I could get Brooks
or Bishop to pick up
- my shifts this weekend.
- No, it's okay.
I've got my instructions
from the doctor,
Toby's here, Kate's here.
They're gonna take care of me.
I'm in good hands.
(sighs): Okay.
How's your pain?
On a scale of one to ten.
It's manageable, you know,
but my needing to pee is
about a 12 and a half right now,
so I'm gonna let you go.
- Okay?
- Okay. If you need anything...
I know, I know. You're here.
I love you. I'll talk to you soon.
- I love you, too.
- Good-bye.
- Oh, hey, Tobe?
- Hmm?
Will you be good with him for a while?
I'm gonna try to make my yoga class.
What? No. He literally
just got out of surgery.
You heard him, he's fine.
Plus, I missed my workout this morning,
'cause we were at the hospital.
Sorry. Are you kidding me?
Go get the dress.
Try it on. I swear it fits.
- You know what, I'll go get the dress.
- Tobe?
- Yeah?
- I'm not trying on the dress.
- I'm going to yoga class. Kev?
- KEVIN: Hmm?
- I'll be back in an hour.
- Okay.
- Tobe's here.
- Love you.
- KEVIN: You, too.
Love you, Tobe. Love you.
(door closes)
Ah, maybe give her a break, you know?
- She's got bat mitzvah jitters.
- Yeah.
Um...
All right, it says you're supposed
to... take these painkillers
with food, so you want me to make you
- a quesadilla or something?
- No, no, no, I'm good.
I'm not taking those things.
I took a couple of those
when I first got injured,
they made my mind all fuzzy,
and I need to be sharp
for this recovery.
- Okay, um...
- Oh, it's time.
I'm gonna peel this
sucker off right now.
Uh, no, no. Don't.
The nurse said that step one
- is RICE.
- Yeah.
All right?
Rest, ice, compress, elevate.
- In about... in a week's time,
- (groans)
I got to be parachuting down
on a bunch of Nazis in Normandy,
so this has to go quickly,
you know? Don't worry.
Trust me, Toby, I'm a champion
when it comes to stuff like this.
KEVIN: Dad!
Hey, Kev, you can't
be scratching like that.
- Wh-Where are your oven mitts?
- They were too hot.
Everything's too hot.
You said the medicine would help.
Yeah, well, it's only been seven
minutes since you took it, pal.
You got to give it time.
It's gonna kick in and help, I promise.
No, it won't!
I feel worse than I did before.
Kev, stop, stop.
- Let go! I need to itch!
- No.
Look, being sick sucks. I know it, okay?
I-I think you're making it
worse on yourself
by focusing on it so much.
Hey, look, come here. Stand up.
Come on, trust me. Stand up.
(sighs)
(roars)
What are you doing?! Stop!
You... are tougher than that itch.
Look at me.
You're stronger than that itch.
You're not a mere mortal, son.
You are a Pearson. Look at me.
Now, let me hear your battle cry.
- (roars)
- (short roar)
Do it like you mean it. From here.
(roars)
(roars loudly)
- (roars)
- There you go! Own that itch!
Own that itch. Let me hear
your roar one more time.
(both roaring)
Uh, please don't. Please don't.
Grandma has a headache.
Don't scratch that
beautiful face of yours, Kevin.
It's gonna take you far one day.
Really?
(crickets chirping)
Baby, stop.
- What?
- Your internal meltdown
is literally making the bed hot.
Why did I think she'd like bowling?
Well, who actually likes bowling?
It was cool for a minute there
when The Big Lebowski came out,
but that was, like, 20 years ago, right?
I meant go to sleep, but okay.
I was so sure I had
the right angle on this, Beth.
We were gonna have fun,
and then she would feel good,
and we could talk.
And instead I just made things
a whole lot worse for her.
Can't believe you were gonna throw down
- with some jackass in bowling shoes.
- (sighs)
I should've just listened
to you in the first place.
You knew. Of course you knew.
You got the hygiene talk on lock.
Right up there with...
untangling necklaces
and perfectly round scoops of ice cream.
The trick is you just
have to run the scooper
- under hot water first.
- I know what the trick is, Beth.
I'm just wallowing. Okay, I'm done.
I'm sorry it didn't end up
the way you wanted it.
You should talk to her.
I will.
- In the morning.
- Right.
- Just let me hug you!
- (Kate screams)
- I need to get sick!
- Leave me alone!
Guys, enough! Guys! Stop!
Hey, Randall, there are germs
all over this house.
You will get sick, you
just have to be patient, okay?
Why don't you go upstairs
and finish your project
- before you get sick?
- Good idea.
- Whoa. Sorry, Grandma.
- Okay.
Wait, do you want to
see my Rube Goldberg
machine I'm building
for the science fair?
You knock over some dominoes,
and then a race car goes down
a slide and hits a marble.
And then I haven't
figured out the middle yet,
but by the end, a marker draws
a line on a piece of paper.
Right. Well, why don't you
show me when it works.
Did you sauté the onions first?
- I did.
- How much thyme did you add?
- 'Cause you don't need more than a...
- I did half a tablespoon.
Well, you're gonna need more than that.
Do you want to make the soup, Mom?
- Sure.
- Yeah?
- I'm more than happy to help.
- Thank you.
Go for it.
- I like your soup best, Mom.
- Thank you.
Well, your mother actually learned
how to make this from me.
I can teach you, too, if you want.
A woman should know how to
cook if she wants to have
a husband and children of her own.
- She's ten, Mom.
- Well, Lord knows
I wasn't the prettiest girl
in Erie, Pennsylvania,
but I somehow roped your father
with the best pot roast and
green bean casserole in town.
- Did your mom teach you?
- Yeah, she did.
But this recipe right here
actually comes from a maid that we had
- when your mother was a little girl.
- You had a maid?
Mm-hmm. A lovely black woman named Dora.
Of course, I was always
correcting her English,
so that you girls didn't start
speaking like street kids.
- Jack? Where are you?
- Dad's got a fever, too.
- What? -Yeah, it-it... it just hit me.
- JANET: Oh, God.
I thought you said you'd
had the chickenpox before.
- No, I did. I did, I think.
- (Groans)
Probably measles.
- Jack.
- Oh, crap.
Why don't you go upstairs
and go to bed, Jack.
We got everything
under control here without you.
Don't we, Bunny?
♪
You going somewhere?
I pushed a girl, so you're
kicking me out, right?
You spent the whole night thinking that?
We're not kicking you out, Deja.
Honey, sit.
Come on, Deja, bag down.
- Please, sit.
- (pats bed)
You're right.
We don't push other people in our house.
You push somebody again,
and you'll be grounded.
But I hope it doesn't happen again.
Is that it, then?
Um...
you know...
I grew up with three
very opinionated sisters
and one very opinionated mother.
Fights, arguments,
cold shoulders, yelling matches...
You name it, the Clarke
women did not play.
But no matter who wasn't talking to who,
or who stole whose favorite
tube of candy apple lipstick,
we always came together
to do each other's hair.
Because my mom believed...
Still believes...
That... how you present
yourself on the outside
reflects how you feel on the inside.
Look, I don't know why you're
not washing your hair, Deja.
But I do know we have to
get it taken care of.
So, if you don't want to do it yourself,
I'm happy to take you
to my salon. I love it there.
It's really nice,
and I spend way too much money there,
and it's worth every damn penny.
Let me know what you decide, okay?
In the meantime,
you can just go ahead and unpack.
Will you do my hair?
Brady, hey. What's up? Come on in.
- Hey. Uh, it's from the producers.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just go ahead and, uh, put that
on the counter there.
Look at all that kiwi on
a stick. You know I always say
you can never have
enough kiwi on a stick.
(chuckles) They, uh, wanted
to wish you a speedy recovery.
- Well, that's nice.
- I also have a hard copy
of the revised script pages.
Okay. Thank you.
Cool. Well, I will, uh...
I'll see you in a few days.
- Yep. See ya.
- All right.
(paper rustling)
♪
Hey, Peter, it's Kate Pearson.
Yeah, I'm excited
about the gig tomorrow, too.
Yeah. I-I just talked to Ms. Silver.
She said we could set up at 6:00.
Yeah.
Uh, and you're good for
rehearsal tonight? Okay.
Thanks.
I'm just gonna comb you out
a little bit before I wash it.
Don't worry. I won't pull
too hard. I promise.
How long have you had these patches?
You know, my sister
Renee gets them, too.
These areas where the hair doesn't grow.
What she has is called alopecia.
- Have you ever heard of that before?
- No.
It's not that uncommon in black hair.
Some people are just born with it.
It's not their fault.
Oh.
I didn't know that.
Is it always like this?
You know, it's okay to talk about it.
It's just the two of us here.
It gets worse when
there's a lot going on.
What do you mean?
Like...
Like, when bad stuff happens.
When Mom gets in trouble.
Or... when I have to move houses.
That makes sense.
Stress can make it flare up.
My mom has really pretty hair.
(clears throat)
You know what?
Over the years, I've gotten really good
at braiding my sister's hair
in a way that covers up her patches.
After I wash you out,
I think I can do the
same thing with yours.
Does that sound okay?
JANET: Oh, I remember this trip.
Your father took the twins
and Randall out on the lake.
- Remember?
- No, Mom.
It's not "the twins and Randall."
It's "the kids." Or even just
Kevin, Kate and Randall. Okay?
- Are you okay, honey?
- Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just tired.
It's not just tonight.
I mean, since I've been here,
you haven't seemed like yourself.
Is everything all right
with you and Jack?
Yeah. Never better, actually.
Then what's going on?
You don't call home much anymore,
you stopped coming to see
us for the holidays.
- (sighs)
- You don't seem very happy.
(chuckles): I am happy.
- We're all very happy.
- Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm your mother,
I'm allowed to worry.
Who would've thought that
Randall would be the one
to get into private school.
I'm sorry.
What... what does that mean?
What? Nothing.
Okay.
(sighs): All right. You
want to talk about this?
Um...
Do you want to know why
we don't come home
for the holidays anymore?
It's because of you.
You constantly criticize my family.
I am not a good enough cook.
I don't clean well enough.
Uh, Jack doesn't provide.
You're gonna most certainly
give Kate a complex about food.
And Kevin is gonna think that his only
value in life comes from how he looks.
And all of that is fine.
All of that I can sort of
explain away to the kids, but...
(sighs)
But Randall...
tries so hard to get you to like him.
And, honestly,
I've always wondered if the reason
that you never bonded with him
was because he was adopted.
But you've made it alarmingly clear
that it's because he's black.
That is an appalling thing
for you to say.
You know, just 'cause
he's black doesn't mean
that he likes basketball.
He likes football,
like the rest of us, okay?
And you got to stop constantly
separating him from Kevin and Kate.
They're all my kids, okay?
I'm sorry, I call them "the twins."
That's what they are.
And Dora, our maid Dora,
she wasn't just a child
that you had to train
how to speak, she wasn't.
She was a 50-year-old woman
who had four kids of her own.
I can't talk to you when
you're being hysterical.
And St. Mary's, right?
We went to St. Mary's my whole
life, and then suddenly at 16,
we switched churches because
we got a pastor from Ghana.
Oh, for God's sakes,
I couldn't understand
the man's accent, Rebecca.
When the snow is gone,
I want you gone, too.
'Cause I will not expose Randall
to any more of this crap.
What are you talking about?
You're racist, Mom.
You're a racist.
Sweetheart.
(sighs) Sweetheart, I thought
that you were upstairs.
I got my first chicken pock.
Okay. All right.
Um... (sniffles)
Uh, let's take you back upstairs
and I'll put some
calamine lotion on, okay?
TOBY: Hey, babe have you seen my...
Holy hell of a hot fiancée.
Wow. That looks great.
I told you the dress would fit. Hmm?
Yeah, you did.
Hey. You set a goal
and you made a goal,
so now is the part
where you get excited.
What's going on with you?
Nothing. Can you just unzip me?
I have to meet my pianist for rehearsal.
Yeah.
How can Grandma be racist?
She never says anything mean
to me about being black.
Yeah, that's-that's not always
how racism works, kiddo.
REBECCA: Yeah. Do you remember
how we were talking about
what Martin Luther King Day means?
Someone shot him because he wanted
to get black people equal rights.
- Did Grandma shoot him?!
- No, no, no, no, no. Grandma... mm.
Look, you know how sometimes
Mom gets really mad at me
and she says some things
that... aren't really nice
but she makes it sound nice?
Like, "Jack, I love when you leave
your muddy boots in the
middle of the living room."
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So racism can sometimes be like that.
You know, people don't
actually say bad things
to people that are different than them.
- What they say sounds fine...
- REBECCA: Mm.
But there's this mean
undertone to it, you know?
I think I'm gonna go to bed now.
(sighs)
I mean, I said alopecia, and it was like
no one had ever talked
to her about it before.
I honestly don't know what
I would've done in that moment.
They come to me for the boo-boo kiss,
but they go to you for the
Band-Aid and the boo-boo song.
I don't know anyone else
who has a three-verse song
about how antibiotic ointment
can help them heal faster.
♪ And prevent an infection disaster. ♪
That's the...
They need the both of us.
We make a good team.
Nope. We were right the first time.
(knock on door)
Dang, girl.
You look really cool.
Alicia Keys cool.
She's old.
(laughs)
Look, I... I just wanted to apologize
for the way I acted
at the bowling alley.
I'm ashamed that I made a scene.
I shouldn't have let
things get so heated.
Definitely not Alicia Keys cool.
Still no love? All right.
Anyway, um, I just wanted to say that...
I've had two nervous
breakdowns in my life.
One right before Tess was born,
and one just earlier this year.
And they happen when
I let myself get stressed out,
and it just builds up
inside, and then...
(imitates explosion)
But, uh, one of the things that helps me
when I'm feeling stressed,
though, is running.
I run, like, every day.
Just helps me clear my mind.
So...
if you ever feel like you want to,
I would love to go running with you.
She told you what I said?
Oh.
- Hey, Kev, do you...
- (Kevin sighs)
Dude, come on.
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean,
what am I doing?
I'm getting better.
- No pain, no gain, right?
- No.
Actually, no pain, full recovery.
Take your hand off that.
No, no, no. Dude, come on. (chuckles)
I hereby release you
from all of your nursing duties.
Okay? You can go back to your room
and binge-watch
The Handmaid's Tale
- or whatever it was you were doing.
- Handmaid's Tale?
- What? Okay. Here.
- (sighs)
Come on, don't do that. Don't do that.
You know what,
I might not be your nurse,
but I am your future brother-in-law,
and I'm not gonna let you
screw up your knee
for the rest of your life.
Well, that's really sweet
of you. I appreciate it.
But I'm not gonna let this stupid knee
screw up the rest of my life. Not again.
Again? What-what?
Kev?
Hey. Hey, just...
- (sighs)
- Would you just slow down?
What's going on?
Toby, I was three years old
when I threw my first football.
I made the varsity team
when I was a sophomore.
I wasn't good at football, Toby.
I was great.
My dad used to come to the games.
He started taping them for a reel.
Colleges were coming.
They were scouting me.
I-I had this whole future
planned, you know. I...
- And then the knee goes, and then bam,
- (snaps)
just like that, it's over in one second.
Gone.
(exhales)
Wow.
I mean, I knew you played
high school football, but...
Geez.
So, what do you do, you know?
I started acting, right?
At first, I started doing it
to, uh, sort of pass the time
rather than just sit there
and feel sorry for myself.
But then, after a while,
I-I started to...
I started to get the same thrill from it
that I did from football.
And here we are, man.
It's 20 years later.
Right? I've been working my ass off,
and I am finally on the brink
of something special
and real and fulfilling,
and I will be damned
if I let this stupid knee
destroy another one of my dreams.
And that is why you have
to let it heal fully, all right?
The... It's not that big a deal.
The production said they would shift
- the schedule around for you.
- They did shift the schedule.
All right, apparently
they can, they can shoot
part of the Normandy scene
without me... and Ron,
Ron doesn't think it's a big deal
if the other guy says,
"I got you, Jimmy."
Well, it's a big deal to me.
And I-I appreciate all of your effort,
all of your concern,
but I'm not blowing this one.
Okay, man? I'm not blowing it this time.
I'm gonna do whatever it takes.
- Hey.
- Hi, Dad.
When did you all get here?
REBECCA: Kevin crawled in around 3:00,
and the others came not that long after.
- Oh.
- But you...
you've been passed out
with a fever for hours.
I was getting worried about you.
How are you feeling?
Do you think you could
itch my whole body?
'Cause I don't know
that I have the strength.
- I told you chicken pox is the worst.
- Oh, yeah.
Sure is, kiddo.
Hey, babe, could you get me the Tylenol?
I-I think I left it in the kitchen.
(sniffs)
Hmm. The kitchen, huh?
That's downstairs.
Uh, I have been avoiding
going downstairs
because my mother is down there.
- Oh, babe.
- But you are my husband,
and I love you, and you're sick,
so I will risk going downstairs
and interacting with her.
- Thank you, babe.
- All right, guys.
I'm gonna go downstairs.
Uh, who wants something?
This is your one and only shot.
Hot cocoa.
Cap'n Crunch.
My Game Boy and some Cheetos.
Wait, hold on a second.
Has everyone been avoiding
going downstairs?
- Okay. I got this, Bec.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Lie down. I'm already going down.
- Jack, you're sick.
- No.
We will not be held prisoner
in our own home.
I'm gonna get your mother out of here.
("Madman Across the Water"
by Elton John playing)
♪ I can see ♪
♪ Very well ♪
♪ There's a boat on the reef
with a broken back ♪
♪ And I can see it very well ♪
(Kevin grunts)
There you go.
♪ There's a joke ♪
♪ And I know it very well ♪
(exhales)
♪ It's one of those
that I told you long ago... ♪
JACK (over TV): All right, Kevin!
Yeah, he's the real deal!
He's going all the way, baby!
- (cheering)
- MAN: Oh!
- Good job, Kevin!
- MAN: Yeah!
I want you to know
my boy's the total package!
My son is-is tough!
My son is tough as hell.
Go, Kevin! Go, go, go!
My boy's unstoppable! Yes! Yes!
Did you see that?!
The kid just ran the ball
88 freaking yards
for a touchdown! Touchdown!
Yes!
♪ Get a load of him ♪
♪ He's so insane ♪
♪ You better get your coat, dear ♪
♪ It looks like rain ♪
♪ We'll come again
next Thursday afternoon ♪
♪ The in-laws hope
they'll see you very soon ♪
♪ But is it in your conscience ♪
♪ That you're after ♪
♪ Another glimpse of the madman ♪
♪ Across the water. ♪
- Brian.
- Kevin. Kevin.
Wow. You look amazing.
- You look amazing. All right.
- (laughs)
It's good to be back.
I told you I wouldn't
slow this puppy down.
You're absolutely a man of your
word, Kevin. Thanks so much.
- I will see you in there, all right?
- Totally. Really appreciate it.
Jack just finished digging out your car.
So...
I...
You know, I didn't sleep
at all last night.
I was truly haunted
by what you said to me.
You have to understand,
I grew up in a very different time.
- In my day, people didn't...
- Mom, I... Stop.
(sighs)
It's not because he's black.
Or I don't know if it's adoption
or it-it's just all of it.
It just all feels really
foreign to me, I guess.
But I swear, Rebecca, I swear I try.
You shouldn't have to try.
(sighs) I know.
But I do.
REBECCA: Hey, sweetheart.
Grandma wanted to say good-bye to you.
It's nice to see you again, Randall.
Okay.
Wow.
This looks impressive.
I finally got it to work this morning
when I switched this little marble
for the heavier Super Ball.
It's Newton's second law.
You're a special young man, aren't you?
Took you long enough.
♪
(sniffles)
And me and Queen Latifah
were looking everywhere for the puppies,
but I woke up before we found them.
RANDALL: Oh, that's too bad.
I have to commend
your commitment to your health.
I can tell how seriously
you're taking all this.
Thank you.
Oh, um...
I bought the vitamins
that you recommended.
Are these the right ones?
You know, it's just because...
(sighs) my age and my weight,
I want to follow the instructions.
You're doing everything you can
right now to stay healthy.
Thanks.
So, is it still there?
It's still there.
Your poppy seed is now
the size of a lentil.
Congratulations.
You're officially six weeks along.
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*