Hey!
Hello? Hello?
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, finally, I get the remote.
Hmm. Hmm?
Homer, are you ever planning on
putting this stuff together?
Sure, right after I watch this DVD.
Just what are you watching
that's so important?
Outstanding College Mascot Fights?
S.E.C. edition.
The top-heavy mascots always lose.
Unless they're fighting
something with no arms.
See? The Stanford Tree
is no match for the Tulane Green Wave.
There's people inside.
Marge, do you see?
Maggie!
That's it, mister.
You're putting everything
together today.
Marjorie,
isn't it a little sexist
to expect me to do all the carpentry?
Or you can take Bart to the
mall to get fitted for...
Sorry,
the drill is too loud!
I can't hear the options!
"Vous avez 'termine'"?
"Du ar klar"?
"Du bist fertig"?
"You are 'fini-shed'"?
Oh, I am finished!
Whoo-hoo!
D'oh!
I'm trapped.
Here, boy. Come here.
Who's a good Allen wrench?
You's a good Allen wrench.
Come here.
Come on.
Huh? That isn't the same
Allen wrench I swallowed.
Hey, Barney, how's it going?
Fine. How are you?
I need help. Can you come right over?
Homer, you should use
the Choremonkey app.
People do all your chores,
so you're free to follow your dreams.
My dream right now is
beer and toilet paper.
Mr. Gumble, because I'm a decent person,
this is the last beer
I'm going to bring you.
I'll just use Uburp.
Stop eating me, I'm not dead yet!
Choremonkey to the rescue.
Oh!
Oh, thank you.
I think this is the beginning
of an unhealthy dependence.
Aw.
♪ I'm a fool
to do my dirty work ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I can hire all these nerdy jerks ♪
♪ For free ♪
♪ I ain't gonna do my dirty work ♪
♪ No more ♪
♪ Gonna leave my socks and dirty shirt ♪
♪ On the floor. ♪
Homie,
I don't like that the house
is full of strangers all the time.
And I... wait, wait, why are
you taking out your phone?
No. Don't you Choremonkey me!
Sweetie, you know I'm
no good at arguments,
so I brought in a professional.
Hello, ma'am, my name's Blake,
and I'm a retired FBI
hostage negotiator.
I wouldn't say this is
a hostage situation.
Mm, no one said it was, ma'am.
I'm just here to listen.
So that was step one: listening.
Next, empathy.
I'm standing right here, you know.
Mm, it must be frustrating
for you to hear me talk
like you're invisible.
It is. It is.
Step Three: I build a rapport.
You know, I love the color
scheme in your home.
I feel like you're saying that
just to build a rapport with me.
Wow, that's very observant.
Very wise.
Oh, well, thank you.
Nice.
This ain't my first rodeo.
Marge, right now
I bet you wish you were just back home
in your kitchen.
I am back home in my kitchen!
Then life is good.
Am I right?
Mm-hmm. You are.
While I'm here, could I
also fix your icemaker?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Blake, I adore you.
Shh. It's over now.
Go get some rest.
Hmm.
Homer, can we throw the ball around?
Oh, um...
By "we," I mean me and
your chore monkey.
Oh, of course! Sure, buddy.
For you I'll get one
without a criminal record.
Which means I'll have to
use Choremonkey Gold.
Good one, Bart.
Wait, are you Heisman
Trophy-winner Matt Leinart?
Yep, I am.
And you need this job?
Yeah, I haven't really
been smart with my money
after football.
But what about your broadcasting work?
Uh, sunk it all into my
Thai-Irish fusion restaurant,
Shamrock Spice.
On the plus side, he taught me
how to throw a perfect spiral.
Yes!
Frozen rope, kiddo!
Aw, love you, man.
Ah, I love you.
Maybe I should play a little
catch with my son now.
Whatever, Hoss, let's see what you got.
My zinnias!
Annuals.
Wait, please, just let me try again.
Dad, you're embarrassing me
in front of Matt Leinart.
- But...
- Wow.
You made that for me?
No, it used to be O.J.'s.
Yeah, Little Juice.
Oh, stupid Choremonkey.
Another thing I overdo
bites me in the butt.
Uh-oh.
You're late.
There's no specified time, sir.
And you did receive progress alerts.
Whatever, fine.
Just throw the damn ball.
- So, how was your day?
- Pretty good.
I've thrown various balls with
six different middle-aged men.
All right, stop talking,
you're ruining it.
Nice pass, sir.
For someone your age.
Ju... This isn't fun at all.
- I'm done.
- Fine.
You know the monkeys
also rate the customers.
Now everyone will know
what kind of man you are.
Good-bye, Tyler.
Jerk.
"Jerk." Bart used to call me that.
Be careful, Dad.
Being careful is not going to get us
on America's Funniest Home Videos.
Now, when I nod, you pull
the bottom brick out
and the wall falls on me.
Then call Vin Di Bona Productions,
then an ambulance.
Wait. Won't they know
this video is fake?
Why would I be filming
you making a wall?
Why didn't you bring these things up
at the production meeting?
Well, it's too late now!
Oh, great!
Dad, can I get you one
of my children's Xanax?
What I need is that $10,000 prize.
Not $5,000. I already
spent that on bricks.
Now pull that rope.
If I pull the rope and it kills you,
I'll need a lot of therapy.
I'm not gonna die, son.
Uh, but if I do, can you
play "Nobody Does It Better"
at my funeral on the recorder?
I can't be a part of this.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Luann, help!
I'm in a hurry.
Well, at least I got it on video.
Delete.
Ah, come on.
Haw-haw!
Dad, it's me.
What are you doing here?
It's not pudding day.
My son doesn't
want to be with me anymore.
So you realize that's how you've
treated me all these years
and you've come to apologize.
Look, Dad, I would visit more
if I hadn't put you in
such a depressing place.
Whatever.
I've got a real problem here.
I'm gonna be a father again!
My girlfriend's pregnant.
That's insane!
I leave you alone for six months
and this is what happens?
How did you even meet her?
Oh, this home just got the Internet
and everyone's using
senior dating sites.
Gray Date,
Friends with Social Security Benefits.
Everyone's making whoopee
and hanky-panky.
A few are even having sex.
You can't leave me.
We started a puzzle together.
My heart's bleeding.
Seriously.
Please call 911.
Abraham Simpson.
Are you skipping town on me?
No, no. I like you.
It's the baby I'm skipping town on.
You don't want our baby?
Before you judge me,
look where my DNA leads.
I'm fine.
Hmm.
I think he's sweet.
Would he like to play with my keys?
I am a normal person, and yes.
All right, I'll man up.
But remember, men of my generation
don't change a diaper, attend a birth,
or talk to the child
before he's drafted.
I couldn't ask for more.
I thought you just rolled.
Those were my knees.
Rent six dollars?!
You can't even buy a
Monopoly set for that.
Great commentary, Bart.
Love you, man.
I love you.
Hi, I'm Matt.
Milhouse.
I'm Bart's best friend.
Aw, sounds like someone
wants an autograph.
I do.
Who are you?
I misspelled my name.
But that makes it worth more.
Come on, Leinart, get
your head in the game.
Bart, I got a straight up swap.
How 'bout I give you
Boardwalk and Park Place,
and you give me Ventnor?
That's crazy talk.
Oh, yeah?
What "History of Board
Games" class did you take
when you were in college?
My friend, you have a deal.
You got Chance.
"Take a walk on the Boardwalk,"
which I now own, and you're bankrupt
and I win.
Wow, you beat me at every game,
even Heisman Trophy Trivial Pursuit.
Oh! Can I play Bart next?
I carry my own little top hat with me.
Oh.
Is this guy bothering you, Bart?
I'll make sure he finds the door.
Could you throw me out
in a perfect spiral?
I can walk you out in a straight line.
Wow! No one's gonna
believe that at school.
Huh?
"Always let him win"?
"Don't let him see this sheet"?
He called me the greatest
receiver he'd ever thrown to.
Was that a lie, too?
Get out there.
Hey, Mr. Simpson.
Hey, Milk Dud.
Uh, listen, I got to go
change the oil in my car.
Don't you want to get a Choremonkey?
They cut me off.
I never dreamed when I gave
'em my credit card number
that they would charge me.
You could help me out if you want.
I have an old shirt you could wear.
An old shirt! Wow!
My dad doesn't have any of those.
Wow.
Anyone ever tell you that
you're excellent at gluing?
Um, no.
And your rubber cement boogers
were very convincing.
Look, I know you're doing
this because you have to.
How would you like it if the other team
had just let you win all the time?
That would have been really great.
Listen, I have another Choremonkey job.
I'll see you around.
Huh? Huh. Hmm.
Wait, I don't think a bouncer
throws people into a bar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You
just bounce, all right?
I'll tell you which way.
Get in there.
Ralph.
Yay! I'm a touchdown.
Boop!
Look who's a greasy guy!
Now you're greasy, too!
Look at you.
Bloop, bloop.
Well, hello, Tony Stark.
We've never had fun like
that in my whole life.
Oh, look! The engine block
pizza is almost done.
Engine block pizza?
Car food is our thing.
Careful you don't burn your mouth.
Oh. He never warns me.
Vijay Singh
has chosen a seven iron
for his approach here
at the fifth on St Andrews.
My zombies have got you now.
Mm.
What's the matter? Aren't
you into the game?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Good luck with that zombie Bing Crosby!
B-B-Brains.
Eh, I won. Whoo-hoo.
Huh? Didn't seem like
you were too excited
when you sliced me in half.
It's just hard when you think
you're gonna be slicing
the same boy in half all your life.
Uh-huh...
Well, I guess I'd better get to work.
On a Friday?
Why are you wearing a fishing hat?
Are you going
fishing without me?
What is happening with us?
If you've got something
to say, just say it.
Unless it's boring.
Is there someone else?
Oh! Spare me your melodramata!
Marge, I can't have a baby.
Coordinating our sleep
schedules will be a nightmare.
Plus, the only good relationship
I ever had was with my hat.
Then the wind blew it away.
You didn't have a good
relationship with your father?
Hmm.
Come here, sweet pea, give me a burp.
Youse can do it.
Aah! Youse got milk on me!
I'll murdalize ya!
Oh... that was before
throwin' your baby into the sun
was considered child abuse.
So you see, Simpson men just don't...
Wait a minute!
Now yank the hook out and throw
him back because we're humane.
I've never seen Homer and Bart so close.
Maybe I can finally be a good dad!
That's not Bart.
Don't ruin my epiphany!
Hey, Mr. Van Houten.
- Oh, hey, Bart. Milhouse isn't here.
- I know.
And I don't care.
Are you making envelope soup?
Envelope soup?
That'd be silly.
No, I'm stamp mining.
You steam off the stamp,
color in the postmark,
and you just made half a dollar. Almost.
Want to try?
Careful! That's a forever stamp!
Could be worth a fortune some day.
Well done.
And look at me.
I'm hangin' out with Bart Simpson.
That's so cool.
I can't wait till Wendell
sees us hangin' out.
Oh, hey.
Oh, I built it up too much.
♪ What do you do with a drunken Homer? ♪
♪ Make him watch
"Hunt for Red October" ♪
♪ Let him drive in a lunar rover ♪
♪ Tickle his nose with a... ♪
Oh, hi, Marge.
Homer, why were you
fishing with Milhouse?
Because for once, I'm with
a kid who respects me.
One who doesn't call me "Homer."
I didn't know that bothered you.
It does. A lot.
Oh, Homer.
Feels good when you say it.
Homer.
Ah...
Honey, maybe you should talk to Bart.
He's just behind that wall.
Yeah, Homer!
Get your fat ass over here!
You see? You see?!
It's not bad enough he calls me "Homer."
He calls my buttocks "ass."
Hmm. He probably learned that at school.
You bet your ass he did.
Maybe you and Lisa can talk to him.
Lisa and I aren't speaking right now.
I can't believe you threw
away my Utne Readers!
Oh, is that how
you pronounce it? Aah!
For most of my child's
life, I'll be gone.
When you're cremated, you feel it!
Warn everyone!
Aah.
Oh, Abe, hi.
I-I was about to call you.
I had an ultrasound today. But...
Does this mean...?
Yup, I'm the father.
And I thought she was just
using me for a beard.
I'm so sorry, Abe.
Well, I just want to say...
Yes! I can't raise my left arm,
much less a child!
Yippee! Not having kids keeps you young!
Oh, I knew you'd come back!
- Kirk.
- Homer.
- Dad.
- Fat Ass.
That is not my name!
Mm, mm, mm!
Let's roll.
Can't let 'em catch us.
I can't take the pressure!
Son, I'm so sorry!
I'm getting rid of this stupid stop sign
before it hurts somebody else!
I'm sorry, too, Dad.
You called me Dad!
There's a first time for everything.
Also, a last.
Milhouse, I'd be lying if I
said riding in a go-cart
with Bart Simpson wasn't
the highlight of my life,
but you're my son and I love you.
I love you, too, Dad.
You're my favorite guy
that Mom's brought home.
Aw...
Last one home is a rotten father!
Those aren't yours to keep!
They take them out of our pay!
We'll bring them back
when we get tired of them!
Oh, that never happens.
But, Chief, I... I don't
think those vehicles
are certified for highway use.
Yeah, well, I don't
think you're certified
to understand the relationship
between a father and son, Lou.
Yeah, well, I have a son...
He lives in Baltimore.
What do you want, a parade, Lou?
Listen, Maggie... Can
I call you Maggie?...
Is there a way I can get you
to put that pacifier down?
Oh, don't worry.
I'll be here as long as it takes.
You know, if you cooperate,
I can talk to your mother
about a reduced time out.
Look, you wanted a helicopter,
I got you a helicopter.
Okay, I've got your nose, and if
you want to see your nose again,
you'll give me that pacifier!
Swing and a miss! Strike two.
Sanchez batting .269.
Fun fact: His father was one
of those soccer players
who ate his teammate
after a plane crashed
in the Andes.
Look at him bite at the high fastball.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com