(Lisa grumbles)
(exclaiming)
- (school bell ringing)
- _
(Barney belches)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
No! Not there!
Anywhere but there!
- Oh, a museum?
- _
(Marge grunts)
♪ ♪
(plays discordant notes)
(gasps)
(moans)
(groans)
(belches)
Hmm.
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show! ♪
(crows cawing)
(dramatic music playing)
Ooh! I'd like a slice.
(both laughing)
Hey, hey! What time is it, kids?
KIDS: Product tie-in time!
That's right!
I'm introducing a new line
of candy so delicious
that the Krusty Corporation
board of directors
will stop threatening to oust me.
(drum roll)
Presenting Krustaceans!
They look like shrimp,
they taste like candy,
and they're organic!
Uh... "Clown eats snack"?
Uh-oh, this could get ugly.
What do you know. They're actually good!
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
Hey, hey, kids, Krusty won't
be needing the spit bucket!
(laughs)
Mmm! They are good.
How did you get them so fast?
I'm a Krusty Prime member.
$75 a month, but it's worth it.
What? Tibor's getting a corner office?
Oh, yeah, yeah, Tibor got
promoted to senior VP.
(groans)
CARL: Cooling tower views,
two chairs for two visitors.
LENNY: A picture of a
nondescript lighthouse.
CARL: Oh, my God, what is he
getting out of that mini fridge?
It's filled with mini-colas!
LENNY: Wow, he looks like a
giant drinking that thing.
I was in line for that job,
and I lost it to someone
who barely speaks English.
It's humidifying.
HOMER'S VOICE: Well, then why the
hell don't you do something about it?
Huh? Who said that?!
Me! (grunts)
Who are you?
I'm your ambition.
How come I never met you before?
I've been locked up for 30 years
by Apathy and Alcoholism!
(both groaning)
Now, Homer, Tibor is no better than you.
He just dresses nicer.
I guess I could dress a little better.
Probably.
That's the most ambitious
thing you've ever said.
Guys, is there something
wrong with the way I dress?
No. If you're a typewriter
salesman in 1953.
Also, for a guy, you show
way too much cleavage.
Hey, these two have gotten me
out of so many traffic tickets.
Look, man, if people think
your clothes are outdated,
they'll think you're outdated.
Lenny wears suspenders.
Correction: I rock suspenders.
Ah, Tibor.
There's my go-getter.
Thank you, Witch of the Mountains.
(band plays upbeat
music, audience cheers)
Tonight we have with us
a distinguished senior journalist
for another installment of our
pointless Internet sensation:
Talking Heads Sing Talking Heads.
Kent Brockman, everybody!
(Talking Heads music playing)
And you may ask yourself...
How do I work this?
Where is that large automobile?
And you may tell yourself...
Okay, that's it.
(band plays upbeat
music, audience cheers)
Speaking of once-in-a-lifetime
experiences, Kent,
I understand you have
a fascinating story
about your time in Basra.
Well, Jimmy, I was embedded
with the 98th Airborne.
My lullaby was the thwap-thwap-thwap
of the blades of a Chinook.
I was in the 98th Airborne.
I don't remember him.
I don't even remember what I said
at the start of this sentence!
Out there, everyone was equal.
I was "Brock," the pilot was "Bama."
Was he from Alabama?
He was from America, Jimmy.
To me, it was just another
day at the office.
Only this day, the office was
a burning piece of metal
where an RPG just took out the pilot.
So I grabbed the joystick and
guided that wounded bird
down onto a container ship...
which was sinking.
I bailed it with my helmet
and guided her home.
(audience cheering)
That didn't happen, man!
Oh, you Iraq War vets
are always complaining.
(mocking): "That didn't happen."
"The temperature was 125."
"The U.S.O. show was Rob Schneider."
"American objectives have been,
and remain, incomprehensible."
Wah-wah-wah.
MARGE: Dinnertime!
(humming)
No junk food!
We're at the dinner tables.
KENT BROCKMAN: This is
Kent Brockman with a...
humble apology.
(dramatic kettle drum plays)
You know, we in the news business
like to report the story; we
don't like to be the story.
That's what I said to Nelson
Mandela atop the Berlin Wall,
but... No, I didn't. That's the problem!
Now you're not eating.
I can't eat when I'm
watching the spectacle
of an imploding celebrity.
We have lip-quiver, people.
I'm sorry to report to
you that over the years,
every interesting thing I've done is,
in fact, a complete lie.
I did not land a Chinook helicopter.
I did not see bin Laden die, or
even see the movie about it.
Now that I've apologized,
my station has assured me
that it has full confidence...
These were the last words of
disgraced anchor Kent Brockman
before he was escorted out by security
and replaced by me, Arnie Pye.
This reporter promises
to restore our news
department's credibility.
In our top story, corporate
taxes are too high.
Geez, I'm really gonna
miss Anderson Cooper.
That wasn't Anderson Cooper.
Oh, thank God.
I'm not licked yet...
not as long as I've got
a cell phone and a place to sit.
Company car.
(tires screech)
Marge, I think I may
have to get new clothes.
(whispers): At last!
It's time for me to project the image
of a powerful, self-reliant man.
Will you take me shopping after school?
Sure. And after that, maybe you could...
oh, I don't know, lose a little weight?
Marge, no, don't get
greedy, don't get greedy.
Sweetheart, I'm always happy
to temporarily lose weight.
Oh...
So, this app is called Smothr.
Lets my mom keep a
healthy eye on me 24/7.
Milhouse, you're overexcited.
You're going to get a bloody nose.
I will not!
See?
Hmm. I call these num-nums
because they make my fingers numb.
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
Why are the only ingredients here
"water, fun and hydrogenated chuckles"?
Hey, Krusty makes quality products.
Incoming!
Mm, let me try one of those candies.
I shared a meal with Lisa.
It's halfway to a kiss.
Now I kissed Lisa.
No one kissed Lisa!
- Hmm?
Hmm, I don't think candy
should give me a tingling
in my left arm.
I'm gonna prove to you that Krusty
is a good clown with nonlethal candy.
Hey, Otto-man, can you take us
to the food processing district?
No way, Bartman.
Hey, Otto, I just remembered,
we have a field trip to the
food processing district.
Oh, man, we're late!
(tires screech)
FRANK SINATRA: ♪ This town ♪
♪ Is a lonely town ♪
♪ Not the only town... ♪
You're a very lucky lady.
(laughs)
(humming)
Hmm? (groans)
Hmm.
(grunting)
Really? You're thwarted by a shirt?
Never!
This is so exciting...
with my Homie in a haberdashers.
My husband needs a complete makeover.
Well, thank you, lady
with the beehive hair.
Ooh, intimate but heterosexual.
CLERK: Here you are, pal.
(moaning): Oh! Oh!
Homie?
Oh, baby, you had the same idea I did.
Mmm!
This wasn't my idea, but... (gasps)
Oh...
(chuckles) They all think
they're the first ones.
Wow. Ready for the corner office.
I feel like Mrs. Mad Men.
Now let's get you rung up, lard-ass.
- What did you call me?
- Uh, Lord S.
Oh.
Well, we've got a nice-
looking couple here.
Walk away, Marge, just walk away.
I'm holding my sharpest key.
Wait, Homie. It's Kent Brockman.
The man who betrayed our trust.
I'm producing my own news content now.
Could you spare a few sound bites
(chuckles): for this rudderless anchor?
Forget it. We only like
newspeople we can trust.
So no newspeople!
Oh, well, I have bigger problems.
Can't afford toothpaste, so
tonight my teeth will have...
film at 11:00.
OTTO: Adios!
Don't worry, Krusty's favorite number
is how many jokes he's written.
♪ ♪
Wow! Hydroponic gardening.
Organic fertilizer.
Maybe I was wrong about Krusty.
(groans) This candy is
reeking with chemicals!
Just once I'd like to be wrong.
Well, from what I read in your
diary, you're rarely right.
(groans)
We've got to get these samples analyzed.
Bart, do you think we'll
get out of here safely?
I think the guard's no problem.
(snores)
(robotic voice): Z, Z, Z-Z-Z.
Z, Z, Z-Z-Z.
(snores) Z, Z, Z-Z-Z.
Here comes our ride.
(bicycle bell dings)
I called UberKid.
(Eastern European
accent): Please get in.
You want bottled water? Mints? Take.
Your accent is so interesting.
Where are you from?
Uh, small town in Latvia.
You don't know it.
Well, I'd like to hear.
Why do you have to make
friends with everyone?
(sighs) So much great work for naught.
Kent, as your agent, I promise
we will find you something,
or so help me, we will drop you.
That's a promise.
Well, could you, uh, get me on Fox News?
Would you be willing to
call yourself a liberal
and lose every discussion?
Every single one?
Okay, you've already asked
too many questions.
The offer's dead.
(sighs)
♪ Empower your horse ♪
♪ Right through the sun ♪
♪ Blast a rainbow light from
your empowerment gun. ♪
So, you're gonna get this to Katy Perry?
I never said that.
Hey, guys. Notice anything different?
Whoa, whoa, impressive!
Italian?
Oh-ho. Better.
Connecticut! (chuckles)
Yeah, I think I'm gonna go
into old man Burns and say,
"Here is a leader of men... and women."
'Cause that's what you have to say now.
High five, man!
Why do we call it "high five"
when we only have four fingers?
You know, I've always wondered that.
FRINK: Oh, what have we here?
Uh, Lisa, these vials
are filled with formaldehyde.
Formaldehyde! Do you understand?
Do not imbibe!
Check. No imbibing.
Bart! Imbibing is eating,
and formaldehyde is poison.
Oh, you take all the fun
out of eating poison.
You're just an apologist for Krusty.
I am not a paid apologist for Krusty!
I didn't say "paid."
Got to go. I'll see you in the future.
(mechanical humming)
Uh, that's just my bathing suit dryer.
I, uh... yes.
(groaning)
Sorry, kid, not
interested in your story.
Krusty's our biggest star,
and formaldehyde's our biggest sponsor.
I'm gonna have to go off the grid.
All right, Kent Brockman.
Welcome to BizzFad.
We are so crunched.
(chuckles): Well, the
crunching is mutual.
"The crunching is mutual"?
What the hell does that mean?
Well, I know that the media has changed,
but this old newshound can
still find his way home.
Okay...
I thought I might do a piece on
all the crazy ice cream flavors
they have these days.
Bacon? Really?
(chuckles)
Kent, I like it. I do.
But we just went bankrupt.
Uh, people, people, you're all fired.
But, seriously, it's
been a great four days.
Thank you.
Uh, gentlemen, I suggest
we ramp up production.
I have a few suggestions
right here in my pocket.
Do it, Homer! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
(gasps) Are you Lust?
No. Lupus.
(shrieks)
Huh? Huh? Huh?
(chuckles) Hey, fatso,
I'd close that tent flap
before the mosquitoes get in.
(chuckles)
What the...?
I thought you would like it.
Actually, I think you
should take this tarp
back to the baseball
stadium you got it from.
In case there's a rain delay.
(chuckles) I did not
see that coming, sir.
Off you go, Simpson.
Never seek to better yourself again.
I'm just going to shove my foot
on your back for emphasis.
Yes, sir. I understand.
But could you try not to
get my new jacket dirty?
Sorry, but no.
Well done, sir.
Now your turn, Smithers.
I never thought you'd ask.
So, why do you want to give
the story to Brockman?
Because the best thing you
can do is offer a lifeline
to a person with no hope.
Here I am!
Sorry, not you.
Thank God!
Well, how do you know
where Brockman will be?
To find a fallen man,
you must visit the scene
of his highest peak.
When he reported on the flood of '09.
My career and these flood waters
crested at the same time.
This is Kent Brockman blowing a sad song
on his beer bottle.
(playing sad tune)
Mr. Brockman, we've
uncovered a huge story!
And we need a real newsman
to break it wide open.
(sighs)
A real newsman, eh?
Then you've come to the wrong corner.
What do you mean?
Oh, I'm through.
Now, please, let me just go out
with my remaining dignity intact.
This is Kent Brockman thinking
dark and suicidal thoughts.
It's quiet here in the gutter.
Very quiet.
Well, it was.
_
Okay, who would like to start today?
Anyone? Anyone?
Oh, come on.
In three, two...
I'm here live at the support group...
Our top feeling today...
This just in: I'm sad.
(slurring): You know,
I'll be tooling around,
and I'll just constantly lapse
into my elocution exercises.
"A Lockheed L-1011 landed safely
in Bogalusa, Louisiana, after an alert."
Oh, I've been there.
- Too true.
- Courage.
Kent, you're looking
unusually thoughtful
and silent for an anchor.
You know, I thought I'd come to terms
with life off the news
cycle, and then, bang,
I was offered a scoop on a platter.
(slurring): Well, did
you leap on that lead
like a lion on a lemur?
I passed! As in, "I
am a thing of the..."
Dan Rather, do you have
something to contribute
besides this delicious
homemade Bundt cake?
Mmm.
Kent, why are you doing this?
Why did you get into this business?
Money, women, free coffee. The usual.
Sir, if you please, these days,
a bona fide uncorrupted story
is rarer than a snake with sneakers.
It's harder to find than a
yellow-fronted bowerbird.
Jump on it, hoss,
and ride till Gramma
churns the buttermilk.
That's when the barn dance starts.
What is that feeling?
Is it integrity?
♪ ♪
Good to see ya, buddy. I'm in!
Anybody got eyeliner and pancake makeup?
Take mine, brother.
Works great on Mediterranean skin.
It's from my personal
line, Rather Handsome.
Well, Marge, I was humiliated by Mr.
Burns, it's true.
But, to me, this is nothing
more than a temporary setback.
Good for you, Homie. I'm proud of you.
Hey, Homer Simpson is not deterred
by a footprint on his suit.
It'll come out, right?
- I don't know.
- (shrieks)
Homer, I have a 12-step
plan for your success.
Step number one: get in a 12-step plan.
(grunts) This is an opportunity!
(screams)
I think I'm going to Moe's.
(tires screech)
Krusty, we have evidence
that your product
is laced with toxic additives.
Yeah. So why you bothering me?
LISA: Because your tasty
little treat did this.
(whirring)
I made the doctor cry.
They told me the paralysis
would be temporary!
Five years, tops.
Seriously, come on,
that kid wasn't going anywhere anyway.
It looks like this clown could
not formalde-hide the truth.
(chuckles) This is Kent
Brockman, saying...
No! I'm gonna sing Beatles songs
so you can't afford to show this video!
- A-one, two, three, four!
- Too late!
Well, you're back on top, Kent.
And now for a once monthly feature we do
called Serious Question.
(horn honks)
Tell us, how did you get this story?
Well, it's funny, actually.
I was trapped in a burning building...
(gasps) Is he really gonna
take all the credit for this?
Don't ask me.
The last newsman I could trust
was that bigamist, Charles Kuralt.
It was a burning building
called my career.
Thank God I had help.
Lisa Simpson, you deserve to
be on this couch with me.
But because I don't lie anymore,
I have to say I didn't fight
too hard when they said no.
Hmm. Is that enough?
Are you kidding?
You got Hollywood's highest honor:
shared credit, no money.
I've been informed that
this is my last newscast
as anchor of the Channel 6 News.
Before I go, I'd like to get
a few things off my chest.
I've made out with Kent's daughter.
The grown-up one!
Are you almost through?
In a hurry to fail again, Kent?!
No, it's just I've been off
the air for six weeks,
and it was torture.
Sometimes I'd watch Bill O'Reilly
and pretend it was an older,
stupider version of me.
Go ahead. Take your chair.
Do what you do best.
Tonight's lotto numbers: six, 17, 42,
45 and 83!
I'm back!
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -