Pack up your stuff. Starting tomorrow,
you're gonna go to East Dillon High.
- Kind of looking for a place.
- I do have this trailer.
I'm gonna give my daughter a call.
Don't you scare her!
I'm your new intern.
I've got a bunch of crap in here,
I need you to start moving it.
Why did you forfeit the game?
You just quit on us?
I've got shame
and I apologize to you.
Who wants to finish this fight?
Let's finish it!
Hey, listen!
Ten of you are gonna push the car.
Once we get out there,
the rest of you hold the helmets
and collect the money.
Be careful, don't get
your feet run over.
- Any questions?
- Matter of fact, I do.
- What is it, Tinker?
- Why are we pushing this damn car?
One, watch your language.
Two, next time, I want whatever that
is on your upper lip shaved off.
And I'll tell you
why we're pushing the car,
because
it's a fun football fundraiser.
And we're gonna have fun, so we're gonna
put smiles on our faces right about now.
Team comes out, town comes out,
money gets exchanged.
It's a good thing. Understood?
Got it, Coach!
Let's be kind
and courteous out there.
Hello, neighborhood!
We're the Lions!
Let's hear it, guys!
Even at church, everyone is
really not being nice to me
about this whole
Luke Cafferty thing.
That's our congregation.
All sweet and holy
inside the church,
then as soon as
they get out the door,
- bitchy and judgmental.
- Well, welcome to the world, honey.
It's not gonna be my world.
What isn't?
Going to church
with a bunch of hypocrites.
Hypocrites are everywhere.
It has nothing to do with church.
That's no way to think about it.
There's always gonna be some bad apples,
but church is about you and God...
So if it's just about me and God,
why can't I just worship at home?
I mean, I think that church
is also about community
and family and you know,
there's just a lot to it.
We need your quarters,
your dollar bills,
your good wishes
in monetary fashion!
Let's hear it, boys!
Not feeling love out there.
You feeling love?
Tink, shut up,
stop sweating on me
and push this piece of junk, okay?
We got forty bucks, people!
Thank you, good people of the street!
Good to see ya!
Thank you very much!
We are the East Dillon Lions!
Feed us! Feed us!
- I'm out.
- What do you mean?
- I'm out of money.
- Listen to me.
It's all I got left.
That's about a 100 bucks.
Don't give it all to one person.
Spread it out.
- I'm trying, some are taking it.
- Give it to people who don't take it.
Look at these boys
pushing this car for ten miles!
There's your tricycle.
- What?
- The tricycle!
That's great.
I need you to drive me to Clearwater
on Tuesday. I need to pick up some metal
so I can finish this piece of crap.
Why do you call
everything you work on crap?
Because it is all crap.
I call the Mona Lisa crap.
In fact, the Mona Lisa is crap.
There are better things I call crap.
Clearwater is 200 miles away.
- Just about.
- Right.
And I got a shift I gotta do so...
I mean, I can't take the whole day
and chauffeur you up there.
You're here to learn about art
from an artist!
You can't take a day off because
you got a shift to deliver pizza?!
We already have uniforms.
Why do we need new ones?
- Because I burned the uniforms.
- Taylor...
I burned them. That's what you do.
They were damn 30 years old.
This is not like I just burned them
for no reason.
You end the old cycle,
you start the new, Levi.
You know, you get rid of the past.
Fact of the matter is
the team and I we went out
and we made up a good amount
of money, it's just that...
Now we're just a little shy
of what we need
and all I'm asking is you
and the school is, you know...
if you'd help us with the downpayment.
We can pay for the rest.
I don't think you understand
the financial situation here.
We ain't close to talking about
more money for football.
Levi, it's expensive starting up
a new football program...
Starting up a new football program
is a little premature.
Let's see if we can finish up some games
before we start writing checks.
What is that supposed to mean?
If you can't finish games,
I can't keep this program going.
Students are getting hurt.
I don't want no jokes down
at the school board meetings. I'm tired.
Either you turn it around
or we're gonna shut it down.
What do you mean?
You're gonna shut down the program?
You weren't even supposed
to take this job!
Or to be here.
So you're the only
that didn't get the joke.
Friday Night Lights 4x03
- In The Skin Of A Lion -
Subtitles: Team Lions
With the participation of:
Benj!, Collioure, DarKsh,
GillesSilb, Jenn, Ju, Nam, Tactactac
Morning! I made you toast.
Are you serious?
It's worth it, eat it.
What time is it?
Morning. And since you're up, anyways,
can you give me a ride to school?
Come on. Put some pants on.
Watch your head. Watch your head!
Hurry up!
I'll be waiting in the truck.
Here you go, sweetheart.
There.
Here's your sippy.
- Hey, Honey.
- Good Morney, Grace.
You know, yesterday in church,
all that stuff you were saying...
Do you feel like
we're making you go to church or...
It's not like you're making me
go to church, it's just...
You know, something
that we all do as a family.
It's like a tradition, but...
If you stop going, then I don't think
I'd probably keep going.
Coach Taylor at half-time,
"We"re done!"
"We're beat up,
we can play anymore."
I can't believe it.
Hey, guys.
You're waiting on me.
You're backing up. Let's go.
We missed you
at the game Friday night, Buddy.
Yeah,
I had to listen to it on the radio.
I was really sick, it was terrible.
Anything you feel like
sharing with us, Buddy?
Anything about a certain mailbox
or an old friend of yours
named Eric Taylor?
I don't think so.
I don't know what you're implying.
I think this Luke deal has made
everybody go a little crazy.
You know, Joe,
I was a Panther
before everybody here.
So,
I'll pretend you didn't say that.
Go ahead with the agenda.
Alright then.
Gentlemen,
there is a 13-year old quarterback
in a Pop Warner League
down in Little Tree
that needs a closer look at.
Who's gonna go down there?
Lions in the house.
Let me hear you say, "Oh yeah!"
- What is that dude so happy about?
- I don't know what he is happy about.
I guess he thinks he gonna come out here
and kick our asses.
- Something, man.
- He's all, I'm a Panther.
Let's go!
Execute!
You're a long way from home, boy.
I guess so.
Come on, get after him.
Pick him up.
Come on, Vince.
What are you doing?
You're dancing out here. Dancing.
Don't start my day off like this.
Why is it I'm always talking to you?
I spend half my day and my practice,
out here, talking to you.
Get in the front. Do it again.
Get in the front.
Let me see it.
Luke, come here.
- I want you at the defensive backs.
- I don't play D, coach.
If I tell you to get down
to the defensive backs, you do.
Get on the defensive backs.
Tim, you wanna take him down?
If you'd like to hurry that up,
that'd be just fine.
It's a pleasure, man.
Do it again. Let me see it again.
Get after him!
Move him! Come on,
let me see some of the speed!
How you doing?
I mean, I'm alright,
that's just I don't play DB.
It's alright.
What are you doing here?
Coaching now?
- I'm helping out when I can.
- Nice.
I saw you win State.
There you go.
DB it up.
"His last installment
at the Austin Museum of Modern Art
"is nothing short of mind bending.
"A violent fusion of metal and artistry
that invokes somehow
"both anger and beauty through a complex
interplay of architecture and light.
"Brilliant, visceral,
and ultimately, ethereal,
"this work is not to be missed."
- You got the right Richard Sherman?
- Yep, it's him.
"Brilliant and ethereal"?
- It's what it says.
- The dude is an angry, abusive idiot.
I don't understand
how he can get described as ethereal.
I don't know.
Maybe it's his evil twin.
Yeah, maybe.
Clearwater and back.
This is going to be 400 miles
of hell.
Hey, coach.
Hey, Doug, how you doing?
I'm good.
Nicely done.
- How is everything?
- Good, good.
The uniforms look great,
they're coming along, look beautiful.
You're gonna be real happy.
Look, I know... I know I'm late
on payment and all this but...
I know things are
rough here right now.
It's just
if we're gonna deliver on Friday...
Well, I understand. We've had a few
little hiccups with our fundraising.
- Sure.
- And...
Look, Coach, you've been a friend
of Under Armor for a long while and...
that's why we're doing this at our cost
and I'm gonna throw in some...
hats and polos for your staff,
'cause you helped me out
when I was starting off.
So I won't forget that.
I appreciate that,
I appreciate the...
But I'm gonna need
a little something
- to take back to Baltimore.
- Sure, I understand.
How much?
How much is it that you need today?
Five.
Five thousand?
Alright...
You give me
three now and two more on delivery
and we'll let it go with that.
Alright. That's good, thank you.
Listen, I appreciate that very much.
I appreciate your understanding.
- Is this a personal check, Coach?
- Yes, it is.
This gonna be okay with you?
If it's okay with you,
it is with me.
- Alright. I'll get it going.
- Thank you very much.
Alrighty.
Julie the other day
was talking about
how she doesn't want to go
to church anymore.
Like she's questioning her faith
or something.
You know what?
She's a teenager.
You give her a week
and she'll turn around.
Be a hundred and eighty degrees.
But who knows
where she'll go from there.
I don't think she's going to hell
anytime soon so don't worry about it.
I gotta go meet with Buddy.
I'm gonna try to figure out
how in the hell
you're supposed to...
- beg money from the Boosters.
- I hate that.
Alright. Hey, listen.
Did you write a check...
and not put it in the book?
Because there's a check missing.
Yeah, it's for Reds.
It's for the Dry Cleaners.
It's for $45.
- Sorry.
- You've got to put that in the book.
I can't keep track.
- I'm here.
- Come on, let's go.
- We got 200 miles to cover.
- We're taking my car?
- I hope you're paying for gas.
- I'm teaching you the meaning of life
- and I'm supposed to cover for gas too?
- Meaning of life...
Maybe I should get you a lunch
and how about a damn souvenir?
I'm just saying
this is a non-paying internship, okay?
- Smells like old pizza in here, man.
- Well, that's how I pay for gas.
I'm glad you're masking it
with cigarette smoke.
- That's cool.
- Let's roll.
- Yes, sir?
- Come here.
Yeah, coach?
I want you on special teams today
working on punting.
- Yeah. I'd love to catch some punts.
- Good.
I don't want you catching.
I want you to work on the punting.
You want me, like, kicking the ball?
I don't know if I've ever...
That's what you do
when you punt the ball.
- I understand. I know what it is.
- Special teams punting.
- Can you do that for me?
- Yes. I'm only considering myself...
a hands man.
I need a punter.
So if you would consider
hang times and couffin corners,
I'd appreciate that.
- Thank you very much.
- I'll go start practicing right now.
Thank you, coach.
- Coach, can I have a word please?
- Sure. Come on in.
I think we got off on the wrong foot
and I wanted to clear everything out.
I just wanna say...
I don't hold anything against you
for the thing between me and your wife.
And...
I'm not here to give you a hard time
but to play football.
Good, I'm glad.
'Coz I don't think you should be.
As far as my wife's concerned, she was
not the one who caused these problems.
You caused these problems
for yourself, isn't it?
You were doing something knowingly wrong
and you got caught, yeah?
That lands yourself responsible
so take that responsibility.
As far as the rest, we'll see
what you got when you're out there.
Thanks, coach.
You see stuff like this, okay?
Get that, too.
All right.
When you're looking at all this rusty,
metal stuff, it's all dirty...
do you see something in it?
Do I see something in it?
I mean, like something,
for your art.
I see the face of God.
- Right.
- I don't know, man! I don't know.
You ask too many damn questions.
Questions.
- It was one question.
- Gonna take a little break.
Not you, but...
let's get the rest in there.
Yeah.
I had to borrow your bathroom,
'coz mine's not working.
I talked to your mom about it.
She said it's cool, so...
Okay, I don't care.
Hey, which one do you like better?
The red one?
Or the pink one?
- For what?
- I have a pageant coming up
and these are kinda old
but I don't think they're too short.
What do you think?
I don't think I'm qualified. I think
it's best to ask your mom for this.
She's not here, and it's just a dress.
Which one do you prefer?
- Where's your mom?
- She's working.
Every night?
She can't help out with this ever?
Yeah. It's not a big deal.
- I can try it on if that's easier?
- What?
- I can try them on for you.
- I don't know.
- I don't think I...
- Wait, which one?
You're good. Pink for sure!
Get the pink.
You'll win with that.
Good luck.
Alright, so how about I just throw
my last two pucks and we take off?
Why?
I got stuff to do.
I got people to take care of.
We're doing anything here.
- We're just playing shuffleboard.
- Alright, let's talk then.
- You want to talk now?
- I can talk.
I'm not a dick all the time.
- So talk. Talk.
- Okay.
Fine.
What would you say is the most
important tool
for an artist to have?
- What's with you and these questions?
- You just told me to talk.
I meant, you know,
talk about yourself while
I'm secretly mocking you in my head.
You know what? How about I settle up
our tab and then we'll take off.
Watch out.
The most important tool
an artist can have
is selfishness.
- Selfishness?
- Yeah.
It means
you're gonna spend your life
trying to express some quiet
dark corner, deep, deep inside you.
You will put aside love,
God,
life...
in order to follow this craving.
So my advice to you is
to just screw everybody else
and maybe you got a chance.
I wrote a personal check.
I've got to get that money together
and quick.
I don't know how to talk to boosters.
You do.
I don't know how to ask for money.
You're great at asking for money.
All I'm doing is asking your help.
I know and I'd like to Eric
but I got Joe McCoy and thoses guys
breathing down my neck.
They think I'm the one
who told you about the mailbox.
- You are the one who told me.
- I know,
but I've got to unknow that
right now.
They may be having me followed.
They probably got my phone tapped
or maybe bugged. You know the guys,
- they're crazy, man!
- A little crazy, but let me tell you.
Levi, now, Principal Burnwell
has informed me he's willing
to shut down the football at the school,
if need be.
That's what I'm up against.
I'm asking you for your help.
That's terrible.
And I'm sorry to say this
but I cannot help you right now.
I just can't.
- You know what?
- What?
You need to polish that ring of yours.
It's looking a bit tarnished.
An earthquake in West Texas?
Yeah.
They have 'em. Odessa?
Odessa's on the permian basin
and that's a fault line, honey.
They have 'em.
What would you do? Would you pray?
I'd probably check on you
and Gracie and Dad
and then I'd stand under a doorway.
Alright, I hear you. That's great.
It's all good but would you pray?
How about...
next time...
there's an earthquake in West Texas
I'll let you know?
Come on, now!
Way to bring the wood, Cafferty!
Bring that wood!
All right!
Come on!
Hey, Vince, what are you doing, man?
You've got to make that play.
You've gotta catch that ball.
How can you miss that?
You're not gonna make that play today,
how are you gonna make it Friday?
Look at me.
You can't make that play,
what are you out here for?
Hey guys, let's bring it in!
Good job.
What am I, the Invisible Man out here?
Did you see that?
It's like he's not even seeing me
work my butt off out there.
- What do you mean?
- Coach didn't even look at me.
He's got a lot on his plate, that's why.
Keep doing what you're doing though.
Thank you for noticing.
I'll see ya later.
Who's that?
I'm renting a room from her mom,
that's it.
- You're what?
- I'm renting a room from her mom.
Wish I was renting a room
from her mom.
Just joking.
Look man. You make sure he know
the difference between coach and dad.
He's always yelling at me, you know,
on the field. Telling me what to do.
Pushing me. Grabbing my jersey.
He embarrass me in front of everyone.
That's not how I get down, dude.
That white boy sucks.
Why's he all up in my face?
Coming up where I hang out,
at my house, talking to my moms.
And you already know my mom's situation.
You know how I feel about that.
It's alright though, it's cool
'coz he's bringing that white boy Luke.
He think he gonna take over.
He's supposed to be
a Panther's star.
That's my spot. That's my team.
I'm the Running Back.
Look man! At the end of the day,
white man gonna stick with the white.
They're gonna look out for each other.
That's what we gotta do.
We gotta look out for us, alright?
25 more.
Hey, Riggins, why don't you wear
your Panthers state ring?
I don't know. That's a good question.
I guess I don't like rings.
What was it like, going to State
and winning that ring?
It's pretty good, man.
You gotta give this team a chance.
Dude, be serious.
This team is not the Dillon Panthers.
The Coach doesn't like me.
He's been pretty clear on the field.
In practice, sticking me on D,
no disrespect, that's not what I do.
He's mad about his wife
getting all backlash
for throwing me off the Panthers.
I want to play football, man.
I want a State ring.
Like I said,
give it a chance, trust the coach.
- What?
- How're you?
- Good, what's up?
- Where you going?
Drum up some business from local leaders
in the form of cash. What do you need?
As you know I've been working
with Luke, a lot. And he's good.
Damn good. And I think he's worth
getting a tougher look at.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- He thinks you hate him
is what I'm trying to say.
I don't have the time or resources
for sensitivity training.
He's got to get rid of the concept
that we're gonna kiss his ass 24/7
'coz he's gracing us with his presence.
Tell him to shut up and work him hard.
- I'll deal with the rest later. Thanks.
- Yes, sir.
Can we play?
I mean, I was supposed to be...
working on my punting
but if you all want to play afterwards
- or if you want to watch...
- Yeah! Let's do it!
You suck!
That's nice.
- I'm sorry.
- The ball's supposed to go straight.
See that was actually all planned...
Want some pointers?
Do you know a lot about punting?
Yeah, actually I do.
Here look, you wanna...
Okay, I can show you 3 steps, alright?
You wanna make sure
that you keep that lean forward position
so keep your head down.
Make sure
that you hit the middle of the ball
with this part of your foot, okay?
So point your toes, okay?
And make sure you follow through
all the way with your leg.
But don't be stiff.
Like, loosen up, okay?
- But don't think!
- Okay.
- Well, that was better.
- That was good.
I'm good, right?
Yeah, I'm good.
I don't think
that's ever gonna happen again.
Yeah, it will...
Especially not whenever all the
thousands of screaming fans are around.
- What fans?
- I mean, one away game or something...
- Can you all go get the balls?
- Let's go!
My little men...
You just gotta keep doing it, okay?
Over and over.
Do it thousands of times
'coz you'll get that muscle memory.
Just forget about the...
you know, the guys,
the big guys charging at you,
the fans, the chaos...
Just like zone in,
zone in inside yourself
and forget it all.
Let all chaos just go...
Just let it go...
Let it go, you know?
Where'd you learn so much
about football?
My... my father.
He used to play football,
he was a quarterback.
He almost went pro, too,
but now he can't stand it.
Thinks it's a big waste of time.
Where'd you learn so much
about the...
Did you study Buddhism?
No, no, no, I just...
It's my life,
you know?
How'd it go trying to get the Boosters
together and all that what not?
I went to about
twelve of the local businesses
and found out
that they either don't know
there's a football team,
or they could give a damn less.
Sorry about that.
Yeah...
And I stopped over at the bar
and I had a drink and I left the car
over there and Alan gave me a ride home.
So if you could take me
to get it, I'd appreciate it.
Okay.
You know yesterday, you asked me
about the check for the Dry Cleaners?
It wasn't for the Dry Cleaners.
It wasn't for $45 dollars.
It was for Under Armor.
It was for gear for the team
and it was for $3,000.
You wrote a check for $3,000?
- We don't have $3,000 in our account!
- I know that.
But when I wrote the check...
It's not gonna be run through right away
so you don't have to worry about it.
I would have appreciated
if you had talked to me.
I didn't have time to.
- You didn't have time to talk about it?
- No, I didn't.
I'm telling you about it now.
Listen, I know you're having
a hard time, but come on now.
Why would you not
talk to me about that?
They said if I don't write the check,
I don't have uniforms.
Without team, I don't make money anyway,
so what the hell does it matter?
If I can get the money from Burnwell
who I've been talking to,
which I think I can do,
everything will be fine.
It's just a matter of doing it.
I just need time.
- I'm just telling you for the sake...
- Don't raise your voice.
I'm not raising my voice.
Why don't you just stay calm
and stop getting all riled up?
You'll get your damn uniforms, but in
the meantime, what about our accounts?
You write yourself
a check for $3,000
without talking to me about it, you lie
to me about it, we don't have that money
and then you come in here
and yell at me?
I don't think so.
Hey, Luke!
Your football coach is here.
He's got work to do before school.
- I won't take much time at all.
- I appreciate it.
Morning, Coach.
- I'm alright. And you?
- Good.
- Why are you here?
- I understand
you're not happy at practice.
Wanna talk?
No disrespect, Coach,
I just feel like I'm not being used.
You're not giving me
a chance out there.
What do you want from me?
First of all, I haven't gotten a chance
to play offense, which is what I do.
You'll get your chance.
You'll get it when I give it to you.
I'm trying to put a team together.
I got 18 other players
I'm trying to pay attention to.
I can't put you up on a pedestal
and pay all the attention to you.
I want to get out of here, alright?
That's why I'm playing football.
I mean, this is it for me.
This is all I care about.
All I ever cared about. My parents don't
help me out with this, they don't care.
I was on my fast track, got to Dillon
Panthers and I'm not there anymore.
But here I am, willing to kill myself
'coz I want to get out of here.
I just want a chance to play ball.
I want a chance to get noticed.
I understand...
that you're helluva player. You can run
circles around all the people out there.
I understand everything
you've been through.
I understand what it's like
to wanna be a Panther.
Believe me, that's not lost on me.
Anything else that you need?
What I need? I need a scholarship to
a good school so I can get out of here.
Listen, I'll tell you what.
I will do everything in my power
to get you just that,
if you do one thing for me.
What?
I need you to lead.
Alright.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
- Yeah.
- Lead...
Alright, thank you.
- Want a slap on the back? You earn it.
- Alright.
- See you out there this afternoon.
- Alright, see you out there.
Thanks for the ride.
Yeah. You got a boyfriend?
No, why?
That's the guy that should be doing
all this, giving you rides everywhere.
Since you're already doing it,
you'd be more efficient if you were.
I'm just kidding.
Have you ever run
into that new Cafferty kid?
- Luke?
- Yeah, Luke.
He likes you.
I've been working with him
on the field and everything and...
he doesn't stop
talking about you, so...
And?
I'm just giving you a heads up,
just in case you want a boyfriend.
He's a pretty good guy.
I'll talk to him.
Good.
I just thought I'd swing by
on my way home from work.
I'm sorry.
I appreciate that.
Doug called from Under Armor.
He said he's willing to wait
for the school to pay for the 2,000
and the other 3,000,
he's gonna take it easy on me.
And I will get it paid.
OK.
Honey, don't ever do that again.
I won't.
And I'm sorry
you're having such a hard time.
Sounds like Coach is gonna be
moving up Sobel
- to take Luke's spot, tonight.
- Yeah, meanwhile, Luke Cafferty
is on his way of being massacred
in his first Lions game.
What a waste.
One good thing is gonna
come out of this, tough.
McCoy is gunning
for Principal Taylor.
What are you talking about, Lester?
McCoy'll figure a way
to get that bitch out of there.
- There you go.
- I can't even believe you, Moore.
I got something to say to everybody.
I hate to...
spoil the party, but...
This is to everybody.
You know what?
I'm not a Panther anymore.
You used to be my friends,
I don't know who you are.
I don't know what you believe in,
but it's not the Panthers.
It's not the Panthers I believed in,
it's not the Panthers we grew up with.
I'll tell you that right now,
you wanna know another thing?
I'm the one who told Eric
about the mailbox.
I can't live with myself anymore,
I put that mailbox in, 12 years ago.
In the middle of the night,
I dug that hole and put it in.
It's my mailbox, I can do
whatever I want to with it.
And Joe...
I tried,
but ever since you got here,
you've been a cancer to me,
you've been a cancer to my friends
and you've been a cancer to this team.
And just one more thing I wanna say.
It's clear eyes,
full hearts,
can't lose.
- I just gotta drop this off real quick.
- Yeah, no problem, take your time.
Who the hell are you, little girl?
Hi, I'm Julie.
Matt's girlfriend.
He went inside
to drop off that tool
you asked him to pick up.
So you're the ball and chain
that keep dragging him down.
I think I married you
about 20 years ago, babe.
Thought we'll get new uniforms. What are
we doing, playing in our practice stuff?
Tinker, why don't you do less talking
and more thinking about the game, son?
Let's go.
Let's go, gentlemen.
Let's go!
Look at this!
Alright!
Oh, these are official right here.
Hey, listen up!
Listen up, gentlemen.
Listen up!
They may be new...
but they're still work clothes.
Let's go to work!
All of a sudden,
he was talking to me.
That's the first time
I have a real conversation with him.
He's actually a really smart guy.
He had real interesting things to say,
it was crazy.
Do you think I'm holding you back?
No.
Why?
I was outside waiting for you...
and Richard Sherman came out
and started talking to me.
About what?
He said I was the ball and chain
holding you back.
That's stupid.
You're the most
important thing in my life.
What if that's the point?
No, that's not the point.
The point is that he's stupid,
that he was drunk.
He don't know about us.
Eat your bean curd.
- Alright.
Lions down, 27-0 late in the fourth.
They are definitely
gonna finish this one, folks.
Cafferty on the Bronco blitz.
He hits him in the backfield!
Luke Cafferty has been
bringing it all night!
Nice hit, Luke!
If the Lions could just
get on the board, tonight,
it'd make a whole heck of a lot
of difference to this football team.
- That's it!
- It drops back in the pocket.
And Howard gets burned
on the wheel route.
He's got a man open.
He's got the outside!
Luke Cafferty makes
another touchdown saving hit.
Vince Howard has just gotten smoked
all night long.
A real disappointment
after such a promising start.
Stay in it!
Huddle up, defense.
Huddle up, defense!
Vince, don't jump on the front,
it's 3 & 10.
Who made you coach?
That's what I thought.
4-3-code 2.
- 4-3-code 2. Ready?
- Break.
Never say die, never quit.
30 seconds left in the game.
Let's see if Cafferty and Howard
can put some pressure
on this Rattler offense
and make something happen.
And back to pass.
Looking to cross the middle.
Fires!
Luke Cafferty! Interception!
He's bringing it the other way!
- There you go!
- Here we go!
He's got a line up the sideline,
look at it go!
Man, is this kid fast!
One man to beat,
he's got a blocker on front!
He could go!
- Stop him, Vince!
- Oh, mercy!
What was that?
Luke Cafferty is up
and I'll tell you what,
he's not happy about it,
Vince Howard is getting an earful.
- You are your own problem, Vince!
- Too fast, man. You're too fast.
Vince, what was that?
- What was that?
- I didn't have an angle!
What do you mean, didn't have an angle?
You could've run circles around him!
- Don't waste no energy, Coach!
- Let me tell you something!
You know why I always pick on you?
'Coz you're good, that's why.
You know why you have a problem?
'Coz you're your own worst damn enemy!
- Fine! Get out of my face!
- No! You get out of my face
and let me tell you something:
put that damn helmet right now.
Don't you dare talk to me like that.
You change it right now.
Or you will be out of this game
so damn fast you will never...
- Yes, sir!
- Understood?
- Landry!
- Yes, Coach.
- Get out there. Get us a field goal.
- Field goal! Here we go! Here we go!
You're on the field goal team!
Get in there, then!
Don't you ever take that helmet off
in front of me. Do you understand me?
Taylor lining up for the field goal.
Trying to get on the board.
Clock is ticking, folks.
Snap the ball!
- Snap the ball!
- There's the snap. It's over his head.
Bouncing around the carpet.
That was not pretty.
Clark picks it up.
I don't know what he's going to do.
Oh, he shovels it forward.
Vince Howard on the outside.
Oh, what a move!
Just on the edge!
Howard could go.
This could be it folks!
Oh my, touchdown!
Touchdown, East Dillon!
Vince Howard has scored.
Coach Taylor and the East Dillon Lions
are on the board.
Touchdown, hallelujah!
Alright, Lions!
How was your date?
- It was good.
- It was?
It was good.
I've been thinking.
I think I want you to come
to church with me,
'cause it makes me feel like family.
And I like having you sit next to me,
at least for a little bit longer.
And I think it's good
that you're questioning your faith.
I just want you to have faith
in something.
Something that can hold you...
when I'm not going to be able
to hold you anymore.
I'll be there Sunday.
I'm sorry, but you're always
going to be my little girl.
Richard!
- Get up!
- Ah, screw you.
Alright, screw you, too.
What are you doing?
I'm just looking at this thing.
That's a piece of crap.
That's a beautiful piece of crap.
Thank you.
I'll get the money together somehow.
- I know you will.
- I love you.
I love you, too.
And you know what?
Now that you've gotten
all the way through the game,
you gotta feel
pretty good about that.
Bet you'll sleep better tonight.