Son, you all right? -
- Oh, god! Contraction!
- You're seven months pregnant.
You're not contracting.
Please go to the hospital.
You're going to need to go on bed rest
Until the baby's full-term.
I don't exactly have insurance right now.
I'll figure out something.
I got a business opportunity
That really could make you a rich man.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
I thought he was the one.
I know, sweetie.
I'm sorry, babe. - Do your thg, skeeter.
That's pretty great.
Texas forever.
I think either one of
them would be nice, hon.
This one still has a tag on it.
Might as well wear that one.
It's brand-new.
Honey, you know you've got
to put your toiletries
Into the plastic travel bag. These are ugly.
I'm not bringing those. - Don't take those.
Have you seen my bright blue shirt?
Gracie doesn't have any pants.
It's in with the dry cleaning.
Let me get it.
But now get that stuff together.
We've got to go.
Do you know where gracie's pants are?
We've got less than a half an hour.
Do you know where fracie's pants are?
Hi, sweet angel.
They're in the bottom drawer.
You're gonna help your
daddy find your pants.
The bottom drawer, sweetie.
You realize none of my
outfits are gonna work
Unless I have that shirt.
I'm getting it right now.
They're not in the bottom drawer.
Well, if not, then check in the dryer.
Come on. Bring your spaceman.
I know. We got to get your pants on.
Mom, every outfit you packed
I look like a realtor in.
All right now. Hey, y'all need to pack up...
Honey, you're gonna look
amazing and beautiful
For your interviews. - And let's get going.
You give 'em hell up there,
You understand me? - See.
You found the pants.
That's great. - All right?
All right, time to go.
You were five minutes late
Five minutes ago. - Bye, dad.
- Good
-bye.
You're gonna be great for your daddy.
Oh, shoot, I got to grab my briefcase.
Andnot that anybody cares we have
The league's two last-place teams facing off
This Friday-- the east dillon lions
Versus the campo park timberwolves.
Folks, I don't mean to be crude,
But I understand that this game
Has unofficially been called
The toilet bowl.
If you're coach taylor,
You got to see this game
As a singular opportunity
To get a "w" on the books this season.
Hey, ma, do I have a follo
w-up with the doctor?
He said he didn't need to see you again
Unless it's still hurting
in a couple of weeks.
It's doing good, right?
I mean, you've been going
to practice and everything.
Yeah. No, I'm good.
I've been driving by this property and...
yeah.
Wow.
It doesn't have a price on there,
And I was just... - Yeah. A steal.
$85,000.
$75,000 if you could pay half
the purchasing price up front.
Might that be an option?
Um...
Hey, yeah, I know that we
hang out all the time--
Exactly. So why we got to call it a date?
Because there's a very distinct difference
In just hanging out and an actual date.
I would be wearing a nice button-up shirt.
And you would probably be wearing,
like, a nice skirt
Or something like that. - Yeah.
And it would be nighttime.
When you say a nice shirt, though,
You don't mean the one
with the periodic table.
I have other really nice shirts.
I have a bunch of really nice shirts.
Yeah, um, I have Wednesday night off.
- Perfect.
- So Wednesday night?
Wednes--I love wednesdays.
Yeah. - Okay.
- Great.
- All right.
- Good night.
- Cool.
Okay.
Full-pad Monday. Everyone ought to be happy.
You know what, it doesn't matter
Whether you win or lose,
It's how you plaz the gam
e- who's heard that before?
Well, that doesn't apply
to this team anymore.
Listen to me.
Individually, we ought to be damn proud
Of where we come from
And where we are right now.
Collectively, I think we've got
A hell of a football team here.
But we're not scrappers anymore.
We're lions.
And this is our time.
This is your time.
We got a week for this game coming up.
I want you to know I'm proud
To take the field with you.
Let's practice.
Let's go!
What's going on?
* *
So we have a fabulous contradiction here.
Chaucer is the founder
Of modern english poetry,
But he also uses words
Like "ass" and "fart."
So what does chaucer's very deliberate use
Of language tell us?
Anyone?
Someone. Come on, really.
Yes, ma'am?
Do you want to answer?
Oh, no, I'm just observing.
Oh, no, that's okay.
It seems you have a thought.
Please, share.
Oh, well, would it have
to do with the context?
You know, who's speaking?
Exactly.
- - context. Who's speaking.
Think about the knight's tale.
- Mm
-hmm.
A story of romantic love...
To the middle!
Whoo!
Let's see you throw it like that
Without tipping off the
safety with your shoulders.
All right, looking good.
Looking good!
Yeah!
- Let's blitz.
- Here we go.
Hit to hurt, gentlemen. Let's go.
Down the field. That's it, that's it.
Fours, come here.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right, let's go.
Grab the ball, luke. Here we go.
Whoo!
Look what the cat drug in.
Ain't got any need for a toilet, do you?
No, I don't.
I've never heard such malarkey
in my life. Hey, eric.
- Good to see you.
- You too.
joe, keep the elbow up.
Toilet bowl, god help us.
I just want to tell you that I...
I used to be something
For the dillon panthers.
And I want to be that way here.
I can help you.
I'm gonna do that.
I just want to let you know that.
All right.
keep your hands--
No, no, put it back.
darius!
darius! Caleb!
Let go!
What's up? Look, look, look, look.
We're gonna run a pos
t-route with the sunflower seeds.
Go, go, go. - Look at this.
Are you seriously teaching
them to throw food in a--
Oh, you can't teach that.
That was a great job.
What's wrong with you?
- That's talent.
- Hey.
Look at all you boys.
I haven't seen you in such a long time.
You've grown.
Darius, did anybody tell you you look
More and more like your daddy?
Yes, ma'am.
I bet they do.
You know, I tell you what,
I'm cooking dinner next week,
And I want you to be there.
- Me?
- Yup.
Oh, no, I wouldn't want
To impose on...
No, no, no, you're not imposing.
I'm gonna cook for us,
And I expect you to be there, okay?
Final answer.
Hey, you boys be good now.
Listen to what she tells you to do, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
I'll see you. Come on, baby. Come on.
Keep those.
Let 'em have the pancakes.
Can I get the pancakes, please?
- No, you can't.
- Let 'em.
Stop. You hush.
I mean, honestly, before you
were a guidance counselor,
I don't think  got any applications
From your district.
Well, you know, I think once y'all came down
To the fair, it just put
a face to the school
And let the kids realize
It's not so far away,
And it's a real opportunity for 'em.
Well, I'm just so glad you came up to b.C.
We are too.
Julie, how do you like it so far?
Um, it looks exactly like the brochure.
Beautiful.
Did you get a chance to
sit in on any classes?
Yeah, an english class.
Oh, great. How was it?
It was good.
It was great.
We had so much fun.
It was professor paulson's class.
Oh, vanessa.
Her class is like being at
some fabulous dinner party.
- It made me want to go
get the canterbury tales,
Just read it for fun all over again.
- Mm-hmm.
- Jules loves to read too,
Don't you, honey?
I think she got that from me.
This place is so gorgeous.
You have a big game coming up this weekend.
What do you have to say about it?
All right.
Yeah.
Some chick named mindy's
on the phone for you,
And she sounds really crazy,
So do you want me to just blow her off?
No.
Hey, skeeter.
Hi. - Mins.
Hey, tim, I can't get a hold of billy,
And the toilet's backed up,
And I need you to get over here.
Um, see, I've had a few too many,
So I can't drive.
Actually, this isn't about you
and your drinking problem.
It's about me and my baby,
And the toilet is toxic.
And I pee every five minutes.
And I don't know where your brother is,
And I really need you to be here.
So go in the bathtub.
I'm not gonna go in the bathtub!
I am on bed rest. Get your ass over here!
Can you drive stick?
Remember, the clutch is
your best friend, okay?
I'm not really sure what
you mean when you say that.
Just let--
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't have air bags, by the way.
Relax. Relax.
So why were you in a suit today?
Oh, that's a good question.
Some guys aren't meant to be in a suit,
And some guys are.
It's green.
The light's green. Here we go.
Wrench me.
- Ew.
- Where is billy anyways?
Doing some big job down at the rig.
This late?
You didn't know that?
Yeah, I knew that.
He's been working a lot of nights lately.
Yeah, well, it's getting busy, min,
Which is a good thing.
It's not a big deal, right?
What do you mean?
Like, if I call him,
And he's all distracted,
and he's tired all the time,
And if I walk into a room
and he's on the phone,
Then he hangs up really quickly?
Mins, what you're saying is not happening.
He is having an affair, isn't he?
No, he's not.
I don't even want to know.
That's the sad part.
How pathetic am I?
I don't even want to know
If my husband's cheating on me
Because I'm a total mess.
Yeah, I mean, this is an emerging team.
Equals emerging opportunity.
- Oh, no, no.
- He thinks you want free time.
I understand. I'm a businessman.
I understand that.
This is a new demographic for you--
Football.
- Football.
- American football, yeah.
- No, no, I understood that.
- Buddy.
American football.
And I understand you.
- Uno momento. Yeah, what?
You think this is really necessary?
If they want to talk trash about us,
the hell with them.
Let's just get out of here. I'm an investor.
They understand that.
This is a chance for us to have a voice.
We can stop all the trash talk
That's going on. This can make a difference.
Do you think we can do this
within another five minutes?
Yes.
Just...Keep going.
- Senor. - Yes.
Yes.
You say you want english
on a spanish station?
Just--just for the football games.
What the hell you doing?
Mornin'.
Yeah, morning.
You can be honest with me, man.
I'm just-- are you messing around on mindy?
No. No.
'cause I know you've been working late
And all that kind of stuff,
and I was over there,
And she's all worried and stressed out.
And maybe-- - I'm not cheating on mindy.
All right?
- What's all this late
-night stuff then?
Just doing a little afte
r-hours work, that's all.
- What kind of after
-hours work?
You know, it's the kind of after-hours work
That you can't really do in the daytime.
You get it? - No, billy, I don't get it.
That's why I'm asking. What do you mean?
After-hours-- - okay.
A couple guys came to me a couple weeks ago,
And they gave me a little proposition, and--
What kind of proposition?
Once or twice a week,
they come by with a car,
And I break it down to its component parts.
They need it turned around in a quick time,
And they pay really well... - Chop shop.
That's the stupidest...
Yeah, well, it's a plan, tim.
You got a better plan?
Yeah, billy.
We had a plan.
I mean, we just had a party here
And raised buckets of money.
Buckets of money?
Where's all that money then, billy?
Buckets of money. You want to know
Where that money is, tim? - Yeah, I do.
One meeting with a specialist.
That money's gone.
You got any other plans, tell me about 'em.
Yeah, billy.
This.
This was our plan, billy.
Riggins' rigs.
Tim, it's a temporary thing.
- Temporary thing
--you have no idea what you're risking.
Look, nobody's getting hurt here, man.
You keep reminding me,
Like, every week that you have a family,
And this mechanic shop
is some dream of yours.
Tim, that's the whole
reason I'm doing this, okay?
The whole reason I'm doing
this is for my family.
This is gonna prevent
me from going bankrupt.
It's gonna make sure
That mindy's gonna be okay and
that my baby's gonna be okay.
All right?
And once it's over with,
Everything will go back to normal.
I can't...
oh, I love this school.
I know. It's your favorite.
Did I ever tell you this
was my first-choice school?
Only, like, a million times.
But no pressure or anything, right?
What do you mean? Of course, no pressure.
You'd have disowned me if I
didn't apply to this college.
What are you talking about?
You've just been staring over my shoulder,
Looking at every syllable that
I've put into every application
Since I started the college process.
Wait a minute. You decided
where you wanted to apply.
I have been trying to help you
In that process.
But, honey, it's up to you
what school you go to.
It's not up to me.
All I'm trying to do
Is--is support you as
you're making that decision,
That's all.
You get me?
Yeah.
You sure about that?
- * shoobie
-doo-wah *
* shoobie-doo-wah *
* *
* oh *
* strange *-- hold on.
* oh * - * feel strange *
I can't hit that note.
I'm sorry.
Is something the matter today, landry?
No, I just couldn't hit that note,
And I got frustrated. - He got stood up.
I did not get stood up, jimmy.
Actually, the date was rescheduled
Because of conflicts.
And that might be a good thing
Because Thursday is more of,
like, a sexual night anyways.
So we're just gonna go
Through the whole psychoanalytic breakdown?
No, I'm saying, by 7:00 p.M.
On Thursday, your brain
has basically clicked in
That it's pretty much the weekend,
But Wednesday's closer to Monday.
And no one's getting busy on Monday, but...
Get busy?
Every now and then, people want to get busy.
Ms. Howard, can I help you out in there?
Oh, no, no, no, you stay put.
I know you've been working hard.
- You need help with that?
- Oh, no, baby, I got it.
mm. Wow.
So, jess, I must say bless your heart
For joining us
'cause I ain't never seen this boy
Wear anything but a t-shirt.
How you been?
Oh, well, you know, I can't complain.
Well, you know, I lost
my job down at the hotel,
But that was because it was closing
And whatnot, but, you know,
I'm keeping myself really busy,
So, um, I did some part-time work
For this cleaning company,
And, you know, that just
really didn't pan out.
I think it was just because of doing
The night school thing down at tech.
You know, things start changing--
Mama, these mashed potatoes are delicious.
- Yeah, I know, baby.
- It's good.
- So I'm planning, and...
- That's good.
Yeah. My aunt said to tell you hello.
- Oh.
- She's working down at this--
For this new company-
you know what, honey?
Do you know how amazing you are?
I mean, do you know how amazing you are?
'cause, when you were a little girl,
I mean, this light would
just shine through you.
And--and now look at you.
You've become a beautiful young woman.
- Thank you.
- Vincent, isn't she beautiful?
- - I mean, look at her.
Isn't she beautiful?
- Oh, stop it.
- She's gorgeous.
Mm. Yeah.
Coach, you know you doomed,
Unless you can come up with
some kind opassing game.
Hey, why don't you let
coach worry about his game?
Y'all need to worry about buying
some of this radio airtime.
You know, buddy called me the other day.
That man is on a mission.
The roto-rooter talk's not
exactly morale-boosting, is it?
Who are you telling?
I bought 60 seconds, I'm a damn preacher.
Hey, sure hope you make it
worth my while, come Friday.
We'll do our best.
Hey, this is pretty good brisket here.
Thank you. Now I can die happy.
He's warming up to me.
Great. The internet's not working.
I'm sorry, honey.
Want to call downstairs?
No.
Jules.
You all right, honey?
I know I should be excited about this trip,
And I know that we've been planning it
For a really long time, and it's...
Everything's just-- just happening so fast.
I know. I know it seems like it.
I know I'm letting yo.
- Hey, huh
-uh.
No, ma'am. Don't go there.
How could you be letting me down?
I feel like such a stupid mess.
Like, hi, here I am. I got dumped.
And I'm hanging out at
all these universities
Where I don't belong.
Of course you do.
You belong anywhere you want.
I don't know. It's like,
all these interviews,
It's like... I'm expected to recite
All these factoids about myself
And tell them how perfect I am
And why I'd be a good student,
And it's just...
It just seems fake.
Well, I'll tell you what.
The only thing you need to do
In all these interviews
is go in and just be you.
Just, you know,
look at this as an opportunity.
This is an opportunity for your future.
It's exciting.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
- Yo.
- What's up, man?
- What up, c?
- Chillin'.
Another day.
I know you hungry.
Go ahead and eat something.
What's up?
Getting kind of boring stealing
these cars without you.
Need my road dawg.
I can't, man.
I wish I could, but, you know,
Gotta study these plays, you know.
Right. Right. Plays.
Plays. Yo.
You know, ty and some of his boys
Are gonna be down at the
park hooping later, man.
You should definitely roll.
We could take 'em.
I mean, you ain't that good,
But, you know, you got me on your team,
So we solid.
Yeah, bro.
Can't do it.
Practice, you know.
Coach is on my butt about it, so...
Coach come first, huh?
All right.
It's not even like that, man.
Listen, look, we gonna be hanging
Real soon.
I just can't get caught up, you know.
My p.O., you know how it is.
Yeah, I know how it is, man.
All right.
Okay, so when you walk in,
you want to have a presence.
So smile-- are you paying attention?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Walk tall.
Come in. Sit.
With your shoulders pulled back,
Like there's a beam of energy
coming out of your chest.
I don't think I'm trying
to be a superhero here.
I just want a job.
okay, now, get up,
And let's do it from the beginning.
Oh. It's my turn.
Okay. You ready for this?
I am so ready. -
- Walk tall.
- Walking tall.
That's my resume, sir.
So, mr. Riggins,
I understand you're applying for a job here.
What kind of situation are you looking for?
I'm looking for a situation
where I can achieve something,
Be proud of it,
And do it, start to finish,
On my own.
You know what I think?
What?
I think you're a strong person,
An honest worker,
And I think you can grow up
to be whoever you want to be,
Tim riggins.
I'm guessing that's for you.
What are you doing here?
Just came to talk to tim riggins.
Oh.
- It's for you.
- Yep.
How are you doing?
- Fine.
- Good.
Fours.
What can I do you for?
Um, I got hurt real bad at the farm.
I mean, it's like,
when I push off and when I get hit,
It's like someone's trying to
rip my leg off with a crowbar.
What about the meds the doc gave you?
It's like three weeks of meds.
I went through 'em in one.
All right.
This is what I need you to do, all right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Dr. Cooney.
Mental note this, all right?
When you see him, first thing you got to do,
Tell him how great he was at tmu.
Bring up your hip.
And then there's four questions.
One-word answers.
- Mm-hmm.
- No, no, yes, no.
That's it.
All right. Okay.
well, the joke is on you,
Mr. Kangaroo, for my sword
was dipped in poison.
Okay. Yay! Whoo!
Whoo!
Yay, thanks, landry, for the story.
Now it's bedtime.
What?
Come on.
Now be careful with those swords.
And start the--
You're trying to scare me.
Aren't you gonna kiss?
- Go inside.
- No.
Start the bathwater.
Vince is gonna kick your butt.
He's gonna kick who's butt?
this is gonna be fun!
Jess likes the punter!
She's gonna kiss him!
Smoochy!
What'd he say about vince?
I don't-- I don't know.
I think they like--yeah.
Well, either way,
I had a really good time tonight.
I did too.
I'll see you tomorrow at school.
- Yeah.
- Thanks for the sword.
- Be careful.
- And for the story.
That--thanks.
All right.
Good night.
Yeah.
Well, I got a toy.
All right, it's a vegetarian place,
And it's around here somewhere.
It's supposed to be great.
I read a review about it.
Can't we just go back
and order room service?
What are you talking about?
This is gonna be fun.
I just want to go back.
Hey, hon, come here, come here,
Come here, come here, come here, listen.
I know you're sad about matt leaving,
And I am sorry for that.
But we're here. All right?
This is a great opportunity for you.
I just want to make sure you're
seeing the bigger picture.
I don't know what that big picture is.
It's you. It's your life.
It's your future.
It's getting into the school of your dreams.
You mean the school of your dreams.
Hey.
Stop acting like you're here
Because of me, like I've been
Masterminding your
applications and all that.
No, you've always wanted
to go to a great school
Your whole life.
I am just here to support you.
You get that?
Well, I'm sorry I'm not giving
you the command performance
That you deserve. - Well, you know what?
You've got an opportunity tomorrow.
And you can either show
up and be your best self,
But if you blow it off
because of a break-up,
You are gonna regret that.
So what do you want me to do?
I want you to pull it together, girl.
Yeah, well, I'm trying to
pull it together, okay?
- Well, try harder.
- Try harder?
Yes.
Thanks for your support, mom.
Jules, come-- jules, come here.
Come here. Jules.
- We were assigned a
christmas memory last year,
And, after that, I started reading
All of capote's short stories.
They're really great.
Well, that's impressive.
You know what I think is really amazing?
Is that he and harper lee were best friends.
That, in a little town, two great artists
Found each other when they were kids.
Hmm. I never thought of it that way.
Now, julie,
Is there anything else you
want to say about yourself,
Something that we wouldn't pick
up from reading your transcript?
Um...
When I started high school,
I couldn't wait to get out of dillon.
I thought that every book I
read was like a rung on a ladder
That I built to escape this town
That was all about high school
football and nothing else.
And now that I'm actually
getting close to leaving,
I'm starting to appreciate
That I was shaped by my town,
That I have different viewpoint
than every other person.
I guess what I'm trying to say is that...
I'm surprised by how happy I am
To be from where I'm from.
Does that make any sense?
Yes, it does.
Thanks for coming in.
Well, I appreciate you taking the meeting.
- Absolutely.
- Great.
So anything you want to
add before we're done?
- Resume seems pretty up
-to-date
And, I mean, the state
champ's on there and stuff.
Yeah. Hey, that was impressive, man.
I know I could really come
Into this kind of workplace and
have a sense of achievement.
Well, tim, I think you'd be a good fit here.
- Awesome. Great.
- Great.
- Yeah.
- And so we'll be in touch.
Okay.
You take care.
Yeah. You too.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So?
Is that you asking me how it went?
I mean, you know,
I'm not pressuring you.
You tell me if you want to tell me.
It went well.
Good.
Actually, it went great.
And I went in there,
and I totally kicked ass.
Oh.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
But you know what, hon?
You know I'd be proud of
you no matter what, right?
I know.
And this whole thing about the fact
That I applied to this school--
I know, I know. It's your dream.
No, honey, honey, that's the thing.
I got my dream.
I went to a good school,
I got the degree I wanted,
I met your dad,
And I had you.
You're my dream, baby.
I got what I wanted.
I got it all.
And now it's your job to
dream up whatever you want,
And I will support you to the
ends of the earth to do that.
Our plane's not till tonight.
We could go-- go to a museum
Or go get a hot fudge sundae and celebrate.
Could we just go home?
Sure we can, sweetie.
You allergic to any medication?
No.
Use alcohol?
You ever try any ove
r-the-counter medications?
Yes.
They do any good for the pain?
- No.
- Hmm.
Who's gonna win the bcs?
Tmu, sir.
At least your head's in the right spot.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
- Good luck tonight.
- Yes, sir.
They said I came close,
Whatever that means.
And they'll--they'll, of course,
keep the resume close by.
So you never know.
There's no accounting for taste.
That's what my mom always says.
I've heard that a few times myself.
So this is it, huh?
This is it.
It's beautiful.
You know what?
I didn't want that job anyways.
See those trees right there?
That little ridge?
That's where the house is gonna go.
And then I want that deck
That goes all the way around.
- A wraparound.
- Yeah.
Maybe even a little guest house.
You never know.
You see the tree line right there,
I mean, I've walked this
property a few times,
And it goes way, way beyond that.
It's endless.
I wanted to--
I wanted to thank you...
For helping me with...
The process.
So thank you.
I'm sorry.
Welcome, folks, and all the fans
Of the east dillon lions.
We invite you tonight to the radio debut
Of lions football on 1040 a.M., el fuego.
Now over to my partner
And your play-by-play man willie gault.
Thank you, buddy garrity,
And thank you to all you fans who tuned in
To hear a game that has been given
A very special billing--
The toilet bowl.
One, two, three! All: Lions!
* *
Oh!
Go! Go! Go!
There's the snap. Looking left.
He cuts up the middle.
Too late. Makes a move.
Touchdown! - There we go.
And the lions draw first blood.
What an impressive first series
That coach eric taylor
Has designed here in east dillon tonight.
Yeah!
I tell you what, vince howard is gunned up,
He is yoked up, and he is playing
Like he's been playing
quarterback his whole life.
And this touchdown was brought to you
By el amigo restaurant.
* *
Vince howard comes back out in the spread.
He's got his a back setup in the slot.
Rolling right to throw back.
* *
Oh! Beautiful pass!
Oh, he overthrew him. It's incomplete.
Would you look at the gun on that kid?
Howard has just thrown the ball
It looks like 60 yards, willie.
It seems like inexperience
Finally caught up with young howard.
Landry!
Field goal.
But it's on the 25 yard line.
Just go kick the damn thing.
go, landry, go!
* *
Ladies and gentlemen,
Landry clarke has hit a 42-yard field goal.
East dillon lions go into halftime
With a 17 to 7 lead.
You scared the crap out of me.
What's with the monkey suit?
How much money are we talking about?
Tim.
I don't want you involved in this.
How much?
You'll make more money in two months
Than you could in two years.
Two months?
Two months max.
- It's 17
-7, east dillon,
And the way the lions
have been playing tonight,
I hope coach taylor just lets 'em play.
All right, go on one. Ready? All: Break.
Howard over center.
There's your snap.
He's looking left.
Under pressure, throws the ball.
Oh, it's picked off!
Oh, what are you doing?
Timberwolves have it. Going the other way!
The pack on the move.
Touchdown, timberwolves.
You know what,
A good quarterback's got a short memory.
* *
Cafferty's looking for a place to go.
There's nowhere to run.
And cafferty gets swarmed
by the timberwolf team.
- Come on!
- Oh, my, fumble!
Campo picks it up.
Looks like reservations for six.
Touchdown, timberwolves!
Another timberwolf touchdown.
This cannot be.
The lions have squandered their lead.
Now how did this happen?
I think I'm gonna be sick, willie.
let's go, lions, let's go!
* *
Hey, hey, time out. Time.
Hey, you all right? - Yeah, I'm fine.
You all right till next series?
Yeah. Let's go. Yes, sir.
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
60 seconds left in the game,
The lions third and goal
from the two-yard line.
Coach taylor out of time-outs.
You know, sometimes, willie,
There are other forces at work.
Damn it, coach taylor
has inspired these boys,
He's worked these boys,
And these boys are a team.
* *
Go, go, go!
Yeah!
The east dillon lions win! We won!
We won a game!
Yeah.
* *
I got to admit,
my man's been insane tonight.
No doubt.
I'll see you later.
Hey, landry! - Hey there.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com