- Give me my wallet back.
- Oh!
[police sirens]
- We are at
a crossroads right now.
You are gonna cut
the tough guy crap.
- My mother never took me
shopping for a pageant gown,
And because of that
I never placed at miss texas.
- [chuckles]
- Mrs. Saracen?
- [sobbing]
- It's your dad.
He was killed.
I'm sorry.
- It's late in the game
here at east dillon, folks.
And once again, the lions
are going gently
Into that good night.
- You understand me?
All right, let's get some points
out of this thing.
- Hey, water! Let's go!
- Down 24,
Another short gain
for east dillon.
- They know what we're
gonna do before we do it.
- What do you want me to do?
- Let's run wildcat.
- No, no, no.
Coach said we ain't ready.
- I'm ready, all right?
Let's go out there and get
some of our pride back,
Some dignity.
- All right, he's gonna kick
our asses all over the state.
I hope you know that.
- Yeah, coach can't catch me.
- Hey!
- All right, guys,
we're gonna go with right--
- Nah, nah, nah,
new play, new play.
All right, we're gonna go with
spread texas "a," skinny max.
- That's not what coach said.
- Shut up. You get your ass
out to "x"
And make some blocks,
all right?
Listen, we're going
option right, all right?
On one, on one.
Ready?
All: Break!
♪ ♪
- Look at this.
Coach taylor's come out
in a texas spread, ace set.
Cafferty to the outside.
- What are you doing?
- Here we go.
This could be fun, folks.
- It's cafferty
on the counter.
He cuts inside.
Oh, wait a second, folks!
It's a pitch to vince howard.
Oh, and he smokes the safety!
One man to beat.
Oh, my! What a move!
Howard taking it to the barn,
folks.
Touchdown east dillon.
Touchdown dillon!
[cheering]
♪ ♪
- My goodness!
Vince howard absolutely mudholed
The free safety.
- Good call, coach!
- 54 yards--the best run
from scrimmage all season,
And a hell of a read
from luke cafferty.
- Come here!
Come here!
Who called that?
Who called that play?
- It happened so fast.
- Who called the play?
- I blacked out, coach.
Cafferty, who called the play?
- I don't know
who called the play.
- Who called the play?
- Get out there on kickoff.
Get out there. Let's go!
[cheers and applause]
- You want to get
some more of that?
- Yeah.
- If you want some more of that,
get the damn ball back.
- 41. Number?
- 4-3.
- 4-3?
- [shouting plays]
Hike!
- South pines
back to pass.
Vince howard coming off the edge
on the speed rush.
Oh, and he strips him
on the playing side!
Ball's on the court,
but who wants it?
- Get there, get there,
get there.
- Oh, dallas tinker pounces
on the ball.
East dillon has come up with it.
First down east dillon.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Listen up here.
Listen up.
Hey, I call the play.
You understand?
- Yes, sir.
- I call the play.
You run the play.
You got that?
- You got it.
- Wildcat gun "x" throwback.
You understand me?
- Wait, you want me
to throw it?
- No, I want you to stand here.
I want to talk about it
all night.
Yes, I want you to throw it.
I want you to hit him
in-stride, you got me?
- Yeah.
- Hit him in-stride.
- Let's go!
- Here we go!
- Watch this.
- Make it count.
♪ ♪
- Here we go, folks.
Vince howard on the wildcat
sweep going right.
Oh, he pulls out
looking backside.
Going deep to cafferty.
A littlerickeration.
He's wide open.
Oh, my. Pay dirt!
Touchdown east dillon.
Touch down lions.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
♪ ♪
- Real strong finish to a game
that could not be won, folks.
But a monster game
out of vince howard.
A little light for a team
that's been stuck in the dark
All season.
[excited chatter]
- All right, hey!
- Listen up!
- Hey!
Y'all got nothing
to be ashamed of.
Let's hear it.
[cheering]
Hey, listen up now.
Listen up.
Y'all do me a favor.
Y'all take a knee real quick.
- Yes, sir.
- Most of you know
matt saracen.
Some of you know him
better than others.
A few of you have played
with him before.
You might have heard that
his father passed away.
The funeral's gonna be
in a couple days.
Thought it'd be nice
if maybe we say a word for him
And his family.
Lands.
- Bow your heads.
Our father,
who art in heaven.
All: Hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done,
On earth as it is in heaven.
- Hello. This is first sergeant
henry saracen
In mosul, iraq.
It's your son.
It's dad, it's me.
I wish you, mom,
and you, matt,
Want to wish the two of you
a merry christmas.
[knock at door]
- You got company.
- Okay.
- Bad movie night, matt.
It's not an option.
- Hey.
- Okay, grandma's sleeping,
So keep it down.
I'll make some popcorn
for you.
- Thanks.
How was the game?
- Uh, it was good.
Twinkle toes over here
kicked two points.
- Twinkle toes?
- Twinkle toes.
- That is not my nickname.
- I think it should be.
- It's golden foot.
I think I like
this one, matt.
A lot of hands.
- Yeah, I guess.
- What's this?
- Uh, it's just
this video
That my dad sent me
a couple christmases ago.
- Matt, I sent you
something in the mail.
Hopefully,
by now you got it.
This hat looks dumb.
- 50 bucks.
- We're doing
a good job here.
Gonna be out of here soon.
So I just wanted
to wish you a merry christmas.
That's good.
- That's nice.
- Yeah.
What do y'all
think of this one?
- Is that a hand?
I liked it.
- It's good.
- Let's go watch the movie.
♪ ♪
[phone rings]
[beep]
- hello.
- Hey, did you read
the paper today?
- Paper?
I don't get a paper, coach.
- Well, you got your face
in the paper
As one of the co-conference
players of the week.
- My picture?
How do I look?
- You look like an idiot.
That's how you look.
- Okay.
- Picture looks great.
- Yeah, but we still lost.
- I understand that.
It means you played
a hell of a game though.
Listen,
what they want you to do
Is they want you to come over
for the pancake breakfast.
It's at 1:00.
They have you speak to,
you know, the little guys,
The pop warner kids
and stuff.
You do that?
- Yeah, but why is it called
called a breakfast?
It's at 1:00.
Wouldn't it be, like, a lunch?
- Son, I don't know
why they do that.
That's just what they call it.
Can you do it though?
Can you be there then, right?
- I like pancakes.
- All right, good-bye.
- Daddy, we need you
off the phone now.
- Hey, mom,
we ain't got no electrics.
No nothing.
Mom!
Mom.
Mom, come on.
Come on.
♪ ♪
- I think the best thing
she could do right now
Is just quit.
I'm serious.
That's just wrong.
- Hush.
- Why the xylophone?
This whole thing is confusing.
- Shiftless son of a bitch.
- What?
- My ex, her dad.
Gonna miss her singing again.
Always gone somewhere.
He never shows up.
- [playing xylophone]
[applause]
- that was wonderful.
Next up in the miss young
texas pageant,
We have miss becky sproles...
- Whoo!
- Of east dillon.
- Miss becky sproles will be
singing the song popular
From the musical
the wicked.
- Oh, it's just wicked.
[song begins]
♪ ♪
- So you just have
to know, matt,
That what your dad did--
What your daddy did
was important.
I mean, right now I know
it seems real far away,
But we're over there
for a reason.
And your daddy knew that.
- [sobbing]
- He was a hero.
And that will
give you strength.
- Thank you, mr. Garrity.
- Remember that.
- I will.
- Excuse me.
- Matty, you haven't moved
from that chair in an hour.
- I don't really need to.
Everybody just keeps
coming up to me.
All I gotta do
is say thank you.
And grandma's over there.
He stepped on an I.E.D.
How long do these things
go for?
- You know what?
Screw you, bull.
The pageant goes
for another two days.
You know what,
you can still get here.
I don't care!
I really don't care
if you're hauling pieces
Of jesus' cross
back to bethlehem.
You promised her
you were gonna be here,
And you are gonna be here.
This is so damn
typical of you, you--
- Please.
- Do you have any idea what
you're doing to this girl?
Any idea?
She was so disappointed today.
She sang her heart out for you,
and you didn't hear anything.
[phone rings]
- Hello.
- That new place that
just opened up by smitty's.
- Excuse me, boys.
Excuse me.
It's the telephone
for you, tim.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Why are you
getting a phone call?
- I don't know.
Hello.
- Hey, tim.
- Becky?
- Well, I know.
I just--I tried your cell,
And I tried you at work,
so I figured you must
Be at matt saracen's.
- What are you doing right now?
I'm at a wake.
Do you know
what a wake is?
- Yeah, I just--
I figured that you weren't
close to the dead guy,
But if you are, I'm sorry.
I'll hang up now.
- What's the problem?
What is it, the trailer's
on fire or what?
- No, I just--
I just wanted
to tell you that, um,
Thanks for coming today.
It meant a lot to me.
- [sigh]
you're welcome.
You did good,
and good luck.
You'll probably win,
so don't blow it.
- You really think so?
- All right, I gotta go.
- Oh, yeah.
Thanks, bye.
- I'll see you around.
- Wait, so your job
Is, like, to see the bodies
home or something?
- I'm a recruiter,
mostly here in west texas.
But this is an honor job.
- So you didn't
even know my dad?
- No.
But I do my best to find out
about every man.
Heard he was quite the joker
in his unit.
A funny guy.
- My dad?
- Yeah.
He always kept up morale.
Did practical jokes and such.
It's important, matt.
- Yeah, no, I'm sure it is,
But I'm also sure
that wasn't my dad.
I bet he was
a really good soldier
And all that,
but he wasn't a funny guy.
He was not funny ever.
So maybe you talked
to the wrong people.
Maybe it was another guy
who was the joker,
But my dad was not,
all right?
I've never even seen him
smile in his life.
So I can't--
- excuse me, matt.
I think someone's--
someone's asking for you.
- Yeah, it was good
talking to you.
- Yeah, you too.
Thank you for coming.
- Are you okay?
- I don't know.
And I don't even understand
why they send this guy.
He's never even seen my dad
before in his life.
We all know that he was not
a very funny--
- I know, I know.
That's why the riggins clan
and myself,
We're gonna take you
out of here tomorrow night,
Away from all the death
and the dying
And the deviled eggs.
- Yeah, fine.
Whatever, fine.
I just don't want...
[knock on door]
Someone talking about
my dad anymore.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Hey, matt.
- Our condolences.
On behalf of the boosters--
- are you serious?
- Excuse me?
On behalf of the boosters
And the entire
panther organization,
We just--
- Ah.
[horn honks]
- 'sup cafferty?
- I'm running, man.
- I think he's--
you know, I think he's mad
That I'm co-conference
player of the week.
- Yeah, that's what
I'm pissed about.
- See this right here?
Look, hey, luke.
That's me.
That's j.D. Mccoy right there.
But I'm sharing this
with this guy.
I don't know who this guy is.
What's his name, vince howard?
Do you know a guy
by that name?
- Yeah, come to think of it,
I do recall spending
A couple hours in jail
with someone by that name.
I don't know how I got there,
Considering my friends
were with me at the time,
Kevin and--what did you say
your name was, j.D. Mcdick?
- Oh, come on, man.
Look, the cops were there, okay?
We took off.
I'm sorry.
- You're a jackass, dude.
- Look, what do you
want me to do?
You want me to get out
and get on my hands and knees,
Is that what you want me to do?
I'll do it.
- Look, man.
Buddy, we're both sorry.
All right, but we're going
paintballing tomorrow night.
We want you to come.
It'll be fun, man.
Come on, please.
- I'll think about it.
- Think about it.
- All right, but hey, luke,
right here, man.
Give it to me.
- Luke, we'll see you
around, man.
We're sorry.
Later, bud.
- Julie will sit here
with you.
- Good idea.
- Thank you, julie.
- You don't think
she'll get hot in there?
- No, she'll be fine.
Julie's with her.
She'll be okay.
Don't you worry, okay,
hon?
- Uh-huh.
- What you've got here
is what we like to call
Our american hero
memorial package.
Now, this comes
with your choice
Of a mahogany
or cherry wood casket.
The standard outer
burial container.
- What--
what's that?
- Well, over time,
the caskets themselves
Deteriorate in the soil,
the moisture.
- Oh.
- And since veteran affairs
will be picking up
Most of the bill,
you can honor your father
In a manner he deserves.
- Right, thanks.
- So there's the embalming.
- Is--is my dad here?
- Oh, he's being prepared
right now.
- Do I see him?
- I think, in this case,
A closed casket
is most appropriate.
- Right, right.
- Okay. So--
- Actually, if that's
the case,
Can I just ask
one quick question?
Sorry to interrupt.
This viewing/visitation day,
Use of facilities,
use of staff, day prior.
That wouldn't be necessary
if it's a closed casket,
Is that right?
- Of course.
- Okay, so we can
get rid of those charges.
That would be great.
Thank you.
- Now see,
the rest is laid out.
This is for
the funeral service escort.
- I don't understand
that either.
The funeral service escort,
what does that mean exactly?
- Well, those are the cars
that will--
You know, for the family,
friends.
- Well, they have cars.
I mean, we all have cars.
- Yeah, and, um--
And my grandma's
in the car right now.
So can we just decide
whatever this is and--
- You know, why don't you--
you go on out there.
I can finish up with him.
I think we're just about
at the end of it anyway.
You go on out.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I think so.
I think so.
All right,
I think this is just--
- Thank you.
- You have any questions,
call me.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you.
- I'll be right there.
I need to ask you
a quick question.
With all due respect,
does that boy look like
He can pay $9,000
to bury his father?
- Well, veterans affairs
will be picking up--
- You look me in the eye,
you tell me veterans affairs
Is gonna pick up
a $9,000 bill.
- No, not the entire $9,000.
- Mm-hmm.
- But they do pick up
a large portion.
- Okay, well, I think--
we need to start over
From the beginning, okay?
And let's do this quickly,
please.
Do you have another listing
you can give me?
- Keep your hands
to yourself, man.
We're looking
for old cars like this.
- What is this, man?
- Old models, man,
all right?
You see when they stop
making the cars,
They stop making the parts.
It makes the parts worth more,
you feel me?
- Like a bunch of junk parts in
here, man.
- You see a new car,
Think it's sharp,
think it's fly,
You need to walk away.
- Walk away? Why?
- Oh, it's 'cause they got
that lojack, man.
- Man, we're in west texas.
Ain't nobody
got no lojack.
You walk away
'cause half them new cars
Got them steering locks.
Lojack.
Man, what's wrong with you?
- I told him his braids
too tight sometimes.
He don't listen.
- Hey, man, watch out.
- Watch out, what?
Watch out.
- Yo, yo, both of you
need to shut up.
This here is school,
And the more you talk,
the more you miss.
The more you miss, the more
likely your bitch asses
Are gonna
do something stupid.
All right, this place where
you put the keys in,
It's called a tumbler.
You stick your
screwdriver in it,
Jiggle it a little bit.
Sometimes the dashboard
might come on.
Sometimes the engine.
Yo, don't panic.
Be cool and get paid.
[engine starts]
Most of the times,
this ain't an option.
Then you gotta
hot box the bitch.
Come in closer.
This is the magic.
- Honey, we're gonna leave
in just a minute.
- Yeah, all right.
Hey.
- Hi.
That was really nice
of your mom.
I appreciate it.
- She's good in crisis.
She's pretty much
built for crisis.
- Yeah.
- She's invited you over
for dinner tonight
If you want to come.
I said you probably
had family stuff to do,
But if you want to get away
for an hour or something,
I'd love to see you.
- Wkay.
- Okay, you'll come or...?
- Um...
Yeah, okay, I'll--
Okay, I'll come.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I just--
You know,
this stuff happens.
Right now
it's happening to me.
Someday it's gonna
happen to you.
And--
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
That was a stupid thing
to say.
- It's okay.
- So what time
is this dinner?
- Koala bears--
you know what they eat?
Do you know
what koala bears eat?
- And that's more than enough
for a first down.
That makes it six carries
for 38 yards.
I'm not saying
this young man's ready to start,
But brian "smash" williams
Is making the most
of this blowout.
- Look at him run, huh?
Look at him go.
- Hey.
- How 'bout that?
- Look at y'all.
- Mmm.
- Hi, sweet girl.
Hey.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Did y'all have fun?
- It's almost time
for a nap for you.
- Mm-hmm.
- How'd it go?
- It went.
Somebody ready for a nap?
- "no, no."
- Maybe we'll both
lie down together for a nap.
- [whispering] here, here, here,
here, here.
Take that with you.
- All right.
- How's he holding up?
- Um...
He's trying.
- Oh.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Who's your favorite
football player?
- You ever heard
of johnny unitas?
- Mm-hmm.
- My old coach over there
Used to tell me
about johnny unitas.
Said I remind him a lot
of johnny unitas.
See that old man
over there in the back,
One of the oldest guys
in this room?
[laughter]
That's my dad.
He taught me
everything I know.
You gotta be fast.
You gotta know
what plays you're calling.
You gotta look around.
You gotta see everything moving.
When I step to the line,
I see everything happening
way before it happens.
I'm a good one or two seconds
ahead of the coverage.
- The boy scout's
pretty arrogant.
- You guys are all the team,
okay?
- He's got a hell of an arm.
- All right, be a hero,
win championships.
I see it in you.
All right?
[applause]
- Thank you, j.D.
Now for our other
dillon gazette
Conference player
of the week,
Vince howard
of the east dillon lions.
[applause]
Now some of you kids here,
this is your first year
Playing pop warner,
but guess what.
This is vince's
first year too.
So pay attention,
all right?
You've got a role model here.
What do you say, vince?
You got some words
for these players here?
- What am I supposed to say?
- Just talk about the game.
Just tell 'em about it.
- Don't panic,
all right?
Stay cool,
and you'll get paid.
- Yeah!
[applause]
- Stop.
- Hold on, one--
- Seriously, get away from me.
- Two, say it.
- No regrets.
- No regret.
- [groans]
[laughter]
- Ahh!
That feels good.
- That was really close.
- Hey, you guys remember
the state finals game
Three years ago?
- Uh-uh.
- No, billy.
- What game?
- Who played in it?
- Stop messing with me, man.
- Are you really reminiscing
about three years ago?
- You guys remember,
there was, like,
Ten seconds
left on the clock.
We had matt "mayday" saracen
Sitting back there
behind the center.
- Never has he been called
"mayday."
- Well, we need to come up
with a nickname.
I like "cobra."
it's got a good sound to it.
Hey, cobra, think fast.
You're cobra.
- Dude.
- Why would you kill
cobra's beer?
- I know.
Hey, let's see your hands.
- You guys know
I have to give a eulogy
At this thing tomorrow?
I got to get up there
in front of everybody
And say good stuff
about this man.
And all I really
want to say is,
"here lies henry saracen.
"his mother annoyed him.
"his wife couldn't stand him.
"and he didn't want to be a dad,
so he took off
"to be in the army,
'cause that was the only way
"you cou come up with
to get out of here
"and ditch
all your responsibilities
"and no one could
call you out on it.
"and that worked out great,
so you just decided
"to enlist four more times,
"and that ended up
getting you killed.
"and now here you are.
"and all you got left,
all you left behind
"is a mother with dementia,
"a divorced wife,
"and a son
who delivers pizza.
Thank you for coming,
100 people I do not know."
And you know what
the worst part is?
Even if I did get up there
and say that,
Even if I finally did, like,
say all that to him,
I don't even know
if I'd be saying it to him
Because I don't even know
if he's in that damn box.
It's a closed casket.
For all I know,
it's someone else.
It's someone funnier.
Or a bunch of rocks.
I don't ev--
- Well...
- There's only one way
to find out then.
Right?
Cobra, you got the key.
- There's no key.
- Break the window.
- There's probably a door--
- Just break it.
- It's stuck.
- Yeah.
- Go.
- All right, go in.
- You sure we're supposed
to be doing--
- You're wasted.
- Where is he?
Where is he?
- That's where
I saw him before.
Hold on.
All right, it's this guy,
it's this guy.
Hey.
- Hey, matt.
- Hey, my friend--
- hey, hold on.
- My friend wants to see
his old man.
- I want to see my dad.
- Um, well, I thought
we agreed earlier
That that probably
wasn't a very good idea.
- Look, buddy,
he wants to see his dad.
- Hey, hey.
Just hey, stop, stop, stop.
Landry.
Look, I know what
we decided earlier,
But now...
I want to see my dad. Now.
That's him?
- Yeah.
Son, I really don't think
this is a very good idea.
- I appreciate that,
But please just open it.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Matt, you all right?
- Hey, kevin,
right here, man.
[paintball guns shooting]
pictures, baby.
- Dude, I thought we were going
to the field, man, come on.
- We are going to the field.
We're just getting
a little practice in first.
- Kevin, cut that out, dude.
You're getting paint
on my truck, man, come on.
- This truck's
a piece of crap anyways.
Don't worry about it.
- Yeah, it's a piece of crap
I had to pay for
with my own money, dumbass.
- Hey, yo, yo.
- All right, bud.
- Get this pedestrian
right here.
- Hey, don't shoot him.
Don't shoot him.
- Whoo!
- Oh, my god.
What are you doing?
[tires squeal]
- What are you
stopping the car for?
- Get out of the truck.
Get out of the truck!
- Hey, yo, relax.
Just chill out.
You got some kind
of chip on your shoulder, man.
- I'm fine.
- Look, that school you go to
Is a dump, okay?
We all know this.
Do you want us
to pretend it's not
And lie about it to you?
- Oh, okay, so every time
we get to hang out,
That means I get to be the one
that you all look down on?
- We don't look down on you.
- [scoffs]
- We look down on you
with you.
- [laughs] that's right.
That was a good one.
- All right, jokers.
All right, that's funny.
- What?
Come on, luke.
- Get out.
- Why you gotta do this?
- Get out of the truck.
- What's your problem
tonight, man?
- What's my problem?
You're my problem, idiot.
- What are you doing?
- Ah, god!
- What are you doing, dude?
- I'm not going paintballing
is what I'm doing.
- You know what,
screw you, luke.
How's it feel being second best
on the worst team in texas?
- All right,
better watch it.
Ah!
- Come on, man.
Luke, I'm sorry.
- Oh, yeah, I'm sorry too.
You're done, dude.
You're done.
- Come on, luke.
- Get off my truck!
Get off my truck.
- Screw you, luke!
[firing]
- Hey.
How'd it go?
- Second runner-up.
- That's, um--
that's third, right?
- Yeah.
- Then I guess
it's not really--
- Third place sucks.
- Yeah, it's crap.
Yep.
- So how was your day?
- Weird.
- Weird how?
- I saw something that, uh--
Or rather I saw someone
see something that...
You ever just feel
completely useless?
- You're not useless.
- Right.
- Close your eyes.
Just do it.
- [clears throat]
No.
This--
This can't happen.
I can't do this.
Good night.
♪ ♪
- Hi.
- You got I.D.?
- Oh, it's for my mama.
She ain't feeling too good.
- I need to see I.D.
- Okay, you know what,
I walked all--
- Hey bud,
you're almost out of soap.
Hey.
Becky, right?
- Yeah.
- There you go.
- That doesn't look good.
- Mm-mm.
What do you think?
- I think you ought
to buy something.
- We're together.
This is my stuff.
♪ ♪
Here's my I.D.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- Well, thanks again.
- Yeah, yeah.
My name's luke.
- I know who you are.
- Oh.
Here you go.
- Yeah.
See you later.
- All right, night.
Hey, you want to go
to a car wash?
I got to go
to a car wash.
Look at that thing.
- Sure.
Why the hell not?
- All right.
[knocking at door]
- You want to get that,
sweetie?
- Hey.
- Sorry, um,
I know I'm really late.
- It's okay.
We saved you a plate.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Mrs. Taylor, I'm sorry.
I know that--
- Oh, you're fine, honey.
We saved you a plate.
We saved our dessert
for now.
We'll have dessert with you.
You're fine.
- Thank you.
- Come on, sit down.
Don't you worry.
- You drive?
- No, sir, no, no.
I had a nice walk though.
- Well?
- You don't have to eat it
if you don't want to.
- I'm hungry.
- Well, do you want
something else, hon?
You don't--
- no, it's--
I'm sorry, mrs. Taylor,
I don't like carrots.
- Oh, well, then--
- And I don't like when
they touch the meat so...
- Well, I'll just
take it away then.
- No, look, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
- No, no, no, no.
- No, it's fine.
I'm being rude.
I'm sorry, I don't--
- Honey, you're fine.
- I don't like being rude.
I don't like being rude.
- It's okay.
- I'm just having
a moment here.
I just--
I'm just having a moment.
I don't think I'm okay.
- Matt.
- [sobbing]
I hate him.
And I don't--
I don't like hating people.
But I just put
all my hate on him
So I don't have to hate
anybody else
And so that I could be
a good person, you know,
To my grandmother
and to my friends.
To your daughter.
That's all I want to say.
I just want to tell him
to his face that I hate him.
But he doesn't
even have a face.
I'm sorry, mrs. Taylor.
I'm--I'll see y'all
tomorrow.
- Matt.
Matt, you don't have to go.
- It's all right.
- Matt!
- Honey, honey.
Come here, sweetie.
It's okay.
- You're just gonna
let him go like that?
- Shh.
I'll get him.
It'll be all right.
Be all right.
- It's okay.
- I have to do something.
I can't just let him
hurt like that.
- Matt.
Matt!
I'm gonna walk you home.
- Okay.
- Looks good.
- It's pretty.
- Thank you.
- The picture.
Look at his picture.
- Yeah.
- Lead us not
into temptation,
But deliver us
from evil.
For thine is the kingdom
and the power
And the glory forever
and ever.
Amen.
Now, matt would like to share
Some words of remembrance
with us.
- Um...
I'm just gonna tell you
one story I remember,
And that'll be it.
We were at the...
Supermarket.
It was me and my mom,
Grandma...
And my dad--
All four of us,
our whole family.
My dad was pushing the cart,
And he stopped to grab
some toilet paper
And put it in the cart,
and my grandma said,
"no, that's not
the right one.
That's not the right toilet
paper that we use."
She grabbed
the right toilet paper
And put it in the cart
And stormed off.
And my dad just kinda
stared off at her.
And then he just started
grabbing all the toilet paper
Off the shelf
and putting it in the cart.
I mean, he just
stacked it full of--
And it wasn't spiteful
or nothing.
He--
I don't know,
maybe you had to be there,
But as a six-year-old,
It was the funniest thing
I'd ever seen in my life,
And I just laughed about it
for weeks.
I guess...
My dad was just a funnier
person than he really let on.
He was kinda private
in that way,
And I don't really know y.
But one thing
that he wasn't private about
Was his service.
He was in the army
for 20 years,
And that was something
that he was--
He was proud of.
And he missed--
He missed
some of my birthdays,
And he missed
A lot of me growing up.
But I think the point
is that I got to grow up.
And I got to have
those birthdays.
You know,
he went and did a job
That not many people
want to do.
Because of that,
we all get to be here,
And we get to grow up,
And we get to have
our birthdays.
And I think that's
something to be proud of.
So thank you
for being here.
And my family thanks you.
♪ ♪
- On behalf of the president
of the United States
And our grateful nation,
For the faithful service
rendered by your loved one.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Fire.
[gunshot]
Fire.
- Y'all are invited now
To the saracen house
for a reception.
So we hope to see you there.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com