- No.
I can't do this.
- My name's luke.
- I know who you are.
- It's your dad.
He was killed.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- And this Friday's game between
the east dillon lions
And the mcnulty mavericks
promises to be a barn burner,
At least on one side
of the ball.
Mcnulty is the favorite to upset
the panthers' reign this year,
And their undefeated record
has them in prime position
For that playoff spot.
You got to wonder
how fast and how often
This mcnulty offense
is gonna score
On this poor lions' defense.
Flip the tv on
for this game.
It's gonna be a track meet.
- You hear that, man?
You one sorry, brother.
You know that, vince?
- Go ahead, cal.
- I mean, it's one thing
to be on the team that sucks.
It's a whole other thing
to be on a team
That suck on tv,
all right?
Everybody watching too?
- Calvin, shut up.
- Couldn't be me, man.
- All right, yeah, I know.
- That's why I quit that
sorry-ass team.
You know what
I'm saying?
- Mcnulty's averaging
53 points a game.
They got the second ranked
offense in the state.
Coach, they've only punted twice
the whole damn season.
- Friday, we are gonna
keep it simple.
- These are offensive plays.
- "offensive," stan.
"offensive" plays.
- Listen up now.
Mcnulty's undefeated.
Game's televised.
It's a game-changer.
I don't like it.
- That's what
I'm talking about.
- What we're gonna do
is we're gonna
Go down to the field
with the media.
We're gonna talk briefly
with the reporters.
- All right,
let's keep it simple.
- I'm not finished.
- Wait, wait, wait.
I totally just
remembered something.
- Oh, no.
What? You're pregnant?
- you are, aren't you?
- I'm having twins actually,
but they're aliens.
- Damn it!
I don't want twins.
- So I bought these tickets
For the austin
indie music festival,
And it was supposed
to be a surprise, but--
- Oh, but then my dad died.
- Yeah.
I can give 'em to devin
or something.
- No, no, no, no, no.
We ought to go.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
And you know what?
Actually someone gave me, like,
this grieving handbook thing,
And chapter two said,
"when your dad dies,
"you should most
likely probably go
To a music festival,
preferably in austin."
- You're such a liar.
- I'm not a liar.
- Are you sure
you're gonna be okay?
- I'll be fine.
Look, he's--
He's dead, all right?
And I'm--I'm alive.
So let's go.
- Okay.
- Hey, guys.
How you doing?
Hey, mike. How are you?
- Coach, what are your goals
going into this game?
- Goals going into the game?
Well, we'd like
to stop their offense
And put a few holes
in their defense.
- How do you intend to measure
your success in doing that?
- Well, we're gonna use
the scoreboard
To measure that success.
- What do you hope
to accomplish there?
I mean, what do you want
the score to reflect?
- I would like
for the score to reflect
That we left everything
on the field that we had.
- So are you saying you're
gonna win this game, coach?
- Well, what I'm saying is--
- We can win
and we will win.
- Are you guaranteeing
a victory?
- I am guaranteeing a victory.
We got to start practice,
okay?
- Good. Let's do this.
- Get these fine young
men out here
Who are gonna be putting
their blood on the field!
Becky, come on.
- Hey.
Nice place.
- Yeah, it's,
um, something.
So I saw you at the funeral.
- Yeah, I saw you too.
- Thought you'd be back
at college by now.
- Midterm break.
I stayed to see my dad.
- Oh.
That's nice.
- "that's nice."
that's it?
- I mean...
It's not nice?
Oh, you are something, huh?
You stop calling.
You disappear.
That's nice.
My dad says you threw away
the scholarship.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I did.
- Wow.
I am--
I'm so glad I came over.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- No, no, no.
- Mom!
It's two days.
It's not a week.
- It is two nights
in austin during exams.
Absolutely not.
It's a ridiculous thing.
You haven't even been
accepted into college yet.
- So if I would have gotten
into college,
This would be a completely
conversation because...
- If you had passed
your exams already
And you had gotten accepted
into three schools
Early decision then, yes,
you can go to austin, texas,
On two school nights
and enjoy a music show.
Yes, I think in that situation,
I'd be all right with it.
- Matt's dad just died, mom.
- I'm not gonna dignify
that with even a response.
Come on, jules.
- What's going on?
- Dad, can I go to the music
festival with matt?
- Hi, sweet girl--
the music festival
In the middle of the week
in austin, texas, sweetheart.
- No, I don't think you're gonna
be going to austin with matt.
- You guys are awful!
- Oh.
Look, matt, I'm sorry.
- You should be, man.
You suck.
I been working
with you a lot lately--
- That is not at all
what I was talking about.
I was talking about your dad,
so thanks.
- I know. I know.
You know they--
They're giving us,
like, a death gratuity.
- A what?
Death gratuity?
- Yeah, it's, like, $100,000.
- Does it come in a tip jar?
- No.
They just--
I guess they tack it on with
the life insurance policies,
So grandma's--
You know, she's just set up
for the rest of her life.
- Well, that's good.
What about you?
- What about me?
- I don't know.
How are you doing,
I guess?
- I'm fine, man.
I don't understand
why people keep
Asking me how I'm doing.
I'm fine.
People just keep saying,
"are you okay?"
- Well, matt,
I don't really know
What to say
in this situation.
- Well, then don't say--
You don't have
to say anything, all right?
It's over with.
We took care of all that,
And now we're just
throwing a football.
Is that okay?
Is that okay with you?
- I'm really start
to get the feeling
That you just want
to fight.
I don't know if you
want me to give you
Some kind of big, uh, speech.
I don't know what it is
that you want me to do.
But I'm not gonna do that.
I don't care what you do.
But either way, I'm gonna
be your best friend,
'cause you've been my best
friend since we were five.
- Yeah, all right.
- Hey, honey.
Hey, y'all.
Oh, messages, messages?
- Of course.
Of course.
The pta meeting has been changed
to Friday the 28th.
Clint wants you
to meet the new hire
For ap spanish,
and mrs. Corrigan called
To request that her son
be moved out of calculus.
- Oh, goodness.
- Her number's here--
- Okay, thank you so much.
- Oh, and your daughter
called and she said
For you not to worry
about anything.
She'd see you on Saturday.
- Wait.
What was that?
- Yeah, she said--
She said she was going
to austin.
- She did?
- Called 15 minutes ago,
maybe.
- All right.
Could you just, um,
get that door?
Thank you very much.
Julie, this is your
mother calling.
I just got
the strangest message
From the secretary
in the office
That you have gone
to austin,
Which I know cannot
be true,
Considering the fact that both
your father and I told you
That you could not go
to austin.
So you had best
call me back right away.
Thank you very much.
- Hello, stranger.
- So look, I think--
I think the best thing
To do here in this situation
is just completely mature
About all this.
- Uh-huh?
- You know?
And first off,
I just want to say
Kissing you was great.
You know?
Um, you're--that was great.
You're great.
So just know that
bottom line, you know?
- Uh-huh?
- Well, you see,
there's this part of me
That's like,
maybe we should just kind of
See where it goes,
see what happens,
Not really think
about it too much.
Then there's
this other really, really
Kind of tiny part
of me
That's still hung up
on this other girl tyra,
Who's, like, embedded
in the back of my mind,
So I think
the mature thing--
I really didn't
see that coming.
- Will I see you later?
- Like when?
- Five minutes.
Maybe three.
- I go back to school
in three days.
- You go back to school
See, I don't know
if you know this,
But I'm kind of a
moment-to-moment kind of guy,
So three days...
- Uh-huh?
- I can work with that.
- What's that mean exactly?
That you can
"work with that?"
- No.
I could probably tell you,
but...
- I'm dying to know.
- showing you might be
even better.
I can show you what it means
to work with it.
- Ow!
- They're sharp, I know.
- How you doing?
- I'm good.
- Good.
I'll miss you.
- Tim riggins!
Okay, look,
I know you're inhere.
- Just 'cause there's
a girl at my door,
I don't have a girlfriend.
- Okay, you're not ignoring me,
right?
Because I just want
to let you know that
I'm not gonna jump on you every
time I see you or anything.
- Yeah, hi.
- Oh, hey.
- Lyla, becky.
Becky, lyla.
- Hi.
- Yeah, I was just gonna ask
for a ride to school,
But it's cool.
I know you're busy.
- Okay.
- I'll see you later.
- That was, um,
the landlord's daughter.
- Mm-hmm.
- How are you gonna play
this Friday night?
- We've been through the storm.
We've been through the rain.
Now we fixing
to bring the pain.
- Well, emily, I think,
you know,
I scored a perfect score
on my math portion of the s.A.T.
So, you know,
if the pressure's on,
I think I'm the guy
to go to, emily.
- Do you have anything more
to say about
That guaranteed win?
- Well, I'm more of the brains
and brawn, you know?
I got it all.
I'm the total package, baby.
- Are you gonna win?
- Coach, could we talk about
your history of quitting,
First with the panthers
back in '06,
And more recently,
forfeiting your first game
As head coach of the lions?
- Don't know why you
come out here
And waste people's time
with this.
- This is romantic.
Nice breeze.
It's perfect.
- Mmm.
Good sandwiches.
- Good sandwiches that I put
my heart and soul into.
- It's hard making
peanut butters.
your phone's ringing.
- It's just devin.
I'll call her back later.
- You sure?
- Uh-huh.
We're having our romantic picnic
right now, okay?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Uh-uh. Wait.
- Excuse me, miss.
Can I get some service,
please?
Excuse me, miss?
Can I get some menus over here
and some service?
Thank you.
- I'm sorry.
Okay, vince, you really need
to go away.
- I can't get some food?
- No.
It don't make no sense
you being here.
- Why not?
You know your dad got
the best ribs in town.
- What you want?
- Hey, mr. Merriweather.
I was just talking
to your daughter jess.
About to order some
of them baby back ribs.
- Mm-hmm?
Well, you can get that over
at the counter to go.
- No, that's cool.
I was gon' sit here and eat it.
- Get your ass over
to the counter.
- Yes, sir.
Here.
It was a pleasure talking
to you, jess.
I'll see you around school.
- Hey, it's the girl
who loves her candy.
Got you some gummy bears.
- Okay, look...
Our little thing
the other night,
That was a mistake,
okay?
That was a big mistake.
And I would really
appreciate it
If you didn't try to treat me
like a girlfriend or anything,
And I don't need you
buying me stuff.
I don't want anything
from you.
Especially not for you
to talk about me
To your little
football buddies.
- I didn't say anything
to my football buddies.
- Yeah, I'll bet you didn't.
Just forget it.
We just don't have to talk
at all anymore, okay?
- Sorry.
I just--
I think you're cute
and I just
Would really love to go
out again sometime, but...
I must be, uh--
Yeah.
I don't know.
Sorry.
- Julie, I know that
you probably do not
Think this is a big deal,
but I assure you
This is a gigantic deal.
You had best turn around from
wherever you are right now
And get yourself home,
and you answer the phone
When I call you!
You are my favorite daughter.
Be right back, sweetie.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
Wait, no.
You know what?
I think we should go--
because that would add--
- Jess.
Jess.
No, come on.
Seriously, it's fine.
- Is fine okay for tv?
'cause if y'all okay
with fine,
Then we can stop right now.
Come on.
Five, six, seven, eight.
All right, five, six,
seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
- Three, two, one.
- Bring it in, guys.
Let's go.
here we go, here we go.
- Hey, listen up.
Who can tell me
mcnulty's record?
- Yeah, coach,
they never lost.
- That's right.
They haven't.
But we're gonna
change that,
And here's how we're gonna
do it, gentlemen.
We're gonna play 11
on offense today,
But we are gonna
do 13 on defense,
Because if you can punch
one hole into 13,
You damn well ought
to be able to punch
2 holes into 11.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
- We got tim and billy
coming over to help.
- Ah, here we go.
- You boys ever play
a couple state champions?
- Here we go!
- Show 'em your ring, tim.
- All the guys in yellow
on defense,
Over there,
huddle 'em up.
Over here, offense.
- Let's go, boys!
Here we go!
Feel good!
We feel good!
How you guys feel?
- Let's go!
- Here we go!
Here we go!
Let's go!
Let's go, d!
- Strong red, strong red,
strong red!
- you was open on that one?
- I got hit before
I even got the ball.
- Guy's all over the place.
So fast.
- All right,
let's do it.
- Let's go.
Oh!
- yeah!
- It's like playing against
a brick wall over here.
Come on.
- I know.
I can feel it.
- We're not ready for this.
- Here we go.
Come on, come on, come on.
- Go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go.
Aww!
Copeland, you got
to respond to that!
- They're getting there.
They're getting there.
- Touch down!
- Love it, love it.
âTª âTª
- âTª you've got a way âTª
âTª to make my heart sing âTª
- Seriously, I mean,
I'm telling you right now,
If we had to play a game
tomorrow, I would be a madman.
- Okay, so here's what I want.
- Honestly I was running--
- I want you guys to just stop
talking about football.
- How's being pregnant?
- Oh, it's great, you know?
I mean, she just thinks her
water's gonna break,
Like, every 15 minutes,
but--
- Really?
I mean, I know
You have the belly,
but not the baby,
'cause she asked me what it was
like to be pregnant.
What you could do is you
could just thank me
For always being
your designated driver.
- I do.
I thank you constantly.
I thank you constantly, baby.
- Mm-hmm.
- 'cause I love you.
- It's true.
What?
- Y'all know what I miss?
- What?
- Getting on that bull
and letting off some steam.
- I'd ride that bull.
- No, you shouldn't.
- I would ride that bull.
- Hey, lyla, not a good call.
- It's totally a good call.
- No, it's not a good call.
Don't get on the death ride.
- I'm riding the bull.
- Yeah, you're riding the bull.
- What'd you just do?
- Amazing.
- Can I go next?
- Sure, little lady.
- This might not end well.
- Oh, my god.
- Whoo!
I'm ready!
- Whoa!
She's pretty good.
- Ow!
Whoo!
- That's very smooth.
- You missed me.
- You have no idea.
- Ll see you later.
- All right, buddy.
- Landry!
- Bye.
- Hey, landry.
- Hey.
- How are you doing?
- I'm doing good.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you over here
at east dillon.
- I know.
Well, you know, I had to drop
off something for coach.
Rushing off to my school.
- Right.
- Hey, have you talked
to matt and jules
Since they've gone off
on their big trip to austin?
- No, not since they left.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Listen, I'm just
gonna be
Real straightforward
with you, landry.
My daughter's awol
and I'm sick about it,
And if you could shed
any light on where they are
And when they're gonna be there,
anything like that,
It would just be real--
real helpful to me.
- Well, I mean,
I don't know.
Obviously I don't know
their whole schedule...
- You know, I--
well, just--
- I think they were planning on
seeing the heartless bastards
At emo's tomorrow night.
- Okay, that's good to--
- Like 7:30 or 8:00
or something.
But other than that, I don't--
- uh-huh.
And you know where
they're staying
Or anything like that?
- Are you going?
Are you gonna go visit?
- No.
I don't--no.
But I just--I'm a mother.
Um, all right, well,
I got to--
I'll have to get over
to my school now, but--
- Okay, well, it's--
- nice to see you.
- It was good to see you.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Hi.
Becky, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm lyla.
- Yeah, I remember.
- Is tim around?
- Oh, no.
I, um--I haven't seen him.
- Okay.
- So you're in college,
right?
Is it great?
- Yeah.
It's pretty cool.
Guess I've been a little
homesick lately.
- For dillon?
- Yeah, I didn't expect
that either.
- Did you come back
'cause you miss tim?
- No.
You know, I really don't know
what I'm doing here.
Um, you go away
to college and, uh...
You think you're getting over
the whole thing,
'cause being away helps
with that.
But...
Now I'm here
and here we are.
- I'll tell tim
you stopped by.
You're so lucky.
So pretty.
- This is the mcnulty film.
I want y'all to watch
this together.
You understand?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, good enough.
Anything confusing about that?
- Where?
- Wherever you can find
out to watch 'em.
Would you step out of my way
so I can see the tv, please?
- Okay.
Why do we have
to get killed on tv?
- I don't know.
I don't know
what we're gonna do.
- Gotta do something.
- Oh.
Look who it is.
- Look who it is.
- What are you guys doing?
- Watching game tape?
- What's it look like, genius?
- In sears?
- Funny.
- Yeah, I'm surprised you
haven't stolen one of these.
- Dude, shut up.
- Got a problem?
- Nah, but I can get one
real quick.
- Can I help you boys?
- Yeah.
- You know what?
Why don't you get the hell out
of my department
And the hell out
of my store?
- For what?
- 'cause I'm just
one jackass comment
Away from doing
some serious damage,
And if that happens,
I would lose my job...
And I love my job.
You get me?
- Let's go.
- Let's go, man.
- Yeah.
- From the east side.
Coach, I didn't even know.
What's up?
- Down.
Look for the gaps.
- Okay.
- Yes, sir.
- Matt, get off the bedspread.
- What?
- They don't wash it.
There's, like,
bugs that live in it.
Get off, off, off,
off, off, off, off.
- Okay, sorry, sorry.
- It's getting--get some
kind of disease.
- Jesus.
- There.
Now you can sit down.
- Would you like to dance?
- Are you being serious?
- Yeah, it's pretty music.
- Wow. Mr. Romance.
- Shut up.
Stop ruining the moment.
- I am not ruining the moment.
- Shut up and enjoy it.
- We're in a hotel dancing.
- Whoo.
- This is real romantical.
- Yeah and it's beautiful.
Look, we're in austin.
- It's the capital.
- Hi.
Thanks for coming back.
- You're welcome.
- Now I can't believe
my son
Gon' be on tv.
- Yeah, your son's gon' get his
butt whooped on tv too.
- Man, you don't know that.
Oh, I got to find something
to wear.
- Wear for what?
- To the game.
- You don't got
to come all the way up
To mcnulty just
to see me lose.
- Well, um...
Selena said she'd drop me off.
Look, I need to see you play.
- I do.
- Okay.
- Look, I won't--
I won't make no scenes
or nothing.
You know, I'll be cleaned up.
- I'm going
to austin tomorrow.
- You're what?
- I'm going to find our daughter
in austin tomorrow.
- Now listen, babe--
- Because I don't care
that she is 17 years old.
She bald-faced lied to us
And she went there
without our permission.
We told her not to go.
We expressly said,
"do not go to austin,"
And she went off
without telling us.
Even though we told her not
to go, she's there.
- You can't go down--find her
in a music festival.
- She's not answered one
single one of my phone calls.
I have no idea where she is.
She has not called us.
She could be--
I have no idea if she's okay.
I am concerned.
I can't think
of another thing right now.
Can't focus on anything,
so I'm just gonna
Go to austin
and I'm going to find her.
- And I support
your decision 100%.
- Thank you, babe.
It's so darn selfish.
- But more importantly--
More importantly,
riggins rigs--
Yeah, granted,
it's not doing so well.
I understand that.
Hence me in the trailer
right now.
That will change.
So give me six months,
a year.
He's got his kid and
all this kind of stuff.
It's gonna get busy.
I'm pitching away,
doing my thing.
Handing out cards.
All this kind of stuff.
It's gonna get super busy.
I'll be under that car
all the time.
That's where you come in,
miss garrity.
We're gonna need someone
to manage it
When it gets, like,
just super busy.
I mean, granted, yeah,
it's a simple life,
But, I mean, that--
it's kind of a great life.
- That's your pitch?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Take that.
That's a hard one
to walk away from.
- So don't.
- Tim--
- I'm serious.
- What do you want?
- You.
- What else do you want?
- Hey, what's wrong?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's going on?
- Why would she do that?
Scare us to death like that?
- I trust julie.
I trust matt.
And I know that she's safe
anywhere, all right?
- I don't know that.
I don't know at all
that she's safe.
She has not returned
one single phone call.
I don't know why
she would do that.
- Because she's 17 years old.
That's why.
- Just breaks my heart.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
The more we make
her try to stay,
The more she's gonna stray.
You know that.
- I know, but I hate it.
I don't want her to go.
But I know
she's gonna go and...
I don't want her to.
- You're not going then?
- To austin?
- Mm-hmm.
- No.
Seems kind of silly,
I guess.
I'm just gonna beat her ass
when she gets home.
- Mm.
- Hello?
- Hey, matt.
How you doing?
- Yeah, no, it's good.
Um, we saw him
yesterday
And we're about to go see
the heartless bastards tonight.
- That sounds like
a lot of fun.
Um, just a--kind of a fyi.
Miss taylor kind of cornered me
at school yesterday
And started drilling me
with all these questions
About where you
and julie might be.
- Wait, what?
- And I kind of panicked
and told her
That y'all were going to
the heartless bastards tonight,
Which, now thinking back,
I might not should have done.
- What?
- Just wanted to give you
the heads-up.
It's probably fine.
- Wait, she doesn't know--
- I'm sure she's not gonna come
to austin or anything.
But I just wanted
to let you know.
So there it is.
- So she doesn't know
that she's in austin with me?
- Oh, great.
Well, I think I'm gonna go
'cause I just
Let another cat out
of the bag.
I guess I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
- Thanks.
- Aren't you ready?
- Um...You lied
to your parents?
- I didn't lie
to my parents, matt.
- Okay, well,
'cause that was landry
And he said that your mom was
interrogating landry
About where you were.
- Yeah, well, I told them
I was gonna be in austin.
I left them a message.
- Oh, you left them a message
that you were in austin.
That's good.
- Look, you're blowing it
out of proportion.
It's--matt, it's rlly--
- No, it is a big deal,
'cause you know what?
I actually care what your
parents think about me.
I really don't want them
to hate me,
Which is what's gonna happen
if they think
That I just ran away
to austin with you.
- I told them where I was
gonna be and I'm sorry!
I did this whole thing
to make you happy, okay?
I bought the music festival
tickets so you could get out
Of dillon, because I know
how much you hate dillon.
- I don't--I don't hate dillon.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
- Look, you hate dillon.
You only stay there
because of me
And maybe for once I don't
want the responsibility
Of you having
to stay in dillon.
- Look, hey.
I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't--
I didn't mean--I didn't mean
to freak out.
So let's just go see this
concert, all right?
- I'm sorry too.
I didn't mean to yell.
- No, that's--it's fine.
It's fine.
- Yeah.
âTª âTª
- Folks, we are just one hour
away from kickoff.
Mcnulty's rolling in
an undefeated, top-ranked team.
Versus the east dillon lions,
A team that has yet
to name a quarterback.
Coach taylor's put this team
together with spit
And scotch tape, and tonight,
this monumental mismatch
Is gonna be captured
on television.
It's a beautiful night
for football, folks.
Vince howard in shotgun.
- Let's go, o!
- Cafferty goes in motion.
There's the snap.
It's a speed sweep,
going left.
Oh! Howard keeps it
going right.
- Got a lane.
This could be something, folks.
Oh, and he trucks
the quarterback.
- First down to the 41.
Roll lions.
- Coach taylor's moving
luke cafferty
Under center for the snap.
It's a little speed draw.
Lanes are up the middle.
Got some room.
Oh, nice run by luke cafferty
The lions, believe it or not,
Got a little something-something
going, folks.
No one saw this coming,
But this could turn out to be
one hell of a football game.
East dillon lions
in the red zone.
This could be big, folks.
Howard at quarterback.
There's the snap.
Howard takes off.
On a little speed draw up
the middle.
Got a little room.
This kid's got something.
Oh, my goodness.
A touchdown, east dillon lions!
Touchdown!
East scores, and that
is the first touchdown
Mcnulty has given up
in four games.
It looks like
the east dillon lions
Have found an identity,
folks.
And quite possibly a quarterback
that is the real deal.
- Yeah!
- Here we go.
Late in the second half.
These lions have battled
these mavericks
All night long,
And they are just seven
points away
From tying this game up--
Something no one,
including yours truly,
Thought was even remotely
possible.
- Good job!
Good job!
- Howard takes the snap.
He rolls left.
Pressure coming.
- Upfield, go!
- This could be big, folks.
Inside the ten-yard line.
First down, lions.
- Get your ass up.
Let's go!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Let's go, let's go.
Howard takes the snap.
- Right there, right there,
right there!
- Under pressure.
Great spin move.
Howard trying to make a play.
He's gonna have to get rid
of the ball!
Oh, and he gets pasted,
in the back field,
The clock winds out,
And the upset is not to be,
folks.
- Get off me, man.
We have seen a team emerge
tonight,
Lead by a young quarterback,
vince howard,
The rising star of the east
dillon lions.
- Hey, let's go.
Bring it in.
Bring it in. Let's go.
- Here we go.
- Come on, fellas.
Let's go.
Hey, listen to me.
Listen, everyone.
Listen up right now.
Every single person
out here--
Every single person out here
respects you fellas.
Every one.
I respect you.
You need to respect yourselves.
Hell of a job.
Take that with you,
carry it,
And we're gonna
build on it.
- âTª I want to stay âTª
âTª out here in the sun âTª
âTª a while âTª
âTª and I saw âTª
âTª I saw the wide old world âTª
- Hey, do you want to leave?
- No, they just started playing.
Let's finish the set.
- No, do you want me
to leave?
Maybe you were right.
I mean, maybe I should have
left already.
Do you even want me to stay?
- Of course I want you
to stay!
I was just--I was saying
stupid things.
I'm sorry!
I love you, okay?
I was being stupid!
Don't think about it,
okay?
- Okay.
- I love you!
- I love you.
- âTª out into âTª
âTª out into âTª
âTª the world âTª
- Morning.
- Good-bye, lyla garrity.
- Good-bye.
- Really cool festival.
Thank you.
- I'm glad you had
a good time.
It was nice just
to get away with you.
- I love you, julie.
- I love you, matty.
I, um--
I better go.
- Yeah.
I'll see you later.
- That better have been
a great concert, babe.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, we have been
worried sick.
- Sorry.
I'm sorry.
- What happened, hon?
Did something happen?
I think he's leaving.
- Okay.
It's okay.
- That's good.
That's better.
- Is it better?
Let me move these
and you watch and see
If those lines come off.
Do you really think
we need a new tv?
Look, this is working
just fine.
- No, I mean, it might be
something to invest in.
- Well--
- that's--
- Ooh, that is--
go back.
Let's watch that channel,
'cause it looks better.
I don't really care.
Okay.
And I guess we could think
about getting a new tv.
- Lorraine,
you'd be shocked.
- Would we want to get
a bigger screen, you think?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- How's lyla?
- Gone.
- Do you have a broken heart?
- I don't know.
- Is she the love of your life?
Maybe there's more
than one soul mate
For everybody, you know?
'cause, like, say I'm born
in texas, right?
And my soul mate's born all
the way over in sri lanka.
That seems randomly unfair.
It only makes sense that there
would be more than one.
You know,
'cause you have your first,
And it's new, and you
feel things that you never
Thought you'd feel
and they break your heart.
Then you cry about it
and you're sad over it...
And then you meet someone else.
And for that time,
they're your new soul mate,
Because they made you feel
things the other one couldn't.
And then they break your heart.
- Becky...
- Yeah?
- Shut up.
Please?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com