The fields are brown,
this town has been divided.
We need to acknowledge the huge part
you played in this redistricting effort.
We just brought this kid in.
Next stop is juvie for him,
and that's a bad path.
- If I need you to be here at 6 a.m.?
- I'll be here.
- How is it to have been Tim Riggins?
- I'm still Tim Riggins.
Yeah, but you know
what I mean, though.
You're all the center of universe
in Texas one year, and the next...
Boom, fall off a cliff.
This is as bad as anything
I've ever seen on a football field.
Game is over.
Dillon has forfeited.
Wake up.
Come on, get up. You can't be here,
this is private property.
Aren't you...
Aren't you Tim Riggins?
Yes, sir.
You need to get yourself together
and get outta here. You can't be here.
Hey, Coach.
Hey, dad.
Morning.
Morning, Gracie Belle.
- We made coffee.
- Did you bring the paper in yet?
- I'll go get it.
- I'll get it.
I'll get the paper...
I'll get my own paper.
Thank you for the coffee.
You're welcome.
Morning.
Hey, hon.
Babe, just go on. Come on now,
just let me just do this.
That's a hell of a combo.
Boy, I can smell State.
State! State! State!
They know
they're supposed to be here.
I know.
I've looked everywhere.
I went to the training room,
I went to the bus stop...
Nobody's here, Coach.
Nowhere in the building.
Hey friend!
Come on, come go with me.
I'm not in the mood.
I don't have time right now.
I got to show you something, Eric.
Please.
Come here.
Do you know what you're looking at?
No, why don't you fill me in?
This is the address
for Luke Cafferty.
Star Running Back.
Dillon Panthers.
Future Super Star, Luke.
This is the address they have.
Where does he really live?
East Dillon...
He's supposed to be yours.
Friday Night Lights 4x02
- After The Fall -
Subtitles: Team Lions
With the participation of:
Benj!, Collioure, DarKsh,
GillesSilb, Jenn, Ju, Nam, Tactactac
Here she is!
They were thinking that we were not
gonna notice that it's an empty field
out there?
Do they think we're stupid?
We wouldn't have known
unless Buddy told us. Come on, Julie!
That's another thing,
don't say anything about that
because he's afraid half the town
will boycott his dealership.
Well, I don't blame him.
I'm a little worried myself.
- Julie, let's go!
- They considered kind of a...
- Mrs Coach kind of a mood.
- You don't have to worry.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I know but these people are all about
doing the wrong thing. They don't care.
And I feel just terrible
for poor Luke Cafferty.
That poor boy...
I'm gonna have to tell him about this.
I feel so sorry for him, that he has
to come to my school and be on my team.
- That's awful.
- Honey, come on now.
- Let's go.
- Ready to go, dad?
- Yes, I'm very ready.
- Are you ready for your big first day?
It should be fun.
New teachers,
news friends, new school...
- Let's go to school half naked.
- Be careful.
It's a high school, mom.
Not a prison yard.
- Bye, I love you.
- I love you too.
Bye, honey.
- What's up?
- You know who did this?
- Do what?
- Put flags on my locker.
I ain't see no one,
I'll tell ya if I'd seen him.
Come on, man.
You know me better than that.
I took the liberty of putting up
in a internship,
with a local artist out here.
His name is Richard Sherman.
He selected you.
He did?
It's quite a honor,
the guy is a genious.
Can you go this afternoon?
Yeah, of course.
But why did you put me up
for internship?
Because you have
whatever important artist needs.
- What's that?
- Pluck.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, I just need to...
If I squeezed by you here...
It's a open...
Oh my God, are you okay?
What the hell, uh?
Look what you did to my bike,
you freaking idiot.
I mean, honestly, you're not even
wearing a helmet or something...
Come on, are you serious?
You know what, junior? I think I might
need to explain something to you.
- I'm listening.
- It took me a lot of months
to save up for that bike, okay?
So it means a lot to me.
Because not everybody gets a car
bought from their dad.
So you're gonna pay me damages.
- That's right.
- For my bike.
- What's your name?
- Landry Clarke.
- Jess Merriweather.
Nice to meet you.
M-E-R-R-I-W-E-A-T-H-E-R.
That's how you spell my last name. Don't
forget that when you make up the check.
What the hell
is so important out here?
Nothing, I'm sorry...
I think I've a wrong adress.
I just can't find this artist...
Who?
Richard Sherman,
I'm gonna take off.
- I'm sorry I bothered you.
- I'm Richard Sherman, dumbass.
I'm Matt Saracen,
I'm your new intern.
I got a bunch of crap in here,
I need you to start moving it.
Come on in, there's shards on the front,
I don't want any crap about it.
- You got shoes on?
- Yes, I wear shoes.
Close the door.
There's the coach.
I'm gonna go ahead and take off.
I'll see you all later.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I don't know what's going on with
my football players, I need your help.
Why did you forfeit the game, Coach?
I'm sorry?
- I said why'd you forfeit the game?
- I heard your question.
You have an answer to that
cause I don't understand.
Let me tell you something. I don't have
to explain my decisions to you, Landry.
I can explain to you
that everyone gave
everything they had out there
and you just quit on us?
Do you know what it feels like?
It's not a good feeling.
So I'm done
and everyone else is done.
Give me some piece!
Gimme something to work with!
There you go, babe!
Come here, son.
Hey, Principal Taylor.
- Did you see that?
- I... that was amazing.
- That was amazing.
- Thank you.
- I need to talk to you.
- Yes, ma'am.
I need you to tell me
where you live.
2268 Oakdale Rd.
- Is that where you live?
- Yes.
2268 Oakdale Rd.
You know that's an empty field
with a mailbox in front of it, right?
You live on Kilroy, don't you?
And you know that Kilroy is zoned
for East Dillon High,
isn't that right?
I've worked so hard for the Panthers
and this team means everything to me.
I mean,
there's no team at East Dillon.
There is a team actually.
They're starting one.
Well, I mean...
Is there anything that we can do?
Can you write...
a letter to the Governor or somehow?
I tell you what. The only thing,
the only thing you could do
is your parents could move.
That's the only thing.
- That's not gonna happen.
- I'm sorry, son.
Go over there, you have
to pack up your stuff.
Starting tomorrow you're going
at East Dillon High.
What?
That's it?
That's it.
I mean...
I will get an A
in every single class.
- I know, you're a good student.
- Every one. I promise you that.
I will...
I will do anything, I swear to you,
I will do anything...
I'm... begging you.
Sorry, son.
I hate that it has
to be this way, too.
No, I'm okay, I'm okay...
Thank you.
- You gonna be alright?
- I'm fine. Thank you very much.
Go on, now.
Principal Taylor! Hey!
I'm real sorry for lying to you.
For the whole time
and for lying to you right now
to your face. I'm real sorry, okay?
I appreciate that, Luke.
I do appreciate that.
- It'll be alright, son.
- No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Thank you.
I'll be right there, coach!
Why hasn't the part
for Mrs. Carlson's Taurus come in yet?
I don't know.
The part was ordered ten days ago.
Did you order from Tahiti?
Finish this transmission, man.
Finish it today. You were
working on it all day yesterday.
Just throwing it out there...
It's been well over two weeks,
- you think I'll get paid or?
- I'm waiting on money to come in.
When?
Seriously, could you back off
for two seconds?
Do you have any clue
what I've got on my plate right now?
Seriously, man.
I'm trying to run a garage,
I gotta a pregnant wife,
and I haven't slept for two weeks
because Mindy's reading some stupid book
about what's supposed to happen
every 2 seconds of your pregnant life
and now every time she farts,
she's thinking her water's breaking.
Or, or that's she's going
into contractions. So back off!
Billy, could you pass me
that violin please?
Would you shut up?!
- You're hogging it!
- Shut up!
No, that wasn't
directed towards you, ma'am.
Where are you?
We'll send a truck out
as soon as we can.
When you're done with it,
I need the violin.
Get your ass up, okay?
Get your ass up, we got a tow.
Principal Taylor.
Hey, y'all.
What's it gonna take?
What conversation we're having here?
What is all about?
I think you know.
- Are we talking about Luke?
- Yeah, we're talking about Luke.
So what's it gonna take?
New books for the library,
new instruments for the orchestra, what?
Are you all coming to me
in the school parking lot
and offering me a bribe?
You need to be reasonable
about this, Tami.
It's gonna hurt this kid.
We can't let that happen to him
or to our team.
- Or to the school.
- Or to you.
I mean, what's gonna happen to you
if this goes down?
You're gonna get lynched.
That is so sweet.
You are so sweet to think about me.
I appreciate that so much.
I can take care of myself, thank you.
Think of this: that first win'll have
to be forfeited because of this.
If that happens
we might not make it back from that.
That means we might not make it
to state this year.
- Now do you want that?
- That boy was enrolled here illegally.
Ironically, he just happens
to be going to a school
where your husband
is the football coach.
Would you do me a favor?
Would you go home
and ask your husband one thing.
Ask him who put up that mailbox.
Because the Dillon Panthers
have been using that mailbox
long before I got here.
And if I want to do
a little digging around...
things could come up.
I think games could be forfeited.
I think rings...
could be lost.
You gotta be kidding me.
Hey, Tim Riggins
who used to be a Panther.
Good morning.
Tell me you need a tow.
Yeah, no,
but I do need a ride to school.
Which would be awesome
because my mom's not here,
I don't know what she's doing,
she's MIA for some reason
and I had to find my dog this morning
cuz little Squirt
got out again and I missed the bus
and my hair was doing this weird
flip thing that I wasn't
really too sure about
and it was a really rough morning
altogether so...
Let's get on the road!
Let's get going. I'm gonna be late.
Don't ever do this again.
I mean, all I did all day
was carrying big, rusty, dirty
pieces of metal in a junk yard.
It sucked.
- I still can't believe you were naked.
- No, I wasn't naked. He was naked.
Whatever.
He never even asked me about my art.
Why does he think I'm there?
He thinks I like manual labor?
Maybe he thinks, you know,
you're not a great artist
cuz you go to community college
No offense.
I didn't mean it to sound...
It's fine.
I'm just saying that...
you need to get him excited.
You need to show him who you are
and your art
and just take the bull by the horns.
You know I have been told
that I have pluck.
Really?
I don't know what that means.
I'm Coach Taylor
from over at the high school.
Are you Vince's mother by chance?
Yeah, why?
Well, I just wanted to...
talk with him, that's all.
I just came by to talk him.
He missed practice for few days.
That's his business.
There ain't no laws
about missing no practice.
Ma'am...
I'm just trying to help your son.
You got twenty bucks?
Please?
Lincoln and Victory.
Almost every night.
Hey, do you know
how to get to Lubbock?
You gotta take 61 up to 23.
Dillon East, right?
You're the coach at Dillon East.
You've lost your inner pirate.
* have you ever heard
"swing your sword"?
You're supposed
to swing your sword like this.
You're swinging yours like this.
I mean, you gotta find
your inner pirate.
A lot of times,
things just happen for a reason.
We don't know
why God wants it that way,
but you can't make the best out of it
until you get back your inner pirate.
You might be the luckiest man alive
and not even know it.
Hey, babe.
- Smells good.
- Babe?
What?
Did you know that that mailbox
was out there by that empty field?
Did you know that?
- What are you talking about?
- Joe McCoy told me today
that that mailbox has been out there
since you were in the Panthers.
Did you know?
Listen.
I don't follow...
what the boosters and parents do.
That's not my job.
There's a lot of different ways
that people try to get kids on the team.
What does that mean?
That means you sure were paying
a lot of attention
the last 2 days when you were trying
to get Luke Cafferty on your team.
And you know, now I'm in
a really bad position because Joe McCoy
is about to go out and do
all kinds of research and digging
into things like State Titles...
Don't talk to me like that.
I'm talking about your State Title.
And not just you but your team.
Well, you know what, honey?
I may not even have a team.
- Of course you have.
- No, I might not.
I'm surprised your friend Joe
didn't inform you that my team
hasn't been showing up for practice
since the forfeit.
- I didn't know. Sorry to hear that.
- I'm glad you're sorry. I'm, too.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I tried to get Landry to get together
bring the team out there
and you know what he did?
In the middle of the cafeteria,
he looks at me and basically says,
"Hey, Coach, go to Hell."
Babe, I'm sorry to hear that,
but you still...
- shouldn't have lied to me.
- I didn't.
I wish you had told me...
You should have told me you knew that.
Knew what?
I don't know who put the mailbox!
You saying I put the mailbox there?
- Anyone else say I did? Cuz I didn't!
- Don't raise your voice.
I'm not raising my voice! I don't want
to come home and be accused!
- Then don't lie to me next time!
- I didn't lie to you!
- Where are you going?
- Get some milk.
What the hell, man?
Say, V. Vince!
Hey, you came to the wrong gym.
Vince, let me talk to you.
- Can't you see we're hooping?
- Yeah, I can see.
I can see, I understand.
He's not in school, is he?
You're making a mistake, man.
Officer Shaw keeps calling.
I can't keep him away forever, man.
I've been watching
those game tapes, man.
You're running the 40 in under 5
a full pass. You got all the moves, man.
You've got a lot of talent,
I'm telling you. Don't throw it away.
You're gonna talk to me?
You gonna throw it away?
You gonna throw that away?
Last chance.
I'm not gonna waste my time anymore.
Your choice, Big Man.
There's some Chevy parts
in the back,
I want you to move them here
because I gotta start cutting them.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Can you get me the sausage
from out back?
- Alright. You want the spicy kind?
- Yeah, that'll do. Here you go.
Maam. Extra BBQ sauce.
There you go.
Enjoy.
There your pickles, ma'am.
I got it...
- You wanted the spicy kind, right?
- Yeah.
- I could... You want me to...
- No, no. You're good.
- There you go.
- What are you doing?
What's your problem?
I don't have a problem.
I was just...
She looked busy, I just thought I'd help
her out. We go to school together.
This is...
Landry.
My dad...
- Landry?
- Yeah.
Here, Landry.
Take that out, man.
Thanks for the help.
Yeah. Very nice kitchen, cool.
Landry?
I'll get back... Yeah.
What do you want?
Here's what we're gonna do.
- Special practice Saturday night.
- Saturday?
If it doesn't work out,
we're gonna start over.
What exactly does that mean,
start over?
I don't know, Stan.
I don't know what start over means.
Saturday night.
Tim, how're you doin'?
I heard you were back.
How come you're not back at college?
I...
You what?
I'm working full-time with my brother,
making some money.
You... look different.
- It's the color.
- Yeah, it's pretty red.
I heard about the forfeit.
And...
it's a shaky start, so...
I mean, I'd love to be a part of it
if I could help in any way.
- You're offering your help to me?
- Yes, sir.
Come with me.
Come on.
Do we have the latest injury report
for Rural Rock?
Is that middle linebacker of theirs
still messed up? Cuz if he is,
boy, it's gonna be party time...
- He's out?
- Left knee...
Yeah?
Excellent, thank you.
And Buddy, are we looking...
- to talk to that...
- Sorry.
I hate to interrupt.
How are you? Good to see you, Sam.
Don't mean to interrupt, I just...
Can I have a quick word with you, Joe?
Talk amongst yourselves.
I wanted to make sure that we didn't
have any misunderstanding the other day
when we had that conversation
in the parking lot.
You know, with the golf cart
and all of that stuff...
And I just wanted to make sure
I was clear
that my decision
has been made and is made
and that Luke Cafferty
is going to East Dillon High.
Are you clear about what I told you?
Oh, yeah, I think I heard you.
You mean about
doing an investigation
and retroactively taking away Panther
State titles? That's the thing you said?
Because I just want
to make sure that you also checked
with all these gentlemen about that,
because as you said...
you know, that's gonna mean
rings being taken away
and things like that, and I can betcha
there are a lot of rings in this group.
Family and what not.
So, you do what you have to do.
I know you're going to,
but I wanted to make sure I've been
clear with you where I stand on it.
So, I'll let you all get back to it.
Thank you so much y'all!
Enjoy.
Hey, I cut my hand
and I don't have a tetnus shot,
so I'm gonna have to go get one.
- That was brilliant.
- Thank you, that was brilliant.
- Thanks for everything, see you later.
- What the hell is your problem?
I don't know what your deal is.
You're rude, nasty and that's fine,
that's your thing, you're an artist.
And I'll carry all your crap,
but I'm here and doing all this
is 'cause I wanna
be an artist, alright?
So, the least you could do
is say something about it.
- You want me to say something?
- I would like you to say something.
Alright, then I'll say something.
That's very helpful.
Yeah, just wrinkle them up.
Are you...
Alright, this part here
doesn't make me wanna puke.
Try to work from this place.
Okay.
You're not my father.
I support my family.
She had no business
taking that from you.
You shouldn't have gave it to her.
Sit down.
Sit down...
I'm sorry.
Don't quit on me.
Don't quit on yourself.
I'm gonna ask you to do me a favor.
This team is broken all to hell.
I could use somebody to help me
put those pieces back together again.
I don't know where I'm going...
but I'll get another job.
This job doesn't work out for you,
we both know where you're going.
Bring 'em to me.
Talk to 'em and bring 'em to me.
Talk to 'em for me.
Talk to 'em and bring 'em to me
tomorrow night.
Special practice,
ten o'clock, out here...
At the field.
Just us, just the Lions.
Hey, talk to 'em.
We are...
Panthers!
Welcome, Panthers!
We have a big game coming up,
with West Cambria.
I will wait.
We want Luke!
I'm Luke Cafferty.
I'm here for special practice,
Coach Taylor called.
- Nice to see you.
- Welcome
- to East Dillon, son.
- Thank you.
Luke, how are you doing?
Good to see you.
- Stan Traub.
- How are you?
- Great admirer.
- Nice to meet you. Thanks.
Where's the team?
How are you doing, fellas?
- Coach.
- How are you doing, Tinker?
Good evening, gentlemen.
Good to see you.
Listen...
Last week, we got our asses beat
doing our best,
there is no shame in that, gentlemen.
But I'll tell you what,
I've got shame.
I've got shame
and I apologize to you.
I apologize
for not giving you the chance
to finish your fight.
I wanna finish that fight with you.
And I'm asking you,
right here, right now,
to allow me to help you
finish that fight.
See this, gentlemen?
This right here, this is the past.
Who wants to finish this fight?
Who'll finish this fight with me?
I will, sir.
Glad to have you on board, Tinker.
Let's finish it.
Let's finish it!
Let's do this, boys!
Hey, sailor.
Looks like
you haven't slept in a week.
Feels that way.
Kinda looking for a place
if you know any.
It shouldn't be so hard.
It is when you don't have
first and last.
I do have this trailer...
in my backyard.
I'll charge you a $100 a month.
You can stay there
until you find a place.
It's very sweet.
Don't get me wrong,
that was unbelievable,
but I'm not that into you.
More importantly, you're not into me,
so who really needs to go there, right?
I'm not gonna come
banging on your door
in the middle of the night,
you know what I mean?
But I could use the cash.
When?
Start right now.
- Let me get you the keys.
- Like tonight?
Remember where I live?
I'm gonna give my daughter a call.
She's not gonna know you from Adam.
I don't want you to scare her.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Drinking wine.
How are you?
How did everything go today?
I got booed at the pep rally.
What do you mean booed?
I mean booed.
But I did get one little bit
of satisfaction.
Just being able to stand up
to those good old boys,
Joe McCoy and his crew.
So I got that going for me.
And wine.
How was your day?
They showed up.
They did?
It's a start.
That's great.
I'm sorry I lied.
I know.