It's up for discussion
at the board meeting.
I love my job, I'm good at it,
and I'd like to keep it.
I love you,
I just think we should break up.
You're the only one who's never left me.
I'm not gonna leave you.
I'm gonna stay here. For good.
You're gonna go to college
and get a degree.
Do you hear me?
They offered the job to Wade Aikmen.
The board would like to offer you
the position of head coach
at East Dillon High.
I'm Sammy Meade,
and folks, let me tell you,
the sky is dry, the fields are brown,
the drought is long
and it has happened:
this town has been divided.
Thanks, babe.
Good luck.
I love you.
- Wade, listen to me!
- Buddy, I know.
¿Qué estás haciendo aquí, tú?
Sorry...
- Coach Taylor.
- ¿Quién?
Coach Taylor, football team.
Coach Taylor.
- Here, no hay football team.
- The new coach for the football team.
- New football team?
- That's right.
Don't kick my door, por favor.
You know there's a raccoon in here?
On the ground! On your stomach!
On your stomach! Right now!
Let's go! Buddy, it's over.
On the ground!
Next, let's go, come on!
Name?
- Calvin.
- Take the chain off.
Take the chain off.
Do you see this man?
It's 18 G's right here, dawg.
Take the chain off
and you're gonna call me Coach Taylor.
Landry, hey, what's up?
Kenny...
Olsen, from JV.
- What position you want to play?
- Quarterback.
- What are you going out for?
- Let's go, next.
- I'm...
- I'm going out for quarterback.
- What position you wanna play?
- You know, quarterback.
- Quarterback.
We found our quarterback, gentlemen!
Step off, next!
All the way up!
All the way down!
Listen up!
Called you out here today
to see what we got.
And after 18 minutes,
I think I've seen enough.
I want you all to go home tonight
and think long and hard...
on how much you want this,
on whether you want this.
If you don't, that's fine,
there's no shame in that.
I don't want you wasting my time
and I don't wanna waste yours either.
If you do want it,
then be out here tomorrow morning
at 6 a.m, we'll get after it.
But get your rest tonight, 'cause
I promise you you're gonna need that.
Hey, Coach.
Good, good.
Ken Shaw. 12th precinct.
Your brother used
to play ball for me?
- Sure did. Mike Shaw.
- That's right, Mike.
Linebacker. How's he doing?
He's doing pretty good,
speaks very highly of you.
- He ended up playing?
- He played for a couple of years,
but he got hurt,
so he had to step out.
- Tell him I said hello.
- I will.
What d'you got here?
You've heard
of Cops 'N' Jocks, right?
- Second chance.
- Yeah, second chance program.
Well, we just brought this kid
in this morning.
You know, he's a decent kid,
but he's got a record now.
Next stop is juvie for him
and that's a bad path.
- What kind of record?
- Minor stuff, nothing major.
I'm talking about
breaking and entering...
Did he kill anyone?
Not animals?
Like I said, these are
mostly non-violent offenses.
- What do you mean, mostly?
- You can help him out.
You wanna meet him?
Since you brought him,
- I guess I should.
- I hope so, yeah.
How you doing, son?
Coach Taylor.
- Vince.
- Vince?
You've ever played football?
Yeah, all the time.
Madden.
How's that?
- Madden.
- Madden?
- It's a video game, Coach, Madden.
Madden football.
You ever play any real football?
- Threw the ball around with my friends.
- Do you like to run?
He can run, Coach.
The boy is fast, real fast.
- You like to hit?
- Hit what?
People.
I like that.
But what would you say if I needed you
to be here tomorrow at 6 a.m. sharp?
6 a.m. sharp means 5:45.
I'll be here.
Friday Night Lights 4x01
- East Of Dillon -
Subtitles: Team Lions
With the participation of:
Benj!, Collioure, DarKsh, Gates44
GillesSilb, Jenn, Ju, Nam, Tactactac
Buddy, you know those people.
You can get them to refile their papers.
We can handle that,
that's not a big deal.
- We can fix that...
- Gentlemen, Tami Taylor!
Not necessary, thank you.
Thank you very much.
We need to acknowledge the huge part
you played in this redistricting effort.
Because of it, our athletic program
is already seeing the positive effects.
Good, good. I hope y'all get
everything you deserve this year.
Thank you for stepping up
and doing the right thing.
Good, good.
Are we gonna talk about football?
Were your ears burning,
'cause we were just talking about you?
Yeah, we were.
Talking about Friday's festivities.
We would love for you
to do the coin toss this Friday.
The coin toss?
Ain't that Mayor Roddell's...
I'll handle Lucy. I'll handle her.
We want you.
We think it is very important
that all of us show
that we are all in this together.
So, it would be an honor
and it would mean a lot to us
and we're thinking that maybe
you should call "heads".
We're just kidding.
You call whatever you wanna call!
You can call whatever you want
in the coin toss.
I'm honored. Thank you.
- Make sure you think about it.
- Okay, I'm thinking about it.
"... your thoughts are my own thoughts.
My daughter should be yours,
"and you my son-in-law,"
so he's entreating there,
"if you remained."
That's the difference of going home.
Every hero has a journey.
Early literature is obsessed
with the journey.
Strain the hero.
Odysseus's journey is like a process
to help him appreciate his earlier life,
his love, Penelope, right...
the home he left.
So why don't we pick up then
where we left off yesterday?
Come on now!
Look alive, look alive!
That's awful!
Get 'em in a huddle, right now.
You gotta clip your hips, right.
Push' em up, right?
Put your hands down on your knees.
Heads up, alright?
This is called a huddle.
You gotta understand
what a huddle is.
This is your quarterback here.
He's gonna tell you what to do.
Toss us the rock, man, for real.
It's boring as hell, man.
You can have the ball
when you can actually run a play.
Alright, now knock it off.
It's called a huddle.
It's called a rock
and it looks like I got it now.
- You think that's funny?
- I'm just joking man.
My bad.
Man, I was just joking.
Somebody get somebody!
I'm sorry.
Coach, you all right?
- I'm done. I'm done.
- What's wrong?
I'm done! I'm done!
Where you going?
Coach, where you going?
So...
is your focus in metal works
or electronics?
My focus is in art.
What kind of art
are you interested in?
I don't know.
The kind that I do, I guess.
Well, that's the thing.
I don't know I would call this art.
What would you call it?
I would call it drawing,
without a point of view.
It's not that I don't like it.
- But it's not saying anything.
- They thought the opposite
at the Art Institute in Chicago
when they accepted me.
And that's a much better art school
than Dillon Tech.
Then why are you here
in Dillon Tech?
Kiddo, so do you have a plan...
- Something?
- What do you mean?
For life.
For life?
- To do...
- Riggins Riggs.
That's your plan?
Awesome.
So, where are you gonna stay?
- What do you mean?
- Like live.
- Billy, tater me.
- In Dillon?
- I'm gonna stay right here.
- Here?
Here.
That's great.
Baby, can I...
talk to you, for a second?
Over here.
Thanks.
- So good.
- Yeah, it's really good.
How are you?
Good to see you.
How you doing?
How's you dad?
Gentlemen, how you doing?
How's it going?
Same old time, you?
Skeletons.
I hear Wade's got a golf cart
out there, is that the case?
The man loves his ride, he does.
We move the ball 15 yards down field,
he drives to the next hole.
Why don't you all come on over?
Why dontcha all come over?
That'd be nice.
I don't think
I could explain it to Susan.
Job security and all that stuff.
Not young enough to take pay cut.
All those chances, you know.
- All right.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
- Principal Taylor.
- Hey, everybody.
Nice to see y'all.
Thanks for coming out.
And I just...
I'm thrilled to welcome everybody
to another great year
in Dillon High.
And, before I get going
with the events tonight...
- I wanna thank you...
- I have a question.
- We're gonna have a Q&A at the end.
- Why is my child being forced?
- Nobody is being forced...
- That's exactly what's happened!
Why you making my brother
go to a different school?
First, I'd like to clarify,
we're gonna have a Q&A...
My parents went to this school
before you ever heard
of Dillon High.
Yeah, exactly.
I wanna know why our daughter
is being sent out
to that hellhole
- with that element.
- First of all,
let's not refer to East Dillon
in this way, okay?
I do not tolerate...
Would you say
the two schools are equal?
- Yes, I would.
- You'd send your child there?
I would. She has been zoned
for West Dillon and she's going there.
- Her dad works there...
- I do look at the 2 schools as equal.
You should send her there.
This is impossible to get anything
accomplished this way, y'all.
Hey, how you doin' today?
- Haven't seen one in a while.
- Something wrong with it,
and gotta get it repaired
if that's alright.
I won't do it.
- What?
- Sir, it's garbage.
It's garbage now
and it was back in 1992.
It wasn't purchased here.
If you think I'm gonna let
the finest football coach
in the state of Texas
walk out that door with a box
of garbage, you do not know me.
- You got a manager around here?
- Stan Traub.
I'm a great admirer of Coach Taylor.
Well... Thank you, Stan.
Traub... How I know that name?
Nobeck County.
Pop Warner Coach of the Year 2005.
Second place finisher
in 2006, 7 and 8.
I also faxed 5 or 6 of my resumes
to you at East Dillon.
I left you messages
on the voicemail.
Oh yeah, that's it.
- How you'll handle South King?
- How's that?
They run that spread,
but that QB's gonna freeze up on you
- if you blitz...
- You had a repair guy?
- I can help you.
- I need to get this...
I got you covered.
I'm the real deal. I'm good,
I'm cheap. I'm volunteer cheap.
You will not regret this.
I think it'll be fun.
- It's a Panther party.
- It's not a Panther party.
Beth is a cheerleader,
Friday is the first game.
We can acquiesce to the fact
that it's a Panther party.
Devin and Landry
are going to be there.
It's like a kick-back.
Fine. You know what,
let's stay in,
and watch
the Deadliest Catch marathon.
- We can get pizza after your shift.
- Fine, we'll go.
I have to deliver a pizza right now.
Here are your pizzas.
So, do you make your girlfriend
deliver pizza with you all the time?
$18.75.
It sucks you didn't go to Chicago
like you were supposed to.
I was gonna go
after Julie this year.
I'm just kidding.
Weren't these supposed
to have cinnamon sticks?
Thanks for the tip.
Let's go! Hustle up!
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What hole are you going through?
Was it 24-power?
- 4 hole.
- The 4 hole?
- Then go through the 4 hole!
- The 4 hole!
Come on, now.
What are you doing now?
Wait a sec!
- What are you doing? You're killing me.
- I'm moving closer!
- You're moving closer...
- So I can get to the 4 hole!
Don't talk back to me!
Those fellas in stripped uniforms,
they'll throw flags,
how many yards it'll be?
- 5.
- Right, 5 yards.
Here's what you're wanna do,
right over here.
This is the 4 hole,
you'll go through the 4 hole
and once you get through there
you're keep going downhill.
- Yes, sir.
- Come on, let's go!
Goddamn, I didn't expect that.
I cannot believe what I witnessed.
That's genius, Coach.
This is exactly why I am here,
I'm serious.
- I got goose-bumps.
- That's good.
Hey, Vince.
That was damn nice.
Damn nice.
What do we got next? Let's go!
- Ignore it.
- So pretty rough over at East Dillon?
It's rough, to say the least.
I'm constantly, like, ready.
I got a piece on me at all times.
Julie Taylor!
- How are you?
- Hey, J.D.
So where's pizza man?
He's gonna meet me later.
My mom said she'd die
before she'd send me there.
Like, she would literally
end her life?
Hunger strike probably.
Hey, you know Luke?
You come watch me
make history on Friday night?
Actually, I'm gonna go
see the Lions.
I have news for you.
Your dad's coaching a team
that's not gonna have one "W".
But...
I'm liking your chances.
He's been kicking a few back.
You know what, your dad could still
be coaching for Dillon.
My dad gave your dad a shot.
Your dad's an ass.
Okay, so now
I gotta throw you in the pool.
- Stop it! Stop it!
- Hey, J.D.
- What? Hey!
- Gonna throw you in the pool.
Get the hell off her!
What are you doing? Get off her!
Don't put your hands
- on my girlfriend, okay?
- What's your problem?
Shut the hell up!
- What, Landry?
- Get off him!
Coach shouldn't have
taken me out of the game!
He just felt sorry for you.
- Just shut up!
- You suck!
I'm really glad
this wasn't a Panther party.
It's my Dillon now!
Billy, gotta be honest with you.
This is kind of gross.
I mean, whatever just happened
to pink or blue?
Boy or girl?
Mindy doesn't wanna know,
so we gotta use neutral tones.
- Which is puke in this case?
- It's mustard, jackass.
If I threw up on this wall
you wouldn't know it, this color's puke.
It's mustard.
- Agree to disagree.
- Seriously, do you have a problem?
- Whatever.
- Whatever?
- Billy, watch yourself.
- Shut your mouth.
- Watch yourself.
- Or what? What are you gonna do?
Billy, what the hell?
You come into my house
and act like this?
Get off me!
What the hell was that?
I made a joke.
It's not a freaking joke!
You're throwing away your life!
I busted my ass for 8 years
to try and put you into college
and you can't even make a month.
You and Lyla...
wanted me to go to college,
I never said once...
- I wanna go to college.
- What you gonna do?
I don't know
what you're thinking sometimes.
That you're gonna waltz back in here
and everything's gonna be okay?
I got a wife, Tim.
I'm about to be a dad.
There's no room for you here.
Guess you're right.
You know what, Billy?
All I want to do is come home.
I don't like
that we have to do this.
Nine students here
have been notified their transfer
and are refusing to change schools.
What choice do we have?
Ms. Cody?
I'm sorry to interrupt...
y'all.
Devin, honey,
- I'm gonna need you to come with me.
- Should I bring all my stuff?
That'd be good.
Thank you.
You just have to pull the slot machine
and elbow the midget in the face.
You understand though,
I'm always gonna be a Panther
- in my heart.
- Who cares?
They're a bunch of idiots this year.
But a bunch
of talented, fast idiots.
We're just a bunch of sucky idiots.
Alright, so in the Panthers,
you're a scrub right?
On the Lions, you might play.
You might even start!
So you're trying to encourage me
by saying that the Lions
are bad enough
that someone as bad as me might
actually see some playing time?
Yeah, basically.
Yeah, grandma.
Why aren't you throwing the ball?
You know you got a game Friday night.
Coach Taylor
is gonna expect you to be ready.
Remember,
I'm not on the team anymore.
Coach isn't either...
Yeah, that'll be the day,
I adore you.
Coach Taylor not a Panther...
Stop throwing the ball,
you look like a girl.
- I'm gonna throw one more.
- No, you look like a girl!
- You're just a funny looking creature.
- It's good seeing you.
She seems to be doing well.
You think it's a bad sign
Julie ain't call me back?
Probably not a good sign.
You did look like a jackass
at the party the other night.
J.D. is a chump!
He's pretentious, he's...
Aren't you supposed
to rise above that?
to turn the other cheek?
In your typical
Matt Saracen kind of way.
Take the high road.
Right. Take the high road.
What Matt always does.
Get behind me Satan...
Dog?
Brother.
Bottoms up.
What's your name?
Olan, you need
to tighten up your splits.
We're gonna run the ball,
play defense.
Defense!
You need to figure out...
why it is you're out here.
This dude can talk, man.
Like that dude from the infomercial.
You're a funny looking dude, man.
Kinda look like Opie.
You understand?
Maybe if I shine you up...
Do you need a toy or something
to keep your attention?
Will you please
just shut up and listen to him?
Cowards!
Cowards, that's what you all look like.
A bunch of cowards.
You all look like
a bunch of dumb asses out there.
You don't fight on my field!
Y'all wanna fight?
Go ahead and fight, but not on my field
and not in my colors.
You got me?
- Is that understood?
- Yes, sir.
You don't fight in my house!
Let me tell you something else,
there's no talking back on the field.
There's no wearing earrings.
There's no jewelry.
There's no damn necklaces out there!
There's no talking to each other.
There's you shutting up
and there's me talking!
You two.
You two are gonna make it right,
right now!
Make it right, right now.
I apologize.
- Screw you, Rudy.
- Get your stuff and get out of here!
You get your stuff
and get out of here right now!
Get it right now
and get out of my house!
Get the hell out of my house!
Go, go!
Pack it up and get out!
If anyone else in here
doesn't wanna be here, get out now!
Get the hell out of my house
if you don't wanna be here!
Get out now!
You don't wanna be here, then leave!
Anybody else?
No, sir.
We're good?
I wanna play, Coach.
I wanna play.
Aren't you Tim Riggins?
Panthers Tim Riggins?
I know you hear me talking.
I wonder if my mom
knows she slept with you?
Well, she knows it, but...
maybe it was dark,
she didn't realize it was Tim Riggins.
So, is she alive back there?
She's alive.
Is she gonna be
in any condition to drive anytime soon?
That's what I thought.
Look, whatever you did to her,
way to go #33,
but I need a ride to school.
OK, try it again.
- Your truck always break down?
- Sometimes.
Why don't you get a new truck?
So did you hear me singing
this morning?
Sounded good, huh?
Kinda makes you wanna stand up
and put your hand over your heart.
- Like Faith Hill.
- For real?
I love her!
- I could sing for you if you wanted to.
- Try it again.
What's it like being the guy
who used to be Tim Riggins?
I'm still Tim Riggins.
But, you know what I mean, though.
You're all center of the universe
in Texas one year and the next,
- fall off a cliff.
- I haven't really thought about it.
What do you do with yourself now?
How far is your school from here?
- Not far, why?
- You gonna need to walk.
Guys don't usually do
repeat performances with my mom,
so guess I won't be seeing you.
Good luck, Tim Riggins.
Hope you find
what you're looking for.
There's only eighteen here.
Guess more of them decided
to take up on your offer to leave.
That was a risky move.
That might not have paid off.
I wish you'd learn
to filter your thoughts better.
That'd be helpful.
Filter my thoughts.
Malcolm left, too?
Malcolm left, too.
Malcolm left too.
Here's what we'll do.
We're gonna line up in the power Iowa
and perfect the 5 and the 6.
Perfect 5 and 6.
We're gonna power the ball downfield
and keep the ball away from South King.
You need to stop doing that.
You need to stop repeating
everything I say!
It's freaking me out.
You know we got no chance
to win this game.
What are you doing here?
- I came to coach them up.
- Not with that hat on, you know.
You got another one?
The last one I got.
We're outta money.
It's alright.
Folks, it is here.
D-Day.
Not one, but two football games
in our little town.
Will redistricting destroy
Dillon football as we know it?
Smells funny in there...
OK, you look nice.
We need some more cream.
I'll try to get it this weekend.
Can you see that hook back there?
Can you get it for me, thank you.
I can't believe I'll miss your game.
The first game of our relationship.
- A good one to miss.
- I'm sad about it.
- You flip the coin, critical role.
- Are you sad, stressed out?
- Don't be brave.
- Nothing to be stressed out.
There you go, I gotcha.
Tell you what I'm gonna do,
I'll flip my coin.
And then I'm gonna sneak out,
and come over to East Dillon.
- And gonna watch y'all get your "W".
- Flip the coin!
- Gross, gross, gross...
- Hi, honey!
Are you ready for school?
I think I'm gonna go
to East Dillon this year.
What?
Well, I mean...
Devin goes there, Landry goes there,
all my other friends have graduated.
So I think
that it's a really good move for me.
You keep saying how East Dillon
is just as good as West Dillon.
And I just think
it would be beneficial to our family
if I went to East Dillon.
Alright.
Good. It's decided.
Say something.
I am on the battlefield
For my Lord.
I'm on the battlefield
For my Lord,
And I promise Him that I...
I will serve Him 'til I die.
I'm on the battlefield...
For my Lord.
Here we go. Take a knee!
How we doing on time?
Good? Alright.
Everybody got what they need?
Everybody squared the way
with equipment?
Listen up, now.
A few of you have been here before.
A few of you have not.
One thing we've all got to do tonight,
is we've got to focus.
The game plan.
The fundamentals.
Moving the sticks,
that's what we're gonna do.
And listen, fellas.
There's a joy in this game,
is there not?
There's a passion to this game
as a reason why we're all out here.
Other than the fact
that the pride that it gives us
and the respect that it demands,
we love to play the game,
so let's go out there
and let's have fun tonight.
Do you understand me?
Because tomorrow...
if you give a 100% of yourself tonight,
people will look at you differently.
People are gonna
think of you differently.
And I promise you...
You're gonna look and think
differently about yourselves.
Clear eyes, full hearts...
Can't lose.
Can't lose!
Let's hear it, gentlemen.
Clear eyes, full hearts...
- Can't lose!
- Let's go play some football.
Let's go!
Opening night here
in Panther Stadium.
And I tell you,
this crowd is pumped up!
O say, does that star-spangled
banner yet wave
O'er the land of the free
and the home
of the brave.
You've got four quarters to play
your hearts out. You understand that?
- Yes, sir!
- Go for it!
Listen up, we win the toss,
we wanna go D, okay?
That means we're kicking off,
we wanna go D.
Defense, we're kicking off!
- Let's go, boys!
- Tami, we like heads!
- How you doing? Tami Taylor.
- Good evening.
- Shake your hands, please.
- Well done.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome.
Principal Taylor is honorary captain,
she's gonna call the toss.
We have heads, we have tails.
What are you gonna call?
- Tails.
- The call is tails.
Tails it is.
- Choice?
- We will take the ball. Offense.
What did she say?
- No, we wanted defense.
- Please step around right here.
What did she say?
Offense? Offense?
Y'all have a great game, now.
Change of plans!
Listen up!
And here we go, folks.
Oh, it's a long, high,
beautiful kick.
And East Dillon football is back.
It's Vince Howard to the goal line.
He finds a lane to the outside.
Run it, baby!
Look at this kid go, he is fast.
Brutal hit!
Vince Howard is down.
Oh, my!
- I can't believe he's getting up.
- 24-power!
Keep you focus, alright?
Get him out there.
Keep focus, gentlemen.
Let's go!
24-power, on one.
Ready?
This is it, folks.
Olsen bringing the Lions to the line.
Set!
There's the snap. Oh, my!
I think that went right through.
- What are you doing?
- Fumble!
The first play from scrimmage,
we are not off to a pretty start here.
Come on, now!
Olsen opens left.
Quick toss to Howard.
Trying to get to the outside,
he's got nowhere to go.
Don't give me that!
Vince Howard gets drilled
to the backfield.
He got decimated
on that play, folks.
Shut up!
Barracuda right trips.
What? That's not the play.
- Oklahoma right trip.
- Oklahoma right! Ready?
Olsen back to pass.
Pressure coming!
- Olsen goes down hard.
- What is that?
- Why is that?
- Come on, open your eye!
South King on the speed's way,
he's got the outside.
Fantastic blocking.
He could go, folks.
Here we go!
Touchdown, South King.
Someone to get him off the field?
Get him off the field!
Late in second quarter,
South King back to pass.
He's got a man. Reservation for six.
Another South King touchdown.
Alright. Come on, guys.
28-bounce.
28-bound!
- Can't even feel my arms, man.
- We need you!
28-bounce, on one. Ready?
Olsen back to pass.
They need something here.
Across the middle.
Oh, it's picked up by South King!
He's got a lane to the outside.
Howard's got an angle.
And Vince Howard is cracked
at the 40, and another
South King touchdown.
This is getting
flat out ugly, folks.
Coach Taylor is known for his
remarkable half-time adjustments,
but I don't know if there is
an adjustment to this.
This is as bad as anything
I have ever seen on a football field.
Can you flex it for me?
We'll unwrap it.
Easy, just relax.
I can't stop it from twitching.
He didn't break it, but he's got
a hell of a high ankle sprain.
Tell him.
Tell him I'll still go.
Alright, we'll tape it and see.
- I can play.
- I hear you.
- What you got? Let me see.
- Stitches.
He didn't say anything.
How you doing?
I'm solid.
- You alright?
- Yes, sir.
- What you got?
- Nothing, just...
- Does this hurt?
- I think it's alright.
Hey, Coach,
you got a few more minutes.
We gotta call the game.
- What?
- I said we gotta call the game.
- Are you sure...
- Yeah, I gotta call the end game.
- Just like that?
- You want a dissertation?
- I understand you're upset.
- Fine.
We would like to forfeit the game,
how does that sound?
Game is over.
Dillon has forfeited,
South King has won.