- To you, to our fearless leader!
- To all of y'all, to everybody!
Oh, Glenn!
You wanna go to car wash?
Sure.
Why the hell not?
You have a gun? Yes or no?
There you go.
I'm offering you
everything I've got.
This is not just about football.
- This is it.
- It's beautiful.
How you doing, today?
I'm Coach Taylor,
I was looking for Dallas.
- Are you his sister?
- Yeah, he's not here.
Hasn't showed up for practice for days,
I was wondering where he is.
You wanna find him?
He's probably at Carrol Park.
- He hangs there all the time.
- Carrol Park?
You do me a favor, if you see him,
you tell him I stopped by?
- All right.
- All right, thank you.
I know you get this a lot,
but how accurate are your tests?
But they can be wrong, right?
Yeah.
Okay, so I just take it again?
Thanks.
We'll hold on to this and...
I'll give you a call
if something opens up.
I thought we were gonna do an interview.
On the phone, that's what you said.
We're not really ready
to make a decision right now, but...
I'll definitely keep
your application on file.
- "On file"? What does that mean?
- We'll call you.
If something opens up,
I'll call you.
This is the number
right here, right?
Yeah, that's it.
Thanks.
Farmer's up.
Excuse me.
May I ask you a question?
Looking for a fellow
named Dallas Tinker.
You know him by chance?
He's a player of mine, I'm his coach.
- Heard he would be out in this park.
- Tinker who?
Tinkerbell?
Y'all do me favor if you would...
If you see him, just tell him
his coach is looking for him.
Look like some damn messager
to you, Coach?
Everybody get back, please!
Sheriff department.
43 County, we're out in Carrol
and we have a shooting victim...
Everybody step back.
Step back!
Are there any witnesses around here?
You guys seen anything?
Can you tell me how old you are?
Great.
Are you having any trouble breathing?
Notify EMS
that he's having trouble breathing.
4x09: THE LIGHTS OF CARROL PARK
Subtitles: Team Lions
With the participation of:
Benj!, Collioure, DarKsh,
GillesSilb, Ju, Ouazo
Hey, hon.
Good morning.
- How are ya?
- Good. Where is dad?
He had to go down
the police station,
you know, for that whole thing
that happened last night.
Feel like you guys are never in the same
place at the same time anymore.
I kind of do, too.
Are you excited
for Habitat for Humanity today?
I'm getting there.
Good.
Think you're gonna enjoy it.
Yeah, you should know, you're the one
who forced me to sign up for it.
I did not force you to sign... No!
You did. "Juls, it's gonna look great on
your applications, you should sign up."
It's gonna be great
for your college applications.
Get ready. We got to go.
How did that boy do last night?
The kid is gonna be okay.
Let me ask you something, Coach.
I saw your name on the witness list.
- What were you doing there?
- Got 1 of my players not showing up
for practice,
I was looking for him, he's fine.
Said that, that park I saw
was that dangerous at night?
Look, Coach,
you can't man a park 24/7.
I'm not asking you that. I got
a lot of players that live in the area.
So I'm trying to find out
if we can get one extra person down
there and get the lights turned on.
Look, Coach,
I completely urderstand,
but I've been to Mayor Rodell myself
and she can't even do anything for me.
Now it's all about
a matter of resources, all right?
And we just ain't got them.
It's always about the money,
isn't it?
How you doing?
I was due for rinse,
so I had to borrow your shower,
if that's cool.
Cool.
Hey, just...
Are you all right?
Yeah, fine.
Good times.
Hey, Coach!
Coach Taylor.
- Hey, Glenn, how are you?
- Good. How you doing?
- How's everything on the west side?
- It's good.
- Sorry to drop in on you like this.
- It's all right, what do you need?
Look, I...
I just wanna say I really appreciate you
just taking the high road
like this, I really do.
I mean, I'm a science teacher,
I know how these things work
with adrenaline and hormones...
And by all accounts,
you got every right to just deck me,
just tell me go to hell...
What are you talking about?
Does she not...
Did Tami not tell you
what happened the other night?
No...
This is a little awkward, I just...
I kissed your wife.
Please, please don't hit me.
I just...
I came here to apologize
and to explain myself, I...
We were at this karaoke bar,
everybody having a great time,
and I just got a little excited, boy,
I was walking her to her cab, and...
next thing I know, my lips are
on hers, I thought,
"Wow, my mouth
is on Tami Taylor's mouth."
And she pushed me back, and she told me,
"That can never happen again."
And that's why I came here, Coach.
I had to get if off my chest.
I don't know what else to say.
I guess I'll see you around
at the game
- or something.
- You'll see me sooner than that.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, I'm sorry.
I appreciate you coming in.
Well, I needed to talk to you
because we had a problem with J.D.
He called his math teacher a bitch,
and was disrespectful to me.
And he will be in detention
for the next week,
which means he will miss
some practice.
I wanted to let you know that.
Well, I think that's for the best.
- You do?
- Yes, I do.
J.D. has been
a real handful, of late.
I tried to talk to him,
he won't listen to me...
You know, he's just cannot go around
treating people like crap.
Well, that's right.
There need to be consequences.
There do need to be consequences.
I mean, he has...
acted out a lot since the split.
I'm not trying to make excuses...
When you say "split", I'm sorry...
You don't mean you and Katie?
- You didn't know?
- No, I'm so sorry.
Feels like everybody in town knows.
No, I didn't know, I'm sorry.
It happens, I guess.
I guess it can happen to anybody.
Yes, it can.
One, two, three
four, five, six, seven...
- You talked to Mayor Rodell lately?
- No, not too much.
She's not too happy
with me after that...
mailbox incident.
Was over at Carrol Pak last night.
12-year-old kid got shot over there.
Most of them are living in that area.
I wanted to talk to the mayor,
- maybe get the lights turned on.
- Yeah, I'm sorry about that, Eric.
But that's a good idea.
- Take back the park, I love that.
- I'm not trying to take anything back.
- Just want to get it cleaned up a bit.
- Okay, I'll talk to her.
Maybe we can raise money.
What? You said she was mad at you.
Well, she is.
But you know, we go back.
We have a little history, you know?
Before she starts playing
for the other team.
You know what I mean?
- I'll talk to her.
- All right, let's go!
It's looking good, Julie.
Nice work.
Thanks.
It's Ryan, right?
It's harder the first day.
To work out.
It's a lot harder to Habitat
*** than I thought.
I know, it can be.
It's kind of why
I hate to tell you this,
but this is the closet,
and you were supposed
to tile the bathroom.
- You're joking?
- It's an easy mistake to make.
It happens a lot
when we move this fast.
So what? I take it all out and...
retile over there?
That's pretty much it.
I'm sorry, I should have been
more focused on it, I just have....
so much many things going on
right now and I just...
I don't know.
Well, building is a little like...
meditation, you have to...
keep your brain in the moment.
Believe me, I learned the hard way.
No worries, though.
I'm gonna give you a hand,
we're gonna get this done in no time.
It's the fun part.
Thanks.
You got a second?
What you need?
I need some cash.
I need to bring it in
like yesterday.
I've been trying to find some work,
but there's not a lot of jobs out there
that's cool with me having a record.
And I was wondering
if you could help.
You're asking me
to look around for you?
If you hear of anything.
An application has references.
And I wanted to know if...
you were cool with me giving your number
as a reference, if they call, you...
just say I'm playing
football for you,
and I'm doing good.
And stuff.
You do that
and I'll look around for you.
Really?
You ask me to ask around for you,
I'm gonna ask around for you.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
I need to talk to you.
Yeah, it's funny because I wanted
to talk to for a while, actually.
- I'm kind of feeling like we're just...
- I've got some bad news, okay?
I'm pregnant,
and it's yours,
and I need an abortion.
It's really expensive,
it's like $300.
I don't have all of it right now.
But I can come up with half
if you can come up with the other half.
You talked to your mom, right?
I'm doing this.
You don't have to be involved
or anything,
but I just really need help
with the money.
Yes.
Please, don't tell anyone.
Please.
Just let me know
if you can get the money.
I ran into Glenn yesterday.
Glenn science teacher?
Yeah, he came over to school.
What did he have to say?
He just wanted to share
a little experience
he had over at the karaoke party.
Honey, what did he tell you?
Why don't you tell me
what he told me?
Honey, he was so drunk.
He was so drunk.
And I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
But I've been wanting to tell you
- but we haven't really had one minute.
- You kissed Glenn?
You didn't hit him, did you?
No, I didn't hit him.
What do you worry about him for?
You just happen to get kissed
by so many people over at school
you just forget to even talk about it,
is that why?
Don't blame the victim.
I'm the victim here, honey.
Do you realize by proxy
I have now kissed Glenn?
- Honey, that's awful. That's awful.
- Yeah!
Honey, did you hear that...
Joe and Katie McCoy
are getting a divorce?
Honey...
I think we need a date.
I got one date with you.
- The post-baby damn date.
- All right.
- Crack open some wine...
- Really?
If we check to make sure
it's got some nice legs,
check to make sure what year it is,
if you want bigger legs.
- Big M!
- Hey, Buddy.
How you doing?
- I'm good, man. How about yourself?
- Good, good.
Well, let's see. I'll have...
You'll have some baby back ribs,
a side of collard and fruitage.
You get 'em every damn time.
- Let the money on the counter.
- And...
Extra BBQ sauce.
I know, I know.
Hey, where are you coming from?
Prom?
No, I went to see Mayor Rodell.
Well, well, well...
Ain't you special?
No, I'm just trying to get the lights
turned back on over at Carrol Park
so we can clean
the park up a little bit.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
You're an idiot, Buddy.
What?
You're an idiot.
That's really funny, big M.
Why are you saying that?
You're an idiot for thinking your Snow
White ass can make a difference.
Do you realize that the other night,
when that little boy got shot,
Coach Taylor was in the park?
Coach Taylor...
Yeah, it figures.
You know, we're trying to organize.
And maybe you could just
help us out a little bit
instead of criticizing.
You're gonna get your ass kicked.
Here's your food.
And I might need
some water, too, please.
Look...
You gonna need somebody who can
talk to these kids. I know a guy.
He's an ex gangster.
He does community work now.
I'll get that water for you.
I should go.
Yeah, I gotta work.
You know,
that's why I gotta go, so...
Well, can I see you later?
I work until closing,
it's a restaurant, and...
What about tomorrow night?
I work every night.
This is, like, the first step
to us breaking up.
- You just pulled me off.
- Yeah. That's what this is.
- The beginning of the end?
- Yeah, I can't lie.
Why don't you come after
closing tomorrow night?
Okay.
Help me clean up?
What does that mean?
Use your imagination.
All right, Jess.
Looks pretty good, yeah?
So...
How long you've been doing this,
like, working for Habitat?
I've been doing it a while.
I did my first one 'cause I thought
it'd be good for my résumé,
and I just kinda got hooked.
I can see how that would happen.
So, I was gonna grab
some food after.
Thought maybe you'd wanna come.
Look, you're really nice...
and really cute,
but I wanna be honest.
I got out of a really long,
very serious relationship, and...
I'm still broken.
You know what? I get it.
I really do. I've been there myself.
But...
What if we...
didn't go to lunch or anything?
just were spontaneous
and lived in the moment
and just kissed
and there'd be no strings attached?
Would that be weird?
No, that wouldn't be weird.
That'd be okay.
All right, I'll give you a call.
I thought she would never go down.
She was crying so much.
Look, I got us the wine.
I need it right now.
I need to take a rain check.
Buddy just talked to Virgil,
Virgil knows a fella.
If we could talk to him, he might be
able to help us with this park situation
but it's gotta be tonight.
All right...
You all right?
I mean...
What am I gonna do?
Thank you.
I'll just call Glenn.
If you call Glenn, make sure
he doesn't drink all my scotch.
I'm not making any guarantees
about what Glenn is gonna do or not do.
I'll see you later tonight.
Good luck.
Eric Taylor, Elden Crumpler.
Hey, how are you doin'?
Nice to meet you.
Buddy Garrity. Good to meet you.
Come on in.
Thanks much.
Nice place.
- How long have you been here?
- Since I got out of jail.
What exactly can I do for you?
Well, we're trying
to clean up Carrol Park.
Take it back.
Take it back from who?
We're nice.
We don't wanna take anything back.
We're trying to get the lights turned on
there. I got players who live there.
We're trying to make some space for them
to have somewhere safe to be at night.
I don't wanna offend you, Coach.
I'm sure you're a great football man
like everybody say, but...
there are more problems down there
than just the lights won't work.
So my question to you is:
do you really wanna make a difference,
or are you just feeling sad
because you saw a boy got shot?
Both.
This is what we need.
We need money, for programs.
We need some
of the local businesses like Virgil here
and Buddy here, to send a little
something-something our way.
And not just this week
because there's a boy in a hospital.
As far as the great white hope coming in
from the football field to save the day,
those kids can't see you as an outsider.
They'd smell that a mile away.
It'd do more harm than good.
We need to give them a reason
to believe in this thing,
- whatever this thing is.
- Well, I got an idea.
I think we ought
to have a football game.
- Football game?
- I think we ought to get the Lions
versus the kids at the park,
That doesn't sound like a bad idea.
Go ahead.
Good clean fun.
No, no, wait.
Friday night, we got a by.
We could do it saturday night.
What do you think, Elden?
Well, the kids do love the football.
Everyone loves football.
Most important is it's voluntary.
If you wanna be out there, that's great,
if you don't, that's fine, too.
As a matter of fact, if you don't,
I don't want you out there.
But if you do, know there'll be some
rules. We're not gonna have street ball.
We're gonna stick to those rules,
understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Understood?
- All right. Good. Tinker!
- Yes, sir!
Break 'em down.
Vince, I wanna talk to you.
Let's go, baby, let's go!
- What's up?
- Listen, I talked to Big Merri.
He's got something over there for you.
Possibly dishwasher or busboy.
- At Ray's Barbeque?
- That's right.
Coach, that wasn't...
- That's not what I was expecting...
- What do you mean? It's a job.
You show up, you work, you get paid.
That's why you want the job, right?
All right. Then show up this afternoon
and see what he's got to say.
Don't let me down,
I stuck my neck out for you.
You be here all the time.
Work hard. No flirting with the girls,
no jaw-jacking with the guys.
Somebody come in and tell you how great
you was on friday night, you thank him,
and you get back to work.
- Yes, sir.
- We'll start you up at a minimum wage.
If things work out, you'll get a raise
in another couple of months.
- That'll work. Thank you.
- It ain't gonna be a lot.
- You ain't gonna get rich here.
- With all due respect, I want a job
that, you know, keep me out of trouble,
plus the food on the table.
That's it.
Last thing:
stay away from my daughter.
She don't want it,
I don't either.
- Understood.
- I ain't gonna remind you of that one.
If I see anything I don't like,
you got to find new employment
elsewhere. Are we clear?
Crystal clear.
Go in the back.
Get you an apron.
- Thank you.
- Go in the back and get you an apron.
Yes, sir.
Hey, honey.
I just wanted to come by
and see how it's going. This is great!
Pretty cool, right?
You look like you know
what you're doing.
Kind of.
Good.
You're having fun?
I am. Actually,
I'm having a real good time.
You are?
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad some smart person
encouraged you to do this.
"So glad some smart person..."
- Who is this, honey?
- Hold on. I'll be back.
I'll watch your saw.
So we need to get the measurements
on this railing, all right?
I'm gonna use it on the pressure treated
wood out back. Can you handle it?
I think I can handle it.
You're such a dork.
No wonder
you're having such a good time.
Who's that?
That's Ryan.
He works for Habitat.
Nice. He seems nice.
Is there something
you wanna tell me about Ryan?
But...
I will say that I feel a lot better.
I'm glad, honey.
I really am.
Make sure you get real good
underneath that one right there.
I can clean up a toilet by myself,
thank you.
I'm just saying
there's no point in paying you
to do a job if I'm gonna have to follow
after everything and clean up after you.
Seems my little brother
has cleaned toilets.
Well, I'm not your little brother.
Yeah, you're not.
I can't believe you hired him.
I'm doing a favor for somebody.
Can't you do me a favor
and tell him to go home?
No, I can't do that.
Working hard, doing a good job.
After all the grief you gave me
about spending time with him?
It just seemed
like the right thing to do.
Besides, I trust you to take care
of yourself and make smart choices.
I appreciate you're trusting me.
I'm gonna scrub that grill.
Look, I'm not even
here on my behalf.
Skeeter's upset.
All day.
Don't care.
- What?
- There you go.
Just get it out
in the open, all right?
This kiss.
You've been just awkward
and avoiding me, and...
It's just weird
and I don't like it, so...
I apologize.
All right? It won't happen again.
It was a mistake.
Are we cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
Thanks...
so much.
Okay. Somehow,
I don't think we're cool.
Go away!
- What are you doing here?
- I just left my jacket.
Yeah, well, hurry up.
Good night.
Hey, Vince.
How's it going?
We got some homework...
to do.
Sorry...
Can I just say something? I don't
wanna get in your business, but...
I just wanna make sure
that you thought through everything.
Look, I'm 16.
I'm 16 and by the time I'm 17,
I'm gonna be a single parent.
Just like my mom.
You know, if this is about the money,
I can figure it out. Just let me know.
It's not the money, all right?
I have some.
- Then what's the problem?
- I'm just...
I'm worried, all right? I haven't been
able to sleep last few nights.
- What are you worried about?
- I'm worried about you, Becky.
And I just...
I mean, I feel responsible.
That's a two-way street.
No, that's not what I'm saying.
You're pregnant, all right?
Whatever you decide to do,
that's a huge decision.
A decision you'll have
to live with the rest of your life.
And I'm gonna have to live with.
And it's not like
I wanna be a dad, all right?
But there's something about...
not being one, you know?
You not being a mom
just because we decide
to make the baby go away,
and that just makes me
really, really uncomfortable.
You know what I mean?
Will you just take me home?
Yo, man, I'm so hungry right now
I might be able to eat a whole damn pig.
That's right!
Yeah, man.
Don't ask, don't tell.
You already know what it is.
What's up?
- I see you in a minute.
- They got you sweeping there?
- It's the job.
- If you need some money,
- holla to your boy Calvin, man.
- What's up? You need something?
We was thinking you was gonna
bring us something to eat.
How about some of them ribs?
Some of them collard greens, yo.
Go to the counter order to Big Merr.
He'll take care of you.
Come on, dog.
Just bring in some damn food, man.
You're hungry?
You wanna eat?
Like I said before,
you gotta go inside like everybody else,
and order at the counter.
- You can't even hook up your boys?
- What kind of crap job is this?
Who's this dude?
You better chill out...
You tell me to chill out?!
That's enough.
We're closing up.
That means goodbye.
You heard the man.
They're closing up.
No trouble, man.
Let's roll out.
Let's roll.
Look, I know this job ain't fun.
But it pays,
and it keeps you out of joint.
You're better than them.
No, I'm not.
You're here, ain't you?
Let's close up,
and get on over to the park.
Yes, sir.
Eric, what's...
Eric, what's the deal with the lights?
Honey, you know the lights
aren't coming on, right?
Honey, I know the lights aren't on.
That's why I'm on the phone with
the city guy trying to get some answers.
- Trying to get the lights turned on.
- Can I do something?
No, there's nothing you can do.
Eric, we need to speak...
We might have a problem.
What?
That's the other team.
Right.
Hi, y'all.
Have a good game.
- Thanks for coming.
- Good game.
How are you?
Good game.
Hey Elden.
- Can I talk to you? Excuse me.
- Yeah, yeah.
- What's up?
- We got a problem with these lights.
Well, you gotta get into
the switch box over there.
Would you have any knowledge of
how we might get past the padlock
that's on the switch box?
What are you laughing at?
That was funny.
You guys be careful.
Here it is.
- How's it going, ya'll? How you doing?
- What's going on?
Hey, Vince.
I'm not sure if there's something that
you feel like you need to say or do,
and I realize that you and Jess
have some sort of history, but...
I really do like her a lot
so if you...
wanna hit me or
whatever it is that you need to do,
I'd really like to get
past that at some point,
'cause this is kind of getting
a little silly.
Your honor.
What does that mean?
Alright,
I want this to be a clean game.
I don't wanna see any crap.
If I see any crap,
I'm gonna call it.
- Ya'll got it?
- You got it, sir.
- Y'all got that?
- Yes, sir.
All right.
- Call it.
- Heads.
- Heads it is...
- Let's go!
Alright, we got the lights on.
Let's have some fun! Let's go!
Go get 'em, Lions.
Man, it's little Vince,
it's little Vince, baby.
- Ain't you on the wrong side, homey?
- You'll see. Come on, man.
Ready.
I told you you was
on the wrong side.
- Next time, I'll just snap you two.
- Just try.
- Should I say something to my guys?
- No...
It'll be alright.
All right.
Listen.
I know these dudes, all right?
To beat them, we can't give up,
and we can't back down.
Let's have some fun.
Put it at work, all right?
- On 3. 38 Jet. 1, 2, 3...
- Break!
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- What's that kid's name?
- It's Maurice.
Come here!
- How old are you?
- 13.
- What school do you go to?
- Kilroy Middle.
- You like football?
- Yes.
Next year, you wanna play
football with me?
- Of course.
- You come find me next year? Promise?
Don't make me come
looking after you.
- No, sir.
- All right. Do that.
- Thanks, Coach.
- All right.
- You make sure he comes see me?
- Yeah, you got it.
All right.
You know that it's not lost
on me that I owe you a date.
It's not lost on me either, honey.
While we may not be the McCoy's,
I also realize that our relationship
needs nurturing.
- What are you laughing at?
- It's funny.
Nurturing.
I'm not trying to be funny.
I'm being serious.
Oh, honey,
I love you to pieces for that.
- Honey, go left. Go left.
- What?
Why?
- Where are we going now?
- Honey, you'll see.
Oh, man...
That's gorgeous.
So beautiful.
Does that ring
any bells for you, hon?
Remember...
Okay, not our first date,
but our first date.
That'd be our first date,
or first date?
First date.
- I think I remember.
- Do you?
You think you remember?
I wanna remind you of that.
I mean, it's been a long time.
And you're old.
You're really old and grouchy.
Damn I love you.
Damn I love you too, babe...
- Can we talk?
- Yeah, you wanna come in, or...
- Can you get out here?
- Yeah, absolutely.
What's up?
Just a couple things, really.
First, it really...
It really hurt me that you said
that kissing me was a mistake.
Because I didn't think it was a mistake,
and that meant something to me.
How come...
I don't mean to hurt you, ever.
It just...
Since the kiss, it's been different.
You've been avoiding me, and...
to be honest, you seem lost.
So...
I didn't know what else to say,
you know?
I felt...
I just don't want to ruin
what we had before.
That's it.
Tim, I'm pregnant.
What?
I'm pregnant.
And I don't know what I'm gonna do.
And I am...
so scared...
Come here.
You're gonna be fine.
- I don't know...
- It's gonna be fine.