Resynced, not perfect, but better
Xenzai
TOP GEAR S13E03
Tonight -
we shout at the Government,
a man drives a Subaru
through a building...
and a dog goes in a car.
Hello!
Hello! Thanks, guys. Thank you.
Thanks very much.
Thank you. Now...
Now, as we know, as we know...
nothing in life is very good
and appalling at the same time...
apart from the Jeremy Kyle Show...
..and Manchester United.
And all of Burt Reynolds' films.
And actually,
now there's a car as well.
This is the latest creation
from the skunk works inside AMG -
the Mercedes SL65 Black.
Good looking, isn't it?
In a Jean-Claude
I'm-going-to-kick-you-in-the-face
sort of way.
Certainly, with those massively
flared arches and all that ducting,
it looks like it might be
pretty fast.
But it isn't.
It's mind boggling.
I have 660 horsepower
at the disposal of my right foot.
That's 50 more than you get from
a Ferrari 599.
Then there's the torque.
740 foot pounds.
That's 300 more than you get
from a 599.
Of course, to protect the
environment and other road users,
the top speed is limited...
to 199mph.
The engine that produces
this almighty oomph is enormous -
a 6-litre twin turbo V12.
But the rest of the car
is quite simple.
The brakes are steel,
not carbon ceramic.
The gearbox only has five speeds,
not the usual seven.
The traction control has
two settings - on or off.
It even comes with
run-of-the-mill suspension.
The steering in this is
a bit woolly... No, not woolly,
more sort of nylon,
but because Mercedes has thrown
away the silly electronic
suspension,
gone back to a conventional set-up,
it's very predictable.
In many ways, then, this is like
an American muscle car -
fast, simple and, in some ways,
quite cheap.
It costs £250,000 and, yes,
I know that sounds like a lot,
but it's £100,000 less than
the McLaren Mercedes.
And is the McLaren £100,000 faster?
Well, let's find out.
ENGINES ROAR
God, that McLaren sounds dirty.
If my children made
a noise like that, I'd make them
sit on the naughty step.
I reckon, in a straight line,
Mr McLaren IS faster.
Not by £100,000,
but in the corners...
Hm-hm-hmm!
Smoke coming off the back end!
Ten more horsepower, I reckon,
ten more, and I'd have him.
But the best thing about the Black
is that, despite performance
and the anabolic "look at me!"
wheel arch extensions,
it's a normal SL in here.
I've got satellite navigation
and climate control
and iPod compatibility.
I've even got an automatic gearbox.
All good so far, then.
But it doesn't last.
First of all,
it is THE most uncomfortable car
in all of human history.
There is no give at all
in the tyre side wall.
There is no give, either,
in the suspension. Look.
And look at these seats.
One-piece carbon fibre
from the Mercedes Agony range!
You would honestly be
more comfortable on
a Georgian's kitchen wheelback.
I can't imagine what Mercedes
was using for inspiration.
No, hang on a minute!
I can imagine what Mercedes was
using for inspiration.
Look! A pile of stones.
This is almost identical
to the SL Black.
I'll just try it out.
Oh, hang on.
Hmm. Yeah.
Yeah, I would rather go to work
on a cairn than in an SL Black.
A cairn would be faster, too.
The problem is,
is that there's so much torque
that if you pull out to overtake
a lorry and put your foot down,
the traction control comes down
like an anvil
and you're not going anywhere.
Of course, you can turn
the traction control off.
But don't forget -
those back tyres cost £358 each.
Really, the only way you can
drive this car,
even when the road is dry,
is slowly.
And I don't know, but I think that
rather spoils the point.
Then there's the rear spoiler which
comes up at 75mph.
So if it's up, you're speeding...
and some policemen will come.
There are other niggles, too,
like the fact it's out of fuel
after 250 miles,
and it has the turning circle
of a moon.
Look at this.
A normal SL can get round here
no problem at at...
whereas the Black...can't.
That means you're going to
run off the road
and damage that low-riding
air-splitter.
And I haven't even got to
the worst bit yet.
In a normal SL,
which can turn round
and run up kerbs without
breaking your back, or itself,
and go more than six feet without
running out of petrol,
you have a roof which folds away
into the boot.
In an SL Black, to save weight,
the roof doesn't go anywhere.
And then we have to go
back to the price.
Yes, the Black is good value
compared to the McLaren.
But it's five times more than
its little sister,
and I'm sorry...
but it just isn't worth it.
Superb, sublime, brilliant,
super-exciting rubbish!
But... It is!
Am I right in saying that
they've only imported
eight of these into the UK? Yeah.
So that means they need to find
eight people in Great Britain
with more money than sense? Yeah.
So who does this one belong to?
Theo Walcott.
Go on, then.
Now where are you going?
Anything I say now is going to be
libellous, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah.
I'll tell you what we'll do.
We'll find out how fast
this goes round our track.
That means handing it over
to our tame racing driver.
Some say that he thinks
crisps are animals...
..and that if he'd done well
at Wimbledon once in a while,
he might have been able to
raise a smile.
All we know is,
he's called the Stig.
Away he goes!
Traction control off because,
of course, he can put
those tyres on expenses.
Into the first corner.
Can't help thinking this is
going to be a handful.
Oh, yes, it is.
Oh, dear. Yes, I'm sorry.
The Stig has gone all Scottish.
He loves to Strip The Willow
with all those other Stigs
that the Daily Mail's invented.
Just a very big mess in Chicago.
So Hammerhead...
Lord alone knows
what's going to happen here.
Under-steer...over-steer...
Under-steer then over-steer again.
Every sort of steer,
and all happening practically
at the same time.
Is that bagpipes or is it the sound
of someone deflating a cat?
Through the tyres -
very, very fast.
Now he comes in to
the second-to-last corner,
holding it nicely. Just Gambon left.
Seems to be juddering through that.
Across the line!
I have the time in my hand.
It did it...
It did it in one minute 23 dead,
so if we look, it's faster than
the original Murcielago,
it's faster than the original Zonda,
faster than the original Koenigsegg,
which means it's faster than
a lot of cars that are now...
faster than it.
And now we must do the news,
and starting off with Citroen,
they've made a new C3.
Here it is.
And, well, it's a Citroen.
It looks like that, but the most
important thing about it is, for this
car, they've invented a new word.
Word?! They've put it
in their publicity material,
and it's "visiodrive".
They confessed they've made that up.
It's a whole new word. Visiodrive.
I'm sort of sympathetic. Why?
Because none of the words you'd
normally use to describe a Citroen
would work very well in their own
publicity blurb, would they? Like,
flimsy. Plasticky. Lightweight.
Anybody else got
any thoughts on Citroens?
Box on wheels. What? Box on wheels.
That's not very good.
That was terrible.
Anyway, the point is that if you
want a car that is Visiodrive,
that's your only choice,
even if you are
the Sultan of Brunei.
Now, pay attention. OK?
As men, we all know you should
never, ever buy a woman something
with a plug on it. Yeah?
We know that. Yeah. I did. What?
I did!
You bought your girlfriend
an electrical appliance?
Yeah. I got her a power drill.
James! James,
she's a ballet correspondent.
That's what she wanted.
She said, "I want a power drill,"
so I got her one. She SAID that!
Do you know nothing?! Women say they
want a power drill but they don't.
They want soap. No... They do.
But it's impossible to buy soap
for a woman. Eh? Hang on.
No, soap's soap. You can't...
Did you hear that, girls?
Soap is soap! But it is.
Go on, then. Buy your
wife some Swarfega. Well, that's...
That's an effective cleaning agent.
She'd be chuffed, I'm sure.
However, the worst thing
that you would ever have to buy,
ever have to buy a girl,
is a handbag. That's bad. Even if,
by some miracle, you got the right
colour, it'd be the wrong shape,
it wouldn't have the right
number of pockets,
it would be last season's handbag.
Is there a season for handbags?
Did you hear him?
Is...? Oh, yes!
What, at certain times of the year,
I can shoot handbags? Yes. OK.
No. The fact is, OK,
my wife has a handbag -
I kid you not - it is this big, OK?
And in it, she'll go, "I've lost
my mobile phone! Ring it!
"Ring it!" "It's in there.
You must be able to see it."
"I can't see it!" The point is,
salvation is at hand, OK?
New type of handbag out this week.
Here it is.
Look at that. Yeah. Now,
that is made from Camaro seats.
What? Yeah...
And it says in the bumph...
and I'm going to quote, OK?
"Try to picture your lady friend
grasping it tightly
"and the next vintage car show
you both attend." Ohhhh!
So this is made from seat cloth
of a Classic Camaro? Yes.
So that's had a Texan's
sweaty buttocks on it? Yes.
And now it's a handbag. On the
other side - you can't see it -
are the skid marks... NO! No!
Hey! What?
My bull mastiff keeps trying to mate
with my Labradoodle.
Bear with me, I do get back to cars.
It keeps trying to mate
with my Labradoodle, and I think
I've worked out what the results
of that coupling would look like.
Here it is.
Is that a motorcycle and sidecar?
Sport of melted into one
hideous lump. It's a Laverda 3CL.
The man behind this is a French
medical technician.
Did he not, at any point whilst
building it, just take one step back?
"Agh! It's horrible!"
If you know of anything uglier than
that, you should write to us at
"I live next door to David Guest",
Top Gear...
LAUGHTER
Can I say...? Sorry about this.
Moving on.
On Tuesday, or it might have been
Monday, the Government announced
what it called
a level 2 heat wave alert, OK?,
for what we used to call
a lovely summer's day.
Actually, we quite like
a good heat wave here on Top Gear,
because it means we can play
Car Sauna. It's really very simple.
You park the car with the engine
running, turn the air conditioning
off, wind the windows up,
turn the heater to maximum,
and the first person to get out
is the loser.
You think he's making that up,
don't you?
Because earlier today, while we were
waiting for all you lot to turn up,
this is what we got up to.
It's now 37.8 degrees in here,
as you can see,
before the test begins.
Let's just make it fair, OK?
Whichever one gets out first pays
the other a tenner.
Coming up to four minutes.
Temperature check, please.
Oh, yes. It's 53 degrees
in our Mercedes now.
Can you see my face?
Can you see my face now? I'm not
sure they'll want to.
Given that we are made of...
What percentage of us is water?
98%. Or less.
Water that then evaporates. So what
we are breathing is each other...
Agh! Agh! You're breathing my chest!
Agh! Agh!
59.7 degrees.
This is a stupid game.
I've changed my mind.
61.9 degrees.
Guys...
Oh, come on.
You owe us £10 each!
A good idea.
Gordon...
Gordon, if you're watching,
and you're probably not,
if you're going to set these
ridiculous heat wave level alerts...
What was it we got up to? 62. 62.
..62 degrees is your bottom...
It gets a bit toasty. Uncomfortable.
Yeah. About there.
Gordon, they're something else
I discovered in that test,
if you're watching, and that is,
I KNOW when I'm too hot.
I don't need the Government to tell
me to have a drink of water
and put sun cream on.
Leave us alone!
Anyway...
Guys...
You'll have to split it.
I've only got a 20.
Don't worry.
I'll put it on expenses(!)
Now, the recession.
We all know what caused it. Banks
were lending money they didn't have
to people who couldn't pay them back
and now no-one can afford anything.
Yes. And this begs a question.
In these difficult times, is there
such a thing as cheap and cheerful?
No!
I mean, when have you ever heard
anyone say,
"Right! I'm going to deploy
my cheap and cheerful parachute?"
"I could have had an expensive
heart operation
"but I decided to go for one
that was cheap and cheerful!"
This Perodua Myvi suffers from
the same problem.
It costs £7,600, so it is cheap,
but is it cheerful? No.
Brakes are rubbish.
Ride's rubbish.
Seats are rubbish.
That's rubbish.
Honestly, I would rather be inside
Paul Scholes.
This is a car you drive
with a long face.
Still, could be worse.
You could be in a Chevrolet Aveo.
I like a basic, underpowered car,
I think they can be fantastic fun,
so it amazes me that they can
make this thing so dull.
The steering is meaningless,
the pedals feel mushy,
the seats are flat.
The gear change is out of a...
I think it's out of a
Mark I Cavalier.
No. That's not fair on the Cavalier.
And the cost of all this misery?
£8,500.
The only reason you would
buy this car
is not because it's cheap,
because it's not that cheap,
it would be because you hadn't
tried any others.
I have! I've tried this,
the Proton Satria Neo.
It's actually not so bad
when you're moving.
That's not cos it's in any way
fun to drive - it isn't.
The gear change is awful,
the engine's got no power low down
whatsoever, but when you move it,
at least you're obliged to
look ahead, out of the cabin.
Only when you stop do you think,
"I'm sure I saw a nice surround on
that air vent! I'll just adjust...
"Oh, no! It's horrible.
And look at all this!
"Ugh! That's not metal, either."
At nearly £10,000, the Proton
is the most expensive of the three,
but you do get some unique features.
The wing mirrors have been made using
fairground hall-of-mirrors glass,
so when I move my head like that,
all the cars...blbl-bbb-blbl.
So that's either a bus, now it's skip
and now it's a big clown...
Soon, we all met up
and this was an ideal opportunity
to show Jeremy one of the
Proton's other unique features.
Now, it's a sunny day.
Put the visor down.
Ha! You can't see a thing!
You can't make the seat go down?
You can a bit,
but you have to open the door.
So every time the sun comes out, you
then have to open the door? Yeah.
Look. They've managed to make
Allen-headed bolts out of plastic.
Cos I believe..
That's a disappointment.
That's wrong!
Talking of fake, look at this.
Ooh! That's not a real alloy.
Are these fake, as well? Yes,
they are. So fake wheel nuts?
A year ago, we'd have been here
with a Ferrari,
a Lamborghini and an Aston Martin.
Now... This is it.
We'd chosen as our meeting point
London's financial district,
so we thought it'd be a good idea,
while we were there,
to introduce all the passing bankers
and money men
to the motoring world
they'd created.
What have you got now? XJR. An XJR?
And you've got a...? BMW M3. M3?
BMW X5. X5?
So, welcome to the future.
Your future.
I'm not sure this is the right car
for me. It's the ONLY car for you.
You'd better get used to it.
Lavishly equipped with doors.
I'm not sure it's going to do the
acceleration that the M3 does.
It doesn't. I can assure you!
You've been lending money to
Mexicans who haven't got enough to
pay you back, haven't you?
You have! That's what you've done,
and now look. Check it out.
That one any better? No.
Are all three terrible? Yes.
Do you have this every day
going round? Yeah, it does.
Every day, constantly down? Yep.
Thought about
jumping out of a window?
It's a bit plasticky. A bit?!
What are you doing at work today?
We are looking into new markets
in European gas.
That might not be a bad thing
for you lot - just flip it down,
you wouldn't see the bridge
coming up - everybody's happy.
Have you noticed this?
I put that back on earlier.
Thanks(!)
It just disintegrated
while I was looking at it.
What's the 0-60?
Excuse me. Good news. What?
You know we're here? A distraction?
See the crowds? Yeah.
That means that none of them
can actually get into their offices
and lose all our money!
It's safe! We're providing
a service to the nation.
And then, after we'd moved on,
I came up with another
service for the nation.
All the banks that go to
the Government for OUR money,
to keep going, make them have,
as company cars,
Perodua Myvis.
RBS - you've been really bad. You
can have a Proton "septic nappy".
Yeah, Fred Goodwin,
you keep your pension.
Just one thing.
Your car.
Of course, bankers aren't entirely
responsible for the problems...
..which is why we pulled over,
decorated our cars a bit
and went to shout at the Government.
What do we want? ALL: Aston Martins!
When do we want them? ALL: Now!
V8 not G8!
Give us a Rolls-Royce Phantom now!
2, 4, 6, 8, Jacqui Smith's husband
likes to mast...
I can't do that one.
Supercars not ministers...
I'm not very good at this.
Mind you, compared to James...
Acceleration not nationalisation...
of the banks.
Although it's easy to make a case
for state ownership of other
industries, such as utilities.
Ker-ching! Hit the banks not our
tanks! He means your petrol tanks,
if you were confused.
Although, whilst we're at it,
the Armed Forces are under-equipped
for the job they have to do.
A policemen then came
to tell us off.
Please don't hit me with
your riot shield.
But it was quite hard
to understand him.
What?
I think that policeman's quite cross.
In fact, he was so fed up
that he told us to leave.
That's not gone well, our protest.
But we were fed up too...
with our cars.
So we left them in a stupid place
and went home on foot.
This tunnel handles better
than my car
and the interior
is a lot more welcoming.
It's a fact!
Um...I should point out the producers
were very angry with us about that,
because they said we'd deliberately
just gone and chosen three cars
that we didn't like.
Yeah, but we said we'd made a film
to show just how many terrible
cheap cars there are out there.
And that buyers need to be careful.
Exactly. Yeah.
But they didn't buy that.
They said we had to go out and make
that film again
and this time, choose three
cheap cars that we actually like.
Yeah. And we'll be looking at
that later on.
Now it is time to put a star
in OUR Chevrolet.
Er...over the years, 105 different
people have driven round our track,
and yet, unbelievably, only three of
them have ever been called Michael.
Well, don't worry -
I can tell you're concerned -
because that's all about to change.
Ladies and gentlemen, put your hands
together for Michael McIntyre!
Jeremy Clarkson! How are you?
Hello. Thank you, Top Gear.
Why do announcers always say,
"Put your hands together"? You'd
just go like that, wouldn't you?
I think it's like, "Put your hands
together and pray that he's funny!"
I gather that, on the way down here,
people were offering you advice
as to how you should drive... I got
endless advice. From everybody.
There was a woman at home... There's
a woman at home?! She's my wife!
Yeah, my wife gave me advice.
The drycleaner told me to turn
the air conditioning off in the car,
because it makes it go faster.
The drycleaner is talking sense.
The guy who drove me here said,
"Don't brake."
I think he didn't like me very much.
He just said, "Don't brake!"
Let's have a look...
Cos you have just boinged into
the public consciousness.
Two years ago - Michael who?
And now all these girls...
They've been queuing here all day.
HIGH-PITCHED VOICE: Hi, girls.
It's being going well lately.
My show is on the telly
on Saturday night after Casualty.
# Do-do-do-do... #
That's when my show starts.
What, after it goes,
do-do-do-do?
I'm trying desperately to get
on Casualty to publicise my show.
I'd just like to be on a gurney
and then sit up and go,
"Watch my show afterwards."
That'd be ideal. Anyway,
your early life. School, obviously.
University. Is it true you can't
remember what degree you did?
That is true, yes.
I did biology or chemistry.
I've narrowed it down to two.
But you don't know which you did?
I know it wasn't physics.
Is that good enough?
How can you not remember
what you did at university?
I remember being in the lab.
I remember there was a lab...
I remember finding a girl attractive
on the first day and thinking,
"That'll be the love of my life,"
then they gave me a lab coat and
huge specs. I realised the odds were
against me. Was it a girl thing?
Um... University?
Well, it didn't work.
If you did biology,
it would've done.
My voice didn't break
till I was about 23.
When you sound like your mother on
the phone...Hello?
It's not Mummy, it's Michael.
I'll get Mummy for you. Mummy?
Phone!
She'd come in...
Hello?
I actually had hair under one arm
for a year. That was an odd...
It was a difficult transition
to manhood.
But I did buy my first car
to try and seduce women.
Which was a...?
I got a Triumph Spitfire
convertible.
I had it for about six months
and I hit a...
a parked Volvo, which was not...
Of all the cars to hit...
It's not like I was picking them!
And then the owner of the Volvo -
it was outside his house -
he ran out and said...
He was very angry.
He came up to the car and said,
"Are you drunk?!"
And I was so flustered and I'd been
told if you get into a crash,
don't admit responsibility,
so I just said, "Are you drunk?"
To which he said,
"I'm at home having dinner.
What are you talking about?!"
So, what are you driving
at the moment?
At the moment, I have... My wife's
car and my car - we have two cars.
That's allowed.
They haven't banned it yet.
They will, but they haven't yet.
I feel a bit guilty about the car
that I got her.
You won't feel guilty, because
I know you like these big cars.
I like all cars!
Except for the three...
I got her an X5, 4x4 car.
I don't like that. Right. I do.
A BMW X5. Yeah, I like it.
It's got seats and you go,
"Urr-urr-urr-urr-uh" like that.
"Urr-urr!"
So it's got adjustable...
I love that, though.
I've never had a car with that.
"Urr..."
I try and drive
in the most awkward positions.
As far back... "Urr...urr!"
Another thing with the modern issue
with the car
is the parking sensors,
which is brand-new to me.
It senses when the cars
behind you... I love it. Exactly.
It goes green and red.
"bup-bup-bpp-bpp-bb-bb-bb-BEEP!"
It screams, like there's a little
person going, "Aaaaargh!"
It's like there's two little people,
unseen, and they just go,
"No, no, no, no, NO, NO! Stop it!"
Why did you describe motorways
as the "highway of life"?
Well, after the Spitfire,
I went into some really bad cars.
I had my wife's car after that -
we shared that. That was the Mini,
Mini Mayfair. That's all right.
Nice little car.
Then I had my Austin Metro Princess,
1.0.
It had no fuel gauge, which was a
bit of an issue, because it meant I
had to look up the miles per gallon,
then count the miles
on the milometer
to work out how much fuel I had,
which worked until the milometer
broke. Then I had to guess
what a mile was... Then, ultimately,
I ended up getting it wrong.
I ran out of petrol, and I knew
there was a petrol station
quite near and I ran there
and I didn't have a jerry can,
and I presumed they'd sell them
in the petrol station.
I was queuing up and I completely
forgot the word for jerry can.
My mind went blank.
There was quite a long queue
and I went, "Hi, I need a...um...
"Ooh, I need a thing, you know.
Oh, God, it's a thing
that you put petrol in?"
And the bloke just went, "Car?"
The closest I got to was
"petrol suitcase?"
So this was why, I suppose, cos I
spent a lot of time with the Metro
in the loser lane, the slow lane...
Loser lane? ..with the trucks
and the lorries and the horses
and the old people.
The only way you could feel better
about having such a terrible car
is you would occasionally try and
overtake nicer cars on the motorway.
It's quite a manly moment.
You're chugging along at 60,
you're quite comfortable.
You'll see a Porsche
in the middle lane,
I'd say to my wife,
"You see that Porsche?" She'd say,
"Yes, what of it?" "I'm having it."
She's like, "The Princess couldn't
overtake that Porsche, it's a 1.0!"
"I can do this!"
You pull into the middle lane,
you start to get excited,
then you get into the fast lane.
When you're in the fast lane in a
bad car, you know you don't belong.
Big Range Rovers right up behind
you, flashing, "Retreat to
the loser lane, where you belong!"
There are horses in the slow lane,
going, "I've gotta see this.
What's going on?"
I think the top speed was about 76.
You put your foot down and the whole
car would shake uncontrollably.
It takes somewhere between 40
and 45 minutes to pull alongside
the Porsche.
My wife's going, "I told you!"
And you always have to look over,
when you're overtaking,
to see your victim.
"Who are you, Porsche driver?"
He's normally on the phone. He goes,
"Hold on, I'll call you back.
"Some dick from the loser lane's
trying to overtake."
I do that to people! "Get back
where you belong!" I am that person.
When I'm in the X5 now,
if I get overtaken, even if I'm
home, I will get back out and...
"Get back to where you belong.
I've worked hard for this car."
I've driven hundreds of miles past
where I live, just to overtake
someone back again.
Thing is, though, when we asked
if you'd like to come on...
Yes. ..you told the person who rang
you up that you'd be incredibly fast
going round our lap. No,
I don't know if I did. Did I?
I said I'll try hard to be fast.
You said you'd be very fast. It was
more difficult than I imagined.
Who here would like to see the lap?
ALL: Yes!
Come on, let's have a look.
Here we go. I suspect...
Go, go, go!
Heading down to the first corner...
Oh, my giddy aunt,
that's...ambitious!
Ambitiously fast, Michael.
OK, now, into Chicago.
Again, I'm suspecting
you're going too fast.
Lost a lot of time
with understeer.
That's a screamingly .
Straight into the Hammerhead.
Trickiest corner.
Did you enjoy this? I didn't
really... I lost track of time.
There we go.
Actually, that's not bad at all.
No, you can relax after that.
Ah! And you are doing!
You are doing...
And that's pretty fast.
I'm impressed with this.
And impressed with that!
God, you really had picked up
some... Second to last corner,
that's nicely done!
Here we go, just Gambon...
It's gonna be... Oh, my God!
Well done!
You nearly flipped it!
You nearly turned
the damn thing over! I nearly did.
How close was that to rolling?
I thought that was it.
I said my goodbyes.
That was pretty spectacular,
wasn't it?
It was a very ambitious
second half to the lap
and a very...
rubbish first half.
It was, it was. I know.
Too fast into the corners.
Mmm, where do you think?
Where do you think you've come?
Anywhere in the middle,
I'd be happy with. As the Stig said,
"conditions were perfect".
Michael McIntyre, you did it...
in one minute...
..forty... I like that.
I'm fine with that.
..eight point seven.
You're in here.
Oh, look.
Marky Mark and Michael McIntyre.
That's not a bad time.
I'm all right with that.
That's right...
Didn't I say in the middle?
It's in the middle of the whole
thing! You are the most average man
in an averagely-priced car
we've ever had.
You are also one of the funniest.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Michael McIntyre! Thank you.
Now...if you are
any sort of a car fan,
and you own an internet,
you will most probably have come
across a chap called Ken Block
on your "Youbook" site.
Young people tell me he is
an internet sensation.
That's why I went all the way
to the United States in America
to spend the day with him.
I was told to meet him
not at Dunkin' Donuts,
but here, at Inyokern airfield
in California.
I can hear him coming now
and I suspect he won't be arriving
in a straight line.
No, he's more like a game station
character who has emerged into
the real world.
And that's why his films get more
than ten million hits
on "Facetube".
Now, by day, Ken is a rally driver.
But what's special about him
is the way he sharpens his skills.
You see, most rallyists prefer to
practise in the forests of Wales
or Finland.
But Ken prefers to use...
airports.
Thing is, Mr Block, I look at this
sleepy old airfield and this hangar
and I think about preflight checks
and the problems of weathercocking
in crosswinds.
Looks like a playground to me.
In what way?
There's not so many places where you
have a great mix of dirt and Tarmac
and open areas...
And parked aeroplanes.
They're nice obstacles.
Obstacles... I mean, the owners of
them probably... Do they know?
I'm not really sure.
Ken has devised a course
around this place,
but he wants to keep the details
a surprise. All I know is
he'll be using his specially
strengthened, 380 horsepower
Subaru Impreza rally car
and that today,
there's a seat going spare.
I, Captain Slow, will be here,
with my bum on the best seat
in the theatre of petrol,
in the royal box of rallying,
riding shotgun with
Kenny from the block.
And I don't even have to do pace
notes, because he knows the route.
You do, don't you? Mm...
Where are we going?
Bloody hell!
Mind the aeroplanes!
Are you sure?
Door!
Here we go again!
God, that's unbelievable!
Mind the pole!
Cor, that was nice!
Where the hell are we going now?!
That's a fire station.
Next stop,
Ken's eyeball spin dryer.
Tarmac session over,
it was time for a dirt workout.
Ooh, God!
Whoa! Ha-ha-ha!
Whoa!
Oh, that's Mr Ricky Carmichael,
a good friend of mine. I think he's
come out to play with us.
'As it happens, Ricky is the
greatest dirt-biker in history,
'15 times undefeated champion.'
Go get him, Mr Block.
Ow!
Oh, there... BLEEP!
'On the straights,
Kenny was much faster,
'but Ricky was a genius
at finding shortcuts.'
Where's he gone?
'Kenny and Ricky wanted to play with
some more planes.'
No, no! Goodbye, viewers!
That's the nose of a DC-2.
He's getting away.
Not over there, that's a jump.
That's a motocross jump. No!
We're alive!
That was incredible!
God!
Now look what you've done!
Am I right in saying he's coming
to Britain later this year,
to play on our track?
Yes.
We could use his aeroplane
as one of the obstacles. Yes! No.
The man's useless.
He can't drive in a straight line.
Captain Slow rather missing
the point there. Anyway,
earlier on, we sort of suggested
that all cheap cars are rubbish
and the producers told us to go away,
put our heads in some books
and not take them out again till
we'd come up with a cheap car
that we all liked.
After a solid 24 minutes of reading,
inevitably,
we'd come up with three cheap cars
that we liked.
So, it was time to go down to our
track to find out which was best.
This is my choice.
It's a Skoda with a microscopic
diesel engine
and a top speed of 92.
That doesn't sound so good,
but it's called the Roomster.
And that sounds great!
Roomster.
I like to think that's what Marc
Bolan would've called his lounge.
This is what I've chosen - the Mito.
At £11,500, it costs exactly the same
as Jeremy's diesel-powered van.
But this is an Alfa Romeo.
£11,500 for a brand-new Alfa Romeo.
You'd have to have a heart of stone
and a soul of custard
to turn that down.
Then James arrived...
in a dishwasher.
This may have the engine
from a dishwasher -
just three cylinders and 1,000cc -
but it is the most futuristic
and modern car here.
It's called the Toyota IQ and
it's the biggest leap in small car
design since Dinky went bust.
In order to sort out
which is the best car,
we've each been allowed
to choose one test.
I'm going first and I've decided
the first test will be...
a drag race...obviously.
I'm not feeling confident
about this,
because, although I have the same
power as James has in his Zanussi,
the Roomster's a lot bigger
and heavier.
0-60 in 16.4 seconds.
And that, in English, is exactly...
..one year.
Got James!
Lost James.
He-he-he! Not bad.
And we're through. Ha-ha-ha!
'Shortly afterwards,
the Indesit finished as well.
And then the waiting began.'
50.
51!
And in 1976, we went to Tenby,
hired a cottage.
We went there. A cottage? Yeah. You
must've been posh. We had a tent.
Ooh, look! Is that him, or is that
just another car that's going past?
I don't know.
I've actually forgotten
what his car looks like.
Power, power, power, speed -
irrelevant.
What's the excuse going to be?
Ooh, tyre pressure.
You lost,
in case you were wondering.
This car -
faster than a Porsche 911 Turbo.
Yes, of course(!)
How did you make that out?
Well, if a Porsche is doing 30, I'm
doing 35, I could easily get by.
What about if it was doing 93?
That would be against the law.
He'd hopefully have
his licence taken away.
There's another thing about this.
What?
That is pure Lancia Stratos.
No, it isn't. I'll grant you...
What do you mean?! It just isn't.
Says the man in the Indesit!
What...come on! Chaps,
I'll just bring you back to
my point, which is that only one of
these three cars is an Alfa Romeo.
The Alfa Romeo, which, if you peel
away the body, is a Fiat Punto.
It's an Alfa Romeo!
It's a Fiat Punto with Alfa
written on it! This is a Stratos!
'It was then my turn to dream up
a test and, since I had a Toyota,
'I thought
we should measure quality.'
Right, each car is equipped
with one of these.
It's a decibel-o-meter. This will
measure how loud your car is
through Lionel Richie's head
in the 1980s.
You'll also be sitting on
one of these -
this is a vibration
and harshness-o-meter
and this measures vibration
and harshness. Right! Let's do it.
It's got three axes
of measurement...
Does it produce a number
at the end of the test? Yes.
Right, good. Good. Let's do it.
With the equipment installed,
we set off at a scientific 50mph.
This may only have a three-cylinder
diesel engine, but it's so quiet in
here, I can hear my hair growing.
Jeremy, it's a noise test and the
machine is picking up your voice.
After another run,
we pulled over to see who'd won.
How big is my victory?
Not great.
You two are neck-and-neck
at 63 decibels of noise.
I have 61. So it's better.
It's quieter?! Yes.
Low numbers are better. Vibration
and harshness, Jeremy - 2.1. Yes!
Let's see. Hammond, 1.8. Ha-ha!
And I'm 1.5.
It doesn't matter,
because it is now time for my test.
What we're going to do now
is a lap of the track.
The Skoda van's
going to cream that(!)
While carrying something. What?
A dog. Let me guess -
is it a King Charles spaniel?
In fact, I'd lined up Lance,
an Irish Wolfhound,
Milly, a Great Dane and Alfie,
a St Bernard.
OK, here's how it works, right?
Start the clock,
then you load the dog into the car,
you may have to lower
your rear seats, yes?
Do a lap, cross the line,
stop the clock.
I'll get my dog then.
There is one rule in my test, yes?
Don't drive like an idiot on the
lap. If, when you get back,
this dog looks sad,
you're disqualified.
OK, Lance, come on.
But St Bernards always look sad.
Ready? Go!
He's in. Oh.
I don't need that.
No, flat, flat. I can't get it flat.
I've got to... Lance, mind out, mate.
'Rearranging the innards
of the Alfa was tricky.'
There are three bits to lift up?
Yeah.
Are you in? No.
One minute 32 and the dog
is still not in the car.
Up, up. Up, Lance. Two minutes,
nine seconds.
In you get, in you get.
There you go! Good boy.
Oh, that's awkward.
This is quite embarrassing now.
'Finally, Phil Drabble
was ready to go.'
Now, there's a racing start...
and there's that.
That's it, good boy!
Your breath stinks. It's terrible.
This is a brilliant test.
There are eight million dogs
in the UK.
23% of all households have a dog.
Oh-hoh! Urgh!
A car that can't handle a dog,
frankly, is useless.
Oh, God, it's all right.
You're all right. Oh, good boy.
It's the first Alfa to have Alfa
Romeo's new DNA system.
What that means is you get a switch
down here that says DNA.
They stand for Normal, Dynamic -
which tightens up and sharpens
the throttle.
If you put it in All-weather,
that lets the traction control know
it might get slippy.
'But, anxious not to be disqualified
for upsetting the dog,
'I left everything in very normal.'
Seven minutes... Yeah. Now,
I happen to know that, actually,
that is a very good time
for an Alfa Romeo Mito
with a wolfhound on board.
Does he look sad? No, I wouldn't
say that's a sad dog.
Bored out of his mind.
'Maybe my Great Dane would have
a more exciting time.' Go.
Come on, Milly, up, up.
There you go. Look at that!
There's a water tray for you.
Oh, it leaks a bit.
£11,500, you can lift
the rear seats out,
or fold them down. All I'm going to
do is pull them forwards,
which gives Milly a bit more room.
Here we go.
How do you feel now, dog?
Yeah! What do you think of that?
What it needs is a substantial snack
halfway round the lap, say a leg...
A head.
This, of course,
isn't really a Skoda.
Peel away the body and underneath,
at the front,
it's a Volkswagen Polo.
At the back, it's a Volkswagen Golf.
The engine is from a Volkswagen.
And it's so beautifully made.
Sorry.
Now, building up speed -
dogs don't mind speed
in a straight line - they love it!
Dr Dolittle's on his way.
And...
Oh, it's not a lumpy yawn!
Delighted! She's had light, space,
air-conditioning...
slobbered on the car,
she loved it so much.
How do we know that wasn't you?
Just tell me the time.
Four minutes 13. Oh, God.
Three minutes faster than you?!
'But would the Skoda be a match
for the genius of the IQ?'
This is one of the most cleverly
packaged small cars in history.
It is, in fact, the smallest
four-seat car ever
and it's all down to very innovative
stuff, like the fuel tank, which is
very shallow and very long,
so it doesn't intrude into
the passenger space.
The engine is the other way round
from other front-wheel drive cars,
so the differential and the
transmission are at the front.
That saves more space down here.
I think all this will stand me in
good stead with my enormous dog.
Three, two, one...go!
Right.
There's no space at all!
The seats go down.
Can you stop
interfering with my time?
He can't get in! He can! He can't!
He doesn't know whether to get in
or mate with it!
Alfie, come on. Drive like that
and hope he can keep up?
Alfie, come on. You can stick
your head out the window.
What are you doing?!
That's no good!
Sit up.
Alfie! Good dog.
'Eventually,
James's Hotpoint set off.'
Oh, you've got gob
on the gearstick!
Of course, the IQ is a bit like
a small, city supercar.
The wheels are right on the corners,
it's extremely agile.
And it has a really small boot,
like the Bugatti Veyron.
Thanks for that.
Nobody, unless they have no legs,
could possibly sit in the back.
Hold on, there's a bit of a...
Oh, bloody hell!
'In James's hands, the dishwasher
was on a very slow cycle.'
Gambon corner - he could spin off
here at any point.
Two dogs, coming across the line
in a Hotpoint. Oh, no!
Walkies, walkies.
Oh, that is
a miserable-looking dog!
Look at that face! Oh, that's
making me sad just looking at it!
That's his normal face!
You want to hear your time?
Six forty-eight...?
You beat an Alfa Romeo.
That's the saddest-looking spectacle
I've ever seen and it's your fault.
If you're from the RSPCA, write to
us at "James May is a bastard,
Top Gear, London".
'With the score at one each,
we left the track and headed out
into the real world.'
The idea's very simple.
We shall drive to London to see
which one looks best in the
fashionable streets of Notting Hill.
Well, it'll be mine. It just will.
This is an Alfa Romeo, which
is Latin for "yes, I will, but only
because of your special car".
'Meanwhile, I'd unearthed a problem
with this, the cheapest version
of the Roomster.'
This just isn't powerful enough.
There's never a gap big enough
for you to pull out
and get up to 70 before someone's
caught you up.
Here we go...foot hard down...
Sorry, sorry. He's shaking his head
and I don't blame him.
'In London, we pulled over
for another real world test.'
OK, we brimmed the tanks down at
the track, so now we're in London,
let's see who's used the least fuel.
I don't feel all that confident
on this one.
£4.16.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
The three-cylinder diesel engine...
Yes? Follow me.
Eh? What?! You have to
mash your foot down
just to do 20mph.
And that's the result. You're
better off with a bigger engine.
Anyway, listen, I've got an idea.
First one to see another one
of their own cars wins.
So, if in Notting Hill,
you see an Alfa Mito...
I'll go with that.
'As darkness fell, we began to near
ciabatta central.'
Cor, this is posh round here.
Richard Branson lives up here
on the right-hand side.
Does he have a Roomster?
Nnnnnno.
We're about to penetrate
Notting Hill, James.
We'll go round that bend,
it will be awash with brand-new IQs.
'He was wrong.
'We all were.'
Fiat 500, Fiat 500...
Fiat 500, Fiat 500...Fiat 500.
Hmm.
Now, there's a very good reason
why I chose the Skoda Roomster
rather than the Fiat 500
as the best cheap car in Britain.
It's because, quite simply,
I forgot about the Fiat.
But...what if you want a car
that begins with A?
'So, there we are. If you want
a small, cheap, good-looking,
practical car
'that's fast, economical and can
carry a St Bernard, remember...
'we know nothing.'
If we'd have done more minutes
of research...
we'd have remembered it.
We are numpties, aren't we?
If we did a travel programme,
we'd finish up by saying,
"And there you are, the best place
to go on holiday in Europe
"is Belgium.
Oh, no, we forgot France!"
I don't like the Fiat 500. Oh, God.
Or France.
That really isn't a bombshell,
is it?
But, we do have a couple next week,
because these two have a race
with Postman Pat
and I declare war on the British
Army! See you then. Take care.
Good night!
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
Modified By BerHoM
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk