Tonight, we save the entire world.
We test a fat spaniel from Jaguar.
And we annoy France's
second-best racing driver.
APPLAUSE AND CHEERING
Thank you!
Hello, hello, everybody.
Hello and welcome.
Now.
All keen drivers will tell you that
front-wheel drive modern cars are
for the weak.
And that if you're at all serious
about your driving, you have to have
a car with rear wheel drive.
And we agree with them,
even James May.
But our producers disagree.
They think we're talking claptrap.
So, to try and prove their point,
they gave each of us £1,500,
told us to buy a
rear-wheel drive car with it,
and then go to Calais,
where we would be given
a number of stab wounds.
No, not stab wounds...hats.
No, what's the word?
CALL FROM THE CROWD
Sausages! Not sausages!
Challenges! Yes, that!
Mmm, Calais.
Beautiful.
But it has been enlivened
this morning by the arrival
of this magnificent Porsche 944.
And this is the S2 model,
the last and the best.
Three litre engine, at the front,
rear wheel drive,
and the gear box is at
the back as well.
Now, that does mean the, um...
..the boot floor is a bit shallow.
But really, that's a small
price to pay, frankly,
for engineering balance,
engineering perfection.
It is remarkable that you can buy a
car as good as this,
for £1,500.
And equally remarkable that someone
should spend £1,500 on what can only
be described as a Datsun.
A-ha! That's utterly hideous.
It is. Now, let me
just talk you through.
Nissan 300 ZX.
Headlines, technical stuff.
Three litre V6,
four-wheel steer, twin turbo.
I bet you Paul Raymond
had a Nissan 300 ZX.
It's a pornographer's car, isn't it?
It is a pornographer's car.
And then, the 1980s arrived.
MUSIC: Theme to "Minder"
Oh, Lord!
We're on the set of Minder!
Terry McCann is here!
All right, Tel?
I wanna see claret on the pavement!
The Capri 2.8 injection. The last
hurrah of the common man's coupe.
I love these things. It's fantastic.
It's terrible.
Seriously? It's hateful.
All I would say is,
BMW 635, 323, 325,
I saw all of these for £1,500.
Yeah, I know.
But didn't you always want a Capri?
Yes, but the producers aren't going
to say, "The winner is the one who
always wanted their car most."
'Hammond and I then
discovered an interesting
feature on Jeremy's Porsche.'
RICHARD AND JAMES: One, two, three...
Yay! Oh, sorry! Did I hit you?
You actually hit him in the plums!
He does that, he
actually goes for them.
When I was mended, we were
given a challenge.
Right. You will now drive your
£1,500 rear-wheel drive cars
to a racetrack! Yes!
It's called Circuit de Lac... Circuit
de something or other. The only
drawback is, it's 500 miles away.
A Nissan. 500 miles, that's
just...I'm there.
I'm not entirely confident about
that, if I'm being brutally honest.
Our convoy hit the autoroute
for the long drive south.
This car has done 201,000 miles.
That's very nearly
Earth to the moon.
And it feels...like it's done
201,000 miles.
My window switches have come out,
my boot release has come out,
sunroof is broken,
rear wiper is broken.
There were, however, no quality
issues at all in Paul Raymond's car.
So it's done an indicated 103,000
miles. And do you know what?
It feels as tight as a drum.
Everything is
electric and everything works.
Air-con, cruise control,
controls on the steering wheel.
Nothing had that back then!
54.9 miles into our 500-mile
odyssey, and some of the
gauges have starting working.
Soon, the producers told us
to pull in at a rest area,
where, weirdly, we were given
another challenge.
We're going to a racetrack,
we know that.
Should one of your cars not make it
to the destination...
That'll be you.
..producers have provided a back-up
car that also has rear-wheel drive.
That'll be all right, then.
That's very generous.
That's... I have wondered.
It's not that, is it?
'It was.
'And for us,
Morris Marinas spell trouble.'
I should explain, viewers, we've had
a few run-ins with the Morris Marina
Owners Club over the years.
We keep breaking them.
Not out fault. The last one
really wasn't our fault,
a piano just fell on it.
It rains pianos at our track.
So, is that thing gonna follow us in
the usual... It is, isn't it?
It did follow us, waiting to pounce.
But, for hour after hour, our three
cars - even the Capri - ran without
a single problem.
What we should have said at the
start of the programme is,
"Tonight, three middle-aged men
drive reliable cars across France
without incident."
Of course, as night fell,
our luck ran out.
Are you saying that the
rear lights don't work?
Well, I'm not blinded by it. Look.
Only that one's not working. When
you're driving there's nothing.
'Normally, this would put the
world's least practical man
in the Marina.'
'But, for the first time in
his life, he decided to
try and fix something.'
If I mend this, you lot are going to
have to stand back in amazement.
The thing is, he's actually,
genuinely changed a bulb.
He's done it.
I mended something!
I mended it! You changed a bulb.
Well, it's never happened before.
This opened the floodgates.
It's like losing your virginity.
There's a sense that I've unlocked
a treasure chest of possibilities.
I want to mend lots of things, now.
'That night, at the hotel,
"Jez'll Fix It" went berserk.'
Here we go.
Look at that! My boot release switch
is now back in.
I would never have attempted this
before, but now I can.
Well, it gives us some time on our
own, which is nice.
Hang on, where was it? Ha-ha!
Electric window switches
are now back in.
Oh, no, wait a minute. The sun-roof.
I could just fix that, couldn't I?
The next morning, my show-room
fresh Porsche led our little convoy
on to the race track.
It's not a bad looking track.
It looks great.
Bit nippy. I look forward to giving
it a... Oh, here we go.
"You are in France." Yes.
"The country that practically
invented front-wheel drive,
and have stuck with it."
Yeah, they have.
"And so, the Stig will now set a lap
time in a very French and very
front-wheel drive Renault Twingo 133.
I thought France
made the Stig violent.
Evidently not, he looks calm.
All you have to do is beat his time.
You get one point for every second
you are faster than him,
a point lost for every
second you are slower.
How can a Porsche 944 S2 be slower
than a Renault Twingo?
I've got a three litre, twin turbo
V6. I know, Stig's good...
Why are you looking like that?
I've driven one of those,
they're really fast.
It's a shopping car. Relax!
Go!
He'll have torque steer,
he'll have under-steer.
We're gonna have the tail
drifting out nicely.
Elegant, sweeping drift.
'Despite the front drive Renault,
the Stig was very quick.'
Finish.
1:32:31.
Who's going first? Baggy not me.
Baggy not me. Baggy not me.
That's too late. Aww!
Go!
Was that the crummiest start you've
ever seen from a human being?
It wasn't good.
There is one quite important thing,
I have no idea of the way
around this circuit.
It's the fast and the furious, this.
Very furious, I should imagine,
knowing Hammond.
Oh, for God's sake,
where's the BLEEP apex?
'Soon, though, I was in the groove.'
Oh, you can see already,
she's drifting round. Yes!
'And then, soon,
I was out of it again.'
Oh, he'll be
clenching in there, now!
I meant that!
'With Hammond out, it was my turn.'
That didn't go as well as I'd hoped.
'Soon, though, I was revelling in
the 944's rear-drive balance.'
Here we go, you see? Front wheels do
the steering, I then plant the
power at the back.
Oooh! Oops...
You're just feeling
the perfect weight. It's all
just absolutely magnificent.
I may have missed the apex
quite a lot there, but...
Here we go. Come on, Porsche!
Confident.
RICHARD CLEARS HIS THROAT
Now, the Stig, 1:32. Yeah.
Jeremy Clarkson. One thirty...
Yeah, I made a bit of a mess of it,
Yeah.
But it's OK! Because everything now
hangs on James!
How can the world of
rear-wheel drive now hang...
On James May in an old Capri?
I want you to win this for the
prog-rock generation.
So I should think King Crimson,
Pink Floyd... Yeah. Genesis.
Unfortunately, like prog-rock,
James's lap is gonna last 48 minutes
and make no sense to anyone.
GO!
Here we go.
I don't know if I've ever mentioned
this. James isn't a fast driver.
Come on, come on! Come on for the
honour of rear-wheel drive!
That's gotta be good.
1:32 to beat.
1:48. What?
But I was going like hell!
'Following our terrible failure,
'The Stig broke out his portable,
rear-wheel drive drifting car,
'to show the front-wheel drive
generation what they're missing.'
'And because we are
all eight years old,
'we thought we'd have a go.'
'But there was a hitch.'
Hammond. Is there any steam coming
from your car?
None whatsoever, no, no, yours?
There's none coming from mine.
However, there's quite a...
How are you going to be able to
drift when you can't see where
you're going?
It'll blow off when I'm going along.
Have you got any tea bags?
It's harmless. This is what
happens when you push a
car to the ragged edge.
Which you haven't done.
'Sadly, by the time Terry McCann's
kettle had cooled down,
'the producers were ready with their
next challenge.'
What are those things?
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
The middle one is exactly the
same colour as my bike.
That one... Yes, my
Christmas present bike.
That's funny, because
the thing on the right looks
suspiciously like my drum kit.
Well that's what I was thinking,
it looks like my piano.
It can't be, because
we smashed that to bits.
Exactly. But I bought another one.
I don't imagine it's coincidence,
and it's there. This is...
Here we go. "You will
accelerate from nought to
60 miles per hour and then brake.
"All within 200 metres."
I know what they're there for.
"If you fail to pull up, you will
not only lose points, but something
dear to your heart as well."
Pianos are really heavy.
You're gonna crash into
your piano in about a minute.
This is a stupid idea.
Airbag, no.
I'm wearing a crash helmet to protect
me from my own motorcycle coming
through the windscreen.
Traction control, no.
I've really gotta get on
the brakes with this.
Anti-lock brakes. Don't know.
Remember to brake at 60, remember to
brake at 60, you stupid boy.
Yes, it's a good start.
Come on, brake.
Good change into second.
40. No!
Come on, car!
60... 60, now!
Cock!
That didn't look good for James.
Look at your Capri.
Never mind the sodding Capri,
look at that!
I think, this...
You could get these in order...
I'm sorry, mate. I'm really sorry.
You're not sorry!
'Then, for James, things got worse.'
Is this normal?
Of course it's not bloody normal.
Look at it this way -
no more challenges.
Good. Oh.
Apart from that one.
What now?
"So far, real-wheel drive has not
been relevant in any way."
Steady on!
"So you will now drive to
Val Thorens in the Alps, to see if
some use can be found for it there."
What's Val Thorens?
Well, it's a skiing resort.
I've been there.
Is it far?
115 miles.
With bits of piano sticking out
the front. That's a long way.
Don't need that.
Oh, yeah, good luck to you.
There's nothing wrong with the car.
It's got a dent in it, that's all.
Come on,
Val Thorens.
He just drove over this.
APPLAUSE
That's from back in the days when
Porsche could style cars.
It was a good looking car.
It was. We'll pick up on that later,
because now we're going
to do the news.
Yes, yes. And the people who
have collaborated with Google
on their Smartphone
have turned their attention to cars.
They've researched motoring and come
to a conclusion. Their conclusion is
this, and I can quote -
they say, that humans
are not meant to drive.
LAUGHTER
We're not meant to use ovens,
either, or wear shoes,
but that's just ridiculous.
That's the conclusion they've come
to, and they've come up with this!
It's called the Autonomobile.
LAUGHTER
I can tell you like it,
I can tell that.
You'll notice there's no steering
wheel or brakes or any controls at
all for you to operate.
It's the Autonomobile, it does it
itself, you see?
Yes, it's very clever. You get in
it, you tell it where you want to
go, and then it says -
and I'm gonna make sure
I get this right -
they say you "sit back, enjoy
the view with a nice wine,
cheese and a baguette."
Oh, lovely.
How lovely.
I think this is a brilliant idea. I
genuinely like the idea of sitting
about with a glass of wine,
some cheese, and going home.
However, there is one problem with a
sort of laser-guided, radar-guided,
satellite-guided car.
We know - because it's
statistically proven -
that half of all plane crashes are
caused by pilot error, yes?
Yeah. We also know,
that planes can take off, fly and
land by themselves, yes?
This is a fact.
So, if you remove the pilot
from the plane, you would
half the number of crashes.
Stands to reason.
However, would you get on a plane
that had no pilot?
BOTH: No.
You see? Then that's
the problem with this.
Great idea, but the problem is, you
just happen to know, this has been
invented by a brilliant man.
But, five years down the line,
it's going to be bought
by someone called Keith.
Keith is going to wake up one day
and think he can service it himself.
Yes.
Which means you wont be able to
relax in your Autonomobile.
Because you'll be thinking,
"I know that somebody called Keith,
"reading the Daily Star
and watching EastEnders
is coming the other way."
LAUGHTER
And there's going to be
a horrible accident.
It's all rubbish. What?
Cars that drive
themselves were invented ages
ago. They're called taxis.
LAUGHTER
Right, now, news from India.
There's a company over there, car
company, Tata, they've got a large
car division.
Got a new car out, here it is.
It's the Jaguar XJ.
It's quite striking to look at.
The interior is gorgeous as well. It
looks fabulous, look at that!
It costs £50,000 to £90,000,
depending on the model,
the direct injection V8, two new
diesels, with 271 and I think...
270... 271...
Nobody gives a pig's arse about
all that Diesel stuff.
It's a new XJ, the important
question is, "Is it a proper Jag?"
What you mean is,
is this car slightly caddish?
That's what you mean.
Yes.
Is the person who drives it... Oh,
what's the word, I'm not quite sure
how to sum it up, but they're the
sort of person who'd go away for the
weekend with his wife to a hotel,
some romantic place, and spend the
entire night flirting outrageously
with the waitress.
And it's OK because he's got a Jag.
LAUGHTER
You can get away with anything!
"I'm terribly sorry,
I ran over your dog." "Oh!"
"In my Jag."
"Never mind."
Is it fair to say, do you think,
that no Jag driver is ever entirely
trustworthy,
but it's in a really nice,
likeable way?
Because if you went to a prison -
forget the stabbists
and the stranglers,
the ones that are in there for
a bit of tax-dodging -
I bet 80% have got Jags.
You know what I mean, don't you?
Have you got a Jag?
Who here's got a Jag?
You've got a Jag? Look at him!
He goes away with a girl
for the weekend and then goes,
"Awfully sorry."
"Bit of an issue with the wallet."
"Do you mind, awfully, settling this
while I go warm up the Jag?"
LAUGHTER
The thing is, I think that is
just a brilliant, brilliant
piece of design, because
it's a Jag. But it's kind of modern.
That's an absolutely
fantastic looking car, that.
Can't wait to have a go on in it.
Oh! Guys, guys, guys, guys. I want
to show you this.
It's a speeding ticket,
which was issued in California, OK?
We see here that the car in question
is a Bugatti two-door.
I'm guessing a Veyron.
Speed limit on the road, 65 miles
per hour. Recorded speed, 210.4.
Whoa!
APPLAUSE
Yeah, what about that?
Unbelievable.
If he'd done that in this
country, you'd be put in
prison for 2,000 years.
Do you want to know what
the fine in California is
for doing 210 miles per hour
on a road with a 65 miles per hour
speed limit?
You get, basically, the maximum fine
a judge can impose is 500.
For 210 miles per hour.
And if you do it again,
it's just 750.
So, goodbye. We're off.
Yeah, that's it!
Why aren't we there
doing what we do? I know!
This is the worst country for making
a car programme.
Honestly, I think we should go,
that is civilised behaviour.
Now. Bad news.
It's about this,
the Honda FRV it's called.
It's a six-seater car, it had
three seats in the front,
three in the back. Well, Honda say
it's been such an enormous success,
they're dropping it.
The problem with this car is
with the picture they sent us,
which is when the car
came out a few years ago.
Nobody wants to drive around
with a small girl's severed
head on the dash.
The worst thing about this was that
when it came out, we all got
suckered into it and thought,
"Three in the front, three in
the back, it makes sense,"
but it doesn't.
If you think, I've got two daughters,
so if I have one girl in the
front between me and my wife,
that leaves one girl on her own!
You're just gonna have an argument
every time you go near it!
Exactly. It's not gonna work.
That's not the worst bit.
It could be worse if you had your
wife in the front, and both
daughters, and you sat in the back.
Oh... But you do see that
occasionally.
The mother in the front and
a bloke in the back.
It's tragic. There's
nothing more pathetic.
It's the most
pitiable sight you can see.
She's effectively saying,
"You've given me the baby,
now get in the back." Yeah.
No.
That concludes the news, OK?
That concludes the news,
and now, if you don't mind,
I want to talk about the BMW M5.
You see, what we have here
are two cars.
One of them is a spacious,
practical four-door saloon.
The other is a blistering,
growling monster.
For 24 years, this has been
the ultimate sports saloon.
But now, there is a new Jag.
The new XFR doesn't look much like
a blistering, growling monster.
There are no bulges in its flex.
There are no scoops.
There's no Cheshire-ishness at all.
It looks like it might
even be a diesel.
It's the same story on the inside.
Sitting in an M5 is like actually
sitting in a laptop.
It couldn't be more geeky, even if
the sat-nav voice was Buffy.
In the Jag, though, all I've got is
a steering wheel and some pedals.
It even has an automatic gearbox.
Don't be fooled by the
plain-Jane simplicity, though.
Because the speed of this thing is
simply unbelievable.
Right. That is nought to 60 in four
and a half seconds, and look at it.
80...90...100...
110...115...it's supposed to be
limited to 155, but, look!
165 and it's still accelerating!
That's unbelievable!
What's it limited by?
"If you don't stick to 155, I shall
jolly well write to the
Daily Telegraph about it."
'The key to this rampant savagery is
an all-new, all-Welsh supercharged
five-litre V8 engine.
'There's no other word.
It's fantastic.
'And there's more good news.
At £60,000, the Jag is
noticeably cheaper than an M5.
'It's also quieter, and
it's way more comfortable.'
It is uncannily comfortable.
It's so soft and so absorbent,
it's like sitting on a fat dog.
You can't really believe it'll
go round a corner at all,
leave alone like this.
I'm doing that wearing brogues!
'To keep it planted,
it has an electronic diff
like you get on a Ferrari.
'And suspension that adjusts itself
hundreds of times a second.'
You can be just inch-perfect,
even when you're driving like
a complete lunatic.
Whoa! Ha-ha!
So easy!
So, this is two cars as well. It's
amazingly comfortable and quiet
when you're not in the mood
for fun and games,
and it's savagely fast when you are.
But, can it really be as
fast as an M5?
Let's find out.
Both cars produce as near as makes
no difference, 500 horse-power.
And both weigh about the same.
There are some differences,
of course.
He can rev to 8,000, I can only rev
to six and a half.
He's got ten cylinders, I've only
got eight. He's got seven speeds in
his gear box, I've only got six.
BUT I have 80 more torques
than him. 80!
I've got so much torque,
I could tear a hole in TIME!
Yes, he's got better brakes,
but coming out of the corner,
I'm gonna unleash my meteorite of
torque, here we go!
This is getting hot, hard and
dangerous now. I need to stay cool.
There's the air-con.
I'm not for a moment
going to suggest that this
is better than an M5.
But it's as good as. And praise
doesn't get higher than that.
Boot full of stolen videos.
So, right, on the track,
the Jag is as good as the BMW.
..Nearly.
On the road?
Honestly, I think on
the road it's better.
Tell you what we'll do now, we'll
put some maths into the mix.
Because we'll find out how fast
it goes around our track,
and that means handing it over
to our tame racing driver.
Some say he has 12 GCSEs,
all in domestic science.
LAUGHTER
And that he's been producing
artificial sperm for years.
Even though we have
repeatedly asked him not to.
All we know is
he's called the Stig.
And he's off!
503 Welsh horsepowers!
Charging him down
to the first corner.
This is still a two-ton car, so
let's see how it battles the laws
of physics here.
Looking nice so far.
And a lovely little slide
on the way out.
BAGPIPE MUSIC PLAYS ON THE RADIO
The sound of bits, there,
being served in a stomach lining.
Chicago.
There goes the tail again,
this thing really is a
leathery drift machine.
As he comes into the Hammerhead.
The Jag's clever diff runs
in open mode when you don't
need limited slip...
That doesn't eliminate under-steer.
Fortunately, Stig does with a boot
full of supercharged goodness!
BAGPIPE MUSIC PLAYS ON THE RADIO
Terrible smell of oats all of a
sudden. There he is through
the follow-through.
Punishing its tires, battling on
well. That was fast.
Here he goes, second to last corner.
More over-steer, and up to Gambon,
wonder what will happen here.
Yep, there goes the tail again.
And across the line!
APPLAUSE
Now...
Here we are, look. BMW, M5.
1:26:2.
Now, I expected the Jag to be a
little bit slower than that.
And it was.
Unfortunately, just half a second in
it. But, look at it this way,
If you have an XFR, "Do you know,
I've lost my wallet!" You never have
to pay for anything.
Now, normally, that would be that.
However, these days, as
I'm sure you know,
the amount of tax you pay on a car
depends on how much carbon dioxide
it produces.
Yeah, and according to official
figures, the XFR produces 292 carbon
dioxides per kilometre.
Which is very impressive,
no other car of its type
gets even close to that.
But, predictably, Jeremy
thought he could do better.
As we know, plants absorb
carbon dioxide, and
then breathe out oxygen.
So why not put plants in the
exhaust system of your car?
Impossible?
Well, Alan Titchmarsh might say so,
but, er, what does HE know?
What we have here is a Range Rover,
which now has the same 5 litre V8
that you get in the Jag.
At the back, we have tubes
which takes the exhaust gases
into this greenhouse, which is full
of plants - tomato plants,
on this occasion.
And that means the tailpipes emit
no greenhouse gases at all.
What you're looking at here,
ladies and gentlemen,
is the future.
It really is impossible to
overemphasise the importance
of what has been achieved here
today.
Look at what I'm driving.
A big, heavy, thirsty
four-wheel drive car,
and the only waste product is
some juicy tomatoes!
GLASS SMASHES
You thought Greenpeace would save
the world, but no!
It's Top Gear! We've done it!
Where's it gone?
APPLAUSE
Why are they applauding?!
Well done(!) I know there was
a bit of glass on the runway.
Yeah, brilliant. Brilliant Top Gear
WOULD have saved the planet,
except you smashed your greenhouse
to bits. I admit, it didn't go
brilliantly. But you also said
that you weren't giving out any
greenhouse emissions at all. Yes.
That's rubbish cos you only had 100
tomato plants. How many tomato
plants do you need
to get rid of the emissions
from a Range Rover?
400,000.
LAUGHTER
Seriously? And we've worked this
out. To accommodate that many,
your greenhouse would have to be
six miles long.
I can tell why you two
aren't astronauts. Eh?
Who here has seen Apollo 13? Yeah?
You know what I'm on about.
That bit when Houston telephones
the astronauts in the spacecraft
because carbon dioxide is building
up and they need to build something
to get rid of it. Remember?
Yes? Good. These two would go,
"We're a bit cold and frightened!"
Whereas I am Commander Jim Lovell.
I didn't give up
after my greenhouse failure.
I came back, rolled up my sleeves
and came up with another idea.
Oh, God!
If you fire up the Jag, right?
ENGINE STARTS
What we've got is a gasometer.
And its prong is up that exhaust.
What it's telling me
is that 15% of the gas
coming out of this exhaust pipe
is carbon dioxide.
Come here and verify that for me.
It's actually 14.5%, yes?
OK, yeah. Yeah.
Right. Take the prong out
because, on this side,
on THIS tailpipe, I've modified it.
Got tubes feeding into
this Apollo 13 homemade filter...
LAUGHTER
..which is full
of lime soda crystals,
which are used to absorb the carbon
dioxide in those huge
Australian mines, OK?
We're gonna pop the prong in the top
because the gas is going down there,
through the crystals, out of there.
Let's have a look
at how much carbon dioxide
THAT'S producing...
It's none. What, nothing?! NONE?!
Absolutely NO carbon dioxide
is coming out of that car.
Wow!
APPLAUSE
Now, I know we have a reputation on
Top Gear for cocking about, OK?
But on this occasion, we aren't.
This is not a Toyota Prius
or a stupid G-Wiz,
it's got a 5 litre, supercharged V8,
and all that's coming
out of this tailpipe
is nitrogen and oxygen, which is...?
Air. Hang on a sec. What?
These little rocks of yours.
Yes. They absorb carbon dioxide?
They absorb it, yes.
So, how far can you go
before they get all clogged up
and can't absorb any more?
On a motorway...
six miles.
LAUGHTER
With something that size. How much
does it cost for a new box of rocks?
£75. Oh, God!
I know. Barnes Wallis had setbacks,
but he persevered, and I'm sure,
if science can make
genetically-modified wheat,
they can make those absorb more.
I really do think
that we're onto something here.
Shall I go and work on it?
Yes, go and work on it
because it is now time to put a
star...in our reasonably priced car.
We're often criticised
by politicians and newspapers
for being sexist on this programme.
Well, tonight we answer those
critics because my guest is a girl.
And a dead fit one!
Ladies and gentlemen, Sienna Miller!
APPLAUSE AND CHEERING
Hello!
How are you? I'm good. Have a seat.
I like that - "Yeah!"
This is momentous stuff.
Even as we speak,
James May is out the back
looking up in his dictionary
what "girl" means.
Yes, he is.
Now, you weren't actually born
to be in theatre, you were born...
IN a theatre. Literally? Literally.
Mum went into labour in the
Nutcracker Suite in New York,
and stayed, throughout the labour,
to finish the show.
So you were born in... That makes
you an Americanista. Well, both.
My mum's English, my dad's American,
so I have two passports.
You went to boarding school
in England. I did.
I heard that while you were there...
Oh, God. How can I put this? You
got into trouble for doing things
with a rabbit.
Oh, my sweet Lord! I did not do
anything personally with a rabbit,
I got another rabbit to do something
to another rabbit to get
baby rabbits. And it worked!
They really do do it like rabbits!
Fair enough.
So you went into films, obviously.
Yes. Having been born in theatre.
Most of them, let's be honest, have
been quite brainy, quite Channel 4.
To you, boring - just say it.
No, I liked Layer Cake, that bit...
Oh, God! Yeah. You remember the bit
in Layer Cake?
AUDIENCE: Yes!
That was a long time ago,
it's all gone tits up since then -
or tits down!
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
I can't believe I just said that!
You see... Oh, God.
You say that, but your new film,
which is called GI... GI Joe.
GI Joe. That's not sort of cerebral
at all. No. Everything blows up.
Lots of guns, leather. It's perfect
for Top Gear. Leather? Yes.
Really?
Normally we don't show clips,
but on this occasion, I think
we can struggle into doing that.
Let's have a look.
We're running out of time! Eject!
This has only just begun.
APPLAUSE AND CHEERING
Just one thing. Why did the film
company send us a clip
without you in it?!
I was in it! I had a black wig on!
Let's get this straight. This is GI
Joe, who's the American equivalent
of the Action Man toy. Yeah.
Well, he's not called Joe, Joe
is an elite force of fighter...
world protector people.
But I'm on the bad camp, the Cobra
camp. Oh, you're a baddie? I am.
I understand there's a record set
with it, with cars? We blew up
112 cars, destroyed 112 cars,
which is a record.
The Blues Brothers held it before.
Yeah. So, 112? Yes.
But you're still some way behind us.
Probably quite far behind you!
112 every 20 minutes.
I've added one to that today,
I think, with my lap.
We'll find that out later.
Before that, though, I want to talk
about fashion magazines.
They always talk about the Sienna
look. We should look at what you're
wearing now. It's not very exciting!
I should've brought another T-shirt
for after my lap, it's quite sweaty.
Have you not changed since...? No!
I didn't realise it would be that
scary! It's soaking wet!
Pop it off if you want to.
LAUGHTER
I say the same to the male guests.
I mean, you are a trendsetter.
I suppose the problem is, it does
make you a massive paparazzi target.
But I sued them all, and won!
I was the first to sue and win on
harassment, so now they can't do
anything. I saw two of them
the other day, and I ran. They were
like, "We can't." And I was like...
I flashed them!
It was the best feeling!
That's fantastic!
APPLAUSE
Yeah!
It's true, you really genuinely did
set legal history.
I did! How bad was it for you?
Every day, probably 15 people
following you everywhere.
Did they chase you?
They were being mean. Shouting,
"Slapper." I can handle that,
but kicking the car and trying
to make you scared.
Do they chase you in the car?
Yes, did you ever have car chases?
Yeah, tons. Really? Yeah.
The other night,
James and Richard were leaving here,
and someone was beside them on
the M4, taking pictures of them,
and he drove his Mini into the back
of the car in front.
That was a result!
We need to talk about your driving
test because I'm confused.
You recently took your driving test.
I passed my driving test last week.
Just last week?! Five days ago!
APPLAUSE
Thank you! Five days?!
Five days.
Now, I'm very baffled because
you've been driving for years.
No, I haven't! I found a loophole.
Which is? My father lives
in the US Virgin Islands,
which is a Caribbean island, which
is technically part of America.
So I got a licence there that meant
I could drive in America and England
for a year, as an American.
It was an interesting driving test,
for sure.
I had to drive down the street
and back.
And that's the test?
Window down, he had the reggae on!
That's the test in the Virgin
Islands! Exactly! There's a top tip
for anybody finding it a struggle
to get a driving licence here!
Pop over there! Slip over there.
So, how is your driving record?
Good, bad, indifferent?
Mm, the first time I drove,
I wrote off a car,
so not good. My best friend and her
brother had a little car on a farm
that they lived on,
and I pretended I could drive, and
got in it, and pushed the
accelerator instead of the brakes,
through a concrete bollard...
Ditch, fence, cows out...
stuck. I had to climb out
of the window covered in oil.
And that was your first ever
experience? It was.
Then you drove around the Virgin
Islands, which can't have taken more
than five minutes. No.
Then you took your driving test five
days ago. Yes! And now you're here!
We've never had
a better-qualified person, really,
to do our lap! How was it out there?
Did you enjoy it?
It was pretty scary. I've never
really driven a stick shift.
You deserve credit, genuinely, if
you've never driven a manual car,
and belting round with the Stig.
Yes. Who would like to see
Sienna's lap? Oh, no!
AUDIENCE: Yes!
Let's have a look at this! Oh, God!
TYRES SQUEAL
Is that your first wheel spin start?
Yes.
I'm gonna nail it.
Oh, I say, that was brave! Not
accurate, but brave! It looks slow!
No, it's not.
Excuse my language. Oh, BLEEP!
Potty mouth!
That's impressive, nobody's gonna
complain about that.
I just passed my driving test...
I really should not be doing this.
I love the straight-out
arm position. I know!
It looks so slow! It doesn't!
It looks the same as this
every week.
Oh, BLEEP!
I'm letting women down!
There's nothing wrong with it!
That's quick. How will you be
through the tyres...?
Oh, my God! Mummy!
Holy cow!
That is fast!
You're having a crisis!
Oh, it's off again! And you held it!
Yes, you got it! That's it, Gambon!
And you made it across the line!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
That's a cracking lap!
Now... Oh, God!
So, where do you think, then,
on the...?
It felt quite slow, watching it
back. It felt so fast
when I was doing it!
I have no idea. Tell me it's good.
You did it, Sienna Miller, in...
one minute...
..forty...
AUDIENCE: Ooooh!
..9.8 seconds! Yeah!
That is not bad because
that puts you... Oh!
What a nice place to be!
That's all right!
Anything above 1 minute 50
we always say is quick. OK. I beat
Gambon, that's a first. You beat
Michael Gambon, Alan Davies,
Steve Coogan. For someone
who's never driven a manual car,
and only been driving a week,
it was amazing!
Thanks! Now, best of luck
with your new film. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, Sienna Miller!
Thank you!
APPLAUSE AND CHEERING
Thank you! Was that all right?
Now, tonight we are in France,
demonstrating the virtues
of rear-wheel drive with one
of our Cheap Car Challenges.
When we left the action, I'd crashed
into a piano, and we were on our way
to a ski resort in the Alps.
All three of our £1,500 cars
are running well,
so none of us is in danger of needing
the back-up car, a Morris Marina,
which is a good thing,
because we're bound to break it,
and the Morris Marina Owners Club
already sort of hates us
and wants to kill us.
All is perfect
aboard the mighty Nissan.
All was perfect in the Porsche too.
However...
There's something coming out
from under the bonnet.
Did they forecast fog in your car
this morning, James?
It's like driving through a horror
film. Chaps, my car's started
making some really bad noises.
Started?!
'We had to pull over.'
# Marina... #
LAUGHTER
I wish this was smelly-vision,
because you would not...
That smell of a car. You know when
a body's been in a flat for
nine months
and people ring up and say...
That's a distinctive smell.
..there is a smell.
You really think you're gonna get
that going? Yeah. You're just not!
'We decided to help...
'by leaving.'
I'm just thinking, on these big
foreign Top Gear cheap car
challenges,
the cars always make it.
And James won't want to be the one
that lets the side down.
I don't know if you can see this,
but I've got some fairly dramatic
wheel wobble going on here.
RATTLING
I can fix this.
I can fix anything.
'With my new mending powers,
'I worked out
I'd lost a wheel weight.'
How much, 5g, something like that,
possibly? Goodbye, Jeremy.
'Hammond decided to help
by leaving.'
It just needs some weight.
Funny euros!
They're like wheel weights.
Sometimes, I amaze even myself
with my brilliance.
Gaffer tape them on.
Let's go.
It's worked!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
At 60, the exact speed it was bad,
it's now perfect.
RATTLING STARTS AGAIN
However, at 62...
'At the next town, Hammond and I
re-grouped to wait for May.'
Can I just say, we've now been
waiting, what, half an hour?
Easy, yeah.
Now, if it's... More, 40 minutes.
If it's 40 minutes,
he must have mended the Capri.
Because if it was ruined, he would
have just got in the Marina,
so he must be in the Capri.
'My logic was exactly 100%...
'wrong.'
HE'S HERE!
Oh, God, it's Pinky and Perky!
He's failed!
Let's embrace the failure.
That suits you. Thank you. It does,
I'm sorry. You know we've had
problems
with the Morris Marina Owners' Club?
Problems?! They declared a fatwa
on us! Exactly. This car... Mmm.
..you have to understand this,
belonged to the wife of
the president. Right.
Just take care of it. Your comments
should be addressed to... Ahem! Why?
I don't want you to drive into this.
This used to belong...
to the wife of the President of...
Where was it? France. ..France.
'Hammond really wasn't impressed
with James' new wheels.'
I'll guarantee that nothing exciting,
vibrant, dynamic,
new, creative,
hopeful or beneficial in any way
to humanity has ever been done,
thought of, or driven to
in that drab,
dreary, entirely beige,
wilfully awful pile of misery!
Oh, come on, it's not so bad.
Erm, it's well-equipped.
No, it isn't well-equipped,
to be honest, it's got one dial.
It's tastefully upholstered.
It isn't tastefully upholstered,
really, it's brown.
But the seats are velour,
and look how well it's worn.
'Soon, we began to climb into
the mountains.'
Now, look at this. We have snow.
And if we have ice, I have
the chassis to deal with it.
This is more like it!
Don't tell me rear-wheel drive
isn't more fun on this road.
TYRES SCREECH
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Come on, Hammond, live with this!
This is brilliant.
£1,500.
Drives down here, hardly uses
any fuel and now look at it!
Belting up an alp.
TYRES SCREECH
Twisty, this is where the
Morris Marina comes into its own.
CLUNKING
'Meanwhile, further up the road,
'I'd had an idea.'
Now, remember, viewers,
Hammond broke my drum kit. So,
as he waits down there
for James to arrive...
Oh, God!
JEREMY LAUGHS
What if it were to go down the hill?
Very funny!
Oh, no! Oh, my God!
Oh, I'm sorry(!) What do I do now?!
May's here. Oh, joy!
Did you break my drum kit?
Yes! Have you got a cold car now?
Not...
No, not cold...
I'm going to die!
Fantastic! Driving a car
that terrible...that old.
See his Targa roof? Yeah.
LAUGHTER
It may have fallen in the raging
torrents. I've no idea how(!)
The faster I make him drive,
the colder he'll be.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's quite cold now.
Really very cold, in fact.
That does mean war, I'd say.
'As night fell, we reached
Val Thorens, still wondering
'what our final challenge might be.'
Rear-wheel drive...
..on an alp.
'The answer lay
just round the next bend.'
Is that an ice driving track?
'It was. And the next morning,
the producers had entered us
'for a race on it.
'However, between us and it,
'there was a small hill.'
Watch this.
Agh!
And there he is!
JEREMY LAUGHS
'Using Top Gear logic,
I applied even more speed.'
Oh, dear, no!
That's not gone at all well.
'Eventually, some locals
helped us onto the track,
'where we decided to get
some practice.'
Easy.
Gentleness is the... Oh. BLEEP!
'It was unbelievably slippery.'
Oi!
He's pushing me up with his wing
mirror. Get off my racing line!
You blithering idiot!
Don't keep doing that to me!
How is this racing?
It's just fighting!
It's just not racing.
Aah! Aah! No!
Oi, do you mind?!
Oh, I'm gonna hit the Marina!
'Ten minutes later,
we stormed into the first corner.'
Yes, I'm winning, I'm winning!
Get out of the way! I'm not winning!
This doesn't work. It's impossible.
It's a very slow accident in slow
motion. Could we get snow tyres?
Yes. Spiky things. Yes.
Snow tyres...
and modify.
MUSIC: Theme from "The A-Team"
'We were towed to the pits,
where we fitted spiked tyres,
'roll cages...'
I can't drive like this.
'..and because it was a race,
'some sponsorship decals.'
Oh...shit!
I mean, bother.
No! Does anyone have a hammer?
'The next morning, Val Thorens
basked in glorious alpine sunshine.
'Actually, it didn't,
because this is some film
from the Tourist Board. For us,
'it looked like this...
'No matter, at least our cars,
'on their new spiked tyres,
were ready for battle.'
Check it out.
May I look inside your car, James?
Please do. It'll still be awful!
Look at that! Can I say briefly,
from the outside,
it does actually look quite good.
It looks quite serious.
And then, Hammond... Yes?
..I can see one massive problem
with your car. What?
Ooh, dearie me! Yes.
JAMES LAUGHS
Look at that! Oh!
Yes, I'm sitting in a snowdrift.
How did you get your roll cage in,
in the end? Well, work.
I've got door bars. Oh, well,
that's a very thorough set-up.
It's a very thorough job.
Now, I'm looking forward to this,
because I think a Porsche
will look good drifting.
You couldn't do this
with front-wheel drive.
'We were feeling confident.
'And when we saw the cars our French
rivals had, that confidence grew.'
These are all just little hatchbacks.
That's a Kia.
And a BMW 1 Series.
I've got a V6 and a twin turbo.
This is the crib sheet, right,
on these cars, yes?
They have a top speed of...
80.
Even your Marina
can go faster than that, 80.
And it says here, "Cars rarely
exceed 50-60 mph during a race."
Wow, look at that! I haven't got one
of those. Did you fit one of those on
your Marina? No. A windscreen wiper
on the side. They're obviously
expecting to go sideways... Look!
..with their wayward handling.
'The other drivers -
including a youth
'and an old bloke - didn't look like
much of a threat either.
'But then I spotted
a familiar face.'
Where? There. It's Olivier Panis.
What, the designer?
Please tell me
you've heard of Olivier Panis?
Panis is a type of Italian bread,
isn't it?
Formula One racing driver.
Formula One.
Won the Monaco Grand Prix.
Oh, I knew that. Really? Won it.
I suppose it's unfair to ask for
tips when we're gonna thrash you,
but... Not at all.
..what would you say we had to do
to not hit things?
Well, it's quite hard, because
this car is four-wheel... Four-wheel
drive? Drive, yeah, and turning.
The rear-wheel also turning... Oh.
..it means to turn the car
much quicker.
Like yours. Yeah.
It's very, very sporting of you to
let us bring Porsche, Nissan 300ZX.
Much more powerful cars.
And the Morris. And the Morris.
It's like bringing, well, longbows
to a bow and arrow fight.
Yeah, it is, thank you. I thought
you were gonna say something really
inappropriate then. I did wonder!
I mentioned Agincourt once,
but I think I got away with it.
'With our romper suits on,
'we lined up for the ten-lap race.'
I cannot believe
I'm in a race with Olivier Panis,
France's second best racing driver.
Quite often, racers find it difficult
when they get too hot.
This won't happen today.
Here's my plan. I'm gonna take the
one in front on the left-hand side,
cut across to the right,
then I'll be alongside Panis
for the first tight right-hander.
He's bound to swing left,
they all do that in Formula One.
I'm going right.
That'll surprise him.
Here I go!
We're off!
They may have got away from us
a bit there. How did they do that?!
'It turned out
they weren't crummy hatchbacks.
'They were mid-engine rocket ships.
'So immediately, we were lapped...'
Oh, God!
Sorry!
'..and then immediately,
we were lapped again.'
HELP!
How many other cars...? HELP...ME!
'This wasn't Agincourt,
this was the Battle of Hastings.'
He's taken me.
He's taken me as well.
That's right, put me in there.
No, no, really, help yourself(!)
We're being humiliated!
You...cheese-eating...
sideways monkeys!
Olivier Panis found the Morris
particularly annoying.
What is this shitbox?!
What is this car?
A Morris.
Ow! Ow!
'Soon, it became clear
there were two races going on.
'One for people
who'd brought the right tools
'and one for those who WERE tools.'
I can't see a bloody thing!
Argh! I pulled my own glove off!
Try a Scandinavian flick.
No!
No! Oh, what the... BLEEP ?!
OK, that's them going past.
That was that Oliver man again.
I'm being lapped again!
'To make matters worse, Hammond had
turned our race into
a grudge match.'
No! What the hell?!
Ha-ha-ha! That's for throwing my roof
away, you fool! You're going off.
You're going off. No!
No! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
'Unfortunately...
'..as we knocked seven bells
out of each other...'
Sorry, mate. What are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?!
Ha-ha!
'..James was sneaking up
from the rear.'
Power.
What there is of it.
He's got me back.
Whoa!
May's got us!
That's a pass for the Marina!
You stupid idiot, Hammond!
'At this point,
the French race finished.
'And with them out of the way,
I set off after May.'
Right, come on,
must be able to catch a Marina.
Nice and smooth and straight.
Where's the corner?
There he is.
May is in my sight.
'I now had less than a lap
to get past.'
Don't hit him!
Morris extremists will come
if I hit him.
I hope you're watching this,
wife of the President of...France!
I don't believe it,
May's going to win!
It's the flag!
Surely not, not the Marina?!
I'm gonna have to kill myself!
Ah...
I believe I won. Hammond, you idiot!
What?!
You threw my roof away,
and as a result, the inside
of my windscreen froze up.
Every time I went round a corner,
there was this wildly fishtailing
Datsun!
Every time I went smoothly round
a corner, there was some idiot
in a multi-blue Porsche ramming me
and sticking me in the ditch!
I believe this is what's know as
racing drivers' excuses, isn't it?
No, I'll tell you what I believe.
What? I believe that as a result of
our... Erm, exuberance.
..revenge... Yes.
..we must now conclude
that the best rear-wheel drive car
that money can buy
is the Morris Marina!
Yes! And do you know what? What?
I think the Morris Marina
Owners' Club are gonna be
thrilled with that.
I think it will finally make amends.
They'll forgive us. They will,
finally! Finally.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
What are we gonna do?!
We're gonna be killed and eaten
by Morrismen! Look, we did explain
in the last series that we're based
next to an air-freight piano removal
company. Absolutely.
They're called Careless Air. Yes.
And now, they have a French
sister company
called Piano Avion Malheureusement.
Yes, I read about that in Helicopter
News - they're based in Val Thorens.
Exactly. So, if you're watching,
Carla Bruni, OK, wife of
the President of France,
it wasn't our fault your Marina got
broken. No. And now, gentlemen,
if I might make a suggestion...
run! Yeah, good one. See you
next week, everyone! Bye! Bye!
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk