(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(stone sizzles)
(chuckles) This sting
can't miss, boys.
I mailed these
bogus prize certificates
to every scofflaw
in Springfield.
When they show up
for their free motorboats,
we arrest them and beat them
to the full extent of the law.
(chuckles)
So the hook is baited.
Nice metaphor, Eddie.
Yeah, good work, Eddie.
♪ Up, up and away
in my beautiful ♪
♪ My beautiful motorboat ♪
♪ Tan tan ta-da-dan ♪
But we didn't enter
any police raffle.
That doesn't matter.
The important thing is we won.
(tires screeching)
I don't know.
There's something
very peculiar about this.
Sheesh!
You're the most paranoid family
I've ever been affiliated with.
(whistling)
I'd like a yellow boat,
please, with extra motors.
Yo, no cuts, bro.
Where's my motorboat, pig?
Uh, right through that door.
(titters)
(cuffs clicking)
Whoa! Yo! Ouch!
(Snake groans)
I call brutality on you.
You have the right to remain-
(chuckles)
All right, uh,
"Simpson, Homer."
-You're next.
-Whoo-hoo!
Howdy, gents.
I'm here to collect my free-
Ow! Oh, my boating arm!
What's going on?
You're under arrest, slimebag.
What's this perp in for, Lou?
Two hundred and thirty-five
unpaid parking tickets
totaling $175.
(snickers) I hope you brought
your checkbook, wise guy.
You lousy cops.
Lucky for you
I'm double-parked or I'd--
There. Now, could I
please have my motorboat?
Dad, why aren't you
saying anything?
Where's our motorboat?
I didn't like it.
The mast had termites.
Why would a motorboat
have a mast?
Because!
The thing, it was... shut up!
(tires screeching)
Whoo! There's that new
mega-mall they're building.
They say
the air conditioner will be
more powerful
than a million hydrogen bombs.
Hey, they can't just
build a parking lot
on Sabertooth Meadow!
That's where they discovered
all those fossils.
Fossils, schmossils.
You can't stop progress
'cause of some moldy old bones.
Bones, schmones.
But they might be paving
over rare specimens.
Pull over
so we can complain, Dad.
Come on!
Who wants to complain with me?
Fine. I'll come back later.
Who wants to come back with me?
(mutters) Fine.
My attorney, Lionel Hutz,
calls your attention
to municipal code 147-C-
"protection of
antiquities and fossils."
That's right.
There aren't any fossils here,
little girl.
Museum folks
dug 'em all up years ago.
But what if they
missed something?
You have to allow
an archaeological survey.
Who's gonna make us? You?
(laughing)
Now, hold on, Sid. Hold on.
May be we should
let the kid dig.
Could be good publicity.
(indistinct whispering)
Oh, yes.
I'd rather do that.
OK. You wanna dig? Be my guest.
Fine! We'll see you in court!
-Mr. Hutz, we won.
-"We"?
Principal Skinner,
remember how I didn't sue
when I found that scorpion
in my applesauce?
Well, I'm calling in a favor.
Mm, I knew
this day would come.
SKINNER: Attention.
All honor students
will be rewarded
with a trip
to an archaeological dig!
(cheering)
Conversely, all detention
students will be punished
with a trip
to an archaeological dig.
-Oh, no. Not tomorrow.
-Oh, crud.
♪ Gonna dig me a hole ♪
♪ Gonna put a nerd in it ♪
♪ Gonna take a firecracker ♪
This is so exciting.
I can't wait to see
what we find.
I must admit,
it is rather exciting. And--
Look!
Here's something right here.
It appears to be
some sort of rock.
Oh, no, no.
It's just a clump of dirt.
(chuckles) Even so, my heart
is pounding like a kettle drum.
I'd better
sit down for a moment.
"Prinskipper Skippal"
"Prinnipple Skipper"-
I-I found something!
(teachers, students exclaiming)
-(gasps)
-RALPH: It's a spearhead!
That's your
trowel blade, Ralph.
It fell off the handle.
And I found it!
OK, everyone, back to work!
You never know when we might
uncover a tyrannosaurus.
(screams)
(whimpering)
(snoring)
(grunting)
(snickering)
Well, this was a big bust.
Come on, kids.
Let's go home to our mothers.
Don't give up.
I'm sure we'll find something.
(grunts) Come on. Come on!
A bottle cap, a shoe,
a bar of gold-- anything!
(exclaims)
(gasps) Everybody, come quick!
(indistinct chattering)
CLANCY WIGGUM:
Hey, what is that?
Hope it's not-
Let me through.
I got here late.
(crowd chattering)
Hmm, from the looks of it,
I'd say this fellow died
from causes unknown.
(laughs)
Look, there's more!
What the heck is this thing?
Speaking from a strictly medical
point of view, that ain't right.
(gasps) Oh, my goodness!
What is it, Lisa?
It looks like a human skeleton.
But these other bones
look almost like wings.
You mean, like... an angel?
Well, obviously,
that's impossible.
Lisa's right. It's an angel!
(gasps)
HOMER: Now, that's
interesting.
(chattering continues)
But it can't be an angel!
Oh, no?
Well, if you're so sure
what it ain't,
how about telling us
what it am?
(onlookers clamoring)
Well, maybe it's, uh...
uh, a neanderthal who got bitten
by some angry fish.
(whiny grunt)
(muttering, cries out)
(screaming)
(chuckles)
Oh, I got to say, Lisa.
It sounds like you're straining
to do some explaining.
Yeah, everyone's heard
of angels, but...
Who's ever heard of
a "neanderthal"?
(chuckles)
It could be anything.
It could be a mutant
from the nuclear plant.
Oh, fiddle-faddle.
Everyone knows
our mutants have flippers.
Ooh, oops. I've said too much.
(clears throat)
Smithers, use the amnesia ray.
-You mean, the revolver, sir?
-Precisely.
Be sure to wipe your own memory
clear when you're finished.
Now, regardless
of what this thing is,
it's a priceless
scientific find.
So our most
pressing concern now
is determining who owns
such a valuable skeleton.
And I'd like to suggest
that I do.
(onlookers protesting)
WOMAN: Excuse me.
I'd like to hear
from Lionel Hutz.
It's a thorny legal issue,
all right.
I'll need to refer to the case
of finders versus keepers.
Oh, we can work this out,
friends.
In the spirit of sharing,
what say we simply place
-the sacred bones--
-(horn honking)
So long, suckers!
(grunting)
Come on. Come on, angel.
-(grunts)
-What are you doing with that?
I'm locking it up
in my safe-deposit closet
with my other valuables.
I'll just leave it
in here a few years
and let it appreciate in value.
It's probably
a million years old, Dad.
I think it's as valuable
as it's gonna get.
(scoffs)
That's what they said about
this billy beer, smarty-pants.
(sighs)
We elected the wrong Carter.
KENT (on TV):
Coming up next,
an hilarious boat
giveaway scam,
nets Springfield's
dumbest criminals.
(laughs)
Sounds like good watching.
(doorbell rings)
He-hey there, Marge.
Just brought the kids over
to share a prayer with
the blessed angel,
if it's okay with you.
HOMER (shouting): Get your own
angel, you moocher!
(sighs) Thanks anyway, Homer.
(doorbell rings)
Oh, hello, Agnes.
Sorry to trouble you,
but I'm going in
for surgery tomorrow
and I wondered if I could
rub the angel with my foot
for good luck.
It's foot surgery.
HOMER:
Hey, I'm trying to eat here!
Beat it, peg leg!
Jackass!
Marge.
We wanna see the angel.
(crowd clamoring)
Come on, Homer.
I just want a quick look-see.
-Pay you a buck.
-A buck, eh?
That gives me an idea.
-Fifty cents, please.
-(coins clattering)
(Homer's voice)
♪ Here's the angel ♪
♪ See the angel
it's my angel ♪
♪ No one else's
next to the rags ♪
Dad, it's not fair to claim
this thing is an angel.
There's no proof of that.
No one's
calling it an angel, Lisa.
If you look carefully,
you'll notice I never
once used the word "angel."
What about
that sign right there?
That's a typo.
Just let me take it
to the museum for one day.
They can do scientific tests
and prove it's not an angel.
Oh, no. Oh, no. We could lose
out on bags and bags of money.
It's sacrilegious, I tell ya.
(door creaking)
Wow, it's so lifelike.
(moaning)
(gulps)
DR. GOULD: Astonishing.
Simply astonishing.
One of the most singular
specimens I've encountered
in all my distinguished career.
But enough about my work.
What did you
want to show me, Lisa?
It's a bone scraping
from that skeleton I found.
Oh, yeah. The so-called angel.
The whole thing's
preposterous, of course.
Quite preposterous.
But no one will believe me
until I can prove what it really is.
Can't you do a DNA test
or something?
Certainly. I'll have
the results by tomorrow.
Oh, thank you so much.
Um, you know,
I can't afford to pay you.
I didn't become a scientist
for financial gain.
Whatever little money
you have will be just fine.
I say it's the angel of peace,
you idiot.
I say it's the angel of mercy,
you jerk.
LISA: Excuse me.
I took a piece of the skeleton
for scientific analysis.
Soon we'll have all the facts.
You did what?
You know what?
I don't like that.
(scoffs)
Facts are meaningless.
You can use
facts to prove anything
that's even remotely true.
Facts, schmacts.
-(panting)
-Ah, here's Dr. Gould now.
What were the results,
professor?
Inconclusive.
"Inconclusive"?
Then why'd you come
running up like that?
Can I use your bathroom?
(groans)
Well, it appears science
has faltered once again
in the face of overwhelming
religious evidence.
-But--
-Go home, science girl.
I am home.
Good. Stay there.
OK, folks.
Get your "angel glow sticks."
No one gets into heaven
without a glow stick.
I'll take four.
Agh! Those morons
make me so angry.
Maybe so, but I'd appreciate it
if you didn't call them morons.
But they are morons.
What grown person
could believe in angels?
Well...
Your mother, for one.
You?
But, y-you're
an intelligent person, Mom.
There has to be more to life
than just what we see, Lisa.
Everyone needs
something to believe in.
It's not that I don't have
a spiritual side.
I just find it hard to believe
there's a dead angel
hanging in our garage.
Hmm. My poor Lisa.
If you can't make a leap
of faith now and then,
well, I feel sorry for you.
Don't feel sorry for me, Mom.
I feel sorry for you.
KENT:
Next on Smartline,
the Springfield
angel controversy.
Our guest tonight, making her 13th
appearance on Smartline,
-Miss Lisa Simpson.
-Kent.
Miss Simpson, how can you
maintain your skepticism
in spite of the fact
this thing really,
really looks like an angel?
I just think it's a fantasy.
If you believe in angels,
then why not unicorns
or sea monsters or leprechauns?
Oh, that's a bunch of baloney, Lisa!
Everyone knows
leprechauns are extinct.
Look, you can either accept
science and face reality
or you can believe in angels
and live in a childish dreamworld.
Science? What's science
ever done for us?
TV off.
Science is like a blabbermouth
who ruins a movie
by telling you how it ends.
Well, I say
there are some things
we don't wanna know,
important things.
Yeah, he's right!
Enough talk.
It's smashing time!
(indistinct screams)
(mob yelling)
Take that and that and--
(groans) I'm paralyzed.
I just hope medical science
can cure me.
(screaming continues)
Why? Why was I programmed
to feel pain?
Technocrats are learning
a lesson in humility tonight
as angel supporters lay waste
to Springfield's
scientific institutions.
Ugh! I wish I'd never found
those stupid bones!
It's time to put
an end to this.
Bart, I'm borrowing
your blue crowbar.
Good ol' blue-y.
Hey, she's gonna
smash the angel!
Somebody stop her!
(gasps)
It's gone!
(weeping) Oh, no!
This can't be happening!
What the hell are we gonna do
with 10,000 angel ashtrays?
-I could take up smoking.
-You damn well better.
Okay. Okay, don't panic.
Marge, stop panicking!
We need a replacement skeleton,
and we need it now.
Bart, strip down
to your skeleton.
(door opening)
We've come
for the angel, Homer.
It's not safe
with the unbeliever.
It's gone! We're too late.
Little girl, what have you done
with our precious angel?
Nothing!
Someone must have stolen it.
Looks to me like Lisa Simpson
found something
science couldn't explain,
so she had to destroy it.
Well, that's all the evidence
I need. Arrest the girl.
-(gasps) Hey!
-What? She didn't do anything.
Give her a nice cell--
something in "C" block.
Lisa Simpson, you are charged
with destruction of an historic curiosity,
a misdemeanor.
But in a larger sense,
this trial will settle
the age-old question
of science versus religion.
Let the opening
statements commence.
Your Honor, over the coming
weeks and months,
we intend to prove Lisa Simpson
willfully destroyed--
There's the angel!
(murmuring)
(shouting, chattering)
I find the defendant
not guilty.
As for science versus religion,
I'm issuing a restraining order.
Religion must stay 500 yards
from science at all times.
(chattering continues)
Wow!
Do you think it flew up here?
Well, it didn't
ride up on no zebra.
Look, a message!
"The end will
come at sundown."
(laughing) Hey...
Wait a second.
I don't like the sound of that.
I'm scared, Daddy.
Too scared
to even wet my pants.
It's OK, son.
Just relax, and it'll come.
Even Lisa Simpson
must now agree.
We have witnessed a miracle.
Hardly.
Anyone could've written that.
Oh, angel, listen not
to this child of Satan.
Reverend, I've got to admit.
This doomsday warning
has me just a smidge twitterpated.
Oh, now, be calm, Ned.
But be afraid also,
tremendously afraid
for the day
of reckoning is upon us!
(gasping, murmuring)
Reckoning?
Your Holiness,
there is word from America.
They say an angel
has foretold the apocalypse.
Um, keep an eye on it.
MRS. KRABAPPEL: This could be
our last day together, my love.
How about a farewell romp
in the garden of earthly delights?
Oh, Edna, my sweet buttercup,
you read my mind.
Just, uh, give me 20 minutes
or so to finish
these tardy slips.
Why we getting dressed-up, Mom?
Are we going to Black Angus?
Well, you might say we're going
to the best steakhouse
in the whole universe.
So we're not going
to Black Angus.
Will you leave me alone?
It's bad enough
you're making me
go to your stupid judgment day.
Please, Lisa.
I don't know
exactly what's gonna happen.
But I really wish we could
make peace before sunset.
Nothing is going
to happen, Mom!
I hate to disappoint you,
but the world
is not coming to an end.
Well, shall we sing a hymn?
Uh, "Nearer,
My God, to Thee" maybe?
Or-or-or-or "Amazing Grace"?
Mm. Nah.
Oh, Marge.
Don't let go, no matter what.
If they want you in heaven,
they got to take me, too.
Ten seconds till sundown.
(indistinct chatter)
(taking deep drag)
(huffing exhale)
We did it. We beat cancer.
Oh, what the hell?
Mwah!
Seven, six...
Five, four,
three, two, one.
(all gasping)
(crickets chirping)
(all sigh)
(all muttering)
Well, there you go.
I hope you all learned a val--
MALE VOICE: Silence!
(all gasp)
(all gasping)
Prepare for the end!
(whimpering)
The end of high prices!
What?
Ooh.
Behold!
The grand opening
of the Heavenly Hills Mall.
Please just follow the angel
for all your shopping needs!
(mechanized whirring)
Wait a second!
You planted a phony skeleton
for me to find!
This was all a big hoax!
(chuckles)
Not a hoax, a publicity stunt.
You exploited
people's deepest beliefs
just to hawk your cheesy wares?
Well, we are outraged!
Aren't we?
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we're outraged.
Very, uh, very much so.
But look at all the stores!
A-a pottery barn!
And 20% off everything?
Hey, does that
include rat spray?
Oh, yeah.
-Out of my way, shorty!
-Hey!
(all clamoring)
I don't understand, professor.
Why didn't your tests
show the skeleton was a fake?
I'm gonna be honest
with you, Lisa.
I never did the tests.
(electrical current sizzling)
(excited chattering)
Uh, sir, about that, uh...
that kiss-l-I hope
you understand it was merely
a sign of my respect.
Yes. Yes, of course.
Well, I guess
you were right, honey.
But you have to admit,
when that angel started to talk
you were squeezing
my hand pretty hard.
(embarrassed chuckle) Well, it was just
so loud and... (laughs)
Thanks for squeezing back.
Anytime, my angel.
(theme music playing)
Shh.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services