(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
(indistinct chatter)
Well, your cholesterol level
is lethally high, Homer,
but I'm more concerned
about your gravy level.
Now, wait a second.
You doctors
have been telling us
to drink eight glasses
of gravy a day.
(laughs)
Well, you're a little confused.
Oh, confused, would we?
OK, gentlemen.
I want you to raise your hand
when you hear the tone.
You can't tell me what to do.
(tone)
(louder tone)
Nothing yet.
(people grunting)
Now, make no mistake.
When I say "first aid,"
I'm not talking about some sort
of charity rock concert.
(laughing)
I'm talking about
treating serious injuries.
(laughing)
(chuckles)
Serious injuries.
Oh, that's gold.
(woodenly) Mom. Mom.
I stepped in a bear trap.
Sounds like you need
some first aid.
(murmuring agreement)
-Bravo.
-All right.
(grunts)
Come on.
You can't do one sit-up?
(panting) I loved your last
McBain movie,
Mr. Wolfcastle.
Quit stalling, fatty.
(inhaling)
We can wait.
-(exhales)
-Come to papa.
-(grunting)
-Come on.
Even my fat mama
can touch her toes.
-(cloth tearing)
-Hey, Bart.
We wear the same underpants.
Results from yesterday's
health fair are in
and the news is not good.
Springfield is in terrible shape,
particularly our young boys.
(grunting)
(cloth tearing)
(laughing)
Hey, tubby.
Want another pop-tart, tubby?
I'm comfortable with who I am.
(muffled) You're a disgrace
to this family.
In this reporter's opinion,
it's time for our
lard-laden lads to shape up,
get out and try fun activities,
like military service,
frenetic dancing,
or good, old-fashioned
peewee football.
There you go, Bart.
Peewee football will melt away
those unsightly
pounds and inches.
Yeah, but I could get seriously hurt.
Then it's settled.
We don't have to play football,
do we, Daddy?
(chuckles)
You betcha.
Team sports will keep you away
from temptations
like rock music and girls.
(cheering)
You know, Milhouse,
you are getting
a little doughy.
Aw!
Can't I just have the surgery?
He's going to need a...
You know-- protection.
Sure. One helmet coming up.
I was thinking more like
protection for...
(quietly) Down there.
Oh, why didn't you say so?
Knee pads. You got it.
(nervous laugh)
I'm talking about his...
(mutters) Personal area.
Aha! Say no more.
I read you loud and clear.
The old shoulder pads.
Look, I want a cup!
"Cup"? Could you spell that?
C-U-P.
I want a C-U...
Oh, my God!
OK, Milhouse,
let's try out the new cup.
-(grunts)
-(laughs)
Again!
-(grunts)
-(yawns)
(grunting)
MARGE: Milhouse, stop that!
-(grunts)
-A little higher, Wendell.
-(chuckles)
-A lot higher, Martin.
-RALPH: (grunts)
Uh, Ralph, that's a basketball.
(grunts)
(gasps)
OK, Nelson's our quarterback.
Thanks, four-eyes.
Ralph, you'll be
on special teams.
I'm special!
And, uh, Bart,
you'll be a tackle.
Cool!
(grunts)
Careful, Bart!
You'll break my calculator--
By which, I mean my head.
LISA: What position
have you got for me?
BOYS: What? Huh?
That's right.
A girl wants to play football.
How about that?
Well, that's super duper, Lisa.
In fact, we already have
four girls on the team.
-You do?
-Uh-huh,
but we'd love
to have you on board.
Well...
Football's not really my thing.
After all,
what civilized person
would play a game
with the skin
of an innocent pig?
(chuckles) Well, actually, Lisa,
these balls are synthetic.
And for every ball we buy,
a dollar goes
to Amnesty International.
I've got to go.
Who are we?
The Wildcats!
Who are we gonna beat?
The Wildcats.
Hey, Flanders!
You're the worst coach
this team has ever had!
He's the only coach
this team has ever had,
and the season hasn't
even started yet.
Yeah, well...
He's wearing that hat
like an idiot.
You know, Homer,
it's very easy to criticize.
Fun, too.
All right, Wildcats,
are you ready to give 110%,
take it one game at a time
and go the whole nine yards?
Yeah! Nine yards!
Okely-dokely.
Let's put on our game faces.
(indistinct chatter)
(grunts)
Got it.
Gimme the ball,
and your lunch money.
I love this game.
(cheering, whistling)
Ooh! He's quite
a little dancer.
Oh, you got lucky, Flanders.
And fix that hat!
Yeah. Thanks
for the tip, Homer.
OK, Simpson, you're blocking
for me on this play.
All right!
(growls)
Oops.
Hut-hut, hike-hike, hut!
(grunts)
It's clobberin' time.
(grunting)
You OK, Bart?
(squeaks) Yeah.
-(whistles)
-(cheering)
I'm special!
(gasps) (laughs)
(cheering)
Eh, big deal.
I been carried out of Moe's
like that hundreds of times.
Yeah, I'm telling you,
Flanders can't coach at all.
Now, I'm not the type to have
a grudge for no reason...
Sir, if I could
just break in for a moment.
HOMER: Yes, Roy?
Do you have a question
for Sandy Koufax?
Yes. Mr. Koufax, don't you think
Flanders is a big jerk?
-(line disconnects)
-Y'ello? Y'ello?
(keypad beeping)
Yeah. Homer again.
I think we got cut off.
-(line disconnects)
-Y'ello?
(keypad beeping)
BOY: 5F03, hut!
(all grunting)
(audience cheering)
Flan-ders!
What?
What? What is it?
Game's out there.
(laughing)
Made you look.
(grumbling)
They're just words, Neddy.
Words can't hurt you.
Ow! That's it!
Dad, that was really mean.
I know, sweetie,
and I got him right
in the... Uh-oh.
(nervous chuckle)
H-hi, Flanders.
(quietly) Go, Wildcats.
Do you have a problem
with the way I'm coaching?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's just that, well,
like I was yelling earlier,
it seems like anyone
with half a brain
could coach better than you.
Uh-huh! Half a brain, huh?
Well, you know what?
It sounds like you
just volunteered.
Me? But you were doing
such a great job.
(groans)
(yelling)
You're not going
to make the team
with that kind of attitude.
I don't want to make the team.
Then why are you running
the obstacle course?
Are you wearing
my self-defense whistle?
You never use it.
-(grumbles)
-(whistling)
Good morning, everybody.
Wipe that smile off your face.
What did I do?
I'm tired
of watching you dog it
on that football field.
From now on, I'm going
to work you like a dog.
Now, go fetch me 20 laps.
-Oh, man.
-Do it.
You shouldn't pressure Bart
like that.
Well, if you know a better way
for me to live through my son,
I'd like to hear it.
(panting)
I knew it.
Slowing down already, huh?
How can you treat him that way?
Don't you remember
how bad your father made you feel
when you played sports?
Well, that's the end
of the girls' floor exercise.
Now, let's bring on the men!
Wish me luck, Dad.
Just don't screw up
like you always do.
("Music Box Dancer" playing)
Wow! He's dy-no-mite!
What's his name again?
(inhales sharply)
You're going to blow it!
(gasping)
Ah!
That's what I get
for havin' faith in ya.
(sadly) Oh, my father
never believed in me.
Well, I'm not going
to make the same mistake.
From now on, I'm going
to be kinder to my son
and meaner to my dad.
Quit running, son.
I just want
to give you a big hug.
BART: It's got to be a trick.
Run like the wind.
I believe in you!
Hug me!
(grunting)
Will you hug me?
Hug me!
(whistle blows)
Good practice, team.
OK, it's time for the easiest part
of any coach's job--
The cuts.
Now, while I wasn't able
to cut everyone I wanted to,
I have cut a lot of you.
Wendell is cut.
Rudy is cut.
Janey, you're gone.
Steven, I like your hustle.
That's why it was
so hard to cut you.
Congratulations.
The rest of you made the team.
(all sigh)
Except you, you and you.
Bart didn't get cut.
What a surprise.
Now, just because
I'm his father,
he'll get no special treatment.
He calls me "coach"
just like everyone else,
which he'll be doing
as our new starting quarterback.
What? Get out of here!
Aw, man! No way!
What a rip!
-But, coach...
-What is it, sweetie?
Nelson's a great quarterback.
He's carrying this team.
ALL: Yeah, that's right.
Not anymore.
From now on,
you're my main man.
OK, now, everyone,
give me five laps
and hit the showers.
Oh, Rod, you don't have to.
You're cut.
BART:
But I can't play quarterback.
I don't even know how.
Son, you can do
anything you want.
I have total faith in you.
-Since when?
-Since your mother yelled at me.
-Now, how about that hug?
-(tires screech)
Dad, the car!
I got it.
Good luck, Homer.
No hard feelings.
Not so easy
to keep your mouth shut now,
is it, Flanders?
Ready, set, hut!
Hut!
(grunt)
(screams)
It's OK, son.
You'll do better next time.
No, please, Bart, don't!
Ooh!
Help. Help, help.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look at him go!
No, no. Uh.
Excellent poise, son.
You panicked,
but you didn't lose your cool.
(groans)
Bart, over here! Come on!
(all yelling)
Just throw it, doofus.
Aw, crap.
Great debut, son.
You really settled in
after some early jitters.
Are you kidding? I reeked.
Oh, really?
Do reeky players
get the game ball?
Hey, everybody,
let's hear it for Bart!
Give me a "B"?
I won't give you a "B",
but I'll tear you a new "A."
If I wasn't your friend,
I'd tell you you sucked.
You ruined
our undefeated season.
You ruined everything, ruiner!
My sister likes you.
Listen here, daddy's boy.
You cost us one more game,
and you're dead.
You're going to heaven.
Oh!
Oh, it's going
to take a miracle
for me to become
a good quarterback.
(gate creaking)
Excuse me, son.
Wow, Joe Namath!
That's right. My car broke
down in front of your house.
I cannot believe you are here.
Do you think maybe
you could give me some pointers?
Sure. There's only one thing
you need to know
to be a great quarterback.
-(car engine revving)
-WOMAN: Joe, honey, I fixed it.
It was just vapor lock.
Ah. Oops.
Hey, look, I got to run.
Remember what I told you.
OK, Bart, concentrate.
NAMATH:
Remember what I told you.
Just one thing.
My car broke down.
I'm Joe Namath.
WOMAN: It was just vapor lock.
Vapor lock... Vapor lock...
Vapor lock.
I'm dead.
So if I play, the guys
are going to kill me.
If I don't, I'll be
letting Homer down.
What am I going to do?
Well, I know you don't want
to disappoint Dad,
but how do you feel
about lying to him?
Good.
Oh, you guys are so cut.
Dad, I got some bad news.
Oh, your mother's not pregnant,
is she?
No. I got hit
by a couple of cars.
I won't be able to play today.
BOTH: Yes!
Oh, boy.
Well, I'll just have to go
to my backup plan.
Nelson, how's your arm feeling?
-Great!
-Good.
Take this note
over to the referee.
"We forfeit"?
Forfeit? What?
Come on. Oh, man.
Come on, guys.
We can't play without Bart.
He's the heart of this team.
No, I'm not. I suck.
It's true. He does.
(all agreeing)
Yeah, he does. Yeah.
Don't listen to them, son.
I have total faith in you.
(grunts)
You don't get it, do you?
I don't want to be
your stupid quarterback.
I quit!
What?
Well, I got news for you,
mister.
You can't quit.
You're cut!
You, too, Milhouse.
All right!
(munching)
So, like I said,
I've never had a tick
burrow in so deep.
Little guy's just
got a mind of his own.
Mom, please! We're eating.
Well, at least
I'm making conversation.
May I be excused, Mom?
Oh, so now
you're quitting dinner, too.
Homer, please.
I didn't raise him
to be a quitter, Marge.
It must have been you.
You quit every job
you've ever had--
Cop, pretzel vendor,
church counselor,
professional gambler...
He's doing
what he thinks is best.
Well, if quitting is the best,
maybe I should just quit my job.
Ahoy-hoy?
Mr. Burns,
this is Homer J. Simpson,
the father of the big quitter.
Well, I just wanted to tell you
I'm a big quitter, too,
and I quit.
MARGE: Homer, Mr. Burns
can't see you winking.
So? (shrieks)
NELSON: Yellow, 25, hut!
Go long!
-Go long!
-(other boys grunting)
Aw, hell, I'll do it myself.
(crowd cheering)
(heavily panting)
I got to quit smoking.
We drove 2,000 miles for this?
We're in the championship.
Way to go, team!
Gee, thanks, coach.
(motorcycle revving)
Great game, son.
Come on, I'm taking
you to hooters.
Aw, I don't want
to bother Mom at work.
Well, Bart, looks like
it's just you and...
Oh.
FEMALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
I'll scratch you.
The hair! The hair!
-Slut!
-Loser!
Skank! Skank! Skank!
I'm feeling kind of low, Apu.
Got any of that beer
that has candy floating in it?
You know, Skittlebrau.
Such a product
does not exist, sir.
I think
you must have dreamed it.
Oh. Well, then just
give me a six-pack
and a couple of bags
of Skittles.
Hello, son.
I want to apologize.
I just got so caught up
trying to encourage you,
I was blinded
to your stinky performance.
If you forgive me
I promise I'll never
encourage you again.
I've got lots of quarters.
This thing only takes dollars.
Aw...
You know, tomorrow's
the championship game
and I could sure use
a good offensive tackle.
I thought Uter took my place.
Consider him cut.
(grunts)
MARGE: Wow!
Homer coaching
in the championship game.
You must be pretty proud
of your son.
You'd think so, wouldn't you?
(snoring)
Time for one last play, coach.
Hold on, I'm working it out.
OK. Half of you vibrate
that way,
two of you fall down...
Nelson, you just spin around
in a circle.
(siren wailing)
All right, I've got
an arrest warrant here
for Nelson Muntz.
Uh, which one
of you little punks is Muntz?
Oh, no, my quarterback!
What are we going to do?
It's OK, Dad.
I can fill in for Nelson.
Are you sure, son?
I knew I could count on you.
(boys grunting)
(cheering)
(snoring)
(laughs) (gasps)
So, what's the charge, chief?
Vandalism? Smoking?
You know what you did, Muntz--
Burglary and arson.
You're going away
for a long time.
Wha...
-(siren wails)
-(chuckling)
Poor Bart.
You know,
we had a lot of fun tonight,
but there's nothing funny
about... Vapor lock.
It's the third most
common cause of car stallings,
so, please, take care
of your car and get it checked.
I'm Joe Namath.
Good night.
HOMER: Scully, you're cut.
Uh, Brooks, Groening, Simon,
you're all cut.
Castellaneta, gone.
Kavner, cut. Can'twright, cut.
Smith, sorry. Cut.
Azaria and Shearer, you're cut.
Firestone, you're cut.
So is Judge. Namath, you stay.
All of those people are cut.
Bill Schultz and Wolf
and Silverman. Goldfreyer.
O'Brlen, Doyle, Selman,
I don't know what you--
Elliott, l-I don't know what you're
doing here because you're all cut.
Pietlla, Bridge
and "Kuwawahawa."
Now there's so many cuts here--
look, I'll just post 'em up
and you just see
where your name is.
Ooh, look at how many cuts
there are there.
Oh, boy! You're cut!
All of you!
He's cut. I cut you!
-Shh!
-HOMER: You're cut too, shushy!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services