♪ Timmy is an average kid ♪
♪ That no one understands ♪
♪ Mom and Dad and Vicky ♪
♪ Always giving him commands ♪
Bed, twerp!
♪ Doom and gloom,
up in his room ♪
♪ Is broken instantly ♪
♪ By his magic little fish ♪
♪ Who grant his every wish ♪
♪ 'Cause in reality ♪
♪ They are his Odd Parents ♪
♪ Fairly Odd Parents ♪
Wands and wings!
Floaty crowny things!
♪ Odd Parents,
Fairly Odd Parents ♪
♪ Really mod, pea pod,
buff bod, hot rod ♪
Obtuse, rubber goose,
green moose, guava juice.
Giant snake, birthday cake,
large fries, chocolate shake!
♪ Odd Parents,
Fairly Odd Parents ♪
♪ It flips your lid
when you are the kid ♪
♪ With Fairly Odd Parents! ♪
Yeah, right.
( bell rings )
♪ On the first day of Christmas
my true love gave to me ♪
♪ A partridge
in a pear tree... ♪
Yes, with the partridge
and pear tree shortage over,
it's Christmastime again.
Good evening, Dimmsdale.
It's Christmas,
and I'm Chet Youbetcha.
Yes, Christmas.
( cheering and applause )
Better than Easter, more loving
than Valentine's Day,
and nowhere near as useless
as Arbor Day.
( thudding )
Even the bitterest of enemies
have put
their differences aside
as everyone anxiously prepares
for the arrival of Santy Claus.
I'm Chet Youbetcha
saying I ho-ho-hope
you have a merry Christmas.
( groans )
What's wrong,
Timmy?
Merry Christmas,
Cosmo?
I bet he never had to spend
Christmas Eve with Vicky.
Hey, Frosty the snow twerp,
got some more fruitcakes
for you to wrap.
Come on, sport,
cheer up.
I can't, Wanda.
Every Christmas Eve,
I'm stuck doing
whatever Vicky tells me to do.
I know. Remember last Christmas
when she sold you
and your friends
as ice sculptures?
( tires squealing )
Ooh-hoo-hoo!
I'll take the Chester
and A.J. ice sculptures.
Timmy will love these.
So cold!
I'm free!
Man...
every Christmas Eve,
my parents are out shopping
and I'm stuck here
with Vicky.
But it's worth it,
because tomorrow's Christmas,
the greatest day ever!
Incoming!
( engine whirring )
That's the last one.
( forklift beeping )
Who are all these gifts for?
Nobody.
I just like making you work.
Merry Christmas, Timmy.
We're ho-ho-home.
( chuckling )
Oh, I'm in the spirit.
( "We Wish You a Merry
Christmas" plays )
Merry Christmas,
Mr. and Mrs. Turner.
Is it time
for my Christmas bonus?
Yup. This year,
you get to leave early.
MRS. TURNER:
Bye, Vicky.
Wow, a Vicky
snowman.
Vicky's gone!
Which means it's time
to decorate the house!
All right!
Tomorrow's Christmas!
Uh, you don't have
to work or shop
or do anything
that would make you
bring Vicky back here, right?
No. All we have
to do tomorrow
is be with you, Timmy.
And drink eggnog.
I mean,
be with you, Noggy.
Come on. Come on.
( rooster crows )
It's Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
Egg ( snores ) nog.
( snores ):
Eggnog.
Merry Christmas!
Mine!
I mean, mine me Christmas,
Timmy.
Come on!
Let's go see what Santa brought.
( gasps )
Wow! It's amazing.
And I don't have
to share any of this.
I love being an only child.
Geronimo!
Mine!
( submarine beeping )
I love the smell of Christmas
in the morning.
( helicopter whirring )
Dive, dive, dive!
♪ Christmas day is here
once more ♪
♪ Gifts and love
and joy galore ♪
♪ A special day
that wipes the floor ♪
♪ With the other 364 ♪
♪ I wish every day
could be Christmas ♪
♪ 'Cause Santa brings gifts
every year ♪
♪ He's reading my list ♪
♪ He's feeding the deer ♪
♪ He's hauling my gifts
from the North Pole to here ♪
♪ I wish
every day could be Christmas ♪
♪ 'Cause every other
holiday reeks ♪
♪ New Years Eve's
for Mom and Dad ♪
♪ The Easter Bunny's eggs
smell really bad ♪
♪ Valentine's Day always
makes me sad ♪
♪ 'Cause Timmy just can't
get a girlfriend ♪
What?
♪ I wish every day
could be Christmas ♪
♪ 'Cause nice fairies
get their rewards ♪
♪ I got pudding,
I got slacks ♪
♪ I got all my back hair waxed ♪
♪ Santa grants wishes
while we relax ♪
♪ And Timmy still can't
get a girlfriend ♪
Stop that!
♪ There's just no other day
like Christmas ♪
♪ My family stays here,
it's real cool ♪
♪ Just me, Mom and Dad,
I'm so very glad ♪
♪ There's no Vicky,
no Vicky, no school ♪
And no Vicky.
Right.
♪ I wish every day
could be Christmas ♪
♪ Then I'd get the best gift
of all ♪
♪ My parents stay home to say ♪
♪ We love you, Noggy ♪
Mine!
♪ Wouldn't Christmas each day
be the coolest of all? ♪
♪ I wish it were Christmas ♪
♪ How I wish it were Christmas ♪
♪ Each day. ♪
( snoring and sighing )
Well, he said "I wish."
I know.
( beep )
I just wish he didn't.
( electronic whirring )
( rooster crowing )
It's Christmas!
Again!
( snores ):
Egg... nog.
Eggnog.
Merry Christmas again.
But honey,
you have to go to school,
and we have to go to work.
No, you don't.
Look!
♪ On the second day
of Christmas ♪
♪ My true love gave to me ♪
♪ Two turtle doves ♪
♪ And a partridge
in a pear tree. ♪
Well... okay.
The calendar's never
lied to me yet.
See.
Santa came again.
It's Christmas again!
Geronimo... again!
Cosmo, Wanda, you did it!
It's Christmas again.
Well, that was
one big wish
you made, Sport.
But there's something
we really should tell you.
I've never been happier.
So, what were you going to say?
Uh...
Dive, dive, dive!
( train horn blowing )
We hope you
enjoyed your
second day
of Christmas,
Timmy.
These have been the best
two Christmases ever.
Wouldn't it be great
if we could be together
like this all the time?
It sure would, Timmy,
but your mother and I have
to work.
Eggnog doesn't buy itself,
you know.
No, you don't.
If it kept being Christmas,
I just don't know
what we'd do.
We'd probably panic.
Oh, well, good night.
It's Christmas!
BOTH:
Again?
It's Christmas.
BOTH:
Again?
Geronimo.
( thud )
Hey, this is a toy puddle.
Where's my toy ocean?
Well, you know, Timmy,
I'm sure
Santa's doing the best he can.
( "Pop Goes the Weasel" plays )
He's never had
to make toys
for this many
Christmases before.
Well, honey, if we're going
to have a fourth day
of Christmas,
I have to get more eggnog!
And I'm good with that.
Oh, thanks, Lockjaw.
All right! Nog!
( singing listlessly ):
♪ It's the 15th day
of Christmas ♪
♪ And my true love gave
to me... ♪
Pants?
Uh, yeah, pants.
Pants.
Okay.
Wow! 15 Christmases
and counting.
I know.
This is the best!
Right?
NEWSMAN:
This is the worst.
It's ho-ho-horrible.
As Christmas enters
its third week,
the world screams,
"Christmas is entering
its third week!"
Because it's still Christmas,
the banks are still closed.
ALL:
We want money!
To buy eggnog!
Stores are closed.
ALL:
We want food!
And eggnog.
To buy.
And the schools remain closed.
I'm good with this.
Everywhere, adults are doing
all that they can
to prevent yet another visit
from Santa.
And military forces across
the globe remain on high alert.
( bells jingling )
Deploy the decoy chimney.
Release the cookies and milk.
Everybody pretend to be asleep.
( cloth ripping )
I hope I get a football.
Hmm...
cookies.
( lasers firing )
What is the matter
with you people?
I'm just doing my job.
As the world falls apart
at the seams,
people everywhere are asking,
"Who is responsible for this,
and how can we tear them
limb from limb?!"
Uh, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Yeah, he's cute
when he's angry.
That may be true,
but I think the world
has had enough Christmas
for one year.
I wish it wasn't
Christmas anymore.
Uh, we can't
do that, Timmy.
We don't have
enough power.
What do you mean?
What's going on?
Who are you guys?
I'm the Easter Bunny.
These are the other holidays.
And you are in a lot
of trouble, kid.
I'm in trouble?
What did I do?
Your stupid "Christmas
every day" wish
means the rest
of us holidays
don't get to deliver joy
to the kids of the world
ever again.
Who are you brightly
colored freaks?
I'm the Easter Bunny.
That's Baby New Year.
( deep voice ):
Goo.
It's going
to be a big year.
Cupid, from
Valentine's Day.
Sometimes...
love hurts!
And please give it up
for the comedy stylings
of the April Fool.
Pull my finger...
and perish!
( laughter )
And that's Halloweenie Dog.
( barks )
That's not the spirit
of Halloween.
All right, he's my dog.
I just hate to travel
without him.
( baby talk ):
Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
What do you second-rate,
not Christmas holidays
want with our Timmy?
He better unwish that wish,
or he's going to get an egg
where the sun don't shine.
You mean the closet?
But there's nothing we can do.
We don't have enough magic left.
What?!
Oh, Timmy, there's
something you didn't know
when you made your wish.
Giving gifts to everyone in
the world takes a lot of magic.
So every Christmas Eve,
all us fairies in Fairy World
get together
and transfer most of our magic
to the one man on Earth
that needs it the most--
Santa Claus!
( phones ringing )
Well, I don't care.
It's "Ho, ho, ho,"
not "Ho, ho, who."
Fix the sign.
VOICE:
You've got magic.
Ho... ho...
holy mackerel!
I'm jolly again!
When Christmas is over,
the magic comes back to us.
But now, because
it's Christmas every day,
it won't.
We're practically powerless.
Because of this kid...
it's always
going to be Christmas.
Which means
we don't get to share
our holidays with the kids.
What's up with that?
I just wanted
more toys,
and to spend more time
with my mom and dad.
And now everybody's
so sick of Christmas,
they even want
to get rid of Santa.
He's right.
As long as Santa's around
this could happen again.
Right.
All we need to do
is banish Santa
to the imaginary day
of February 33rd
and get rid
of him for good.
But to do that, we'll
need a little magic.
( gasping )
Yeah, you two
are a little magic.
I'll be here all week.
Okay.
Let's get hopping.
Santa's in trouble,
and it's all my fault.
I've got
to get to the North Pole.
( "Pop Goes the Weasel" plays )
Oh, this is hopeless.
There's nothing here that'll
help me get to the North Pole.
DAD:
Darn it.
I've looked under this
high-speed snowmobile,
portable power generator,
all this survival gear,
a detailed map from our house
to the North Pole,
so simple that even
a ten-year-old child could read,
and I can't find
the eggnog anywhere!
This trip could be
potentially dangerous,
even life-threatening.
Cool.
But in case I don't die,
I better have a backup plan.
Santa's in trouble, and I'm
off to the North Pole to help.
If you see me, wish me luck.
And, and help me.
Don't just stand there
and stare!
Help me! Help me!
Merry Christmas again,
Timmy Turner.
Timmy's log.
Stardate: Christmas.
Feels like I've been
gone for weeks.
And at this speed,
I'll be there in no time.
( motor dies )
I'm out of gas!
GIRL:
Welcome to Butte,
the gas capital of Montana.
Got your message on
the Internet, Timmy Turner.
Think it's mighty fine
what you're doing for Santa.
Merry Christmas.
Or as we say in Montana,
you're standing
in cow manure.
Awesome.
( weakly ):
Timmy's log.
Stardate: Christmas.
No food. So hungry.
Must eat log book.
KIDS:
Bonjour.
Are you the one
they call Timmy Turner?
Uh, oui.
We got your message
on the Internet,
even here in northern Quebec.
GIRL:
We wish you luck
in your mission.
Merci.
You can keep the snails.
I made it all the way across
the ocean to Greenland
and nothing bad happened.
( growling )
Well, that's inconvenient.
APRIL FOOL:
Greenland.
It's not green
and there's no land.
What's up with that?
Just one country away from
getting rid of Santa for good.
Yeah, and then we'll be able
to create our own super-holiday.
Hallneweasterweenentine Day.
Hallneweasterweenentine
Day?
I didn't think
you'd remember.
Hey!
Who the heck
is that?
Hi. Am I too late
to get Santa?
Who are you?
I'm a holiday, like you.
I'm, uh, Birthday Boy.
Hop in.
I do the hopping around here.
ALL:
No more toys for girls and boys!
No more toys
for girls and boys!
SANTA:
These toys stink!
I'm running out
of creative ideas.
Kris, you're working
yourself to death.
I don't care, honey.
As long as it's Christmas,
and I've got the magic,
I have to give the children
what they wished for.
Psst! Cosmo. Wanda.
Timmy?
No, Timmy has a pink hat.
That's Birthday Boy.
Listen, I've got to get
to Santa before they do,
but I'm going to need help.
But we don't have any magic.
But you do have those.
Hey, these tires
were flattened
with two fairy
godparent crowns.
Who could have done that?
And where's your diaper?
This diaper may be stinky,
but it sure is fast.
I'm traveling
at the speed of smell!
( crashing )
Santa!
We've got to get you
out of here.
Who are you,
and why do you smell
like a dirty diaper?
I'm Timmy Turner.
I'm the dope who wished
it would be Christmas every day.
Well, son, wanting peace
and joy in the world
each and every day
is a wonderful sentiment.
But you're getting coal
for the rest of your life.
COMPUTER:
You've got coal.
Fine.
I don't care if I never get
another decent present again.
You're both in
a lot of danger and...
Oh, no! They're here!
What are you lesser holidays
doing here?
We want to stop Christmas
and we're here for the magic.
Get him!
Darn it. Mistletoe.
ALL:
I like you as a friend.
You're a good person.
You've jingled
your last bell, bub.
Get him!
WANDA:
Hey, they're using us
like sponges
to absorb the magic from Santa.
I find...
no joy...
in this!
Losing... holiday... spirit.
He's weakening.
What's up with that?
Not so jolly now, huh, Kringle?
New Year, hit me.
Oh, no!
( laughing )
When this double Grade-A egg
explodes,
it'll blow you to February 33rd,
which does not exist,
then Christmas will
never come again.
No! Leave him alone!
It's not his fault.
I'll never let you hurt Santa!
How you going to stop us, huh?
You're just one
little kid.
GIRL:
No, he ain't.
He's just the kid
who got here first.
( whinnying )
Wow, it's every Web-enabled kid
in the world.
( cheering )
We can't fight kids.
Can we?
No.
We wanted Santa gone...
so we could bring our own
holiday-specific joy
to children.
So they'd love us, too.
That's what's up
with that.
But we do love you guys.
ALL:
Really?
What's up with that?
Hey.
Just, you know, not as much.
I mean, Santa brings us toys,
and Christmas brings
our families together.
Birthday Boy's
got a point.
All I do is leave eggs that
go bad if you don't find them.
And all I do is get kids to play
horrible pranks on one another.
Yeah, but I make kids
fall in love with each other.
ALL:
Eww!
Point taken.
We're sorry, Santa.
We were both stupid
and jealous.
( cheering )
Will you ever
forgive us, Santa?
I don't have time
to forgive you.
Tomorrow's Christmas again,
and as long as
it's still Christmas
I have to give the kids
what they wish for.
That's it!
That's how we fix this.
Do you know why it will be
Christmas again tomorrow?
Because we keep
telling Santa
we want some
toy or doll,
or some stupid thing.
And Christmas Day,
Santa grants our wishes
whatever
they may be.
But if every kid in the world
wished for it to be
the day after Christmas,
that's what Santa
would have to bring to us.
December 26th!
Quick, everyone
write Santa a letter.
Tell him you wish it were
the day after Christmas.
♪ I wished every day
would be Christmas ♪
♪ Jeepers, how foolish I was ♪
♪ It isn't a gift,
it isn't a toy ♪
♪ It's the family and friends
that I really enjoy ♪
♪ I wish that tomorrow
weren't Christmas ♪
♪ But I wish that
the feeling would stay ♪
♪ 'Cause Christmas can always
be there in your heart ♪
♪ And never be locked
to just one single day ♪
♪ It's great that tomorrow
ain't Christmas ♪
♪ In Dimmsdale
and London and Rome ♪
♪ If I had just one wish,
I think it'd be this-- ♪
♪ I really
just want to go home now ♪
just wish I were home. ♪
Mom, Dad, wake up!
It's not Christmas
anymore!
BOTH:
It's not?
Yes, the endless Christmas
is finally over.
People across the globe
are slowly returning
to their everyday lives.
And the bitterest of enemies
gladly return to being
the bitterest of enemies.
BOTH:
It's a miracle!
( sniffing )
What's that awful smell?
Hey, an egg fell out
of Timmy's noggin.
Egg. Noggin.
Mine!
WANDA:
"And furthermore,
under no circumstances
"is any fairy
allowed to grant
an 'I wish it was Christmas
every day' wish ever again."
Wow, they've added a new rule.
You really got to mess up
big-time to make that happen.
We're proud
of you, Timmy.
Thanks, guys.
Now all we have to do
is make amends to Santa
for making him
work so hard.
How do we do that?
How many houses
do we have to hit?
All of them.
BOTH:
Merry Christmas, Noggy!
Merry Christmas to all,
and to all...
One per year!