♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪
♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BED, TWERP!
♪ THE DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH ♪
♪ WHO GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY ♪
♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY CROWNY THINGS.
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD,
PEA POD ♪
♪ BUFF BOD,
HOT ROD ♪
♪ OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE ♪
♪ GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE ♪
♪ GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE ♪
♪ LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE! ♪
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE THE KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
YEAH, RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
PUNY HUMANS!
WE SHALL NOW SUCK OUT
YOUR BRAINS...
WITH BENDY STRAWS!
[GASPS]
YOU CAN SUCK OUT OUR MINDS,
LIVERS, AND SPLEENS,
BUT WE WILL NEVER SURRENDER.
SILENCE, CAPTAIN
LASER PANTS.
NO ONE CAN SAVE YOU NOW.
IT'S CRASH NEBULA!
HURRAH!
INTERGALACTIC SCUM,
YOUR REIGN OF
TERROR ENDS...
NOW!
TV: ♪ CRASH NEBULA ♪
♪ CRASH NEBULA, SPACE HERO,
IS ON HIS WAY... ♪
IT'S PRETTY COOL,
HUH, CHESTER?
YEAH. DON'T
YOU THINK, A.J.?
POSITIVELY.
TV Narrator:
WILL CRASH NEBULA ESCAPE
THE EVIL CLUTCHES
OF THE CLUTCHULAX?
TUNE IN NEXT WEEK
FOR ANOTHER EXCITING
EPISODE OF...
CRASH NEBULA!
THAT WAS THE BEST
EPISODE EVER.
RIGHT GUYS?
GUYS?
GET HIM!
MEDDLING HUMANS!
YOU'LL NEVER CATCH ME.
[SNIFF SNIFF]
I SMELL FUN.
TWO AGAINST ONE, HUH?
MOTHER SHIP!
COME IN, MOTHER SHIP!
THIS IS TIMMY CALLING
COSMO AND WANDA.
DO YOU READ?
AYE, AYE,
CAPTAIN TIMMY, SIR.
UH, HE SAID,
"MOTHER SHIP."
THAT MEANS
I'M IN CHARGE.
AWAITING ORDERS,
YOUR SPACE
MACHO-NESS.
I NEED MORE FIREPOWER.
YOU'VE GOT IT, KIDDO.
MORE FIREPOWER, LACKEY.
I WANT A FATHER SHIP
NEXT TIME.
COOL!
KILLER
CRASH SUIT, DUDE.
YES. WHEREVER
DID YOU GET IT?
INTERNET.
COOL. NOW ALL
WE NEED IS AN ALIEN
AND WE CAN REENACT EPISODE
621 OF  CRASH NEBULA.
[WHISPERING] I wish we had
an alien monster to play with.
Great job on the alien, guys.
It's so lifelike.
OF COURSE IT IS.
HE'S REAL.
WE'RE NOT SO GOOD
AT CREATING ALIENS.
YEAH. SO WE BORROWED ONE.
WHAT!
QUEEN JIPJURRULEC,
YOU SEEM TROUBLED.
YES, KING GRIPPULON.
OUR SON HASN'T TORTURED
THE PRISONERS YET TODAY.
HMM. THAT'S
NOT LIKE MARK.
COMPUTER, FIND MARK.
UH, READINGS SHOW
THAT YOUR SON HAS
BEEN TAKEN TO EARTH.
[CRYING] OH, NOT EARTH!
ASSEMBLE THE STAR DESTROYERS.
WE'LL BLOW UP THAT FOUL
PLANET AND GET OUR SON BACK.
UH, NOT NECESSARILY
IN THAT ORDER.
[SCREAMING]
AMAZING.
A FULLY AUTOMATED,
AUTOMATONIC SPACE ALIEN!
PUNY HUMANS!
WHAT'S UP? I'M GOING
TO SUCK YOUR BRAINS
THROUGH THESE BENDY STRAWS.
COOL. ACTUAL  CRASH
NEBULA DIALOG.
YOU EARTH CHILDREN
ARE NOT AFRAID OF ME?
OR MY STRAWS?
[SNIFF SNIFF]
HEY! AUTHENTIC
ALIEN BAD BREATH.
I'M TELLING YOU
FOR THE LAST TIME...
[SHOUTING] KEEP
IT QUIET UP HERE!
SHE'S TERRIFIED THE CHILDREN
IN A WAY I COULD NOT.
YOU IN THE STUPID
ALIEN COSTUME,
YOU'RE OUT OF HERE!
BUT VICKY--
YOU CAN PLAY WITH
YOUR GEEK BUDDY
AFTER YOU CLEAN UP
THIS ROOM!
OOH, SHE'S SO...
FORCEFUL!
Queen: YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE TO BLOW UP ALL
THESE PLANETS
IF YOU'D JUST STOP
FOR DIRECTIONS.
QUIET! I'M STILL
THE KING AROUND HERE.
KING OF
GETTING LOST.
SILENCE!
PSST! TIMMY.
What is it?
UH, WE HAVE GOOD
NEWS AND BAD NEWS.
WHAT'S THE GOOD NEWS?
THE ALIEN WE GOT YOU
IS ACTUALLY A PRINCE
FROM THE DREADED WAR
PLANET YUGOPATAMIA.
AND HIS PARENTS
ARE ON THEIR WAY
TO DESTROY THE EARTH
AND RESCUE THEIR SON.
WHAT'S THE BAD NEWS?
OH, WAIT. THAT
WAS THE BAD NEWS.
THEN WHAT'S THE GOOD NEWS?
I FOUND A NICKEL.
OK, THEN...
I WISH THE ALIEN
WAS BACK HOME.
WELL? IS HE GONE?
UH...
MORE GOOD NEWS, NICKEL BOY?
MY NICKEL!
IT SEEMS OUR ALIEN
PRINCE HAS FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH VICKY.
AND THE RULES SAY
WE CAN'T INTERFERE
WITH TRUE LOVE.
WE'VE GOT TO TALK
THE ALIEN OUT OF
LOVING VICKY.
DUDE, ARE YOU TALKING
TO YOUR FISH?
YES--UH, GUYS,
WE NEED TO GET
THE ALIEN AWAY
FROM VICKY.
IT'S, UH,
A COLLECTABLE.
SUPERLATIVE.
HMM. SO WHY WOULD
SHE TAKE IT?
SHE'S NOT EVEN A FAN.
SHE'LL PROBABLY SELL
IT TO BUY MAKEUP AND
OTHER GIRL STUFF.
LET'S GO.
Vicky: YOU KNOW,
I COULD SELL YOUR
STUPID COSTUME
FOR MAKEUP AND
OTHER GIRL STUFF.
VICKY, THE FEAR YOU
INSTILLED IN THE YOUNG
ONES WAS ENCHANTING.
HMM, YOU TALK FUNNY.
ARE YOU FROM EUROPE
OR SOMETHING?
I'M A WARRIOR PRINCE
FROM YUGOPATAMIA
MY NAME IS MARK.
YECH! YOU'RE A FOREIGN
EXCHANGE STUDENT.
TAKE OFF THAT
STUPID COSTUME.
DOES THIS FORM
NOT PLEASE YOU?
[SIGHS] LOOK, IF YOU WANT
TO PLEASE ME SO MUCH,
WHY DON'T YOU MAKE ME
A CHOCOLATE SHAKE?
CHOCOLATE!
THAT'S LIKE
THE FOULEST SUBSTANCE
KNOWN ON MY PLANET!
AH HA!
YOU ROCK!
ALIEN TOY, WE'RE
HERE TO SAVE YOU
FROM VICKY.
I DO NOT WISH TO BE
SAVED FROM VICKY.
VICKY'S THE FOULEST,
MOST EVIL CREATURE
IN THE UNIVERSE.
I KNOW. ISN'T SHE AWESOME?
YOU TWO WILL MAKE
EXCELLENT APPETIZERS
FOR VICKY.
COOL. THIS IS JUST LIKE
WHAT HAPPENED IN TODAY'S
CRASH NEBULA EPISODE.
Timmy: YECH. HOW CAN ANYONE
FALL IN LOVE WITH  HER?
UH, TIMMY, THERE'S
SOMETHING WE'VE GOT
TO SHOW YOU.
Wanda: SEEMS LIKE WE HAVE
LESS TIME THAN WE THOUGHT.
OH, NO. I'D BETTER
GO TALK TO THE
ALIEN'S PARENTS.
MAYBE THEY CAN
TALK SOME SENSE
INTO THEIR SON.
GOOD IDEA.
WE CAN'T DESTROY
TRUE LOVE.
BUT PARENTS CAN.
HALT! WHO GOES THERE?
COSMO, WANDA,
AND TIMMY OF EARTH.
WE NEED TO SPEAK
WITH MARK'S PARENTS.
IF THE KING
AND QUEEN YOU
WISH TO SEE,
THEN YOU MUST
FACE THE PERILS 3.
NOW, PUNY HUMAN,
YOU MUST SKIP ACROSS
THE DREADED...
FIELD OF FLOWERS.
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL.
I MEAN, GASP!
WELL, HERE
GOES NOTHING.
REALLY.
AMAZING. THE FLOWERS
TOUCH HIS SKIN,
BUT HE NEITHER
BLEEDS NOR BURNS.
TA DA.
[GASPS]
BEHOLD
THE SECOND TASK.
YOU MUST HUG THE
GALAXY'S CUTEST AND
SOFTEST TEDDY BEAR.
[GASPS]
YOU CAN DO IT, TIMMY.
THE FATE
OF THE EARTH
DEPENDS ON IT.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
Teddy: I LOVE YOU.
[SCREAMING]
WE DON'T
UNDERSTAND!
HE DIDN'T BURST
INTO FLAMES.
NEVER FEAR, MY QUEEN.
NOT EVEN OUR MIGHTIEST WARRIORS
CAN SURVIVE THE FINAL TEST.
IS THAT?..
IT CAN'T BE.
IT IS.
CHOCOLATE.
NOT SO HIGH AND
MIGHTY NOW, ARE YOU,
EARTH PUNK?
FOR YOUR LAST TASK,
YOU MUST EAT THE
CHOCOLATE BAR.
SURE.
I MEAN, NOT CHOCOLATE!
ANYTHING BUT THAT!
PLEASE DON'T
MAKE ME EAT IT!
HEY! THERE'S
PEANUTS IN IT!
[SCREAMING]
YOU ARE TRULY
THE FOULEST CREATURE
IN THE UNIVERSE.
YOU MAY SPEAK TO
THE KING AND QUEEN.
A MERE CHILD HAS PASSED
OUR TOUGHEST TEST.
YOUR KIND ARE VERY
POWERFUL INDEED.
OH, PLEASE
DON'T HURT US.
WE JUST WANT OUR SON BACK.
I, TIMMY,
CANDY CRUNCHING
WARRIOR OF EARTH,
HAVE GOOD NEWS
AND BAD NEWS.
THE GOOD NEWS IS I'VE
NAMED MY NICKEL PHILIP.
WHAT'S THE BAD NEWS?
IT'S A GIRL NICKEL!
THERE'S A PROBLEM
WITH AN EARTH GIRL.
HE'S FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH HER.
I AND MY RACE OF FLOWER
SKIPPING, BEAR HUGGING
CHOCOLATE EATING WARRIORS
WILL NOT STAND FOR THIS.
WE-WE'LL
TALK TO MARK.
WE'LL SET
THINGS STRAIGHT.
JUST DON'T EAT
THE CHOCOLATE AGAIN!
[SCREAMS]
Mark: OK, DUDES.
THINGS AREN'T GOING
WELL WITH VICKY,
SO I'VE DECIDED TO SUCK
OUT YOUR BRAINS AND GIVE
THEM TO HER AS GIFTS.
YOU CAN SUCK OUT
OUR MINDS, LIVERS,
AND SPLEENS,
BUT WE WILL
NEVER SURRENDER.
SILENCE PUNY EARTH CHILDREN!
NO ONE CAN SAVE YOU NOW.
TIM NEBULA!
INTERGALACTIC SCUM!
YOUR REIGN OF
TERROR ENDS NOW.
EXCELLENT.
ANOTHER BRAIN
I CAN GIVE
TO VICKY.
[DOOR BELL RINGING]
OH, WHAT NOW?
HELLO. WE'RE
MR. AND MRS...CHANG,
AND WE'VE COME TO PICK
UP OUR SON MARK.
Vicky: MARK?
GET OUT HERE!
MY BELOVED CALLS ME.
I'LL BE BACK TO SUCK
YOUR BRAINS OUT IN
A MOMENT. LATER.
MOTHER, FATHER.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
MARK, ENOUGH OF
THIS FOOLISHNESS.
IT'S TIME
TO GO, PAL.
I CANNOT GO WITH
YOU, FOR I AM IN
LOVE WITH VICKY.
YOU SEE, SHE TAUGHT
ME SOMETHING TODAY.
IT DOES NOT MATTER
HOW HIDEOUS YOU ARE
ON THE OUTSIDE
BUT HOW EVIL AND
VICIOUS YOU ARE
ON THE INSIDE.
RIGHT? AM I RIGHT?
WELL, IF YOU'RE IN LOVE--
UH, NO, SON.
IT WOULD NEVER WORK.
SHE'S NOT
WHERE WE'RE FROM.
YOU MEAN EUROPE?
OK.
MARK, LISTEN TO YOUR
FATHER AND GO BACK TO
THE SHIP--I MEAN, CAR.
WHATEVER.
I'LL NEVER
FORGET YOU, MARK,
FOR AN EXCHANGE
STUDENT FROM YUGO...
EUROPE.
HEY! I FOUND
A NICKEL.
PHILIP!
TIMMY, THAT WAS
THE BEST GAME OF
CRASH NEBULA EVER.
DUDE, YOU ROCK.
THANKS, GUYS.
Narrator: WILL TIMMY'S
SECRET EVER BE EXPOSED?
WILL COSMO AND PHILIP
THE NICKEL EVER BE REUNITED?
TUNE IN NEXT WEEK
FOR ANOTHER EXCITING
EPISODE OF...
THE FAIRLY ODDPARENTS.
COOL!
Boy: WELL, MR. CROCKER,
FOR SHOW AND TELL
I BRUNG MY DOG, MANGE.
[GROWLS]
AND THIS IS
WHAT HE EATS.
FIRST GRADERS.
THEY KEEP HIS PELT SHINY.
[GASPS]
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS, GUYS.
OH, DON'T BE NERVOUS, TIMMY.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
THE BEST SHOW AND
TELL DAY EVER.
TRUST US.
YEAH! HOW MANY OTHER KIDS
HAVE FAIRY GODPARENTS
THAT CAN MAGICALLY PRODUCE
AN EXTINCT POLYWALYOCTOSAURUS?
IT WAS MY IDEA.
NO, IT WAS MY IDEA.
WELL, IT WAS MY IDEA
TO TAKE YOUR IDEA.
IT WAS HER IDEA.
THANK YOU, FRANCIS.
THAT WAS RIVETING.
CAN YOU GUESS WHAT
LETTER DOG STARTS WITH?
UH, "D"?
RIGHT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
TIMMY TURNER,
WOULD YOU CARE TO
COME UP AND BORE US
WITH WHATEVER
YOU DRAGGED INTO
SCHOOL TODAY?
FELLOW STUDENTS,
BEHOLD THE GLORY OF
WHEN THE WORLD WAS YOUNG,
AND DINOSAURS WALKED
ACROSS PANGAEA.
BEHOLD THE LETTER THAT
DINOSAUR STARTS WITH.
DUDE, WHAT'S
WITH THE CHICKEN?
IT'S NOT A CHICKEN.
IT'S A--
POLYWALYOCTOSAURUS.
YEAH, WHAT HE SAID.
NOTE THE
DINOSAUR-LIKE JAWBONE.
AND THE DINOSAUR-LIKE TAIL.
AND LOOK, A
DINOSAUR-LIKE BELLY.
A DINOSAUR?
EXTRAORDINARY.
NO NORMAL CHILD COULD
HAVE ACCESSED THAT TYPE
OF GENETIC TECHNOLOGY.
THERE'S ONLY ONE
LOGICAL EXPLANATION.
FAIRY GODPARENTS!
[LAUGHTER]
THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
MR. TURNER.
NO HARM DONE.
I WOULD, HOWEVER,
LIKE TO HAVE A WORD
WITH YOUR FAIRY GOD--
I MEAN, PARENTS.
PLAIN, EVERYDAY,
DON'T HAVE MAGICAL
POWERS PARENTS.
FIRST THING
TOMORROW.
[PHONE DIALING]
DUDES, YOU GOT TO HELP ME
FIND MY SHOW AND TELL THING.
YOU MEAN
THE CHICKEN?
IT WASN'T A CHICKEN.
IT WAS MY, UH...
UNCLE'S DOG IN
A POLYWALYOCTOSAURUS SUIT.
AND I GOT TO GET IT BACK.
WE'RE ON IT.
DOESN'T ANYONE SAY
GOOD-BYE ANYMORE?
WE'RE REALLY SORRY
ABOUT MAKING SHOW AND
TELL DAY A MESS, TIMMY.
YEAH. COME ON,
HIT ME AND MAKE
A MESS OUT OF ME.
THAT'LL MAKE
YOU FEEL BETTER.
I'M GOING
TO NEED A BAT.
YEAH.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
HOW AM I GOING TO EXPLAIN
TO MY PARENTS THAT I BROUGHT
A DINOSAUR TO SCHOOL?
WELL, I DON'T
KNOW, BUT KNOCKING
THE CANDY OUT OF ME
ISN'T GOING
TO SOLVE ANYTHING.
WHY DON'T WE PRETEND
WE'RE YOUR PARENTS
AND TALK TO THIS
MR. CROCKER GUY FOR YOU?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
IT WAS MY IDEA.
I WISH YOU GUYS COULD
POSE AS MY PARENTS.
YIPPEE. THAT HURT.
NO, COSMO, YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO SAY "OUCH"
WHEN YOU'RE HURT.
OH. YIPPEE,
THAT OUCHED.
WOW. THE PLAN'S
ALREADY FALLING
APART.
WHERE'S THE BAT?
WELCOME TO THE SCHOOL
OF BASIC HUMAN TRAINING.
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO BE MY HUMAN PARENTS,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO ACT AS HUMAN AS POSSIBLE.
OK. [BELCHES, FARTS]
WHAT'S NEXT?
THIS.
NO, WANDA. NO MAGIC.
HUMANS CAN'T DO MAGIC.
OH? WHAT ABOUT THOSE
GUYS WITH THE WHITE
TIGERS IN LAS VEGAS?
THEY HAD THOSE
SEQUINED SHIRTS AND
THEY COULD DO MAGIC.
[BABBLING]
BREATHE, BIRD BRAIN.
YOU HAVE LUNGS NOW.
YOU HAVE TO BREATHE!
YOU MEAN ALL THE TIME?
[GASPS]
UGH! YOU GUYS, FOLLOW ME.
WE'LL WORK ON SOME
OTHER HUMAN STUFF.
YOU HAVE TO USE
THE DOOR NOW.
YOU CAN'T JUST WALK
THROUGH WALLS.
YOU'RE SOLID NOW.
YOU MEAN ALL THE TIME?
THIS HUMAN STUFF IS FUN.
WE SHOULD HAVE TRIED
DRIVING YEARS AGO.
YEAH. AND LOOK HOW MANY
FRIENDS YOU'RE MAKING.
[PEOPLE ANGRILY YELLING]
JUST WORRY ABOUT MAKING
FRIENDS WITH CROCKER.
EVEN THOUGH
YOU HAVEN'T
NAILED DOWN--
BEING HUMAN YET--
THERE'S NO
REASON FOR HIM
TO SUSPECT YOU'RE--
FAIRY GODPARENTS!
AFTER ALL THE YEARS
OF SEARCHING,
I'VE FINALLY FOUND PROOF
OF THE EXISTENCE OF
FAIRY GODPARENTS!
[CUCKOO CUCKOO]
[LAUGHING]
ONLY MAGICAL CREATURES COULD
HAVE CREATED THAT DINOSAUR.
NOW IT'S MY CHANCE TO WASH
THE STENCH OF "FAIRIES DON'T
EXIST" OFF ME FOREVER.
WHETHER IT WAS
HARVARD, NEW BALTIMORE
COMMUNITY COLLEGE,
OR RIGHT HERE AT
DIMSDALE ELEMENTARY,
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN THE BUTT
OF MANY A CRUEL JOKE
DUE TO MY SO-CALLED
CRACKPOT THEORIES
ON THE EXISTENCE OF
FAIRY GODPARENTS.
PRINCIPAL WAXELPLAX,
HOW MANY CRACKPOTS--
I MEAN CROCKERS--
DOES IT TAKE TO SCREW
IN A LIGHT BULB?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHO CARES?
CROCKER'S NUTS.
[LAUGHING]
AHEM.
THAT WILL ALL CHANGE SOON.
BUT FIRST I MUST
PREPARE FOR THE FAIRIES.
TO THE CROCKER CAVE.
IT MAY BE JUST A PHONE
BOOTH INSIDE THE JANITOR'S
CLOSET--OUCH!
BUT AFTER I CAPTURE
TIMMY'S FAIRIES
AND HARNESS THEIR MAGICAL
POWERS FOR MY OWN USE--
DARN IT--I'LL GET NOT
ONLY THE PROPER EQUIPMENT
BUT ALSO THE RESPECT
AND--UGH!--
ADMIRATION THAT HAVE
SO LONG ELUDED ME.
MINE WILL BE
A NEW WORLD ORDER
WITH I, MR. CROCKER, AS
THE SUPREME MAGICAL RULER.
SORRY ABOUT
ALL THE JOKES
ABOUT YOU--
THEN, ONLY THEN--
[CUCKOO CUCKOO]
WHERE IS THAT COMING FROM?
HA! TIMMY TURNER'S FAIRY
GODPARENTS WILL NEVER BE
ABLE TO ESCAPE
THE EVER-VIGILANT EYE
OF MY FAIRY FINDER.
PATENT PENDING.
AH HA! THEY'RE HERE!
MANY OF MY FAIRY
ORIENTED TRAPS ARE
BOUND TO EXPOSE THEM
FOR THE FAIRIES
THEY TRULY ARE.
FAIRIES!--OUCH!
[CUCKOO CUCKOO]
YOU'RE NEXT.
WHERE SHOULD I PARK?
Cosmo: HMM.
PRINCIPAL. TEACHERS.
OOH! FAIRIES!
PARK THERE! PARK IN
THE FAIRY SPACE!
IF THEY PARK IN
THE FAIRY SPACE
IT WILL BE ALL THE PROOF
THE WORLD WILL NEED.
OK.
NO! IT'S A TRAP.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Timmy:
OH, THAT WAS CLOSE.
OH! THAT WAS SO CLOSE.
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU
TWO SMALL BOYS DOING
HERE THIS EARLY?
UH...LEARNING?
WE'RE TRYING TO FIND TIMMY'S
SHOW AND TELL PROJECT.
AH, YES.
TIMMY'S PROJECT.
WELL, TIMMY'S
PARENTS AND I ARE
HAVING A CONFERENCE.
WHY DON'T YOU BRING
THE PROJECT TO ME,
AND I'LL GIVE
THE PROJECT
TO HIM FOR YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
AND IN RETURN,
I'LL GIVE YOU
A SEAT OF POWER
IN MY NEW
WORLD ORDER.
DONE AND DONE.
I THINK WE'VE FINALLY
GOTTEN THIS WALKING
THING DOWN, TIMMY.
[WHISPERING]
Just play it cool.
AT LAST, TIMMY'S
GODPAR--I MEAN, PARENTS.
MR. AND MRS. GODTURNER.
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU.
[MARTIAL ARTS YELL]
HOW'S THAT FOR
A HUMAN HELLO?
YOU'RE KUNG SOCIAL.
UH, SORRY,
MR. CROCKER.
MOM'S, UH--
A FAIRY?
NO, NO. I WAS
GOING TO SAY
ENTHUSIASTIC ABOUT
MEETING AN EDUCATOR
OF YOUR STATUS.
OH, YES.
YES, OF COURSE.
OH, THEY'RE GOOD.
I NEED ONLY TO GET THEM
TO SIT IN MY SPECIAL
ELECTRIC FAIRY
DETECTOR CHAIR.
IF THEY SURVIVE,
THEY'RE FAIRIES.
IF THEY DON'T,
I HAVE TENURE.
MAY I OFFER YOU A CHAIR?
CERTAINLY. MAY IF
OFFER YOU A FISH?
OOH, NEAT.
FISH STICKS.
I'M STARVED.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER
I CHIP OFF THE DEAD SKIN.
I THINK HE'S
SUSPICIOUS, SO
BE ON YOUR TOES.
Wanda: OOH!
I'M DOOMED.
[MUNCHING]
ON 3.
READY? 3!
CHARGE!
TAKE COVER.
YOU SAID
A.J.: IT'S
GETTING AWAY.
OH, NO. THE FORBIDDEN ZONE.
YOU GO IN.
I'M NOT GOING IN,
YOU GO IN...
COFFEE?
WHY YES IT IS.
[WHISPERING]
Take the cups.
CAN I OFFER YOU
ANYTHING WITH THAT?
CREAM, SUGAR, MAGIC?
WHAT WAS THAT LAST ONE?
SUGAR.
YOU GO IN.
LOOK, LET'S
BOTH GO IN
AND GET OUT BEFORE
ANY GIRLS SHOW UP.
GOOD PLAN.
SUCKER. YOW!
Cosmo: WOW! THIS
COFFEE STUFF IS GREAT.
COFFEE, COFFEE,
COFFEE. GREAT.
OOH, WHERE DO THEY
GET THIS STUFF?
COLOMBIA.
OH, WE SHOULD
GO THERE,
IT'S THE BEST,
WE CAN GO
THERE NOW--WHOA.
Timmy: WHAT?
SOME SORT OF PRESSURE
IN MY LOWER TUMMY.
Crocker: YOU
HAVE TO GO TO
THE BATHROOM NOW,
DON'T YOU,
MRS. TURN-PARENT?
FOLLOW ME.
HERE YOU GO.
BOYS.
GIRLS.
MYSTICAL
CREATURES.
WELL...
Timmy: UH, MOM?
Principal: GOOD
MORNING, TIMMY.
UH-OH. IT'S THE PRINCIPAL.
OF COURSE.
PRINCIPALS FIRST.
[CRASH]
NEW WORLD ORDER!
UH, MAYBE
I'M NAIVE,
BUT I DON'T
THINK SHE'S
DOING IT RIGHT.
CROCKER!
OH, PERFECT.
WE GOT IT!
WE GOT THE, UH,
DINOSAUR, TIMMY.
GIVE IT TO ME.
DUDE, YOU GOT
TO GIVE ME THE BOX.
POSITION OF POWER,
A SEAT ON THE THRONE,
NEW WORLD ORDER!
HMM.
HEY!
BEFORE SCHOOL
HOURS, YOU AIN'T
THE BOSS OF ME.
Crocker:
GIVE ME THAT.
FINALLY, AFTER
ALL THE YEARS
OF BEING MOCKED.
[WHISPERS]
AND ALL THE
YEARS OF "FAIRIES
DON'T EXIST."
WITH THIS, I, MR. CROCKER,
WILL PROVE ONCE AND FOR ALL
THAT THESE TWO CREATURES
ARE TIMMY TURNER'S--
FAIRY GODPARENTS!
Mange: HUH?
[CHOMPS, GROWLS]
[CUCKOO CUCKOO]
[WHISPERING]
Got to watch out for
crock pot now, you guys.
He's totally
onto our secret.
A WEEK OF DETENTION
FOR ALL OF YOU.
YOU FOR FAKING
YOUR SHOW AND TELL,
YOU TWO FOR GOING
INTO THE GIRLS BATHROOM,
AND YOU FOR TRAPPING ME
IN A TOILET PAPER COCOON
AND PROMISING TWO SMALL BOYS
THEY COULD ENSLAVE THE EARTH.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
YOU MAY HAVE
OUTSMARTED ME
THIS TIME, TURNER.
BUT I'M ONTO YOU.
THEY CAN'T KEEP
ME IN DETENTION
FOREVER!
Principal: CROCKER!
MAYBE THEY CAN.
COFFEE CAN, LET'S GET
COFFEE, WHO WANTS COFFEE?
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--