♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY
ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BED, TWERP!
♪ THE DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
THAT GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY ♪
♪ THEY ARE HIS ODD PARENTS,
FAIRLY ODD PARENTS ♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY CROWNY THINGS.
♪ ODD PARENTS,
FAIRLY ODD PARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD, PEA POD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪
♪ OBTUSE, RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE, GUAVA JUICE ♪
♪ GIANT SNAKE, BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES, CHOCOLATE SHAKE ♪
♪ ODD PARENTS,
FAIRLY ODD PARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU'RE A KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODD PARENTS ♪
YEAH, RIGHT!
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
[BELL RINGING]
[KIDS CHATTERING]
[DOG BARKING]
[DOG BOINGING]
COME ON, HONEY, SMILE!
SMILES MAKE EVERYTHING BETTER.
[MOM GASPING]
CHEST ON FIRE, CAN'T BREATHE.
MAN, IT'S AN AWESOME DAY.
AND I'M STUCK IN THE
HOUSE DOING CHORES.
IF THERE WAS LESS
STUFF IN HERE TO CLEAN,
I'D BE DONE BY NOW.
I KNOW!
YOU COULD MELT SOME OF
IT WITH HEAT VISION.
OR YOU COULD WISH THAT
ALL THE CHORES WERE DONE.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA, WANDA!
I WISH--
OR YOU COULD MELT IT.
WITH HEAT VISION!
RIGHT.
I GOTTA GO WITH THE SUPER POWER.
I WISH I HAD HEAT VISION.
[MAGICAL TINKLING]
AWESOME!
[LASERS FIRING]
HEY, THAT'S NOT FUNNY!
NOW IT'S FUNNY.
[MANIACAL LAUGHING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
AWW, SEE?
LOOK HOW HAPPY WE'VE MADE HIM.
[LASER FIRING]
TOASTER'S CLEAN!
LAUNDRY'S DONE!
[LASER FIRING]
DAD'S TROPHY DUSTED.
SMILE. [GROANING]
TROPHY SENSES TINGLING.
TO THE TROPHY CASE.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
I MELTED YOUR TROPHY
WITH HEAT VISION.
WHERE DID YOU GET HEAT VISION?
INTERNET?
OH, HE'S GOOD.
I WON THIS TROPHY 30 YEARS
AGO WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE.
AND YOU MELTED IT!
I'M SO MAD.
I WISH BEAMS OF HEAT COULD
COME OUT OF MY EYES RIGHT NOW!
NO, NO!
OURS IS THE ONE WITH
THE SILLY PINK HAT.
GO TO YOUR ROOM
AND DON'T COME OUT
UNTIL YOU LEARN RESPONSIBILITY
FOR OTHER PEOPLE'S PROPERTY.
OR WELDING SKILLS.
WHATEVER COMES FIRST.
WHOA, I'VE NEVER SEEN
DAD THAT MAD BEFORE.
ALL OVER A DUMB TROPHY
HE WON 30 YEARS AGO.
WELL, IT WASN'T
SO DUMB TO HIM.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD APOLOGIZE.
YEAH, I GUESS.
OR YOU COULD
GO BACK IN TIME
AND STOP YOUR DAD
FROM EVER WINNING THE
THING IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WHAT HE SAID.
ALL RIGHT!
TWO WISHES FOR
COSMO, ZIP FOR WANDA.
I'M ON FIRE, BABY!
[BLOWING RASPBERRY]
[MAGICAL TINKLING]
THERE YA GO.
ONE MAGIC TIME SCOOTER TO TAKE
YOU ANY WHEN YOU WANT TO GO.
EXCELLENT.
[LOUD BEEPING]
[ALARM RINGING]
WOW, THE TIME STREAM!
WE'RE TRAVELING 30
YEARS INTO THE PAST.
WELL, YOU KNOW
YOU COULD HAVE JUST
WISHED YOURSELF 10
MINUTES INTO THE PAST
AND STOPPED YOURSELF
FROM MELTING THE TROPHY
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I COULD'VE WHAT?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
AWESOME!
WHAT A TOTALLY WICKED TRIP!
YOU MEAN GROOVY, WHAT
A TOTALLY FAR OUT TRIP.
WE'RE IN THE 1970S NOW!
BUT WE WERE IN THE
1970S IN THE 1970S.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
GROOVY, WE'RE
BACK FROM THE 1940S.
AND LIKE, BEST OF ALL,
BILLY, YOU STOPPED YOUR DAD
FROM WINNING THAT MEDAL.
NOW YOU WON'T HAVE
THE CHANCE TO LIKE,
MELT IT WITH HEAT VISION.
LIKE, I'M NEVER GONNA
SUGGEST HEAT VISION AGAIN, MAN.
OH, YEAH, I REMEMBER THAT NOW.
WHOA, CHECK IT OUT!
WOW, LIKE, YOU'RE
LIKE US, BUT LIKE--
MORE MATURE AND
CONCERNED ABOUT WEBSITES
AND THE GLOBAL WARMING.
[SOFT PINGING]
GUYS, I'M GONNA GO
FIND MY FUTURE DAD.
COOL, WE'RE GONNA STAY
HERE AND FIND OURSELVES.
HEY, THERE WE ARE!
LET'S DANCE!
[SCOOTER RUMBLING]
ONE, TWO, ONE, TWO,
ONE, TWO, ONE, TWO.
THERE HE IS!
THAT'S MY DAD AS A KID.
HEY, DAD!
WELL, THAT'S MY
NICKNAME, STRANGER.
MY REAL NAME IS [HORN BLOWING].
BUT EVERYONE CALLS ME DAD.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I GOTTA FINISH TRAINING
FOR THE BIG RACE TOMORROW.
I'M GONNA WIN AND
GIVE THE TROPHY
TO THAT GROOVY CHICK OVER THERE.
[GASPING] CHEST ON FIRE.
CAN'T BREATHE.
WOW, MY MOM AS A KID.
YEAH, AND SHE'S
GOT A BEAUTIFUL NAME.
IT'S [HORN BLOWING].
BUT EVERYONE CALLS HER MOM.
MAN, DAD'S REALLY DETERMINED.
I GOTTA MAKE HIM LOSE THAT RACE
SO HE DOESN'T WIN
THAT DUMB TROPHY.
I HATE LAVA LAMPS.
I KNOW.
THEY'RE REALLY BORING.
OH REALLY?
LIKE, WHAT DO YOU DO FOR FUN?
AND YOU CAN DOWNLOAD
DIFFERENT LAVA.
HEY, THAT GIVES ME AN IDEA.
SOMEDAY I'LL LINK EVERY
COMPUTER IN THE WORLD TOGETHER.
I'LL CALL IT THE INTERNET.
THAT'S SILLY.
YOU SHOULD CALL IT THE TIMMY.
OKAY.
OH, THAT BILLY GATES
WITH HIS CRAZY IDEAS.
COME ON,
PIZZA, ICE CREAM,
PIZZA, ICE CREAM!
YOU SURE THIS IS SOME
FUTURISTIC TRAINING PROGRAM?
OF COURSE.
I'M A FITNESS INSTRUCTOR.
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG.
NO, ACTUALLY I'M 40.
I JUST LOOK 10.
THAT'S HOW FIT I AM.
NOW, KEEP EATING!
COME ON, 16 MORE MILES
AND WE'RE HALFWAY DONE!
[SOFT MUSIC]
NOW IT'S TIME FOR SCARY
STORIES FROM THE FUTURE.
IN THE FUTURE, THERE
WILL BE 500 TV CHANNELS.
FAR OUT.
BUT NOTHING TO WATCH.
NO!
[ALARM RINGING]
OH, MY GOSH!
IT'S TIME FOR THE RACE.
[KIDS CHEERING]
I LOVE A GOOD RACE.
WE THINK ALL RACES
ARE GOOD, MAN.
WE DON'T JUDGE.
OH, LOOK, HERE
COME THE RUNNERS!
[KIDS CHEERING]
ALL RIGHT, DAD DIDN'T
WIN THE STUPID TROPHY!
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
I WONDER HOW THAT'LL
AFFECT YOUR FUTURE?
YEAH, I'LL BET--
[LOUD POOFING]
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
AND FOR COMING
IN LAST PLACE, YOU GET
AN ALL-EXPENSE PAID,
MANDATORY 12-YEAR SCHOLARSHIP
TO DICTATOR'S SCHOOL.
WHAT?
[MEN GRUNTING]
DAD'S NEVER MENTIONED
DICTATOR'S SCHOOL.
[DOORS SLAMMING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
HEY, LITTLE DUDE,
YOU'D BETTER GET BACK
TO YOUR OWN TIME AND FIGURE
OUT WHAT'S GOING DOWN.
AND WE'LL GO, TOO.
TIME ISN'T MY MASTER.
RIGHT ON.
[LOUD ZAPPING]
OOH.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
WHOA, THE FUTURE LOOKS BLEAK.
OH MAN, I CHANGED THE FUTURE.
[SIRENS BLARING]
IT'S THE MAN, MAN.
FIGHT THE POWER!
CHESTER, A.J.!
BOY, AM I GLAD TO SEE--
WELCOME TO DIMSDALE.
HAPPIEST PLACE ON THE PLANET.
OR ELSE.
NOW, SHOW US YOUR PAPERS.
WHOA, MAN!
THE SYSTEM'S TRYING
TO TAKE HIM PRISONER.
WE'RE ALL PRISONERS
ON THE INSIDE.
I LOVE YOU.
GUYS, COME ON, IT'S ME!
YOUR BEST FRIEND!
SILENCE.
OUR BEST FRIEND IS OUR
CHEERFUL LEADER, DAD.
IT'S ME, TIMMY TURNER.
AND THAT'S MY DAD!
WE ARE ALL DAD'S CHILDREN.
AW, MAN, DAD NEVER
MET MOM BECAUSE HE NEVER
WON THE TROPHY.
I DON'T EXIST ANYMORE.
AND SINCE I DON'T
EXIST, COSMO AND WANDA
AREN'T MY GODPARENTS.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
HA, AFTER HIM!
I GOTTA FIND MY DAD AND
GET HIM TO FIX THIS MESS!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
DAD!
THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL ME.
OR ELSE!
COME ON IN, OR ELSE!
WHO ARE YOU, SON?
I'M YOUR SON!
ALL PEOPLE ARE MY CHILDREN.
I RULE THE EARTH.
THAT'S ME, GRADUATING
DICTATOR COLLEGE.
AND THIS IS ME TAKING OVER
THE WORLD, WITH SMILES.
AND THIS IS WHERE I'D PUT
A TROPHY, IF I HAD ONE.
SORRY, LOST THE HAPPY.
BUT THE HAPPY'S BACK.
WHY ARE YOU SO
HAPPY ALL THE TIME?
WELL, 30 YEARS AGO AFTER
LOSING BOTH MY TROPHY
AND THE LOVE OF MY LIFE,
I DOVE INTO DENIAL.
AND AS RULER, I DEMAND
THE WORLD TO DO THE SAME.
THAT'S WHY EVERYONE SMILES
EVERY WAKING MOMENT.
OR ELSE?
NOW YOU'RE GETTING IT.
BUT YOU CAN'T BE
HAPPY ALL THE TIME!
HA, REBELLION.
THAT IS SO '70S.
GUARDS!
LITTLE FREEDOM FIGHTER!
WE'LL GET YOU OUT OF HERE.
OOH, THE COLORS!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
COME ON, I GOTTA
GET BACK TO THE '70S
AND MAKE SURE MY
DAD WINS THAT RACE.
YOU FOLLOWING THIS?
I'M A LEADER, NOT A FOLLOWER.
[DAD SCREAMING]
[ALARM RINGING]
[SOFT TINKLING]
WOW, YOU LOOK JUST
LIKE YOUR DAD AS A KID.
THAT'S THE PLAN.
OH, NOW HE HAS A PLAN.
ON YOUR MARK, GET SET, GO!
[GUN FIRING]
OH MAN, I FORGOT, I'M THE
SLOWEST KID IN MY CLASS!
I'M GONNA LOSE.
OH, I'M SO MAD, I--
[LASER ZAPPING]
I STILL HAVE HEAT VISION!
[CROWD CHEERING]
THE FIRST PRIZE IS
THIS AMAZING TROPHY!
HI, MOM, I'M DAD.
WILL YOU TAKE THIS,
GO OUT WITH ME,
MARRY ME, AND SOMEDAY HAVE
A BOY WITH A SILLY PINK HAT?
OKAY, I'LL COME
BY YOUR HOUSE LATER.
GROOVY.
IF I'M ASLEEP IN MY
TEST IN THE BACKYARD,
WAKE ME UP AND TELL
ME ABOUT THE RACE
WITH EXCRUCIATING DETAIL.
OKAY.
WAY TO GO LITTLE DUDE!
YOU'RE BACK!
THAT MEANS EVERYTHING'S
BACK TO NORMAL.
WHAT IS NORMAL, ANYWAY?
I LOVE YOU!
AND I ALWAYS WILL.
AWW.
HEY, IT WORKED!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
BYE '70S COSMO AND WANDA.
IT'S BEEN--
OUT OF SIGHT?
WHATEVER!
WELL, IT WAS NICE MEETING US.
SOLID!
IF YOU'RE EVER IN THE FUTURE--
OH, WE WILL BE!
OH, RIGHT.
NOW ALL I GOTTA DO
IS APOLOGIZE TO MY DAD
FOR MELTING HIS TROPHY.
YOU COULD JUST
GO FORWARD IN TIME ENOUGH TO--
QUIET!
[LOUD ZAPPING]
GO ON, TIMMY, YOU CAN DO IT.
JUST GO IN AND LET YOUR
DAD KNOW YOU'RE SORRY.
EVERYTHING'S STILL MELTED.
WHICH MEANS THE
TIME STREAM'S FIXED.
AND I'M STILL IN TROUBLE.
COOL!
DAD, WHAT YOU DOING?
OH, TRYING
TO LOCATE A NEW TROPHY OFF
THE TIMMY COMPUTER NETWORK.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY I'M
SORRY ABOUT MELTING YOUR TROPHY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE IT WAS
SO IMPORTANT TO YOU.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED, SON.
YOU KNOW, I WAS
PRETTY MAD YESTERDAY,
BUT FOR SOME REASON, NOW
I'M JUST GLAD YOU EXIST!
YOU KNOW, THAT WHOLE RACE
IS SUCH A BLUR TO ME,
I BARELY REMEMBER IT ANYWAY.
YEAH.
IN FACT, HERE.
GIVE IT TO SOME GIRL
YOU THINK IS GROOVY.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT'LL HAPPEN.
YES, I DO.
[LOUD ZAPPING]
[LOUD HAMMERING]
STUPID TROPHY!
HEY!
YOU'LL THANK ME
FOR THIS LATER.
I'M WELCOME?
OH, INTERNET,
BREAKFAST IS READY!
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY, HONEY.
ARE YOU READY FOR YOUR
ANNIVERSARY PRESENT?
OH, I'M SO EXCITED!
WHAT IS IT, WHAT IS IT?
OPEN YOUR EYES.
[GASPING] IT'S A BLINDFOLD!
OH, I'VE ALWAYS WANTED ONE.
AND I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED ROLLER SKATES.
I LOVE THE BLINDFOLDED
ROLLERSKATE ANNIVERSARY.
WHOA!
[LAUGHING]
IF THEY'RE INTO THAT STUFF,
THEY'RE GOING TO LOVE IT WHEN I
COOK THEM THEIR SPECIAL
ANNIVERSARY DINNER.
DON'T FORGET, TIMMY.
YOU STILL HAVE TO HELP ME
WITH MY ANNIVERSARY SURPRISE.
I KNOW, TODAY'S YOURS AND
WANDA'S ANNIVERSARY, TOO.
THAT'S CONVENIENT.
STYROFOAM?
YEAH, WANDA AND I HAVE BEEN
MARRIED 9,895 YEARS TODAY.
THAT'S THE STYROFOAM
ANNIVERSARY.
COOL.
YEAH.
THANKS FOR SENDING
WANDA AWAY FOR THE DAY
SO I COULD DECORATE THE ROOM.
WHAT SORT OF
MEANINGLESS TASK DID YOU
WISH FOR HER TO DO, ANYWAY?
OH, SOMETHING SHE'LL
NEVER BE ABLE TO DO.
EVEN WITH MAGIC.
FOR THE LAST TIME,
LEARN A TRICK!
SIT UP!
ROLL OVER!
CARE ABOUT SOMETHING
OTHER THAN YOURSELF,
YOU STUPID CAT!
[LOUD SLICING]
MR. WHISKERS.
THANKS FOR THE
STYROFOAM TUXEDO, COSMO.
WANDA'S GONNA BE
REALLY SURPRISED.
I WONDER HOW SHE'S
GOING TO SURPRISE ME?
SHE REALLY LOVES ME, YOU KNOW?
SHE LOVES EVERYTHING.
[LOUD ZAPPING]
I HATE EVERYTHING!
I HATE CATS, I HATE THIS DAY!
I'M GOING TO BED, WHICH I HATE.
HEY, LAMB CHOP, AREN'T
YOU FORGETTING SOMETHING?
OH, RIGHT.
[CAT SCREECHING]
I'M OUTTA HERE.
[COSMO YELLING]
SHE DIDN'T REMEMBER
OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I SPENT ALL MORNING SLAVING
OVER A HOT WAND FOR THIS?
AH, CHEER UP, DUDE.
I'M SURE SHE'LL
LOVE THE STYROFOAM.
[WANDA] AND GET THE
STYROFOAM OUT OF THE FISH BOWL!
FINE, IF SHE CAN'T
REMEMBER OUR ANNIVERSARY,
THEN I'M NOT GONNA
BE AROUND FOR HER NOT
TO REMEMBER ANY MORE
ANNIVERSARIES WITH!
HUH?
I'M GOING HOME
TO MY MOMMY, AND I'M TAKING
MY HALF OF THE MAGIC WITH ME!
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY, COSMO.
YOU MEAN, YOU REMEMBERED?
OF COURSE.
EVERY FAIRY KNOWS THAT
THE 9,895TH ANNIVERSARY
IS THE FALSE ANGER ANNIVERSARY.
EVERY FAIRY EXCEPT COSMO.
HE THINKS IT'S REAL ANGER.
AND HE'S SO UPSET, HE
WENT HOME TO HIS MOTHER.
HIS MOTHER?
MAMA COSMO?
OH, NO, THAT'S REALLY BAD.
SHE DOESN'T EVEN
KNOW COSMO AND I HAVE
BEEN MARRIED 9,895 YEARS.
WHAT DOES SHE
THINK HE'S BEEN DOING
FOR ALMOST 10,000 YEARS?
DID YOU GET THE MILK, COSMO?
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
GONE FOR 10,000 YEARS!
MAMA, I HAVE A
CONFESSION TO MAKE.
I WASN'T EXACTLY
OUT GETTING MILK.
WELL, AS LONG
AS YOU WEREN'T OUT
GETTING MARRIED TO
THAT WANDA GIRL,
THEN I STILL LOVE YOU.
BUT MAMA, I DID
GET MARRIED TO WANDA,
AND I HAD A FIGHT WITH WANDA.
OH, POOR COSMO.
I TOLD YOU SHE WAS HORRIBLE.
GOOD THING YOU DIDN'T MARRY HER.
BUT I DID MARRY HER.
[DOOR SLAMMING]
[COSMO SIGHING]
OH, YOU'VE GOTTEN THE MILK!
BRING YOUR SINGLE SELF IN.
THERE'S SOME LOVELY YOUNG
LADIES WAITING TO MEET YOU.
COOL, WE'RE IN FAIRY WORLD!
I WISH--
BACK OFF, HE'S WITH ME!
POSERS!
HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
GETTING A HUMAN TO FAIRY
WORLD TAKES A LOT OF MAGIC.
WHEN COSMO AND I AREN'T
IN TUNE WITH EACH OTHER,
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU MEAN I'M STUCK HERE
UNTIL YOU GUYS MAKE UP?
I WISH WE COULD GET TO MAMA
COSMO'S HOUSE, AND QUICK!
THAT MUCH I CAN STILL DO.
GIRLS, COSMO'S HERE!
AND HE BROUGHT MILK!
THESE NICE YOUNG LADIES
HAVE BEEN WAITING
ALL THIS TIME TO MARRY YOU.
I MEAN, MEET YOU.
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
NOW, WHO WANTS SOME I RATHER
DISLIKE WANDA COOKIES?
I DO, I'M STARVED!
MAMA COSMO'S PLACE.
COSMO'S MAD, AND HIS
MAMA'S PROBABLY IN THERE
MAKING IT WORSE!
COME ON, WANDA.
I'M SURE COSMO LOVES YOU JUST
AS MUCH AS HE ALWAYS DID.
[GASPS] COSMO!
THIS BETTER NOT BE
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE!
YOU MEAN, COSMO NOT
SURROUNDED BY WOMEN
MORE AESTHETICALLY
PLEASING THAT YOU,
AND BITING YOUR FACE
IN HALF ON A COOKIE?
NOPE, THAT PRETTY MUCH
HITS THE NAIL ON THE HEAD.
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
[LOUD ZAPPING]
[LOUD SLAMMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
HE'S NOT GOING
TO STAND FOR THAT!
THAT'S RIGHT,
TAKE THIS YOU NASTY,
YELLING ANNIVERSARY FORGETTER!
DID HE DO ANYTHING?
I MADE HER HAIR MORE SUMMERY.
I'M NOT A SUMMER,
I'M A WINTER.
HERE, TRY THIS.
YOU'RE SUCH A MAMA'S BOY.
I AM NOT!
NOW YOU ARE.
HEY, YOU MADE ME MAKE A POOPY.
[LOUD CRASHING]
WE DON'T LIKE POTTY MOUTHS.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT!
I WISH YOU GUYS
WOULD STOP FIGHTING.
THIS IS SILLY.
YOU TWO LOVE EACH OTHER.
THAT'S WHY YOU CHOSE EACH OTHER
OVER EVERYONE ELSE IN THE WORLD.
AND IF YOU HAD TO, I BET
YOU'D CHOOSE EACH OTHER
ALL OVER AGAIN.
OKAY, YOU'RE ON.
ON WHAT?
ON THE FAIRY DATING GAME.
I DIDN'T MEAN RIGHT NOW.
AND I WISH I WASN'T
A TOILET ANYMORE!
IT'S GETTING LATE!
I STILL GOTTA MAKE MY
PARENT'S ANNIVERSARY DINNER.
I HOPE SHE'S NOT TOO HUNGRY.
WHEN SHE'S HUNGRY,
MOM GETS KINDA TESTY.
MONKEY FEET!
BOY, I WONDER WHAT'S
TAKING TIMMY SO LONG
WITH OUR DINNER?
[MOM GROWLING]
NOW, HONEY, TOO MUCH FIBER
WILL SPOIL YOUR APPETITE.
[MOM GROWLING]
AND I'M JUST FINE WITH THAT.
AND NOW, HERES' THE HOST
OF THE FAIRY DATING GAME.
CUPID!
HI, THERE!
WELCOME TO THE
FAIRY DATING GAME.
WHERE FAIRY GODPARENTS
FIND THE THE FAIRY
OF THEIR FAIRY DREAMS.
OUR CONTESTANT TODAY,
PRODDED BY HIS MOTHER
IS HERE TO SEE IF HE'D CHOOSE
HIS WIFE ALL OVER AGAIN.
PLEASE WELCOME, FAIRY
AND MAMA'S BOY, COSMO!
I AM NOT A MAMA'S BOY.
YES, YOU ARE!
YES, MAMA.
YOU'LL SEE.
HE'LL PICK WANDA AS HIS TRUE
LOVE, JUST LIKE THE FIRST TIME.
YOU'RE RIGHT, WHICH
IS WHY I BRIBED CUPID
WITH OODLES OF CASH.
HA.
COSMO, IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO START ASKING QUESTIONS
OF OUR TWO, BEAUTIFUL
MYSTERY CONTESTANTS.
HEY!
AND THE AVERAGE-LOOKING ONE.
WHO YELLS A LOT.
WHOEVER YOU CHOOSE
WILL BE HIT BY THESE
MAGIC LOVE ARROWS.
FABULOUS.
WHICH WILL BOND
THEM TO YOU FOREVER.
OKAY, FAIRY BACHELORETTE,
HERE'S A QUESTION.
WOULD YOU EVER, A, YELL AT ME
ON OUR STYROFOAM ANNIVERSARY,
OR B, THROW AN ANGRY CAT ON ME.
NO OR NO?
STYROFOAM?
I THOUGHT IT WAS THE
FALSE ANGER ANNIVERSARY?
WAIT, WAIT!
IT WAS THE FALSE
ANGER ANNIVERSARY?
WHO CARES?
ASK ANOTHER QUESTION.
YEAH.
FAIRY BACHELORETTE,
WOULD YOU TURN ME
INTO A LITERAL EXAMPLE
OF A MAMA'S BOY?
YOU KNOW, WITH A DIAPER,
A BINKY AND EVERYTHING?
WELL, MAYBE THAT
WAS A LITTLE HARSH,
BUT IT WAS FUNNY.
YEAH, IT WAS KINDA FUNNY.
BUT HARSH.
[ARROW WHIRRING]
I'M SORRY, YOU'RE
ALL OUT OF TIME.
WE'LL BE BACK FOR
THE FINAL QUESTION
AFTER THIS COMMERCIAL BREAK.
[BUZZER BUZZING]
IT'S NOT WORKING.
HE'S FALLING IN
LOVE WITH HER AGAIN!
WELL, WHERE'S THE DOUGH?
YOU KNOW AS THE GOD
OF LOVE, I LOVE CASH.
AND I LOVE THE IDEA
OF COSMO NOT BEING ABLE
TO LOVE WANDA.
AT THIS RATE,
I'M NEVER GONNA GET HOME.
I'LL JUST MAKE 'EM FALL
IN LOVE WITH EACH OTHER
AND SORT IT OUT LATER.
OOH, I SPY A NICKEL.
YOU KNOW, MAMA COSMO,
THERE IS SOMETHING
I LOVE MORE THAN MONEY.
YOU!
NOW ALL I GOTTA DO
IS GIVE WANDA A CHANCE
TO WIN COSMO BACK
AND I CAN GET THEM
TO GET ME HOME!
AND NOW, HERE'S CUPID!
HI, TIMMY.
NO, I'M CUPID.
OKAY, THEN I WANNA
BE THE EASTER BUNNY.
I LOVE EGGS.
FOCUS.
OKAY, COSMO, YOUR LAST QUESTION,
AND THEN YOU GET TO CHOOSE
THE FAIRY BACHELORETTE.
IF I THOUGHT YOU WERE MAD
AT ME AND YOU REALLY WEREN'T,
AND I WENT HOME TO MY MOTHER'S,
AND WE BOTH ENDED UP ON A
GAME SHOW, WHAT WOULD YOU SAY?
RED?
RED!
I WOULD SAY I WAS SORRY.
AND I WOULD SAY I'M
PROUD TO BE YOUR WIFE,
WANDA, WHO IS YOUR WIFE.
OH, OOH, HER, I PICK HER!
WHOEVER SHE IS, I
HOPE IT'S WANDA!
GOODBYE, LADIES!
WANDA!
I'M SORRY I YELLED
AT YOU PUDDIN'.
I PROMISE I WON'T DO IT UNLESS
YOU REALLY MESS UP AGAIN.
LIKE I WILL TOMORROW?
IT'S A DATE.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
NO!
I FORBID THIS!
WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL, MAMA?
WHY DO YOU HATE WANDA SO MUCH?
IT'S NOT WANDA.
I DISLIKE ANYBODY WHO
TOOK MY COSMO LO LO AWAY.
THAT'S WHY I WANT YOU TO
MARRY STAR OR TWINKLE.
THEY'RE ROBOTS.
WE LOVE YOU, COSMO.
THEY'D DO ANYTHING
I TOLD THEM TO DO
BECAUSE THAT'S HOW
THEY'RE PROGRAMMED.
UNLIKE YOU, YOU
BOSSY, PINK-HAIRED,
OVERLY CONTROLLING--
HEY!
LET'S GET SOMETHING STRAIGHT.
I'M NOT BRIGHT, BIG
WORDS CONFUSE ME.
I HAVE THE ATTENTION
SPAN OF A RODENT.
AND WANDA LOVES ME ANYWAY.
SHE MAKES ME HAPPY, AND THAT
SHOULD BE ENOUGH FOR YOU.
[SIGN BEEPING]
AWW.
I NEVER REALIZED HOW
MUCH YOU LOVED HER.
SO YOU'LL BACK OFF?
OH, HEAVENS NO!
I'LL JUST HAVE TO TRY HARDER.
I--
OH, MAMA COSMO!
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
THE LAST OF ME.
I'LL BE BACK!
HI.
OH MY GOSH, IT'S
ALMOST MIDNIGHT ON EARTH.
COME ON!
I WISH I COULD GO HOME.
WELL, YOU NOW I NEED
A LITTLE MORE MAGIC
TO GET US BACK, TIMMY.
ME, PICK ME!
EVERY TIME.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
ONE MINUTE TO MIDNIGHT.
ENJOY YOUR ANNIVERSARY
DINNER, GUYS.
I MADE IT MYSELF.
OH, TIMMY, THIS IS
REALLY VERY SWEET.
BUT YOU KNOW I DON'T
REALLY LIKE MUSHY,
SUGAR-COATED CRASH NEBULO'S
POTATO CHIP CHOCOLATE CASSEROLE.
BUT NOW I DO!
AND I LOVE YOUR MOM.
[MOM GROWLING]
BUT I CAN WAIT.
IS THIS THE GETTING RAINED ON
BY MUSHY GOBS OF
FOOD ANNIVERSARY?
IT IS NOW.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY!
IT'S OUR ANNIVERSARY?