♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪
♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BAD TWERP!
♪ DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO'LL GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY... ♪
♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE A KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
YEAH,
RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
MTV NETWORKS
[BUGLE PLAYS  REVEILLE]
[SNORING]
READY, COSMO?
READY, WANDA.
Both: 1, 2, 3...
WAKEY, WAKEY, TIMMY.
[RING]
AAAH!
COME ON, LITTLE FELLA--
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE YOUR
FAIRY GODPARENTS...
WE DON'T NEED
OUR MAGIC TO TELL US
THAT YOU'RE IN FOR
A BORING, ORDINARY
DAY OF SCHOOL.
YIPPEE.
[SCHOOLBELL RINGS]
HA HA.
YOU'D BE ABLE TO REACH THIS
IF YOU WEREN'T SO PUNY.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Man:
WELCOME TO FOOTBALL TRYOUTS!
LISTEN UP
FOR YOUR POSITION.
TAILBACK!
YES, SIR!
LINEBACKER!
BALL!
HUH?
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET HOME.
AT LEAST I'M BIG
IN MY PARENTS' EYES.
HEY, SHORT STUFF!
GUESS WHAT.
WE'RE GOING
TO THE MOVIES.
ALL RIGHT!
NOT "WE'RE"
AS IN ALL OF US--
"WE'RE" AS IN
YOUR MOM AND I.
WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT OLD ENOUGH
FOR THIS MOVIE,
AND  WE'RE NOT
TAKING  YOU.
AIN'T PRONOUNS A KICK?
Both:
HA HA HA HA!
OH, HONEY, CHEER UP.
YOU'LL GET INTO
THOSE MOVIES SOMEDAY.
WHY, SOON, YOU WON'T
EVEN NEED A BABY-SITTER.
REALLY?
YEP, BUT TONIGHT  YOU DO!
HEY, PRONOUNS AGAIN!
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
[AWOO]
OH, NO...
THE BABY-SITTER!
[THUNDER]
HELLO,
MR. AND MRS. TURNER.
IT'S ME, VICKY.
[FLOWERS SCREAM]
YOU CAN'T SPELL "VICKY"
WITHOUT "ICKY."
WE'LL BE BACK REALLY LATE,
SO JUST TUCK TIMMY IN, OK?
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE LITTLE DARLING
LIKE HE WAS MY OWN
CASH AND BLOOD.
HAVE FUN AT THE MOVIES.
BYE!
ALL RIGHT, TWERP,
TIME FOR BED!
BUT IT'S ONLY 6:04.
WELL, IT'S 9:04
ON THE EAST COAST.
BED!
[BEEP]
NOW IT'S 9:05
ON THE EAST COAST.
CHEER UP, TIMMY--
YOU'RE ONLY
GONNA BE LITTLE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
WELL, BEING LITTLE STINKS.
I BET IT WOULD BE GREAT
TO BE AN ADULT.
WHEN I'M BIG, I'M GONNA DO
WHAT I WANT, WHEN I WANT.
I'LL HELP LITTLE OLD LADIES
CROSS THE STREET.
OH.
[HONKING]
THANKS,
OLDER TIMMY.
Timmy: I'M NOT GONNA TAKE
ANY CRUD FROM BULLIES.
YIKES!
YEA,
OLDER TIMMY!
Timmy: AND I WON'T EVEN NEED
A BABY-SITTER.
WILL BABYSIT FOR FOOD.
[CLINK]
PSYCH.
HA HA HA HA!
BLAST YOU,
OLDER TIMMY!
IT SOUNDS LIKE
BEING OLDER
WILL BE A HOOT.
YEAH, AND I DON'T
EVEN HAVE TO WAIT,
'CAUSE I'VE GOT
FAIRY GODPARENTS.
OK, YOU GUYS,
I WISH I WAS OLDER.
WELL, HOW DO I LOOK?
Both: EWWWW.
EWW IS RIGHT.
I DON'T HAVE ANY HAIR.
SURE YOU DO--
IT'S HERE ON YOUR BACK.
THAT'S JUST CREEPY.
I WISH I HAD
A FULL HEAD OF HAIR.
SORRY, TIMMY.
ACCORDING TO THE RULES,
FAIRY GODPARENTS ONLY
GRANT WISHES TO KIDS.
REALLY?
IT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU STILL CAN'T PAL AROUND
WITH ME, RIGHT?
NOT THAT WE KNOW OF.
COOL--
LET'S GO DO ADULT STUFF.
OK!
LIKE WHAT?
DRIVING!
I'M CARSICK.
I'M COSMO!
HELLO,
LITTLE OLD LADY.
MAY I HELP YOU
CROSS THE STREET?
BAAAH!
YOU KNOW, TIMMY, WHEN A KID
HELPS AN OLD LADY
CROSS THE STREET,
IT'S KIND OF CUTE.
BUT WHEN AN ADULT DOES IT,
IT'S JUST PLAIN CREEPY.
FINE. THERE'S STILL OTHER
FUN THINGS ADULTS CAN DO.
FINALLY, I CAN SEE
A GROWN-UP MOVIE.
EW, GROSS--
ADULTS MAKING OUT.
[SMOOCHING]
YOU KNOW, I BET TIMMY
WOULD THINK THIS IS GROSS.
[SMOOCHING]
AAAAH!
IT BURNS!
SHAVING WILL BE FUN.
AAAH!
TRY SOME MANLY COLOGNE.
THEY CALL THIS
SOOTHING?
I'M HUNGRY.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA:
MAYBE IF YOU ATE
SOME ADULT FOOD,
YOU'D HAVE BETTER LUCK
THINKING LIKE AN ADULT.
GREAT IDEA, PUDDIN'.
I'M CHOCK-FULL OF 'EM.
Both: HA HA HA HA!
Waiter: SIR.
THE GROWN-UP MENU--
FOR GROWNUPS LIKE ME!
[MUNCHING]
WHAT'S THIS?
THE BILL.
THAT GOES TO MY...
PARENTS.
VERY AMUSING, SIR.
THAT'LL BE $265.
WHAT?!
THAT'S MORE THAN
I GET IN ALLOWANCE.
I MEAN, THAT'S MORE
THAN I MAKE IN A MONTH.
WELL, YOU SHOULD'VE
FINISHED COLLEGE.
DID YOU FINISH COLLEGE?
NO!
WHY DO YOU THINK
I'M A WAITER?
WAAAH!
COULDN'T YOU GUYS
MAGICALLY CLEAN THESE?
NO. ADULTS HAVE
TO DO EVERYTHING
ALL BY THEMSELVES.
[GULPS]
SO TIRED.
AAAH!
[WHISTLE]
HYAH!
OOF!
AAH!
HYEE!
HEEYAH!
OOF!
OH, MAN, BOOTED OUT
OF MY OWN HOUSE.
NOBODY GETS RID OF CREEPS
LIKE VICKY.
BWAAK!
HMM, TIMMY HASN'T SAID ANYTHING
SINCE I SENT HIM TO BED.
THE BRAT'S USUALLY WHIMPERING
WITH THE HUNGER BY NOW.
AW, MAN, WHAT GOOD
IS BEING BIG
IF I CAN'T EVEN
GO IN MY OWN HOME?
COME ON, I KNOW
WHERE WE CAN STILL GO.
[GASP]
HE'S GONE!
SOMETHING COULD HAVE
HAPPENED TO HIM!
OR WORSE...
SOMETHING COULD
HAPPEN TO ME
BECAUSE SOMETHING
HAPPENED TO HIM!
HIS PARENTS ARE HOME!
NEED TIME TO FIND THE BUG.
Mrs. Taylor:
VICKY, IT'S US...
Mr. Taylor:
TIMMY'S LOVING PARENTS.
AW, LOOK AT THAT BIG,
ORANGE, BASKETBALL-SHAPED
HEAD OF HIS SLEEPING.
GOOD NIGHT, TIMMY.
WELL, UH,
GOOD NIGHT.
Timmy: I CAN'T MAKE WISHES,
I CAN'T SLEEP IN MY OWN BED--
I DIDN'T KNOW BEING AN ADULT
WOULD BE SO HARD.
OH, IT'S OK, SWEETIE,
TOMORROW WILL BE BETTER.
REALLY?
AWE DON'T KNOW--
OWWWIE!
[COCK-A-DOODLE-DO]
Boy: OUCH, OW--
CUT IT OUT, FRANCIS.
THAT'S MY ONLY HEAD.
HUH HUH.
FINALLY, THIS LOOKS
LIKE A JOB FOR...
Both: OLDER TIMMY!
PLUCK ON SOMEBODY
YOUR OWN SIZE.
WAAAH!
FAIRYGRAM
FOR COSMO AND WANDA.
I'M COSMO AND WANDA.
NOW THAT YOUR KID
IS BIG AND HAIRY,
YOUR NEXT ASSIGNMENT
IS MEAN AND SCARY.
MAN, I WISH I HAD SOME FAIRY
GODPARENTS TO KNOCK AROUND
INSTEAD OF THIS STUPID DOLL.
[BUZZ]
WHOA, THE HEAD FELL OFF.
AWESOME!
YOU MEAN WE'RE BEING
REASSIGNED?
HA HA HA HA!
I MEAN, UH, YES,
AND WE'RE ALL
VERY SORRY.
CAN WE HAVE A COUPLE OF HOURS
TO SAY GOOD-BYE TO TIMMY?
CAN I HAVE
$5.00?
TWO HOURS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU SAID YOU JUST
COULDN'T GRANT ME
ANY MORE WISHES.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU'D
HAVE TO LEAVE ME, TOO.
WE DIDN'T KNOW THAT,
EITHER.
APPARENTLY,
THE OTHER THING I'M CHOCK-FULL
OF IS NOT KNOWING STUFF.
HEY, WHAT IF I ACTED
LIKE A KID AGAIN?
I COULD WISH MYSELF
BACK TO NORMAL
AND YOU GUYS
WOULDN'T HAVE TO LEAVE.
HMM, I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING THAT
SAYS YOU CAN'T.
I SMELL LOOPHOLE!
WE'LL DISCUSS IT
AT THE NEXT FAIRY CONVENTION.
COME ON, TIMMY.
OOH, LET'S FIND
YOUR INNER CHILD.
MINIATURE GOLF
IS A GREAT KIDS' GAME.
OW, MY BACK.
LET ME TRY
THE AGE-O-METER.
KID...ADULT...
OH, NO!
YOU'VE BECOME
EVEN MORE
OF AN ADULT.
WE'VE GOT TO RESORT
TO THE HEAVY ARTILLERY.
HA HA HA HA!
THAT'S JUST PLAIN CREEPY.
TIME TO GO.
CAN WE HAVE TWO MORE
HOURS WITH TIMMY?
CAN I HAVE
5 MORE DOLLARS?
COME ON,
WE'VE GOT TO GET
ME YOUNGER...
I'M RUNNING OUT
OF 5s.
Vicky:
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS TWERP?
VICKY!
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO HAPPY
TO SEE YOU IN MY--
ACTUALLY, I'VE NEVER
BEEN HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
[WHISTLE]
OOF!
AAH!
HYAH!
OOF!
YOU ARE ONE
CREEPY ADULT.
WE GOT A PLACE
FOR GUYS LIKE YOU.
HOME?
AW, SWEETIE,
WE TRIED.
LOOK AT IT
THIS WAY:
MEALS DON'T COST
$265 HERE.
Man:
ONE PHONE CALL, CREEP.
MOM, IT'S ME, TIMMY.
HONEY, IT'S SOME OLD GUY
CALLING ME FROM JAIL.
HE SAYS HE'S TIMMY.
THAT'S CREEPY...
AND INACCURATE.
WE KNOW THAT TIMMY
WAS TAKEN TO SCHOOL
BY HIS LOVING
BABY-SITTER, VICKY.
THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE ME.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
GROWN-UP.
[CRIES]
OK, CHOP-CHOP--
SOMEBODY IN THIS ROOM
HAS TO GO HELP THE NEW KID.
WHAT? NO!
I'VE LOST MY HOME, MY HAIR,
AND NOW MY GODPARENTS.
THIS STINKS!
I DON'T WANT TO BE
AN ADULT, YET.
I WANT MY MOM AND DAD!
AAAAH!
Wanda: OH, TIMMY,
WANTING YOUR MOM AND DAD
IS MAKING YOU A KID INSIDE.
QUICK, MAKE A WISH!
I WISH I WAS A KID AGAIN!
I'M PUNY AGAIN!
WOO-HOO!
Godparents:
AND WE GET TO STAY WITH TIMMY!
IN YOUR FACE!
WELL, SOMEONE IN HERE
HAS TO GET ASSIGNED
TO THAT MEAN, LITTLE--
DARN IT!
FINALLY...
DOES YOUR HEAD POP OFF?
IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT BIG, FAT,
CREEPY BALD GUY?
UH, PAROLE?
WELL, JAIL'S FOR
CREEPY ADULTS--NOT KIDS.
LET'S GET YOU
OUT OF HERE.
All: WE WANT OUR MOMMIES
AND DADDIES, TOO.
AAAH!
BEING A KID ROCKS!
I'D RATHER BE A SHRIMP
THAN A HAIRY PRISONER
ANY DAY.
HEY, ME, TOO.
OFFICER...
HE'S A TWERP, YOU KNOW,
AND I CAN'T FIND HIM.
HE'S ABOUT THIS HIGH,
HE'S GOT A STUPID,
LITTLE PINK HAT LIKE THIS,
AND HE'S GOT
A NASALLY LITTLE VOICE LIKE--
HI, VICKY!
TWERP...I'M SAFE!
I--I MEAN, YOU'RE SAFE--
WHICH MEANS I'M SAFE!
Francis:
HUH, YOU'RE JUST A SHRIMP--
A PUNY, LITTLE SHRIMP.
I SURE AM, FRANCIS,
AND I'M NOT IN ANY HURRY
TO GROW UP.
BEST OF ALL,
I'VE GOT ALL MY HAIR
AND NONE OF IT'S
ON MY BACK.
UH...
Both: EWWW.
HERE YOU GO.
HEY, SHAVING WILL BE FUN.
Francis: AAAAAH!
All: HA HA HA HA HA!
IT'S QUIET--
TOO QUIET.
WHAT WAS THAT?
TIMMY!
LOOK OUT!
THAT'S DOUBLE THE DAILY
RECOMMENDED SUPPLY
OF BETA CAROTENE!
NO!
I'M HIT--
A LOT!
LOOK OUT! THEY'RE
COMING CLOSER!
THEY'RE--THEY'RE--
NINJA BUNNIES?
AW, THAT'S IT.
HELMETS OFF.
LOOK AT ME!
I'M CHEESE!
SOMETHING WRONG,
TIMMY?
FUZZY BUNNIES?
WHAT AM I, 4?
HEY! I HEARD HAPPY.
WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
UH, NOTHING. JUST, UH,
PLAYING VIDEO GAMES.
WELL, KEEP IT DOWN.
YOU KNOW WHEN
I'M WATCHING YOU,
I'M WATCHING
SOMETHING ON TV!
THAT WAS CLOSE.
NO, THIS IS CLOSE.
I'M CHAFING.
LOOK, I'M GONNA GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
WHILE I'M GONE,
PLEASE FIX THIS GAME.
NO BUNNIES.
NO PONIES.
MAKE A GAME THAT'LL
SCARE THE PANTS OFF ME.
BUT YOU'LL BE
IN THE CAN.
YOU'LL ALREADY
HAVE YOUR PANTS--
WHY DON'T YOU WISH FOR
EXACTLY WHAT YOU WANT,
AND WE'LL DO OUR BEST.
I WISH FOR A VIDEO GAME
THAT'S CHALLENGING--
A GAME THAT YOU CAN'T WISH
YOURSELF OUT OF.
THAT WISH IS JUST
VAGUE ENOUGH TO WORK.
BUT WE'RE GONNA NEED A LOT
OF POWER TO MAKE IT WORK.
ONE TOUGH VIDEO GAME,
COMING UP.
WHOA.
WHAT WAS THAT?
THE POWER SURGED.
EVERY LIGHT
IN THE CITY DIMMED.
THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING.
Both: TIMMY'S GOT
A NEW VIDEO GAME!
I HOPE TIMMY
LIKES HIS NEW GAME.
[GLASS BREAKING]
HEY, WHERE'S THE DUDE?
IT'S 6:13.
TIMMY ALWAYS GOES
TO THE BATHROOM
AT 6:13.
THAT'S WEIRD.
HE ALWAYS
STRUCK ME AS A...
7:43 WHIZZINATOR.
COOL! VIRTUAL
REALITY HELMETS!
WELL, THAT'S NOT GOOD.
HEY, WHAT'S UP
WITH THE POWER SURGE?
SHH. CHESTER AND AJ
ARE ON TV.
WHAT?
THIS IS WEIRD.
USUALLY TIMMY'S
GAMES ARE FILLED
WITH FUZZY BUNNIES.
I KNOW.
WHAT IS HE, 4?
HA HA HA!
THOSE CREEPS!
WAIT TILL I RESET THEM.
NO! IF YOU
TURN THE GAME OFF
WHILE THEY'RE IN THERE
OR IF THEY LOSE
THEIR 3 LIVES,
THEY'LL DISAPPEAR FOREVER!
WHAT?
THEN I WISH THEM
OUT OF THE GAME.
YOU CAN'T!
QUOTE:
"I WISH FOR A VIDEO GAME
THAT'S CHALLENGING--
A GAME THAT YOU CAN'T WISH
YOURSELF OUT OF."
UNQUOTE.
YOU EITHER WIN THE GAME
OR TAKE OFF THE HELMET.
YOU GUYS DON'T DO
ANYTHING HALFWAY, DO YOU?
NOPE, WE'RE TWO HALVES
OF A WHOLE IDIOT.
OH, NO!
GREAT.
THE VIDEO GAME IS USING
SO MUCH ENERGY
THAT ANYTHING VICKY PLUGS IN
COULD TURN OFF THE POWER
AND TURN THE GAME OFF!
THOSE TWO ARE GONERS UNLESS
I GET THEM OUT OF THERE.
YOU GUYS KEEP VICKY
FROM USING UP ANY MORE POWER.
I'M GOING IN.
HE'S BEING VAGUE AGAIN.
Vicky: AND THIS IS THE TV,
AND THIS IS THE VCR,
AND THIS IS THE DVD
AND THIS IS
THE SURROUNDSOUND,
AND THIS IS THE COMBINATION
MICROWAVE POPCORN MAKER
AND NECK MASSAGER
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THIS PLUG DOES,
BUT I AIN'T PAYIN'
FOR THE ELECTRICITY!
WE CAN'T LET HER PLUG
ALL THOSE THINGS IN.
SHE'LL BLOW
THE POWER.
COME ON.
FOLLOW ME
TO THE TV.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WEDNESDAY, MARCH 22.
COSMO HAD AN IDEA.
WANDA!
YOU GOT SOME
'SPLAININ' TO DO.
EVEN THOUGH THAT'S
NOT THE WAY EVERYBODY
SAYS "EXPLAINING,"
I RESPECT
OUR DIFFERENCES
AND YOUR RIGHT TO SAY IT
IN THE WAY YOU WANT.
EH, BABALOO?
THAT, TOO.
WAH!
BORING.
AND NOW HERE'S COSMO
WITH THE WEATHER.
I THOUGHT
YOU SAID  FEATHER.
COOL! THE ELECTRIC
SHREDDER BALLS OF DOOM.
MAN, COSMO AND WANDA REALLY
MADE THIS GAME A LOT--
TOUGHER.
I LOST A LIFE--
ON LEVEL ONE.
WHAT AM I, 4?
JUST LET ME
CLARIFY THIS.
YOU MARRIED YOUR CAR.
YEP. NOW MY KIDS GET
17 MILES TO THE GALLON.
[HORN HONKING]
AND WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
YAWN!
[PANTING]
AAH! IF I'M NOT CAREFUL,
I COULD GET KILLED.
NEAT!
OH, NO.
ANOTHER POWER SURGE.
AAH!
COOL.
THIS LOOKS LIKE
AN UNDERWATER VERSION
OF MY AUNT GERTRUDE'S HOUSE.
HELLO, TIMMY.
LET AUNT GERTRUDE
PINCH THOSE CHUBBY
CHEEKS OF YOURS.
I HOPE SHE
MEANS MY FACE.
I'M A WANDA COIN.
YOU MAY HAVE ONE WISH.
I WISH I HAD
CHEEKS OF STEEL.
I HOPE YOU MEAN
YOUR FACE.
I DO.
IT'S A SHOW
ABOUT NOTHING.
HOW DO WE KNOW
WHEN IT'S OVER?
I DO.
TV narrator: HIS VELVETY VOICE
AND BEAUTIFUL LYRICS
HAVE MOVED
MANY A GENERATION...
♪ THE WHEELS ON THE BUS
GO ROUND AND ROUND ♪
Narrator: HIS IS A TALENT
THAT WILL FILL YOUR HEART
WITH JOY.
♪ THERE WAS A FARMER
HAD A DOG ♪
♪ AND BINGO
WAS HIS NAME-O ♪
MAN, THERE IS
NOTHING ON TODAY.
WOW, THE CLASSROOM
OF DOOM LEVEL.
HEY, LOOK.
APPARENTLY, IF YOU DON'T
GET THROUGH THIS CLASS,
YOU SPEND THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE AS A JANITOR.
THERE'S A LESSON
IN THAT.
GUYS, I FOUND YOU!
HEY, TIMMY.
GREAT GAME, DUDE.
WE'VE GOTTA
GET OUT OF HERE.
NO WAY! THIS
IS THE GREATEST
VIDEO GAME EVER.
BUT WE ONLY HAVE
TWO LIVES LEFT.
SO? IT'S NOT LIKE IF
WE GET WASTED IN HERE,
WE DISAPPEAR
FOREVER, RIGHT?
UH...
BESIDES,
I HAVE 3 LIVES.
AAH!
STOP IT!
GUYS, WE HAVE
TO STICK TOGETHER.
ONLY TOGETHER,
THROUGH THE POWER
OF TEAMWORK, CAN WE--
WHOA! COME ON!
I'M ON TOP OF THE DESK!
AHH.
WHAT THE HECK IS WRONG
WITH THIS THING?
I'M ALL OUT OF IDEAS.
WELL, EASY COME,
EASY GO.
Vicky: NO WONDER
NOTHING'S WORKING.
ALL THE PLUGS
CAME OUT.
OH, NO!
OH, NO.
THE POWER'S OUT.
TIMMY!
COSMO?
I HAD ANOTHER IDEA.
THIS WAS A MAGNIFICENT
DAY FOR COSMO.
WAY TO KEEP THE POWER
GOING, SWEETIE.
GOOD THING I'M MORE
HUNGRY THAN TIRED.
GUYS, WAIT.
WE REALLY NEED
TO STOP PLAYING.
WHY?
UH, I HAVE TO GO.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YOU JUST WENT
AT 6:13.
BESIDES,
WE'VE ONLY GOT...
ONE LEVEL LEFT!
HEY, WE'RE IN
MY LIVING ROOM.
PHEW. WE'RE FINALLY
OUT OF THE GAME.
HOW ANTICLIMACTIC.
YEAH, WHAT A GYP.
OH, NO. MY HELMET'S
STILL ON.
WE'RE STILL IN THE GAME.
HA HA HA!
WELL, WELL.
LOOKS LIKE I'M HAVING
3 HELPINGS OF TWERP
FOR DINNER.
GUYS, TAKE OFF
THE HELMETS, QUICK!
DON'T FREAK, DUDE.
WE STILL HAVE
TWO LIVES LEFT.
THAT IS ONE
BAD BABY-SITTER.
TIME TO BABY-SIT.
AAH!
NO! THEY'LL BE
GONE FOREVER!
OH, NO! THAT WAS
TIMMY'S LAST LIFE.
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
WHOA, HE GAVE
HIS LAST LIFE FOR US.
EVEN VIRTUALLY,
THAT WAS PRETTY COOL.
HEY, IF TIMMY'S
GONE FOR GOOD,
WHY'S HIS SCORE
STILL GOING UP?
I'M ALIVE? BUT HOW?
SACRIFICING
YOUR LIFE FOR US...
MUST HAVE GIVEN YOU
ENOUGH POINTS
FOR A FREE MAN.
COOL. LET'S ROCK.
A COSMO COIN.
[GROWL]
GUYS, WE'VE GOTTA
GET THAT COIN.
READY? GO.
FEAR MY SITTING BUTT!
WOW, THAT'S COMFY.
BEAUTIFUL!
THE COIN.
[GROWL]
BYE-BYE, TWERPS!
GO, TIMMY.
I'M A COSMO COIN,
AND BOY AM I GLAD
TO SEE YOU.
DITTO.
THIS'LL BE GREAT
FOR MY GLUTS.
WHATCHA NEED, SPORT?
I WISH I HAD SOMETHING
TO STOP VICKY.
HEY, THAT'S JUST
VAGUE ENOUGH TO WORK.
OH, VICKY, IT'S US.
TIMMY'S MOM AND DAD.
WE'RE BACK.
YOU CAN GO HOME NOW.
NO!
[CRASH]
ALL RIGHT, GAME OVER.
YOU TWERPS
ARE OUTTA HERE.
TIMMY'S GOTTA REWIRE
THE HOUSE BECAUSE
I CAN'T WATCH MY SHOWS!
LATER, DUDE.
BYE, TIMMY.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
Timmy: HEY, VICKY.
WHY DON'T YOU WATCH
YOUR SHOWS ON THIS?
THIS VIRTUAL REALITY HELMET
PUTS YOU RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF YOUR FAVORITE
PROGRAMS.
GIVE ME THAT.
COOL, THE TETHERBALL
CHANNEL.
[VICKY SCREAMING]
HA HA HA!
HIGH FIN.
HOW ABOUT
A KISS INSTEAD?
I'M GAME.
Vicky: HEY, IS THAT
TIMMY'S AUNT GERTRUDE?
OW!
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
MTV NETWORKS
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--