♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪
♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BED, TWERP!
♪ THE DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH ♪
♪ WHO GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY ♪
♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY CROWNY THINGS.
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD,
PEA POD ♪
♪ BUFF BOD,
HOT ROD ♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE,
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE THE KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
YEAH,
RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
Kids: CHOMPY!
CHOMPY! CHOMPY!
HEY, TIMMY.
WHAT'S A CHOMPY?
DOES IT HURT?
CHOMPY'S A GOAT.
HE'S DIMMSDALE'S
TOWN HERO AND MASCOT.
Vicky: ONE SIDE,
PARASITES.
ICK! I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOUR PARENTS MADE ME
TAKE YOU
ON THIS STUPID TOUR
OF THE CITY HALL.
THEY'RE PAYING YOU,
AREN'T THEY?
BESIDES,
IT'S CHOMPY!
I CAN'T LEARN
ENOUGH ABOUT CHOMPY.
WELL, HERE'S
A PHYSICS LESSON,
POINDEXTER.
UNDIES PLUS GRAVITY
EQUALS WEDGIE!
HEH HEH. OH, YOU KIDS
AND YOUR GOAT.
I'M THE MAYOR.
DOESN'T ANYONE
WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
MY ACCOMPLISHMENTS?
[WOLF HOWLS]
I HATE NOT BEING
THE GOAT.
LET'S CONTINUE
THE TOUR WITH A WALK
THROUGH THE HALL
OF GOATY GREATNESS.
IT WAS CHOMPY
WHO PULLED A CART
OF CHILDREN
FROM A COLLAPSING
DAY-CARE CENTER
AND THEN CHANGED
THEIR DIAPERS!
All: YAY! CHOMPY!
CHOMPY, WHOSE
TIRELESS RESEARCH
FOUND THE CURE
FOR POLIO.
WASN'T THAT JONAS SALK?
ONLY IF YOU
BELIEVE THOSE LIARS
AT THE PATENT OFFICE!
All: BOO! LIARS
AND CHOMPY,
WHOSE QUICK THINKING
SAVED OUR TOWN
FROM A RAGING FIRE.
[MOO]
[BAA]
All: YAY! CHOMPY!
AND NOW, BEHOLD...
THE LIVING GLORY
THAT IS CHOMPY THE GOAT!
All: OOH!
THAT'S HIM?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
HE'S JUST
A SMELLY OLD GOAT.
WHO SAID THAT?
HOW DARE
YOU MINIMIZE
THE IMPORTANCE
OF CHOMPY?
THE REST OF YOU
CAN HEAD OFF
TO THE CHOMPY THE GOAT
GIFT SHOP...
BECAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE
SOMEBODY NEEDS
A LITTLE ALONE TIME
WITH OUR GOAT HERO.
HA! SEE YOU,
TWERP.
GO! BEG CHOMPY'S
FORGIVENESS!
FOR A TOWN HERO,
HE SURE LOOKS SAD!
YOU THINK
HE LIKES IT
IN THERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WISH I COULD SEE
WHAT HE WAS THINKING.
ONE GOAT MIND-READING
POWER COMING UP.
AW! GOAT LOVE!
THEY SAY IT'S THE MOST
HONEST LOVE THERE IS.
ALL CHOMPY WANTS
IS TO BE FREE--
TO RUN AND FROLIC
AND MEET GIRL GOATS.
WHO DOESN'T
WANT THAT?
I WISH CHOMPY COULD BE
FREE TO LIVE
WHEREVER HIS HEART DESIRES.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
Vicky: HEY, TWERP.
TIME TO GO.
BUT FIRST...
HA HA HA HA!
GET OFF ME,
YOU DORK!
SMELLY OLD GOAT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
CHOMPY'S GONE!
Mayor: AND THAT
MASKED HERO CAPTURED
THE GOATNAPPER.
GOOD WORK,
UNDERWEAR-OVER-
YOUR-HEAD LAD.
UGH! WHEW!
IT'S YOU! THE BOY
WHO DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE RELEVANCE OF CHOMPY.
BUT--
I KNOW.
YOU'RE CRUSHED
BECAUSE YOU COULDN'T
STOP THE GOATNAPPER
BEFORE SHE HANDED
OUR BELOVED GOAT
OVER TO HER TEAM
OF TERRORIST
GOAT-TAKING COHORTS.
WHAT?
TAKE HER AWAY!
HEY! NO!
WOW! VICKY'S GETTING
BLAMED FOR WHAT I DID.
COOL!
Wanda: DON'T YOU
THINK YOU SHOULD
SAY SOMETHING?
WELL, MAYBE--I MEAN,
I SHOULD TELL THE TRUTH.
Mayor:
NEW TOWN HERO TIMMY,
CAN MS. DIMMSDALE
GIVE YOU A RIDE HOME
IN THIS SHINY
NEW HOVERCRAFT?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SEE,
THE TRUTH IS,
VICKY DIDN'T REALLY
TAKE THE--
AND ONCE
YOU GET HOME,
CAN SHE GIVE YOU
THE SHINY NEW HOVERCRAFT?
TIMMY'S NOT
OLD ENOUGH TO DRIVE!
AND HERE'S YOUR SPECIAL
10-AND-UNDER TOWN HERO
DRIVER'S LICENSE.
I CALL SHOTGUN!
SORRY ABOUT
THE HOVERCRAFT,
MS. DIMMSDALE.
THAT'S OK, TIMMY.
YOU'VE GOT TOWN HERO
HOVERCRAFT INSURANCE.
Girl: HEY, LOOK!
IT'S TOWN HERO TIMMY,
A.K.A. UNDERWEAR-
OVER-HIS-HEAD LAD.
LET'S RIP OFF
HIS CLOTHES
AND AUCTION THEM
ON THE INTERNET!
All: TIMMY! YAY!
TIMMY!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
TIMMY.
IT'S NOT
MY BIRTHDAY.
EVERY DAY'S
YOUR BIRTHDAY
WHEN YOU STOP
A GOATNAPPER, HERO.
THANKS FOR SHARING
YOUR HERO CAKE
WITH US, TIMMY.
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE
NOT REALLY A HERO
AND YOU DON'T
DESERVE THE CAKE.
ON TV! THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT TIMMY!
MR. MAYOR,
HAS THE GOATNAPPER
REVEALED THE WHEREABOUTS
OF CHOMPY YET?
NO, BUT WE'RE
GIVING HER
AN INCREASINGLY
BAD HAIR DAY
UNTIL SHE TALKS.
I'M TELLING YOU,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
THE STUPID GOAT--
HEY!
HA HA HA!
IS THAT FAIR?
AFTER ALL,
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO LET CHOMPY GO.
OH, I KNOW.
I'LL FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO FREE HER
AS SOON AS THIS CAKE
STOPS TASTING SO GOOD.
NOPE. STILL TASTY.
VICKY...NOT GUILTY...WISH.
AAH!
I'VE GOT TO BE DREAMING.
[MONKEY
SCREECHING]
AAH!
ARRR!
UHH!
AAH!
Wanda: TIMMY!
OH, THANK HEAVENS
YOU'RE AWAKE.
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
YOU'VE BEEN WISHING
IN YOUR SLEEP,
AND YOU KNOW
THE RULES...
YOU WISH IT,
WE GRANT IT.
I WISH THIS STUFF WAS...
GONE.
OK. I PROBABLY ATE
A LITTLE TOO MUCH
HERO CAKE.
LET'S JUST ALL
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
WISH...GOAT...VICKY.
[GASPS]
AAH!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY WOULD I WISH
FOR THIS STUFF?
Wanda: MAYBE YOUR
DREAMS ARE TRYING
TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
MAYBE I NEED
TO SEE A SHRINK.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA,
CUCKOO CLOCK.
NOW, LET'S TAKE A PEEK
AT WHAT YOUR
SUBCONSCIOUS IS SAYING.
VICKY'S INNOCENT!
I'M THE GOATNAPPER!
ME! ME! ME!
I DON'T DESERVE
TO BE A HERO!
WHOA! TIME-OUT!
I'M NOT GOOD WITH
THIS PSYCHO MUMBO JUMBO.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
I'M SLEEP-WISHING
BECAUSE I FEEL GUILTY?
Mom: TIMMY?
COME IN.
HONEY, ARE YOU OK?
YEAH, BUT CAN I ASK
YOU SOMETHING?
YOU'D STILL LOVE ME
EVEN IF I WASN'T
A HERO, RIGHT?
OH, OF COURSE
WE WOULD, HONEY.
WHAT IF,
HYPOTHETICALLY,
I WAS
THE GOATNAPPER?
WELL, SON,
THEN I'D HAVE
TO DO THIS...
EEK!
HYPOTHETICALLY,
OF COURSE.
WELL, GOOD NIGHT,
SON-WHOM-I-WOULD-HATE-
TO-DISCOVER-WAS-ACTUALLY-
THE-GOATNAPPER.
Dad: OOF!
I CAN'T TELL THEM
I SENT CHOMPY AWAY NOW.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE DREAM-WISHING?
I CAN'T DREAM
IF I DON'T SLEEP, RIGHT?
SO I'LL JUST STAY AWAKE
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[WOLF HOWLS]
Mom: TOWN HERO,
TIME FOR SCHOOL.
IS IT THE REST
OF MY LIFE YET?
Timmy: GUILTY...
MY FAULT...I WISH...
RAINING DUCKS!
[THUNDER]
[QUACK QUACK]
[SNORING]
NOT VICKY...I WISH...
SWARM OF LAB MICE!
AAH!
WE'VE GOT TO GET
CHOMPY BACK HERE.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME BEFORE HE...
WISHES FOR SOMETHING
REALLY DANGEROUS.
I WISH FOR
A GIGANTIC MONSTER
THAT WON'T GO AWAY
UNTIL I TELL THE TRUTH
ABOUT CHOMPY!
[ROARING]
LOOK OUT!
AAH!
I WISH WE WERE
WITH CHOMPY!
THIS MUST BE WHERE
WE SENT CHOMPY.
GREAT. ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS FIND HIM AND--
[SNORING]
I WISH...
FIELD ON FIRE!
[BAA]
CHOMPY, IT'S YOU!
YOU'VE GOT TO COME BACK
TO DIMMSDALE. YOU--
[BAA BAA]
[BAA]
HE'S SO HAPPY HERE.
HE'S GOT A FAMILY
AND KIDS NOW.
I CAN'T TAKE HIM AWAY
FROM ALL THIS
JUST SO HE CAN BE
ON DISPLAY IN A STUPID PEN.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO, TIMMY?
WHAT I SHOULD'VE DONE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I WISH
I WAS AT CITY HALL!
WE'RE HERE
AT CITY HALL,
WHERE TOWN HERO
TIMMY TURNER
HAS SCHEDULED
A PRESS CONFERENCE
ABOUT CHOMPY.
UH, HI, EVERYBODY.
I HAVE A CONFESSION
TO MAKE.
I'M NO HERO.
[AUDIENCE GASPS]
HE'S SO MODEST.
LET'S GIVE HIM
ANOTHER HOVERCRAFT
TO WRECK.
NO! NO!
NO MORE HOVERCRAFTS!
NO MORE GIFTS!
NO MORE CAKE!
I CAN'T TAKE IT
ANYMORE!
VICKY DIDN'T MAKE
CHOMPY GO AWAY!
I DID!
EEK!
Timmy: I DID!
I DID!
I HAD TO LET HIM GO.
DON'T YOU SEE? CHOMPY
WAS MISERABLE IN THAT PEN.
HE DESERVES TO BE
HAPPY AND FREE!
All: AWW...YAY!
THANKS, EVERYONE.
SO I GUESS THAT MEANS
I'M NOT IN TROUBLE?
HEH HEH.
OF COURSE YOU ARE.
GET HIM!
[BAA BAA]
A DEAD END!
I'M DOOMED!
WELL, YOU LIVED
A GOOD LIFE, RIGHT?
I'M ONLY 10!
I SAID "GOOD,"
NOT "LONG."
All: GET HIM!
All: CHOMPY!
AND HE'S GOT
A FAMILY!
All: AWW!
TIMMY TURNER,
BECAUSE OF YOU,
WE NOW HAVE
4 HAPPY MASCOTS
INSTEAD OF ONE
MISERABLE ONE.
YOU'RE A HERO
AGAIN.
AND CHOMPY?
FREE TO COME AND GO
AS HE PLEASES.
[BAA]
3 CHEERS FOR CHOMPY
AND TIMMY!
HIP, HIP, HOORAY!
HIP, HIP, HOO--
GROUNDED?
WELL, SURE, HONEY.
WE'RE PROUD OF YOU
FOR TELLING THE TRUTH,
BUT YOU STILL LIED
TO THE ENTIRE TOWN.
BUT MY LIE MADE
EVERYTHING BETTER.
I KNOW IT WAS WRONG,
BUT DOESN'T THAT COUNT
FOR ANYTHING?
EEK!
APPARENTLY NOT.
GOOD NIGHT,
SON-WE-STILL-LOVE
EVEN-THOUGH-
HE'S-A-GROUNDED-
GOATNAPPER.
AH, CHEER UP,
TIMMY.
5 MONTHS
WILL GO BY LIKE THAT.
IT'S OK. CHOMPY'S BACK
AND HAPPY.
I DON'T FEEL
GUILTY ANYMORE,
AND EVERYTHING
IS BACK TO--
[SNORING]
HE'S SOUND
ASLEEP.
AND NO DREAM-WISHING.
BUT I CAN'T HELP
THINKING WE FORGOT
SOMETHING.
HELLO? HELLO? OH!
CHOMPY! YOU'RE HERE
TO SAVE ME!
EEK! OH!
HA HA HA!
OH, WELL,
IT'S PROBABLY
NOTHING.
RAINING DUCKS!
[QUACK]
HEY,
IS THE COAST CLEAR?
IT WOULD APPEAR
TO BE.
ON 3. READY?
3!
[WHISTLE]
HOLY DOUBLE-WIDE TRAILER!
THAT WHISTLE!
I KNOW THAT WHISTLE!
A.J.: IT'S TIMMY!
LOOK OUT!
OUCH!
YOU GOT NAILED!
WELL, THIS WILL BE
UNPLEASANT. OOF!
HA! IT'S 83 TO, UH...
[WHISTLES]
WHAT DO YOU GUYS
HAVE?
NOTHING. OW!
RIGHT. I WIN!
WOW! TIMMY'S WON
ANOTHER GAME
OF TIMMY-BALL!
THAT'S THE FIRST RULE
IN TIMMY-BALL--
TIMMY WINS.
Wanda: I THOUGHT
THERE WERE NO RULES
IN TIMMY-BALL.
WELL, THAT'S
THE SECOND RULE.
RUN!
HA HA HA!
YOU CAN'T GO
IN THERE!
THAT'S
DR. BENDER'S YARD!
SO?
DUDE, DIDN'T YOU SEE
THE LIGHTNING
AND HEAR
THE WEIRD MUSIC?
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
IT'S NIGHTTIME?
A.J.: DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
HE'S A DENTIST AND MEAN.
HE'S A MEAN  DENTIST!
[THUNDER]
WOW! LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THIS TOOTH!
Timmy: HEY!
MY BALL!
OW!
OH, HELLO.
IS THIS YOUR BALL
ON MY LAWN
AND YOUR ANKLE
IN MY TRAP?
UH, UH...
WOW! IS THAT
SHORT FOR,
"OH, GOSH, MY TEETH
ARE HIDEOUS."
MAY I PLEASE JUST
HAVE MY BALL BACK?
EH, WHAT'S THE WORD
I'M LOOKING FOR?
UH, NO!
ONLY BOYS
WITH PERFECT TEETH
LIKE MINE
CAN HAVE A BALL
AS FUN AS THIS.
AND WHO HAS TEETH
AS GOOD AS YOURS?
MAY I PRESENT TO YOU
AND YOUR BIG,
SILLY TEETH--
MY SON WENDELL.
HERE YOU GO,
WENDELL.
WOW! THIS
SURE IS A FUN BALL
THAT'S MINE NOW.
YOUR TEETH
AREN'T SO GREAT.
WELL, BUCKY,
THE BUCKTOOTHED-
TOOTHED BOY,
THAT'S WHERE
YOU'RE WRONG.
BOTH I AND MY SON
HAVE PERFECT TEETH.
MY COMB
HAS PERFECT TEETH.
AND EVEN OUR DOG
IS ON ITS WAY
TO GOOD ORAL PERFECTION.
[DOG BARKS AND GROWLS]
COME ON, WENDELL.
LET'S PLAY A GAME
OF PERFECT-TEETH BALL.
[OVEN BELL RINGS]
Wanda: OH,
CHEER UP, TIMMY.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST WISH FOR
ANOTHER BALL?
IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE BALL.
HE TOOK MY STUFF
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T
LIKE MY TEETH.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT'S NOT TO GET?
THE SILLY TEETH PART
OR THE NOT-HAVING-
THE-BALL PART?
I'M NOT AGREEING
WITH HIM.
I'M JUST
SAYING IT'S PRETTY
STRAIGHTFORWARD.
Dad: OH, SON.
CAN I HAVE SOME
OF THAT SALT
YOU'RE WHISPERING TO?
SURE.
THANKS, SON.
GOOD OLD
HEALTHY SALT.
Cosmo: OW! OW!
I HAD JUST ENOUGH TIME
WHEN I GOT BACK FROM WORK
TO MAKE MY SPECIAL
PINK FLAMINGO CASSEROLE.
EW! THAT CASSEROLE'S
GRAY--T. GREAT! YEAH!
HA HA HA!
WHO WANTS CHINESE?
Dad: CAN I ADD SALT
TO IT?
Cosmo: YOW! WHOA!
YOU KNOW, YOUR DAD
REALLY OUGHT TO WATCH
HIS SODIUM INTAKE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M BEING TEASED
BECAUSE MY TEETH
ARE DIFFERENT
THAN BENDER'S.
Timmy: TEETH.
STUPID.
BIG?
Dr. Bender:
YOU MIGHT NEED
TO PUT THOSE
IN THE CORRECT ORDER.
HE WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO MAKE FUN OF MY TEETH
IF EVERYBODY
HAD THE SAME TEETH.
HEY, YOU GUYS
COULD DO THAT, RIGHT?
WELL, SURE, TIMMY.
THEN I WISH EVERYTHING
AND EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD
LOOKED EXACTLY THE SAME.
HEY! WHAT HAPPENED?
HEY! I'M A GRAY BLOB!
OH, MY GOSH! EVERYBODY
LOOKS EXACTLY THE SAME!
GRAY BLOBS!
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
BENDER'S FACE
WHEN HE SEES HE'S EXACTLY
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE!
RIGHT, GUYS?
COSMO? WANDA?
GUYS? UH-OH.
ARE YOU TIMMY?
NO, I'M CHET.
I'M DOMINIC.
ARE YOU TIMMY?
I JUST TOLD YOU.
I'M CHET.
I HATE THIS WISH.
I CAN'T TELL WHICH BLOB
IS OUR BLOB.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Woman: VERY WELL.
PLEASE HOLD.
VERY WELL. PLEASE HOLD.
VERY WELL.
THANK YOU FOR HOLDING.
Woman: HEY! WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE?
WHAT HAPPENED?
I WAS JUST GRANTING
MY KID A WISH
FOR A PONY,
AND NOW I'M HERE
IN FAIRY WORLD.
I WAS JUST GRANTING
MY KID A WISH FOR A DUCKIE,
AND NOW
I'M IN FAIRY WORLD.
THAT'S WEIRD...
BECAUSE WE WERE JUST
GRANTING A WISH
THAT EVERYBODY
IN THE WORLD LOOKED
EXACTLY THE SAME
AS EVERYBODY ELSE,
AND NOW WE'RE
IN FAIRY--WHAT?
WAS THAT
A BAD THING?
Man: YES!
OH, NO! IT'S THE TOUGHEST
FAIRY IN THE UNIVERSE--
JORGEN VON STRANGLE!
RIGHT NOW, HE'S DOING
THE VON STRANGLY PART!
YOU TWO HAVE CAUSED
A MAJOR MAGICAL
FLUCTUATION
IN THE MAGIC SPACE
CONTINUUM FLUX!
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
Jorgen: BECAUSE
OF WHAT YOU DID,
EVERYONE NOW LOOKS
EXACTLY THE SAME,
AND NONE
OF THE FAIRIES
CAN FIND THEIR KIDS!
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT'S DOING
TO THE FAIRIES?
OOH! UGH!
OH, NO!
MAGICAL BACKUP!
THAT ONLY HAPPENS
WHEN FAIRIES CAN'T GRANT
WISHES FOR THEIR KIDS!
HA HA HA! I MEAN--
POOR LITTLE FAIRY.
WE GOT TO FIND TIMMY!
BEFORE ALL
THE FAIRIES...EXPLODE!
NO! YOW!
OH, NO! COSMO!
HA! JUST GOOFING
WITH YOU, BABY.
LET'S GO.
HEY THERE.
WANT TO PLAY
SOME BLOB-BALL?
I ONLY PLAY
TIMMY-BALL.
WHAT'S A TIMMY?
MAN,
THIS WORLD REEKS.
Dr. Bender:
OH, HELLO.
IS THIS YOUR BALL
ON OUR LAWN
AND YOUR GRAY
ON OUR GRAY?
HEY, DR. BENDER!
WENDELL!
YOU'RE BIG GRAY BLOBS
JUST LIKE ME! HA HA HA!
ACTUALLY,
WE'RE THE GRAYEST
AND THE BLOBBIEST.
BUT EVERYONE
IS EXACTLY ALIKE!
THAT'S WHERE
YOU'RE WRONG,
LITTLE NOT-THAT-GRAY BOY.
IN FACT, ONLY BLOBS
AS GRAY AND BLOBBY
AS WE ARE
CAN HAVE A GRAY BALL
AS FUN AS THIS.
NOW, BEAT IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD'S
EXACTLY ALIKE,
AND THOSE CREEPS STILL
THINK THEY'RE BETTER
THAN EVERYONE ELSE!
GOT TO GET COSMO
AND WANDA TO FIND ME
SO I CAN UNWISH THIS WISH!
THERE'S NO TIME TO WASTE!
TIMMY?
CHET.
CHET!
NOW ARE YOU TIMMY?
OH, NO!
MAGIC BUILDUP!
I'M NOT FALLING
FOR THAT ONE AGAIN.
HEY!
IT'S RAINING ME!
OH, IF I EXPLODE,
WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FIND TIMMY!
Timmy: GOT TO FIND
SOMETHING THAT'LL MAKE
COSMO AND WANDA NOTICE ME.
GRAY, GRAY, GRAY...
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR, SWEETIE?
DO WE HAVE A MARKER
AND SOME PAPER?
I NEED TO MAKE
A POSTER.
OH, SURE, HON.
YEAH. THAT'S VIBRANT
AND NOTICEABLE.
I'M HOME AND GRAY.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY, DEAR?
GRAY!
BUT I HAD
JUST ENOUGH TIME
TO MAKE MY LOVELY
GRAY FLAMINGO
CASSEROLE.
THAT'S GRAY--T!
HA HA HA!
Timmy: JEEZ. MY PARENTS
MIGHT BE GRAY BLOBS
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE,
BUT THEY'RE STILL
THEIR GOOFY SELVES,
WHICH MEANS...
OH, NO! PINK!
HA HA HA!
MOM STILL CAN'T COOK!
THAT'S WHY
THEY'RE STILL GOOFY
AND BENDER
IS STILL A JERK!
I CHANGED THEIR OUTSIDES,
NOT THEIR INSIDES!
MOM, CAN I HAVE YOUR
HIDEOUS PINK CASSEROLE?
SURE!
THERE'S NO TIME
TO LOSE!
IF I CHANGE MY OUTSIDE,
THEN COSMO AND WANDA
CAN FIND ME.
I HOPE.
COSMO! WANDA! IT'S ME...
WITH MY PINK HAT!
I'M DIFFERENT!
LOOK! DIFFERENT!
HEY! WHO'S THE FREAK
WITH THE PINK ON HIS HEAD?
LET'S GET HIM
AND GRAY HIM UP!
I CAN'T FIND TIMMY
ANYWHERE,
AND...UH-OH!
I'M STARTING TO FEEL
ALL EXPLODY!
COSMO! WANDA!
IT'S ME! TIMMY!
I SEE A LITTLE
PINK DOT!
THAT'S OUR LITTLE
YOU FOUND ME!
OF COURSE.
YOU STICK OUT LIKE
A BIG, SORE, PINK THUMB.
UH, LESS TALKY,
MORE WISHY!
I WISH I WAS
DIFFERENT AGAIN.
I WISH THE WHOLE WORLD
WAS BACK TO THE WAY
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE!
MY TEETH! MY HEAD!
MY HAT! MY GOSH!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
JUST MAKE
ANOTHER WISH.
[ALL SIGH]
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
TIMMY?
WHY AREN'T YOU
AND YOUR FRIENDS
HITTING EACH OTHER
IN THE HEAD WITH YOUR BALL?
AW, THAT CREEP DENTIST
DOWN THE STREET
WON'T GIVE ME
MY BALL BACK
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
LIKE MY TEETH.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, LET'S SEE
IF WE CAN REASON
WITH HIM.
Dr. Bender: NOW GO,
OTHER BAD-TOOTHED BOY
AND NEVER DARKEN
OUR DOORWAY AGAIN
WITH YOUR HORRIBLE
BITE RADIUS.
HERE'S YOUR NEW
BOOMERANG, WENDELL.
HA HA! THIS SURE
IS A FUN BOOMERANG
THAT'S MINE NOW!
HA HA!
[WHISTLE]
GIVE ME BACK
MY BALL, WENDELL.
WHAT'S THE WORD
I'M LOOKING FOR?
OH, YEAH. NO!
HA HA HA!
YOU MUST BE
DR. BENDER,
AND THAT MUST BE
TIMMY'S BALL.
MAY WE HAVE IT BACK?
IN THIS ORDER--
RIGHT, RIGHT, AND NO,
MAMA TOOTH-FACE.
WELL, YOU CLEARLY
DON'T KNOW THE RULES
OF TIMMY-BALL.
OH?
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU PLAY IT LIKE THIS.
[CRASH]
YOU KNOW, TIMMY.
PERFECT TEETH
MIGHT BE NICE,
BUT IF THEY'RE
IN A MOUTH THAT'S MEAN,
THEY MIGHT AS WELL
NOT BE IN THE MOUTH AT ALL.
THANKS, MOM.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU JUST SAID,
BUT IT SURE MAKES ME
FEEL BETTER.
MY DENTURES! GIVE ME BACK
MY PERFECT TEETH!
JUMP BALL. COME ON.
YOU WANT IT?
WORK FOR IT.
AND, DUDE, YOU LEFT
THESE AT MY HOUSE.
AAH!
THOSE DON'T
BELONG IN THERE!
WHO WANTS TO PLAY
TIMMY-BALL?
All: UH, WELL, I...
UHH!
OUCH!
OOH!
All: AAH!
HEY, CUT IT OUT!
NO FAIR! I'M HAIRLESS!
Mom: OH, COME ON,
YOU GUYS.
WHERE'S YOUR
GAME FACE?
BRING IT ON.
IS THERE
A MESSAGE THERE?
I THINK IT'S THIS.
IF YOU'RE PLAYING
TIMMY-BALL, WEAR A HELMET.
WHAT ABOUT
WANDA-BALL?
I KNOW THAT GAME!
DID YOU KNOW I USE
A CINDER BLOCK?
DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
AAH!
Wanda: COME ON.
BRING IT ON, MEAT.
I GOT YOUR GAME
RIGHT HERE.
OH, IS THAT ALL
YOU GOT? COME ON.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--