♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ AND NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪
♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BED, TWERP!
♪ THE DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH ♪
♪ WHO GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY ♪
♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪ ODD PARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪
♪ OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE ♪
♪ GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE ♪
♪ GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE ♪
♪ LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE! ♪
♪ ODD PARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE THE KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
YEAH, RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
Timmy: BOY...
THE COMIC BOOK FANTASY
AND REALITY AVOIDANCE EXPO,
WHERE PEOPLE WHO REALLY LIKE
THIS STUFF CAN GET TOGETHER
AND PROVE THEY'RE NOT GEEKS.
AND THIS YEAR,
I'M GONNA GET MY COMIC SIGNED
BY THE CRIMSON CHIN!
HE'S THE GREATEST
SUPERHERO EVER!
I'M HERE FOR
THE COSTUME CONTEST.
THERE'S
A COSTUME CONTEST?
AW, COOL!
THE CRIMSON CHIN!
I WISH COSMO AND WANDA
COULD BE HERE TO SEE THIS.
HI, TIMMY!
HI, COSMO.
HI, WANDA.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
IF ANYBODY
FINDS YOU, I NEVER
GET TO SEE YOU AGAIN!
RELAX.
WE'RE HERE
EVERY YEAR.
OH, EVERYBODY'S
IN COSTUME.
NOBODY EVER KNOWS
WE'RE REAL.
AS LONG AS EVERYBODY
THINKS WE'RE BIG-HEADED
KIDS IN COSTUMES,
WE HAVEN'T
BROKEN THE RULES.
HEY, NICE WINGS,
BIG-HEADED KID.
THANKS.
GREAT USE OF MULCH.
Announcer: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
PLEASE WELCOME YOUR FAVORITE
SUPERHERO AND MINE...
HE'S HERE.
Announcer: THE CRIMSON CHIN!
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[ONE MAN COUGHS]
WOW, THE CRIMSON CHIN
REALLY LET HIMSELF GO.
THAT CRIMSON CHIN STINKS!
LOOKS LIKE
HE EATS, TOO.
I WISH THE REAL
CRIMSON CHIN WERE HERE.
HEY, WE CAN DO THAT.
ONE HERO...
WITH EVERYTHING
ON IT.
Timmy: IT'S THE REAL
CRIMSON CHIN!
IN THE NAME OF ALL THAT
IS RIGHT, I--WHAT? HEY!
THIS ISN'T MY WORLD.
I'M MUCH MORE HEAVILY
INKED THAN YOU ARE.
WHERE AM I?
YOU'RE IN DIMSDALE,
AND I'M TIMMY.
I'M YOUR BIGGEST FAN.
I WAS JUST
IN A HEROIC BATTLE
OF GOOD VERSUS EVIL,
WHEN SUDDENLY...
GREAT JAWS OF JUSTICE!
SPATULA WOMAN!
BUT THAT'S JUST
A GEEK IN A COSTUME.
NO, DON'T LOOK.
SHE'S NOT NICE.
EGAD! COUNTRY BOY!
WITH ONE OF HIS DEADLY
EXPLODING PIG GRENADES.
AND MY ARCH NEMESIS
WITH HIS KNEECAP OF DEATH:
THE BRONZE KNEECAP!
CLEARLY I'VE STUMBLED
INTO SOME SORT OF MASSIVE
SUPERVILLAIN HOO-HA!
Wanda: HE THINKS
THEY'RE ACTUAL
BAD GUYS.
AND WITH HIS POWERS,
HE'S GONNA RIP THROUGH THEM
LIKE TISSUE.
TIME TO EAT CHIN, FELLAS!
NO! I WISH HIS POWERS
DIDN'T WORK.
[TWINKLING]
Crimson Chin: OH!
COOL WANDS.
WHERE'D YOU GET 'EM?
UH...INTERNET?
MY POWER'S GONE.
MUST BE SOME CHINTONITE
IN THIS FACILITY.
HOLY HYGIENIST!
THIS PERIODICAL.
IT REVEALS
MY SECRET IDENTITY.
Timmy: YEAH.
CHARLES HAMPTON INDIGO,
LANTERN-JAWED REPORTER
FOR THE  DAILY BLABBITY.
QUIET!
AND THE LOCATION
OF MY CHINSTRAP
OF SOLITUDE.
JUST OUTSIDE
OF CHINCINATTI.
STOP THAT!
AND MY DIMPLE SIZE!
THAT'S SO PERSONAL.
BUT--BUT HOW?
WELL, YOU'RE
A MADE-UP CHARACTER
IN MY WORLD.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
DID YOU HAVE
AN IMAGINARY FRIEND
WHEN YOU WERE A KID?
SURE. EDDIE,
THE FURRY GERBIL.
HE WAS ALWAYS
SO CUTE AND--
THAT'S YOU.
I'M AN IMAGINARY
GERBIL?
BASICALLY.
HEY, ARE YOU OK?
OH, I'M FINE.
I'M JUST DEALING
WITH THE FACT
THAT I DON'T EXIST.
BUT...
WHATEVER.
JUST PUT ME BACK
IN MY STUPID,
MADE-UP BOOK.
I HAVE TO GO BACK
AND BE "FICTIONAL."
OK. I WISH YOU WERE
BACK IN THE BOOK
WITH ALL YOUR POWERS.
[TWINKLING]
I, THE BRONZE KNEECAP,
WITH MY BIG BRONZE KNEECAP,
SHALL..
DO YOU MIND?
I'M HAVING A BIT
OF A BREAKDOWN HERE.
HE SURE SEEMS UPSET.
THAT'S OK.
HE'S A HERO.
SOON EVERYTHING WILL BE
JUST FINE IN THE WORLD
OF THE CRIMSON CHIN.
EVERYTHING IS  NOT FINE
IN THE WORLD
OF THE CRIMSON CHIN.
WELCOME TO
HERO CONVENTION NEWS.
I'M ANCHORMAN.
HERE'S ANCHORWOMAN.
THANKS, BOB. WE'VE LEARNED THAT
THE LATEST CRIMSON CHIN ISSUE
HAS EVERYONE'S FAVORITE HERO
LYING IN A FETAL POSITION
CRYING FOR 32 FULL PAGES.
THE BOOK'S CANCELLATION
IS IMMINENT.
WHICH IS  NOT FINE.
WHY ARE THE NEW
CRIMSON CHIN BOOKS
IN THE TRASH?
FETAL POSITION,
FETAL POSITION.
IT'S TRUE!
HE'S LOST
HIS FIGHTING SPIRIT,
AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
Cosmo: REALLY? COOL.
USUALLY IT'S MINE.
I MEAN...
I'M SORRY, TIMMY.
IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO?
MAYBE I SHOULD GO
TALK TO HIM.
I WISH I COULD BE
IN THE CRIMSON CHIN'S
COMIC BOOK.
[TWINKLING]
WOW, BEING IN A COMIC BOOK
IS AWESOME!
COOL!
THE  DAILY BLABBITY.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GET IN?
I KNOW.
I'LL JUST GO TO
THE NEXT PANEL
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
I'LL BE OUTSIDE THE OFFICE OF...
ACE REPORTER
CHARLES HAMPTON INDIGO,
WHO IS SECRETLY
THE CRIMSON CHIN.
[MAN SOBBING]
EXCUSE ME.
MR. INDIGO?
WHAT? WHO IS IT?
YOU! OH, YOU'RE
THE "REAL BOY"
WHO SHOWED ME
I'M A BIG, FAT LIE.
COME ON, CHARLES.
YOU'RE A HERO.
I'M NO HERO.
SURE YOU ARE.
YOU'VE GOT TO SNAP
OUT OF THIS.
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
THE GOOD TIMES.
LIKE WHEN?
LIKE, OVER THERE!
IT'S A FLASHBACK
TO ISSUE NUMBER ONE
WHEN YOU WERE JUST
A STRUGGLING TALK SHOW HOST
BITTEN BY A RADIOACTIVE
HANDSOME ACTOR.
WELL, HAS
THE RADIOACTIVITY
AFFECTED YOUR LOVE LIFE?
WAH! AH! MY CHIN!
AND IN THIS PANEL
WHEN YOUR LIFE CHANGED FOREVER.
Crimson Chin, voice-over:
FEEL FUNNY...
ACK! MY CHIN IS TINGLING.
Timmy: THAT HANDSOME ACTOR'S
BITE GAVE YOU
AMAZING CHINTASTIC POWERS
AND AN AMAZING
CHINTASTIC COSTUME.
I AM THE CRIMSON CHIN!
♪ HERE COMES THE CRIMSON CHIN ♪
HELLO!
WAIT!
LEAVE ME ALONE.
I'M GOING TO BED.
BUT IT'S 10 A.M.
NOT IN THIS PANEL.
MAN, HE'S DEPRESSED.
HE NEEDS SOMEBODY AT HIS SIDE
TO KICK HIM INTO SHAPE.
WHAT DO THEY CALL THOSE THINGS?
OH, YEAH, SIDE-KICKS.
THIS LOOKS LIKE A JOB FOR...
HEY!
Timmy: COSMO, WANDA!
A LITTLE HELP,
PLEASE.
YOU WANT US TO COME
IN THERE, SWEETIE?
NO, BUT I COULD USE
A COOL SIDE-KICK COSTUME.
[TWINKLING]
PERFECT!
I'M OFF TO FIGHT CRIME AS...
CLEFT, THE BOY CHIN WONDER!
AND WITH MY UTILITY CLEFT,
I CAN SWING FROM PANEL TO PANEL.
[WHISTLING]
I LIKE MY COPS
THE WAY I LIKE
MY EGGS...
SCRAMBLED!
AH HA HA HA HA!
Cleft: AND I LIKE MY COPS
NOT BEING FLIPPED AROUND
ON A BIG SPATULA THINGY!
[GASPS] IT'S...
I GOT TO WORK ON
MY HEROIC DIALOGUE.
Man: HELP! OH, HELP!
OH, NO! THE BRONZE KNEECAP
IS HOLDING THE MAYOR
OF CHINCINATTI HOSTAGE!
YOU FIEND!
THE CRIMSON CHIN
WILL STOP YOU
LIKE HE ALWAYS DOES.
DON'T MAKE ME
USE THIS!
I'D BETTER USE THE CHIN SIGNAL.
THE CHIN SIGNAL!
I KNOW WHAT I MUST DO.
HEY! YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
SPRING INTO ACTION!
WHY AREN'T YOU
SPRINGING?
BECAUSE THIS IS
ALL A LIE.
IT'S NOT REAL.
WHAT'S MY MOTIVATION?
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
THAT'S YOUR MOTIVATION.
THOSE ARE REAL
FICTIONAL PEOPLE
IN REAL FICTIONAL DANGER.
YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
I  AM RIGHT.
NO MORE DOUBTS.
NO MORE DOUBTS!
NO MORE DISTRAC--
TV announcer: WE NOW RETURN
TO  ALL MY PARENTS OFFSPRING.
OOH, MY SOAP.
FINE! IF YOU WON'T STOP
THE BRONZE KNEECAP, I WILL!
OR NOT.
COULDN'T YOU HAVE
SHAVED THIS THING?
DON'T MAKE ME
USE THIS!
THE CRIMSON CHIN
IS STILL A HERO, RIGHT?
HE'LL SAVE ME, RIGHT?
STUPID KETCHUP!
WELL, UH...BESIDES, I'M NOT
IN ANY REAL TROUBLE, RIGHT?
IF I WERE IN ANY REAL DANGER,
MY GODPARENTS WOULD GET ME
OUT OF HERE, RIGHT?
STUPID KETCHUP!
CHIN! YOU'VE GOT TO
SNAP OUT OF IT.
THE CITY NEEDS YOU.
THE WORLD NEEDS YOU.
I NEED YOU!
IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF YOU'RE MADE UP.
YOU'RE REAL TO ME.
BESIDES, WHAT WOULD
EDDIE THE IMAGINARY
FURRY GERBIL SAY?
CHARLES,
YOU CAN DO IT,
CHARLES.
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF
LIKE YOU USED TO
BELIEVE IN ME.
[CHATTERING]
HAVE FAITH.
OH, MAN.
THIS IS IT!
Crimson Chin: BY MY MOTHER'S
MANDIBLE, I SAY NAY!
♪ THE CRIMSON CHIN ♪
IT'S THE CRIMSON CHIN!
NICE GOING, C.C.
YOU SAVED ME.
ACTUALLY, TIMMY,
YOU SAVED ME...
FROM MYSELF.
[RECORD SKIDS]
WOW, THAT WAS
SCHMALTZY.
WHO'D YOU SAY WRITES
MY COMIC BOOK?
SOME 40 YEAR OLD DUDE
WHO LIVES WITH HIS MOM.
ANY...MONEY IN IT?
LIVES WITH HIS MOM.
RIGHT.
LET'S GO KICK
SOME BAD-GUY BOOTIE.
UP, UP, AND AWAY!
AHA! LOOK! IT'S
THE CRIMSON CRYBABY!
THAT CRIMSON CHIN
IS  SO LAST ISSUE.
I GOT IT, I GOT IT!
NICE USE OF CHIN,
CLEFT.
THANKS.
I WARNED YOU NOT TO
MAKE ME USE THIS.
NOW I'M USING IT.
LOOK OUT, DUDE!
YOU MIGHT HAVE
A KNEECAP OF BRONZE,
BRONZE KNEECAP,
BUT YOU'VE ALWAYS HAD
A JAW MADE OF GLASS.
All: HOORAY FOR
THE CRIMSON CHIN!
IT'S BEEN GREAT
WORKING WITH YOU,
MR. CHIN.
THE PLEASURE'S
ALL MINE, TIMMY.
I'M GLAD WE'RE PALS.
WHETHER I'M REAL OR NOT,
YOU'RE PART OF
MY CONTINUITY NOW.
AFTER ALL, EVERY CHIN
NEEDS A CLEFT.
COOL! WHAT'S NEXT?
UH, NOTHIN'.
IT'S THE END OF THE BOOK.
SEE? THAT'S THE LETTERS
TO THE EDITOR PAGE
WHERE GEEKY COMIC FANS
WRITE ABOUT HOW COOL I AM.
HEY, LOOK!
IT'S A LETTER FROM YOU.
UH, I GOT TO GO.
YOU SPELLED "CHIN" WRONG.
AH HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA HA!
Announcer: AND THE WINNER
OF THE COSTUME CONTEST
AND THE VERY VALUABLE
PRETTY PONY ISSUES 2
AND 3 IS...
WOW! WHAT AN AMAZING
ENTRANCE AND COSTUME.
WHOEVER YOU ARE,
YOU WIN!
OH, HE'S MY HERO.
AND THIS IS MINE.
STUPID KETCHUP!
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
BYE, TIMMY.
BYE, VICKY.
WE'RE GOING.
NO! DON'T LEAVE!
TAKE ME WITH YOU!
I LOVE YOU.
YES, I DO.
AW, LISTEN TO VICKY.
ISN'T IT GREAT TO HAVE
A BABY-SITTER THAT LOVES
OUR TIMMY SO MUCH?
YOU'RE SO SMART AND CUTE
AND WELL-GROOMED.
AND SHE'S
SO COMPLIMENTARY.
USUALLY, YOU GOTTA
PAY EXTRA FOR THAT.
[LAUGHING]
THAT'S WHY
I LOVE YOU, DOYDLE.
OH, YES, I DO.
MAN, I HATE IT
WHEN VICKY BRINGS
HER STUPID DOG OVER.
SHE SURE DOES LOVE
THAT DOG MORE THAN
SHE LOVES YOU.
SHE LOVES EVERYTHING
MORE THAN TIMMY.
EVEN DUST BUNNIES?
MEASLES?
OH, MUCH MORE
THAN TIMMY.
DEAD BUGS?
LESS THAN MEASLES
BUT MORE THAN TIMMY.
YOUR PARENTS LEFT
A TO-DO LIST FOR YOU.
THIS IS A LIST
OF THINGS TO DO
FOR YOUR DOG...
IN YOUR HANDWRITING.
AND THE HAND THAT WROTE IT
MAKES THIS! MOVE IT!
[THUNDERCLAP]
[SNIFFING]
Vicky: DOYDLE, DINNER!
OH, BOY!
STEAK!
NOT FOR YOU!
OH, BOY.
PLASTIC.
Timmy: MAN, THIS STINKS.
I'M THIS DOG'S DOG.
ISN'T THAT
A RAP GROUP?
WORD!
[RAP MUSIC PLAYS]
IF I SWITCHED PLACES
WITH DOYDLE,
VICKY'D TREAT ME AS NICE
AS SHE TREATS HIM.
GREAT IDEA, TIMMY.
YEAH. DOGS HAVE
A BETTER SENSE OF SMELL,
AND THEY CAN SEE
IN BLACK AND WHITE,
AND THEY CAN GO TO THE BATHROOM
ANYWHERE THEY WANT!
SO CAN I.
I'M JUST POLITE.
I WISH I COULD
SWITCH PLACES
WITH VICKY'S DOG.
[TWINKLE]
Timmy: COOL!
I HAVE DOG VISION.
[FOOTSTEPS]
YOU! BED!
[RUFF RUFF]
OOH, COME WITH ME!
WHO'S A GOOD BOY?
[PANTING]
SAY YOU LOVE ME.
SAY IT!
[BARKING]
Timmy's voice:
YOU'RE NOT SMART,
AND YOU GOT A BIG, FAT HEAD,
AND BOYS THINK
YOU'RE CREEPY, AND...
THAT'S A GOOD DOYDLE.
OH, DOYDLEY-DOO.
IT MUST BE GREAT
BEING A DOG.
[SNICKERS]
[GROWLING]
COOL! I CAN EAT
MY OWN HOMEWORK!
THAT'S RIGHT, FOLKS,
NEW LIQUID WEEDWHACKER
IS THE BEST DERN WHACKER
FOR WEEDS.
TV announcer: AND AS SHAMROCK,
THE IRISH MAULER, LIFTS MIKE,
THE ACCOUNTANT FROM REDLANDS--
THAT'S IT, DOYDLE.
YOU CAN CHEW
WHAT YOU WANT,
PIDDLE ON
AND EAT WHAT YOU WANT
TONIGHT--YOU KNOW WHY?
[RUFF RUFF RUFF]
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE TOMORROW'S
YOUR SPECIAL DAY.
THE DAY YOU GET FIXED.
[WHIMPERS]
TV announcer: OOH,
THAT'S GOTTA HURT!
[SNORING]
YOU GUYS GOT
TO PUT ME BACK
IN MY OLD BODY.
I WISH I WAS
BACK TO NORMAL.
[BARKING]
TIMMY SURE
SEEMS EXCITED.
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T SPEAK DOG.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU DON'T SPEAK DOG?!
LEARN! LEARN!
[DOG HOWLING]
[HONKING HORN]
COME ON, DOYDLE.
THE TWERP'S PARENTS
ARE HOME.
Cosmo: AW, TIMMY
JUST FILED THOSE.
TIMMY'S LEAVING.
WE SHOULD FOLLOW HIM.
BUT WHICH TIMMY
IS TIMMY?
THAT'S
A GOOD QUESTION.
YOU GO WITH
THE DOG BODY.
I'LL STAY WITH
THE TIMMY BODY
SO THE DOG
DOESN'T RUIN IT.
[CRYING]
OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER,
BIG DADDY?
WE HAVEN'T BEEN APART
SINCE WE'VE BEEN MARRIED.
OH, BUT IT'S ONLY
FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
GOOPY.
AND  DA RULES
DO SAY...
"WE HAVE TO
WATCH OUT FOR TIMMY."
♪ I MARRIED
THE SMART ONE ♪
♪ I MARRIED THE... ♪
WELL, HE'S CUTE,
RIGHT?
Vicky: YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE
YOUR NEW VETERINARIAN--OH, YES.
HE SPEAKS TO ALL MY PETS,
LIKE HAPPY THE GOLDFISH...
SHIVER THE CAT...
AND GIDDY THE PARROT.
POLLY WANT A...
OH, WHO CARES?
HEY, KID, DID SHE
GIVE YOU A STEAK?
YEAH.
[LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY]
Cosmo: HEY, TIMMY.
IT'S ME. I'M A FLEA.
Timmy's voice: HEY,
COSMO, LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET ME
OUT OF HERE--I--
[RUFF RUFF RUFF]
HA HA! ARF, ARF, ARF!
RIGHT BACK AT YOU, WOOF BOY.
IF YOU NEED ME,
I'LL BE ON YOUR BUTT.
AH...THE GREAT OUTDOORS.
AND NO WIFE. OOH, YEAH!
I'M GONNA SWING, DADDY-O.
I'M GONNA CALL
ALL MY OLD FRIENDS.
LET'S SEE...
WANDA. UH, WANDA
WITH A LITTLE STAR NEXT TO IT.
WANDA. PANDA--UH, NO, THAT'S
WANDA WITH A SMUDGE ON THE "W".
I...I...I...
I MISS WANDA.
[SOBBING]
ARRROOO!
Wanda: OH, THAT'S RIGHT, SISSY.
I'VE FINALLY GOT SOME TIME
TO WRITE MY NOVEL.
FINALLY, A ROMANCE NOVEL
TO SHAKE THE AGES.
"IT WAS DAWN. I WAS IN MY TOWEL
WHEN THE NINJAS ATTACKED..."
[TYPING CONTINUES]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
Mom: TIMMY. BREAKFAST.
FOOD! FOOD!
[TWINKLE]
[BARKING]
FOOD! FOOD! FOOD!
FOOD! [SLURPING]
HE SURE IS HUNGRY.
NO, NO. THAT'S JUST
THE WAY ALL KIDS
EAT CEREAL NOW--
FACE FIRST.
I'M HIP. [SLURPING]
[HONKING]
[PANTING]
SCHOOL BUS. SCHOOL BUS.
CHASE CHASE CHASE CHASE!
WOW. DOES TIMMY
LOVE SCHOOL, OR WHAT?
AH! HOT!
IT DOESN'T WORK
WITH HOT.
[BELL RINGS]
DUDE, WHAT'S
THE HAT?
[SNIFFING]
I HAVE TO SAY THIS IS
A MASSIVE VIOLATION OF
MY PERSONAL SPACE.
[GIRL SCREAMS]
WOW!
TIMMY'S TOUGH.
YEAH, FRANCIS.
HE'S TOUGHER
THAN YOU.
NOBODY'S TOUGHER
THAN ME.
[SLURPING]
SLURP, SLURP,
SLURP, SLURP.
IT'S GREAT TO SEE
YOU GIRLS.
YOU MEAN YOU'RE FREE
BECAUSE ALL YOUR KIDS
SWITCHED PLACES
WITH ANIMALS TODAY?
OH, SURE.
KIDS DO THAT
ALL THE TIME.
MY LITTLE SOPHIE
SWITCHED PLACES
WITH A FROG.
BUT DON'T THEY
DISSECT THOSE?
OH, MY GOSH!
WELL, BETTER
CHECK ON TIMMY.
[BELL RINGING]
HEY, CHESTER,
DOES TIMMY SEEM
A LITTLE OFF TODAY?
NO. WHY?
OH, YOU MEAN
THE BUTT THING?
BALL! BALL!
BALL!
TIMMY! OH, MY GOSH!
NOT SO EASY, IS IT,
FANCY PANTS?
[CROAKING]
Man: ALL RIGHTY, WHO'S NEXT?
VICKY, COME ON IN.
[CLAWS SCRAPING]
HI,
DR. SNIPOWITZ.
OK, LET'S TIE
THIS LITTLE PUP UP
SO HE WON'T RUN AWAY.
WHAT'S THIS ONE?
WELL, WE CALL THAT
THE PUSHY THINGY.
AND THIS IS
THE PULLY-LIFTY THINGY.
THE PULLY-PUSHY-LIFTY THING.
AND THIS IS
THE SNIPMASTER 8000.
WOW!
OH, MY GOSH!
SHE'S GONNA HAVE YOU FIXED.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
SAY SOMETHING?
[GROWLS]
[BUZZING]
YIE! YOW!
DOYDLE!
[SNIFFING]
WHAT IS IT, BOY?
SMELL SOMETHING?
BALL BALL BALL BALL!
Cosmo: HEY, TIMMY.
IT'S TIMMY...AND WANDA!
HEY, WANDA, IT'S ME!
Timmy: BALL BALL BALL!
HI, HONEY.
I HAD THE WORST DAY
WITHOUT YOU, PUDDIN',
WHAT WITH THE FLEAS
AND THE GREAT OUTDOORS--
WHICH, INCIDENTALLY,
WASN'T THAT GREAT.
SO HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
DID YOU MISS ME?
DID YA? DID YA?
YES. I MISSED YOU.
BALL BALL BALL BALL!
BALL!
[RUFF RUFF]
I NEED YOU TO SAY
I WISH I WAS BACK
IN MY OWN BODY.
NO WAY.
HE CAN TALK?
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND ME?
DUH! I SPEAK DOG.
IT'S MY NATIVE TONGUE.
I'M JUST A JERK.
BUT YOU CAN WISH US
BACK TO NORMAL NOW.
I MAY STILL HAVE
A DOG'S BRAIN,
BUT I'M NOT THAT STUPID.
I HAVE THUMBS NOW.
SURE, I CAN'T GO TO
THE BATHROOM ANYWHERE I WANT,
BUT WHY WOULD I WANT TO
GO BACK TO BEING A DOG?
[GROWLING]
OH, MY GOSH!
TIMMY AND TIMMY
ARE FIGHTING!
YOU KNOW, LOLLIPOP,
WHEN WE WERE APART,
I WAS SO LONELY.
OH, NO! TIMMY
JUST BIT TIMMY.
TIMMY THIS,
TIMMY THAT.
YOU'RE LUCKY I'M NOT
THE JEALOUS TYPE.
THAT'S IT!
Timmy: HEY, AH! OH!
[GROWLING]
HI THERE, BIG BOY.
HI, I'M DOYDLE.
YOU'RE A PRETTY POODLE.
I LIKE PRETTY POODLES.
I WAS JUST LOOKING
FOR THE RIGHT DOG
TO GIVE THIS BIG,
JUICY BONE TO.
HI, I'M THE REAL DOYDLE.
NO, I'M DOYDLE.
YOU'RE NOT A DOG.
YOU'RE JUST A BOY
WITH A SILLY PINK HAT.
I AM NOT!
[GROWLING]
I WISH I WAS
A DOG AGAIN!
COOL! I'M HUMAN!
I'M HUMAN!
I'M NOT AN ANIMAL.
IN YOUR FACE, DOG.
HERE. SEE THE BALL,
DOGGY?
WELL, FETCH.
HA HA HA!
YOU REALLY THINK
MY HAT IS SILLY?
[RUFF RUFF]
SORRY.
I'M HAPPILY MARRIED.
HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THUMBS ROCK.
[BARKING]
I WISH HE HAD
A MUZZLE.
[MUFFLED]
AND A CAGE.
SMALLER CAGE.
DOYDLE, THERE YOU ARE!
NOW, LET'S GET YOU FIXED.
[MUFFLED GROANING]
TV announcer: SHEARIANO
THE SLASHER HAS BUTCHED
THE BUTCHER IN HIS DEATH STAY--
GUYS. MEET MY NEW
HAMSTER SPUNKY.
YOU CAN STAY HERE.
HERE YOU GO, SPUNKY.
A NICE, JUICY STEAK.
OH, BOY! STEAK!
SHOULD WE TELL HIM?
IT'S ONLY FAIR.
Wanda: HEY, SPUNKY.
MY STEAK! NO WAY!
I'M EATING HERE!
MINE! GET AWAY,
YOU LOSERS--MINE!
MINE! STOP IT.
DON'T TOUCH.
COME ON. GET AWAY.
HE CAN FIND OUT
ON HIS OWN.
[LAUGHING]
TV announcer:
IT'S ALL OVER NOW, FOLKS.
HA HA! WHY AM I LAUGHING?
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--