Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Corrected by Arcinboldi
- Previously on Dexter...
Judging from the spray,
we're looking at somebody tall.
Over six feet.
He moved the arm...
for a reason.
- The killer leaves
the ash as his signature,
making his vics point at it.
Lundy came to Miami
to hunt this guy.
I think he got too close
and I think
it got him killed
and me shot.
- It's been my dad's baby
for years.
A few days ago,
he hands me the keys.
- No, no.
Smooth circular motions, son.
- I got it, dad.
- If you got it,
I wouldn't have to remind you.
- Small cracks
in the perfect family.
- I can lose my job.
Not like I'm the only one.
Being a journalist
these days
is like a straight ticket
to the unemployment line.
Either I get a lead that bleeds
or basically I'm done.
Are the sweeps connected
to the shootings of agent Lundy?
- I know it's really tough
for reporters right now.
So maybe instead of this one,
I can give you
that interview you've
been wanting from me.
Mother shit fuck.
How tall was my shooter?
- My height.
- Then it wasn't Trinity.
- Nope.
- I was a dress-over-the-head
party girl.
You must think I'm--
- Totally charming.
- We broke up officially.
- If I find out
this is bullshit,
there will be severe,
career-ending consequences.
- Fuck it.
- No more confessions,
no more good deeds,
and no more fucking remorse.
No, you're mine.
Arthur Mitchell,
you just got a reprieve.
- This'll do the job.
Cut you into exactly
the right size pieces.
You got one more day.
Happy families are all alike.
They never leave you
by yourself on holidays.
- So I got some interesting
thanksgiving greetings
from your coach Davis.
Well, if you're not gonna
play baseball anymore,
I suppose you aren't
gonna need this.
- No, dad--
- All right?
How about this?
Oh, you're full of awards.
- Once the turkey's gone,
so is Arthur.
- How about this one?
This one's for most
valuable player.
- Fuck you, dad.
- Family business.
- It's my business too.
- Okay.
Healthy way to blow off steam.
- What the hell?
Jonah?
Hey, it's just me.
- Mr. Butler,
what are you doing here?
- I stopped by your house.
I saw you arguing
with your father.
- No, I don't argue.
I never argue.
- Still looked like a bad one.
- Man, you have no idea
what he's like.
How he treats my mother
and Rebecca.
You don't know
what he's capable of.
- Well, actually--
- He hits me.
- That's not right.
- You know, I'm running out
of cliches to tell the coaches.
You know,
"Hey, I fell down some stairs.
I walked into a door."
I know it looks like we have
the perfect fucking family,
but in that house,
when he's there,
it's not a life.
It's a tour of duty.
Shit.
He'd kill me if he knew
I was telling you this stuff.
- I won't say a word.
- You should have just
let him die.
- Where you going?
- Anywhere away from here.
I can't go back.
Not to him.
Not with the car like this.
- So I'll go with you.
I'll be there
when you tell him.
- Why?
- You're not the only one
with father issues.
- Well, you know,
maybe...
I mean, I guess if you came
to thanksgiving tomorrow,
dad would be on his best.
- Thanksgiving?
- Dinner's at 1:00.
I can stay at Luke's house
until then.
- Guess I'm having
two turkey dinners this year.
The DNA sweep didn't
give them Trinity.
But it did bring in
a cornucopia of criminals.
That should keep Miami metro
off the Trinity case
through the holiday.
Deb won't be anywhere
near as easy.
- I'm sorry, Dex,
but I'm spending thanksgiving
with 90 or so
of my newest friends.
Look at these victims.
It looks like
a family portrait.
The bathtub women,
they're always young and single.
A first girlfriend maybe.
And then the jumper's always
a mother of two.
Maybe that represents
his mom or his wife,
but I don't think
this guy's married.
And the bludgeon-ee's
always a father.
- You used to love
thanksgiving when we were kids.
You wore the little
indian headdresses.
Picked the pearl onions
out of the green beans.
- Yeah, mom's green beans.
And then she died.
And it was you and me
and dad and football
and tv dinners
in aluminum trays.
Talk about your lonely.
- Well, you won't
be lonely at our house.
You'll never get the chance.
- Dexter,
I am lead detective
on the biggest case
of my career.
This is where I belong.
- I thought Batista was lead.
- He's the lead on Lundy now.
Once we figured out Trinity
didn't shoot me,
there was no conflict for me--
- What?
Wait.
Trinity didn't shoot you?
- While you were at your
rain man convention,
Masuka and I put it together
form the bullet's trajectory.
- How did I not see that?
- We were too close.
That's what happens
when you make it personal.
So I've heard.
So who shot you?
- Maybe Trinity knows.
I'll ask him when
I haul his ass in here.
- Deb, you really, really need
to come to thanksgiving.
- Tell the family I said,
"Hi."
- All right, heads up,
everybody.
This DNA sweep has been
like christmas.
We got hits
on three open rape cases
and one open burglary case.
But best of all,
hits on two homicides.
Merry thanksgiving,
Soderquist.
And this one is mine.
Keep up the good work,
guys.
- Sarge, any news
on any other cases?
- We'll find the fucker
who shot you.
You know that.
Focus on what you can control.
- Catching Trinity.
I heard the aclu's
filing suit on the sweeps.
- We've got maybe 72 hours
till we're shut down for good.
We'll just have
to keep pushing harder.
- Well, the holidays
may slow us down.
We'll have a skeleton crew.
- I'll be here.
Never been much for family
holidays anyway.
- Particularly when they're
all still in Cuba.
- Particularly.
You with Auri tomorrow?
- She's with her moms
this year.
Plus I have a chance to close
an old case of mine, so...
- So I guess we'll both
be working thanksgiving.
- Together.
- How unfortunate.
- Put it up higher, mom.
- No, I want it lower.
- Are happy families
all alike?
- Much better.
- Dexter's home.
- Oh, good.
They didn't run out of pies.
- Here you go.
- Okay, bird, confess.
How big are you?
- 22 pounds.
- That's a lot of bird.
- Better too much
than not enough.
I mean, that's what
the holiday's about.
That and family.
- About tomorrow...
- Uh-oh.
- It's not a big deal.
But the Monroe County P.D.
needs a spatter interpretation
on a bar fight and their
blood guy's in the Bahamas.
- Should just take
a few hours.
- Does it have
to be tomorrow?
- Well, that's when
the reconstruction is.
- Mm.
- Plus I'll be making
triple overtime.
- Sure, that's a plus,
but you'll be missing
all the fun.
- Yeah.
- Poor you.
Poor us.
At least Elliot will be here.
- Yeah, good old Elliot.
- So is Deb coming?
- She's on the fence.
- No, tell her that this is our
first family thanksgiving
and that we're
establishing traditions
that will shape our kids
and that they'll pass on
to their kids and
that she's a part of that.
An important part of that.
- Rather than me
tell her all that...
Okay, guys,
now look real sad.
I mean, really miserable.
And...
Action.
- Hi, aunt Deb.
We just heard
that you might not come
to thanksgiving dinner,
and well--
- We really want you
to come.
- Look sad, retard.
- All right,
all right.
Just...
take two.
- Will you please come over?
- Fuck me.
You're here late.
- Ah, didn't even notice.
- Big plans tomorrow?
- You're looking at them.
Whatever about tomorrow,
right?
It's just another day
where people eat turkey.
I can eat turkey
any day of the year.
- Dexter's having people over.
Well, me.
He invited me over.
- Have a good time.
- You know...
I could use a wingman.
- Yes.
- I can't promise
it'll be any fun.
- Well, I could be
your thigh man.
- Don't press your luck.
I'll let Rita know.
What time do you want
to eat tomorrow?
- Oh, bad news, babe.
I got to work.
- Oh.
Well, what time
do you get off?
- Uh...
- You do want to spend
the holiday together, don't you?
- It's a holiday.
- Exactly.
- Spending it together makes
things all... serious.
- Ah, it's just
a casual thanksgiving
with your girlfriend.
- Girlfriend?
That sounds really serious.
- Joey...
I don't want
to spend it alone.
Plus, uh...
I make the best pecan pie
in the state of Florida.
- I guess I could,
you know,
come by for dessert.
- Oh, so you just want
to eat my pie.
Is that it?
- Happy thanksgiving,
Mr. Mitchell.
- Happy thanksgiving.
- I'll be at Arthur's by 1:00,
home by 4:00.
A serial killer's thanksgiving
recipe for success.
- How can none
of these be big enough?
- Well, maybe if we,
um...
turn the bird on its side
and then--and, um--
Hey, Dex.
- Howdy, pilgrim.
- Did you hear that the pilgrims
didn't eat turkey
on the first thanksgiving?
- Really?
- They ate corn and eel,
which the native americans
taught them to plant and fish.
- Then the pilgrims
slaughtered them all,
took their food,
and went to church the next day
to thank god
for all their good luck.
- Mm, it's a phase.
Don't worry about it.
- What you said about traditions
shaping our kids...
My not going to work,
will that... misshape them?
- Look.
I wish it was otherwise,
but you'll be home soon, right?
- Right.
I just--
I don't want
to do any damage.
- You're a parent.
Parents do damage.
Hopefully we'll do enough
of the good stuff
to balance it out.
- Hopefully.
Thanks.
- "Ashes to ashes..."
- Doughnut to doughnut.
It's all the store
had left.
- What are you doing here?
- Avoiding Christine.
She can be a little intense.
- Tell me about it.
She keeps calling to set
that interview with me.
- You said you'd do it.
- Little busy here.
Look at the timing
of the Trinity kills.
15 in december,
40 in july and august,
20 or so in the spring.
What's the pattern?
- Long-haul truck driver?
Migrant worker?
Some kind of salesman.
- Yeah.
- Gobble, gobble.
- She's nothing
if not persistent.
- Hey, babe.
What are you doing here?
- I thought I'd bring
thanksgiving to you.
- How sweet.
- There's enough
for both of you.
- Oh, thanks,
but I'm heading out.
- Debra's taking the day off.
- Fuck that.
I'll be multitasking.
- Well, I guess you can
take the day off too.
- Sure he can.
- Yeah, let me just, uh,
check with the boss.
We'll go eat.
- So, Debra,
how are you feeling?
- Do you mind if we put off
that interview
until after the holiday?
- I'm not here as a reporter.
I'm here as Joey's girlfriend.
- My condolences.
You know, he really cares
about you.
After you got shot, you were
all he could talk about.
Really messed him up.
- Well, that makes
two of us.
- I just--
I just wanted to say,
um...
I'm really sorry about
what happened to you.
I can't even imagine
looking into the eyes
of the person you love...
Watching as he takes
his last breath.
- Let's hope you never
have to.
- You got Lloyd Paulson
to confess?
- Been waiting ten years
to close this one.
I promised
the victim's husband
I'd find the man
who killed his wife.
Finally lived up
to that promise.
- You should go
tell the husband.
Give him something
to be thankful for.
- As soon as I process
that pendejo.
Do you want to come with?
- To a next-of-kin
notification?
- It is official business.
- Kyle.
- Happy thanksgiving.
- To you too.
- Kyle.
What a nice surprise.
- Apparently Jonah didn't
mention inviting me.
I just wanted
to drop by and say hi.
It's my first thanksgiving
without my family and I...
Didn't know what
to do with myself.
- I suppose you should eat
with us.
Full tables,
full hearts,
full bellies.
Come on in.
- Aunt Deb's here!
- Happy thanksgiving,
turkeys.
Thanks for the video.
- Hi, Deb.
- Hi.
Who's that?
- Danny and grace's dad.
- Danny, let me help.
You don't know where
that piece is.
- Ah.
Where's Dexter?
- He's at some crime thing
in Monroe .
Said he'd be back for dinner.
- He's more like dad
every day.
- Come look at our puzzle.
We've already got the corners.
- Cody, leave her alone.
- You don't want to help?
- I'm sorry, little man,
but I've got work to do.
- Oh.
- You are good.
- Another three hours to go.
- Oh, when do you want
to put in
the broccoli-cheese
casserole?
- Uh, about an hour before.
The sweet potatoes
need an hour
and the corn pudding needs
about 30 minutes.
- Is it all gonna fit?
No.
None of it's gonna fit.
What was I thinking?
- Well, you were
thinking that,
"My fabulous neighbor has,
not one, but two ovens."
You know, you really are
a lifesaver.
You should just wear
a red cross on your forehead.
Oven crisis.
- Deb, can you
watch the kids?
Harrison's asleep.
- Uh, actually, I was gonna
try to get some...
- Oh!
- Work done.
- Vince, hi.
Vince, Elliot.
Elliot, Vince.
- Hi.
Uh, bye.
- Uh, bye.
- Bye.
- They're using his oven.
- Oh, well, guess I'll be using
his oven too.
Chocolate lava cakes.
My specialty.
- You have a specialty?
- A river of chocolate love
that melts in your mouth.
- Wow.
You can make anything
sound perverted.
- It's a gift.
- Arthur seems to be
in a decent mood.
Maybe I'll be able
to slip out early.
It's almost 1:00.
You want me
to set the table?
- No, we've got
to watch the game first.
- The game?
- Yeah.
It's tradition, Kyle.
- Ah.
Will the kids be joining us?
- That too would
be tradition,
but apparently Jonah
has forgotten.
- I'm sure he's on his way.
He knows how important
holidays are to you.
- Not such a decent mood
after all.
- Do you think Rebecca
could come out now?
- I suppose.
I'll go get her.
- She grounded or something?
- Oh, no.
No, nothing like that.
- This is Carl Haas?
- He's been in a persistent
vegetative state
for several years.
Stepped off a sidewalk,
got hit by a bus.
- I didn't know.
It's been a long time.
- Would it be possible to have
a moment alone with him?
- Have a good turkey day.
- Tell him.
- Like he can hear me.
- He'll hear you.
- Mr. Haas, I'm the one
who told you about your wife.
I also promised
that I'd fi--
This is pointless.
- Mr. Haas,
Angel knows how much
your wife meant to you...
And he wants you to know...
- I want you to know...
That we found
the guy who killed her.
I wish--
I wish we would have
found him sooner.
Really, I wish he would have
never killed your wife,
but I can't change that.
Can't change anything.
But we got the guy.
We got him.
- Hello, Mr. Butler.
How are you?
- Well, I'm fine, Rebecca.
- Kyle, you up for a little
pre-game football toss?
- I suppose.
- I'll go help mom
in the kitchen.
- At least I have
one perfect child.
- Yeah, so it
would appear.
- Come on.
Normally Jonah supplies
the football.
- How about baseball?
- No.
We throw the baseball in spring.
Thanksgiving
we throw the football.
Traditions matter,
Kyle.
- Yes, they...
Shape people.
- Yeah,
and give children
a sense of history,
tradition.
Teaches them who they are
and what's expected of them.
- And what is expected of them?
- Generosity,
common sense, obedience.
It's a father's responsibility
to set the boundaries.
Child's duty to honor them.
No, there's nothing
down there.
Stop!
Kyle, no!
I made that...
When I was still confused.
- Well, it's beautiful.
- Which is why I haven't
torn it apart.
Probably donate it
to the needy.
Obviously I won't
be needing it.
- No, you'll be buried
at sea.
- I have a new lease
on life.
Thanks to you.
Hey.
Huh.
The best laid plans.
- It's Jonah's.
What's the point of giving him
the better things in life
if he can't take care
of them?
- What kind of father keeps
a coffin in his garage?
blood slides in his shed?
Hey, we can still get some--
Here we go.
- Dad, I don't know
what happened.
It was--the car was parked
in Luke's driveway all night.
I came out this morning and,
you know,
someone had just gone
all mental on it.
Dad, I am so sorry.
That's why god invented
car insurance, right?
It'll be okay.
- There.
Now it's drivable
till we can get her fixed.
Well...
Game's about to start.
Shall we?
- Come on, Danny.
Throw it here.
- Oh, good one.
- Hey, you two.
No wiffle ball in the house.
- I don't know how you do it.
All these kids
at home at the same time.
- Thanksgiving's only four days.
You should try keeping
them entertained
for three months
in the summer.
- Yeah, plus spring break
and christmas break.
- That's when you're really
climbing the walls.
- June, july, august...
December.
Oh...
Fu-u-udge.
Trinity's
in the school system.
- Probably a gain of about--
- Quinn.
- Joey, it's Deb.
His kill schedule matches
the school year.
Trinity could be a janitor.
He could be a cafeteria worker,
a bus driver,
a teacher or principal.
We got to get
to the station.
- I haven't eaten yet.
- Jesus, grab a drumstick
to go.
- Deb, no one's
working today
and we're gonna
need a warrant
to access
any school databases.
- We can find a judge.
- Yeah, who's gonna love us
for tearing him
away from his family.
Come on.
We're not gonna get
anywhere today.
- Fu--
Fudge.
- Break in a case?
- We'll see.
Not a horrible thanksgiving,
right?
- No, actually,
it's kind of nice.
- You sound surprised.
- I am a little.
- Hmm.
So having a girlfriend isn't
so bad after all?
- You with the labels.
- Why does it matter?
- I just--
I care about you.
I'd kind of like
to have it returned.
- Come here.
- I have a better idea.
- Aww.
You are so my girlfriend.
- Get--get--
Get him!
Get--get--get--
get him!
Ah!
- Oh, it's okay.
They didn't get
the first down.
- Jonah seems safe
for the moment.
I'm not a big football fan.
I think I'll go see
if I can help Sally.
- Oh, that's very
nice of you.
- Look at that.
There's three men on him.
- Yeah, I know.
- This room's kind of young
for a teenager.
Are those to keep
someone out
or keep someone in?
My god.
He locks his daughter in here.
You need any help?
I'm completely useless
in the kitchen.
- Sure.
Uh, something
for the centerpiece.
Roses.
Dad always likes these.
- Everything for dad, huh?
Those locks on your door
for him too?
- He says they're there
to protect me.
- Do they?
- Third down.
- He's open.
He's open!
Go, go!
Touchdown!
- Oh!
- What a play.
- No.
No, dad.
Ow!
- And that's
for my windshield.
Things of beauty need
to be honored.
- I ran away once.
He caught me and...
It was bad.
- It's not always
gonna be like this.
Jonah told me
that you're helping him.
- Yeah, if you can call
it that.
- You can help me too.
Get me out of here.
- You just need
to wait a while.
You're too young
to be on your own.
- I don't have
to be on my own.
I could be with you.
- With me?
- Jonah also says you're nice.
- I try to be.
- If you're nice to me,
I can be nice to you.
I'll do anything you want.
- Whoa.
I don't--
Rebecca, you're 15.
I don't want anything
from you.
- I don't believe you.
Look, I know what guys like.
- No.
- Rebecca?
Go inside.
- Sally, it's not--
- Shh.
I am so sorry
about Rebecca's behavior.
- Oh.
- Just please don't say
anything to Arthur.
Kyle, you can't.
Whatever you did
with Rebecca...
- I didn't.
- Whatever you're
going to do,
I don't care.
Just please,
I'm begging you.
Don't tell him.
- I wouldn't.
I wouldn't.
I won't.
- Please.
- Yeah, I promise.
- Thank you.
- What the hell is he doing
to these people?
Rita, hi.
- Hey.
How far away are you?
- Uh, probably
about an hour or so.
- All right, well,
I don't want you to be surprised
when you get home.
- Why?
What?
- Cody fell into your shed.
- What?
Is he okay?
What happened?
- Well, he's fine.
He hit a wiffle ball
onto the top of the shed,
climbed up to get it,
the skylight cracked...
And he fell through.
Elliot was gonna push
on the air conditioner.
- No, don't.
- Uh, he didn't.
He took off the door
with an axe.
- So my shed has no door?
- Dexter, Cody was scared
and crying, all right?
I told Elliot to get him
out however he could.
- Yeah, of course.
Of course.
I'll...
Thank Elliot when I get home.
- Well, I'll see you soon,
okay?
No one can get into
the trunk's false bottom.
- You didn't think anyone could
get into your shed either.
- I gotta get home now.
- Arthur, I just got a call
and I think I have to--
- Jonah, what happened?
- I whacked it
on the coffee table.
- My son, the klutz.
This team hasn't been the same
since they traded johnson.
- What else will he do
to Jonah if I leave?
- Turkey wraps, icees.
- And cuervo silver.
Only the best for you.
- You know, I was thinking...
Carl Haas's wife gets mugged.
Boom.
She's dead.
Carl gets hit by a bus.
Boom.
He's a vegetable.
- You never know when you
wake up in the morning
what the day will bring.
- I love you.
I love you.
- Are you saying that
because you're afraid
you'll get hit by a bus?
- No. Well...
Yes, but...
I just want you to know
what I know
before I don't know it
anymore.
And I love you.
I love you!
- Shh.
I can hear you.
- I love Maria Esperanza
Di Alma LaGuer--
- Shh!
- I'm not gonna say it.
- You don't love me?
- I'm afraid
if I say it...
Something will happen,
like you'll get hit by a bus.
So watch out
for moving buses.
'cause I love...
Angel Juan Marcos Batista.
- Ah!
Rats! Ow!
- Uh-oh. Come here.
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
- Ooh.
- There you go.
Isn't thanksgiving fun?
- Thank god it's only
once a year.
Do you have any ice?
- No.
Peas are better.
Come on, Rita.
Give peas a chance.
- Now come on.
Take a seat.
- Oh.
- All right.
Okay.
- There.
Did you say, "rats"?
I guess I've been spending
too much time with the kids.
- Thanks for this.
- I like taking care of you.
I am so sorry.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
- Yeah, I don't either.
- Well, no,
it's just
we have this connection
and it's not just because
we're both lonely--
- No, I'm not lonely.
I have Dexter.
- The guy who's never home?
- Hey, uh...
Deb, I'm gonna take off.
Not feeling so hot.
- Oh, no, you don't.
Here.
You're my wingman.
- No, this family doesn't
really need me around.
I'll see you at the--
- No, no, shh!
You belong here
as much as anyone does.
And if you go, I'll be
the one single person here.
I really don't feel like
remembering
why that is, you know?
Why Frank's gone.
Why I'm here.
- Yeah.
Hey... Yeah.
I'll stay.
But I need booze.
- You and me both.
- Hi.
- Are you the one my mom
told me not to talk to?
- Awkward.
- And for this bounty
before us,
we thank you and look to you,
oh, lord,
to strengthen our resolve
to strive,
to seek, to find,
and not to yield.
Amen.
- Amen.
- Looks marvelous, Sally.
- Thank you, Arthur.
- We, uh--
We have a little...
Family tradition, Kyle,
before we start...
Of saying what
we're thankful for.
I'll start.
I'm thankful for this family.
Pass your plates.
Sally?
- I'm--
I'm thankful
for this lovely home...
And for my son,
who I am so proud of.
- Me too.
- Is that all?
- And for my
beautiful daughter,
who is growing up
so quickly.
I am so blessed.
- I'm thankful
that Mrs. Wilder
gave us an extra two days
to finish our report
on aeschylus.
And I'm also thankful
for this nice home.
- Is this what it takes
to survive with him?
- Um, I'm thankful
for this house too...
And for god.
- You know what
I'm thankful for?
My car.
- I'm thankful for yams.
- Yams?
- Comfort food.
Thank you all for
the comfort of your home.
- Where no one said
they were thankful for me.
Did you, Jonah?
Did you say you were thankful
for me, Jonah?
What's that?
- I did not say
I was thankful for you...
Because I'm not.
- I am so thankful
for you, Arthur.
- Shut up, cunt.
- Whoa, Arthur.
- Kyle, perhaps it's time
for you to go.
- I think I should stay.
- Yeah, sure.
Stay.
Watch the show.
- I'm thankful for you, daddy.
- Go to your room, Vera.
- No!
She's not Vera!
And she's not
your goddamn prisoner
and she's not
eight anymore!
This whole life--
Your life--
is a lie!
These are lies!
Fucking community hero?
- Jonah, this isn't the way.
- I know who you really are.
- Oh, who am I?
- You're a killer.
Sucking the fucking life
out of all of us!
Mom, Becca, me!
- Fucking little--
- No, daddy!
Don't!
Daddy, no!
- You're killing us!
- Put her down.
- Fuck you and fuck Vera.
- Don't.
Fuck you!
- Get the fuck off him!
- Oh, my god!
No! No!
No, daddy!
No!
- No, you don't have
to kill him!
No! Dad!
Dad!
- I should have fucking killed
you when I had the chance.
Oh, my god!
Arthur!
- Sally.
Thankful to be out
of that fucking house!
- You showed Trinity
the monster in you.
He'll see you coming now.
- I don't know.
Seeing them like that--
He's destroyed everyone
in that family.
- That's what happens to people
who live with a monster.
- I am nothing like him!
My family is nothing
like that.
- What's 18 more years of being
with you gonna do to them?
- Arthur's terrorized them
into maintaining his cover.
They're nothing
but human shields.
- The only reason you started
dating Rita was for cover.
She's much more than that now.
She and the kids.
Much more.
My family is nothing
like that.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Dexter's home!
- Who's hungry?
- Me.
- I am.
- I am so happy
you're home.
- Oh, me too.
- Mm.
Mm.
All right.
Uh, Cody, why don't you help
your aunt Deb set the table?
Astor, I can use your help
in the kitchen.
- Sorry about your shed,
Dexter.
- Hey.
Huh.
As long as you're okay,
that's all that matters.
I'm gonna go check on the shed.
Make sure it's safe in there.
- Miss us?
- You have no idea.
God, I miss my apartment.
They're safe.
So's my trunk.
- Is anything
really safe here?
The kids, Rita?
You?
- I'll find an alternative.
- Trinity was supposed
to be the alternative.
- Uh, spoons go inside
or outside the knives?
- Um...
Surprise us.
Ouch.
- Can I see your scars,
aunt Deb?
- Sure.
- Does it still hurt?
- Um...
Sometimes...
Here.
- Did you see that guy die?
- I did.
Looked right in his eyes.
- Were his eyes open?
- Yeah.
Watched him take his
last breath.
How did she know that?
- How did who know what?
- Nobody but me.
How much did you tell Christine
about the Lundy shooting?
- Nothing.
- Well, maybe you left
Lundy's file
lying around accidentally.
- No.
- And maybe Christine saw some
of the pictures.
She saw how he was lying
on his side,
how he fell in front of me,
so that I could see him
take his last--
- Morgan, I'm telling you,
I learned my lesson.
I never even took the Lundy
files out of the station.
There's no way she
could have seen it.
- Dinner's ready.
- Not all happy families
are alike.
They are happy...
Aren't they?
Are they normal kids?
How can you tell a loving wife
from a frightened one?
A friendly neighbor.
Co-worker.
Sister.
Son.
Are any of them
what they seem?
Or are they little bombs
waiting to explode?
- Happy thanksgiving, son.
- Dexter?
Everything okay?
- Yeah.
It is, isn't it?
- Yes.
Everything is exactly
the way it should be.
Perfect.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Why don't we go around
the table and everybody
say what they're thankful for?
- No!
I don't want this yummy food
to get cold.
- I'm thankful for Dexter.
- Let's eat.
- Sure you don't want to stay?
- I'm too tired
to spend the night.
You made sure of that.
- See you tomorrow?
- And the day after that
and after that.
I'm here if you
change your mind.
- Good night.
Joey.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Corrected by Arcinboldi
Hi, dad.