Previously on dexter...
- dexter.
- how's my favorite
serial-killer hunter?
- the reason i'm in miami
is because i'm convinced
That these bathtub murders
are connected
To a series of murders
all over the country.
It's always the same three
kills with trinity.
You got woman
in a bathtub,
Followed by a mother
falling to her death...
- you're next.
- if this is the latest victim
of lundy's trinity killer,
Then he's a very different
monster than i am.
- lundy has this theory--
- you don't work for lundy.
You're welcome to pursue this,
But between the vacation murders
and lisa bell,
I think
you're gonna be very busy.
- yes, i did come to miami
to follow a case,
But i have to admit i'm glad
the killer chose this city,
Knowing i'd find you here.
- hey, good news!
The sandpiper hotel
wants to book my band
For a one-month gig.
Best of all it means
no more time away from you.
- wow, that's great.
- i'm not gonna tell you
who to date.
It's none
of my business.
But you should know
there's no such thing
As "off the record"
with reporters.
So watch the pillow talk
with that woman.
Super-agent lundy
has a hunch
That the dead woman is connected
to this big serial killer case.
Lundy always gets his man.
- well, so do i.
- [laughs]
- look,
i was a little worried
That people
will misinterpret.
- let them misinterpret.
I need this
as much as you do.
- the past few weeks,
you have not been
The most present
father and husband.
My dark passenger is like
a trapped coal miner,
Always helping,
always letting me know
It's still in there,
still alive.
[festive music]
Everyone needs
a vacation.
In my case, it's time off
for bad behavior.
But i intend to make the most
of this family trip
That they're taking
without me.
- shotgun!
- i called it first.
- i called it inside.
- it doesn't count if you
call it inside.
- does so!
mom! dexter!
- how about you switch
every hour?
- want to trade places?
I stay home and...
You can stuff cousin marlene
into some spanx
On her wedding day.
- i wish i could,
but things are pretty hectic
At the station.
- you're not gonna work
the whole time, are you?
- i'll try not to.
- you can't let yourself get
to that boiling point again.
It's not healthy.
And i'd rather not have to lie
to the neighbor again
If you decide to smash
any more security lights.
- i hate that you
saw me that way.
- i'm your wife.
I want to know
what's going on inside you.
- i don't think you do.
Just recharge your batteries,
all right?
Enjoy your freedom.
Go wild.
- right...go wild.
- have fun.
Say, "good-bye, dexter."
all: good-bye, dexter!
- good-bye, dexter!
bye-bye.
- the kids left you a present
in the kitchen.
- just the thing to melt
a father's heart.
Let the good times roll.
[festive music]
Whoops!
Three days.
72 precious hours
to recharge my batteries.
'course rita doesn't know
i'll be recharging
With another woman.
Officer zoey kruger.
Pembroke pines patrol.
Eight months ago, officer
kruger's husband and daughter
Were killed
during a home invasion.
Zoey was shot
in the arm and foot.
She survived...obviously.
But there was one person
who thought it was zoey herself
Who killed her family.
The one person who always knows
the truth of a crime--
The blood guy.
[knocking at door]
- morgan. good to see
a friendly face.
Aren't many around here.
- nice to have
an excuse to visit.
Even if i made it up.
- with your caseload,
I can't believe you have time
to write a paper
On feathering
in blood swipes.
- i have a small window for...
Uh, a side project.
I remembered at the
spatter conference last spring,
You mentioned something about
a questionable swipe
In a case
you were working.
Who was it, cooper?
- kruger, and shh--
we don't talk about that.
- zoey's husband--
shot in the stairway.
Her daughter,
in her bedroom.
Zoey said
she was shot twice
Wrestling the shooter's gun
from him.
And turned it on him
as he fled.
- that blood swipe
Belongs to darius rae,
A drug dealer zoey
roughed up
The day before
her family was murdered.
According to her,
She winged him
in her front hallway.
- the feathering
is textbook.
Why'd you say
it was questionable?
- because it's the only blood
of rae's
Anywhere at the scene.
- interesting.
For my paper.
- my theory?
Uh, forget it.
doesn't matter.
- you think she planted
the blood herself?
- maybe she even provoked
That confrontation
with darius rae.
- that's where
she got his blood.
- also gives her the perfect
narrative for the crime.
Rae breaks in looking
for retribution,
Cop's family becomes
collateral damage.
- was darius rae
ever arrested?
- darius rae
was gunned down
In a supposedly
gang-related incident.
But that's
another theory,
Another day.
I try not
to think about it.
Because if i'm right,
There's a monster
walking around free.
- with a badge
and a gun.
Zoey said she aimed
at darius rae
But only winged him.
But zoey always
hits her targets.
Just ask her husband
and daughter.
I'm feeling
recharged already.
Monsters come
in all shapes and sizes.
Sometimes
it's the very people
Who are supposed to be
protecting us:
A cop, a parent,
The spatter guy.
- god, close the door,
will you?
Here's a bludgeoning
from july.
- the one we're looking for
will be five days
After the suicide.
- right.
Here's a middle-aged guy
from october...
- sorry, i thought
this was my lab.
- we're hiding
from laguerta.
- quinn's reporter fuck buddy
has now officially
Fucked all three of us.
- "catching
the vacation murderer
"may not be
the department's top priority.
"detectives spent last thursday
indulging the pursuits
"of retired fbi man hunter
Frank lundy."
It's a good picture.
- i'm guessing that
lieutenant laguerta's
Open-door policy with me...
is about to close.
- we've got to narrow down
trinity's next move.
- bludgeoning.
Final kill in his cycle?
- and he's repeating his pattern
from 30 years ago,
So if we can find where
he bludgeoned back then--
- then maybe we can keep
the next trinity victim
From becoming
the next trinity victim.
- where's masuka?
- on vacation?
- he's probably in mexico
taking a donkey show tour.
- there's a briefing
in five minutes.
Agent lundy...
- my visitor's badge
is expired?
- sorry.
- crap. fuck.
I guess we'll have to stake out
potential bludgeoning sites
On my off hours.
- hey.
I don't want this theory of mine
to jeopardize your job.
- i want in on this.
- well, okay then.
- okay then.
- you ever feel like you're
this close to nabbing somebody?
- sometime
in the next 67 hours.
- it's a good feeling.
- oh, my god!
I can't believe
he posted that.
- you are so busted.
- i'm busted?
Okay, it's totally
photoshopped.
The point is,
it looks real, so...
- you're busted!
[giggles]
- shh!
- i know, i know,
My dick's been
making some bad decisions.
- so according to
quinn's girlfriend,
These vacation murders
are costing the city
900,000 tourist dollars
a day.
- well, at least the article
got the tip line ringing.
Those assholes can't hide
With all those eyes
on them.
- well, those eyes
are on us too.
[sighs]
- uh-oh.
- what...oh?
- that sigh thing
you do when, you know,
There's something
i'm not gonna like.
- i don't do
a sigh thing.
- okay, you don't.
What was it that
you were gonna say?
- [sighs]
I think we should inform the
brass about our relationship.
Look, it's just
a formality.
Paperwork.
entirely confidential.
- it's none
of their business.
- it's department policy
for good reason.
We will catch these killers,
And a defense attorney
could use the details
Of an off-the-books romance
between us
To sensationalize the case,
distract the jury--
- if they find out.
- on a death penalty case.
- okay,
they will find out.
But not for a while.
And what would we even
report to the brass?
- well, that we're
seeing each other.
- what does that mean?
- what do you think
it means?
- it means it's new.
We're still figuring it out.
- so this could just be
a passing thing.
- no, it's not
- then what is it?
- i don't know.
- well, i don't know
either.
- i'm confused.
- yeah.
I can see that.
- can we just...wait?
- fine.
- as a cop, zoey has been
to plenty of crime scenes.
She knows
what should be there.
And what shouldn't.
No prints
in the blood on the door,
Which means
she wore gloves.
She was still wearing gloves
when she shot herself.
But they were gone when
the emts arrived.
Where'd you leave
those gloves, zoey?
- easier to think here,
isn't it?
Only 52 hours
of freedom left.
You sure chose an interesting
person to spend it on.
- don't read
anything into it.
Zoey was a challenge,
that's all.
- a woman who wiped out
her own family
In order to be free.
- she should have
shot herself
Instead of
her husband and child.
- yeah...except that doesn't
get her free.
Just dead.
- well,
she had other options.
- alimony.
visitation.
Trading off holidays--
there go your weekends.
- fine, she could have
moved away.
- and forfeit her job,
her home?
Her only option was to make
her vacation from her family
As permanent as possible.
- there are
always alternatives.
- why do you think
trinity's been so successful?
- he travels a lot.
Stays on the move.
- he doesn't have a family.
- well, i do.
- miss them yet?
- all right,
trinity used a hammer
In portland
and in fresno,
But wasn't it a tire iron
in albuquerque?
Okay, all right.
We'll go with the dude that
was pulverized by the hammer.
Where was that?
Okay, what time tomorrow?
Great.
Pad thai, my favorite.
- mmm.
How's frank lundy?
- i didn't say
that was lundy.
- oh, your voice did.
It goes up a notch every time
you talk to him,
Which you're doing
a lot of lately.
- your point?
- i get a gig in town
to spend more time with you.
You spend all your time
with your ex.
- our relationship
is strictly professional.
- you twist your hair
when you talk to him?
- you have nothing
to be jealous of
When it comes
to frank lundy.
All right?
- poker night at home.
Zoey's police family
surrounds her
On and off the job.
Between her buddy system
and her security system,
Her house will be difficult
to break in tonight.
But not tomorrow.
- [whistles]
- [belches]
- cunt.
- what the hell
did you just say?
- you're a cunt!
- [laughs]
Fuck off, old man.
- fucking pussy.
[groans]
- you looking to get
the shit kicked out of you?
- [whimpers]
faggot!
[whimpers]
- you gonna shut up now?
- faggot.
Faggot.
[grunts]
[moans]
It's your fault.
- the fuck
is wrong with you?
- all your fault.
[coughs]
- the living room is here
to the left,
Kitchen in the back,
And way out back
is the hot tub.
Oh, welcome, welcome,
welcome.
Oh, you're gonna love
this house.
[laughs]
Newer construction,
only one previous owner,
All sorts of upgrades.
Come on, let me show you
its special wonders.
- uh, would it be all right
If i discovered those
special wonders on my own?
- any questions,
just holler.
- okay.
I do have one question.
Where did zoey
stash her gloves?
I'm sure
they're long gone,
But they could have left
trace evidence.
She swiped the door
with blood here...
Shoots herself,
collapses...
Crawls toward the kitchen
to call 911.
Did she burn them?
If the gloves melted,
there would be residue
On the underside
of the grate.
- it's just for show.
Who needs a fire
in this climate?
I'm zoey. i live here.
- hey.
- i just thought
i'd stop by,
See how the open house
was going.
- oh.
it's a nice place.
- thanks.
- family friendly.
- mm.
I'll be glad to give you
a tour if you're interested.
- very interested.
- okay, follow me.
- wow, my daughter would
go crazy over this room.
- it's a little girl's
dream.
- may i ask
why you're selling?
- my husband and i
are separated.
Now our daughter's
with him.
- so you're single.
- i am.
You've been married long?
- uh, yes,
about six months.
Ah, that came out wrong.
- [laughs]
I understand.
believe me.
- zoey, there's a couple here
who have a question
About the hot tub.
- okay,
i'll be right down.
To be continued.
- sure.
A little girl's dream...
Follow the blood.
Follow the blood...
Zoey crawled
into the kitchen,
Grabbed the counter
to pull herself up,
Then reached
for the phone,
Giving her
a perfect opportunity
To use
the garbage disposal.
- how we doing in here?
- uh, there seems to be
a problem with the disposal.
- oh.
[sighs]
Oh, no, no, no.
- it's probably just
something jammed in there.
It's an easy fix.
Let me take a look.
- you'd do that?
- sure.
Blue nitrile.
The same material found
in police protective gloves.
If the glove fits...
- isn't he a doll?
Fixing the disposal.
- huh.
Wasn't broken this morning.
- give it a try.
- all right.
- yay!
- if i was your wife,
I'd hang on to you.
You're so...handy.
- [chuckles]
- so it's either
The cannery bludgeoning
or the bar beating.
- the cannery body
was a dump.
Trinity's not a dumper.
He picks a location,
takes his victims there.
- so it's the bar.
- hmm.
- fuckin' a.
We've found trinity's
30-year-old kill site.
Oh! oh, no, oh!
- here, here, here.
- fuck me.
- take the file, take the file.
No harm.
[clears throat]
Um, mind if i...?
- yeah, sure,
why don't you?
So, uh, 30 years ago,
A father of two
was bludgeoned to death
Between the hours
of 7:00 and 10:00 p.m.
In the bathroom
of murphy's tavern.
- which is where
i'll be today.
- me too.
- won't that be a problem
with ashton?
- anton.
And, no,
he's cool...sort of.
- sort of?
- he gets jealous
for no reason.
- he's a smart man.
- look, don't make me come up
with thought bubbles
To put over those silent looks
of yours.
Just say
what you're thinking.
- all right.
I, uh, i thought i could keep
my feelings for you
As background noise
to this investigation.
But, in working with you,
That noise has gotten...
- loud?
- deafening.
But they're my feelings.
- yup.
They're your feelings.
- you're in
a committed relationship.
- i am.
- and i would hate to...
- i'd hate that too.
Jesus.
I've gotta go.
- will i see you
tonight?
- i don't...
Fuck!
- is there a break
in the vacation murders case?
- i'm having intimate relations
with laguerta.
- congratulations?
- i need some advice.
- huh, lot of wise people
out there.
- i don't trust anyone else
with this secret.
- that's too bad.
- maria has awakened...
mi pasion.
- right.
- when i'm with her,
i feel like a man.
Like my heart
is blossoming.
- that's a problem?
- no.
The problem is
she wants to disclose
Our relationship
to the higher-ups--
Which i--i understand
is a formality.
I just hate the thought
of them knowing.
- 'cause you're
embarrassed.
- because once
you define it, it's defined.
It's--it's officially
official.
- you're her boyfriend.
- exactly.
- next thing you know,
you're moving in,
Your life is gone, and
it's just kids and neighbors
And painted mugs.
- painted mugs?
- it's a metaphor.
- for what?
- look, if you want out,
get out.
Before you have to do
something drastic.
- i don't want out.
i don't.
I just want to protect it
By keeping it private.
- yeah.
- who knew it would matter
so much to me?
thanks, socio.
I'll keep you posted
on the details.
- great.
I am a stickler
for details.
- you still dating
that she-bag reporter?
Is it that hard
for you to get laid?
- i'm not--
- after she put
Lundy's name in the paper
and ruined everything?
- i'm not seeing her.
- maybe you should have
told her that.
News flash, quinn:
you're an idiot.
- yeah, i got
your messages.
- but you didn't
call me back.
- tell me, is this conversation
gonna end up in the paper too?
'cause you have no idea the
shitstorm you've gotten me into.
- i'm sorry.
Really, but...
we can work this out.
- i'm not interested
in working it out.
- don't say that.
- come on, it's not like
this was a big deal.
- don't you dare tell me
there's nothing here.
- you're right, i won't.
But it's way too
complicated.
- i don't want to lose you.
- christine.
you never had me.
Find yourself
another source.
- on vacation,
we buy snow globes,
Send postcards to preserve
the good times,
Remind us where we've been.
Zoey's crime scene
had its own memento...
A glove whose rolled cuff
preserved the gunshot residue
After she shot herself.
And blood.
Odds are it belongs to
the late darius rae.
Ah, zoey,
wish you were here.
But since you're not...
I'll come to you.
I should get to pembroke pines
just in time
To follow
officer kruger home.
- original structure
was a single-story tavern.
Current building--
12 floors, mostly vacant.
- i'm found.
- lobby's open 24 hours,
guard on duty,
Too much foot traffic--
trinity would have to choose
Another floor.
- so sorry.
I wasn't watching
where i was going.
- no damage done.
Excuse me.
You dropped these.
- thanks.
Bus number 432.
White male, maybe 6'4",
200, 220 pounds,
Age around 60,
Hair gray, eyes blue...
Something in them.
- maybe i do miss
rita and the kids...
[line rings]
- [baby cries]
- hello?
- hi, it's me.
- oh, uh,
hey, guys, keep it down.
- i was just checking in.
- oh, we have the rehearsal
dinner in 20 minutes,
And--astor, your dress
is getting wrinkled.
- sounds like
you got your hands--
- hey, cody.
[indistinct]
I'm sorry,
what were you saying?
- i was just saying
you probably have your hands--
- mom, cody pulled
my barrettes out.
- it was an accident.
- you took them
right off my head.
- i'm sorry, i didn't hear
what you were saying.
- it was...nothing.
- uh, we gotta go.
love you.
- me...
[dial tone]
Too.
[siren whoops]
Shit!
Going the speed limit,
hands-free dialing,
No violations.
[siren wailing]
This is bad.
What a coincidence.
- out of the vehicle,
please.
Hands on the hood,
- my wife and i changed
our mind about buying a house.
- dexter morgan.
You didn't mention that you were
a, uh, spatter analyst,
Miami metro.
- didn't seem relevant
to house hunting.
- hmm.
Well, the file clerk
at my station--
He's a friend.
He told me that sam
had pulled my case file,
And sam told me he'd
loaned it to a colleague.
You can imagine my surprise
when i looked up that colleague
And saw your face.
- i am writing a paper
on blood swipes.
- are you
getting off on this?
- am i supposed to be?
- you're the kind of sicko
who likes watching
A woman in pain?
- not that kind of sicko, no.
- i lost my husband.
I watched my child die
in front of me.
Do you have any idea
how agonizing that was?
- agony would be
the normal reaction.
- i will not let
that wound be reopened.
Do you understand?
Traffic's heavy
on brickell.
Might want to avoid it
on your way home.
Was, uh,
3319 meadow lane,
right?
I'm letting you off
with a warning.
Drive carefully.
- i'm calling it off.
- you can't.
She knows who you are.
- she knows who dexter morgan
lab geek is.
- she knows where you live,
Where your wife and children
will be when they get home
In 48 hours.
- if i back off,
she backs off.
- still leaves you
on the radar of a killer cop
Who has no qualms
about shooting her family,
Much less a lab rat.
- she's stalking me.
Taking her by surprise will be
out of the question.
- you're the one
who wanted a challenge.
And now you've
batted the beehive.
[beeps]
- dexter,
frank lundy here.
Sorry to bother you
at home.
I was just trying to reach
your sister.
Thought
she was maybe with you.
I had an interesting
encounter today.
- me too.
- gotta admit,
she is impressive.
Makes you wonder
why someone like her
Ever got married and had kids
in the first place.
- someone like her?
Someone like her
needs to be in control.
- and she thinks she is.
- she won't see me coming.
[phone rings]
- pembroke pines
police department.
- records, please?
- transferring.
- records,
langsbury speaking.
- uh, yeah,
this is miami metro forensics.
I wanted to request copies
of a suspect's file.
- suspect's name?
- uh, darius rae.
That's rae with an e.
Drug dealer and alleged killer
of zoey kruger's family.
- what is this
in regard to?
- i--we're--it involves
the vacation murders case.
- i'll send the file over.
To whose attention?
- just, uh, forensics.
Batting the beehive.
- dexter.
I know everything.
- i'm gonna choose
not to misinterpret that.
- when angel said
he told you about us, i was...
Angry, to say the least.
- i really didn't
want to know.
- but now you do.
- yeah.
- actually,
i'm glad because
I could really use
a man's opinion on how to handle
Our relationship.
Or fling, or whatever it is
that he and i are doing naked.
- well, i was just
going to lunch.
- that's great.
Beth's cafe sound good?
- oh, actually,
we should just talk here.
It's more private.
- yeah.
Angel's a great cop.
the best i know.
But he doesn't understand
the politics in this building.
And we have to manage
how this thing becomes public.
And if it's handled wrong,
our jobs could be at risk.
And we can't take
that chance.
- i...never leave anything
to chance.
- thank you.
You're getting good
at this relationship stuff.
Mm, marriage agrees
with you.
Thank you.
- lundy called last night.
he was trying to reach you.
- [laughs]
That is just so...
Fucking great.
- okay.
Looks like
the beehive is buzzing.
And here comes the sting.
You're out of your
jurisdiction, officer kruger.
Wait for it.
- [stammers]
what are you doing?
- you want info
on darius rae?
Ask me anything.
- that file was
for a case i'm working.
- i asked you nicely
to leave me alone.
- you threatened me.
- you think that
was a threat?
- what, are you gonna
murder me too?
Like you murdered
your family?
Your own daughter?
- you're sick.
- i know what you did.
I have proof.
- not possible.
- from the garbage disposal,
The gloves
you wore that night.
There was gun residue
on them.
I have a meeting with
my superiors tomorrow morning
To tell them everything.
- there's no chain of
custody.
- still,
it'll raise questions.
And if you left
this much behind,
We'll find something else.
- you're trying to rape me.
- i'm not touching you.
- that's why
you came to my house.
And the real estate agent
will testify that
You were flirting with me.
And then you stalked me here
and tried to assault me.
And i had to defend myself.
- except...
The blowback of my blood
into the muzzle of your gun
Will show
a flat contact shot
That's highly unlikely
during a struggle.
You could shoot me
center mass,
But the low directionality
will show
I was in
a defensive position.
You'd have to calculate
the exact distance
To create a spatter pattern
that supports self-defense.
- go ahead.
Tell them.
No one
is going to believe you
Over me.
So please.
Tell them...
Everything.
- you won't
give me the chance.
I'm counting on it.
[knocks]
- debra.
You're here.
I called because,
trinity, i--
- shut up.
- this time
she won't come in a squad car.
This time it won't be
about threats and intimidation.
This time, it's for real.
They're all props,
The camouflage
of a family man.
She'll believe them.
She has no idea who i am,
But i know exactly
who she is.
Marco...
Polo.
- she's going to make it
look like i walked in
On a home robbery,
Got myself killed.
She's good at creating
the narrative of a crime.
That hand's the first thing
i cut off.
[grunts]
- [cries]
- surprise.
- [grunts]
Help!
help!
Sorry, sorry, i was just
buying your tickets.
You're taking a boat
out of the country.
Eventually you'll land
in the philippines.
You're smart, there's no
extradition treaty there.
- i'm not going anywhere.
- i know something about
creating a narrative too.
Suitcases packed, your car
will be left at the port,
And the blue glove
is back in your disposal.
You'll flee the country.
You'll--whoosh--
never be caught.
You're that good.
Or that dead.
- you're gonna
rape and kill me?
- [laughs]
what is it with you and rape?
No one's raping anyone.
Mm, killing
on the other hand.
- why are you
doing this to me?
- why did you
do this to them?
- it was darius rae.
- no, you wanted out.
You wanted your freedom.
From
the constant demands...
They took it all.
And they wanted more.
- i couldn't breathe.
- you did it to survive.
- you understand.
- i understand, all right.
- look at you.
What kind of father
does this?
What kind of husband?
[groans]
- not the kind
who kills his family.
- you're going to have
to choose.
- not what you chose.
- you can't hide
what you are.
- oh, i can.
I'm better at it
than you.
- you will choose
your life over theirs.
- i won't.
I'd rather risk
them knowing the truth...
Than lose them.
Wow.
[sighs]
I don't want to lose them.
I don't.
That's the difference
between us.
- [groans]
- nice souvenir.
Sure you don't want
to stay here?
- you didn't raise
a loner, dad.
- maybe i should have.
- i'll survive.
- you sure?
Better see
to that drip, son.
You don't want this place
going to hell.
You need it too much.
- my own little
vacation spot.
[phone rings]
Hey, how you guys
doing up there?
- we're on our way.
We left
right after the wedding.
We should be home soon.
- good, i'm glad.
- the house!
- don't hurry.
drive safe.
You're home!
- yeah, we made it.
The wedding
was exhausting.
The kids
were a nightmare.
Just wanted
to strangle them.
Oh, no.
- yeah, it just
slipped out of my hand.
Sorry.
- oh, the kids will be excited
to make you a new one.
[sighs]
[sighs softly]
I missed you so much.
- i missed you too.
- i'm a fuckwad.
- you're not a fuckwad.
- i knew.
From the second
i saw you at the station,
I knew how i felt.
It's how
i've always felt.
I just wouldn't
admit it.
'cause i'm a fuckwad.
- you're human.
- and now i've cheated
on a guy
Who doesn't deserve
to be treated that way.
I should have
broken up with him first.
But i'm a fuckwad.
- no. don't.
You're not.
You're beautiful.
And you were confused.
And now you're not.
So...
We'll set this right,
together.
All right?
- don't go disappearing
on me again.
- not a--
[gunshot]
[two gunshots]
- stay with me.