Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- previously on dexter...
- it's always the same
three kills with trinity.
Young woman
in the bathtub...
- [moans]
- followed by a mother
falling to her death.
- [screams]
- and ending with a man
getting bludgeoned.
Trinity's likely someone
Who's gone his own solitary way
through life,
Foregone all
but the most rudimentary
Of human connections.
A lone wolf.
If we can find where
he bludgeoned back then...
Lobby's open 24 hours,
guard on duty.
Too much foot traffic--
trinity would have
To choose another floor.
- ooh, so sorry.
Wasn't watching
where i was going.
- white male,
Eyes blue,
Something in them.
- super agent lundy has a hunch
that the dead woman
Is connected
to this big serial killer case.
- you still dating
that she-bag reporter?
After she put lundy's name
in the paper?
- tell me, is this conversation
Going to end up
in the paper too?
'cause you have no idea
The shit storm
you've gotten me into.
Find yourself another source.
- just unsealed the juvie
records of johnny rose,
Our vacation murder suspect.
Shoplifting with his high school
girlfriend nikki wald.
- get down!
[gunshots]
- i think we should inform
the brass
About our relationship.
- it's none of their business.
- i get a gig in town
to spend more time with you,
And you spend
all your time
With your ex.
- don't go disappearing
on me again.
- not a...
[gunshot]
[two gunshots]
[radio chatter]
[honking]
- deb.
- hey, you.
Back behind the line.
- no, i was called here.
I'm dexter morgan.
that might be my sister.
- i understand, sir,
but right now i need you
To step back
and let our people do their job.
- no, no, i'm
with miami metro forensics.
My laminate and my wallet
are in the car.
- until i see some i.d.,
i need you to step back.
- and i need you
to fucking listen.
My sister was shot,
No one can tell me
what her condition is,
And that's a dead body.
- sir.
- you want to let me go.
- hansen. hands off.
He's one of us.
- deb's alive.
okay?
They're taking her
to the hospital.
- i have to see her.
How bad is it?
- lost a lot of blood.
- if deb dies,
I'll be...
Lost.
- paramedics think the bullets
are through and through.
- she's gonna be okay?
- it's looking good.
[siren wails]
- who did this?
- we got here
just before you did.
- quinn was first on scene.
He says it's smelling like
the vacation murders' m.o.
- then that's...
- lundy.
- what was deb doing with lundy
at 5:00 in the morning?
Oh.
- dexter, i swear to you,
we will find who did this.
- my kit's in my car.
- hey, hey, hey.
You got better places to be.
Like with your sister.
Go. that's an order.
- you'll know the minute
we know anything.
- lundy was a worthy adversary.
He deserves better
Than to be face down
in a hotel parking lot,
A random victim
of a senseless crime.
- sorry about deb, man.
- did she say anything?
- she was in shock,
Didn't see
who pulled the trigger.
- batista said you think
This looks like
the vacation murders.
- deb's cash
and credit cards are gone.
So's lundy's watch and wallet.
- anything, vince?
- surgeon general wouldn't
have been able to save him.
Gsws to the neck and chest.
He bled out in seconds.
- lundy was shot twice?
Deb was vulnerable
and a potential witness.
The shooter could have easily
finished her off like lundy.
I should get to the hospital.
- deb, she knows.
Even though
we go at it all the time,
We're still...
- yeah, she knows.
- we're gonna
get these fuckers.
- not if you're looking
in the wrong direction.
- detective quinn.
- not now. really.
- i didn't come here
for a quote.
You all right?
- my partner's been shot.
The last thing i am
is all right.
- i know this can't be easy,
But if you need anything,
I'm here for you.
- thanks, christine.
That means a lot.
I got to...
- it's okay.
- all right.
- sergeant batista.
- no comment.
- come on, sergeant.
Is this the work
of the vacation murderers?
- i said no...
On the record.
[clicks pen]
It's too early to tell,
But one of 'em,
johnny rose,
We found out has syphilis,
And it's real bad.
untreatable.
Multiple partners.
Print that.
With pictures.
- i call it in now,
It'll be online this morning
And on the stands
this afternoon.
With pictures.
- while my colleagues
Are working
the vacation murder theory,
I'm gonna follow lundy's theory
And check his hotel room
for clues.
- lundy devoted his life
to hunting trinity.
- he left word for me
He'd had
an interesting encounter
Two days ago.
- you think it was trinity?
- every crime scene
is a jigsaw puzzle.
So many pieces.
Assemble them right,
A picture forms.
If it was trinity,
It'd explain why deb is alive
and lundy isn't.
- trinity's a monster.
If he was the one
who hurt your sister,
You need to kill him.
That was my blood
down there too.
You can't let these
be logged into evidence.
- not until
i have a complete picture.
- police so far
are refusing to comment
On the murder
of a former fbi agent
And the shooting
of a miami metro
Homicide detective.
But channel nine has learned
There may be a connection
To the so called
vacation murders.
Sources tell us that...
- all right. denver omelet,
side of rye toast.
Can i top that off
for ya?
- coffee's fine,
But there are no diced tomatoes
in my omelet.
- i'm sorry about that.
Cook is slammed today.
I'll bring you
a side of tomatoes.
How's that coffee?
- my coffee's not the issue.
My breakfast,
on the other hand, is.
You need to start over.
Denver omelet...
with tomatoes...diced.
- coming right up.
- you're a dear. thanks.
[cell phone rings]
- astor, will you get that?
- but it's dexter's.
- oh, it's okay.
He was in such a hurry
he probably forgot it.
Could be the hospital.
- is aunt deb gonna die?
- oh, no, honey.
no, she's gonna be okay.
- some man.
he says he's dexter's landlord.
There's something wrong
with dexter's apartment.
- oh, there's got to be
a misunderstanding.
Uh, yes, hi.
this is rita morgan?
- how long have you been there?
- not long.
You're sitting up.
It's a good sign.
- i'm fine.
I didn't even need surgery.
Couple stitches.
- looks like
more than a couple.
You have any pain?
- no. just tired.
Whatever they gave me
has some kick.
- you want me to come back?
- it's okay.
i'm fine.
- you remember anything at all?
You see anything unusual?
- it's all still a blur.
- who was hit first?
You, or--?
- jesus, dex.
- am i squeezing too tight?
- i expect
those kind of questions
From batista or quinn,
But not my brother.
- you said you were fine.
Twice.
- doesn't matter, anyway.
- just tell me
what you want me to do.
- that's just it.
You can't do anything.
No one can.
I didn't feel anything.
I didn't even know
i'd been hit
Until i was on the ground.
And then two more shots.
So much blood.
- you're safe.
I'm here.
- lundy had this look
in his eyes.
Like he was apologizing.
I couldn't do anything.
I was helpless.
Fuck, i can't even walk
Three feet to the bathroom.
- do you need to--?
- yeah. bad.
- come on.
Okay?
- mm-hmm.
- i may not know
who shot my sister,
Or why her life was spared,
But i do know i won't
be returning the favor.
- oh, god.
deb, is she--?
- peeing.
I'll just--uh...
Be outside.
Hey.
- how's deb?
- she's lucky to be alive.
- i was so worried.
Can i see her?
- uh, she's peeing.
With anton.
- i would have been here sooner,
But i got hung up
on the phone.
Your landlord called.
A pipe burst in your kitchen...
At your apartment?
- oh.
I was just
hanging on to the place
Until the lease ran out.
So i could get
the security deposit back.
- why'd you tell me
you got rid of it?
- i said that?
[harrison crying]
- talk about this later.
This isn't
the time or the place,
Not with deb here.
Family comes first.
- i'm just so sorry
i wasn't here.
- you don't have
to keep saying that.
- so glad you're all right.
- i'm not.
- babe, what is it?
- i slept with lundy.
- i thought you were happy.
- i thought i was too.
I can move out.
- no. no. no.
Listen, i'll see you
through this, okay?
You did the same for me.
- anton, stop.
You deserve so much better.
- is that what you want?
- sorry i hurt you.
- anton?
- [speaks spanish]
- gracias.
Just hung up from notifying
lundy's daughter.
- then you could really use
A shot of whiskey in there.
I get that the guy's
personally invested in this,
But matthews hovering around
like a vulture
Isn't gonna help us
catch bad guys.
- angel...
I made
official disclosure yesterday
That we're seeing each other.
- we talked about this.
- i know.
But it was
the right thing to do.
- i said i was uncomfortable
with the disclosure stuff,
And you go ahead
and do it anyway?
- i made a judgment call.
- the problem, maria,
Is that you made it
for the both of us.
You shouldn't keep
the deputy chief waiting.
- [sighs]
- what do we got?
- not much.
No witnesses,
no security cameras.
Took a statement from deb,
She can't remember
seeing anything.
- forensics.
- waiting on trace
and ballistics from the lab.
- apbs out on rose and wald.
County's increased
patrols at the airport
And the higher profile
tourist hotels.
- if my face
was all over the media
For shooting a cop and a fed,
I'd be digging a fucking hole
All the way to china.
No one fuckin' go there.
- or you'd be watching the press
To try and stay one step
ahead of us.
It's a hail mary,
But i planted a story
With quinn's girlfriend.
- she's not--
we're not--
- you're the paper's
unnamed online source
About johnny boy's drip?
- i figure
if johnny has syphilis
And nikki wasn't listed
by the county
As one
of his sexual partners...
- she may not know.
- exactly.
Maybe we turn these two
against each other.
- rita was right.
Family does come first.
Finding who did this
to my sister comes first.
Is this
a new page of the code?
Revenge?
My sanctuary.
It's private
and...sacred no more.
If i have
to give up this place,
What will i do
about my roommate,
The dark passenger?
This apartment
is the only thing
That's helped me keep
the mask in place.
Without it...
I'll burst.
[cell phone rings]
- they're letting me out
tomorrow.
- that's great.
- any chance
you can give me a ride?
- of course.
- i'm also kind of
gonna need a place to stay.
I broke up with anton,
And, no, i don't want
to talk about it.
- we can make room for you.
- rita won't mind?
- don't worry, deb.
i'll take care of everything.
- trinity's a lone wolf.
Unable to connect.
Except with his victims.
He never deviates.
Bleeds out a young female
in a bathtub,
Forces a woman
to jump to her death,
And five days later
Bludgeons an older male.
I'll look at potential sites.
This may be the closest
to trinity i've ever been.
- lundy got closer
than he thought.
- he just couldn't see
how all the pieces interlock,
What they form.
A sacred ritual.
- if there's anyone who knows
the importance of ritual,
It's you.
- lundy underestimated
How far trinity would go
To make sure his ritual
Wasn't interrupted.
- lundy was an obstacle.
- and trinity killed him.
- if anyone has ever deserved
to be on your table,
It's this son of a bitch.
- can i help you?
- i'm taking on a project.
- how big?
- almost more
than i can handle.
And i don't have
a lot of time.
- maybe you need
another hand or two.
There's plenty
of laborers out there.
- no, no.
i work alone.
- sounds like you need
the right tool for the job.
- so much work.
But i have to finish
what i started, right?
- yeah, i--i guess.
[ominous music]
- what would you do?
- me?
Oh, i'd go
with the framing hammer.
Got a lot of heft.
It's versatile.
You can't go wrong.
- i see what you mean.
You've been very helpful.
- lobby's open 24 hours.
[tape fast-forwards]
12-story building,
hundreds of rooms.
Trinity could strike anywhere.
He'll have to set up shop
in the surveillance room.
Trinity's
the perfect predator--
Camouflaged, waiting
for his victim to be alone,
And then he strikes.
- trinity struck here
30 years ago.
A bartender,
father of two,
Was found bludgeoned to death
In the men's room of a tavern
At this same address.
If history
is going to repeat itself,
This is where trinity will be.
- problem is, you have no idea
who you're looking for.
- lundy was so methodical,
He would have commented
on trinity's physical appearance
If their paths
had ever crossed,
But there's
nothing in his tapes.
I've listened to them all.
- you sure about that?
that's your recorder.
Where's lundy's?
- it wasn't in the hotel,
Because lundy had it on him.
Must have been
logged into evidence--shit.
- dexter, you need that tape.
You need to be certain
It's trinity on your table.
- there's still time.
He won't complete the cycle
until tomorrow night.
And i'll be here.
Waiting.
- oh, god!
Oh!
[moans, laughs]
- that was, uh...
- unexpected.
- that's not an adjective
i usually hear.
- i'm not complaining.
I'm just--
I'm just wondering
why you're really here.
- my way of saying i appreciate
you running that story
For my boss.
- okay. hmm.
You fucked me to thank me?
- technically,
i went down on you
To thank you.
[laughter]
- i thought you said
this was just too complicated,
You being a cop
and me being a reporter.
- i guess i like complicated.
- look who's here.
- sorry, astor.
I promise
it won't be for long.
- it's okay.
i get cody's room.
- sorry, cody.
- come on, guys.
it's time to go to school.
Check in later.
[door closes]
- everything all right
between you and my brother?
- we just need
to have a talk.
- it isn't about
me staying here, is it?
- no, you're family.
you're always welcome here.
I'm gonna
let you get settled in,
And i'm gonna get you
some water
For these pain pills, okay?
- rita.
Thank you.
[dramatic music]
- thanks for letting deb
stay with us.
- it was either here
or your apartment.
Look, we can't
keep putting this off.
- it's still not a good time.
I need to get to the station.
- so when do you suppose
It'll be a good time
To discuss
why you lied to me?
I'm really trying here,
dexter.
[horn honks]
- dexter.
- i'm just asking for
a little patience, all right?
Not for me, but for deb.
Right now i need to focus
on finding who did this.
- okay.
- you didn't
come over last night.
- so little time
to sleep lately.
I thought i'd get more rest
in my own bed.
- i'm sorry i went
behind your back to matthews.
It was wrong,
and i apologize.
If you haven't noticed,
I'm a bit of a control freak.
- you mean like how like
to guard the remote control
With your life?
Or how you need to be
the first one in the shower
Or how you like to--
- look, the reason
i went to the brass
Was because it'd be
One less thing to worry about
ruining what we have.
- the only thing
that would ruin what we have
Is if we're not honest
with each other.
No more secrets.
- no more secrets.
[timer dings]
- then i'm not going anywhere.
- that's everything collected
From the parking lot
and the hotel rooms
Back there on the right.
- [sighs]
thanks for doing this.
My father gave deb the ring,
And it means the world to her.
- i checked the inventories.
Masuka never logged it in.
- yeah, deb doesn't remember
if she was wearing it or not.
The shooting has her
pretty messed up.
If my coming down here
to double check
Helps ease her mind,
So be it, right?
- yep.
- ah, fuck.
Damn it.
- you morgans and that mouth.
- do you mind?
- oh, yeah.
don't sweat it.
There's plenty more
where those come from.
- thanks.
- here you go.
- guess who just found her ring.
Sorry for the trouble.
Thanks a lot, though.
- no problem.
- i appreciate
the personal tour.
- any time i can do rounds
With a fellow human being
is a win.
- you're alone every night?
- yeah, economy's a bitch.
There used to be two of us
on every shift, but now--
- oh, say no more.
I'm recently laid off myself.
From here on out
i'm gonna be my own boss.
- well, there's plenty
of office space here.
You know, more tenants
means more money.
Then maybe i won't have
to do these double shifts
And i can see my kids
once in a while.
Oh, you end up
setting up shop here,
I guarantee this'll be
your favorite destination
Come lunch time.
- right on schedule.
And you brought me
a customer.
- it's a future renter.
- well,
possible future renter.
- can i get you any?
- no, no.
Caffeine makes me
a different person.
Appreciate the offer, though.
So you say
you walk this whole place
Every two hours?
That's quite a workout.
- my wife calls it
low-impact aerobics
Or some shit like that.
It takes about 45 minutes,
Give or take a smoke break.
- well, we all have our vices.
- so how'd you like
the building?
[elevator bell dings]
- it's perfect.
- great.
- thanks a lot.
- mm-hmm.
[baby crying]
- rita, i think
something's wrong with harrison.
- i know that cry.
Someone's wet, isn't he?
- good.
Thought it was me.
- oh, no.
No, harrison
loves his aunt deb.
Can i ask you something?
- i don't do diapers.
- did dexter tell you
he kept his apartment?
- what the fuck?
Are you kidding?
He told me he got rid of it.
- me too.
Just thought
he might have said something
Since you two are so close.
- not a word.
God, it's like a morgan family
curse or something--
Make the worst choice
possible.
At least dexter's
don't get people killed.
- you think you're responsible
for lundy's death?
- he never would have been
anywhere near that parking lot
If it weren't for me.
- is that why your pain pills
are in the trash?
Punish yourself?
What happened to lundy
isn't your fault.
You had no control over it.
This isn't about choices
Or even about you.
Sometimes bad things
just happen.
- that's the answer to this?
Bad things happen?
- life happens.
- i've yet to find
trinity's signature
At any of his crime scenes.
[tape fast forwards]
Trinity moves
from state to state.
Law enforcement never links
his kill cycles
To one another.
Over 30 years of killing.
- the cycle, the ritual,
They tell me
where trinity will be,
But i have to know
who i'm looking for.
I have to be sure.
- lobby's open 24 hours.
Guard on duty.
Too much foot traffic.
Trinity'd have
to choose another floor.
- ooh. sorry.
- bus number 432.
Male.
Maybe 6'4".
190 to 200 pounds.
Age around 60.
Hair gray, eyes blue.
Something in them.
- lundy saw a ghost.
- okay, listen up, everyone.
I just got word there was
a shooting at a motel.
You all need to get there
as soon as possible, guys.
So quinn's already en route.
Angel, you're with me.
Masuka, grab your stuff.
- what's going on?
- motel shooting.
Body's a match
for johnny rose.
- i'm going with you.
- you can't work this.
You're next of kin.
I've got it.
Let's just hope deb
Is finally
gonna get some justice.
- that's the plan.
- karma.
What a fuckin' concept.
uno, dos, tres.
- the first bullet
didn't quite make her point.
- lieutenant,
we've got nikki wald
Cornered in the alley
behind al's liquor store.
- let's go.
- prick.
Son of a bitch.
god.
[muttering]
- what do we got?
- found her in the alley.
Altered, agitated.
Every time we get near
the gun goes up.
- we good?
- yeah.
- why? why?
[muttering]
- nikki!
- damn it.
He fuckin'--
He fuckin' cheated on me.
- we need you
to put the gun down.
- he ruined everything.
You fuckin' ruined everything.
- she's wasted.
She doesn't
even know where she is.
Cover us.
- nikki.
No one's gonna hurt you.
We just want to talk.
- the alley's sealed off.
You can't go anywhere.
- did you hear that, johnny?
What about the boat?
What about bermuda, johnny?
Wasn't that the plan?
You piece of shit!
[electricity crackles]
aah!
[cell phone rings]
- we got 'em, morgan.
- got who?
- nikki walden, johnny rose.
well, we got nikki.
Johnny's on his way
to the morgue.
- what happened?
- she fuckin' shot him.
long story.
Look, i know this
doesn't change what happened,
But hopefully you'll find
some peace of mind
Knowing this thing's over.
- yeah.
Peace of mind.
- i got to take
this skank down to booking.
Congratulations, partner.
- such a waste.
Lundy,
those other tourists.
For what?
a boat to bermuda?
- hell hath no fury
like a meth addict scorned.
- your office, lieutenant.
- was--was that a smile?
- i don't know.
- congratulations, maria.
That was really good
police work out there today.
- thanks.
But it was sergeant batista's
good police work.
- yes.
Well, i know
he's an asset to your team,
But this department can't risk
A defense attorney turning
your romantic involvement
Into a courtroom sideshow
Every time you work
a case together.
- what are you saying?
- i am saying i need you
to transfer sergeant batista
Out of homicide.
- tom, this is bullshit.
We followed protocol.
Christ, he made this bust.
- which is why
i'm going to make sure
That sergeant batista
gets a promotion
Along with his transfer.
Have the papers
on my desk by monday.
Sergeant.
- fuck.
what is it?
- while everyone's chasing
their tails over nikki wald,
I'm going after the man
who really shot my sister.
In a few hours,
the enigma that is trinity
Will be on my table.
A riddle wrapped in plastic.
[cell phone rings]
Morgan.
- i need to see you.
- i'm kind of
in the middle of something.
Can it wait?
- no.
- well, i'm way over
on the other side of town.
It'll take me
at least an hour to get there.
- i'm not home.
I'm where frank was shot.
You can't even see our blood.
It's like it never happened.
- deb?
- what the fuck's your problem?
- i got here
as fast as i could.
- you have everything,
And you're doing
your goddamn best
To throw it all away.
- rita told you
about the apartment?
- what the fuck
were you thinking?
You have to make this right.
- i'm not sure i know how.
- you figure it out.
I'm the fuck-up in the family.
not you.
- don't say that.
- you have a choice.
To be a good husband.
To be a good father.
- i know.
It's just, uh...
Sometimes i feel trapped.
- by what?
Three kids?
A wife who adores you?
Yesterday,
i had lundy and anton.
And now they're gone
because of me.
- you didn't do anything wrong.
- it doesn't matter what i do.
Or what i choose.
I'm what's wrong.
There's nothing
i can do about it.
If i'm not hurting myself,
I'm hurting
everyone around me.
There's nothing
i can do about it.
I'm--i'm broken.
I'm--
- no, you're not.
I am.
Why don't we
go back to the house?
- don't! don't.
I need to be here.
Where lundy died.
I can't do
a fucking thing about it.
- my sister doesn't deserve
to be in this kind of pain.
But i know who does.
Trinity hurt my sister,
And i'm going
to hurt him back,
And it's going to feel--
uh-oh.
- your manager let me in.
He had no idea
we were married.
Funny thing is,
i'm getting to wonder myself.
- rita, you're upset.
- i actually convinced myself
That by coming here
This would all make sense...
Why it was so important
That you keep this place
a secret.
[harrison whines]
As i was coming over here,
All i could think about--
That you were using
drugs again.
That you were having
an affair again.
- that will never happen.
- i went through your cabinets,
Rifled through your desk,
Looking for anything
That would explain
What would be so horrible
That my husband
would have to keep a place
To hide it from me
Or his own sister.
- and?
- i was gonna break the lock,
But i was too scared
of what i might find.
And you know why?
'cause you put me
in this position, dexter.
This is not the type of person
or wife that i want to be.
- you really want to know
what's inside?
- yes.
- it was harry's.
I wasn't comfortable having it
in the house with the kids,
So i kept it here.
See?
I have nothing to hide.
Except for the syringes,
scalpels, and bone saw
Hidden in that
secret drawer underneath.
- nothing to hide.
Like your car accident
And your concussion
and this apartment?
The most disturbing thing
About your lying is that...
I'm beginning to see
Just how good
you really are at it.
You should sleep here tonight.
When you're ready
to come home,
We have a lot of work to do
If this marriage
has any hope.
- hey.
pulling an all-nighter?
- yep.
no rest for the wicked.
- have a good one.
- always do.
- it's almost poetic--
One serial killer
Ending the 30-year reign
of another.
Trinity could be
anywhere in this building.
I've got to get
To the security
surveillance room.
- huh.
where's that security guard?
He was here last night.
[man whimpering]
- i've been
so focused on trinity,
I've neglected
who his victim might be.
- the bludgeoning victim
30 years ago,
Didn't he have two kids?
- it's the security guard.
[man cries out]
[elevator dings]
- if he's here...
- then where's trinity?
- aah!
- take the bait.
Take the bait.
- [whimpering]
oh, no.
Please.
I'm a father!
- you were no father.
- aah!
- you made me...
You made me...
[thud]
- the recording disc is gone.
- where are you, trinity?
- [grunting]
- oh, my god.
- you made me do this.
- trinity.
[suspenseful music]
Shit.
- the elevators aren't moving.
He's using the stairs.
- which one?
I can't risk
picking the wrong exit
And miss trinity.
His car has to be here.
[gate raising]
No way i lose you again,
trinity.
[indistinct voices]
In miami, nobody sees.
- he's scurrying back
To whatever hole
he crawled out of.
- the lone wolf
thinks this is over.
[tires screech, horn honks]
- asshole!
- what the hell's he doing?
Where are you going,
trinity?
- stay with him.
He's not getting away.
- he doesn't belong here.
it doesn't make sense.
- hi, honey.
Mmm. missed you.
- hey, kids.
- daddy.
- hey, dad.
- lundy was wrong.
I was wrong.
Neither of us
Knew pieces of the puzzle
were missing.
Trinity's a husband,
A father.
He's...
Like me.