- previously on dexter...
Dexter morgan.
Good suburban husband.
Happy father of three.
Living the dream.
Want to know
a secret?
Daddy kills people.
- i'm halfway through
the c.i. files you gave me.
Maybe then i'll
finally get some answers.
- tell me again
this isn't crazy.
- crazy good.
Some guy on his honeymoon took
a shot in the head.
Grave condition.
They're pulling
the plug tomorrow.
- last thing our city needs
is dead tourists.
- brought you a copy
of my article.
My editor okayed a follow-up.
you got anything for me?
I'd love to take you out
for a drink.
- let's make it dinner.
- dexter.
- how's my favorite
serial-killer hunter?
- are you here on a case?
- actually i'm retired now.
Now i have the time
to track down
The one twisted son of a bitch
who got away.
- so who is the twisted
son of a bitch?
- i call him
the trinity killer.
Kills in threes.
Been doing it all over
the country for years.
Trinity's in miami,
dexter,
Starting his cycle
all over again.
- vicky noonan, 22,
found in the bathtub.
- 1979?
- but this is
the gomez hearing.
- yes, mr. morgan.
The defendent's name
is benito gomez.
- i must have brought
the wrong notes.
- wrong notes,
wrong blood type,
Wrong case.
That's what you call
a momentary mix-up
In a murder trial?
- that asshole you let walk?
- benito gomez.
- ahh!
now you get it right.
- quinn's legwork
may have shown me
Where to find
our friend,
But this, benny,
My bloodwork is the stuff
that seals your fate.
- fuck you want?
- you.
Shutdown for decades
way out of town.
A fitting place for a punk
like benny gomez
To go down
for the count.
Tonight's the night
i finally...
Sleep.
[tires squealing]
[crash]
- hang in there, buddy.
we got you.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[indistinct chatter]
[siren wails]
[tires squeal]
- do you know where you are?
- ambulance.
what happened?
- you were in an accident.
- [grunts]
- benny.
benny. benny.
- sir, we found something
in your car.
- benny gomez is in there.
- you're okay.
- a bag.
Says "pediatric" on it.
Thought you might need
to take it with you.
- where are they
taking my car?
- just relax.
they'll take care of it.
- i have no idea
where it's going.
If someone--
when someone finds
what's in back...
- it's never as bad
as it looks.
- oh, i'm pretty sure
this is worse.
[siren wails]
- what's your name?
- dexter morgan.
- you know who
the president is?
- barack obama.
- your pupils
are dilating normally,
Which is the good news.
Bad news is that you've
sustained a concussion.
What's the last thing
you remember?
- working late.
My wife...
Asked me to pick up some
medicine for our son.
He's been sick.
I haven't been
sleeping well.
I must have dozed off
at the wheel.
- so you don't remember
the accident?
- no.
I don't even remember getting
in the car.
- short-term memory loss
is common
For this type of injury.
Can also effect your judgment,
cause confusion,
Disorientation.
- i just need a good night's
sleep, i think.
- not for the next 12 hours.
Any type of head trauma,
we want
To keep
the patient awake.
I'd like to keep you here
for observation.
- not an option.
Mmm.
My wife's a registered nurse.
She'll keep an eye on me.
- you got whacked pretty good,
mr. morgan.
You need to be monitored.
I'll get your admission
paperwork going.
Be right back.
- dexter!
Oh, my god!
- [grunts]
- are you all right?
- i'm fine.
It's just a little fender
bender.
- the nurse said they brought
you in an ambulance.
An ambulance, dexter.
- no, it's just
a liability thing.
Doc says i'm good to go.
- [sighs]
i raced over here.
Look at me.
I'm wearing
two different shoes.
Sure you're okay?
You look so pale.
- [scoffs]
hospitals.
They give me the creeps,
which is why
I want to get out of here.
- i was so scared.
- it's okay.
i'm fine.
Come on.
Let's go.
I got to get ready
for work.
Aspirin, caffeine,
whatever it takes.
If i fall asleep,
it's over.
And i'm not talking
concussion.
If they find benny in my car,
it's lethal injection time.
- cody, you butt-breath,
stay away from my stuff!
- if ever there was a reason
to take a personal day,
This is it.
- i'm okay.
But i love having someone
to worry about me.
- good, 'cause that's exactly
what i'm doing.
- who else needs a kiss?
- i'm good.
- how about a hug?
- oh!
- what's the matter?
- uh, just a little sore
from the accident still.
- you got in an accident?
- anyone die?
- just a little fender bender.
No one died.
[horn honks]
There's my cab.
- dexter, why can't you
just call in?
- and what?
take a vacation day?
I'd rather do that when we can
all go to disneyworld.
- disneyworld!
[horn honks]
- i'm fine.
I got to go to work.
And i need one slow day
at the job
Where nobody gets murdered.
I already have a killer
to clean up after.
Me.
- hay cafe con leche
in the kitchen.
- i'll grab some at work.
Got to make sure to get there
before you do.
- don't want
to arouse suspicion.
- mmm.
Speaking of arousing...
- you keep this up,
there goes your head start.
- [chuckles]
What if we showed up together,
hmm?
What's the worst
that could happen?
Better get to the station.
- yeah, i should get
in the shower.
You've got
a ten-minute head start.
- make it 20 just
to be safe.
You should...
Leave your hair down.
It's beautiful.
- yes, ray's tow yard,
15th, right?
- dexter?
Car trouble?
- i--little accident.
It's my fault.
i'm a knucklehead.
- you got a minute?
I'd like
to pick your brain.
- i need to get over
to the motor pool
Before they run out
of loaners or something.
I need to pick up.
- not a problem.
i'll walk with you.
- uh...
yeah, i do have a minute.
- just want to follow up on that
crime scene investigation
From the other day.
Lisa bell?
- lisa bell?
- the girl in the bathtub.
- right!
uh...of course.
The trinity killer's
most recent victim.
- if my theory holds.
You sure you're okay?
- i'm just, uh, tired.
long night.
What can i tell you
about lisa bell?
- you run across
any hair or fiber
In that second blood sample
you found?
- nothing yet.
- really is kismet,
you know?
- [sighs]
kismet?
- fate.
I mean, if trinity had struck
in buffalo
Instead of miami,
i wouldn't have access
To a blood guy
of your caliber.
- well, thanks...for that.
But the person that you should
really be talking to
Is my sister.
She's lead on lisa bell.
- see?
Already putting good ideas
in my head.
Kismet.
- [chuckles]
More like self-preservation.
Last thing i need right now
is frank lundy,
Rock star fbi profiler
Standing between me
and benny gomez.
No crime scene tape,
no coroner's van.
That bodes well.
Unless s.w.a.t.'s lying
in wait for me.
Ah!
The bag's still there.
wait, a bag.
Not the six it takes
to hold a body.
My kill tools.
If they're here
and benny isn't,
He must have been thrown
from the car.
[tires squeal and car crash]
I have to get
to the crash site.
[cell phone rings]
Shit!
Morgan.
- dexter, i need you
at a crime scene.
Someone found the body.
- oh, you make it sound
so easy.
- vizcaya reef hotel.
- just one murder-free day,
miami.
That's all i asked for.
On my way.
- okay, i need you there asap.
This is high priority.
- one stop first.
higher priority.
If that one stop doesn't
give me benny gomez,
I'll be running
out of options.
- all right,
let's get moving.
Yale, soderquist,
morgan, quinn...
- sarge, i'm working a lead
on the lisa bell case.
I have to--
- where the hell's quinn?
[elevator bell dings]
- here. i'm here.
- not for long.
Another tourist
caught a bullet.
You do what you have
to do with the bell case,
But check in,
we may need you at the hotel.
- okay.
- you came up with something
on our case?
- yeah.
yeah.
While you were looking
for your panties
On some chickie-do's floor.
Frances, hey, deb.
Were you able
to pull anything up
On that 30-year-old homicide
i was asking you about?
Perp's name's eddie noonan.
Great.
can you bring it up?
Thanks.
- [sniffs]
My keen forensic
sense of smell
Tells me you're wearing
a perfume.
Anything to do
with the return
Of one special agent
frank lundy?
- i already have
a boyfriend
Who happens to be coming back
in town tonight.
And if you smell me again,
i'll punch you in the throat.
[door opens]
- so much for keeping these
shootings low profile.
- "a string of robberies
turned deadly
"in what authorities
are now calling
'the vacation murder'."
- imagine how thrilled
the mayor is
This thing had a brand name.
- wait till he hears it's
"vacations murders," plural.
- jesus.
Does anyone know
this christine hill?
- we might have met
a few times.
- well, see if you can get her
to tone down
The creative writing, okay?
I'm gonna need an arrest
here soon.
- don't worry, i'm on it.
- actually, i'm on it.
I told the mayor i'd take lead
on this case.
- okay.
- no reflection on you,
sergeant.
- it's your call,
lieutenant.
- you are so boning
this reporter.
- shut the fuck up.
- guys, vamanos,
we got a crime to solve.
- you here to lend a hand?
- more like find one.
If those body parts
were thrown from the car,
Locating them
is a matter of--
- velocity and trajectory.
Should be right around here.
- just imagine
if harrison had been--
- he wasn't.
- if your ritual
hadn't been interrupted
To go pick up meds
for harrison--
- you saying he's
to blame for this?
- i'm not.
- [shudders]
- dizzy?
- [sighs]
I'm fine.
- unless you can't find
benny gomez.
Those bags aren't here,
dexter.
What did you do
with his body?
- rita called
about harrison and...
Everything else is just fog.
- come on, dex.
think.
- [snorts]
- where is benny?
- i don't know.
[cell phone rings]
[keypad beeps]
Fucking dead people.
- everything we've
got on noonan's
1979 homicide conviction.
Evidence logs,
witness statements.
Plea agreements
in there too.
- frances...
- mmm?
- if i hadn't already gone
through that phase in college,
I'd kiss you.
- so why are you interested
In a murder that happened
while you were in diapers?
- a guy kills his wife while
she's taking a bath
30 years ago.
We found a new victim
a few days ago at,
Get this,
his old address.
A coincidence?
i think fucking not.
- you forgetting something?
Your father's old confidential
informant folders
Aren't gonna re-file
themselves.
- sorry.
Susannah coffey.
another blast from the past.
- hmm, was she
at least useful?
- only as a reminder
to wear sunblock.
But i'm still waiting
on a few call backs
From some other names
on the list,
But so far,
i'm starting to think
Maybe i fucked around more
than my old man did.
- just work the scene.
Don't raise flags.
Just work the scene...
Then get the hell
to the boxing arena.
[indistinct radio chatter]
- get those news trucks
out of here.
I got a coroner's van
coming through.
- copy that.
- hey, joey.
- this is an active
crime scene, ma'am.
I'm gonna need you behind
that tape.
- "ma'am"?
- your article,
"vacation murder"?
- "murders" now,
it seems.
- see, how am i supposed
to talk to you
When i got to watch
everything i say?
- which means you do still
want to talk to me?
- yeah, i do.
- good.
'cause i like talking to you.
Amongst other things.
- those things are good,
but we got
To have some ground rules.
- quinn, i need you
to run an inventory
On the victim's personal
effects.
- i'm on it, boss.
- stay back here, ma'am.
You know better.
- [sighs]
Your timing sucks.
- what have we got here?
- shot from behind as he was
coming in the room.
Caught a medium-caliber bullet
in the back of the neck.
- empty wallet, watch missing,
drawer's empty.
- someone figured out
it's easier to rob
People who are dead first.
- directional swipe pattern
of one of the assailant's shoes
Shows he went that way.
- okay, angel,
start a canvass.
Guests, employees,
security cameras.
- already handled.
- next of kin will have
to be notified.
- got it, if you're good
with that, lieutenant.
- you got your hands
full here.
I'll deal with it.
- what's up with the boss lady
taking lead on your case?
- chain of command is there
for a reason, vince.
Just do your
god damn job.
- [groans]
- dude, your gills are green.
You gonna blow?
- uh, i need to get some air.
[sighs]
don't have time for this.
Oh.
Are we blood?
- join you?
- 1:00.
some things--
Holy-what-the-fuck is that?
- sushi.
- what happened
to the daily cucumber sammy?
It retire along
with the rest of you?
- all that cream cheese
wasn't exactly
Helping my cholesterol.
- [scoffs]
I'm sorry.
this is too fucking weird.
- i can get a sandwich if
it makes you more comfortable.
- no, it's...
This.
Us.
I haven't seen you,
spoken to you,
Or exchanged so much as
a fucking christmas card
With you in two years.
Now all of a sudden
you're in miami
Holding a pair of chopsticks
without so much
As an email saying,
"hey, remember me?
"we used to fuck.
i'm coming to town.
You want to grab lunch?"
I mean, seriously.
what the fuck?
I know.
same old mouth.
- not without its charm.
- really?
That's all you have
to say to me?
- i should have let you know
i was coming to miami.
This task force they're trying
to put together
Is hush-hush.
Plus i knew you'd be busy,
What with making detective
and all.
- yeah, well,
tell me about it.
I have a suspect en route.
- the lisa bell case?
- what do you know
about lisa bell?
- only what your brother's
told me.
- well, "check this,"
she brags.
We found another murder.
30 years old.
Same m.o.,
same address,
Same fucking bathtub.
A guy was convicted.
He's back out in the world.
So how do i not like him
for slicing up lisa bell?
- sounds like he deserves
a good hard look.
- i had patrol pick him up.
Should be here any minute.
- mind if i tag along?
- to the interview?
- i'd like to see detective
morgan in all her glory.
- sounds like someone's bored
with retirement already.
- here you go.
thanks very much.
Keep the change.
Come on, guys.
Come on, boys.
- oh, sorry, sir.
It was an accident.
- it's okay, kiddo.
It happens.
What is that,
strawberry?
- uh, bubble gum gelato.
- how, uh...
repulsive.
[chuckles]
You better catch up
with your mom.
You don't want
to lose her.
- just had to find blood,
didn't you?
- it is my job.
- and you've got
a family to support
And people to dismember.
You're spinning
too many plates, dexter.
- the sooner i wrap this up,
The sooner i get
to the boxing arena.
- you might want
to give some thought
As to what happens
when somebody else
Finds that body.
- [sighs and clears throat]
- manager's on his way
to open the safe.
- what's the date of birth
on his passport?
- 5/5/72.
[keypad tones]
- [sighs]
geez.
- don't sweat it, quinn.
I've got much bigger things
to worry about.
- i filled in the lieutenant
on what we found.
- "we"?
- dude, there's
no "me" in "team."
Well, technically
there is, but--
- blood deposit
on the yucca
On the assailant's
escape route.
He probably scraped himself.
- does that mean
we have his dna?
- i'll run it through
the database
Soon as i get back
to the lab.
- go.
You, come with me.
- i'm going...
Just not where you think.
- you were convicted of killing
your wife back in '79.
Sliced open her
femoral artery.
She bled to death
in your bathtub.
- do i need to talk
to a lawyer?
- at this point,
we're interviewing you
To get more or less
an expert opinion.
- see, your case bears an
uncanny resemblance
To a case we're working
on now.
Same m.o. a la
that femoral artery.
Same house.
- same everything.
- no fucking way.
- yes fucking way.
Sort of puts you at number one,
person-of-interest-wise.
- i didn't kill my wife.
- oh, no?
You're just another
innocent man behind bars
For no good reason.
- the fucking deck
was stacked
Before i walked into
that courtroom
In a death penalty state.
- you copped
to doing the deed.
You took the deal.
- i did my time
and i moved on.
- you moved on to lisa bell.
- who is lisa bell?
- the young lady that you killed
last monday night
In your old house.
Whatever sick fucking poetry
you find in that.
Tell us what you did,
mr. noonan.
- it was muggy
for so late at night.
And vicky, my wife...
Wanted to cool off
in the tub, so...
I went out to score some shit
and i came back.
And i found her.
[weeping]
- i wish i could buy
the tears.
I just...
I can't get there.
- monday night i was working
a swing shift
At the homeless shelter
in allapatah
Hosing piss off
the sidewalk
From the folks waiting
to get inside
Until 8:00-fucking-a.m.
- we'll call
the homeless shelter.
Verify your story.
- one, the guy's
a train wreck.
Two, he's a total slob,
he smells like a sewer,
And his fingernails
are disgusting.
- our killer's meticulous.
Zero dna left
at the crime scene.
- obviously you caught his
case of the shakes.
- given his rehab history,
i'm voting dts.
- and lisa bell was cut
with surgical precision.
- so, detective morgan...
Are we in agreement here?
- violent agreement...
Retired special agent lundy.
- if noonan didn't
kill lisa bell,
Why is the m.o. the same
as his wife's murder?
- copycat?
- of an obscure
30-year-old crime?
- do we think noonan's
telling the truth...
That he didn't kill
his wife?
- i believe we do.
- shit.
- i have a theory i'd like
to run by you.
We could grab dinner,
review the case,
Maybe catch a bad guy.
- i...uh...
Okay, i guess.
Um, i've got
to cut noonan loose
And make sure he talks
to a lawyer.
If our side railroaded him
into that plea bargain,
He could have one fuck mother
of a case.
- you have a good heart,
debra.
Pick you up around 8:00?
- yeah, so i'll--
Yes.
yes.
- the boxing arena's
at the next off ramp,
But i still have miles
to go before i sleep.
Bits and pieces.
Memory fragments.
All i have from last night.
Looks like i got the job done.
Almost.
Blood.
I was off my game.
Sloppy.
With harry's code
ingrained in me,
Cleaning a kill room
should be automatic.
The code.
Etched into my memory
to ensure survival.
What would i do if i couldn't
properly dispose of a body?
I'd hide it.
I investigate crime scenes
all the time.
But this one...
My crime scene...
It's giving me nothing.
Damn it.
Focus.
Track it.
Where did i go from here?
The pharmacy.
Harrison's ear ache medicine.
The only stop i made
before the crash.
The only stop i remember.
- if you thought you
were coming right back,
Not a bad hiding place.
- why are you wearing those?
- this is the way i was dressed
the first time we met.
Your mother's murder
was the last time
Your memory was a blank.
Why do you suppose that is?
- not in front of my baby!
no!
[screaming]
- because not remembering
saved me.
- and now if you want
to save yourself,
You have to remember.
If you don't fix
this screw-up,
Harrison's only memory
of his father
Will be of you behind bars.
- it's not a screw-up.
I just can't remember.
Got to check today's
incident reports.
Make sure benny's body
hasn't surfaced.
It's in this city somewhere.
- thanks for meeting me here.
The sooner we get an estimate
and file a claim,
The sooner my husband
gets his car back.
- well, that much damage,
i wouldn't even try
To talk you into fixing it.
- i thought it was
a fender bender.
- well, i'm sure there's
a bent fender
Somewhere in this mess.
- oh, my god.
- everybody got off easy
on this one.
Your husband, my company.
He should count his blessings.
- yes, he should.
- hey, buddy.
you lose something?
- there's an understatement.
Can't find my i.d.
- use mine to buzz you in.
- all right.
Thanks.
- look, the other day
after court,
I was totally out of line going
off on you like that.
Gomez is the criminal,
not you.
- no, not me.
- plan on having
a heart-to-heart
With the prick
when i find him.
- benny?
- yeah, want him to know
he's still on my radar,
But he's been laying low.
[door buzzes]
- look, can we do this
another time?
My password.
- access denied, dex.
- i can't even remember
my own password.
- i'm here to help.
Think.
- h-a-r-r-y.
Thanks, dad.
Bank hold-up.
Alligator in backyard.
Kidnapped three year old
found safe.
But no body parts turning up.
[sighs]
From boxing arena, to pharmacy,
to the crash.
What am i missing?
- girl scout cookie
time again?
- no, i froze them
in case of emergency.
- what's the emergency?
- frank lundy.
I haven't heard from him
in, like, forever,
And then he shows up out
of the blue
For some hush-hush task force
and wants to know
All about my case.
Not to drag you into my shit.
- drag away.
In this boys' club,
who else you gonna talk to?
- this is about him trying
to get next to me.
- maybe, but you do have
a boyfriend.
- hell yeah, i do.
A good one.
And i'm really fucking happy.
- can i make
a suggestion
Before you eat
the box too?
If there is still
something, anything,
Between you and lundy--
- there's so not.
- closure will set you free.
Does my hair look better
up or down?
- down definitely.
- thanks.
- okay, benny,
i got to find you
Before anyone else does.
Better fucking start
all over again.
Nothing on the dna results
from the blood on the cactus.
No match in the database.
sorry.
- hang on.
no one's going anywhere.
- oh, shit.
- listen up, guys.
Everyone working
the vacation murders,
I'm holding over your shift
until further notice.
Call home, let your people know
they'll see you
When they see you.
- quinn, my office.
I'm gonna ask you
if we have a problem
And i expect the truth.
- look, lieutenant,
what happened at the hotel,
It's not what you think.
- detective...
I'm not gonna tell you
who to date.
It's none of my business.
But you should know
there's no such thing
As off the record
with reporters.
So watch the pillow talk
with that woman.
- not a problem, lieutenant.
Talking isn't
what we do best anyway.
- debra?
I thought i was
picking you up.
- i need to clear
some things up
And i owe you nothing less
than complete transparency.
- want anything?
Tea? water?
- i don't want
to mislead you.
And i certainly don't want
to hurt you.
It's just that
what i have with anton,
It's great.
It's really fucking great
and we live together.
And...
It's great.
And...for the first time
in so long,
I'm actually...
Happy.
No offense.
- you sure you don't
want something to drink?
- did you not hear
a word i just said?
- everything's great.
- exactly.
So if you've come back
here to...
Rekindle something
between us...
It's not gonna happen.
- in the interest
of transparency,
My purpose in coming
to miami is--
- work related.
Cut the shit, frank.
you're retired.
- the reason i'm in miami
Is because i'm convinced that
these bathtub murders--
Noonan's wife, lisa bell--
are connected
To a series of murders
all over the country.
- oh.
- it's become something
of an obsession of mine and...
I'm not about to ride off
into the sunset
And dump something
this horrific
On whoever gets
my office next.
- christ.
I--
[chuckles]
i've got to go.
I'm an idiot.
- debra.
- rita,
what are you doing here?
- you lied to me, dexter.
I saw your car.
it wasn't a fender bender.
It was destroyed.
- i didn't want you to worry.
- yeah, well,
you're not doing a good job.
I'm worried sick about you.
- i'm fine.
All right, a little headache
and a stiff neck.
- get your stuff.
i'm gonna take you home.
- i can't.
The lieutenant is holding
over the shift
Because of these murders
that are in all the papers.
- you fell asleep
at the wheel.
Almost got killed because
of the hours
That they keep you here night
after night after night.
- so much for
my standard alibi.
This is a job
i signed on for.
- i'm sorry.
I didn't sign on
to be a widow.
You know what?
i'll just talk to maria myself.
- rita, no.
don't do this.
Not here.
this is my job.
It's how i support
all of us.
- what if you wind up dead
in a ditch?
- all these people put in
the same hours that i do.
- yes, but you were
in the hospital last night.
They weren't.
- and the doctor gave me
a clean bill of health.
You could talk
to him yourself.
[keypad tones]
- no.
no, i don't--
I don't want to talk
to your doctor.
- i want you to.
- i mean, i guess he wouldn't
have released you
If it was anything serious.
- i'm sure they'd all rather be
home with their families,
Just like me.
- i know.
- come on,
i'll walk you out.
[elevator bell dings]
[sighs]
- you gonna pick that up?
- no, i am not, vince.
You got a problem with that?
- dude, seriously,
86 the caffeine.
You're freaking me out.
- i have someplace
i need to be.
- i also have places
Not good places,
but...places.
- come on, blood.
Talk to me.
If somebody tested positive
for an std,
Would they have to register with
the miami health authorities?
- and why would you
ask me that?
- yes or no, vince?
Lieutenant.
Found your guy.
Name's johnny rose.
- you found a suspect?
- all his info's in there.
- how?
- i reworked the blood sample
looking for other markers
And found a street 14 strain
of drug-resistant syphilis.
I checked that against
the std registry
For anyone being treated
with heavy-duty meds
Over the last week.
Turned up a few prostitutes
and one johnny rose.
Good science says
he's your guy.
- okay, briefing room
in five minutes.
Strategy meeting.
Dexter's turned up a lead
on our shooter.
- hey, dex, hold up.
- i need to be somewhere.
- good work back there.
This rose guy gets syphilis
and fingered for murder?
That's burning it
at both ends, huh?
- yeah, i really got to go.
wife, kids.
- come on, dex.
What do say we grab
a beer this week,
Figure out how to come
at benny gomez next?
- quinn!
I have a life.
you have a life.
Just leave it alone.
all right?
[engine turns]
Benny gomez.
The last place
i'm gonna look
Is the last place
i saw you.
- moment of your time,
lieutenant?
escuchame, maria.
- angel...
People will think
something's up.
- something is.
- angel, if this is
about the mayor,
I had no choice.
- i'm not angry about you taking
me off the case.
It's how you did it.
- angel, por favor.
I don't even know how
to act around you anymore.
- this isn't easy
for me either.
Maybe we need a...
Break.
- yeah, you're right.
It's probably for the best.
So that's that.
- so that's that.
- so?
- so.
Why are we thinking ourselves
out of a good thing?
- what do you think's
going on in there?
- who cares.
[door opens]
- i'm so glad you're home.
- hey, it's not my birthday.
- can't a girlfriend be glad
her boyfriend's home?
- i was gone for two days.
- i fucking love you.
- i love you.
I love you.
- back to square one.
Literally.
[cell phone rings]
Yeah?
- dexter.
frank lundy here.
- the last person the world
i want to hear from.
Glad to hear from you.
- i need to talk to you...
About trinity.
I'm tired
of swimming against
The bureaucratic tide
by myself.
Can we maybe toss
a few ideas around?
You seem to have
the dot-connecting gift.
- more like had.
[sighs]
I'm glad to help,
but tonight's not really, um...
Optimal.
- i get it.
New dad, new family.
Your life has changed
in so many ways.
- [chuckles]
yeah, i see that now.
- trinity is going
to kill again.
Soon.
Another woman.
Older than lisa bell
this time.
Somewhere out there is a woman
who is going to die...
And she'll have
no idea why.
[dog whimpers]
- whoa, whoa!
Watch your step there.
- oh, hey.
How cute are you?
[chuckles]
smell my puppy, don't you?
What's his name?
- this is checkers.
- [chuckles]
- my mother was
a lifelong republican.
- well, no family's perfect.
- indeed.
What kind of pup you have?
- um, just a mutt,
but she's great
With my children.
- so you must live
around here, huh?
- yeah, it's such
a great neighborhood.
Everyone's so friendly.
- well, in the interest
of friendly,
Let me help you with these.
- oh, it's really okay.
i'm just up there.
- so i'll take one,
you take the other.
Lighten the load, huh?
- i appreciate it.
My arms were falling off.
[chuckles]
- my dog won't get your puppy
all riled up?
- molly?
oh, god, no.
She's the calmest little thing
in the world.
- how long have you lived
around here?
- uh, three years next month.
- oh, surprised we've never
run into each other till now.
I'm allen, by the way.
- tarla.
- um, this is me.
Thank you so much
for your help.
- sure.
- great.
Oh, and bye to you too,
checkers.
- until next time.
Off you go, checkers,
or whatever your name is.
- lundy thinks he can
predict the future,
But i'm more interested
in the past.
My past.
I already cleaned this.
That i remember.
Now it makes sense.
Harry was reminding me
the whole time.
I was reminding myself
Hello, benny.
Good-bye, benny.
Got to admit...
pretty clever.
Hiding benny gomez
like that
Until i could come back
and get him.
- you turned to the code.
A core memory.
I taught you well.
Finding gomez
was a band-aid.
You're juggling family,
work...
And a dark passenger
who's always got one hand
On the steering wheel.
- i can do it.
I can manage...
All these moving parts.
- until you can't.
Then what?
- night, dad.
Sleep.
Just one beautiful
night's sleep
Will make everything
better...again.
[snoring]
[harrison crying]
Fuck.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com