Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
Zak failed basic flight.
But he didn't because I passed him.
I can't decode it,
but it means there's someone.
Someone in the military
is still alive and kicking here in Caprica.
I have cancer.
And I fear that knowledge
of my illness will erode hope.
So this has to stay between you and me.
- Zak was my brother.
- What was he to me, nothing?
Same old Lee. You haven't changed either.
Helmet!
- You are so unprepared.
- Shut up!
You're the worst CAG in the history
of CAGs actually.
Raptor pilot
Lt. Dwight Flat-top Sanders...
entering hangar Deck 12 B.
Deck hands, please report.
Repeat, deck hands,
please report to 12 B.
There he is!
Way to go, Lieutenant!
Raptor Pilots flying high!
- Red paint, incoming!
- Brush?
You're the worst. The absolute worst!
Here.
Raptor Pilots flying by!
What the hell is this?
Flat-top's 1,000th landing and
nobody tells me. Now we look like idiots.
Find a wagon!
Yes, sir!
Somebody get me a wagon!
One, zero, zero.
You're not ready yet?
Someone's going to have to pick that up.
- Stop it!
- Let's go, come on.
This one is perfect. Take this.
Here, give me a hand.
Unload this. Put it wherever.
You two, come here.
Take this wagon to the palace.
Did the Commander tell you
what happened on his 1,000th landing?
- I don't remember telling you what I did.
- Whatever.
He's landing on the Atlantia...
and he's been having this ongoing fight
with the LSO...
and so he decides he'll stick it to him good.
This has all been over-exaggerated.
Come on, people, watch them bake
Three Little Cylons in the air
Three Little Cylons in the air.
Watch their metal burn and flare!
So, he skids to a stop on the flight deck...
and the LSO hears over the wire
there's this big, loud, long, obnoxious...
I was young.
It was great. It was really funny.
Two Little Cylons jump in their cave
Come on A-CARS make their grave!
The LSO is freaking out...
your dad doesn't care because
he hates the guy.
He figures he can get away with it
'cause it's his 1,000th landing.
"I can get away with anything today!"
Watch that tin can hit the spot!
Five Little Cylons in the grass
Watch the Raptor light their ass!
Attention!
Fire on the port hangar deck.
Away the fire and rescue team...
Let's go!
Metal fatigue, old equipment.
Worn strap fails, drops a million cubic drone
to the deck.
Kills 13 pilots and lands seven more
in sick bay.
It's hard to hear this,
but we got lucky.
If that had been a missile
instead of a cone drone...
it could've taken out the side of the ship.
Never had a death in my hangar deck.
Accidents. Never a death.
Services for the dead.
Services will commence
at 1100 hours on the forward hangar deck.
Mid-ship's hangar deck remains closed...
for investigation and clean up
until further notice.
Uniforms for the services will be
dress greys.
I wish I knew what to say,
words to make this better.
Can anything make this better?
I don't know.
Attention on deck!
As you were.
May I?
Yes, sir.
Are you Lt. Thrace?
Give me your eyes.
I know this has been a hard day.
There's been plenty of them lately.
I can guarantee you
there'll be more to come.
Remember your self-esteem.
Your self-respect.
And your self-worth.
Hold strong to them,
because people are watching.
You're the guardians of the fleet.
They need to know that they can
count on you.
Even at a time like this.
Are you Lt. Thrace?
I'm Cdr. Adama. Zak's father.
I know, sir. I'm sorry, sir.
I was planning on coming to see you
tomorrow before the funeral.
You don't need to explain anything.
Present arms!
Order arms!
Once again, we are charged
with the solemn duty...
to return the bodies of our own
to the universe...
from which the Lords of Kobol brought
them to us.
The burdens of this life are with us
but a short time.
For Lt. Zak Adama,
son of William and Caroline Adama...
brother of Lee, the time was too short.
But we take comfort in knowing
his life was willingly given...
in service to all of us.
We honour them for that.
And, thus, it falls upon us
to repent our sins...
and with the help of the Lords of Kobol...
make our own lives worthy of that gift.
And now, we commit his body
to the ground from which we were all made.
Secure in the knowledge...
that we will be reunited with them...
in a better world to come.
So say we all.
Present arms!
Pilots we've known.
I have to start training new pilots.
There it is.
I kind of thought this was about that.
I don't know if I'm the right person for this.
- Do you know someone better?
- No.
But there's almost 50,000 people out there.
Trying to tell me there's not one
flight instructor?
There's two. Civilians. Both.
But I need someone
to teach combat tactics.
You know, I don't know
if I'd be of any use to you.
- I wasn't the most patient.
- Let's get down to it.
This is about Zak.
It was not your fault.
You had nothing to do with what happened.
It was an accident.
Lee? Zak failed basic flight.
- What?
- Or at least he should have, but he didn't...
because I passed him.
His technique was sloppy
and he had no feel for flying...
but I passed him.
Because he and I...
Because I felt something and I let it
get in the way of doing my job.
And I couldn't fail him.
Zak passed basic flight.
He was trained
and ready to sit in that cockpit.
What happened to him could've happened
to any qualified pilot.
- You know that's true.
- Right.
You did your job to the best of your ability.
That's all I can ask.
I need new pilots.
And I want you to train them.
I can do that.
Just give them the attention and
the professionalism that you gave my son.
And they'll be one hell of a squadron.
Ten cubits says she takes him this time.
You're on.
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
Ten to stay.
So, Gaeta, how are you and the Doc here
doing on your Cylon detector?
What Cylon detector?
Rumour has it
that Cylons look like people...
and you guys are working on a way
to weed them out, right?
I want you to tell me the truth
about something.
You passed.
By the skin of your teeth, but you passed.
I don't want any special treatment.
Not from my father...
and certainly not from you.
If there were such a programme,
it would be classified...
and I wouldn't be able to talk about it.
Something smells horrible in here.
Is that you, Crashdown?
Yeah, that's me.
Your card.
Zak, I'm a flight instructor.
I'm not going to send you to Vipers
if I don't think you got the chops. Okay?
Hello? Are you all right?
Look...
Maybe you'd like to take a break?
I'm out of here.
Starbuck?
Okay, she can't do that.
She can and she did.
This is it.
Restaurant.
I'm almost on top of the signal.
I don't get it.
How does a military coded signal
end up coming from in here?
Let's find out.
Nothing. Is that thing working?
I checked it three times.
This thing says
we're right on top of it.
Of what?
What?
Helo.
You're frackking kidding me.
Food. Medical supplies.
Wait a minute, the signal.
Disaster beacon.
It's been set to go off if there was an attack.
Some poor slob goes to all the trouble
of building a fallout shelter, stocks it...
has a beacon, the whole planet...
Then what? What happens to him?
Let's just call ourselves lucky
and leave it at that.
- Madame President.
- Would you close that curtain, please?
Thank you.
You are obviously an intelligent,
well-educated young woman.
Would you mind explaining to me why
you waited five years...
in between breast exams?
Yes, I would mind.
It's none of your business.
I was busy.
- And now, here you are.
- Yes. Here we are.
- Would you mind?
- I do, actually.
Your doctor back on Caprica was right.
It's too damn late to operate,
the cancer is too far advanced.
We can try to shrink
the tumour with gamma treatments...
and follow that up with IV cis-Doloxan.
Did he explain to you the side-effects
of Doloxan?
Hair loss, nausea, muscle degeneration.
I watched my mother endure two years
of Doloxan before she died.
I would like to explore alternate treatment.
Prayer?
Witty.
Have you ever heard of Chamalla extract?
Gods. You're one of those.
What if it works?
All the evidence on Chamalla is anecdotal.
It's nothing but a bunch
of loose talk and false hope.
I'll take that as a yes.
All right.
I'll put out a med request
to the civilian fleet.
Maybe there's some other wide-eyed dreamer
out there...
with a secret horde of Chamalla extract
in their luggage.
Put your clothes back on now.
Thank you.
And for what it's worth...
I would seriously consider prayer.
Boonie jumpers. Shuttle jockies.
And a Fleet Academy wash-out. This is
the best that you could come up with?
- Diamonds in the rough.
- Yeah, right.
They're the most qualified pilots
in the fleet.
Great!
Attention on deck.
That means get on your feet, nuggets!
You are joining the Colonial Fleet,
boys and girls, not some after-school club.
Seats.
Pilots call me Starbuck,
but you may refer to me as God.
You've all flown before, but you're about
to enter a whole new world...
so pay attention.
We don't have any flight simulators
on board...
so we're putting you into the cockpit, today.
This is the Viper Mark II.
It's as manoeuvrable as a jack-rabbit,
and can flip end for end...
in 0.35 seconds.
You've never flown anything remotely like it,
so don't think that you have.
Today we'll do basic launch,
approach, and landing manoeuvres...
and anyone not paying attention
is liable to end up...
as a puddle or something to be hosed
out of the cockpit by the chief of the deck.
She's laying it on a little thick.
Costanza, right?
Yes, God, sir.
Not anymore.
From now on, your name is "Hot Dog. "
And when God speaks, Hot Dog, you listen.
Maybe if you had learned that at
the Academy, you wouldn't have washed out.
Sit up!
Viper 791 Galactica,
you are cleared for approach.
Speed 175 port bay,
hands on approach...
checkers green. Call the ball.
I have the ball.
Easy on the throttle, Kat.
Are you listening to me?
Don't chase the lights, okay?
Roger, Starbuck.
Kat, don't chase the lights!
Set it by the numbers
and correct with thrusters.
Wave-off!
Punch it, Kat!
Worse than awful.
Wretched beyond belief, actually.
You call yourselves pilots.
It'll take the knuckle draggers a week to
pound your divots out of the flight deck.
- With due respect, sir, that's unfair.
- Yes, sir. This was only our first day.
No. It's your last.
It would be criminal to let any of you
near a Viper again.
So pack your gear and
get the hell off my ship. You're done.
What are you doing here, Kara?
- You can't wash them out on their first day.
- I just did.
Look, I got 40 Vipers, and 21 pilots.
That's it.
We are sitting ducks
until we finish water-op's.
We can't even maintain a CAP.
And Gods forbid the Cylons show up.
Gods forbid.
Let's bring in the next group of candidates.
The next group has never even been
in a cockpit.
- They're starting basic flight.
- Then they start basic flight.
Because that group is done.
It says so right there.
Maybe you should read it again.
Lt. Thrace, this is not a request.
Well, Capt. Adama!
I am the flight instructor, sir.
My word is scripture, sir.
I will not, repeat, not pass
another student who isn't ready.
So, that's what this is about.
It's not them. It's Zak.
Careful.
Step back.
Starbuck says they can't cut it,
they can't cut it.
She's not giving them a chance. It's Day 1.
She's one of the finest pilots
I've ever seen in my life.
One day in the cockpit is all she needs
to know if they can hack it or not.
She got that.
I'm not arguing that, sir.
I'm just saying that I think she's letting her
personal feelings cloud her judgment.
Please sit down, Captain.
What are those feelings?
About Zak.
- We've talked about, Zak.
- You did?
We've talked about a lot of things.
We've been aboard this ship for over
two years. We know each other very well.
When I asked her to be the instructor...
I knew it was going to release
a lot of loose baggage.
She acknowledged it.
She's a professional. She'll do her job.
Okay.
I'm just saying that you should talk to her.
She's walking around
with a lot of emotion.
She almost decked me in the rec room.
Right. You wouldn't smile if you were there.
- I'll talk to her.
- Thank you.
Personally...
I think she's trying to work out her guilt
over what she did for Zak.
I think she's making up for it
by beating up on these guys.
Guilt? Over what?
What did she do for Zak?
- I thought you just said...
- What did she do?
It's not my place to say and I've already said
more than I should have.
- You'll have to ask her. I'm sorry.
- Captain, just...
Dad, you'll have to ask her.
I don't want any special treatment.
Not from my father,
and certainly not from you.
You passed.
By the skin of your teeth, but you passed.
Attention.
Pass the word to Lt. Thrace.
Lt. Thrace, please report
to the CO's quarters.
Yes. Come in.
Lee was just here before.
I knew it.
He thinks you washed out...
the nuggets without giving them a chance.
They didn't cut it. That's it.
He thought you were letting
personal feelings cloud your judgment.
Really?
Your feelings about Zak.
That's not the case.
Okay.
He said something else.
He said something that
I would like to ask you directly.
He said that you might be feeling
guilty about something that you did for Zak.
What did you do for him?
I don't know. Ask Lee.
I'm asking you.
I don't know...
I don't really know
what he was talking about, so...
Don't fence with me, Kara.
I love you like a daughter.
I don't deserve that.
Zak failed basic flight.
He wasn't a bad pilot.
He just had no feel for flying.
And when it came to his final check-ride,
he busted...
three of the test manoeuvres.
And I should have flunked him, but I didn't.
The bottom line is that your son...
didn't have the chops to fly a Viper.
And it killed him.
He told me that you were
an amazing instructor.
And that he was involved with you,
and that it was serious.
He asked me to come to his graduation
from flight school...
- to watch him get his wings.
- I know. I read the letter.
I see.
Then, maybe you can tell me
what he was hinting at.
Surprise, about you.
We were going to...
You know what, it's not important.
- I don't want that to...
- You were engaged, right?
You did it because you were engaged.
Because I made a mistake.
And because I was just...
I was so in love with him.
And I let that get in the way of doing my job.
He just wanted it so much and I didn't want
to be the one who crushed him.
Reinstate the trainees to flight status.
I will.
- I just want you to understand that I...
- Do your job.
Yes, sir.
And walk out of this cabin
while you still can.
Unpack your gear.
You are all returned to flight status.
We're going to try this again.
Those of you who can be trained to safely fly
the Viper Mark II will pass.
Those of you who cannot, will be cut.
It's my job to figure out which
is which, without personal feeling either way.
And I'm going to do my job.
Kat, Chuckles, Hot Dog, you're up first.
Pre-flight briefing in 20 minutes.
Where the hell
are you going, Hot Dog? Stay on me.
Target acquired and destroyed.
Not bad, Hot Dog,
but you left your leader behind.
Looks like you're having a bad day,
Hot Dog.
- And the moral of this story is?
- Never leave your leader.
Thank you. That is correct.
You never want to be out here alone.
Okay, Chuckles, take Kat's wing.
Hot Dog, you're on me.
We'll try a little manoeuvre called
"Thorch Weave. "
I'll be damned. What's got into Starbuck?
She actually sounds like
a real instructor for a change.
She may actually make Viper pilots
out of some of those nuggets after all.
Holy crap, we've got incoming.
Where the hell did they come from?
Dradis. Multiple contacts.
It's the Cylons.
Why didn't we see them coming?
Launch the alert fighters.
Attention! Set Condition 1
throughout the fleet.
Galactica, send the Calvary.
Nuggets, punch it for home.
Where's the base ship?
No base ships detected, sir.
Eight raiders, bearing 047
carom 118. Range 22,000.
They found us. It was only a matter of time.
Galactica, Starbuck.
Where the hell are the alert fighters?
Starbuck, Alert One.
Be there in two minutes.
The Cylons are gaining!
All right, listen up, nuggets.
Stay together and keep your throttles
firewalled until you hit the deck.
Now, go.
What's she doing?
Starbuck's gonna take on all eight.
And get herself killed.
Hot Dog, where are you going?
Hot Dog, what are you doing?
Got one!
Hot Dog! Get out of here!
Hot Dog, I told you
to get your ass home!
You said never
to leave your leader.
I also said
never to disobey an order.
- I'm hit!
- I got you, Hot Dog!
We're going to make it through this.
Break right. Now!
She'll make it.
I just lost all three mains.
It's all right, Hot Dog. You did good.
We're gonna be okay, I promise you.
At least one of us will.
That about does it.
I think there's only one left.
Frack!
He's right on my tail,
but I got it covered.
Starbuck's wireless and transponder
just cut out.
Alert One, we spotted Hot Dog.
No ID or visual on Starbuck.
Frack me!