Previously on
Battlestar Galactica...
I notice you're calling her Sharon now.
She acts like them, thinks like them.
She's one of them.
But she's one of us.
We gotta go, now.
We gotta travel fast. Even faster than before.
They found him
in the storage compartment.
He's another copy of the Cylon
you know as Leoben.
I'll send a team over to destroy it.
Anything it says cannot be trusted.
- Don't!
- Adama is a Cylon.
Commander? Here's Dr. Baltar's report.
And the President is waiting for you
up in the core.
Thank you.
Clear the deck.
Madame President,
we are the proud owners...
of the universe's first,
bona-fide Cylon detector.
That is great news.
Yeah.
So, when do we begin?
Dr. Baltar would like to start
widespread testing as soon as possible...
but there are some serious limitations.
He can only do one person at a time,
and verification takes hours.
So who's going to go first?
The tests. Right.
I think people in sensitive positions
should go first.
I completely agree. How about you?
Excuse me?
If you're a Cylon, I'd like to know.
If I'm a Cylon, you're really screwed.
Seriously, I do think that you should go first.
Show everyone in the fleet
that they can trust the people at the top.
Then maybe you should go first.
All right, I'll go first.
I think that's good. I do.
Bank on my advice.
- They always do that?
- No, they're just showing off.
They know I'm in here.
You date a special assistant
to the President, word gets out.
So this is officially a date?
Jury's still out.
Observation deck
has two minutes remaining.
You could pull rank.
You could tell them you're on special
business for the President of the Colonies.
Your boss pulls more weight around here
than mine.
- You can tell them Adama wants you to...
- Yeah, what? Wants me to what?
I lost my train of thought.
How is he these days, by the way?
- The old man? He's fine, I guess.
- You guess?
He's been acting kind of funny lately.
Seems distracted or something.
He's been making all these weird calls
from his quarters. Super secret.
- Probably a security thing.
- They don't want me to log the calls, though.
No trace file. Nothing.
- And this just started?
- A few days ago.
Billy Keikeya, are you pumping me
for information about the old man?
Time's up.
- No. Of course not.
- You are.
- You are. You're a spy, that's what you are.
- I was just asking a couple of questions.
I hope you liked the answers.
Because they're the last ones
you're gonna get for a while.
What did you find out?
Dualla couldn't put her finger on it...
but, yeah, she said
he's been acting differently.
I could see that myself. He was distracted
and unfocused. What else?
Some scrambled wireless calls
he didn't want logged.
She didn't know who he called or why.
But none of this is damning evidence.
The calls could be security-related...
and his odd behaviour could be stress,
pure and simple.
- Exhaustion, paranoia...
- All right. It could be any of those things.
But what if it's not?
Madame President, with all due respect...
I cannot believe we're actually
entertaining the idea...
that Commander Adama...
has been somehow replaced
by a Cylon duplicate.
Oh, my gods, Billy...
I hope you're right.
Is suicide really a sin?
A mortal one, I'm afraid.
But it's not that bad, is it, Gaius?
47,905 people in the fleet.
47,905 blood samples.
Eleven hours to test each one
for Cylon indicators.
That'll take awhile.
21,956 days.
60.1534 years.
Now, let's figure in a few hours
to sleep here and there.
We'll call it an even 61, shall we?
Sure.
I prefer to kill myself.
Commander Adama, are you a Cylon?
Tune in tomorrow.
It's hard being a genius.
Yes.
There should be some perks.
What's up, Doc?
Lt. Thrace, good to see you. I was just...
keeping up with the old exercises.
That should do me for today.
I feel all better.
What brings you to the lab
at this time of the night?
It's mid-afternoon.
Yeah, it is.
Crazy workload. I totally lose track of time.
So, what can I do for you?
You can zip up your fly.
- So...
- My blood test.
You're right about one thing, Gaius.
There is something very intriguing about her.
Very good. Very good.
At least I did that much.
Dradis, contact!
- Cylon Raider bearing 738 carom 005.
- Galactica, Apollo.
- Action stations.
- Cylon Raider bearing 738 carom 005.
- Relative zero.
- Close with enemy, destroy. Acknowledge.
We're on it, Galactica.
He jumped right in front of us. His mistake.
- How many?
- Single Raider. Looks like a recon patrol.
Apollo and Beehive have them in their sight.
Where's the old man?
He's not aboard.
- Not aboard? Where the hell is he?
- He left in a Raptor about an hour ago.
No flight plan.
No flight plan?
That's it.
You set him up, I'll knock him down.
I winged him.
Looks like I got his weapon systems.
He jumped.
He jumped away before
we could zero him out.
Damn it. Probably giving away our position
to every Cylon base ship right now.
Where in the hell is the old man?
Order the fleet
to execute emergency jump procedures.
Everyone rendezvous
at the stand-by coordinates.
Contact!
Single Raider bearing 881 carom 247.
Apollo, Galactica,
Cylon Raider detected at 881 carom 24...
Wait, I see him! Same Raider.
What?
It's the same Raider.
I can see the damage from before.
It's behaving erratically.
He jumped away again.
Contact. Single Raider, same telltales.
- It's like he's just flying around in circles.
- Wounded bird. Can't fly home.
Galactica. We got him
on Dradis, but he's pretty far out there.
Take us three minutes
to close to weapons range.
No. This is our perfect chance
to get some intel.
Order Apollo to close with the Raider,
but do not engage.
Put a Raptor in the air.
As long as that's flopping around out there...
tell them I want to suck in
every electronic signal it makes.
Sir. Colonel, Commander Adama's Raptor
is requesting permission...
to enter the landing pattern.
Permission granted.
Stand down to Condition Two.
Mr. Gaeta, you have the deck.
Permission to come aboard?
Granted.
Mind telling me
where the hell you've been?
Col. Tigh, allow me to present your wife.
Ellen?
That noise. I don't get it.
I've blown Centurions away before.
They've never sent an entire army after me.
They're after me.
Why you?
While they were holding me,
I overheard some things.
What?
Plans. Deployments.
There's a big Cylon base at Delphi.
A major hub.
Delphi? Frakking bastards.
The best place to try and grab
a ship and get off this frakking planet.
Dr. Gaius Baltar,
Department of Cylon Detection...
how may I direct your call?
You're in a good mood.
Madame President...
I'm sorry. I was expecting someone else.
We haven't spoken in ages.
Doctor, I'd like you to call me the moment
Commander Adama's test is complete.
Will you do that?
Commander Adama cancelled his test
a short time ago.
- Why?
- I don't know.
He gave me another sample.
He said it had priority.
- Whose?
- I'll just check.
Some woman called Ellen.
No surname. He dropped it off and left.
Is there a problem?
Dr. Baltar, I would like
you to resume testing...
Commander Adama's blood sample
immediately. Thank you.
- I can't believe you're alive.
- I can't believe it myself.
Saul, I don't remember the last few weeks.
It's weeks, right?
Right.
You've been on the Rising Star all this time?
I guess so.
The last thing I remember is being on Picon.
I was at the airport buying a ticket home...
and hearing something about the Cylons.
And then just dreams, mostly dreams...
until a couple days ago.
They tell me I was knocked out
when the Cylons attacked the airport.
And someone just picked me up...
and put me on the last flight out.
Some saviour. I don't even know who.
It's all right. You're here now.
It's like we found
a treasure chest.
One of the major issues we've been having...
with the Raider we captured
is to figure the faster-than-light drive.
This wounded bird is jumping
all over the place out there.
Yeah. And every time it jumps,
it gives us more data that we can use.
But what was it doing out there,
and how long can it keep it up?
The moment you have your FTL data,
give me an update.
Let's not let this thing linger out there
longer than we have to.
Yes, sir.
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- Stay on it.
You have dinner plans?
- What?
- Come on.
I never thought I'd see you again.
Me neither.
The things I said before, the things I did...
In the past? It's all in the past.
- Start over?
- Start over.
- I... I can't.
- Forget it...
I can't. I'm on duty.
XO. Now?
Understood. All right. Tell her I'm on my way.
Girlfriend?
- Official business.
- Feels like old times.
- I'd explain, but...
- It's classified.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I'll be here, waiting.
As soon as I can.
You want to be very, very careful
with what you just said.
You're talking about a man I owe my life to,
many times over.
I know these are uncertain times...
and this has been
a difficult transition for you.
Excuse me, Colonel.
I do appreciate how difficult this is
for you to hear, believe me.
But I would advise you right now
not to say anything that you will regret.
I need to know if you have seen
anything suspicious...
- about his recent behaviour?
- No.
What about the fact
that he left the Galactica...
without telling anyone where he was going
or when he would return...
and at that very moment,
a Cylon Raider jumped into view...
- and started acting strangely?
- I know exactly where he was.
You do?
He was picking up my wife.
Your wife?
Turns out she's been unconscious
aboard the Rising Star ever since the attack.
Oh, my gods!
That's fantastic. That's amazing.
Yes, it is.
When Ellen stepped off that shuttle,
I thought I was going to pass out.
Ellen?
- Your wife's name is Ellen?
- Yes, it is.
Ellen. Ellen Tigh.
I'd very much like to meet your wife, Colonel.
Resume the test on Ellen?
No, it's no trouble at all.
Ellen?
- Did you shut the door?
- I already did.
- Surprise.
- Ambrosia? Where did you get this?
I have my ways.
I thought it might be just the thing
for a little celebration.
- We need to talk.
- First things first.
There.
- Starting over.
- I'm technically still on duty.
- I think they can do without you for a day.
It doesn't really work that way.
Starting over.
Sure, there's whining and complaining
like you would expect...
but the people I talked to
are mostly hopeful and optimistic.
That's good to hear.
There are a few people
who still might wonder...
if a kindergarten teacher
is really the right person to be President...
but they're just a tiny minority.
Wonderful.
Everyone is so truly grateful
to all of you on Galactica.
- You literally are our saviours.
- We're just doing our jobs.
You are so modest.
He's always been that way.
Lee, could I trouble you
for a little more of this lovely Ambrosia?
- Sure.
- Thank you, dear.
Bill, you must be so proud of your sons.
Lee here has grown
into such a handsome man.
I can only imagine
what Zak must look like now.
You are the spitting image of your mother...
and I bet Zak takes just after his daddy.
Zak passed away
a couple of years ago.
I'm sorry. How tragic, the death of a child.
There's been so much death, so much pain.
Sometimes it's completely overwhelming.
I'm sure he was a beautiful boy.
The Captain of the Rising Star
was puzzled as to how you got on his ship.
I know. I know some thoughtful soul
just rescued me...
from almost certain death,
and put me on the last flight out of Picon.
- How lucky for us all.
- Yes, indeed.
The strange thing is no one can recall...
giving you any medical assistance
until about a week ago.
I know.
It's a miracle I'm alive.
I think I better clear
some of these dishes.
- You are so sweet.
- Very good. My compliments to the chef.
So, Bill, now the question
on everyone's mind...
and I do mean everyone...
Sorry.
It's okay.
...is where is Earth
and when do we get there?
- That's classified information.
- That word again.
Leave the man alone.
Come on, if there are no privileges
of being an XO's wife...
then what's the point?
Bill, we're all family here. Come on.
The need for secrecy is paramount, Ellen.
I'm sorry. Perhaps you don't know
that the Cylons look like us now.
That, yes, I knew that.
It's recent news.
Most people found out a few days ago.
A thing like that would travel fast. Right?
Any one of us could be a Cylon.
Boo!
Did you see the looks on their faces?
- You are too easy.
- Thank you so much for coming.
It's been a wonderful evening.
Thought it would never end.
I seemed to have lost one of my shoes.
- I think it's right here.
- Thank you.
Here we are.
- You look very, very happy.
- That's because I am very happy.
Thank you.
- It was nice to see you again.
- The pleasure's all mine.
- Hope to see you soon.
- I'm sure you will.
Hang on.
Watch your step.
- Good night.
- Lovely dinner.
I've got her.
Be careful.
You actually think that woman is a Cylon?
If she's not, then we're all in a lot of trouble.
When did Bill become
such a stick-in-the-mud?
The man's a carving.
He's one of those faces on a totem pole.
She slept with more than half the fleet,
while Saul was in space.
Why the hell did he stay married to her?
- It's obvious. He loves her deeply.
- Blindly.
Ellen used to encourage
the worst instincts in this guy...
- bring out this self-destructive streak in him.
- Used to?
Sharon, stop! I can't keep up.
Helo, come on.
You can do it. Please.
You have to get up.
There. Right there.
Turn your light off.
We gotta find another way out of here.
We're going.
Why aren't you waiting?
You keep going and going.
- You never get tired.
- It's adrenaline.
I'm not gonna die here.
And I'm not gonna let you die here either.
Okay, let's go!
Don't worry, I'll get us home.
Yeah, right.
- Just like Bill's getting us to Earth.
- Don't start on Bill.
He doesn't have the slightest idea
where Earth is.
You don't have to yell it through the halls.
Bill Adama doesn't know where Earth is!
- Colonel.
- Doctor.
Actually, I don't believe
I've had the pleasure.
- I'm Dr. Gaius...
- Baltar. I know exactly who you are.
And the pleasure's all mine.
Something here, isn't there?
You're still holding my hand.
That's funny.
I thought you were still holding onto mine.
I'm watching you. Both of you.
And you should be watching her.
Care to join us for a nightcap, Doctor?
I'd love to.
Dr. Baltar,
report to the lab. The Commander is waiting.
- But I can't. Another time, perhaps.
- Count on it.
Ta-ta!
- Oh, Saulie, are you jealous?
- You said we were starting over.
We are, sweetheart, we are.
That was just a little harmless flirting.
You should know something.
What?
In the middle of dinner...
- Bill put his hand on my leg.
- Ellen, I'm not falling for this.
Did you know he came to see me
on the Rising Star?
What?
He'd come into my room.
I'd pretend to be asleep.
Then he'd sit by the side of my bed...
- and then he'd touch me.
- Why are you doing this? You're lying.
I am not. He was on that ship.
I'll prove it.
Come on!
Look, it's not magic. It's science.
If you want the right result,
you have to wait awhile.
I gave you her sample this morning.
I have started and stopped
the test twice already now...
so I'm running a little behind.
- Twice?
- My fault. Long story.
Your fault?
- I shouldn't have mentioned that.
- You shouldn't have.
- Did you tell him to stop Ellen's test?
- Yes, I did.
- Why?
- I had some concerns.
About what?
In all honesty, I think it's fair to say
that your behaviour recently has been odd.
My behaviour? What do you think,
I'm a Cylon? Me?
You can't deny
that you've been making these...
off-log calls, these mysterious trips
off the ship.
Where did you hear that?
Have you been spying on me?
On my own ship?
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
We're in a laboratory.
There are hazardous
chemical compounds everywhere.
That's a thermo-nuclear bomb,
for frak's sakes.
What do you mean "un-logged"?
"Mysterious trips"? What's going on?
I had to go to the Rising Star
and I didn't want Tigh to know.
Why not?
Because whether or not his wife is a Cylon,
she's trouble...
and I wanted to keep her away
as long as I could.
Then why did you bring her aboard the ship?
Because she's his wife.
And I couldn't refuse her access...
to her own husband
without causing suspicion.
Besides, I wanted her close to me.
I told you. I told you he wanted me.
- Lovely.
- What the hell's going on?
You have been secretly visiting my wife?
No. Yes. But it's complicated.
- I told you. He's been after me for years.
- What?
Now boys, boys, don't fight
over little old me.
- Ellen, be quiet!
- You don't tell me what to do.
We should all take a deep breath.
I will!
I was afraid that she might be a Cylon!
I brought her blood here to test it.
That's why you cancelled your test.
How'd you know that?
You didn't tell me
he was testing my wife.
- You met with the President?
- Yes. She thought you might be a Cylon.
I know.
Attention. Pass the word
for the Commander, XO and the CAG.
Commander Adama, Col. Tigh,
and Captain Adama, please report to CIC.
Mr. Gaeta.
The Raider smoothed out
its flight path about two minutes ago.
It seems to be under control.
- Yeah, but he's not jumping for home.
- No, sir, he isn't.
Has our reconnaissance detected
any outgoing communications...
since he straightened out his flight pattern?
Yes, sir, but it's likely
it's just another distress signal.
Launch the alert fighters.
This is the CAG. Launch the alert fighters.
Sir, I hate to tell you this, but I think
it's been playing with us the entire time.
It was waiting to see how we'd react.
- Playing with us?
- Yeah.
- Order the flight leader to destroy the target!
- Yes, sir.
Galactica, Hot Dog. The Raider just took off!
He doesn't look injured to me.
He's heading back to the fleet!
- They're not going to catch him.
- Action Stations, set Condition One.
- This is not a drill.
- He doesn't have any weapons.
He's on a suicide run.
- Did you launch the alert fighters?
- It was the XO's call.
- I had a hunch.
- Good call.
- One question.
- Because I was worried.
- That she might be a Cylon.
- And if she wasn't.
I know how you feel about her, Saul.
She's been a negative force in your life.
I'm sorry, but it's the truth.
Maybe she was.
Everything was different then.
She was different. I was different.
I've grown accustomed to seeing you
without the cup in your hand.
So I had a couple of drinks tonight.
- I was celebrating. I think I deserved to...
- Yes, you did.
Launching those fighters on a hunch.
You saved our ship.
Just doing my job.
You do your job good.
That's why I need you, Saul.
That, and that we're friends.
I don't want anything to come between that,
not even Ellen.
It won't.
We've searched every street,
every building.
They slipped through. How's that possible?
She thinks she loves him.
Now that she can't live without him.
Her passion is making her more resourceful.
- Bothers you, doesn't it?
- We'll get them in the end.
No, it bothers you
that you've never experienced it.
You saw the way Helo was
when we took her away?
He was pathetic.
I can't help wondering what it would be like
to feel that intensely.
Even in his anguish, he seemed so alive.
Green. Green, everyone.
Mrs. Tigh is definitely human.
- No hard feelings, I hope, Ellen.
- I completely understand.
But let's be sure and test you next.
- Doctor?
- My pleasure. My job.
You don't want to frak with me, Bill.
Try to remember that.
Don't frak with me either, Ellen.
If only they knew
that everyone passes these days.
Why, it's so much simpler that way.
No muss, no fuss.
What did her test really say?
I'll never tell.