Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
Just do it.
Boomer, this could be it.
This is the little planet
that solves all of our problems.
What did you see?
A dome-like structure with six roads
leading out of it.
This planet is Kobol.
Organise a ground survey team.
Three Raptors.
- They're everywhere!
- We're not getting out of here!
We need a way to take out the base ship
before we can attempt a rescue.
If you go back to Caprica
and bring me the arrow...
I will show us the way.
What are you doing, Starbuck?
Galactica. Apollo. She just jumped away.
- Where the hell did she go?
- Home.
This is it! Now, come on!
Now come on! Everybody up!
Come on! Go!
Come on, move! Out!
Come on, get him out of the chair.
Look at me.
I got him!
For gods' sakes, hurry!
Come on!
I got his legs.
I got him!
Put him on your shoulder.
Doc! Come on, Doc!
Crash!
Doc!
Take my hand.
Gaius, take my hand.
Hey, come on!
Wake up! Stay with me! We gotta go!
Stay with me, Doc! Come on!
Come on! Bring him outside!
It's gonna blow!
Get down!
Stay down.
How's he? You okay?
We got full tanks. Let's see what we get.
Getting them down.
You all right? You okay?
Get the supplies
before they burn. Go.
Right away.
We crashed both tanks.
The gas is gone. It's all gone.
It's a museum. So what?
It's more than that.
It's the home of the arrow of Apollo.
What the hell is that?
You never liked history.
Come on, Helo. It's supposed to be
the only clue as to the location of Earth.
Earth? What are you talking about?
Who's going to Earth? It doesn't even exist.
I'm trying to get back to Galactica.
What I need from you is a way off this planet,
and a way back to my ship.
If you don't do that, I'll blow your head off.
Why don't you just shut up for a change?
You're only alive because I've kept you alive.
If it wasn't for me, you'd be dead by now.
So whether you like it or not,
I'm your only hope of getting off this planet.
So if I were you, I'd take that tough guy
attitude of yours and shove it up your ass.
We can't move around the city
during daylight.
So we hole up and we wait till dark.
Unbelievable.
She's crossed the line before,
but this is so far beyond the pale...
She wouldn't have done this on her own.
She was coerced.
No one coerces Starbuck.
Believe me, I've tried.
Commander, I have the President on the line.
Bear witness. Put on your headset.
Madam President, moments ago,
Lt. Thrace took the Cylon Raider...
- on an unscheduled and unauthorised jump.
- Yes.
Do you have any knowledge of this incident?
Let's save some time here, Commander.
The question you really want to ask me...
is whether or not I asked Lt. Thrace
to take the Raider to Caprica.
The answer to your question is yes.
- You and I had talked about this.
- Yes, we had.
We both decided
it was a military decision.
My responsibility as President
is first and foremost...
to protect and preserve
this fleet and its future.
In the end, that outweighs
any other consideration. It has to.
By taking the Raider...
you've placed our people
on the surface of Kobol in direct danger.
I'm very aware of the danger
our men and women are in on Kobol.
I am also deeply aware of the danger
this civilisation will be in...
if I ignore the pursuit of this arrow.
I'm going to have to ask you
for your resignation, Madam President.
No.
Then I'm terminating your presidency
as of this moment.
Commander Adama,
I will exercise the authority of this office...
until I am unable to do so.
So if you want to stage a coup...
you're gonna have to come over here
and arrest me.
- I don't want any bloodshed.
- Of course you don't. Neither do I.
Neither does the press.
They're here, by the way.
The press.
They're recording every minute.
- What is it, Captain?
- Isolate Colonial One.
Mr. Gaeta.
Jam any transmissions
in or out of Colonial One immediately.
- Yes, sir.
- Prepare a strike team.
As long as she's President, she's dangerous.
If she can turn Starbuck against us,
she's capable of anything.
Yes, sir.
- She's bluffing.
- Well, let's hope so.
There's also a Cylon base ship out there
to deal with.
Leave that to me.
This government survived a Cylon attack.
It will survive William Adama.
I think he's bluffing.
But just in case, we need to be prepared.
I know their security detail.
They will defend that ship.
We'll have to take her down
compartment by compartment.
Mr. Gaeta?
Sir.
Am I correct in assuming
that I have two Cylon transponders left?
Yes, sir. But only one of them
is fully functional.
One will do.
Now I need a pilot.
Sir.
As you were.
- How are you feeling?
- It looks worse than it is, sir.
Things are moving very quickly
and I need every pilot.
I'm ready, sir.
I have a very special mission for you
and I won't kid around.
- It's high risk, extremely high risk.
- I understand.
I need you to light-jump to Kobol
and take care of this base star.
We're placing a Cylon transponder
aboard your Raptor.
In theory, it should allow you to approach
the base star without getting fired upon.
But we'll still be ID'd as Colonial Raptors
once we're in visual range.
For all they know,
you could be two Cylon agents...
returning with a captured Raptor.
Once you're inside
the defence perimeter...
I need you to make them think
you want to dock.
You have to fire your nuke
into the loading bay...
and then jump back home immediately.
Do you understand?
I understand.
I can do it, sir. I know I can.
You have to.
Yes, sir.
This doesn't look good.
Please tell me this was not all for nothing.
I'm good.
I am really good.
I'm home.
Wow, I'm home.
Gaeta, please tell me that you're right
about this transponder thing.
Stop. Stop that.
I'm nervous.
Like anything scares you.
Things scare me, Helo. I have feelings.
You have software.
I don't know
if you can hear this or not, Helo...
but what we had between us was important.
It was very important.
- Why?
- Because it was the next step.
Because it brings us closer to God.
Don't mock the gods. It's a human belief.
I'm human. They're our gods.
But beyond that, I just want you to know
that I genuinely feel something for you.
I don't care.
I don't love you.
I loved what I thought was you.
Helo, I think there's something
else that you should know.
I'm pregnant.
Galactica, Apollo.
We have visual on Colonial One.
Tell Apollo he's cleared
to begin the assault...
to contact us when he has soft-seal
on the hull.
Aye, sir.
Commander, Boomer and Racetrack
are in the air, ready for their jump to Kobol.
Put them through down here.
Boomer, Galactica Actual.
I just wanted to say good luck,
good hunting...
and I have complete faith in the both of you.
Thank you, Actual. We won't let you down.
Racetrack, start the jump clock.
Clock is running.
Galactica. Apollo.
We have soft-seal.
I know Commander Adama
and I'm counting on the fact...
that when push comes to shove,
he is the kind of man...
who will not want bloodshed.
Nevertheless, this may not be
the safest place.
Billy, how many civilians
are in the cargo hold?
176.
There is room in the cargo hold
and I implore you to find refuge there...
with the other civilians. This is my choice.
This is my choice.
- You do not have to come with me.
- We stand with our president.
Yes?
Right.
Security commander reports sounds
of someone cutting through the hull.
The Raptors are cutting through the hull, sir.
Get the President on the line.
You think this thing is working?
We're about to find out.
- I guess so.
- Yeah.
- How are we doing on that?
- It's not responding, sir.
Are you even trained to use this thing?
How's he doing, Chief?
Not doing so good. I don't now
if his lungs are burned or what.
Well, he's a tough kid.
He's gonna pull through.
Get those wounds looked at, Chief.
Yeah. Lieutenant?
Shouldn't we be moving out?
- Do you have a plan for tactical deployment?
- Plan for tactical deployment, Chief?
Get to the high ground. It'll be our best
chance of being seen by a search party.
High ground is also our best chance
of being seen by the Cylons.
They're flying around, sir.
They might land the troops...
before we get rescued.
That's true.
Yeah.
Sir, if I may...
suggest that we take cover on the ground...
maybe somewhere
we won't be seen from the air?
Okay, yeah. Chief, that's...
Carry on, Chief.
Launch the nuke and prepare to jump.
Frack.
What?
The bomb release is jammed. I can't free it.
We can dock inside the ship.
- Excuse me?
- They think we're Cylons. They'll let us dock.
We can release the bomb manually
and drop the nuke inside the ship itself.
- It'll work. I know it.
- Oh, my gods.
Petard, Felix?
Wanna give me a hand here, please?
Yes, sir.
Cally, how's he doing?
Not good, sir.
Get a blanket on him.
Keep him warm.
How are you?
Alive.
You saved me.
You saved my life.
- Care to return the favour?
- Are you in need of saving?
You wondered why you were chosen?
Why God chose you above all other humans
to survive and serve His purpose?
Now is the time to find out why.
Lords of Kobol, hear our prayer.
Bring us out of the darkness
and into the light.
Give us the strength to show mercy
to those who are merciless...
The President says she will not yield.
...hearts that they may find peace...
So be it.
Come on, D,
tell me he's not actually gonna do this.
Tell me she's not gonna
make him do it.
Redeem our hearts that they may find peace
in the midst of war.
What's going on?
They're in.
Quickly.
Billy?
Sir, they're in.
Pretty, isn't it?
Hello, Lieutenant.
Something I can help you with?
I'm setting her down.
Open the hatch.
I'll release the bomb.
Keep the engines ready for takeoff
the second I get back.
- Yes, sir.
- Close the hatch after me.
- If I'm not back in five minutes, just go.
- You got it.
Oh, my God.
Welcome back to Caprica, Lieutenant.
Like what we've done with the place?
Sharon.
What the frack are you doing?
Where are you going?
Son of a bitch.
Okay, okay.
Sharon.
This isn't happening.
Come on, Starbuck.
Got anything left?
Starbuck?
Madam President,
no one needs to get hurt here.
Then why don't you get off my ship,
Colonel?
I'm placing you under arrest.
- No. We're not doing this.
- I'm in command here, Captain.
- Colonel, this is wrong.
- You're relieved. Fall back.
Madam President, I wish to...
Men, lay down your weapons.
Have you lost your fracking mind?
Colonel, tell these Marines to fall back.
This is mutiny. You know that.
Yes, I do.
But you can tell my father
I'm listening to my instincts.
And my instincts tell me
we cannot sacrifice our democracy...
just because the President
makes a bad decision.
Put your guns down.
- Madam President, stand back.
- Put your gun down, Captain.
I will not have bloodshed,
neither your men nor my people...
on the Colonial One.
Put your gun down. All of you.
Please, put your gun down.
Let's go.
Let's go, Captain.
You're confused. And scared.
But it's okay.
I'm not a Cylon.
I'm Sharon Valerii. I was born on Troy.
My parents were
Katherine and Abraham Valerii.
You can't fight destiny, Sharon.
It catches up with you.
No matter what you do.
Don't worry about us.
We'll see you again.
- We love you, Sharon.
- And we always will.
Boomer!
Come on, let's go!
What took you so long?
Go!
Where's your helmet?
Go back. Don't turn around.
He put his weapon right to my head.
Said to tell you
he was following his instincts...
whatever the hell that means.
Bring him here.
What about Roslin?
We put her in the brig.
Dradis contacts!
It's Boomer and Racetrack, sir.
Put them on the speakers.
Galactica,
Boomer. Mission accomplished.
Repeat: Mission accomplished.
The base star is history!
There's some good news.
Bring them home, D.
It's good to hear your voice, Boomer.
Come on home.
It's okay.
I can't believe it.
You are like the last person
I expected to see.
I could say the same thing about you.
- You okay?
- Yeah, thank you.
I missed you.
Hey, I...
She's a Cylon!
No!
You can't! She's pregnant.
- I know this place.
- Of course you do.
Go inside.
I don't understand.
Life has a melody, Gaius.
A rhythm of notes
that become your existence...
once they're played in harmony
with God's plan.
It's time to do your part
and realise your destiny.
Which is what, exactly?
You are the guardian and protector
of the new generation of God's children.
The first member of our family
will be with us soon, Gaius.
It's time to make your choice.
But I don't understand
what you're talking about.
I don't understand.
Come. See the face
of the shape of things to come.
Isn't she beautiful, Gaius?
Open the cell.
Close the cell.
Well done, Lieutenant.
Thanks.
Hey, nice work.
Thanks. What's going on?
A lot happened
while you were gone.
Congrats.
Thanks.
Congratulations to both of you.
You carried out a very difficult
and dangerous mission...
and you did it...
despite any personal misgivings
you may or may not have had.
And for that, I'm very proud.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
Someone get a doctor!
Hold his head.