Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
Zak failed basic flight.
And I should have flunked him, but I didn't.
The bottom line is that I killed him.
Walk out of this cabin
while you still can.
I don't get it.
How does a military coded signal
end up coming from in here?
Food.
It's the Cylons.
Starbuck's wireless and transponder
just cut out.
Starbuck's gonna take on all eight.
And get herself killed.
Galactica. Hot Dog's aboard.
Yeah, so is his lunch.
Take it easy, Hot Dog.
You're not the first to lose it in combat.
You won't be the last.
No sign of Starbuck.
He says she was hit but still in the fight
when he lost track of her.
Roger that. Search and rescue ops
are underway for Starbuck.
Bring Hot Dog in.
The old man wants to talk to him.
This is where you found him?
Yes, sir,
he drifted quite a ways from the fight.
Was she manoeuvring?
I think so. Yes. Yes, sir.
So she survived the initial hits.
She could still be alive.
She is alive, Lieutenant.
We're gonna find her.
Yes, sir.
Get this man to sick bay.
I think you earned those today.
The auxiliary RT switch sticks a little, sir,
but she'll fly.
- Polish up the canopy. I want it crystal clear.
- Yes, sir.
- Find her.
- I will.
Still no joy from the search teams.
In the last four hours
we've combed everywhere...
in a 200 click sphere
around Starbuck's last known position.
No ship, no ejection seat, no debris.
So we're extending the radius another 50.
- We need more pilots.
- Everybody who can fly is up, sir.
What about Starbuck's course computations?
The variables of combat manoeuvring
make them almost meaningless.
- It's time to start guessing.
- Yes, sir.
Since there's been no dradis contact
in the area...
I would have to guess that her Viper was
captured by the gravity of a planetary body.
The only nearby gravity wells
are the gas giant and this moon.
If the gas giant pulled her in,
its radiation would fry her like an egg.
What about the moon?
The spectroscope people call the atmosphere
as CO2, methane, some argon.
The clouds are mostly hydrocarbons.
Cold as hell down there,
but she'd survive on the surface.
- Until her oxygen runs out.
- When?
Forty-six hours and change, sir.
Hell of a long time to stay in one place.
- What if the Cylons appear?
- They won't, not for a while.
What makes you say that?
Sending a patrol instead of the base ship
tells me they didn't even know we were here.
So they're searching a lot of other places,
places with potential supplies.
Like staking out water holes in the desert.
If we sent eight fighters
to search an entire star system...
for 60-odd ships, it would take us weeks...
Assume they're better and faster.
It'll take them days.
- A lot of assumptions you're making.
- Educated guess.
- Talk to me about searching the moon.
- That's going to be slow going.
We can't see squat through those clouds.
Send the ships below the cloud cover.
Tell the pilots to take a hard look
the old-fashioned way.
Mark One Eyeball, sir?
Mark One Eyeball.
Commander, call from Colonial One.
Adama.
Commander Adama, I don't wanna take
much of your time.
I wanted to say how happy we all are
you found one of your pilots.
Thank you, Madam President.
How is the search progressing
for the other pilot?
Nothing yet, but we've just begun.
I've spoken
with the other captains in the fleet.
They've agreed to give over their ships
at your disposal...
if it'll increase the odds of finding her.
Frack the odds.
We're going to find her.
Excuse me. Thank you.
Tell them we could sure use the help.
I'll coordinate their efforts with your CIC.
Continued good luck.
Thank you.
So it looks like
we're going to be staying here for a while.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine, it's just a...
How long you think it will be
before the Cylons wonder what happened...
to their missing patrol,
and send another one here to look for it?
You have attacked us hundreds of times.
We're still here.
I think you'll find that we are
more than adequately protected.
Might be a little tricky with the fleet
scattered over half this system...
looking for the lost pilot.
How many days till the Cylons return,
Gaius?
One?
Two?
Three at the most?
Doctor?
Your requisitions.
Thank you.
Madam President,
I don't mean to be impertinent, really, but...
do you honestly think this is wise?
You are compromising the security
of the entire fleet...
while we search for one solitary pilot.
It is a risk, but those pilots put their lives
on the line for us every day.
Yes. I was just saying that, to...
I'm not insensitive,
that is what I'm saying.
I happen to know
the missing pilot personally.
Not as personally as you'd like.
Guess you'll never find out
if she's a real blonde.
It's all the more difficult for me.
On one hand I think of the pilot.
And on the other hand
I think of the thousands of defenceless...
women and children.
I meant, throughout the fleet.
I am sure Commander Adama
has considered all of this.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Yes, of course he has.
Of course he has. Thank you.
It's okay.
Okay, get to higher ground.
Then they see you. Then they rescue you.
Apollo, Galactica, we are being bounced
around like beach balls down here.
Visibility about two, best spectrum.
Copy, Apollo.
Blue! Blue flight, go vertical now!
- Anything?
- No.
- I don't think anyone's left out there.
- Must be someone.
We can't be the only two people
left in the world.
Good news is my leg's much better...
and we've got anti-radiation meds
to last three months.
I say we load up
as much food as we can and...
Move out.
Try to find a Raptor or a transport
or something we can fly off Caprica.
Unless you can think of a reason to stay.
Not really looking forward
to going back out there.
I've almost started to think
of this place as...
home.
Home.
No, sleep a little longer.
Who knows when we'll find
clean sheets again.
I'm going to go topside
and make some breakfast.
Breakfast.
Hey, is breakfast ready?
Get out of here! Go!
Lords, it's Kara Thrace.
I'm running a little low on O2
and I could use a lucky break.
You know? Okay, just thought I'd mention it.
Not bad shooting, if I do say so myself.
Lords, I owe you one.
Looks like I found my ride out of here.
If I can fix you up.
Galactica, Apollo. Bingo fuel.
Roger, Apollo. Return to base.
Can't you tank me in orbit?
Negative, Apollo.
The tankers are refilling.
You'll be dry before they can launch.
Are these figures correct?
Yes, sir.
Atmospheric ops mean Viper
and Raptor engines run continuously.
Fuel's going to be a real problem
if we keep it up.
Any report from the civilian ships?
Nothing. They're spread pretty far out.
We'll have a hell of a time trying
to cover them if the Cylons pop in.
We should consider pulling the civvies
into a defensible formation.
No. Keep all the ships on the search.
We've left enough people behind.
I don't wanna leave Starbuck behind.
- Committing the entire fleet to this...
- I said no!
We are going to find our missing pilot
and we're going to bring her home.
We leave no one behind.
Resume your duties.
Sharon?
Sharon, where are you?
Damn it, Sharon, where are you?
Sharon!
Frack me.
Are you alive?
What the hell happened this time, Captain?
I hit the roll thrusters to level off
for set down but only the left one fired.
It's that crap you're flying into down there.
Gums everything up.
Get me another Viper.
Love to, but this is 13 Vipers
that are down, plus your Mark VII. I'm out.
I've got a pilot down
and I need another Viper now.
I realise that, Captain.
But you can push people a lot further
than machines.
I'm the CAG, you're the Chief.
Just make it happen.
Commander, the clock has passed
five hours, sir, for Starbuck's O2 supply.
Noted.
Here's the photo mosaic
for the area we searched so far.
We've got to do better than this.
Can't see far
when you're hugging the ground.
You can't see anything from altitude.
Not to mention the crap in the air
that keeps screwing up our ships.
Thirteen Vipers down for repairs.
We need more eyes.
Where we going to get them?
Pull the CAP.
What?
Redeploy the Combat Air Patrol
to the search.
Bad idea. The CAP is the fleet's only defence.
If all Vipers are fracking around
on the moon...
when the Cylons come calling,
we're maggot meat.
Then bring the fleet closer to the moon.
We can always scramble the Vipers
from the search to meet any attack.
Bottom line: we can double the area
we can search in the time we have left.
Starbuck would be the first one to tell you
not to do this.
Nothing would make you happier, would it?
Leave her behind.
Get rid of the foul-mouthed insubordinate
pilot that keeps challenging your authority.
You are way out of line. I'm not the one
confusing personal feelings with duty.
What the hell does that mean?
You are way too close to this
because she's your friend.
Gentlemen!
We have work to do. Captain.
Get as many birds up in the air as you can
and you find our girl.
You got it.
Oh, my gods.
You bite me, I'll bite you back.
So I guess
the only thing flying you is you.
This must be your brain.
I don't think you'll need it.
Good thing that I brought one of my own.
Even cockroaches have to breathe.
How the hell do you?
Captain. Call for you, sir.
Can someone finish this up for me?
Where is it?
That way.
Yeah, Apollo.
Hold for President Roslin.
How're you holding up?
Better than my Viper. We're slapping
one together from pieces of the others.
I need your help.
Did you know that your father
just redeployed the Combat Air Patrol?
- Yes, Madam President. It was my idea.
- Your idea?
We need every Viper we've got.
Maybe I'm missing something
about the tactics involved.
But isn't the fleet defenceless
without the CAP?
Only for a short time.
Because after that, Kara's oxygen
will be gone and she'll be dead.
Are you very close with Lt. Thrace?
I'm close with all my pilots.
And I assume
the same is true for your father?
His pilots mean a lot to him. To all of us.
We don't leave anyone behind.
But we have left people behind.
You know that.
Not this time.
Your FTL drive should be spun up and ready.
Just make sure everyone is set to jump
at the first sign of trouble.
With all due respect, Captain...
there are times when it is necessary
for the safety of the fleet to put...
Not this time.
We just haven't exhausted all the options...
and the safety of the fleet
has not been compromised.
- I hope you find her.
- Thank you.
Blue flight reports bingo fuel, sir.
Have them stay on the search.
Send the tanker to them.
Is there a problem, Mr. Gaeta?
It's just that trying to tank in that turbulence,
sir, will be extremely hairy.
I suggest we wait
until the clock has run down...
and then tank up
on the way back to Galactica.
Did someone call them back to Galactica?
- I just assumed...
- The search was over? It was hopeless?
That we should write Starbuck off as dead?
- Is that what you're telling me, Mr. Gaeta?
- No, sir.
Then what are you trying to tell me,
Mr. Gaeta?
- You have your orders.
- Yes, sir.
Time is up. She's out of O2.
The clock is a guess.
We don't know for a fact
that Starbuck is out of air.
Her tank only holds so much oxygen.
She could have a reserve supply
in her survival gear.
A reserve?
Yes.
What, she just happened to pack
an extra bottle today?
It's possible.
We are putting people at risk.
- We have pilots out there...
- We are not quitting.
...pushing themselves, their ships
too hard, all for the sake of...
We are not quitting
and you are relieved, Colonel.
I stand relieved, sir.
Come on, you're part biological, right?
Which means you need oxygen, right?
So it's got to be here, somewhere.
Commander, the President.
Adama.
Commander Adama, I just wanted to say
how very sorry I am about Lt. Thrace.
Please give my condolences to your son
and to the rest of the crew.
Excuse me, Madam,
but I think you've been misinformed.
- How?
- We don't know if Starbuck's dead.
I was told that her oxygen
had run out a half an hour ago.
That's an estimate.
She may have a reserve supply.
We'll continue the search as long as
there's a chance she may be alive.
And how long will that be?
Until I say stop.
This is a military decision,
Madam President.
Thank you for your concern.
First on the list, seal you up...
figure out what controls what.
One of us needs a bath.
Now you're going to teach me how to fly.
Red Flight reports an area of highlands here.
- Increased visibility out to 15 clicks maybe.
- It's the wrong side of the moon.
Commander...
Almost impossible to...
We have a signal
from Colonial One's shuttle.
They request permission to land.
The President's on board.
Why wasn't I notified
the President was coming onboard?
There was no advance notice, sir.
I didn't know she was coming.
Let's go.
Have Col. Tigh meet her
at the airlock.
Bring her to my quarters, please.
Very well.
Every flying machine has four basic controls:
power, pitch, yaw, and roll.
Where are yours?
Safety tip number one: don't touch that.
Are you going to order us
to stop the search?
I came here to talk, not to give orders.
- It may take an order.
- Why?
Col. Tigh, do I need to know something?
It's gone beyond military needs.
It's personal for the Commander and Lee.
Because of Lt. Thrace?
Because of her, and because of Zak Adama.
The Commander's dead son.
It's complicated.
Take about three weeks to explain.
We've got about three minutes. Talk fast.
She's going to press.
I'm with you.
President Roslin.
Madam President.
Skip the formalities.
You both know why I'm here.
Termination of a pilot's rescue mission
is a military decision.
That's a bunch of crap.
This isn't military, it's personal.
Neither of you can let go of Kara Thrace
because she's your last link to Zak.
- You don't know anything about my brother.
- Don't even begin, Captain.
You've lost perspective. As have you.
Under normal circumstances
it would just be sad...
that you two can't come to terms
with Zak's death.
In this situation
you're putting your pilots at risk.
You're exposing the fleet to possible attack
every moment we stay here.
We've been at risk of an attack since day one.
The Cylons won't be missing
their patrol for at least one more day.
Col. Tigh, how much aviation fuel
has been expended in this operation?
Forty-three percent of reserves.
Almost half. That's unacceptable.
Operations in the moon's atmosphere have
put one third of your fighters out of action.
That is also completely unacceptable.
Crap. Unacceptable.
Whatever it is you feel about this...
the recovery of one pilot is a military matter.
All right. It's military. Fine.
And you're both officers.
And you're both honourable men.
You're both perfectly aware
that you are putting the lives...
of over 45,000 people
and the future of this civilisation at risk...
for your personal feelings.
Now if the two of you, of all people,
can live with that...
then the human race doesn't stand a chance.
Clear your heads.
Combat. Stand-by.
This is the Commander.
Terminate search operations.
Bring everyone home.
Prepare the fleet to make a jump
to the next system. We're leaving.
Okay, so it either works or it doesn't.
Okay, it's power, roll, pitch, and yaw.
We have control. Take me home.
You stink,
but you're one hell of a flying machine.
I want you to know, I think she's wrong.
I think we have come to terms
with what happened to Zak.
I haven't.
I need to know something.
Why did you do this? Why did we do this?
Is it for Kara? For Zak? For what?
Kara was family.
You do whatever you have to do.
Sometimes you break the rules.
- And if it was me down there instead?
- You don't have to ask that.
Are you sure?
If it were you...
we'd never leave.
Colonel.
Commander.
- Resume your duties.
- Sir, fighters are aboard, sir.
Civilian ships have begun their jumps
to the next star system.
Give the word, we'll start our clock.
Start the clock.
Mr. Gaeta, start the clock.
Starting clock.
Madam President,
would you like to return to your ship?
Thank you, I'll stay here.
I'd like to see how the professionals do it.
As you wish.
- Execute jump, Lt. Gaeta.
- Aye, sir. Jump clock is running.
Navigation?
Go.
FTL?
Tactical?
Go.
Flight Ops?
Contact. Dradis contact.
Incoming, bearing 060, carom 308.
- Hold count.
- Count held.
Contact is...
Hold the count.
Well?
- Cylon Raider, sir.
- You're right. It's just a matter of time.
He's on an intercept course. He'll be on us
before we complete the jump.
Action stations, launch Vipers.
Action stations. Launch
alert, Vipers. Cylon Raider approaching.
Now look
before you shoot, please.
Gun captains report
weapons manned and ready.
Where the hell are the Vipers?
Most are being fuelled.
Hot Dog and Apollo
are in the tubes.
Viper I, clear forward.
Navcon Green, interval failure. Abort launch.
Frack!
I guess I'm going solo.
Why only one Cylon this time?
It could be a lone recon mission...
or the vanguard for a Cylon base ship
about to jump on top of us.
Either way, we're going to have
to take it out before we can jump.
Galactica, Apollo. Target in sight.
You idiot. Didn't anybody teach you
intercept protocol?
Okay, we're going to have
to do this the hard way then.
This bastard's good.
They're closing fast.
Port guns have a firing solution.
Very well.
- Hold still, you little...
- No cigar for you.
Just come a little bit closer.
Not that close!
What the...
I've lost him.
Galactica, I repeat, he is nowhere to be seen.
- Dradis.
- No help. Their reports have merged.
Launch tube status?
Still fouled.
- We'll have a Viper away in 45 seconds.
- This will be over in 45 seconds.
Holy...
Galactica, the Cylon is now flying
in formation with me...
right above my head.
This thing is acting weird.
Put me through.
It's Starbuck!
What?
Come again, Apollo.
Galactica, the Cylon Raider
is marked "Starbuck. "
It's written under the fracking wing.
Bring it into the bay.
If it does anything, take it out.
Wilco, Galactica,
but I tell you what, it's got to be her.
This thing is flying
with some serious attitude.
Now your ass belongs to me.
Like my new toy?
Boy, when you take a souvenir,
you don't screw around.
- Oh, my God, you smell like a latrine.
- You want to give me a bath?
- How're you feeling?
- Been a hell of a lot worse.
Don't have any ambrosia, but the Doc...
can fix you up with some really nice stuff.
It's not bad, is it? The knee?
Doc says it's too early to tell,
but knowing you, you'll be fine.
- Kara.
- Yeah?
You did good.
Get better, okay?
- Need anything?
- A stogie would be nice.
I had a feeling.
- It's my last one, so enjoy it.
- Thank you.
Get some rest.