Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
What the hell is going on?
You killed her.
We gotta go. Right now.
That's Tom Zarek.
The terrorist?
He's a prisoner of conscience.
He's a butcher.
He blew up a government building,
there is no excuse for that.
I thought you said you respected me.
That was before you resorted
to violence and hostage-taking.
I demand the immediate resignation
of Laura Roslin and her ministers.
I demand free and open elections
to choose a new leadership.
If you let the rest of these hostages go,
we will leave this ship in your hands.
McMANUS: Got it?
Test. There.
McMANUS: Are we on?
Frack, we're on. Go.
McMANUS: Live from Cloud Nine,
the most luxurious ship in the fleet...
it's The Colonial Gang.
It's a new talk show that brings you
the inside scoop on the fleet.
I'm James McManus,
formerly of the Caprica Times.
With me are two of the only remaining
legitimate journalists left.
Playa Palacios, veteran commentator
for the Picon Star Tribune. Welcome.
And my wingman, Sekou Hamilton,
former editor of the Aerilon Gazette.
McMANUS: As most
people know...
Cloud Nine was damaged
during a Cylon attack...
and had to be evacuated.
With repairs now complete,
President Roslin has picked it as the site...
for an historic gathering.
It's the first meeting
of the Interim Quorum of 12...
which will coincide with Colonial Day...
the 52nd anniversary of the signing
of the Articles of Colonisation.
Playa, why don't you weigh in?
Laura Roslin should be applauded...
for restoring
the system of checks and balances.
McMANUS: Every delegate chosen so far
has been a Roslin crony.
It's a puppet Quorum, okay?
That will rubber-stamp every edict
this power-mad schoolteacher will try...
How can you say that when half the Quorum
hasn't even been selected?
McMANUS: I predict every one of them
will be a Roslin lackey...
hand-picked by the power behind the throne,
Presidential Advisor, Wallace Gray.
Don't you see,
Gray orchestrated this whole publicity stunt.
Come on, Jim.
Wallace Gray is no prince of darkness.
I disagree.
He's helped Roslin
regulate the internal economy...
made sure vital food and medical supplies
were fairly distributed...
He's a gasbag who's made a fortune through
deals Quorum members have profited from.
Freedom of the press.
McMANUS: As we speak...
Madam President, the fatuous gasbag
would like 5 minutes of your time.
Wally.
How does it feel to be a celebrity?
Well, I love it.
They'll probably be calling me a fascist next.
No, I'm the fascist.
You stick with being the gasbag.
Madam President, excuse me,
you're going to want to hear this.
McMANUS:... Sagittaron have chosen their
delegate for the Interim Quorum of 12.
Who would've guessed it? Tom Zarek.
- Oh, my gods.
- He's got quite a following out there.
- I should have seen this coming.
- He's a terrorist. Who are they kidding?
McMANUS:... a ruthless terrorist.
Tom Zarek incited a prison riot
that resulted in kidnapping, attempted rape.
He blew up a government building and now
he's gonna sit on the Quorum of 12?
McMANUS: Wrong. The government
trumped up charges to discredit a man...
who's dedicated his life
for the disenfranchised.
Yes? Just a moment.
Commander Adama.
Why am I not surprised?
Hello, Commander.
Are you listening to this?
- Indeed.
- Can't allow a terrorist to sit in government.
My hands are tied.
I don't want to turn him into a martyr.
Sagittaron law allows a prisoner to regain
his citizenship once he's served his time.
Tom Zarek represents
a danger to the entire fleet.
I can bar him from travelling to Cloud Nine
on that basis alone.
I perfectly understand the threat
Tom Zarek represents.
But the last thing I need is for you to start
acting like my own personal goon squad.
We need to let this play out. Thank you.
McMANUS: Hold onto your shorts.
There's another story.
We're getting a live feed
from the Astral Queen.
Tom Zarek is about to make a statement.
Citizens of the 12 Colonies, I am
humbled and moved by this great honour.
I will be a voice
for those who have gone too long unheard...
by a government that serves
only the privileged and the powerful...
that turns a blind eye
to the needs of the weak and the poor.
But Roslin and her confederates
will no longer be able to ignore us.
People of the fleet,
look up. The winds of change are blowing.
A new era is about to dawn.
Hey, Doc.
Lt. Thrace, to what do I owe this honour?
Our shuttle leaves for Cloud Nine
at 05:12 tomorrow, so don't be late.
"Our" shuttle?
A surprise getaway? Just the two of you?
- I'm going to be handling your security.
- Please don't touch that. Thank you.
Security for what?
You haven't heard?
It's all over talk wireless.
When would I have the chance
to listen to talk wireless?
I have 60 years of work in front of me.
Anyway, talk wireless is just an excuse
for lowbrow rabble-rousing.
You've been selected as Caprica's delegate
to the Quorum of 12.
Me?
Is this some kind of joke?
Guess you got the super-genius vote.
No accounting for taste.
Congratulations, Doctor.
Thank you.
Politics is the only thing more boring
than blood samples.
All those interminable speeches.
All that dreary pomp.
Parties full of young women
drawn to men of power.
But when the people call, you must serve.
I can't remember the last time
I felt the sunlight on my face.
Sure feels good. Almost like the real thing.
They could've done a better job
with the horizon, though.
Security's going to be a bitch.
A thousand different places
for a sniper to hide.
How many people are we dealing with?
Five hundred plus.
Each colony's
sending a delegation of leading citizens.
Great. Herds of lookie-loos,
any one of whom could be a Cylon.
Toasters aren't our only problem.
Don't you pay any attention to politics?
- No.
- A lot of unrest out there.
So why is Roslin insisting
on letting so many people come?
I guess she thinks it's important to them...
to be able to observe
how their government works.
So basically,
she's already running for re-election.
No, Kara.
Kara, give me that.
Thank you, sir.
Enjoy your day.
The atmosphere is electric...
as Quorum members arrive
with their delegations.
I'm outside the Cloud Nine Ballroom...
where the reception of
the new Quorum of 12 will take place.
The question is, will President Roslin
shake the hand of the man...
many still regard as a terrorist...
or will she snub him, and by extension,
all the people of Sagittaron?
Col. Tigh.
- My wife Ellen.
- Welcome aboard.
Kill me now.
Col. Tigh.
Starbuck, Apollo. Zarek's here.
Copy.
Don't worry. This guy's mine
the second he makes a wrong move.
Yeah?
Well, you'll have to beat me to him.
Murderer. You don't belong here, Zarek.
Go back.
What did you say?
He's not a murderer, he's a freedom fighter.
All right?
Excuse me.
- May I see your security pass, sir?
- Not a problem.
I'm a citizen of Sagittaron.
I've got every legal right to be here.
Your rights don't extend
to roughing people up.
Lay a hand on anyone else and you'll be
getting to know Galactica's brig.
Well, everything's in order.
Enjoy your stay on Cloud Nine.
Oh, I will.
Tom Zarek.
Col. Tigh, Battlestar Galactica.
I see.
My wife.
- Does she have a name?
- Ellen.
Call me Tom.
I don't like to stand on ceremony.
I'm the same way.
All this pretension makes me sick.
You're holding up the line.
Thank you
for making me feel welcome, Ellen.
I hope to see you again.
Why did you do that?
To get our picture on the front page of every
newsletter and photo service in the fleet.
I don't need my picture taken with a terrorist.
Wake up, Saul. Look at these cameras.
Roslin's the past, Zarek's the future.
A blind man can see that.
Madam President.
Mr. Zarek.
If I were to offer you my hand in friendship...
would you take it?
Well, there's only one way to find out.
That was nicely played.
Thank you.
Just remember, I'm not your enemy,
Madam President.
And I know today's agenda
is rather large...
but I think that if you'll look
at the scheduled meetings...
you'll see that
they concern issues vital to the fleet.
In some cases, existing policies...
regarding matters such as
the distribution of medical supplies...
You're missing
an intriguing opportunity.
Playa's not wearing any underwear.
Don't be absurd.
Really?
She's been eyeing you all afternoon.
She's certainly human.
You're not jealous?
Love isn't about sex, Gaius.
That's an enlightened point of view.
I've been thinking...
as far as I'm concerned
you can have any woman you want.
But always remember...
I have your heart.
Yes. Of course you do.
I can always rip it out of your chest
if I need to.
So if there are no objections...
the Chair will entertain motions
to accept today's agenda as proposed.
I have an objection.
The chair recognises Sagittaron.
All the items on your agenda are important,
I agree.
Ration distribution, education,
medical services, all very important.
But I'm frankly shocked to discover...
the most critical issue of all
is nowhere to be found.
Really? Well, perhaps
Mr. Zarek could enlighten us?
The election of a vice-president.
If, gods forbid, anything
should happen to you, Madam President...
we have no designated successor.
The civilian branch of our government
would be paralysed...
leaving the door wide open
for a military dictatorship.
Sagittaron moves that
the first item on the Quorum's agenda...
should be nominations for vice-president.
Second.
- Second.
Caprica seconds for various reasons...
which are far too obvious
and numerous to go into right now.
But certainly, I think we can all agree
that it'd be a good idea to have a successor.
The motion has been moved and seconded.
All those in favour of opening nominations
for the vice-presidency, say aye.
Aye.
The ayes have it.
The floor is now open for nominations.
The chair recognises Virgon.
Now, there is only one man here...
who is willing to work for the betterment
of people in this fleet.
When I asked for his help...
he sent a crew
to fix the air filtration system on my ship...
and, hell, they were finished and gone
while I was still waiting...
for the President's office to return my call.
I nominate Tom Zarek.
Thanks.
Is there a second?
Gemenon seconds the nomination.
The nomination of Tom Zarek
for the vice-presidency has been accepted.
The Chair will remain open for 72 hours
for nominations.
The session is now adjourned.
Thomas Zarek
is not going to be my vice-president.
Six months until the presidential election.
We could've handpicked a candidate.
It didn't shock me
when Bagot nominated him.
- But Porter, that was surprising.
- Not really.
The Gemenon ships use more water
per capita than any other ship.
She wanted more rations, I said no.
Zarek may have made some friends
in the last few weeks...
but there are still plenty who hate him.
Don't underestimate Zarek.
He's charismatic
and knows what buttons to push.
Frankly, Madam President, I am concerned
about the security aboard Cloud Nine.
I want you leaning forward
on this, Captain.
If they even sneeze,
they better have a handkerchief.
Understood.
We need a candidate.
Someone who will
quickly win the delegates' support.
An established name.
I'm not a politician.
But you know
how to get things done.
You've kept this fleet functioning
all this time.
No. Thanks, but...
I can't allow Tom Zarek to be one heartbeat
away from the presidency, Wally.
I need you.
You've got me, Madam President.
How can you reassure people that
you're looking out for their interests...
as opposed to the rehabilitation
of Tom Zarek?
That's a great question, Playa.
This is how I see it.
We're facing a situation so unique,
so specific...
that I believe
we need not only new leadership...
but a whole new way of thinking.
Like blowing up a building or two?
If things weren't so serious,
I'd say that was funny.
Look, there's no economy.
There's no market. No industry.
No capital. Money is worthless.
And yet, we're all held hostage
by the idea of the way things used to be.
Look where we are.
This man wakes up every morning...
tugs on his boots
and goes to work in this garden.
Why?
Because it's his job? What job?
He labours,
but he gets no benefit from his labour.
He's not the only one.
Many of us are just still going
through the motions of our old lives.
The lawyers still act like lawyers,
but they have no clients.
Businessmen still act like
businessmen, but have no business.
President Roslin and her policies
are all about holding on to a fantasy.
If we want to survive,
we need to completely restructure our lives.
We need to think
about the community of citizens.
The group, not the individual.
We need to completely free ourselves
of the past and operate as a collective.
You're not interested in the citizens.
You just want power.
Turn that crap off.
I was listening to that broadcast.
You again?
That's a shame.
They want to hear Mr. Zarek speak, too.
Don't you, buddy?
See? He wants to hear Mr. Zarek.
How about you?
You want to hear what Mr. Zarek has to say?
I don't mind one way or the other.
Well, I take that as a yes. So turn it on.
- Now.
- Leave it.
Mr. Zarek is a representative of the people
and we are the people.
Well, you're people. Sort of.
You know, I don't like your tone,
flyboy...
so why don't you just move along out of here
and go enjoy the imitation weather?
I'd be happy to, after you leave.
Which is now.
Okay.
Don't want no trouble.
What the hell.
There's a gun.
Starbuck.
Incoming.
Are you looking for this?
The Telamon Building's still standing.
That's Delphi, all right.
Now, all we have to do is wait until dark...
infiltrate the most heavily fortified
military hub on this planet...
hope the Cylons haven't
completely wasted the spaceport...
steal a ship, locate Galactica
and fly to her without getting shot to hell.
- Is that all?
- Yeah.
I guess we can relax until dark.
Might as well make ourselves comfortable.
You hungry?
No, not right now.
Your stomach's feeling better?
Starving.
I'm trying to make sense out of
the two women we saw with the Cylons.
And?
I can't fathom why anybody
would wanna help the toasters.
And they just happened to be twins?
That's too weird.
You got a better explanation?
You think the Cylons could be messing
with human DNA?
Cloning people or something?
Could be.
That would explain
how they took us by surprise.
They had these replicated humans
infiltrating the colonies...
laying the groundwork
for the surprise attack.
You know, if they were human clones...
that means they're capable
of complex emotions, maybe even love.
Maybe they were misguided
in the way that they were indoctrinated.
Whatever they are, they're not human.
No human could do the things they've done.
Killed billions of innocent people.
They've got to be fracking Cylons,
just like the rest of them.
Why do you have a summit itinerary?
Why circle every public appearance
by President Roslin?
It's not mine.
Some stranger wandered down the hall,
picked the lock to your room and left this?
False-bottom with anechoic coating
to absorb x-rays.
Ceramic stealth gun.
You sure went through a lot of trouble
to get that weapon onboard.
I carry a lot of money. I need protection.
Right.
The money's worthless.
Your friend Zarek pointed that out.
I don't even know Zarek.
Your pal Grimes says different.
He gave you up.
You're bluffing. You haven't got anything.
We don't need anything, Valance.
Because this isn't a trial.
This is just you and us in this room.
Like Zarek pointed out,
we're living in a whole new world.
No due process.
This is your courtroom.
And that would make us your executioners.
So you might want to cooperate,
or else you're going out an air lock.
Because that's what we do to traitors.
Look, I...
I just came over here
for the booze and the food.
That's it.
You know what? Frack you!
We put all the heat on Valance
we could but can't tie him to Zarek.
I know Zarek's behind this.
Keep working on Valance.
We will. To be safe, I think you should
send the Sagittaron delegation back.
Can't. Violates their civil rights,
plays right into Zarek's hands.
He could have another shooter
on Cloud Nine...
and if Zarek wins the vote,
he's more than capable...
of ordering your assassination
and ascending to the presidency.
Zarek's not going to win
because I'm not going to let him.
Meanwhile, keep Zarek under surveillance,
tap his phones, bug his room.
If you find anything that remotely connects
Zarek to Valance, shut him down.
The domestic policies we've been
talking about over the last little while...
such as employment,
housing and education...
Latest vote count:
seven for Gray, five for Zarek.
We're slipping. He was four an hour ago.
- Zarek must be making promises.
- Picon flipped.
We've got to hold
the colonies till they vote tomorrow.
On Page 33
of my mission statement...
I lay out a 16-point educational programme
that the President and I have developed.
Individuals with four-year college degrees
will be eligible.
Hi. How are you doing? Remember me?
We got Valance. And you're next.
Health care, it's one thing to talk...
Can I get you something?
So you work here now?
Why should I ask the bartender
to get me a drink?
- What's in it for him?
- A big tip.
What would he spend on?
So, are you worried about Wallace Gray?
I hear he's ahead in the vote count.
Whatever the people want is fine by me.
Everyone has an agenda. I know I do.
And what would that be?
The same as yours, Tom. Me. Myself.
And I.
You are clearly a well-connected,
well-informed woman.
Wife of the XO.
For whatever that's worth.
Quite a bit. Now and in the future.
That's what I'm interested in, Tom.
My place...
and my husband's place in the future.
Okay.
I'm looking for a friend of mine.
His name is Valance.
How the hell did this happen?
We've got to get to the President.
McMANUS: We're here with
Dr. Gaius Baltar, representative of Caprica.
Dr. Baltar, I had one question.
Is President Roslin's political career
terminal or is there hope of resuscitating it?
Laura Roslin's political career
is very much alive...
and to underestimate her
would be a very serious mistake.
- You miss the limelight, don't you, Gaius?
- Yes, I have.
- You have what, Dr. Baltar?
- Nothing. You were saying?
You seriously believe
that this school teacher...
is able to handle the job of presidency?
His wrists were slashed
with broken glass from the room.
- So was it suicide or was it murder?
- It was no suicide.
- Zarek had him killed.
- If only we could prove that.
How'd they get past the Marine Guards?
Through the vent.
I'm glad to hear it...
because all of us have had teachers
who made an impact on our lives.
History is full of examples of leaders...
who have come
from the most humble beginnings...
and have risen to meet the challenge
posed by cataclysmic events.
How many people knew
where Valance was being held?
Just the people in this room
plus two Marines.
...criticise Roslin and the tough
decisions she has to make every day.
Especially, if you're someone
like Tom Zarek...
who's never shouldered
any real responsibility in your life.
To be fair to Tom,
he's been in prison for the last 20 years.
And now that he's had
a drastic personality makeover...
he's posing like
he's the saviour to all your ills.
I think you all have a short memory.
Well, someone talked.
And now we have no assassin,
no evidence of a plot...
no check on Zarek, no nothing.
If he can get to Valance,
he can get to anyone.
Madam President, he will definitely try
and take a shot at you now.
Only if he wins the vote.
What I have to say is, we must survive.
And we will survive.
And we will do so through the values
that have made our colonies great.
Courage. Truth. Justice. Liberty.
With a firm and deep resolve
to make tomorrow better.
Not just for ourselves, but for our children.
Madam President, I still worry
the vote may be trending against you.
Yes, it is.
But I'm going to win this thing.
And Tom Zarek is going back
to his prison ship where he belongs.
But first I have
two very unpleasant duties to perform.
I need a shuttle to Cloud Nine.
What am I supposed to say?
- Health reasons.
- Oh, right, fine. Health reasons.
You know, all those years...
I watched you working with Adar.
You were always so quiet, so polite...
so dignified.
I never thought you'd fit in with
the bare-knuckled, backstabbing politicians.
I guess I was wrong.
All clear.
Dr. Baltar? Are you in here?
Madam President?
I heard you on the wireless.
You were very articulate, quite engaging.
Oh, thank you.
That's very encouraging.
Yeah, I was just trying to do my bit
as the elected representative of Caprica.
Besides, I'm beginning
to get a real feel for politics.
So I take it you're not voting for Mr. Zarek?
A man who uses his intelligence
and resources to blow up buildings...
doesn't get my vote, no.
No, I'm voting for your man Gray.
He's really great.
He is great, which is why he's got my vote.
Unfortunately...
Mr. Gray dropped out of the race.
- Then who do you want me to vote for?
- I was thinking you.
Me?
- Look...
- Doctor, let's cut to the chase.
You're a very popular man
these days.
I would be fortunate to have
your intellect...
and your popularity right by my side.
Under those circumstances, I accept.
Thank you, Madam President.
Thank you.
Wow. What are you going to do now?
Now...
I'm going to give you an exclusive.
After you.
So what are we supposed to do?
Sit on our hands and watch her get killed?
Zarek's too smart to take another shot
at the President during the summit.
If he wins the vote,
he can take her out later...
when everyone's forgotten about Valance.
He'll just bide his time
to find a better opportunity.
That's great.
Anyway, she says
she's not going to lose the vote.
She says a lot of things.
Don't you think you should wash that?
I did.
Like when, a month ago?
- Do you have a problem with my hygiene?
- You have hygiene?
I clean up good sometimes, all right?
Well, let me know
when it's one of those times.
Tauron, Gaius Baltar.
The surprises just keep on coming.
A number of the Quorum delegates
have now shifted their support...
to the scientific genius...
a man who is credited with saving
the fleet on numerous occasions.
At this point, Jim, it is anyone's guess...
as to who's going to win,
but my money is on Gaius. Dr. Baltar.
Aquaria, Thomas Zarek.
Aerilon:
Tom Zarek.
The vote is now six-five
in favour of Tom Zarek.
The next vote
will determine our new vice-president.
If Zarek gets it, he wins.
In the event of a tie,
the President will cast the deciding vote.
Citizens...
I give you your new vice-president,
Dr. Gaius Baltar.
The perks of power, Mr. Vice-President.
We're going to do great things together.
Good. It's difficult to fathom.
I never aspired to power.
Of course you didn't, Gaius.
But someone had to step up.
- Well, after what Laura told me...
- Laura?
Yeah, we're on
a first name basis now.
Now look, I think the people need me.
Excuse us.
So...
that bum knee of yours
is looking pretty good.
And the other one's not too bad either.
Lee, if you want to ask me to dance,
just ask.
You want to dance?
Me in a dress
is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
- Madam President.
- Mr. Zarek.
Oh, don't worry,
I won't be kissing you today.
That's a shame.
I shaved very closely in anticipation
of being smacked by you.
That was very nicely played.
Again.
But there's still a presidential election
in six months.
- I'll see you then.
- I have no doubt.
Oh, one thing you should know.
I didn't kill Valance.
I wonder who did?
Madam President, good evening.
I thought you hated these things.
It's Colonial Day.
Where else would I be? I'm a patriot.
You really are, aren't you?
Dr. Baltar. Interesting choice.
I figured, the devil you know.
Politics. As exciting as war.
Definitely as dangerous.
Though in war you only get killed once.
In politics, it can happen over and over.
You're still standing.
So are you.
And I can dance.
- I have a surprise for you.
- Should I be worried?
Not unless you consider a day...
in a luxury suite aboard the Rising Star
as something to be worried about.
What? How did you swing that?
I have my ways.
What you need to do...
is figure out a way to get slave-driving Bill
to give you the day off.
Yeah.
And while we're there, we might want
to talk to a few people...
- about your future.
- What?
Later, my love. It can all wait until later.
Any second now.
If we get caught... If anything happens...
You don't have to say anything. I know.
We're going to make it, Sharon. Okay?
Okay. Go.
Sharon?
We're still alive. Why nobody else?
You never get tired.
Trust me.
Helo, come with me. Helo.
Helo.