Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
Like my new toy?
It's my very own Cylon Raider.
Boy, when you take a souvenir,
you don't screw around.
Congratulations, Doctor.
You've just uncovered your very first Cylon.
She probably doesn't know.
If something happened to you...
I wouldn't know how to deal with it.
I feel the same way.
I'm a Cylon.
Helo, come with me. Helo.
Helo, come with me!
New piece of equipment
that just appeared in CIC.
He had this when we found him.
Send it to Galactica. The lab can look at it.
It's a Cylon device.
I'll continue to take the Chamalla.
It has other benefits.
The hallucinations?
You're going to find Kobol.
Birthplace of us all.
He says we're gonna find Kobol,
and that it's gonna lead us to Earth.
You all right?
Stop! Don't come any closer.
Just do it.
Oh, Lee!
Oh, God.
Attention.
Pass the word for Lt. Valerii.
Lt. Valerii, report to the Ready Room
for a pre-flight briefing.
You don't lose control.
Thanks.
No.
You got to lose control.
Let your instincts take over.
I thought we were just sparring.
That's why you don't win.
The doctor said I have six months
at the outside.
He said the cancer's moved
into my lymphatic system.
Aggressively moved in.
I want you to hear me on this.
You made a true believer out of me.
Strange as that sounds, considering.
But I believe.
I know you're the one to lead us
to our salvation.
You are going to guide us to Earth.
Then we better find it soon.
- I'm out.
- Like it's yours.
- I picked up your five.
- Frankly, I don't care.
No, thank you, Doctor, I have a watch later.
Crashdown hits. Davis?
What?
A little bit of this.
A little bit of that.
You guys always play this slow?
What did you say?
Don't distract me.
Uncanny, I know.
All right, 20, I call.
And I raise you another 30.
You can't compete with me.
I always win.
I'm sorry.
Never seen you like this, Gaius.
It's disappointing somehow.
Common.
So sorry to disappoint you.
Disappoint you all.
Thirty.
And I call it.
What do you got, buddy?
- Absolutely nothing.
- Not bad, Crash.
But not compared to that.
Oh!
You are...
No!
You win every time.
Sorry, I have to do it.
Very sorry to disappoint you.
There's a card game...
Hey.
She's back on her feet, ladies and gentlemen.
- How are you feeling?
- Hey, Gaius.
Good.
Mr. Vice President,
if you don't mind, Lt. Thrace.
Some level of decorum must be maintained,
or is it a pirate ship you're running?
No. Just a Battlestar, sir.
All right, let's play.
Would you like to play?
Maybe you'd like to sit next to Capt. Adama?
Sure, Kara. Why don't you pull up a pew?
No, that's okay, Lee. I've got things to do.
Nothing's wild. Here we go.
All right, currency.
While bartering will continue
for the foreseeable future...
we do have a system in place now
to take the economy back...
to a currency-based standard.
Do you love her?
Did you...
Dr. Baltar...
if something should happen to me,
it is vital that you comprehend...
and are familiar with the political structures
beginning to fall into place here.
- Do you understand this?
- Answer me.
Yes, of course I understand.
My answer is no.
No, I don't think I can handle this right now.
The intricacies of the bureaucracy,
I can't get my head around.
This which,
with all due respect, Madam President...
you have spent your entire political career
learning to understand.
More to the point...
how you could think that
my head could be turned so quickly...
by a new thing...
it just astounds me.
How did you seriously think I could
cope with this kind of responsibility?
I don't believe you.
You're a genius, are you not?
Well, quite frankly,
I don't give a flying frack...
whether you believe me or not. All right?
Because I've had it.
I am tired of being pushed and
prodded around like I'm some kind of toy.
- I'm not your plaything.
- Plaything?
I don't work for you!
And quite frankly,
I don't have to sit here anymore...
and take this kind of abuse
from either of you!
You either!
Either in here, either in there.
Wherever it is, I don't need to take it.
- I love you, Gaius.
- Do me a favour.
Yeah?
I think perhaps you need a break from this.
You're right.
We need a break.
I'd like to be alone if you don't mind.
How can you love her, Gaius?
I don't.
You can't lie to me,
I know everything you know.
That's lovely.
Thank you.
Did you...
Did you want
something in particular this time?
I thought you should know...
that it's not safe to remain on Galactica.
What are you talking about?
It's a surprise.
Tell me, what is it? What is it?
Is it a bomb? Another Cylon bomb, right?
Is it an agent?
Is a Cylon agent about to be activated?
Tell me!
Galactica, this is Raptor 1
preparing to jump to Sector 728.
Let's hope we find some supplies out there.
Roger that. Good hunting out there.
Crash, counter our spinner?
Fuel drive's spun up and ready.
Jump in five, four, three, two, one.
Whoa, baby!
Frack me!
Gaeta, the fracking idiot.
You can't plan a jump that close to a planet.
What if we jumped into it?
It was great. It's fine. We made it. We're cool.
Are you seeing this?
Yeah.
Oceans.
Continents.
No. Let me at this thing.
Okay. Atmosphere reads as:
Nitrogen, oxygen. Looks like enough CO2
for green leafy things.
I'm getting excited here, Boomer.
Boomer, this could be it.
This could be the big one. This is the little
planet that solves all our problems.
Boomer?
Do you think this is Earth?
No. It's not Earth.
It's more important than that.
Doesn't really work as well as before, huh?
You know, I do get cold.
There's some things you should know, Helo.
Don't call me that.
You're not even Sharon.
You're not even human.
So don't act like you know me...
because you don't!
But I am Sharon! And that's part
of what you need to understand!
Sharon was a friend of mine!
Whatever twisted thing you are,
you are not Sharon! You got that?
The only thing I want from you
is a way off this fracked up world. That's it!
Going hunting?
I'm adding a gunnery run
to the jump test tomorrow.
See if our boy
can shoot anything with our ammo.
So it's a boy now?
I changed my mind.
You ever wonder why
everyone calls it a she, but to you, it's a he?
It's fascinating, Lee.
You should write a paper.
It's not really my scene.
I'm not as smart as, say, Dr. Baltar.
How is the Vice President,
by the way?
I don't know. Haven't seen him.
So he's a "love them and leave them"
kind of guy, I guess.
I guess.
Ships just pass in the night.
Yup.
Didn't mean a thing.
Nope.
Just bored. Looking for something to do.
So fracking the Vice President
seemed like a great way to waste some time.
- You want something from me?
- Not a thing.
- I don't owe you anything.
- You don't owe me anything.
Because I'm just a CAG,
and you're just a pilot.
- Right.
- A pilot that can't keep her pants on!
Right.
It's just like old times, Kara.
Like when you got drunk and couldn't keep
your hands off the major from wherever...
God!
Why did you do it, Kara? Just tell me why.
Because I'm a screw-up, Lee.
Try and keep that in mind.
Commander Adama is
sending out another Raptor...
to conduct an aerial survey of this planet.
It appears to have suffered
some sort of calamity...
but it could actually be inhabitable.
Aerial survey shows evidence
of at least one city on the surface.
It was obviously abandoned
long ago.
How old are the ruins?
We won't know for sure
until we send a ground team...
but the initial estimates have it...
on the order of approximately 2,000 years.
That's around the time
the 13 Tribes first left Kobol.
Let me see.
Ruins? What ruins?
This is an inhabited city.
Look at the buildings.
Buildings?
Look.
What did you see? Tell me, Laura.
A dome-like structure with six roads
leading out of it like spokes.
With something around it like columns, like
a forum, like the forum on Caprica, actually.
The forum in the opera house
in the city of the gods on Kobol.
This planet is Kobol.
Kobol like Kobol?
The birthplace of mankind.
Where the gods and man lived in paradise.
Until the exodus of the 13 Tribes.
Madam President, what's going on?
It's real. The scriptures, the myths,
the prophecies. They're all real.
So say we all.
Hello, Lieutenant.
Hey, Doc.
This is a bad time, right?
No. I'm just cleaning my gun.
What's going on?
I was going to ask you the same question.
Actually, I was looking
for Lt. Thrace.
But sometimes,
it's good to talk these things over.
Deep down, she knows she's a Cylon.
But her conscious mind won't accept it.
Sometimes I have these dark thoughts.
- What kind of dark thoughts?
- Her model is weak.
Always has been.
But in the end, she'll carry out her mission.
I don't know.
But I'm afraid I'm going to hurt someone.
I feel like I have to be stopped.
She can't be stopped. She's a Cylon.
You can't help her, Gaius.
But you could probably sleep with her.
That's what you want, right?
I'm not sure why...
Sometimes...
we must embrace that which opens up for us.
Embrace?
Life can be a curse...
as well as a blessing.
You will believe me when I tell you...
there are far worse things than death
in this world.
So you're saying...
No.
What I say is meaningless.
Listen to your heart.
Embrace that which you know
to be the right decision.
You might be right. This may be Kobol.
We should seriously consider
permanent settlement on this planet.
The scriptures tell us that
Kobol points the way to Earth.
Organise a ground survey team.
Three Raptors.
I want a complete survey
of the ruins immediately.
Yes, sir.
You should go.
Remember what I said, Gaius?
You don't want to be here when it happens.
When what happens?
What would happen if I go?
In fact, I think I'm going to volunteer
for the survey party.
Your presence won't be necessary, Doctor.
Thank you.
I'm the Vice President of the colony,
selected in my own right.
And I feel that my presence on the planet
will be necessary, Commander.
As your chief science advisor,
I have to analyse the samples...
the team brings,
and it would be more efficient...
if I can gather the samples by myself.
Unless you have any objection,
Madam President.
No objections. Thank you.
We need to talk.
Sure.
You okay?
What do you think?
I think it's hard to imagine
that you forgot to check the chamber.
I didn't forget.
Sharon, what's going on?
I know things
haven't been so great lately, but...
I wake up in the morning...
and I wonder who I am.
I wake up and wonder
if I'm going to hurt someone.
Sharon, you need help.
Not from you.
You made that clear.
I'm on my own.
No, you're not.
Thanks for coming out, Chief.
You're dismissed.
So according to the scriptures...
if we had the arrow of Apollo, we could
take it down to Kobol, and we could use it...
to open the tomb of Athena
and find our way to Earth.
I didn't know you were that religious.
Neither did I.
Something wrong with that?
No.
It's just new.
There is no Earth. You understand that.
It would seem that we were wrong.
Commander, just because you and I
don't know where it is...
it doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
Madam President...
I am not trying to mock your faith,
so please understand me.
These stories about Kobol, gods...
the arrow of Apollo...
they're just stories, legends, myths.
Don't let it blind you
to the reality that we face.
Reality is that the Cylon Raider
has been successfully jump-tested.
Reality is that Cylon technology
obviously outstrips our own.
And reality is there is a good chance...
the Raider can jump all the way back
to Caprica and retrieve that arrow...
and find our way to Earth.
The real Earth.
The Raider's a military asset.
I won't use it to go chasing
some mythical arrow.
I'm sorry.
I say we find Kobol,
count our blessings, and just stay there.
But the sacred scrolls say
that this could guide us to Earth. Right?
Okay. Cut the chatter. Raptors 2 and 3 on me.
FTL's spun up and ready?
Cally, hold onto your lunch.
Jump in ten...
nine, eight...
seven, six, five...
four, three...
two, one.
Jump complete, gentlemen.
Bring the nose down,
we should see the planet directly ahead.
What the hell is that?
Oh, my God!
Cartman! Get us out of here!
We got a fire in the turbine.
Shutting it down!
Put it down!
Out of the way! Come on!
Get out of the seat, Doc!
Everybody hang on!
Can you jump us out?
No, the out drive's been hit.
Socinus, get on the horn...
and tell Raptor 2 to jump back to Galactica!
Right now!
Jump back to Galactica!
Jump back to Galactica, over.
You are ordered to jump back to Galactica.
Whenever they're within
proximity of one another...
they send off a short IFF burst.
Essentially, they are Cylon transponders...
programmed to identify themselves
to any other Cylon transponder.
- Damn nice work, Lieutenant.
- That's very good.
Now that we know what they are,
I want to test one in the Raider.
Draidus contact.
Raptor 275, sir.
Back early.
Something's wrong.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, God!
Hang on!
God! Oh, my God!
Do it!
Everybody hit the deck!
I can't see!
Pull it up!
Watch the hill!
Thanks for watching!
How many people did we lose?
Ten souls aboard Raptor 3.
Raptor 1, last visual contact was seen...
under power flight
heading toward the surface.
We need a way to take out the base ship
before we can attempt a rescue.
Starbuck's working on a plan...
using the captured Raider
to get a nuke into the base ship.
- The Raider?
- When did this happen?
About 19 minutes ago.
She said she's working on the details
and we'll have a report at 1400.
Go talk to Starbuck right away.
My pleasure.
And report back to me.
Yes, sir.
Is there something to worry about,
Madam President?
Why do you ask that?
- That look on your face.
- Not now.
Take that out.
The Chief said we need it, but I don't.
Lt. Thrace, attention!
I gave you a command.
You will obey it. Attention!
You do not take
your harebrained ideas to the XO...
without going through me first.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
At ease. So what's the plan?
I'm putting an autopilot in the Raider.
Jump him to the base ship.
Engage the autopilot, punch out.
Get picked up by a Raptor.
The Raider heads
to the base ship.
Except the transponder
allows the Raider to approach.
Nuke goes off.
Boom, sir.
Might work. Might get you killed.
Would you miss me, sir?
I need every pilot I have.
Even the screw-ups.
Captain.
I'm really sorry.
If you do this, it could threaten
everything we've accomplished.
It may bring down the government
and you don't have a right...
to risk that for a...
Go on.
For a drug-induced vision of prophecy.
I am well aware of that.
But it would seem that
the gods have a different plan.
Would you please get me
Lt. Thrace?
Can I get you some more water?
Yes. Thanks.
You can't be serious.
All of this has happened before
and will happen again.
That Cylon you interrogated,
he quoted that bit of scripture.
He also said that we would find Kobol...
and Kobol would show us the way,
did he not?
Yes, he did.
We have found Kobol.
Do you believe in the gods, Lieutenant?
Not that it's any of your business,
but, yes, I believe.
Lieutenant, I am not trying to put you
on the defensive...
I would like you
to think this through with me.
If you believe in the gods...
then you believe in the cycle of time...
that we are all playing our parts in a story...
that is told again and again
and again throughout eternity.
That's the way I was raised.
But that doesn't mean
that my part in the story...
is to go off on some crazy-ass mission
against orders.
May I tell you the part of the story
that it would seem I am playing?
I am dying.
- What?
- I have terminal breast cancer.
I have six months at the outside to live,
and I have only told three people...
so I'd appreciate it if you kept it to yourself.
Of course.
Are you saying that you are...
The scripture tells us a dying leader...
lead humanity to the promised land.
If you go back to Caprica
and bring me the arrow...
I will show us the way.
This is crazy.
People keep using that word.
It is crazy. Perhaps.
That doesn't mean it isn't true.
And it may be our only chance.
Our only chance...
to find Earth.
The old man is our last chance to find Earth.
He knows where it is. He said so.
You were there.
The location is a secret.
But he is going to take us there.
Commander Adama has no idea...
where Earth is. He never did.
He made it up in order to give people hope.
- You're lying.
- Go ask him.
I will.
I need one more in-flight test...
for the autopilot and NAV systems
before I jump for Kobol.
Right.
Can I ask you a question, boss?
Shoot.
How much longer till we reach Earth?
It's hard to say.
You got a guess?
You know I don't like to guess.
Are we getting closer?
I'm sure we are.
Good luck on the next test.
Apollo. Starbuck. I'm ready over here.
Okay, Starbuck. The board is green.
Copy that.
Powering up for the autopilot test.
This is Starbuck, request permission
to speak with Galactica actual.
Starbuck wants to speak to you, sir.
She's on a scrambled channel.
Go ahead.
I believed you. Believed in Earth.
What are you doing, Starbuck?
Bringing home the CAG, sir.
We can talk about this.
No, I don't think so.
I want you to remember one thing.
I do not regret anything that I did.
Be sure that whatever you're going to do,
you don't regret it later.
Do you understand me?
I guess we'll find out.
Commander, she's spinning up
the Raider's FTL drive.
What?
This is an autopilot test,
what the hell is she doing?
What are you doing, Kara?
Galactica. Apollo. She just jumped away.
Repeat. Starbuck and the Raider
just jumped away.
She wasn't scheduled for a jump test.
Where the hell did she go?
Home.