Previously on
Battlestar Galactica:
Sharon, get out of here!
Where are you? Sharon!
Halt! No sudden moves.
Get on your knees
and cross your ankles. Now!
I'm human. I'm from Oasis.
It's a hamlet, public stop.
I'm out of Havoca City.
I'm not a Cylon!
Don't leave me!
Attention, the Scorpia Traveller
has docked.
Any civilians currently boarding Galactica
please proceed to security checkpoint.
Thank you.
Flight Maintenance Crew Bravo
report to Flight 3.
Next.
Yes, okay.
It's all clear?
I've got your back, Chief.
Thanks.
- Anybody see you?
- No.
I went through the hatch combing
on C Causeway.
Good girl.
Bravo team, EOD,
stand by for munitions off-loading.
Hangar Bay 2.
You know, sometimes at work...
I try to conjure up what your face looks like.
The curve of your lips...
the way your hair falls, how you smell.
You see my face every day.
Yeah, but not like this.
Security, XO.
Send an armed detail to meet me...
in the midpoint promenade deck causeway,
C level. Approach from the aft.
Repeat. Approach from the aft.
Doral!
What's the count?
- Three dead. 13 injured.
- Did you get a good look at the bomber?
- Yes.
- It was him, right?
Yes.
I want to see the Master at Arms
in my office in ten minutes.
A Cylon?
Eyewitness accounts state
the bomber was a man.
The Cylons look like us now.
Like us?
Yes, they appear human.
The flesh, the blood...
the whole thing.
The bomber was another copy
of a man we knew as Doral...
posing as the Public Relations Officer
aboard this ship.
They've learned that there are
multiple versions of the same Cylon.
I want you to open
an investigation immediately.
I want to find out how that Cylon
or any civilian...
- could break through our security.
- There's been a string...
of security incidents aboard ship, sir.
The water tank explosion, the discovery
of explosives aboard a Raptor...
- and now this.
- Your point?
I need a free hand.
The authority to follow evidence
wherever it might lead...
without command review.
- Independent tribunal?
- Yes, sir.
You'll get it.
Thank you.
That will be all, Sergeant.
I also strongly recommend
alerting the public to the Cylon threat.
If there are other copies of this man
aboard the fleet...
we should find them
before they strike again.
I'll take that under advisement.
That will be all.
Yes, sir.
Open to the public. There's a can of worms.
Keeping silent hasn't helped us very much.
Maybe shining a light on the situation
will make things pop up.
All right.
Hey.
I owe you one.
- Sir.
- Colonel.
Get me the President.
Don't kink the line.
There, we've got it.
Okay, let's go.
So who's first?
How about me?
- Hey, Chief.
- How's it going there, on top?
- Hi.
- Come on. Let's have it. Come on.
You people are
the sorriest of the sorry.
The dumbest of the dumb.
The only thing
you're making out of this...
is a one-way trip to sick bay or the morgue.
Now, tonight, after night call...
one of you brings me
twice this length of copper tubing...
a spot heater and a CO2 scrubber.
I'll show you people how this is done.
All right?
Now get the hell out of here
before I change my mind.
Thank you.
Children.
He's very handsome.
You really think so?
She says that about everyone.
You disagree?
He's attractive.
I hope you're more convincing
than that with him.
If he wants to find me, he'll head north,
toward Cylon forces he's already seen.
If he wants to go alone, he'll go south,
hoping to find another way off the planet.
Either way,
he won't make his move until nightfall.
If he flees, he dies.
There's going to be a huge reaction.
If there are any other Cylons...
aboard any of our ships,
we need to find them.
If we enlist the help of the public,
it'll make it a lot easier.
People are going to be shocked, angry,
terrified, paranoid.
There is a price to be paid
when asking for the public's help.
They're going to demand, at the very least,
that someone be held accountable.
I'm setting up a tribunal.
That tribunal will have to come back
to the public with a name.
Someone who screwed up.
We don't know if anybody screwed up.
A Cylon agent penetrated your security,
killing three people.
At least one of your men
or women screwed up.
Look, here's my view:
Independent tribunal, openness,
transparency, it all sounds great.
But after 20 years in political office,
I'm telling you these things have a way...
of inflicting damage on the people
you least expect.
I do not want a witch hunt on our hands.
So, where were you
at the time of the bombing?
In my rack, reading some trashy novel
Socinus gave me.
- Did you see the Chief?
- Chief?
He was on the Hangar Deck
going over some paperwork, I think.
How do you know that
if you were in your rack?
I saw him right before I turned in.
I was with Cally playing Pyramid
in the mess hall corridor.
You sure?
Yeah. She's pretty good.
- Did you see the Chief?
- Yeah, he was there.
I mean, not the whole time.
He dropped in, watched us play for a while.
Okay.
I was on watch.
Did you see the Chief?
The Chief? No.
- He wasn't on the Hangar Deck?
- No.
Wait. Yeah. Yeah, he was.
He came in, did some work
on one of the Vipers that the Captain rides.
Thank you.
- Asleep in my rack.
- Sure about that?
Positive.
I was asleep, Sergeant.
All right. That'll be all for now.
Good afternoon and thank you for coming.
Please be seated.
I'm sure by now, word of the explosion...
on the Galactica
has spread to the entire fleet.
We offer our continued gratitude
to the brave men and women...
aboard this mighty ship.
In consultation with Commander Adama...
I have appointed an independent tribunal...
to investigate the circumstances
surrounding this explosion.
Also, in the interest of security
and public safety...
I feel it is time to reveal certain information
that has until now...
remained a tightly-guarded secret.
This information was known only to myself,
Commander Adama...
- and a few select advisors.
- The cat's out of the bag.
The Cylons have the ability to mimic
human form. They look like us now.
We have reason to believe
that a Cylon agent was responsible...
for the explosions aboard Galactica.
This man has been identified
as a Cylon agent.
We believe him to be responsible
for the bombing.
He evidently slipped aboard the Galactica
with a civilian group...
killed a Marine guard,
stole the explosives and detonated them...
killing three members of the crew
and destroying himself.
This man has also been identified
as a Cylon.
And we now know that
there are duplicates of each Cylon model.
Anyone seeing either of these two men
at anytime, anywhere in the fleet...
should immediately contact
the Battlestar Galactica...
and the office of the President.
Now I'll take your questions.
They've known about this the whole time
and they tell us now?
Cylon?
- I mean, who's the Cylon now?
- This is too much.
I don't even want to know this.
Excuse me, sir.
Will you come with us, please?
What? Why?
What's going on, Sergeant?
Chief, we need you
to come along as well.
You're arresting the Chief?
Who's arresting him?
- No one is under arrest.
- What's all this?
Step back.
Lieutenant asked you a question, Sergeant.
A Tribunal has been convened...
to look into the Cylon penetration
of our defences.
It requires the presence
of Lt. Valerii and Chief Tyrol.
I am here to escort them
to the Wardroom. Sir.
Very well.
Proceed.
Thank you, sir.
Lieutenant, Chief,
you'll come with me, please.
You're it till I get back. Don't worry.
Lt. Valerii, where were you
at the time of the explosion?
I was in my rack. Asleep.
Did anyone see you, sir?
I don't know. I was asleep.
Lieutenant...
is it true that you and the Chief are involved
in a romantic and physical relationship...
in violation of
the Colonial Code of Military Conduct?
- I thought this was about...
- Just answer the question, please.
Are you and the Chief
involved in a relationship?
No.
The XO ordered us to put a stop to it.
And so we did.
Sir, can you testify
as to the whereabouts...
of Chief Petty Officer Tyrol
at the time of the bombing?
I have no idea where he was.
- Thank you, sir.
- You're excused, Lieutenant.
But I am sure he had nothing to do
with the bombing...
You are excused, Lieutenant.
Bring in the next witness, please.
The testimony you give before
this tribunal may be used...
to adjudicate your guilt or innocence
in the matter under investigation.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The matter being investigated
is first...
how a Cylon,
penetrated Galactica's security system...
and second,
whether one of Galactica's crew members...
aided and abetted this crime through...
conspiracy and collusion with the Cylons.
Collusion with the Cylons?
Do you consent to give
your testimony freely without invoking...
your right to remain silent as provided for
under the 23rd Article of Colonization?
- I do.
- Then let's begin.
They're going after the Chief.
They're going after the Cylons.
- What the hell does that mean?
- Wake up.
The world's changed while you were asleep.
Frak you.
Cylons look like people.
That means anyone. Anyone.
- Not the Chief.
- How do you know?
- I know.
- This is stupid.
You two just don't want to deal with reality.
You want to keep your heads
buried in the sand.
That's exactly what the Cylons want.
For us to turn on each other.
Start getting suspicious, paranoid.
She's right.
If we don't believe in each other
when the heat comes down, we're nothing.
That kind of thinking is over.
It's every man for himself now.
You better watch your backs.
You had the mid-watch
before the bombing, correct?
Yes.
Would you please explain to the tribunal
what you do on watch?
I walk the perimeter
of the Hangar Deck...
the tool rooms, storage facilities.
To make sure all hatches are sealed?
Yes.
That no unauthorised personnel
is poking around where they shouldn't?
That's right. And there was no one
on the Hangar Deck that night.
I believe that's what your log says.
What about the hatch combing
for Causeway C?
- Anybody see you?
- No.
I went through the hatch combing
on C Causeway.
Your log indicates that all hatches
and portals were locked and sealed.
If that's what the log indicates,
then that's the case.
Which would include
the hatch combing for Causeway C?
I don't know where the Sergeant
is going with this.
But they're not related.
What if I told you that...
I found the hatch open after the bombing?
I would say that
I don't know how that's possible.
It's not just any hatch on the Hangar Deck.
It opens onto a causeway which leads
directly to a small arms locker...
where a Marine guard was found dead
at the scene.
The locker was opened
with the correct code.
Do you have the correct code
to that locker, Chief?
Yes, I do, as do dozens of others,
including the guard.
It's possible the Cylon forced the guard
to open it before he killed him.
I want to take this opportunity to state that,
that was an internal security matter.
And this falls under the purview
of the Master at Arms.
And the Master at Arms is Sergeant Hadrian.
Did Lt. Valerii leave
the hatch combing open last night?
I have no idea
who left the hatch combing open last night.
Chief, were you doing paperwork
at the time of the bombing?
- No.
- Were you working on a Viper at that time?
No.
Were you watching a pick-up game
of Pyramid in the mess hall...
at the time of the bombing?
No! As I told you earlier today,
I was asleep in my rack.
Then why do I have
three different statements...
from three of your deckhands...
stating variously that they all saw you
and you were anywhere but in your rack?
Chief Tyrol, where were you
at the time of the bombing?
Were you, in fact,
meeting with a Cylon agent?
I exercise my right under Article 23.
By invoking the 23rd Article at this time,
the tribunal will look on this...
as further evidence of your guilt.
So I will ask you one last time.
Who were you with
at the time of the bombing...
and was this person a Cylon agent?
Your sworn statement
indicates that you were on watch...
at the time of the bombing
and that you saw Chief Tyrol...
- work on one of the Vipers. Is that true?
- Yes, sir.
Specialist, can you explain to us
why Chief Tyrol told us in his testimony...
that he was in his rack asleep
at the time of the bombing?
Speak up, Specialist.
He said that?
Did you see him or didn't you?
Specialist!
No, I did not, sir.
So the Chief did not come
to the Hangar Deck after all?
I don't know.
I left my post.
Excuse me?
I left my post, sir.
I ducked out to get a smoke.
I went to the galley to get some chow.
The Chief...
I mean, I don't know where he was.
I'm sure he was asleep in his rack
just like he said.
You went to the galley?
Yes, sir.
Did you go through
the hatch combing on C Deck?
Well, to get to the galley,
that would be the best way.
Yes, sir, I went through that hatch.
- Did you leave it open?
- I'm not sure.
Yes, sir. I think I did.
The Chief had nothing to do with it.
It was me.
I left my post and I left the hatch open.
It was me. Just me.
You realise, that by leaving the hatch open,
you allowed a Cylon...
to gain access to the small arms locker?
Yes, sir.
Specialist, did Chief Tyrol instruct you
to leave the hatch open deliberately...
as part of a conspiracy to allow the Cylon
to gain access to the small arms locker?
The Chief is innocent. He didn't do anything.
Specialist, did you leave
the hatch open deliberately?
Yes, sir.
Whatever happened, it was me. Just me.
South.
You overestimated his willingness
to risk himself for you.
He just doesn't love you.
Wait.
North. Toward his love.
Seems you made an impression after all.
He's a good man.
He always does the right thing.
Are you prepared for the next step?
Yes.
- Hello, Lieutenant.
- Doctor.
I brought you a cigar. A recovery gift.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
The food is good, company is better.
Yes, I just happened to be
absolutely nowhere near sick bay.
I thought I would...
- see how you were doing.
- So, Doctor...
your super secret project's on C Deck, right?
I'm not at liberty to divulge exactly
what I am doing on C Deck.
But you're more than welcome to pop by.
Once you're ambulatory.
- The bomber was on C Deck, right?
- Yes, I know. I heard the explosion.
- Very frightening.
- Do you think that's where he was headed?
- I'm sorry. I didn't follow you.
- The Cylon bomber?
Do you think that he was trying
to blow up your project?
And you along with it?
It's funny.
I hadn't thought of that.
Kind of hits you where you live, huh?
Yes, it does, actually.
You get well soon.
They're trying to kill me.
Me, always me.
They're trying to destroy your work.
Destroying you is an added bonus.
But why?
I don't understand.
Why are they trying to blow me up?
You told me what to do.
I wouldn't be making
this Cylon detector if it wasn't for you.
But I'm just in your head, Gaius.
They don't know about me or us
or our life together.
How romantic.
I'm going to have to destroy
that Cylon detector myself.
Blame the sabotage on Cylon agents.
That's what I'll tell Adama.
No, you won't.
You're gonna complete the project
just like I told you.
Really? Would I?
Or what?
Don't make me angry, Gaius.
You wouldn't like me when I'm angry.
Sharon.
Is that enough?
No, Sharon wouldn't give up
without a much earned fight.
Did you read the tribunal report?
Yes.
And I'm sorry to read that one of your men
has been charged with conspiracy...
- and collusion with a Cylon agent.
- Specialist Socinus.
But after reading the transcripts
I have my doubts.
What about this other man,
your Chief Tyrol, he took the 23rd?
- What is that about, do you think?
- It's his right.
The courts have never held
that invoking the right to remain silent...
can be used as evidence of guilt.
You sound like a lawyer.
My father was a lawyer. Civil liberties.
Let's set aside the legalities for a moment.
Obviously, you are defending your man.
I respect that, I do.
But he is hiding something.
Chief Tyrol has been under my command
for over five years.
And if he had really wanted
to take this ship down...
he could. This is over.
Madam President,
I'm gonna have to call you right back.
What?
I have orders to bring you
before the tribunal, sir.
Let's go.
It's okay.
Helo.
What's happening?
Can you walk?
I think so.
Come on. I got you. Okay.
Now we're even.
- I think we should go.
- Right. Okay.
Come on.
It's going to be all right.
You're going to be just fine.
Commander Adama, when did you
first learn the truth about the Cylons?
On Ragnar station. Before we left.
And you chose to withhold
this crucial information, sir?
Yes.
Why?
I felt that...
to alarm the public,
would only cause chaos and panic.
But...
you also withheld the information...
from your own security detachment
aboard ship, sir.
Not knowing who to trust,
I decided to keep the information...
compartmentalised for the time being.
Sir, isn't it true that had we known that
the Cylons appeared human...
different security procedures
would have been followed?
Probably.
But I had to weigh
the possible ramifications of both.
Isn't it also true, sir, that
had different procedures been followed...
- the bombing may have been prevented?
- That's speculative.
- I'm asking if it's possible.
- I know what you're asking, Sergeant.
I will not speculate as to
what might have happened.
Do you personally believe that...
a Cylon agent planted explosives
in the ship's water tank?
Yes.
Do you believe that there are Cylon agents
aboard ship even as we speak?
Yes, I do.
Sir, isn't it true that you knew...
that Lt. Valerii and Chief Tyrol
were having an illicit relationship...
in violation of regulations?
I don't see the relevance
of this line of questioning, Sergeant.
The commander should bear in mind...
that my questions are not subject
to the Commander's review.
Why did you allow the relationship
to continue...
knowing it was against regulations?
I'm a soft touch.
Sir, are you aware that
both Lt. Valerii and Chief Tyrol...
have been implicated as possibly being
in collusion with the Cylons?
I'm aware of the allegations.
Where are you going with this?
I will ask the questions, sir.
Isn't it true that by allowing
their relationship to continue...
in violation of regulations...
you may have made it possible
for two Cylon collaborators...
to compromise the safety and security
of this ship?
We're done here.
Excuse me, sir,
but my questions are not finished.
You've lost your way, Sergeant.
You've lost sight of the purpose of the law...
to protect its citizens, not persecute them.
Whatever we are, whatever is left of us.
We're better than that.
Now these proceedings are closed.
You'll be transported back to your ships,
and we appreciate your help.
Commander.
This is an independent board.
You have no authority to close our inquiry.
This is a witch hunt.
I will not have it aboard my ship.
Corporal of the guard!
Restrain the Commander
and return him back to the witness chair.
Your orders are to escort
Sergeant Hadrian back to her quarters...
and keep her in confinement
until further notice.
Make your choice, son.
Sergeant Hadrian,
you'll come with us, please.
She's just about to speak.
Yes, I tried to get an interview
with her myself.
Good evening, have a seat.
The investigation into the suicide bombing
aboard Galactica...
and how it was allowed to occur
has come to a close.
You are all aware that the bomber
was a Cylon agent.
The tribunal has determined...
that the Cylon gained access
to the explosives...
by going through a hatch door
in the Hangar Deck of the ship.
This door was left open due to negligence...
of one of the ship's crewmen.
His name is Specialist Socinus.
He has confessed to lying under oath
and dereliction of duty in a time of war.
He has been stripped of his rank
and confined to the Brig.
At this point, we have no reason to believe...
that there were
any other parties responsible.
Now I'll take your questions. You, sir.
Commander, permission to enter?
What is it, Chief?
Thank you, sir.
Sir, I believe that Socinus...
I believe that his confession was a lie.
I think that he's covering for me.
For you?
I think that he's doing this
out of a sense of misplaced loyalty to me.
Somewhere in this there's truth.
Care to take me to it?
Sir, I was with Lt. Valerii
at the time of the bombing.
The Deck gang, they all knew it.
They've known all along.
They're trying to cover for me.
They started lying. Socinus...
I think that he thinks he's helping
protect me by taking a fall like this.
You don't really know
if he was on duty or not, do you?
Commander, he's innocent.
I know that much. I should be in the Brig.
Well, that's a fact.
You should be in the Brig.
Commander, this isn't right.
- You can't let an innocent kid...
- I can't?
What I can't do...
is I can't let someone
that wears this uniform...
get on the witness stand and lie under oath.
And that's what your man did.
He either lied the first time
or he lied the second time.
And it doesn't matter.
He's guilty and he'll pay the price.
You? You'll pay a different price.
You'll have to walk out
on that Hangar Deck every day...
knowing that one of your men
is in the Brig...
because you couldn't keep your fly zipped.
You're the most experienced,
noncommissioned officer we have left.
You keep my planes flying.
I need my planes to fly.
Dismissed.
Sir.
Sharon, no.
What?
Sharon, we're done. It's over.
- What do you mean it's over?
- I love you.
I really do.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I deserve more of an explanation
than that.
Sure.
One of my men is in the Brig.
He confessed to a crime he didn't commit
to protect me, to protect us.
There can be no more "us. "
No more secrets, no more lies, that's it.
It's over.
I can't believe
you can just turn your back on us.
I put everything on the line for you.
Everything. I cover for you, I protect you.
I risk my career, my freedom,
my integrity, for what?
So some innocent kid,
one of my kids, can take the fall for me?
No!
We are not worth that.
Okay.
Right.
I guess I'll see you around.
One more thing.
Did you leave the hatch combing
open last night?
What?
Did you leave the hatch combing
open last night?
What are you saying?
That I helped the Cylon?
I didn't say anything.
I'm just asking a question.
I think I deserve an answer.
You have the only answer
you're ever gonna get.