Mum died three years ago.
She had a double mastectomy,
but never really recovered.
So why do you think your father
suggested you come for counselling?
Because my mother died
and he can't talk about it.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Get your hands off my miscarriage!
- I'm sorry for your loss.
- What?
- Your baby.
- Oh.
So, there is a particular person
you're not having sex with?
He's not available.
I believe God meant for me
to love people as a father.
I'll go up to three.
No-one's asked me a
question in 45 minutes...
So, what do you do?
You'll always be interesting
with your quirky cafe
and your dead best friend.
Celibacy is a lot less complicated
than romantic relationships.
But what if you meet someone you like?
I talk and drink and laugh
and give them Bibles
and hope they eventually leave me alone.
What if you meet someone you love?
We're not going to have sex.
I'd really like to be
your friend, though.
I'd like to be your friend too.
What makes you a normal person?
Well, I don't believe in God...
I love it when he does that.
I don't know.
Just come out.
- I prefer the last one.
- Me too.
- It's a bit more subtle.
- Elegant, yeah.
- It's these bits, isn't it?
- Yep.
- Yep, last one, definitely.
- Yep. Great.
- Really pleased with that!
- Yeah.
- Once it's nipped in there...
- Oh, it'll be perfect.
His arms.
- Do you prefer weddings or funerals?
- Weddings.
His arms.
I think there's something
humbling about funerals.
Really?
Yeah, it's good to dwell
on the next life.
You really think there's a next life?
What do you believe? Worm food?
- Why?!
- Why what?
His neck.
Why would you believe in something
awful when you could
believe in something wonderful?
Don't make me an optimist,
you will ruin my life.
- Have you been to many funerals?
- A couple.
His neck.
And you've never felt them go somewhere?
No, they were already gone.
His beautiful neck.
What?
You just said, "His beautiful neck".
No, I said that they'd already gone.
Okay. Weird.
Oh, right, so...
This might be your idea of hell...
...but I think it's kind of special.
His beautiful neck.
Quaker meeting.
You're not allowed to speak.
If the Spirit moves you to speak,
you have to stand up
and share it with everyone.
It's very intense.
It's very quiet.
It's very, very...
...erotic.
Oh.
I think...
I'm going to go home in November.
I think.
What's he thinking?
I don't really think it's...
I'm not really feeling the...
I don't think it's really
affecting me...
Oh, my...
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
What am I going to say?
I sometimes worry
that I wouldn't be such a feminist
if I had bigger tits.
[HE CHUCKLES]
- Well, it's good you felt something.
- Is it?
Something moved you.
I'm not sure I needed to me
moved to discover that about myself.
What were you thinking?
I was thinking about how peaceful
I felt and then for some reason,
I was thinking about your tits,
which kind of ruined it.
- Oh, my tits ruined your peace?
- Yeah. You could say that.
[THEY LAUGH]
- I should probably open the cafe...
- I've got a confession actually...
- Oh, can I see it?
- Uh...
Oh, yeah...
It's a bit...
What?
- It's a bit...
- What...
...the fuck?
[HE LAUGHS]
Hello.
Oh, you gorgeous little thing.
[GUINEA PIG SQUEAKS]
Can I ask, um,
why so many guinea pigs?
Oh, um...
I just, um...
This is an excellent one.
I just thought it'd be
a unique selling point.
Yeah.
Which came first, the guinea pig
or the guinea pig cafe?
That is a big, old question.
Fair enough.
What do guinea pigs do?
They are born, they shit themselves
with fear and then they die.
[HE LAUGHS]
Can I use that at the wedding?
Seriously, I need material.
Tell me about your stepmother-to-be.
Any... What's she like?
Oh, she's, um...
- she's from Exeter.
- Mm.
Okay, thank you, that's very helpful.
- How did she meet your dad?
- Through my mother.
Right.
She was my mother's
student at one point.
- Do your parents get on?
- No.
- Were you close to your mum?
- Yeah.
You?
Not really.
- How come?
- So, that must've been a bit weird?
I don't really think about it.
[GUINEA PIG SQUEAKS]
- So, you run... No, no.
- Do you go back a lot to...
Do you run this place on your own?
- No, I opened it with a friend.
- Oh, cool, right.
- So, you run it together?
- No, she's...
...she, uh...
She what?
What?
- What?
- She... she what?
She...
[THEY LAUGH]
He's a bit annoying actually.
What is that?
What?
That thing that you're doing.
It's like you disappear.
- What?
- What are you not telling me?
Nothing!
Tell me what going on underneath there.
- Nothing!
- Tell me, come on!
- No!
- You can tell me.
- Nothing! Nothing!
- Argh! What are you doing?!
- Stop being so churchy.
- I'm not being churchy.
- I'm just trying to get to know you.
- Well, I don't want that.
Listen, I'm just trying to help you.
What?
No. No, I didn't mean...
Oh, I know what you mean, Father.
Thank you so much for your guidance.
Come on, I didn't mean...
I really should get back to work.
A customer's bound to turn
up any minute.
And you should be getting back to
God, don't you think?
I think you played with my guinea
pig long enough.
[HE SIGHS]
Okay.
All right, bye.
Sorry, girls.
People are starting to arrive.
She was a spectacular woman.
Don't worry. We can sort this out.
Stop doing that to your face.
No, I have to.
I don't know what's wrong!
I just...
I look so good.
It's okay. We can sort it out.
Just... Take some of your makeup off.
I'm not wearing any makeup.
What?
What has happened?
- I have never seen you look so good.
- I don't know, I just woke up...
...looking amazing and then
everyone's going to think
I got a fucking facial
for my mother's funeral.
Oh, what the hell? You look incredible.
We're trying to mess her up.
No matter what I do to my hair,
it just keeps falling in this
really chic way.
Oh, God.
- You look perfect.
- Thank you.
Sorry, girls. People are starting to
arrive.
Thank you.
You don't have to greet
them if it's too...
Gosh, you look gorgeous.
Thank you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Thank you.
- You look glorious.
- Have you spoken to Dad?
- No, not yet.
He's avoiding me.
My deepest condolences, girls.
She was magnificent.
BOTH: Thanks so much.
- My God, you look well.
Thank you. Have you?
No, he's not really engaging.
She was a spectacular woman.
- Thanks.
- Darling, you look wonderful.
Oh, my God.
- Hi, Claire.
- Hi.
Gosh. Grief clearly agrees with you.
Thank you, Jeremy.
Oh. Incoming.
How are you doing?
My God, she's shameless.
Can you not think the fucking
worst of someone for just a split
fucking second?
Not everyone is after cock.
She's definitely trying to fuck my dad.
Well, she ain't made of wood.
Do you want a ciggie?
Ooh, incoming.
Hi, Harry.
Hi. Hi.
- You okay?
- Mm-hm.
You?
Do you need anything?
No, I'm good thanks. I've just
had a large glass of water.
Are your trousers okay?
Yeah, sorry, I left them in the drier.
Ah, mate.
Ah, shit, sorry.
It's okay.
It's just funerals when you actually
knew the person...
They're so...
It just doesn't feel real.
I'm just going to miss her so much.
[HE SNIFFS]
- Have you cried yet?
- Yes.
But I didn't see you cr...
Wow, you look..
Have you had your eyebrows done?
Hi, girls. How you doing?
- All right.
- Okay, thanks.
You know, the hard bit's going to
come in a few weeks
when it all calms down.
- Yeah, I have heard.
- They do say that, yeah.
When people start to forget
and the cards and the
flowers stop turning up.
- Yeah.
- Uh-huh, yeah.
And people just disappear
because it spooks them
to be around someone
perpetually in pain.
- Okay.
- Right.
And your lovely boyfriends might
not be able to cope.
- Well, he's my husband...
- I'm sure they'll push through.
I just want you to know that
I will always be there for you, always.
- Always.
- Thank you.
Always.
I'm going to check on the sausagerolls.
Okay.
See?
Hey.
I don't know how you're eating.
Do something.
Hi.
Oh. Hello, darling.
- Bit tight.
- Oh, yeah.
Tell me about it.
I found her very difficult, you know.
I know.
I loved her, but, um...
- That's all that really matters.
- No, I don't think it is.
Her instincts were...
She just knew how to be fun.
How to be kind.
She just knew.
I'm just guessing.
You're fun, Dad.
No, I didn't like that about her.
I loved her, but I didn't like
that she was...
For a long time, I...
And today...
...I was jealous of her.
[HE CHUCKLES]
That is a lovely thing to say, really.
Oh, sorry.
I'll leave you two.
- She's a bit annoying, isn't she?
- Mm.
Look, let's go and find your sister.
Yeah, I don't think she wants to see me.
She loves you.
She just didn't get the fun gene.
[THEY LAUGH]
[SHE SNIFFS]
I just...
- I don't know what to...
- I know.
Buck up.
Smile.
Charm.
Off we go.
We'll be okay.
I'll follow you.
You look lovely, by the way.
Thank you.
I don't know what to do with it.
With what?
With all the love I have for her.
I don't know where to put it now.
- I'll take it.
- [FLEABAG LAUGHS]
No, I'm serious.
It sounds lovely.
I'll have it.
- You have to give it to me.
- Okay.
It's got to go somewhere.
- [J. Lopez's "Jenny From The Block"]
- ♪ Children grow and women producing ♪
♪ Men go working, some go stealing ♪
♪ Everyone's got to make a living ♪
♪ L O X, yeah ♪
♪ J. Lo, yeah ♪
♪ We off the block this year ♪
♪ Went from a little to
a lot this year ♪
♪ Don't be fooled by
the rocks that I got ♪
♪ I'm still, I'm still Jenny
from the block ♪
♪ Used to have a little,
now I have a lot ♪
♪ No matter where I go,
I know where I came from... ♪
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- Oh, fuck! Fuck! Jesus!
Why are you awake? It's 9:45!
Oh, my God! I thought you were
just in my head, then!
But, I mean, you were in my head, then.
But now you're there!
[CHUCKLES]
You okay, Father?
Ah, fuck, you calling me "Father"
like it doesn't turn
you on just to say it.
- Do you want a drink?
- Okay.
Don't move.
Are you a nostalgic person?
Yeah.
- Do you like Winnie the Pooh?
- Yeah.
I fucking love Winnie the Pooh.
I can't read a Winnie the Pooh
quote without crying.
Fuck.
Piglet.
Why are you here?
Sorry, but I mean why, why are you...
Were you looking for me?
I was on the verge of having
a little prayer, actually.
[HE CHUCKLES]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't, don't you... That's my thing.
What were you praying about?
Please say you were praying for me.
I could do with the extra pair of hands.
Mine don't seem to have the
fucking reach any more.
God help me!
Whoa!
- Thank you.
- [CHUCKLES]
Do you know there was a man who
wanted to be a saint
so badly he castrated himself just
to stop himself?
You know... whack!
Wow!
Here's to peace.
And those who get in the way of it.
I'm sorry about today.
Forget it.
Look at this.
Look at it.
That's the first one I ever got.
Went all the way to Rome for that.
Such a nerd!
Two years before I was even allowed
to wear it, but I just...
I couldn't wait.
I couldn't wait! I knew I wanted a bold,
you know, this colour, but proper plum.
You can only get proper plum in Italy.
Sometimes I worry I'm
only in it for the outfits.
So beautiful, isn't it?
I mean, your stuff is lovely, too.
What were you praying about?
You don't like answering
questions, do you?
Okay.
Come with me.
I know what to do with you.
You go in there, I go in there.
And you make me tell you all my secrets
so you can ultimately trap
and control me?
- Yeah. No.
- [LAUGHS]
You tell me what's weighing
on your heart
and I listen without judgment
- and in complete confidence.
- Sounds dodgy!
I just listen.
At the very least it'll
shut me up for a minute.
- I'm not Catholic.
- Tonight, that doesn't matter.
Won't I catch fire or something?
If you did, it would confirm
my faith, so let's try it.
Go on.
All right.
Okay, now you say, "Bless me
father for I have sinned."
- I'm not going to say that!
- Well, very good.
"It's been..."
Uh, enter days, years, months
- "...since my last confession."
- Mm-hmm.
Then I say, "That's okay,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah",
till you tell me what's on your mind.
Tell me your ssss...
- Sins.
- Sins, if you want. [CHUCKLES]
- Why would I tell you my sins?
- Because it will make you feel better!
And because I want to know.
[THEY BOTH CHUCKLE]
Okay.
I lied.
To you.
- About?
- About the miscarriage.
I was just covering for my sister
who actually had the miscarriage,
because her husband didn't know
she was pregnant, and it just...
Okay.
Keep going.
And I've stolen things.
I've had a lot of sex
outside of marriage.
And once or twice inside someone else's.
And there's been a spot of sodomy.
Um, there's been much masturbation,
a bit of violence, and of course
the endless fucking blasphemy.
[HE CHUCKLES]
And?
And...
- Go on.
- And...
I...
...I can't...
It's okay, go on.
- Frightened.
- Of what?
Forgetting things.
People.
Forgetting people.
And I'm ashamed of not knowing what I...
What you want?
It's okay not to know what you want.
No, I know what I want. I know
exactly what I want right now.
What's that?
It's bad.
It's okay.
I want someone to tell me
what to wear in the morning.
[HE LAUGHS]
Okay, well, I think
there are people who can...
No, I want someone to tell me
what to wear every morning.
I want someone to tell me what to eat,
what to like, what to hate,
what to rage about,
what to listen to, what band to like,
what to buy tickets for,
what to joke about,
what not to joke about.
I want someone to tell me
what to believe in,
who to vote for,
and who to love,
and how to... tell them.
I just think I want someone to tell me
how to live my life, Father,
because so far I think
I've been getting it wrong.
And I know that's why people want
people like you in their lives.
Because you just tell them how to do it.
You just tell them what to do,
and what they'll get
out of the end of it.
Even though I don't believe
your bullshit, and I know that
scientifically nothing I do makes
any difference in the end anyway,
I'm still scared!
Why am I still scared?!
So just tell me what to do.
Just fucking tell me what to do, Father!
Kneel.
What?
Just kneel.
[CHORAL MUSIC PLAYS]
- Is this a skirt and trousers?
- Sorry, sorry.
[PANTING]
[LOUD THUD]
[CHORAL MUSIC PLAYS]