This programme contains strong
language and adult humour.
I opened a cafe with my friend, Boo.
Yeah, she's dead now.
Thank you for coming in today.
That kind of thing won't get
you very far here any more.
Oh! Argh!
I suppose you should meet Hillary.
She's beautiful!
Mum died three years ago.
Loo, doo, ooh, badoo!
All right, Dad?
Dad's way of coping with two
motherless daughters was to buy us
tickets to feminist lectures,
start fucking our godmother,
and eventually stop calling.
Did you take the sculpture?
What sculpture?
Martin's being lovely.
I am not drunk. Always drunk.
Jake's her step-son. He's really
weird, probably clinically,
but no-one really talks about that.
No. I got the Finland promotion.
That's amazing! Thank you.<
People make mistakes.
Your husband tried to kiss
me on your birthday.
I'm just going to say this once.
He didn't try to kiss you.
He says it was more like the other
way around. Believe me!</f
How can I believe you?
Because I'm your sister!
After what you did to Boo?
I'm sorry. I think you should go.
♪ Strangers in the night
♪ Exchanging glances
♪ Wondering in the night
♪ What were the chances
♪ We'd be sharing love
♪ Before the night was through? ♪
KNOCK ON DOOR
Can I do anything?
No, thank you.
They've gone. So...
♪ Was so exciting
♪ Something in my heart... ♪
Thank you.
♪ ..told me I must have you. ♪
This is a love story.
You know when you've done
everything? When you've been all...
Squat! Squat! Squat! Squat!</font
..and...
You've even...
Do you want to have sex?
No!
Can I at least go down on you? No!
You've done everything,
and you feel great.
You're not even thinking about...
You don't even think about...
And even though your sister
still hates you... Thank you.</fo
..you're pretending to be friends
because your dad is...
I'm joking, he's just there...
Here's to love.
..and engaged.
ALL: To love!
Love. Hey!
Urgh.
Congratulations, you assholes!
THEY LAUGH
HE TAPS A GLASS
STAMMERING: So, it means a great
deal to both of us
that you, that we,
the family, are...
..are all...
..together here for a very special
family, er...
..gang-bang, um...
TENTATIVE LAUGHTER
It's just, you know, being here...
..you know, I know we've had our...
Cos I...
I have the feeling, um...
..in... here...
So I just want to say...
..very much.
And that's it. Oh, darling!
Congratulations, Dad.
Congratulations! Cheers.
May these be the worst of our days.
Don't know who this guy is.
Happy for you, old boy.
Best decision a man can make.
Urgh.
You look well. Thank you.
Right. Wine, everyone?
I'd love some wine.
Oh, you'll adore it. I chose it.
Not for us, thanks.
Off the sauce!
Six months and counting.
Why would you do that? We just...
AT SAME TIME: Don't want to miss a thing.
<font color
THEY LAUGH
I haven't seen her since...
Except for...
Nice jumpsuit. Thank you.
You look well, where've you been?
Boots.
It's lovely there this time of year.
Oh, you look fantastic.
Oh, well, you both look gorgeous!
Oh, thank you. Is that fur?
Yes, but it's OK
because it had a stroke.
Oh, lovely!
LAUGHTER
I can't go to hell for
that, can I, Father?
No. Not as long as you confess.
Oh, God, he's their priest.
Then you've nothing to fucking worry
about! Their cool, swea
Love the Catholics! You can get away
with anything. A lot of
LAUGHTER
It's an honour to be marrying
you two. Thank you.
I didn't realise you were allowed
out without your little doggy thing.
Oh, sorry, have I disappointed you?
Of course not. Devastated.
Can I get you another bottle?
Needy waitress. Ah, no, it's all
right. We've already order
Oh, no, really?
I'll have another tequila.
I'll have a tequila.
Great, thank you so much.
Can I get a glass of sparkling water
with a dash of lime, please?
Oh, yes, I'll have the same.
Dream team.
THEY CHUCKLE SMUGLY
You know the most fascinating
thing about Father here,
is that his mother was
originally a lesbi...!
SHE SIGHS
You do look tired.
Oh, it's not as exhausting as I
thought it would be, actually.
She's commuting from Finland.
She has narrowed down her packing
to a ten-minute turnaround.
It's... Fabulous! It's all about...
Rolling it up, rather than...
Folding it.
I read about that. Now, are you sure
you don't want any wine?
Oh, no, thank you!
It really is delicious.
I admire you both so much.
Well, it's really turned us around,
hasn't it, honey?
Oh, so much more energy.
You know, in Finland...
Is there a reason that you're not
drinking? He's an alcohol
Oh, fun, my parents are alcoholics.
Oh, great.
We thought it'd be easier
if we did it together,
and I don't really like the taste...
And we are trying for a baby!
Oh, Claire!
We thought you couldn't have them!
What? Why?
Well, you just seem a little...
Well, they say a lifestyle change
can help, so here we go.
That is so exciting, darling.
Thanks, Dad.
Good luck. That's wonderful.
Something's up. And now you have the
money to pay for proper
Ghastly without help, I imagine.
Tell us about Finland.
Oh, well, it's, um...
..cold and beautiful and dark.
I think she might be happy.
It's a lot of pressure, but I love
it. I have this amazing new partner
out there, he's really pushed the
company forward...
I can't remember the last time we
went away.
Weren't you both in Japan recently?
Japan, wow. Oh, yes, but that was
just a little fortnight.</f
Don't ask her!
Why were you in Japan?
Well, the... I was...
Oh, sorry, darling.
Oh, no, no. Thank you.
They flew us over
with the Sexhibition.
HE INTERRUPTS
Sorry, darling, do you want to...?
No, no, no. No? Oh.
You see, you think of the Japanese
as a very prudish people.
Not to generalise.
But actually they have a very deep
interest in sex in their culture,
it's just hidden in the underbelly.
It's not allowed to come to the
surface. Fair enough.
TALKING OVER EACH OTHER: They really...
The honesty of the</f
The Americans, oh, well... Well,
they just took me in their s
But the Japanese were deeply moved
by my work, I think.
Weren't they, darling? Yeah.
It caused quite a cultural wave
A ripple.
Wave.
No-one's asked me a question
in 45 minutes. So what do you d
Er, I run a cafe.
Oh, wow.
It's going well, is it?
Yes, it is. It really is.
It actually is.
It is.
HE LAUGHS
Can I get anyone any ice?
Fellow smoker.
Do you have a spare one? Sure.
So, do your family get
together much, or...?
Fuck you, then.
We should wait.
OK.
He's such a lovely man. Yes.
THEY TALK OVER EACH OTHER</font
Did you have a cigarette? Yeah.
I just, I wish you
could've seen him in...
You know, they can't even
masturbate!
Shit alive, man. Oh, sorry.
We were just saying, it's
fascinating,
the notion of a calling.
Yeah, well, marriage
is a calling, too, of course.
Did you always want to join the
priesthood? Oh, fuck, no.</fo
THEY LAUGH
Sorry.
No, no, no. I came quite late to it,
actually, but it's been a really
good life to me.
I've really found peace in it.
Is anyone in your family
in the Church?
Actually, both my parents
are lawyers and my brother
is a long-distance lorry driver.
How unusual!
Are your parents successful?
They were very successful
alcoholics, yeah.
THEY LAUGH
Better than you, anyway.
No, but beyond them,
my family's literally crawling
with nuns, so it wasn't
too much of a leap.
Must be hard on the balls.
LAUGHTER Martin!
Not as hard on them as trying to
make a baby for five months,
I imagine. Food good?
This sauce is disgusting.
Is everything OK?
Oh, it's delicious, thank you.
Delicious. Lovely, lovely.
Um, darling...
No, no. We'll just pour our
own wine, please.
Oh, I actually love doing...
Thank you.
You can pour me some. Oh, thank you.
So, do you do a lot
of older weddings?
I don't think that's how we...
No, this is my first-ever wedding,
actually.
ALL: Oh!
Do you know, I've always
been so suspicious of religion,
but I must say, I think there's
something rather chic
about having a real
priest at a wedding.
HE CHUCKLES
Are you a real priest?
Yeah.
Do you know, it's so nice spending
time getting to know the man
who's going to marry us.
Is that usual?
No, but I'm new to the parish,
and I guess I'm just...
HE LAUGHS
I'm really fucking lonely!
LAUGHTER
So I appreciate this.
Thank you very much.
New to the parish?
Father Patrick sadly died,
so I got the gig.
What did he die of?
Just, um, time.
But he was a dedicated man,
he was a brilliant priest.
Sounds like a riot.
He was, actually.
Do you know how we met?
No. Through Jake.
Creepy step-son.
He plays the flute...
ALL: The bassoon.
..in the church band. Just adorable!
And Claire introduced us
and we just hit it off.
Didn't we? We did, yeah.
They did.
She's donating a painting for the
fete, it's going to cause
quite the stir!
Oh, it's just an old one.
Now, listen, um, we don't want
gifts at the wedding.
I mean, it's enough
that people slug it over
without then expecting a gift.
So we've decided to ask people
to make a small donation,
to a charity of their
choosing, in our name.
That sounds lovely.
Do you want to know what gift
I'm giving your father? Oh, Go
It's a portrait... Oh, God.
..of you girls. Oh, God. Um...
You mean...? Together, or...?
I'd only need a couple of sittings.
Right. Can't you use photos?
No, because the lighting's
never good enough,
and if you're not very photogenic
then it does you no favours.
And besides, the only photos
there are of you two together
are of when you were children,
and you looked like a boy, so...
You never told me you had a sister,
Claire. Oh, well, we, um.
We don't get to see each other much.
Do you see your brother?
Oh, I don't really
speak to my brother.
Oh, God, how desperately sad!
Why is that? Oh. Um, well...
You don't have to... No, that's OK.
Does he not approve of what you do,
of your choices?
No, it's not that, it's not that.
Is he not in the Church?
No, he's not in the Church.
Oh, it must be so hard!
Well, it's mainly hard...
Is it cos he's Mummy's favourite?
..because he's a paedophile.
Oh.
I'm aware of the irony of that.
LAUGHTER
Just a... Just a breath of air, eh?
Interesting man.
Mm.
No, thanks.
Darling, I'm sorry
I missed your birthday,
so I just got... Oh, that's OK.
No, no. I just...
In case you're struggling.
Oh, Dad, the cafe's going well...
No, no, this is not for work.
It's just for you.
Thanks.
You look, er...
..strong.
LAUGHING: Thanks.
Are you?
SHE LAUGHS
Are we going to have a fight?!
No, no! I'm sorry, no.
I just want to check that...
..that you and I are...
Well, you're being very...
You're not being naughty.
SHE LAUGHS
No! Why? Oh...
Because, I guess...
Yeah?
..it doesn't matter.
Oh.
OK. Is that right?
I'm happy for you, Dad.
Thank you.
Ah! Thank you.
You're an exceptional waitress.
Apple juice?
Yeah.
I...
I just wanted to say,
I am so intrigued to see
how you're going to make this whole
evening about yourself.
HE LAUGHS
Oh, no.
We probably shouldn't arrive
at the table together.
A lot of people would say praying
is just talking to yourself
in the dark.
HE CHUCKLES
I guess it could look
like that, but, no,
it's more just about connecting
with yourself
at the end of each day.
It takes a bit of effort, but...
Yes, yes, I completely agree.
Positive energy takes work.
In the last six months,
I've excelled.
I take all the negative emotions
and just bottle them and bury them
and they never come out.
I'm not sure...
I've basically never been better.
Us neither.
I feel fantastic!
You're a very positive family,
I must say. Oh, absolutely.</
I think it's all about positivity.
It takes real commitment
to be this happy.
It's not just about eating
and drinking well, either.
Putting pine nuts on your salad
doesn't make you a grown-up.
Fucking does. It's about...
Well, in Finland, we, um...
They have this saying,
which I can't quite remember now...
It's, um... It's about
opening yourself up to the people
who want to love you.
And she is wide open lately.
THEY CHUCKLE
What do you do?
Oh, I work in finance.
What? What?
Across two firms, one
in Finland and one here.
No, no, she's a lawyer.
I thought you were a lawyer?
No. What?
I work with lawyers,
I'm not a lawyer.
Darling, you are a solicitor.
I went to business school.
You're being so quiet!
Why aren't you saying anything?
What do you want me to say?
Anything!
What's that in your hand?
She doesn't need to...
Birthday present from Dad.
It's a good thing, Claire.
Chunk of change? No, it's, er...
What is it? Don't know.
You don't need to...
I love presents,
I never get presents.
Well, it's because you might...
It's a voucher -
for a counselling session.
Thanks, Dad.
MARTIN LAUGHS
So thoughtful!
I'd kill for one of those!
I don't believe you can
pay your problems away,
I think you have to face who you are
and suffer the consequences.
It's the only road to happiness.
Maybe happiness isn't in what you
believe but who you believe.
Fuck.
Excuse me.
Oh! Do you think she needs anything?
ALL: No.
That was meant to be
a bedroom present.
A what? A present that you open in
your bedroom, alone.</font
All my presents are bedroom
presents, aren't they?
HE CHUCKLES
Do you want some more wine? Oh, yes.
No, actually.
Claire?
You've been ages.
Are you pissed off or
are you doing a poo?
SHE WHISPERS: Fuck. Fuck it.
Claire, can we just...
Have you got a... sanitary towel?
Oh, no, but I know a waitress
who would jump on that request.
Do you want me to ask her? No!
OK, well, there are some
sturdy hand towels here.
I could try and fashion something
with wings out of these.
Yes, fine.
Open the door.
Fuck, just give it...
Fuck! Give it to me! Don't come in!
It's a period!
It's not going to bite me!
Don't look at it!
I'm not looking at your period!
Just take this.
Oh, God. It's not a period, it's a
fucking miscarriage, OK?
Jesus, Claire!
It's OK. No, it's not OK, you need
to go to a hospital!</fo
It's fine, I just need the...
Let me just... No!
SHOUTING: Just get your hands off my
miscarriage!
SHE SIGHS It's mine.
It's mine.
DOOR SLAMS
SHE EXHALES
TOILET FLUSHES
OK.
Claire.
It's OK. It's OK.
OK, we need to go to a hospital now.
Now.
Yes.
OK. OK.
CLAIRE SIGHS
Come on.
It's all good. OK.
Don't tell anyone. OK.
Let's get the coats,
I'll get a taxi.
I'll tell them I don't feel right.
OK. Thank you. <f
I've never been there, I get
antiques from there all the time.
I still haven't gone. Oh, really?
It'd be a wonderful place
to buy things like that. Yeah.</fo
MARTIN LAUGHS
I don't like all the water...
Fuck it, I'm having some.
Sorry, darling.
HE LAUGHS
Oh, good girl! Have one night off.
Wow! What did you say to her?
I, um...
Oh, nothing. I just, er...
Just sit down.
Come on, it's a party.
Can I have some?
Oh, someone's suddenly getting
into the party spirit now!
Sit down!
What did you take in there?
Your sister is finally
a good influence on you.
No, we just suddenly realised what a
monumental fucking day this is!
Drink. Honestly, just leave them in
there two minutes
and they're suddenly being
teenagers again!
LAUGHTER
Shall I get another bottle? Yes!
OK! Where's the waitress?
We were just talking about Venice,
and this wonderful trip we had...
How many times have we said
we have to go to Venice?
I've always wanted to go there.
Top of my list.
It's great. Yeah, I know...
SHOUTS: Oh, for fuck's sake,
stop it!
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm, er...
Er... Is, um... Is it...?
No, I'm sorry, I just...
Here we go. Sorry, I just...
What's happened? Nothing's happened.
What's happened?</fon
Something's happened. Come on!
Come on!
Well, spit it out.
I just had a little...
Just say it. I just a little...
THEY ALL TALK OVER EACH OTHER
I just... What, darling?
I had a little miscarriage.
Oh, my God. What?
Um... What the fuck?
Er... How far gone were you?
You should go to the hospital.
Whose was it?
Maybe leave that for later.
Was it the tooth man? Hospital, n
What about the bill? Sit down.
No, I'll cover her, I'll cover you.
She doesn't want to go! Why?!
Cos I'm stubborn,
and for some inexplicable reason
I'd rather stay here and have
a passive-aggressive party, so.
How far gone were you?
It was VERY early stages. You knew?
I really think she should see a
doctor. Yeah, so do I.
I thought you hadn't spoken?
She's fine. She's absolutely fine!
Drink. If it's gone, it's gone!
Claire... What if it's not gone?
It's gone. Darling...
Probably ectopic. Awful.
I'll pay you back.
Do you need someone to go with you?
No, I think I'll just deal with this
in my own insane, irrational,
anal way, if that's OK.
CHUCKLING: That's probably for
the best. <font color=
Ignore him, he's been drinking.
What?
You know, it's like a goldfish out
the bowl, sort of thing.
If it didn't want to be in there,
it didn't want to be in there -
something wasn't right.
What?
It's the kid's choice if it wants to
jump ship, right?
Now, Martin, just... Either way...
..she got her spotlight.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the fuck?! Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
Jeez... Jesus Chr...!
Is there anything I can do...?
SHE SCREAMS
CLAIRE GASPS
THEY ALL GROAN
Fuck! Argh...
SHOUTS: Oh, for God's sake!
KNOCK ON DOOR
Can I do anything?
No, thank you.
They've gone. So...
Thank you.
Fucking hell...
Oh, hey.
I got your stuff. You OK?
Yeah, are you OK? Yeah, yeah.
If you ever need someone to talk to,
or, you know, be there...
..I'm always there.
Hey!
OUT OF BREATH: Thank you.
Just tell him where you live
and we'll talk about this tomorrow.
Can you take us to the nearest
hospital, please? Yeah.
The priest is quite hot. So hot.