Got you! Broken arm!
Broken nose!
Gonna flip you!
Once a year, Dwight holds a seminar,
updating us on the developments
in the world of karate,
because,
the one thing that thousand-year-old
martial arts do all the time
is change.
How can I
pose this to you in a relatable way?
You are all members of the Yakuza,
and you happen to be visiting
the Lackawanna trolley museum,
and you are attacked by Triads.
How can you hold them off
until your clan arrives?
You cannot go wrong
with a throat punch.
So there's no defense for that?
Good to know.
No, there is a defense for that.
Let me demonstrate.
Someone attack me. Kevin, go!
No way.
Last time, you pulled my pants down,
and then you tried to choke me
with my shoelace.
False. I did choke you
with your shoelace.
Come at me!
With all due respect to everyone here,
I think the most worthy opponent of you
is you.
That is correct,
unless there happen to be
measles present.
So let's just say that Dwight
has come at you with the throat punch.
Now, how would you, Dwight,
defend against it?
Easy. Allow me to demonstrate.
I am attacking myself
with a throat punch.
Here it comes.
Block.
Grasp wrist as such.
And with the other hand?
He does have two.
Good point.
Second throat punch.
Absorb the blow.
Groin punch.
Hit, block, elbow to the gut!
Up to the nose! No, you're not!
My God,
he's making you look like such a fool.
He really is, but not for long.
Instep!
Not again!
You let go!
You're right! I can't hold on!
You are so evenly matched,
who's gonna get the upper hand?
The important thing to remember,
we always have
what is called the element
of surprise.
- Feygnasse Team -
.:: La Fabrique ::.
Collioure
Jarick
loky
Sk0r
yomoy
The Ni.Knight
Episode 6x09
Murder
But I would say my favorite art form
is a tie between sculpting
and stand-up comedy.
I did stand-up comedy once.
I killed.
- That sounds like it was hilarious.
- It was hilarious.
What is the meaning of this email
that everyone got?
You'll have to be more specific.
I get like eight emails a day.
This one. "From David Wallace,
to all Dunder Mifflin."
Shout-out.
"I'm sure you've seen
the item in the journal.
"Just want to stress
it's all conjecture.
"If there's any concrete news,
you will know A.S.A.P."
Do we have the journal?
Your journal? You told me
to put it in a time capsule.
Did you?
He means
the Wall Street Journal online.
The Wall.
I found the article.
"On a day marked by panicked
corporate board meetings,
"one that is relatively unsurprising
is Dunder Mifflin's.
"It is rumored
that they will recommend..."
and the article cuts off.
It's $1.99 to finish the article.
I wonder what it was gonna say.
Are you serious?
I got it.
Tuna beat me to it.
"It is rumored that they will
recommend declaring bankruptcy"?
That doesn't make any sense.
Lord, we're all gonna lose our jobs.
Bankruptcy could mean
a lot of things.
Maybe they're just restructuring
to get out of debt.
That sounds awful.
Or it could mean
the end of Dunder Mifflin.
That's an interesting theory.
You know what?
You can all have jobs
at Schrute farms...
as human scarecrows.
It doesn't pay much
and you can't unionize.
I'm sorry. David's in a meeting.
Maybe you should spy on him.
My God!
Wouldn't that be hilarious?
I'll just have him call you back.
Good.
I'll catch you on the flippity-flip.
He's busy.
Call me back when he's free.
Michael, are you okay?
Did you throw up in there?
No, just poopin'.
You know how I be.
But it smells like throw-up in here.
Crazy world, lotta smells.
What if this is
our last day at work?
What if we never see
each other ever again?
I like Erin.
There, I said it.
I was hoping she would ask me out,
but things have not
panned out on that front, so...
It is time for the Nard-Dog
to take matters into his own paws.
We have to do something,
because people are losin' it out there.
We need some sort of distraction
for everybody.
Anything new in YouTube?
Doesn't even need to be good.
I can't think. I need more Mullins.
Wallace said
these were just rumors, right?
So we have no reason to think
at the company's anything but fine.
So if we just go on with our work,
you and me, they'll follow along.
Monkey see, monkey do.
- Monkey pee all over you.
- That rhymes.
So what have we on the docket today?
We have a...
a monthly staff meeting.
All right!
Let's conference room it up!
Here's the deal.
There is no new information as of yet,
so I suggest we keep working.
Sure, I'm a little nervous,
but work will make us feel better.
I only slack off
when things are good.
Customers have to use
the coupon code from the website.
There is no differentiation
between the letter "o"
and the zero,
but we are working on that.
- Stay tuned for that.
- He needs me.
- Seat-save infinity.
- Okay, great.
Also...
What?
- What?
- What happened?
- Is there news?
- There has been a murder!
What?
There's been a murder...
in Savannah.
Games have
the power to distract people
from stressful situations.
"Battleship" got me
through my parents' divorce.
"Operation" got me
through my vasectomy,
i.e. my operation.
I don't think
I would have been able
to endure my break-up with Holly
had it not been for "Toss Across."
"Belles, Bourbon and Bullets.
A murder mystery dinner party game."
It is so much fun.
Everybody plays a character,
we go around the room,
we try to figure out who did it.
I'm wondering if this is a...
- terrible idea.
- This is my call, Jim.
Big picture stuff.
It's about murder.
I thought we agreed
that we wouldn't do things like this.
Tube City. You owe me one.
Co-managing is a give and take.
You have to pick your battles.
One of the battles that I picked
was to stop Michael
from running plastic tubes
all over the office
and placing hamsters inside of them.
He was gonna call it Tube City.
So, yes...
I do owe him one.
August 5th, 1955.
It's a sad day
down here in Savannah.
Local magnate Bill Bourbon
was killed last night,
and all y'all have congregated tonight
for a meal to celebrate Bill
as he passes on to his great reward.
But you're not just here
to pay your respects.
You have to figure out which of y'all
is the scoundrel who killed him.
This is ridiculous.
You leave, you do not get food.
- What kind?
- Sandwich platters.
- I'm in.
- Baby carrots.
Here are your character cards.
Take one, pass it down.
Here is your prop box.
Some of your characters will have props.
Now, on your character card,
it tells you who you are
and what your alibi is.
Everything else
is up to your imagination.
So if you talk slowly in real life,
your character could, say,
have been kicked in the head
by a horse.
Cool. I'll try it.
Use your imaginations.
- Who did you get?
- "Naughty Nellie Nutmeg,
"a vivacious young socialite
with a penchant for scandal."
- Saucy.
- How about you?
"Nathaniel nutmeg,
the local bartender and...
Nellie's brother."
I don't like this game.
It's scary.
- It's not scary.
- I don't like my character.
Who are you?
"Voodoo Mama Juju, the witch doctor
of the Savannah swamps."
- I'm not comfortable with this.
- How do you think I feel?
I mean,
I have to play Caleb Crawdad,
handsome playboy.
Every night, a different woman,
being oogled,
having to hug and kiss
and spoon.
I make them feel beautiful.
What is this contraption,
I do declare?
It's my Blackberry.
I'm trying to get updates.
Who's Michael?
I'm Caleb Crawdad, I do declare.
You don't have to keep saying that.
You say something, you're declaring.
That is the way
southern people talk.
What designing woman
are you basing that on?
Delta Buck, I do declare.
Now, shall we get to the mystery?
I'll go.
"My name is Deborah Utante,
"Deb for short."
That's clever.
Debutante.
"Bill Bourbon was my uncle.
"I would have never hurt him
"any more than I'd hurt a june bug."
Nice accent.
You sound like Forrest Gump.
I do not.
You do, actually.
You got this kind of like
Florida Panhandle thing goin',
whereas what you really want
is more of a Savannah accent,
which is more like molasses,
just sort of spillin'
out of your mouth.
Now do the Swedish chef.
I'm not familiar.
What province is he from?
He lives on Sesame Street, dumbass.
I think I'm supposed
to say something to Pam...
I mean, Deb.
"I overheard you askin' the butler
where the pistol was kept."
Wait a minute!
I'm the butler.
You were listening in on that?
You rich people. You think you can do
whatever you want to the servant class!
- It's not a political thing.
- I will poison your food.
I reckon I got somethin' to say
to Miss Beatrix Bourbon
if and she don't mind.
Doggy! We got a party now!
I do believe
that the game is a big hit.
People are really divin'
into their characters.
Y'all...
- I made a mistake.
- Sorry I'm late. What's goin' on?
Sir,
there has been a murder,
and you are a suspect.
Hang on just a second.
Let me settle in, I'll be right back.
Very good! Very good!
No one was there in the wine cellar.
Hey, there, young lady.
I would be remiss if I did not ask
the pretty young lady
out on a date for this weekend.
Sounds like a plan, sugar.
All right!
A plan it is.
Voodoo Mama Juju,
explain your dalliance
with the dark arts.
It's not my fault.
I was exposed to Harry Potter.
I know you did it!
I know she didn't do it.
It's never the person
you most suspect.
It's also never
the person you least suspect,
since anyone with half a brain
would suspect them the most.
Therefore,
I know the killer to be...
Phyllis,
a.k.a.
Beatrix Bourbon,
the person I most medium suspect.
Do you want to go out on a date
with me? We can
make out by the horses.
You know old Nellie
is always up for a romp in the hay.
How'bout a threesome?
My boudoir's always open.
Nice.
I'm a worried I might have asked out
Naughty Nellie and not Erin.
Which would be a lot less appealing,
because Nellie says yes to everyone,
and she might be a murderer.
Follow before...
I just got an email from corporate,
specifically for accounting
to stop all payments to our vendors.
What does that mean?
Maybe nothing,
but it could be a prob...
What's this strange yankee accent
comin' out of your mouth, son?
This here is Savannah.
This...
plan... planta...
This plantation,
we're runnin' low on greenbacks,
and we're havin' problems payin'
the people who give us
the seeds and the dirt.
We can't pay 'em.
I can't...
It could mean a lot of things,
but it is unprecedented,
so it's cause for concern.
I'm going back to work.
I'm gonna skip forward
to a really big clue. Here we go.
Well, by now, you figured out
that old Beatrix Bourbon was the killer.
What?
I was doing so well.
Are you goin' to believe that?
That is a mis...
That's a misdirection.
We still don't know
who the murderer is.
Nellie Nutmeg, come back in heyah!
I can't do this myself.
Voodoo Mama Juju!
What am I gonna do?
Okay, so corporate
is still in their meeting.
That could be a good sign.
Kevin's gonna give us his take
on the situation. Let's listen up.
All right, guys, it's a workday,
and you guys work here,
so let's go do some work.
Now, Jim telling us all to work,
I think that is a very good sign.
Don't just say things.
Good, Michael.
I wrote up those sales targets...
I do believe you have me mistaken.
My name is Caleb Crawdad.
Y'all skedaddled way too soon.
We need to re-open this case.
You're not re-opening the case.
The case is closed.
No, it ain't.
Frankly, I'm not surprised.
A lot of the evidence
seemed to be based
on puns.
I was thinking
about Weekend at Bernie's.
So funny.
The guy's dead the whole time.
I haven't seen it.
Speaking of weekends,
you excited
about our date this weekend?
Of course, Nathaniel.
Where are you takin' me?
The finest steakhouse
in all Savannah.
Savannah?
That's a far way from Scranton.
Did you mean a real date?
Did you?
Totally
not.
I thought it was for real.
So I was excited, but it was just...
part of the game.
You're sure it was water?
It couldn't have been acid?
I already declared you
it was too dark to tell!
- Stop playing games with me, crawdad!
- This is not a game! This is my life!
- You are out of order, sir!
- Answer me!
- You are out of order!
I think Michael may have snapped.
Or maybe he's stuck in character.
Well, which is worse?
Snapped or stuck?
Both.
They're both worse.
It's gonna be all right.
We're a good company.
We'll figure this out.
We're not going under.
What if we both lose our jobs?
I'm trying to think of a way
that this all ends up fine,
and I can't think of one.
Deb, what in the world?
Do you have the vapors?
- Not now.
- Can't wait.
We have to get you
to our witch doctor right now.
Come on.
- Come on!
- I should just go.
Where to now, Caleb?
To...
Mama Juju Boo-Boo.
Michael, can I...
I'm just gonna skip right past the what
and go with why?
Because this is
the re-creation of a crime scene.
I'm the dead body,
and these are my brain chunks.
Shut up. You're dead.
- Can I talk to you?
- No Michael here.
Caleb!
- Today, of all days...
- No! You shut up!
They need this game, Jim.
Let us have this stupid little game,
all right?
You startled me!
My stars,
my heart nearly leapt out of my chest.
What can I do you for?
Wallace is on the phone.
He's returning your call.
- Detective Wallace?
- I don't think so.
I think it's David Wallace
from Dunder Mifflin.
- Tell him I'm not heyah.
- You're not gonna answer the phone?
I only answer to detective Wallace,
'cause I got a warm body
in the other room.
I'll take it.
Sorry to be gettin' back
to you guys so late.
Things are still a bit unclear.
We didn't officially decide anything.
But if I can be candid
with you here, Jim...
It's not good. We fully expect to be
out of money by the end of the year.
Insolvent.
So I think you know...
I'm sorry. I have to run.
- But we will talk soon?
- Sure.
You know, while I have you,
today I was working on this pitch
for a supermarket chain...
And it would actually be
a big account.
Okay, look, you know what?
I can't really get my head around that
but that's great.
Keep after it, but I gotta run.
See ya.
What's the news?
Nothing yet.
I guess that's not...
There is some bad news.
There has been another murder.
A murder, you say?
I do declare.
Conference room, everyone.
Do we have to play?
Super.
This could be a juicy one.
- Get in there!
- I do declare.
I think today was a good day
to have two managers,
because if you're a family
stuck in the middle of the ocean,
one parent might want
to just keep rowing.
But if the other parent
wants to play a game,
it's not because they're crazy.
It's because
they're doing it for the kids.
And I get that now.
There has been a lot of murder
and a lot of intrigue.
My little heart
can barely take it no more.
Today is the hardest I have worked
in a long, long time.
I didn't do it!
Everybody just calm down.
Count of three,
we're all gonna put down our guns.
I have crossbows.
We'll put down our weaponry
on the count of three.
- You ready?
- I'm ready.
One...
Two...
Three.
Andy revealed himself
to be a double agent,
at which point,
Dwight felt comfortable
revealing that he also
was a double agent,
and then, Michael announced
to everybody that,
get this,
he was a double agent.
And it is 6:00.
Really?
It wasn't me!
I'm not goin' down for this!
I want to go home.
Get the keys out of my purse,
start the car.