Parkour!
- Extreme!
- Parkour!
This is parkour.
Internet sensation of 2004.
And it was in one of the Bond films.
It's pretty impressive.
The goal is to get from point A
to point B as creatively as possible.
So technically they are doing parkour
as long as point A is delusion
and point B is the hospital.
Parkour!
- Okay, here we go!
- Andy, leapfrog!
Do me! Do me!
Parkour!
-Get off! Get off!
-Okay
Jump over it.
Jump over the camera.
Okay, we all go together
or we go one at a time.
Here it is.
Truck to refrigerators,
to dumpster,
360 spin onto the pallets,
backflip gainer into the trash can.
Yeah gainer!
- Hardcore parkour!
- I'm right behind you, Andy! Come on!
- Let's do it!
Parkour.
- Feygnasse Team -
- La Fabrique -
Collioure
Jarick
do_Ob
Sk0r
yomoy
The Ni.Knight
Episode 6x01
Gossip
Good.
Excellent.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Is there anything else I can do?
Yes ehm.
See those files
behind Kevin's desk?
Go put them all
in random order.
Then come back here
for your next assignment
concerning their order.
This is the last day
of our summer interns.
It's been nice.
We haven't had interns in a while
ever since Michael's
Monica Lewinsky incident.
He didn't do anything sexual.
He just made far, far too many
Monica Lewinsky jokes.
It was just easier for corporate
to shutdown the program.
- Think she did him?
- There's something there.
I was
in the kitchen yesterday
and they were too happy
to be cleaning the freezer.
If they get married before I do,
I'm gonna kill myself.
- Who's getting married?
- Nobody.
Somebody doesn't tell me,
I'm gonna start screaming.
Eric and Megan.
Oh hey
I hired them.
Matchmaker.
This place is like Spaniard fly.
They're not getting married.
It's just talk.
Did everybody knows about this but me?
There's nothing to know.
It's gossip.
Okey.
We haven't told anyone
that I'm pregnant.
What with her being unmarried.
Knocked up by some guy.
The yakkity-yaks in this office
would have a field day.
We don't want them
at the wedding thinking
Jim's being marched down the aisle
by my dad with a shotgun.
Wait,
there's not gonna be a shotgun?
No shotgun?
- 'Cause that changes everything.
- Can't back out now, Halpert.
What are you gonna do about it?
There's no shotgun, so...
Free at last. Free at last.
No, keep it up.
You'll never guess what I know.
Let me finish this thought.
Eric likes Megan.
He most definitely does.
He's been asking her out for weeks.
She finally said yes.
They went out the other night.
Apparently it went very well.
- How do you know this?
- People tell me things.
I guess I have a face you can trust.
I think
it's because of my low cheekbones.
And...
Okay, what is it?
What can't I guess?
I hate, hate, hate being left out.
Whether
it's not being picked for a team
or being picked for a team
and then showing up
and realizing
that the team doesn't exist
or that the sport doesn't exist.
I should have known. Poopball?
Man, I know how you feel.
Third wheel.
I have been the third wheel
so many times in my life.
My mom told me something once
that made me feel better. She said...
the third wheel
is what makes it a tricycle.
- What are you talking about?
- Your group date with Megan and Eric.
At Tink's?
How'd you know about that?
Did Stanley tell you?
Stanley was on your group date?
No, Stanley was with his wife.
I waved at him but he didn't wave back.
Does anybody else know about this?
There he goes.
So what is the scuttlebutt?
Anybody hear anything?
Nothing?
I got a little something-something.
- I don't know if I should say.
- So just keep it to yourself then.
Stanley is having a midlife crisis.
Stanley is way past
the middle of his life,
considering
his height to weight ratio.
Apparently he and his wife
were out dancing
at a club for young people.
Teri's out of town.
- Who?
- Stanley's wife, Teri.
She's at an interior decorating expo
in Philly.
And Stanley hates crowds,
kids, and music.
I think you should check your facts.
You stupid son of a bitch.
You set me up.
- What are you talking about?
- Stanley's wife is out of town.
- He was with somebody.
- Definitely.
Was he? Who, his sister?
I don't get it!
If that was his sister,
then what they were doing was illegal.
Drugs?
Making out.
No, it's okay.
Never mind. Carry on.
Stanley is having an affair.
- What?
- I know.
I am very happy right now,
thrilled perhaps,
to be a part of the office,
to be a part of the conversation.
When you have somebody's attention
and their eyes are lighting up
because they are very interested
in what you have to say,
that is a great feeling
and I experienced that firsthand today.
It is wonderful
to be the center of attention.
That and that are the same letter.
"Q".
No...no
Okey.
He's holding a pencil.
He could be doing a crossword puzzle
with that pencil.
What's that letter right there?
Same letter here and here.
- What haven't you guessed?
- "T".
"T", yes!
Yes!
That is a "t"
and there's another one right there.
Just sound that out.
You're almost there.
Hey Stanley.
Where you going, big guy?
Up to no good?
I'm meeting a client.
Do you have a problem?
No no no
I just had a quick question for you.
I'm casting
a movie and I'm looking
for a woman who can dance.
Beautiful woman.
Do you know anybody?
Good-bye.
Pays $5 million.
Nudity required.
You have to stop this.
Did you hear?
Stanley's having an affair.
I did from you.
You got to stop telling people.
Okay, I get it.
You feel out of the loop
and sorry for yourself
and it's really sad,
everybody thinks you're a loser.
Do you even know if it's true?
Do you have any idea? Because...
you might be ruining his life.
Hold up! Hold up!
Time to stop being polite
and get real.
Stanley,
you having an affair?
That is ridiculous. Of course not.
Why would you think that?
So it's not true.
well
Those interns. They told me
they saw you at the club
and they all said it was you.
It was clearly just...
racial profiling gossip.
- The little...
- Damn!
- Told her it was a stupid idea.
- That's so stupid.
It's just that...
- Teri's been traveling a lot lately.
- I know.
- It's been lonely.
- I bet.
Cynthia's been keeping me company.
She was my nurse
when I was in rehabilitation.
We used to go on these long walks
on the treadmill.
I didn't intend...
Wait, wait, wait.
So it is true?
But I'm going to go break it off.
That's where I'm headed right now,
I swear.
Wait a second.
Do people often say they're going
on sales calls
and then go someplace else?
That's not cool.
I just need you to promise
not to say a word about this to anyone.
Michael, please.
- I'm not saying a damn thing.
- I'm counting on you, Michael.
Okay
You can count on me.
Oh that smells good.
I might have extra.
It just depends on how many I eat.
Did you hear about Angela?
That's pretty weird.
Yeah
What do you mean exactly?
Well, the fact
that she apparently is dating
an 81-year-old billionaire
who owns a Quiznos on the turnpike.
Really?
Right?
How do you untell something?
You can't.
You can't put words
back in your mouth.
What you can do
is spread false gossip
so that people think that everything
that's been said is untrue,
including
Stanley is having an affair.
It's like the end of Spartacus.
I've seen that movie half a dozen times
and I still don't know
who the real Spartacus is.
And that is what makes
that movie a classic whodunit.
Kelly has an eating disorder.
She always eats my lunch.
Anorexia. She's ana...
She's an "anorexitec."
- We should do something.
- Nothing can be done.
Just have to tell everybody
and hope for the best, I guess.
I'm worried about Erin
because she's not a very good worker.
I don't know how long she's gonna last.
Really?
So...
And Andy...
is gay.
Did you hear Pam is pregnant?
Really?
She's gonna hate being a mom.
What?
Tea.
- So?
- You would.
I like tea.
I bet you like it.
I like it a lot.
I love tea.
Do you like it as much
as you like men's butts?
What?
'Cause you're gay.
Who told you that?
Was it Broccoli Rob?
Someone from Chi Psi?
Did you run
in someone from my high school?
This is not the first time
rumors about me being gay
have come up.
Twice before, actually.
Just a weird coincidence.
It's a little too weird.
Almost makes you wonder
if it's not a coincidence at all.
Which it is, of course.
But it makes you wonder.
Did you hear the rumor about me?
That I'm gay?
I did.
And?
What?
Do you think it's true?
Do you think that I'm...
gay?
Are you attracted to other men?
No...but
Let me kick you a scenario.
I'm at, like, a beach cabana
and Brad Pitt approaches,
tries to lean in and kiss me.
I would definitely resist,
like, at first.
But if he was persistent,
I might...
give in a little bit
to just really see what it felt like.
Would I push him away?
How hard?
Like, what if he's,
like, really aggressive?
If you resisted Brad Pitt
a little bit,
he would still...
- need to get to you?
- This is not real Brad Pitt.
This is, like, in my...
This is my fantasy.
Or it's, like, not fantasy.
It's, like, what I'm...
It's just a scenario.
I wish I could help you. I don't...
You might be gay.
What exactly
is my responsibility here?
To comfort
insecure heterosexual men?
That can't possibly fall to me.
- How far is Pam?
- A few months.
That's why
they're rushing the wedding.
You can't believe
everything you hear.
Like Stanley having an affair.
That is crazy.
Just there's no stock in it.
It's a weird day for false facts.
Let it go.
OK, everybody.
Big day. Last day for our interns.
Lot of other stuff.
Who knows what to believe?
Dwight, the honors.
Present these
to the dean for credit.
And as a gift,
I've attached my card.
Call me anytime of the day or night.
Why would we call you at night?
Now you can't call me at all,
so problem solved.
You will regret when you find yourself
between a moose and her cubs.
Look to the intern on your left.
Now to your right.
One of you will do
exceedingly well in business.
Just unlimited potential.
One of you will make a living
and nothing more.
And one of you
will make a great mother.
It's up to you
to choose which you want to be.
I am so happy you're eating again.
Me too.
Dude, how come you never try
to set me up?
I don't really do that.
Pam might have some friends though.
Women friends?
Not guy friends?
Are you interested
in her guy friends?
For the record, I prefer women.
But off the record,
I'm kind of confused.
Really?
The evidence is stacked against me,
I feel like.
- You got to figure this out.
- Yeah, right? How?
You got to have sex with a woman.
- Right-o.
- And then a man and then compare.
All right.
well.. hey
- Congratulations to you.
- On what?
Come on.
Little baby tuna.
Little junior toro.
A baby conceived out of wedlock
is still a bastard.
What?
Want me to say it again?
- Why did that come into your brain?
- Can I talk to you?
So they know.
- Who did you tell?
- I didn't tell anyone. And you?
Nobody.
Did one of you tell Stanley
that I have asthma, 'cause I don't.
If it gets out,
they won't let me scuba.
If I can't scuba,
then what's this all been about?
What am I working toward?
What?
You think I'm the voice
of the Taco Bell Dog?
What are you talking about?
I have a daughter.
How could I be a virgin?
Has everyone heard
a crazy rumor about themselves today?
You know what?
Let's discredit these rumors.
Sure, but who's been saying
all that stuff?
That's not important,
We shouldn't listen to this crap.
Sure, but we should get to the bottom of this.
Let's pick a rumor
and trace it back to the beginning.
I need to do mine first.
Who's been saying that
there's another person inside of me
working me with controls?
I heard that from Andy.
I heard it from Erin.
I heard it from Michael.
Michael?
He's over here!
- Where you going?
- Nowhere.
Michael.
You told people
that I use store-bought manure
when I showed you
where my manure comes from.
- Don't get on it.
- Michael, don't.
Don't get on.
Do not.
- Stay, Michael.
- Step away.
Come on, boss.
Okay, I made it all up.
What?
Even the fact that I'm gay?
-Yes
But, guys, I'm a victim here too.
Okay?
People have been saying
that I am a J. Crew model.
No, we heard that about Jim.
Jim? No no
I spread the rumor
that somebody was a J. Crew model
and I was referring to myself.
- How is that a bad rumor?
- 'Cause people think that models,
even though they're very attractive
are somewhat vapid.
It set our industry back
quite a bit.
Michael, why?
Why say all these things?
Why make up an eating disorder,
Stanley's affair,
me being a spokes dog?
You told everyone
I was having an affair?
Here's the thing.
There was one true rumor
out there today.
I didn't want everybody
to know what it was,
so all of you are off the hook
except for this one person.
Well, then
what's the one true rumor?
We have a right to know.
Am I gay?
The one true rumor...
This is gonna ruin
this person's life, is...
That Pam's pregnant.
- I knew it.
Her breasts were a tiny bit bigger.
At first I thought,
she has a new bra with padding.
But then I thought,
Pam doesn't need padding.
It just didn't add up, Jim.
- Congratulations.
- That's really great.
- Don't vaccinate it.
- Who's the father?
- How far along?
- Four months.
- Who's the ob-gyn?
- Stop.
All right, you know...
This is not the truth
and you can't fall
on a sword this way.
The real thing
is that Stanley Hudson
had an affair.
Thank you to defend us, but actually,
Pam is pregnant and we can prove it.
If you would like to see proof.
- Just gonna wait for her?
- What's the "proof" mean?
- There it is!
- It's true!
Pam!
Look at that!
That is the inside of your vagina.
That's not how it works, but...
It's clear
why we were trying not to tell people.
That's clear now.
How long have you known
about the pregnancy?
A week? Month?
A year?
We only told our parents last week.
- Did you pee on a stick?
- I did.
But it was inconclusive.
You should have told me.
You're right.
We should have realized
that you are an equal part of this.
Yes
Michael, Teri Hudson
returning your call.
You called Stanley's wife?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Just to make sure she was out of town.
- God.
- Don't take it.
I have to take it
or it'll seem suspicious.
If you talk to her,
you're gonna tell her about Stanley
- and that's gonna seem more suspicious.
- I can do this.
- You can't do this.
- I can. I am going to tell her
that I need to redecorate my condo
and I need her help.
We will haggle about money
and I will back down
and then I won't talk to her
until this Cynthia thing's blown over.
- Sounds terrible.
- Please don't.
What up, Cynthia?
Just hang on a second, Cynthia.
It turns out
that Teri was already suspicious
because she had caught Stanley
and Cynthia a few months ago.
So Stanley promised
that he would stop and he did.
End of story. Well...
not exactly.
Cynthia kept calling him.
She would not stop calling him
and she was in love with him.
And get this.
Cynthia? Also married.
So...
you can't stop love, I guess.
And quite frankly,
I don't think
you should ever even try.
I learned that a company
can describe an internship
as full of exciting experiences,
even if that's a lie.
There's no regulation.
I learned that half
these people's email password
is "password."
I learned that a ream of paper
is 300 sheets.
I thought it was 500.
I guess I didn't learn anything.
I learned that if you look
even the tiniest bit like Jet Li
Michael will call you
Jet Li all summer.
- Julia Stiles.
- Alan Thicke.