Andy,
I'm getting married in eight hours.
Everyone else is too drunk.
Just don't let me die here.
Where are you?
Can you take Andy to the hospital?
- What?
- He tore his scrotum dancing.
- He is in my room, icing his balls.
- What?
- Please stop saying "What?"
- Can you take him?
- I would so take him
in any other circumstance,
but I'm pretty certain
I'm completely wasted.
Your brothers took you out drinking?
Is that Pam?
Have her come out.
Have her come out!
It'll be like Coyote Ugly.
That's Michael.
You're out with Michael?
And Dwight.
- Pam, it just happened.
- Fine.
I'll take him.
I love you. I got to go.
I love you!
- Are you pushing me off the phone?
- No. Let's talk for a long time.
Good-bye.
It's after midnight.
You're married.
He's married!
That's not how that works.
- You'll not be able to talk back.
- You'll have Pam to answer to.
She'll be sitting at home saying:
"Jim, take the baby to the zoo,
"cause I want to sit at home
and eat bonbons...
"and clip my toenails."
"Why don't you braid my hair?
- "I want to watch TV."
- Now you sound like Kermit.
Are you sure this is the right way?
I, like you,
have never been here before.
At least slow down a little bit,
because every little bump in the road
is major pain on...
my scrotum.
I'm not the one
who asked you to do a split
when you'd never done one before.
I was trying to liven things up.
I was kind of doing your job, so...
My job?
My job is to get married
in the morning.
That's my job.
It's also to make sure we have
a great time at your stupid wedding,
so...
Just spent the night with the bride
the night before the wedding.
She stepped on my hand
on her way to the bathroom.
Andy, did I dream
that you were crying through the night?
That was real.
Why don't you take a picture?
It'll last longer.
Can I get a little privacy?
Good morning.
How can I help you?
I left
a pair of dress shoes in a bag
outside my door last night
to be cleaned and polished,
but they haven't been returned yet.
You must be Mr. Malone.
One moment please.
Sir, this is the man with the shoes.
Mr. Malone, your shoes are gone.
They were stolen?
No, destroyed.
When the bag was opened
by our shoeshine,
the smell overcame him.
I, too, smelled them
and made the choice
that they must be thrown away.
Incinerated, actually.
But that was my only pair of shoes.
It became a safety issue, sir.
Damn it.
I can offer you
a complimentary breakfast.
You have everything?
Cell phone?
Charger?
So you sure you don't want breakfast?
It's the most important meal of the day.
It really is.
I'm not hungry.
I ate a bunch of sunflower seeds
after you went to sleep.
And besides,
I don't want to take you away from Pam
on the morning of her wedding.
She needs you, Isabel.
That's really sweet, Dwight.
So I'll see you at the wedding?
You know it.
Get out of here.
Good morning.
It's about damn time, I haven't gone
to the bathroom in a day and a half.
- This room is a pit.
- Really? Hadn't noticed.
Too busy knockin' boots.
How can you eat like that?
I'm ravenous
after a night of lovemaking.
You?
I'm hungry, but I'm not gonna make
a pig out of myself.
What was she like?
She was cute.
You know, she was hot.
She was very hot.
She made love like a tiger.
Bride side or groom side?
Or townie?
She was from Europe.
No kidding.
Bet she had hairy armpits.
Isabel was nice, but...
I hope she doesn't think
this is going anywhere.
Wait a second.
You're not into her?
Are you kidding me?
She's Pam's best friend.
You guys could double date.
Swap maybe?
Put a gun in my mouth.
You're crazy.
She's a dental hygienist
from Carbondale,
and she makes love like one.
She's a bumpkin. Pass.
You know how hard it is?
You have to take X-Rays.
You have to scrape the plaque of teeth.
You have to tell kids when to spit
and make sure that they're not scared
when the dentist comes in.
Ask her out.
I already have
a European girlfriend.
Are you in a lot of pain?
'Cause of last night?
No way.
Reports have been exaggerated.
Weddings make me very emotional.
I have that side.
People say you cry all the time.
That's...
not...
Crotch injuries are the worst.
You don't need to tell me.
I wasn't telling you.
- There's still something there?
- Excuse me?
It didn't get torn off?
They didn't...
Nothing got torn off.
Who told you that?
I may have told some people that.
I'm nervous.
I'm about to get married.
If you want to sit on this...
I was thinking the wood might be
too hard on your damaged penis.
Make it softer.
It's my scrotum.
And it was.
Sure.
Here we go.
They asked for cash, but,
you know,
I give 'em cash every week.
So how much cash does a person need?
I have taken it upon myself
to do something a little more special.
I have painted a portrait
of the two of them
from memory.
And I have
another one of them in the nude.
But that one is for me.
I got them
a set of turtle-boiling pots,
shell hammer,
and bibs.
Is it zipping over your belly?
Don't squish the baby.
Thank you, weirdo.
Everybody see
Kristy's stupid, blond extensions?
It's like they were made
from a plastic broom.
Here I come.
Darling, you look beautiful.
Thanks, mom.
I hope he deserves you.
He does.
Are you sure?
Remember, you don't have to do this.
You don't.
You're totally projecting
and being a drag.
Thank you, mom.
I'm gonna go outside
and talk to Dwight.
Great.
I'll see you in a second.
Wait, what?
- Can you come here please?
- Is this allowed?
But I'm allowing it.
Just come here.
That was an intelligent comment.
Hello, stranger.
How do I look?
Fine.
Isabel, nice to see you.
What do you want?
Nothing...
anymore.
So...
tell me again the difference
between Filene's and Filene's basement.
He's not sitting with me, either.
Where are you sitting?
You need a seat, buddy?
I'm standing.
I'm a bridesmaid.
I wish I was a bridesmaid.
Where am I gonna go?
You look...
Terrible.
So beautiful.
My veil tore.
I knew when we were getting married
and I'm five months pregnant
that I'm not gonna be able
to wear the dress that I always wanted,
or high heels.
You look just as I imagined you.
Pam, you're so pretty.
And who cares?
It's a stupid veil, right?
No, this is the one thing
I was supposed to be able to control
was this veil.
There.
Now we're even.
Everyone's driving me crazy.
I know way too much
about Andy's scrotum,
and my mom won't stop
freaking out
about my dad's new girlfriend.
This is supposed
to be our wedding day.
Why did we invite all these people?
I think Pam ran away
because she knew deep down
she wouldn't be a good wife.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to decide
if I have time to pee.
- How long do you take to pee?
- The peeing is fast, Oscar.
It's getting my tie back on.
Would you have a snack
in your purse?
You're a mom.
I just figured you might have...
Apricot.
Do you have any of the Very Berry
or Ocean Splash, or...
Were you saving it?
That's okay. I just...
I've had a very rough...
weekend.
I'm sorry.
Apricot. Made of real apes.
They canceled the wedding?
Relax.
You'll get your shot at Jim.
Those two treat the whole office
like a 1970's key party.
My weekend's bad so far.
I came here hoping to meet somebody.
You know, as you do,
at weddings.
End up...
going to sleep
by the vending machine.
- It was loud, but it was warm.
- That sounds awful.
And...
the love of my life
is dating somebody else.
It's just...
It is a terrible year for love.
I guess.
Thinking
about having my sperm frozen.
Excuse me, are you Michael Scott?
Heard you might have
a whoopee cushion on you.
Our sister's in the can, and we want
to get her when she comes back.
That sounds hilarious.
I do, actually.
There you go.
Use it in good health.
Wait a minute, what is the etiquette
on taking the gifts?
Can you only take your own back,
or is it
a whatever-you-can-carry type of thing?
Anyone have anything
they want to trade for a toaster?
Does it have slots for hot dogs?
Who would want it?
Guys, maybe we should wait
a little more time
before we start grabbing boxes.
I like to lodge a complaint against Jim
for making us wait for over an hour.
Get in there.
I guess this wedding
is not gonna happen.
Wonder if this is it for them.
What happened?
Where were you?
Do you know I've been waiting here?
We are here now, so let's go.
I have so much joy in my heart
right now.
How do I look?
- You look great.
Wear a tie much?
I begged them not to.
I know you specifically put this song
on your do not play list.
I did.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
I think it's your turn.
What happened?
You're okay with this?
I'm okay.
Okay then.
Did you see this?
It was on YouTube.
Saw it.
I bought those boat tickets
the day I saw that YouTube video.
I knew we'd need a backup plan.
The boat was actually plan C,
the church was plan B,
and plan A was...
marrying her a long, long time ago.
Pretty much the day I met her.
What an awesome party.
The best wedding I've ever been to.
I got six numbers.
One more would have been
a complete telephone number.
This was epic.
My Kleenex shoes
were a huge conversation piece,
but man,
my dogs are barking.
My feet were so sweaty,
I can't even feel the cold.
What a lovely hotel.