Good morning, everybody.
Who would like
an authentic New York bagel?
I got a pumpernickel just for you.
H and H.
You went all the way to New York City
to get us bagels?
Why, is there a place closer
that sells them?
This was really nice, Dwight.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
You owe me one.
You all owe me one.
- Good morning, Michael.
- Good morning, Dwight.
- Hungry?
- No. I had a fish stick sandwich.
Actually, I had two.
My girlfriend didn't want hers,
because I guess
I'm the only aphrodisiac she needs.
Fish sticks are not an ahrodisiac.
You're thinking of deer penis.
- It worked.
- Regardless, that was two hours ago,
and it is now a scientific fact
that you are hungry... Bagel?
- I don't mind if I do.
- I brought cheese too.
I'm taking one for my lady friend.
- Excellent.
- Brain food.
Thank you very much.
You owe me.
Can't a guy just buy
some bagels for his friends
so they'll owe him a favor,
which he can use
to get someone fired who stole
a co-manager position from him anymore?
Jeez...
When did everyone get so cynical?
- Feygnasse Team -
.:: La Fabrique ::.
Collioure
Jarick
loky
Sk0r
yomoy
The Ni.Knight
Episode 6x08
Double Date
Pam, would you care for a bagel?
That's right, you're a woman,
and you need to refuse the first time.
I'll try again.
Please, Pam,
reconsider and have a bagel.
I have an early lunch.
Michael's been trying
to get Jim and me to hang out
since he started dating my mom.
I don't know, I really hoped
this thing would just die out.
But today he's planning
a birthday lunch for my mom,
and we have to go.
No way out.
These are amazing.
You took all these?
I've always found beauty
in uncommon places.
Homeless people.
Graffiti.
Photography lets me
capture all that.
Have you ever been photographed?
Just by, like, friends.
Here's what I've been doing
around here.
It's for a series
on exposure in the workplace.
Happy birthday.
Girls... There they are.
Birthday lunch...
There's no better medicine
than birthday lunch.
It'll cure all of your...
"Gee, I don't know if Michael
should be dating my mother."
and fixes all occurrences of,
"I don't really see them together."
so open wide, Pam,
and take a big ol'spoonful
of birthday lunch medicine.
Take with food.
Aren't you gonna introduce us
to Michael's girlfriend?
I think you guys all remember my mom
from the wedding.
I think everyone's met Helene.
Shall we?
Wait,
is that another present for me?
'Cause you already
gave me a necklace.
- I love it.
- Tell her how you gave it to me.
He put it around my neck
while I was still asleep this morning.
What a nice way to wake up.
The rest of the story has been censored
due to inappropriosity.
Because of sex?
Please, Kevin...
You're fired.
Sorry.
Work with a bunch of idiots.
- Shall we go?
- Yes, let's go.
Wait. Swartz Lumber
is on the phone for you, Pam,
and they say it's urgent.
You guys, just one second.
My gosh!
Are you serious?
Shipping emergency.
I don't think I can go to lunch.
Man, that's crazy.
We were on our way out too.
I know.
Isn't that always how it goes?
Rarely, if ever.
I'll talk to him.
- I want to handle it. I feel like.
- It's my pleasure.
That's great.
Turns out the paper was there all along.
Thank god.
Something's up.
That paper
was never supposed to arrive.
So, Pammy,
are you still liking sales?
It's exciting.
You know, Michael and I were...
talking, and...
maybe if you put in a little more
face-to-face time with your clients,
you could improve your sales.
Pam's sales are fine, actually.
Just want you to succeed, Pammy.
We shouldn't even be talking
about business today.
Today's about family.
Why did I get in the car?
I could have struggled.
I have a whistle in my purse.
I didn't even blow it.
Dwight,
I have a little surprise for you.
Let me guess,
you ate the bagel and loved it.
And I wanted to return the favor.
I was polishing my loafers,
and I happened to look over
and notice that your briefcase
was a little worse for the wear.
So a little elbow grease,
and she's polished right up,
back to her former glory.
Feel it against your cheek.
I will.
You give me a gift...
Thank you note.
You invite me somewhere...
RSVP.
You do me a favor...
Favor returned.
Do not test my politeness.
Let me get that door for you.
There we go.
Thank you very much.
And I got it for you.
Goodness.
You know,
here's a healthy fitness tip.
If you clench
your buttocks together,
you can take the pressure
off your knees.
- Is that right?
- Observe.
That really works.
Feel free to use that anytime.
Hold on a second.
Do not walk around with your
jacket cattywampus.
And that needs to be
straight as an arrow.
Boy.
Thank you very much for that.
Have a seat. Allow me.
Have a seat yourself.
You know what, I am going
to preemptively change the batteries
- in your wireless mouse.
- Not necessary.
You don't have to do that.
Andy is complicating things.
But I'm not worried.
This will only up my game.
Hello. "Scott", table for four.
Welcome, Scott family.
It'll be just a moment.
I used to love coming here.
The chicken parm is good.
Big part of my childhood.
Maybe Michael
will start dating that too.
What table should we take?
So many to choose from.
What?
All I see are boring old tables
with no birthday decorations.
Wait a second!
You mean this one?
Michael, you did all this?
It's not about taking credit.
We all did it.
Thank you. All of you.
It was actually me alone, so...
Look at this place.
It really makes me
want to go to Italy someday.
You'll love it.
You can have my guide books.
I think I'm done
with those really long plane rides.
Thank you for...
lending me the book.
So, mom, which birthday
are we celebrating this year?
Sticking with 49.
49 again?
That's nine years in a row.
This is our longest family tradition.
That's funny.
As long as you're running numbers,
help me out with this one.
Let's see, honey,
you're six months pregnant,
but only been married for 30 days.
So what does that add up to?
Burn on you.
And a little bit on me too.
You're 54 years old.
I'm 58.
You're 58 years old?
Congratulations.
The only time you should care
about a woman's age
is if she is too young for you.
And I am not robbing the cradle.
If anything,
I am robbing the grave.
Have you decided
what you want to be called?
I like "nana."
But I also like
the classic "grandma."
- I want you to be grandma.
- Definitely.
Michael, what do you think?
Grandma?
Grandma.
Would you guys
ever do a triathlon, you think?
Maybe.
I don't think so.
I am.
I'm definitely gonna do it.
I've already got
the run and the bike thing down.
I just need to learn how to swim.
Come on, you in?
No, I think a triathlon
is pretty much something I can
rule out.
It doesn't interest me.
So it's a matter of interest. Good.
It's not anything
you would have ever done.
I might when I was younger,
but there are other things
that I'd rather be doing
than running and jumping.
There's no jumping in a triathlon.
You're thinking the broad jump.
Would you try...
- Bungee jumping?
- No.
- Snowboarding?
- You want to go snowboarding?
I might.
Michael, what are you talking about?
Nothing.
Just life and...
doing things...
Before you die.
I don't know.
Do I really want to go snowboarding?
But I would like to if I wanted to.
- What's going on in here?
- Andy bought lunch.
No, really?
Took a page right out
of the old Schrute book of niceness.
There is no book.
There's only a survival guide.
You bought breakfast for everyone,
so I got lunch for everyone.
Allow me.
You know what...
Gosh, these tacos
are awfully complicated to make.
I will make everyone's tacos.
- So we should get the check?
- What about your gift, Michael?
It's stupid.
You'd hate it. I hate it.
- I'm sure I won't.
- You will.
He locked himself in his office
all morning working on it.
Gimme!
Look at this wrapping paper.
It's got the word "love"
on it in every language!
I literally put no thought
into the wrapping at all.
Might as well
have been toilet paper.
Toilet paper...
"A scrapbook of our first memories"
by Michael Gary Scott.
"For my girlfriend Helene
"on your birthday."
That's just an arbitrary title.
- Here's a penny. What's that from?
- Penny for your thoughts.
It was from the wishing well
at the mall.
You threw it in, and I went back later,
waded in, and I found it.
- That's amazing!
- It's not amazing at all.
It's sort of weird
that I went and did that.
And now your wish won't come true,
so that blows.
- A poem.
- That I plagiarized, I think.
"I cannot go to school today
said little Peggy Ann McKay."
- Is that Shel Silverstein?
- "I have the measles and the mumps,
"a gash, a rash, and purple bumps,
"and my teacher's really mean...
Happy birthday,
I love you, Helene. "
That's really nice, Michael.
I think it sucks.
I think it's absolutely wonderful.
That's because you and I
have very different taste.
And you like lame things.
It's a generational
sort of gap between us.
God, a scrapbook.
- Home run, Michael.
- You set the bar so high.
That was a bunt.
Dwight, I'm gonna do this.
- Relax. I got it covered.
- No, I insist.
No, I insist.
This is ridiculous.
Don't worry about it.
You can just owe me.
- Where'd you go?
- Just went to the bathroom.
And then you stopped at the bar
on the way back?
Got thirsty.
Okay, weirdo.
Come on, it's time for cake.
Honestly, for a long time I thought
I was going to grow old with Holly.
And then I met Helene,
and she is great.
And she already knows
and has done everything
that I have ever wanted to do,
and...
can tell me about it.
But...
I think
I want to do those things myself.
The cake's really good.
I know. I love it
when they use butter-cream frosting.
Finish your cake.
I want you to enjoy that cake
because I have something terrible
I need to tell you,
and I want you
to enjoy your cake
before I tell you
this terrible thing.
I think you're a wonderful person...
God, I've enjoyed dating you
and being your boyfriend so much.
But I have to consider
Pam's feelings as a friend
and a co-worker,
I cannot in good conscience
continue to date you
when I know
what this is doing to her.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
I know that it took me
a little while to come around,
and it's still a little weird
to get used to,
but...
you obviously make my mom
very happy.
And that makes me happy.
You've really grown.
Well...
Oh, thank you, Pam.
And I hope you're as gracious
during this next part.
Helene, once again,
you are a wonderful person,
and you have lived a great life.
And I envy it.
And I want it, someday.
But just in the future.
You need somebody
who understands your references.
Who is Kafkaesque?
I've never... I don't know him.
There's another woman,
and her name is Italy...
And skydiving...
- And bungee jumping.
- Okay, so...
And I want kids.
And you, unfortunately,
have already completed
that part of your journey down there.
It's not my decision.
It's mother nature.
And mother
has very strict rules about fer...
tility.
I got it.
I'm 58.
What am I supposed to do now?
- Well, hobbies...
- Stop.
What?
Stupid thing wedged up there.
No one in this office will help me.
Yeah. Move it.
What if Dwight dies
and I still owe him something?
That is a recipe for a ghost.
- You're gonna owe me big time.
- It's like a little envel...
Yep. Got it.
"To Dwight"?
- A starbucks gift card.
- Surprise!
It's for everybody.
$15 value.
Damn it!
I am no closer to taking Jim down.
What a waste of the day.
I could have grown poison mushrooms
that'd be this high by now!
They're mushrooms.
They don't get that high.
- Pamela Beesly Halpert.
- What?
May I have a word with you
in my office?
- I am working.
- Well...
- This is a work-related matter.
- Really?
Join me, please, won't you?
- I'm going to give you a raise.
- Why?
Because of all the good work
you've done.
I have the lowest sales record
of anyone here.
It's not about numbers.
It's about attitude.
I have the worst attitude
of any person here.
Do you want the raise or what?
Yeah, I'll take it.
With this raise
there are strings attached.
And the string
is attached from my heart
to your mean attitude.
You're bribing me.
No, I am not.
Unless you want me to.
You want me to? 'cause I will.
I will bribe you.
Your face is saying... don't.
Unless I haven't offered you enough.
Your face isn't changing.
What is it?
Talk to me, face.
Tell me what Pam's brain is thinking.
Come on, what do you want?
What do you want?
Do you want a million dollars?
Do you want to hit me?
You want me to get down and beg you?
I want to hit you.
- What?
- I want to hit you. I'll do that.
What? I don't...
Are you kidding?
No. Are you kidding?
Ye... No. I don't...
All right, come on.
I take off my jacket, tense my stomach,
and you just...
I don't think I can hit you...
in the office.
So we'll do it after work.
In the parking lot.
In front of everyone.
I'm gonna hit you as hard as I can.
- See you then.
- See you.
Quick question.
Are you scared?
Never.
About what? A little.
What are you talking about?
- We heard about the punch.
- What punch?
Pam's gonna punch the crap
out of your face after work.
I'm pretty sure we said "slap."
No, it's a punch.
And Pam has that crazy
pregnancy strength now.
I'm getting concerned
that you don't seem to understand
what's going to happen.
Do you?
- I'm good.
- All right, see you there.
- Do you and Pam ever get frisky?
- Inappropriate.
I mean,
do you ever wrestle?
- All the time.
- Really? Is she strong?
- She wants it bad.
- Can you stop this?
I can.
And I don't support
her choice to hit you.
- I don't either.
- But at the same time, she goes crazy.
And I do understand her reasoning.
I know.
I just need some time
to think about it.
You gotta do something.
How much time do you need?
- No more than a week. Maybe two.
- Come on, man!
Can I talk to you for a second?
I heard about the hit.
It's off company property, right?
So, it's okay.
The power comes from the back foot.
So it's all one motion
through the body.
So there's...
You stay a little low.
There's a twist.
You keep your shoulder down.
You kind of throw out the arm.
Okay, wait. It's...
Yore saying it comes from the foot?
Hey, everybody,
he's not in the men's room,
although the seat was warm,
so we may have just missed him.
My money's on Pam.
It's not a fight.
What other outcome could there be?
- Michael could win.
- How? He can't hit back.
Why can't you just
agree with me sometimes?
Am I scared
of getting hit in the face? No.
Every day, weirdos pay dominatrices
hundreds of dollars
for that very privilege.
I'm scared I'm gonna love it.
Let's do this!
It's okay, guys, I can handle this.
- Everybody can go home.
- We're here for the show, Michael.
You're just a bunch of voyeurs.
- Are you eating popcorn?
- It has almost no calories.
You ready?
- You have to keep your hands down.
- I know.
- Keep your hands down.
- Put your hands in your pockets.
- I'm really sorry. I'm sorry.
- What are you sorry for?
So many things.
I don't know, it's hard to choose.
- How'bout for dating my mom.
- Maybe that's...
And dumping her on her birthday.
Don't ever date
a member of my family again.
No problem.
For the record,
your mom came on to me.
Holy crap!
- Are you okay?
- No!
You're okay.
- Feel better?
- No. You were right.
- Wait, why are you limping?
- I don't know.
Let's get some raw meat
on that face.
I've got a chicken
in the freezer upstairs.
As I watched Pam's
big, strong hand
coming toward my face,
I saw my entire life flash
before my eyes.
And guess what.
I have four kids.
And I have a hover-car
and a hover-house.
And my wife is a runner,
and it shows.
And Pam and Jim are my best friends,
and our kids play together.
And I am happy,
I'm rich,
and I never die.
It doesn't sound like much,
but it's enough for me.
Good, just keep it
for another five minutes,
let the swelling go down.
Thanks, I owe you one.
Fire Jim.
- I'm cashing in the favor. Fire him.
- What are you talking about?
Promote me, try manager.
- Forget that.
- Can I have an office?
You can keep your stupid favor,
it's worthless.
And this is my dinner on your face.
I'm keeping it.
It feels better.