I'm sorry, you probably noticed
my stomach's
a little more sensitive lately,
so if you wouldn't mind
wearing a little less perfume...
And if your lunch is especially pungent,
maybe have it in the break room.
We would really appreciate it.
Pam is constantly throwing up
because of the pregnancy.
If she eats something
the fetus doesn't like,
she is screwed.
It's amazing.
A three-ounce fetus
is calling the shots.
It's so badass.
If you could switch to a different soap
just for a month or two...
yours is kind of perfumey.
This is getting ridiculous.
Gee, I'm sorry.
I guess I missed the meeting
where we voted for you to get pregnant.
I reserve the right to peel
my hardboiled eggs at my desk.
All morning I look forward
to my afternoon cigars,
and I am not stopping for anybody.
I don't think
I'm asking for too much.
I guess it's just the end
of courtesy in the workplace.
Watching people get sick
always makes me sick.
And...
Frankly,
so does talking about it, so...
- Feygnasse Team -
.:: La Fabrique ::.
Collioure
Jarick
loky
do_Ob
Titou
Sk0r
yomoy
The Ni.Knight
Episodes 6x04 - 6x05
Niagara
What do you think?
- Spent all morning doing it.
- It is really special.
But aren't you supposed
to do that to our...
No, it's great.
It's just
a really important day for me.
Congrats.
Dunder Mifflin Scranton
will be closed today and Friday
for a company wedding
in Niagara Falls,
so please leave a message,
and we'll get back to you.
Have a great day.
Believe it or not, Kevin,
firecrackers are in the "don't" column.
So you're gonna provide them, then?
This is a firecracker-free wedding.
- What the hell?
- You've got to be kidding me.
These things are important to remember,
but the most important thing
is that no one say anything
about my pregnancy at the wedding.
Absolutely, because not everyone knows,
and some people might be offended.
Decent people everywhere
will get offended.
We're thinking of my grandmother,
who we haven't told,
and who is very old-fashioned.
You're lucky
to have a grandmother.
Some of us have to be
our own grandmother.
You know, Angela,
you don't have to come to the wedding.
- Really, Pam?
- Yes, she does.
We're all gonna go,
and we're gonna have a good time.
He pinched me.
Next time we're all in this room,
Jim and I will be married.
We'll see.
Thank you, Dwight.
See you later.
Hey, and don't
embarrass me
when we go to Niagara.
What happens in Niagara
stays in Niagara.
Don't, don't, don't.
You stole my joke.
Don't steal my joke.
- No, I didn't steal your joke.
- Yes, I said that yesterday.
You can say that about anything.
What happens in accounting
stays in accounting.
Please, please.
Dwight, that's my joke.
It's so easy.
That's what I'm saying.
This is what I am talking about.
When we leave here
and go up to Niagara Falls,
we are representing Dunder Mifflin,
everyone.
This is a very important wedding
for this branch.
The most important
until I get married,
so I want you all
on your best behavior.
Or so help me, God!
So I will see you up there
in "Viagra" Falls.
Pam and Jim's wedding will be
the single best pickup destination
in the history of the universe.
I stole the guest list
from Jim's desk,
and I search-engined every female
on both sides of the family.
Get out of here.
My God.
For instance, Pam's cousin
Jocelyn Webster.
There's a name.
Two years ago, she was selling
a mountain bike.
Tell me about Jocelyn.
What's she like?
She's really into mountain biking,
but not so much lately.
She had
a couple hundred dollars to spend.
I mean, if she was able
to sell her bike.
Is that all you have on her?
If this in fact her,
because it's a very common name.
You're an idiot.
People don't think of me
as one of the sharper dressers
in the office,
but I'm going to turn that around
at this wedding.
I thought,
"how can I take it
to the next level?"
The hair.
It's the hair.
I'm going.
God.
Did one of you want to sit up front
so I have someone to talk to?
It's, like, a five-hour drive...
Ish. You know.
This is so much cooler.
We feel like we're in a limo
and you're our driver.
That wouldn't be fair
to leave Kelly alone in back.
Not only is Erin
really sweet and cute...
she smells like my mom.
My aunt told me something neat.
She said everything with the wedding
goes by so fast,
we should try to take
mental pictures of the high points.
That's cool.
You blinked.
Damn it.
Now that's in my brain forever.
What a lousy picture.
Should have hired a professional
to take the mental pictures.
- I was asleep.
- What? No way.
Those glasses are super dark.
All right.
We need some tunes, I think.
I made you a CD.
You did?
That was nice of you.
This is to play when you bring
a woman back to your hotel room.
Very thoughtful.
A little mix to set the mood.
Delightful. Pop that in.
You're gonna like this.
Hello.
My name is Dwight Schrute.
If you're listening to this,
you're a lucky woman
Michael has seduced.
To be in your shoes.
"What's next?"
you're probably wondering.
Don't be scared
of your night in heaven.
Seriously? You want me to play that
for a woman coming to my room?
It's practical.
That's not how it works.
Niagara Falls used to be,
like, a spiritual experience to people.
They stayed in tents,
and it blew their minds.
But it's really kitschy now,
which is a lot of fun.
Halpert.
- Halpert.
- And Beesly.
Tonight we're in two separate rooms,
and tomorrow is the honeymoon suite.
- Great.
- I know, we're pretty excited too.
Can we take a look at the suite now?
I'm sorry.
Somebody just checked in.
Is there another wedding
at the hotel this weekend?
Just an individual.
That man there.
I got the room
the night before you guys.
I'll break in the bed.
I don't like that.
I'm gonna need
the name of the housekeeper
responsible
for changing the sheets, please.
- Reservation for Michael Scott.
- One moment while I check.
Their proximity to the Falls
makes everything smell like a basement.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm not seeing you in here.
- When did you make your reservation?
- I don't have a reservation,
but I want a room
in the Beesly-Halpert block of rooms.
Unfortunately, sir,
the block only applies to the rate.
I'm afraid we're all sold out.
I have a reservation.
Confirmation number:
Romeo, Tango,
G, 7, 7,
4, 5.
Yes. Schrute.
And I had spoken to Theresa
about a room with two safes.
Sure. No problem.
There's your key, Mr. Schrute.
Thank you.
- I need to stay in your room.
- What if I meet someone?
I'm staying in...
Come on, I would do the same for you.
You would? Really?
Let's just... Go.
Wait a second.
This must be some kind of mistake.
This reservation
is under an M. Scott.
- This must be yours.
- Thank God.
Now that I don't have a room,
can I stay with you?
You know what?
I would say yes,
but you can't,
and I'll tell you why.
If I have a woman up there
and things are getting amorous,
she's gonna get turned off
if she looks in the bathroom
and she sees you brushing your teeth
with butter and clay, okay?
That was a test, and you have failed,
for this is my room.
- You'd not share it.
- I don't have a room?
No, you do not.
You must pass
the dungeon wisdom test.
It worked.
When Mary was denied
a room at the inn,
Jesus was born.
When Michael was denied
a room at the inn,
we don't know what happens,
because that story hasn't been told yet.
Mr. And Mrs. Stanley Hudson.
Favor.
Could I stay in your room tonight?
Are you out of your mind?
I brought Cynthia with me.
Not in the same bed.
In the other bed.
I got one queen-size bed.
You are kidding me.
A queen-size bed is five-feet wide.
I am not five-feet wide, Michael.
I'm not a physics major, Stanley.
I'm just saying be careful.
Hey, guys.
Could I stay in your room tonight?
- Gross.
- Blow my brains out.
That's rude.
I have an extra twin bed,
if you want.
You are going to be sleeping by yourself
for the rest of your life,
so you should just get used to it.
So...
which one is Pam's grandma?
Meemaw?
She's the one in the teal suit.
She's the only 80-year-old
with no smile wrinkles.
Dad, remember.
No mention of the baby, right?
She's very conservative.
So mum's the word.
- Dad, this is Michael Scott.
- How you doing? Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Who's doing a toast?
I would like to go third,
sort of back clean up.
I thought we discussed
that we'd rather you not speak,
like, at all,
because
it's just gonna be blood relatives.
That is seriously going to impede
my ability to hook up
with your female relatives.
Pretty sure everybody heard that.
Didn't move my lips.
{\BEESLY - HALPRET
WEDDING REHEARSAL DINNER}
Hey, meemaw.
I wasn't sure
about your branch of the family.
After I heard
about your parents divorce.
But you and Jim are...
just perfect.
God bless you.
But nobody's perfect.
I wouldn't care to live
if I thought that.
- Mr. Beesly, how are you?
- I'd like you to meet Kristy Kelly.
This your niece?
She's my girlfriend.
Can you make room at that table?
From quarter three to quarter four,
up 17%.
While his sales, down 2%.
It's in the report.
Why they make the bad man your boss
if you're so much smarter?
Excellent question.
Because while I was busy
trying to improve the company
and make it a success,
Jim...
the bad man
was busy
kissing the boss man's butt.
That's right. It is ew.
It's very ew.
Oscar, Kevin,
this is my sister, Penny.
She's also my maid of honor.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm sorry. It's Kevin?
I thought it was Gill.
She thought I was your boyfriend.
You thought I was dating this?
What is wrong with you?
Oscar, it was an honest mistake.
Him?
Oscar, I would be proud to date you.
I'm sorry.
I'm not gay. I'm Kevin.
Nice to meet you.
- Owe me an apology.
- I'm so sorry.
Are you seeing anyone?
She has a boyfriend.
He's out of town.
I was the youngest VP
in company history.
More recently,
he worked in a bowling alley.
Tell 'em
one of your funny bowling alley stories.
How did Meredith get put
at the young people's table?
She probably switched cards
with someone.
Like I did with Erin.
What?
That's...
Jim and Pam,
I can't tell you
how happy I am to be here.
Head table.
Where I belong.
- It's just for family.
- I know.
Who's that one?
Isabel Poreba.
I got stuff on her.
In 1996,
her 10th grade volleyball team
went 10 and 2.
What am I supposed to do with that?
That's a very good record.
Right, so I'll be like,
"you're so sweet and so kind."
- I'll do the face like...
- Like, "what?"
And then we'll just give 'em
a little punch to the back.
A noogie.
You know what? Never to married...
for a noogie.
They have hilarious material,
and they are going to deliver it wrong.
I would kill with the brother stuff.
It should be me...
up there.
Should be me and Pete.
Not Pete and Tom.
You've got the greatest smile,
- and your body is really fine.
- Smoking.
Hoping it'll make our wives
kick it up a notch.
A little mo' cardio.
That's not appropriate.
Hello. Hi, everybody.
I promise I wasn't gonna make a toast,
and I'm not going to.
Just going to do
a little freestanding comedy,
and if at the end, everybody wants
to raise their glasses to Pam and Jim,
then so be it.
What is the deal with the Smart car?
How smart is that?
Those things are tiny.
Can you even drive them in traffic?
"I'm so smart.
E equals MC...
squared. I drive a Smart car."
That's not smart in my book.
The real smart car is Kitt.
From Knight Rider.
That's a car that can talk.
Can a Smart car talk?
That's not smart.
And also Chitty Chitty Bang Bang.
- Very smart.
- And...
Everybody can laugh.
It doesn't have
to just be the idiots.
Everybody can laugh.
Go ahead.
All right.
Hey, everyone. Thanks for coming.
Douche.
Thanks, Pete. Really nice.
I just want to say how happy we are
that all of you are here tonight,
and I want to especially thank
those who have traveled from far away
to be here with us tonight,
especially the Florida cousins,
who obviously can't take a hint.
Four years ago, I was...
just a guy who had a crush on a girl
who had a boyfriend.
And...
I had to do the hardest thing
that I've ever had to do,
which was just to...
wait.
Don't get me wrong.
I flirted with her.
Pam, I can now admit
that I do know how to make a photocopy.
Didn't need your help
that many times.
And do you remember
how long it took you
- to teach me how to drive stick?
- Like, a year.
I've been driving stick
since high school, so...
For a really long time,
that's all I had.
Little moments
with a girl who saw me as a friend.
And a lot of people told me
I was crazy to wait this long
for a date
with a girl who I worked with,
but I think even then I knew that...
I was waiting for my wife.
I would like to propose a toast.
If you'd all raise your glasses...
Not Pam, for obvious reasons,
but everyone else, if you would...
What's obvious?
Why can't Pam drink?
Pam can't drink?
I didn't... I shouldn't have said that.
I don't know why I did.
She can do whatever she wants.
Though she shouldn't.
She shouldn't,
because she's an alcoholic.
Pam is an alcoholic.
That's not true.
What we wanted...
The real reason is that...
That Pam's pregnant.
What I think Jim
is trying to say is that...
they had an accident.
And you know what?
These two people,
they're living together.
They are having
lots of consensual sex.
- They were living together?
- Yes, they were living...
And you know what? You can't...
expect them
to be careful every time,
because, frankly,
it's just a different sensation.
When you come... Am I wrong?
They say it's not different,
but it's a different sensation...
- Don't. Please.
- When you use something
to block...
I think everybody knows
what I am talking about.
It's not necessarily different
for the woman,
but it is different...
My point is,
I said what I wanted to say,
and, meemaw,
I hope you heard every word.
To waiting.
I should have known.
The hotel's television set
had a movie on
called Bruno last night.
The remote control
had so darn many buttons on it,
I couldn't turn it off.
So I had to just sit there
while it happened to me.
I wondered,
"how could they pick such a hotel?"
Now I know.
Think it was a little touch and go,
but we saved it, I believe.
I can't believe it was me.
I can't believe it was you, either.
I actually think
it takes a lot of pressure off of me.
Is there something about being a manager
that makes you say stupid things?
I haven't found that to be the case.
- Smooth guys.
- I'm so sorry.
Can you believe it?
He screwed up, not me.
Meemaw's not coming to the wedding.
She's leaving.
Are you serious?
There's gonna be a free room?
It's Michael.
You're that foul man
that kept talking about intercourse.
One and the same. May I?
I'm actually great with old women.
In fact, for the longest time,
my best friend was my grandmother.
And then she met Harriet,
and now she thinks
she's better than everybody.
I want to go to bed,
but I can't.
I can't turn that television off.
Hook you up there.
- You're welcome.
- It was that horrible Charlie Rose.
Isn't he terrible?
May I?
Here's the thing.
I think you just need to chill out
about this whole
Pam getting pregnant thing.
It's not 1890 anymore.
It's modern day.
And women have sex before marriage.
And I think
we need to celebrate that.
And I know in your day
she would be considered a whore,
but now
women go out
and they have sex and they get wild
and they take their tops off
and they have
pictures taken of them.
We need to encourage that.
That's part of life.
People are like cats and dogs
these days.
Exactly.
This used to be
such a great country.
- I know.
- I don't know what happened.
They're gonna name
the baby after you, you know?
- They're gonna call it meemaw.
- You mean Sylvia.
And if it's a boy,
they will call it Sylvio.
Par-tay. Room 639.
Chicks are gonna be off the hook.
Guys too, Oscar.
Like Calvin Klein models.
That sounds epic.
Can we bring anything?
Nothing.
Except for $40 for beer
and any hot chicks you know.
'Cause that would help me deliver
on some promises I made.
No one from the office has been
to a real Bernard
throw-down.
If I was a girl,
I would seriously reconsider coming.
But don't tell them that I said that,
'cause I want them there.
And where do you think you're going?
I was gonna go down
to the hotel bar.
Why don't I just save you some time
and kick you in the stomach instead?
I wanted to get out of my room
for a little while.
I'll go with you.
Come on.
Never mind.
Are you sure? Could be fun.
What are you wearing?
Come on.
It's a casual, social outfit.
Looks
like you're going to a fish fry.
They're howling at the moon.
It's suggestive to women.
Because of howling during sex.
That's not appropriate.
Uncool, Dwight.
Come on. Let's go.
- It's good.
- It's not a good idea.
There's no such thing
as a good hairpiece.
But that's easy enough for you
to say, Oscar.
You've that thick,
beautiful Chicano hair.
So nice.
I'm just worried about the farm.
Mose hates to geld the horses
by himself.
Shut up about the farm.
It's not relatable.
Nobody owns a farm.
Wait,
you're worried about your horses?
That's cool.
How many horses do you have?
Nine and three quarters.
I invented a device
called "Burger on the go".
It allows you to obtain
six regular-sized hamburgers,
or 12 sliders,
from a horse
without killing the animal.
George Foreman
is still considering it.
Sharper Image is still considering it,
Skymall's still considering it,
Hammacher Schlemmer's
still considering it.
Sears said no.
Toy Story,
Finding Nemo, Up,
I balled the entire time.
I can not watch Pixar.
- Drop this one. Abort.
- Why?
I found twins.
Twins.
I'm sorry. You understand.
Nice to meet you.
Aren't they magnificent?
They're men, Dwight.
I love finding a good set of twins.
Something's wrong with you.
Nice moves!
You call that a robot?
Try being more robotic, okay?
Like this.
Lame.
What else you got, Andy?
How about a little bit of this?
What else you got?
Did someone change my name
to Baskin Robbins?
Because I feel like a banana split.
What else you got?
It's gonna be fine.
Pam's here.
I was dancing and I did a split,
and I landed
on my car keys in my pocket.
What?
I tore my scrotum.
I need you to take me to the hospital.
Andy,
I'm getting married in eight hours.
Everyone else is too drunk.
Just don't let me die here.
Where are you?
Can you take Andy to the hospital?
- What?
- He tore his scrotum dancing.
- He is in my room, icing his balls.
- What?
- Please stop saying "What?"
- Can you take him?
- I would so take him
in any other circumstance,
but I'm pretty certain
I'm completely wasted.
Your brothers took you out drinking?
Is that Pam?
Have her come out.
Have her come out!
It'll be like Coyote Ugly.
That's Michael.
You're out with Michael?
And Dwight.
- Pam, it just happened.
- Fine.
I'll take him.
I love you. I got to go.
I love you!
- Are you pushing me off the phone?
- No. Let's talk for a long time.
Good-bye.
It's after midnight.
You're married.
He's married!
That's not how that works.
- You'll not be able to talk back.
- You'll have Pam to answer to.
She'll be sitting at home saying:
"Jim, take the baby to the zoo,
"cause I want to sit at home
and eat bonbons...
"and clip my toenails."
"Why don't you braid my hair?
- "I want to watch TV."
- Now you sound like Kermit.
Are you sure this is the right way?
I, like you,
have never been here before.
At least slow down a little bit,
because every little bump in the road
is major pain on...
my scrotum.
I'm not the one
who asked you to do a split
when you'd never done one before.
I was trying to liven things up.
I was kind of doing your job, so...
My job?
My job is to get married
in the morning.
That's my job.
It's also to make sure we have
a great time at your stupid wedding,
so...
Just spent the night with the bride
the night before the wedding.
She stepped on my hand
on her way to the bathroom.
Andy, did I dream
that you were crying through the night?
That was real.
Why don't you take a picture?
It'll last longer.
Can I get a little privacy?
Good morning.
How can I help you?
I left
a pair of dress shoes in a bag
outside my door last night
to be cleaned and polished,
but they haven't been returned yet.
You must be Mr. Malone.
One moment please.
Sir, this is the man with the shoes.
Mr. Malone, your shoes are gone.
They were stolen?
No, destroyed.
When the bag was opened
by our shoeshine,
the smell overcame him.
I, too, smelled them
and made the choice
that they must be thrown away.
Incinerated, actually.
But that was my only pair of shoes.
It became a safety issue, sir.
Damn it.
I can offer you
a complimentary breakfast.
You have everything?
Cell phone?
Charger?
So you sure you don't want breakfast?
It's the most important meal of the day.
It really is.
I'm not hungry.
I ate a bunch of sunflower seeds
after you went to sleep.
And besides,
I don't want to take you away from Pam
on the morning of her wedding.
She needs you, Isabel.
That's really sweet, Dwight.
So I'll see you at the wedding?
You know it.
Get out of here.
Good morning.
It's about damn time, I haven't gone
to the bathroom in a day and a half.
- This room is a pit.
- Really? Hadn't noticed.
Too busy knockin' boots.
How can you eat like that?
I'm ravenous
after a night of lovemaking.
You?
I'm hungry, but I'm not gonna make
a pig out of myself.
What was she like?
She was cute.
You know, she was hot.
She was very hot.
She made love like a tiger.
Bride side or groom side?
Or townie?
She was from Europe.
No kidding.
Bet she had hairy armpits.
Isabel was nice, but...
I hope she doesn't think
this is going anywhere.
Wait a second.
You're not into her?
Are you kidding me?
She's Pam's best friend.
You guys could double date.
Swap maybe?
Put a gun in my mouth.
You're crazy.
She's a dental hygienist
from Carbondale,
and she makes love like one.
She's a bumpkin. Pass.
You know how hard it is?
You have to take X-Rays.
You have to scrape the plaque of teeth.
You have to tell kids when to spit
and make sure that they're not scared
when the dentist comes in.
Ask her out.
I already have
a European girlfriend.
Are you in a lot of pain?
'Cause of last night?
No way.
Reports have been exaggerated.
Weddings make me very emotional.
I have that side.
People say you cry all the time.
That's...
not...
Crotch injuries are the worst.
You don't need to tell me.
I wasn't telling you.
- There's still something there?
- Excuse me?
It didn't get torn off?
They didn't...
Nothing got torn off.
Who told you that?
I may have told some people that.
I'm nervous.
I'm about to get married.
If you want to sit on this...
I was thinking the wood might be
too hard on your damaged penis.
Make it softer.
It's my scrotum.
And it was.
Sure.
Here we go.
They asked for cash, but,
you know,
I give 'em cash every week.
So how much cash does a person need?
I have taken it upon myself
to do something a little more special.
I have painted a portrait
of the two of them
from memory.
And I have
another one of them in the nude.
But that one is for me.
I got them
a set of turtle-boiling pots,
shell hammer,
and bibs.
Is it zipping over your belly?
Don't squish the baby.
Thank you, weirdo.
Everybody see
Kristy's stupid, blond extensions?
It's like they were made
from a plastic broom.
Here I come.
Darling, you look beautiful.
Thanks, mom.
I hope he deserves you.
He does.
Are you sure?
Remember, you don't have to do this.
You don't.
You're totally projecting
and being a drag.
Thank you, mom.
I'm gonna go outside
and talk to Dwight.
Great.
I'll see you in a second.
Wait, what?
- Can you come here please?
- Is this allowed?
But I'm allowing it.
Just come here.
That was an intelligent comment.
Hello, stranger.
How do I look?
Fine.
Isabel, nice to see you.
What do you want?
Nothing...
anymore.
So...
tell me again the difference
between Filene's and Filene's basement.
He's not sitting with me, either.
Where are you sitting?
You need a seat, buddy?
I'm standing.
I'm a bridesmaid.
I wish I was a bridesmaid.
Where am I gonna go?
You look...
Terrible.
So beautiful.
My veil tore.
I knew when we were getting married
and I'm five months pregnant
that I'm not gonna be able
to wear the dress that I always wanted,
or high heels.
You look just as I imagined you.
Pam, you're so pretty.
And who cares?
It's a stupid veil, right?
No, this is the one thing
I was supposed to be able to control
was this veil.
There.
Now we're even.
Everyone's driving me crazy.
I know way too much
about Andy's scrotum,
and my mom won't stop
freaking out
about my dad's new girlfriend.
This is supposed
to be our wedding day.
Why did we invite all these people?
I think Pam ran away
because she knew deep down
she wouldn't be a good wife.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to decide
if I have time to pee.
- How long do you take to pee?
- The peeing is fast, Oscar.
It's getting my tie back on.
Would you have a snack
in your purse?
You're a mom.
I just figured you might have...
Apricot.
Do you have any of the Very Berry
or Ocean Splash, or...
Were you saving it?
That's okay. I just...
I've had a very rough...
weekend.
I'm sorry.
Apricot. Made of real apes.
They canceled the wedding?
Relax.
You'll get your shot at Jim.
Those two treat the whole office
like a 1970's key party.
My weekend's bad so far.
I came here hoping to meet somebody.
You know, as you do,
at weddings.
End up...
going to sleep
by the vending machine.
- It was loud, but it was warm.
- That sounds awful.
And...
the love of my life
is dating somebody else.
It's just...
It is a terrible year for love.
I guess.
Thinking
about having my sperm frozen.
Excuse me, are you Michael Scott?
Heard you might have
a whoopee cushion on you.
Our sister's in the can, and we want
to get her when she comes back.
That sounds hilarious.
I do, actually.
There you go.
Use it in good health.
Wait a minute, what is the etiquette
on taking the gifts?
Can you only take your own back,
or is it
a whatever-you-can-carry type of thing?
Anyone have anything
they want to trade for a toaster?
Does it have slots for hot dogs?
Who would want it?
Guys, maybe we should wait
a little more time
before we start grabbing boxes.
I like to lodge a complaint against Jim
for making us wait for over an hour.
Get in there.
I guess this wedding
is not gonna happen.
Wonder if this is it for them.
What happened?
Where were you?
Do you know I've been waiting here?
We are here now, so let's go.
I have so much joy in my heart
right now.
How do I look?
- You look great.
Wear a tie much?
I begged them not to.
I know you specifically put this song
on your do not play list.
I did.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
I think it's your turn.
What happened?
You're okay with this?
I'm okay.
Okay then.
Did you see this?
It was on YouTube.
Saw it.
I bought those boat tickets
the day I saw that YouTube video.
I knew we'd need a backup plan.
The boat was actually plan C,
the church was plan B,
and plan A was...
marrying her a long, long time ago.
Pretty much the day I met her.
What an awesome party.
The best wedding I've ever been to.
I got six numbers.
One more would have been
a complete telephone number.
This was epic.
My Kleenex shoes
were a huge conversation piece,
but man,
my dogs are barking.
My feet were so sweaty,
I can't even feel the cold.
What a lovely hotel.