Previously on This Is Us...
Now remember, big brothers look
out for their little brothers.
It's their only job.
I want to enlist, Doc.
I need to be there with him.
Hey, little brother.
BETH: I have known her all of her life.
Her background is complicated.
She will break you, Kevin.
KEVIN: That is a visa application
for a trip to Vietnam.
I'm gonna go to the place
where my dad last served.
I'm gonna track down that woman,
and I'm gonna figure out my dad's story.
Vietnam, huh?
- Do you want to go?
- Yeah.
Yeah, all right.
Do you want to go on a drive?
Where do you want to go?
Los Angeles.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah, let's go to Los Angeles.
♪
Hi. Uh, could I get a look at that one?
Shiny. Girls like shiny, right?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
PILOT (OVER P.A.): Preparing for landing
at Tân Son Nhat International Airport.
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
(FLAMES CRACKLING)
Jack.
Is that really you?
Yeah, it's really me.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
If you die out here, that's not on me.
It's okay.
Don't, no. Don't touch me.
Don't look at me.
You're not here. I'm not here.
I'm not even here.
(NICKY SNIFFS)
What are you on, Nick?
(SNIFFS)
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING)
I'm gonna get you out of here.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
(LAUGHS): How?
- I'll figure something out.
- Oh, yeah?
Why, do you got a plan, Jack?
I got charged with Article 15.
That's unbecoming conduct.
I'll figure something out.
Jesus Christ.
You know...
it was just a nickname, man.
You're not Superman.
It's just a... stupid nickname.
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO)
♪ Sitting in a park in Paris, France ♪
♪ Reading the news
and it sure looks bad ♪
- ♪ They won't give peace a chance ♪
- (SIGHS)
♪ That was just a dream
some of us had... ♪
Well, we're officially
out of Pittsburgh.
Only 2,423 more miles
till we get to Los Angeles.
- So almost there.
- Yeah, exactly.
(BOTH LAUGH)
♪ I'll even kiss a sunset pig ♪
♪ California, I'm coming home... ♪
My mom says I'm nuts for doing
this with a guy I barely know.
We've known each other a whole week.
(CHUCKLES)
♪ Who did the goat dance very well ♪
♪ He gave me back my smile, but
he kept my camera to sell... ♪
The record label that
I'm meeting with out in L.A.?
- Mm-hmm.
- They actually released this album.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- (TURNS UP VOLUME)
- ♪ But my heart cried out for you... ♪
They'd be lucky to have you. I mean...
This woman's got nothing on you.
D... "This woman" is Joni Mitchell,
and she runs circles around me.
- I don't think so.
- Um, she does.
(SIGHS)
Oh, I can't wait to get to L.A.
Sunset Boulevard.
The Pacific Ocean.
- Mm.
See, I love being from Pittsburgh,
but sometimes it just feels
a little small.
- Yeah.
- ♪ All the news of home... ♪
Oh, my friend, Nicole,
says that we can stay with her
- as long as we need to.
- Sounds good.
♪ Bought me a ticket,
I got on a plane to Spain ♪
♪ Went to a party
down a red dirt road... ♪
Is there anything that you want
to do in particular
when you're out in L.A.?
I want to go see some folks
I know in Reseda.
Oh.
Friends of yours or...?
Yeah, sort of.
♪ Oh, will you take me as I am? ♪
♪ Strung out on another man... ♪
I made some turkey sandwiches.
I don't know if you're
a turkey fan, but...
- I love turkey.
- Ah, me, too.
Look at us... couple of turkey freaks.
- (LAUGHS)
- Driving across the country.
And my mom said it was too soon
to take a road trip.
Yeah?
♪ Take me as I am. ♪
I can't believe we're in Vietnam.
It's amazing.
I wonder if my dad actually
flew in here before
he was stationed, you know?
It's like I already kind of feel
connected to him just being here.
Hey, when do we get
to my dad's fishing village?
- Monday.
- Awesome.
Hey.
Say "Vietna-cheese."
- I just made that up.
- I'm sure.
Just don't tag me on Instagram.
Really?
I thought we graduated
to "tagging" status.
It's not that.
I just don't want my dad
to know I'm in Vietnam.
I'm gonna need more words.
My father lives in China.
If he sees I'm in Vietnam, he'll
try and reach out and see me.
Don't want to see him.
- Your father lives in China?
- Yeah.
You literally never
mentioned that before.
Or-or really anything about your family.
Well... Hey, I found us
this great market for lunch.
Best bánh bèo in town.
It's like eating the ocean.
Okay. Yeah, no. Looks great.
Let's, uh, let the greatest trip
of all time begin.
Major Dawson?
- Who are you?
- I'm Jack Pearson.
Nicky Pearson's brother.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
I'm a staff sergeant down
a ville on the Sông Trà Khúc.
Came here for my brother.
I was hoping to take him back with me.
- Get his ass squared away.
- (SCOFFS)
That kid hasn't been
"squared away" for months.
Insubordination,
partying like it's Woodstock.
That's why I got him on doo-doo detail.
I can get him right, sir. I know I can.
Why's that, Pearson?
'Cause you're his brother?
'Cause you used to share a room?
Used to whisper ghost stories
to each other in the dark?
He's not cut out for this.
That's why I'm here.
Well, you're too late.
You know, we did used to share a room.
Drafty old house,
a lot of spiders, big spiders.
Spiders so big,
you could see their knees.
My father saw one of them,
he'd take the nearest
rolled-up newspaper,
smash the hell out of it.
You know what Nicky would do
when he saw a spider?
He'd go to the kitchen,
he'd get himself a glass,
grab a comic book,
and then carefully, so carefully,
he would guide the spider onto the book,
trap it under the glass
and then take it outside,
so it could crawl away.
That was his favorite part,
watching it be okay.
(SIGHS)
I need to try and save my little brother
before 'Nam eats him alive.
Sir, please.
We don't put brothers
in the same outfit.
That's basic policy.
I mean, who wants to write
two condolence letters
to the same mother?
Now I suggest you make your way
back to your ville.
Guess you're walking.
V.C. owns the road at night.
You better move out.
Sir.
Thank you.
Chicken. Bat.
KEVIN: Great. Appreciate it.
I wonder what "bat" means in English.
It means bat.
Hmm?
Really? You're just gonna sit
there and casually eat a bat?
I like to immerse myself when I travel.
- You want to try?
- No. No, I do not.
No way. No way in hell. You enjoy.
- Coward.
- Well, I'm sorry
my taste buds aren't
eclectic like yours.
We were more of a, like, a beige
food fam growing up, you know?
A lot of chicken nuggets,
lot of mac and cheese.
Want to get wild, we'd go,
like, chicken potpie
every once in a while. What about you?
What about me?
Well, you know, what was dinner
like when you were a kid?
For you. I mean, I know you
moved in with Beth's family
when you were eight,
I know that, but before that.
I don't know. Dinner's dinner.
- Right. Got it.
- Oh, God.
Please tell me we don't look
that touristy.
Excuse me. Excu...
Excuse me. Hi.
Your necklace, I... uh,
uh, do you mind telling me
where you got that?
Souvenir shop, at the entrance.
Here.
(MOUTHS)
Can I ask you a question.
Do you sell a lot of these?
(SALESGIRL SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
Sell many, many, many.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
JACK: So how did you get this meeting?
With the record company?
My friend Nicole got my demo
to an assistant,
and then the assistant
got it to an A&R guy there.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
And what happens when they fall
in love with you?
- Which they will.
- (LAUGHS)
I think I make a more
professional-sounding demo.
And then, if by some miracle,
that goes well,
I make a full album.
And then, if we're really
getting into fantasyland, I...
...I open up for Neil Young.
Mm. And then I'm just on the road.
Is that what you want?
- I don't know.
- Hmm.
I just love watching
people dance while I sing.
People don't slow dance nearly
as much as they should.
- (EXHALES)
- (SONG ENDS)
And I... love doing my small part
to keep it alive.
Hint taken.
("LONELY COMIN' DOWN"
BY DOLLY PARTON PLAYING)
Oh.
(LAUGHS): Okay.
♪ I woke up ♪
♪ This morning ♪
♪ In a strange place ♪
- Ooh.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
♪ I looked into... ♪
Where did you get those moves?
Well, it wasn't Christmas in my
house until my mom got to dance
- to Frank Sinatra's Christmas record.
- Mm-hmm.
My dad, he didn't
like to dance with her.
So I, I might have picked up
a move or two.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
♪ But you could not be found... ♪
(QUIETLY): Look how sweet they are.
(CHUCKLING)
Sorry, I'm kind of an easy cry.
That's okay.
I mean, I usually make it
past the third date.
(BOTH LAUGH)
What about you? Are you a crier?
Nope. Never.
- Never?
- Mm-mmm.
Like...
not even at the end of Old Yeller?
No, I...
I've gotten really good at just
swallowing the bad stuff.
This is nice.
You know, it's like I always say.
People don't slow dance nearly
as much as they should.
♪ I woke up this morning ♪
♪ In a strange place... ♪
- Yeah, that's...
- Yeah, exactly.
♪ I looked into the mirror... ♪
Did you want to use the sink first?
- Hmm?
- To, uh, brush your teeth, or...
Oh, yeah. Okay.
♪ Then I looked ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ But you could not ♪
♪ Be found ♪
♪ And then I felt the lonely ♪
♪ Coming down... ♪
You know, I think my grandfather
had those pajamas.
Be quiet. I like to be toasty
when I sleep.
♪ To the empty bed ♪
♪ Saw the imprint ♪
♪ On the pillow ♪
♪ Where you laid your head ♪
♪ The presence of you... ♪
Three dates, three kisses.
Three amazing kisses.
♪ Around ♪
♪ And once again ♪
♪ I felt the lonely ♪
♪ Coming down ♪
♪ Then I felt the lonely ♪
♪ Dripping down ♪
♪ My face ♪
♪ As I realized ♪
♪ No one could take your place ♪
♪ And then again, I felt the lonely ♪
♪ Coming down ♪
♪ Hmm, hmm... ♪
(LAUGHS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GASPING)
REBECCA: Hey.
Hey, Jack.
Hey, Jack, Jack. Hey, Jack.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay. (SNIFFS)
♪
Have you been having a lot of bad dreams
since you got back from Vietnam?
You know, I don't really
remember my dreams much, so...
Okay.
But maybe, you're having these
nightmares because you...
Rebecca.
- Please.
- Sorry.
It's okay.
(CANS RATTLING)
Hello. Hi.
I'm trying to get to the river.
(SPEAKS IN VIETNAMESE)
- Sông Trà Khúc.
- Sông Trà Khúc?
Yeah. Yeah, the, uh,
fishing-fishing ville.
Y-You know the fishing ville...
you take me there?
(WHISTLES)
I'm Jack.
Jack.
- You...?
- Bao.
Bao.
Nice to meet you, Bao.
- You walk. No drive?
- No. No walk.
No drive. My ride left, I...
- You can take me.
- Yeah?
(CHUCKLES)
Of course.
("STAY WITH ME" BY FACES PLAYING)
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
You are gonna love Nicole.
She moved from Pittsburgh
to be an actress.
- Uh-huh.
- She just did a paper towel commercial.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
♪ In the morning,
don't say you love me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll only kick
you out of the door ♪
♪ I know your name is Rita ♪
♪ 'Cause your perfume smelling sweeter ♪
♪ Since when I saw you
down on the floor ♪
NICOLE: Oh, Becky!
- Becky.
- Becky?
She is the only one
allowed to call me that.
Don't get any ideas. Oh...
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Oh, is this him?
Uh, this is, uh, Jack.
Hey. Thanks for having us.
This place is amazing. You live here?
I'm staying here while Greg's
on location in Canada.
Greg Billagio.
He's an up-and-coming director,
- and my occasional sweetheart.
- Oh.
- Oh, drinks. You guys need drinks.
- Yes.
I'll get them. Let you two catch up.
- Thank you.
- Oh, he's a gentleman.
- (BOTH CHUCKLING)
- Okay, tell me about your Jack.
I don't even know what to say.
It's still so new.
(SIGHS) So, we've been traveling
together for a few days now,
and I just, I feel like I don't
know any more about him
than when we first started.
Like, he's going to visit
someone in Reseda tomorrow,
- and he won't tell me who it is.
- You think it's a girl?
No, no, no, no, no. Not like that.
It's just, he, um...
he just got back from Vietnam,
so he's clearly working through
some things,
but he won't talk to me about it.
I just... ugh, I wish he would let me
be in it with him.
You're really wild
about this guy, huh, Becky?
Yeah. I just...
I want to be wherever he is.
I just wish he would let me in.
(SIGHS)
KEVIN: I was positive that
this necklace came
from that woman in the photo, you know,
that it had some epic
origin story to it.
It turns out you can get it
anywhere here.
- Kevin...
- Maybe Randall was right.
I should've just left well
enough alone, you know.
Let my father be remembered the
way he wanted to be remembered,
and stop asking so many questions.
You ever go through anything like that?
Did I ever travel to Vietnam to
find out my father's war story?
No. I think I would've mentioned
that uncanny coincidence to you.
I think you know what I mean.
Mind if we go back to the hotel?
I-I think I want to lay down.
Yeah, no, let's go back to the hotel.
You can continue to tell me
absolutely nothing about your life.
- That's not fair.
- Really?
- I tell you plenty.
- I'm just saying, you know,
you're obviously going through
something with your dad.
I'm not going through anything, Kevin.
It's just a constant,
terrible part of my life
that I try not to dwell on.
So... can we please go back
to the hotel?
I-I don't think I feel well.
That's real mature. That's great.
(RETCHING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, wow. That's a lot of bad bat.
There you go, m'am.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Champagne.
- Thank you.
- ALL: Cheers.
- (LOUD POP)
Mm! (SIGHS)
- It was just champagne.
- Okay.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine.
Bao, why are we stopping?
(SPEAKS VIETNAMESE)
What is this place? Where are we, Bao?
You.
(SPEAKS VIETNAMESE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER IN VIETNAMESE)
Please be a good guy, Bao.
(SPEAKS VIETNAMESE)
What you got, Squirrel?
Toe popper. Homemade.
(TALKS QUIETLY)
(SPEAKS VIETNAMESE)
You gonna take me back to my squad, Bao?
(ENGINE STARTS)
The bathroom's down the hall,
if you need it.
Okay.
I can't talk about it.
Vietnam.
What I did and what I saw.
I just, I don't...
I don't want to bring that part
of my life
into... this
with you.
Okay.
Are you gonna come back to Pittsburgh?
I don't know.
(SOFT LAUGH)
♪
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Good luck with... yours, too.
Thanks.
REBECCA: ♪ Give it enough time ♪
♪ Just give it time. ♪
(SONG ENDS)
Good stuff. Great stuff.
- That was beautiful.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
Thank you for coming in.
- So...
- So keep in touch.
Definitely keep us posted
on what you're up to.
All right, thank you very much
for your time.
Nice to meet you. Thank you. Thanks.
(EXECUTIVE SIGHS)
Um, I'm-I'm sorry. (CHUCKLES)
Could you actually just be
a little bit more specific
with your feedback?
Meaning?
"Keep in touch,"
what does that look like?
You let us know if you have a show,
and we will try to get
someone out to see it.
And then what?
And then we keep in touch.
(CHUCKLES)
Please, I-I drove a really long way.
If you could be very clear.
- Where'd you say you were from?
- Pittsburgh.
(SIGHS)
I think you're Pittsburgh good.
Thank you. I appreciate the feedback.
Mrs. Watterson?
Yes. Can I help you?
Mr. Watterson.
I'm Staff Sergeant Jack Pearson.
Your son was under my command.
I'm responsible for his death.
Bao, why-why are you stopping?
Why are you stopping?
The ville is that way.
You walk. You walk. (SPEAKS VIETNAMESE)
You go. You walk.
Are you a good guy or a bad guy, Bao?
Are you V.C.?
Sometime.
Everything about the war is murky,
and all my memories are just... murky.
I don't know whose idea it was
to pick up the football first
that day, but knowing Squirrel...
excuse me, Roger...
knowing Roger, it was probably his idea.
A lot of energy, that kid.
It was a quiet night.
At least, we... we thought it was.
- (INSECTS CHIRRING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, Townie, knock it off.
- Oh, just one more, Sarge.
- No.
- Go long, pretty boy.
- Boon, you got a can?
I don't think you got the arm, Townie.
Yeah, want to bet? Go deep.
Now, for a big boy, you sure throw
- like a small...
- (EXPLOSION)
I let my guard down.
I failed many times
when I was over there,
but taking my eye off your son, that...
It was the worst thing I did,
and I take responsibility.
I take full responsibility.
And I know it may not mean much but...
I needed to come here
and tell you that,
well, he was one of the good ones.
And that I am sorry.
♪
It wasn't your fault, son.
It wasn't.
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Don't say anything.
It's the safest place
for me to be right now.
Okay. Uh...
I got you this. I can't read
the label, but, um,
it's either coconut water
or suntan lotion.
I'd give it a little sniff
before I drank it, if I were you.
- Want me to help you with that?
- No, I-I can do it.
No, you can't.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(SIGHS)
Coconut water?
- Suntan lotion.
- Ah.
You know, my dad, um...
he kept the first 28 years of
his life a secret from my mom,
which worked for them, you know.
I mean, it more than worked
for them, actually, but...
I don't want that for us.
Okay? I don't.
I-I want to be able to tell you
everything and I want to know...
I want to know everything
about you. (CHUCKLES)
But if I can't,
um,
it's okay.
That's okay
because you smell like peaches,
and, well, right now you-you don't.
You smell like garbage
right now, actually,
but, typically, you smell like peaches.
And you keep snacks in that
big purse that you have and...
Well, I'm falling in love with you.
Whether you open up to me or not,
I'm falling in love with you.
My father sexually abused me.
He, uh...
he tries to contact me every so often,
try and make amends,
but I have no interest.
I've moved on.
Um, I'm not telling you this
because you asked me to,
or because you told me
you-you're falling in love with me,
or even because I'm falling
in love with you, too.
I'm telling you this because my father
has already ruined so much for me,
and I'm not gonna let him
ruin this, too.
I d... I didn't, um...
It's just you-you always seem
so strong, you know.
I-I didn't, uh...
I am strong.
Thank you.
How'd it go?
Uh, it went okay.
How did it go, your visit?
Yeah, it went, uh,
as good as it could go.
It's kind of nuts here, right?
I mean, every day you wake up,
it's 73 and sunny.
What is that? I like the rain.
They said that I was "Pittsburgh good,"
which I've decided to take
as a compliment.
Can I hear the song?
I think that I'm done singing for today.
Bec, please.
Bec?
No one has ever called me that.
I like it.
(SIGHS)
♪ People say it's nice to meet me ♪
♪ I often wonder why ♪
♪ I've studied my reflections ♪
♪ I've looked me in the eye ♪
♪ But I still can't draw conclusions ♪
♪ I'm still talking out of turn ♪
♪ Now I ask too many questions ♪
♪ About the lessons I won't learn ♪
♪ It turns out all my mistakes ♪
♪ Were forgivable ♪
♪ And the time I spend lost... ♪
(SNIFFLES)
♪ Was a sign ♪
♪ That all the ink ♪
♪ Is invisible ♪
♪ If you give it ♪
- ♪ Give it enough time ♪
- (RUSTLING)
♪ Now I think my eyes are open ♪
♪ I take a deeper dive ♪
♪ When I feel the blue surround me ♪
♪ That's when I come alive ♪
♪ When it starts to feel too lonely ♪
♪ When it's out of my control ♪
♪ When the world goes on without me ♪
♪ Will I feel it take its toll? ♪
♪ Turns out all my mistakes ♪
♪ Were forgivable ♪
♪ The time I spent lost ♪
♪ Was a sign... ♪
You got two weeks.
♪ And all the ink ♪
♪ Is invisible... ♪
You should've left me to rot!
♪ If you give it ♪
♪ Give it enough time. ♪
(SNIFFLES)
Come on.
Let's go home.
Okay.
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*