Previously on This Is Us...
‭GROSS: Your father's a veteran.
He served in Vietnam.
- Did he see combat?
- I don't know.
ZOE: Some of these men
have to still be alive.
We can find them.
See if they know your dad's story.
RANDALL: Why doesn't somebody
call the city or Parks and Rec,
fix this place up?
The city doesn't care
about our problems,
but if you think you can do better,
talk to Councilman Brown.
If this councilman won't do his job,
then maybe I can.
I think I'm gonna run against him.
I got fired today, Randall.
I take medication for depression.
Without it, life gets pretty scary.
Kate's never seen me that way, though.
I hope she never has to.
- How you feeling?
- Fine.
Did we get any eggs?
We got eight.
(LAUGHS)
(WHISPERING): So good, you did so good.
♪ Nobody ever loved me
like she does... ♪
BOY: There's something very
important I forgot to tell you.
Don't cross the streams.
Why? Let's just say it would be bad.
What do you mean by "bad?"
DAD: Well, I don't know what to
do with either of you anymore.
The hysteria, the moods!
MOM: Oh, I think that
I'm entitled to a little mood
every now and then, don't you?
Yeah, that's right, that's right,
just-just run to her house.
She's all shiny and new,
but before you know it
she's gonna turn real.
God knows you can't handle real!
♪ Don't let me down... ♪
Toby, honey, it's freezing in here.
Why is your fan on?
Oh, sweetie, your fingernails.
Just bitten them right down to the nubs.
(MARY SIGHS)
Everything is gonna be okay.
♪ I'm in love for the first time ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna last ♪
♪ It's a love... ♪
Okay, little eggies.
Now I know Dr. Jasper put Daddy's
best swimmers inside of you.
They're gonna be all up in your bidness,
trying to get you to fertilize, so...
today we find out if you let them.
Kate, it's time.
Dr. J said she'd call at 11:00.
♪ Don't let me down... ♪
- (CELL PHONE RINGS)
- Okay, all right.
Hello?
Yes, Dr. Jasper, hi.
Okay. Well, how many?
So that's three chances to get pregnant?
Tobe, it's 12:01.
She said she'd call in the morning
to tell us if the embryos were viable.
It's, like, officially the
afternoon, so what does it mean?
What is she trying to tell us
by not telling us something?
Does she not have good news? Is
that why? She's afraid to call.
I don't know. She's gonna call
when she calls.
- (CELL PHONE RINGS)
- See?
- Oh, no.
- Yeah.
- Oh, no, I can't do it.
- It's okay.
No, I'm nervous, I can't, I'm...
- No, you go ahead.
- No, please?
All right. Okay. Hello?
Yeah, this is she, he, yeah, it's Toby.
♪ Don't let me down ♪
♪ Don't let me down... ♪
♪ One singular sensation. ♪
(LAUGHS)
One embryo, Tobes.
We've got one shot.
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
Is anyone gonna fix this friggin' thing?
The cable bill.
Thank you. Yes, Kev,
I will call the super again.
"Well, that's quite all right,
Mrs. Sycamore."
REBECCA: What's that, hon?
It's a line
from the school play he's in.
- You Can't Take It with You.
- Oh.
Hey, can you take it with you
into the shower, Kev?
We're gonna be late for the prom.
Prom's not for three hours, Randall.
(SCOFFS) Which is about how long
it takes you to do your hair.
- (RANDALL LAUGHS)
- And I exit.
Are the girls gonna come here
to take their pictures?
We're going to take pictures
at Allison's, actually.
Apparently her dad's obsessed
with documenting
every single moment of her life, so...
All right.
Well, I'll be sure
to get lots of copies then.
Yeah, well, have fun, dude. Live large.
I already asked.
She said she doesn't want
to come with us. Just leave it.
Now I got to go turn myself
from Urkel to Stefan.
(RANDALL LAUGHS)
- Hey, question.
- Hey.
- You first.
- Okay.
Hoop earrings. "Hey, how you doing?"
Or power necklace. "What's up?"
I like them hoochie hoops.
"Hoochie?" Okay, necklace.
You ready to crush this interview?
I am coming home with no less than
- a six-figure offer.
- Mm-hmm.
I spoke with the CEO on
the phone for an hour yesterday.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Meeting with department heads today.
Okay? Not gonna jinx it.
- You go.
- Um, let's see.
Tie, right? No tie?
Uh, tie's too formal and
you should show some neck.
What do you mean, like, like this?
Mm-hmm. Oh, God.
It's the first official
day of my campaign.
- Oh. (LAUGHS)
- I'm doing it, Beth. Uh-huh.
Running for city council
of Philadelphia's 12th district.
Am I a resident there? No.
But am I technically allowed to run
because I put my name on William's lease
when he moved in with us?
You damn Skippy.
I'm having my first meet
and greet in a down-home joint
my birth father probably knew and loved
in the city where he lived...
(SNIFFLES)
You cannot cry on the campaign trail.
- I'm not gonna.
- No, you're an emotional man, Randall.
You talk about fathers, you cry.
You talk about daughters, you cry.
Okay, you talk about the little
round boy on the corner
who tried to sell lemonade
in the winter...
All his lemonade froze, Beth.
Yeah, well he was stupid, baby.
Now look, you have a big open
heart and I love that about you,
okay, but these people
do not want to see
a rich man from Alpine
- crying when he talks to them.
- Understood.
Yeah. All right.
I'll get there as soon as I can.
Hey, remember what we said.
If after five minutes,
five days, five weeks,
if you're not feeling this, I drop out.
Knock them dead, Councilman.
You take no prisoners, baby.
Go on now, go on now. Mm!
Is this crazy, huh?
Driving all the way to Baltimore
to meet some dude
that my dad served with?
I mean, this guy, Robinson,
right, he's a complete unknown.
So how do I introduce you, anyway?
Documentarian girlfriend,
does that work?
You introduce me as Zoe, human being,
who is a documentarian
who you happen to be dating.
It's kind of a mouthful,
but we'll go with it.
Oh, damn. I forgot my silk pillowcase.
No, you didn't. Really?
(CRIES MOCKINGLY)
Well, turn it around, you know,
because Zoe Baker cannot sleep
on cheap hotel bedding.
No. (SCOFFS) No, that's, uh...
Forget it. Baltimore, baby.
Baltimore, baby.
Here's to you, Mr. Robinson.
I am really too tired for this today.
Mom, you're constantly in bed.
I need new school clothes.
- Shh. It's okay, it's okay.
- (BABY CRYING)
Please, don't cry. Please, please.
(CRYING): Can't I just have
one damn day?
Please, stop crying.
Toby, you don't need a blazer.
Yeah, I do. Look.
"'Cause I don't get no respect.
No respect at all." (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES) Are-are you doing
Rodney Dangerfield?
Dad lets me watch Johnny Carson.
"Me and my wife were happy
for 20 years. Then we met."
(LAUGHS)
Oh, Toby.
Oh, Toby. (SNIFFLES)
Come on. Let's see if we can
find you some shirts.
Hi.
Hey, there's my maybe-mama.
Morning maybe-daddy.
Okay, I don't want to jinx us,
but I think I'm pregnant.
(LAUGHS)
The test results are coming back today.
I'm going with pregnant.
What do you think?
Today is nothing but good news.
What time is the doctor supposed
to call with the results?
- 4:00?
- 4:00.
- Yeah.
Right. So here's what we're gonna do.
We are gonna keep ourselves busy.
I'm gonna go to work,
you're gonna go to work
and nobody is gonna take
a home pregnancy test.
Okay.
- Kate, say why.
- Okay.
Because at this stage
it's just not accurate
and it causes emotional chaos.
- And what do we want?
- We want...
- calm.
- Calm.
All right, see you soon.
I can't wait eight hours.
You'll pass the time easy.
It'll take you at least two
hours to get ready for your gig.
Well, three if I do my
nails before my lashes.
Yeah, the gigs will get better.
All right, we meet back here at 4:00
to get the results together.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Hey, babe.
Yeah? Mm-hmm?
Thanks for being my rock.
Always.
- Surprise!
- What? Miguel.
Yeah, I was driving by a-a yard
sale and-and there it was.
I know that your old piano used
to be the center of your house,
so I thought that maybe
you all could use something
that says home.
Yeah, or-or we can take it away.
I mean, two of us'll probably
drop dead, but we could...
No, no, no. Come on in, of course.
- I'm just so surprised.
- Great, okay.
- All right, come on, guys.
- Just... ah.
Help me swing it around this way.
Great, now this place is smaller.
(REFRIGERATOR WHIRRING)
- Is your fridge still...?
- Still.
(GROANS) Let me take a look at it.
- Really? Thank you.
- Yeah.
Oh, my goodness. Wow.
(PLAYING MELODY)
Hmm.
- KEVIN: No girlfriend.
- No.
No. Okay, how about, how about friends
with mind-blowing benefits
that are close enough
to share some questionable
beef jerky at a gas station
while on a road trip together?
- I'm gonna hit the ladies' room.
- Okay.
- Yep.
- Thank you.
- See you in a bit.
Pardon me.
- How are you?
- All right.
- Good. Good...
- Good.
And... you got no Hi-Chew?
- No.
- Ugh!
- Really? Perfect.
- Bathroom was out of order.
Hang on, ma'am, I'll be right with you.
- KEVIN: Oh, no, we're together.
- Oh.
Yeah, take those.
And then, do you like, um...
do you like generic Twizzlers?
Harder to digest, the more I like them.
RANDALL: All right, people. Our goal
is to have a lot of Pearson
signs leaving this place today,
along with a lot of changed minds. Yeah?
Where are the owners? Owners here?
Hello. How you doing, sir?
- Honored to meet you, sir.
- Yeah.
- Albert Jones, my wife Doris.
- How you doing, ma'am?
I can't thank you all
enough for hosting today.
Fixtures of the neighborhood
like yourselves
supporting change, it's more
meaningful than you know.
What we support is you paying up-front.
Oh, yes, ma'am. I can, uh,
got my checkbook right here.
DORIS: Mm-hmm.
RANDALL: You guys enjoying yourselves?
Randall Pearson, nice to meet you.
Let me know if I can
do anything for you. Okay.
Enjoying the food? Right on.
How you doing, ma'am? Randall Pearson.
- Peasing?
- No ma'am, Pearson.
I'm running for councilman
for the 12th District.
Oh, I don't know nothing about
that. You in line for food?
No, ma'am, I didn't mean
to interrupt you.
You go right ahead. Oh, man.
Hey, how you doing, big man?
Randall Pearson. You are?
Hungry as a horse. Smells good.
Right on. Hope you enjoy.
- Hey, ChiChi.
- CHICHI: Mm-hmm?
Take a look at this flyer,
and tell me, where is my name?
Right... there.
In the fine print,
like a pharmaceutical warning.
- Really?
- You asked me to fill the place.
I filled the place.
The rest is up to you.
♪ You just want somebody new... ♪
ALAN: For God's sakes, Toby,
don't start.
This has been coming for a long time.
(SNIFFLES)
You'll spend the weekends with me.
I know, Dad. I'm fine.
You're a good kid, Toby.
But there's so much of her in you,
it scares the hell out of me.
This sad-sack thing that comes over you,
you better find a way
to get a handle on it.
Because this crap simply
will not fly when you're grown.
(KNUCKLE TAPPING)
- Hi, hi.
- Hi, can I help you sir?
Yeah, uh, look, it-it's,
this is a funny story.
I-I did... I did something
a little... (WHISTLES)
My, uh, my wife was having a
hell of a time getting pregnant,
and our-our doctor said
that my antidepressants
were killing my sperm.
She also said that the IVF
we were gonna do had,
like, a 90% chance of failing,
and my guys needed to be strong
in case we had to try again naturally.
Mm, sir, I don't think
we can help you...
So, so, uh, I-I went off my
meds, and today, I find out
if I can go back on them,
and if I can go back on them,
then I need to go back on them,
like, right away, right now.
Tout de suite, you know what I mean?
You need to go back
on your meds properly.
Call your doctor, sir, today.
Is there someone that can pick you up?
Uh... (GRUNTING)
Well, yeah, uh, no,
she can't know. She can't know.
♪ ♪
I'm the singing Adele-o-gram.
Uh, I was booked for a birthday party.
Oh, right. Uh, he'll be right out.
- (ELEVATOR CHIMES)
- Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Amaze. (LAUGHS)
- Oh.
- Kate, right?
- Yeah. Hi.
- I'm John.
So, everyone's waiting in the conf.
This is gonna be so epic. (CHUCKLES)
Ooh, so epic. (LAUGHS)
Okay.
What's up with you, tweaker?
It's my first time meeting
Allison's parents.
Oh, y-you're good, man.
You're a parents' dream: straight As,
good manners, no idea how to have sex.
Shut up. You look like a bellhop.
Well, how nice everyone looks.
H-Hi, Mrs. Walsh. Uh, I'm Randall.
And this is Kevin, my brother.
And that's Sophie.
Well, come in.
Randall, give me a hug.
(CHUCKLES)
It's so good to finally meet you.
Allison, they're here!
Wow.
Y-You look amazing.
(CHUCKLES) So do you.
Thanks.
- Um, shall I?
- Yeah.
Hello there, Randall.
I've heard so much a...
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
ALLISON: Dad!
Randall, I'm so sorry.
I'm Randall Pearson,
and I'm running for councilman
for the 12th District.
All right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Say, can, um... can we get
a round of applause
for Doris and Al's hospitality,
and the best damn ribs I've ever had?
- All right.
- (CHEERING, CLAPPING)
Thank you all very much.
Now, um, they've made it
very clear to me
that while they may be hosting today,
I have not won their support.
Not yet. And that's fine.
I get it. I do.
'Cause, uh, most of y'all
are probably wondering
who the hell I am,
all of a sudden, right?
- Yeah...
- (LAUGHTER)
RANDALL: Okay, I got a laugh.
I like that, keep them coming.
(QUIETLY): Hey.
For the last decade,
I've been living in Alpine,
New Jersey, raising a family.
But my father William lived six
blocks from here for 20 years.
And he cared for the people
in his building.
He fought for their quality of life
by speaking up to management, often.
Was kind of like that, uh, mosquito
in your ear you can never quite catch?
You know what I'm saying? Another laugh.
- (LAUGHTER)
- That's cool.
Anyway, um, when he died,
my wife Beth and I... hey, wife...
we decided to take up his mantle,
and we bought the building
and I became a landlord.
And I fixed what was
broken as fast as I could.
And then I saw the neighborhood:
the broken streetlights,
the rising crime, and I decided
I wanted to fix that, too.
Thought this wasn't gonna be a speech.
- Yeah.
- Right.
RANDALL: You're right, you're right.
Get to the point, Pearson. Okay.
Um... (CLEARS THROAT)
You all have been
under the same leadership
for-for a very long time
with a man that many of you
- think of as a friend.
- He is a friend.
- Been a friend for 30 years.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I know that you are...
- I don't know what you talking about.
I know you're comfortable
with Sol Brown. Right?
- Yeah.
- So comfortable,
that when he lets you down,
you may be willing
to look the other way.
- (GROANING, MURMURING)
- MAN: Go home!
- WOMAN: Yeah!
- Okay.
You are not from here, honey.
Listen, 33% of your businesses
have been boarded up
in the last ten years.
40% of your children don't have
a place to go after school.
Kids are walking home in the
dark, they're getting hurt.
Please. Ma'am, will you just
take a poster on your way out?
(DISTANT): And I'd really love
to hear your concerns...
♪ ♪
KATE: ♪ Everybody loves
the things you do ♪
♪ From the way you talk ♪
♪ To the way you move... ♪
Hey, Dr. Weiss, it's Toby Damon.
I know I've missed a couple of sessions,
but if you can give me
a call back right away,
that'd be great. Thanks. Bye.
♪ Everybody here is watching you ♪
♪ 'Cause you feel like home ♪
♪ You're like a dream come true ♪
♪ But if by chance you're here alone ♪
♪ Can I have a moment ♪
♪ Before I go? ♪
Miguel, I'm so sorry.
I-I've almost got it, I swear.
Honestly, you don't
have to fix our fridge.
No, I... I do. I do, Rebecca.
♪ I used to know ♪
♪ You look like a movie ♪
♪ You sound like a song ♪
♪ My God, this reminds me ♪
♪ Of when we were young ♪
♪ Let me photograph you in this light ♪
♪ In case it is the last time ♪
♪ That we might be exactly
like we were ♪
♪ Before we realized ♪
♪ We were sad of getting old ♪
So you're Jack Pearson's son.
♪ It was just like a movie ♪
♪ It was just like a song ♪
♪ When we were young. ♪
(VIDEO GAME CHIMING)
TOBY: Josie, don't go.
I'm going through a rough patch.
- All right? If...
- Rough patch?
All you do is play your Xbox
for hours on end online.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, look. I'll-I'll get,
- I'll get back on the meds.
- Look, we gave it a shot.
Okay? Maybe it's just
not meant to be, with us.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What the hell are you doing here?
Right now, I'm waiting for the elevator.
I have to be home at 4:00.
No, I'm saying you're, like,
seriously talented.
Like, you should be on The Voice.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah. Yeah, well.
Yeah, no, this pays the bills.
It pays the gas bill.
Let's be honest,
it pays half the gas bill.
(CHUCKLES) Well, you're amazing.
- So...
- Here's the thing.
When sad things happen to me,
I tend to shut music out of my life.
A lot of sad things have happened to me,
which is why I'm nearly 40,
singing Adele-o-grams.
Fits and starts, right?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Well, I hope things stay happy, then.
Me, too.
(ELEVATOR CHIMES)
(MOUTHS)
(PLAYING AND HUMMING)
♪ Head and in ♪
♪ To my heart ♪
♪ Gonna find ♪
♪ The strength... ♪
(SNIFFLES)
(LAUGHING)
And, uh, this one is a Purple Heart,
which I got in exchange
- for my right foot. (CHUCKLES)
- Oh, wow.
Yeah. Your father...
You want to join me
in a nip of bourbon, son?
Um...
I would love to, but I can't, I'm sober.
- Oh. Well, good for you.
- Thank you.
Yeah. My, uh,
my dad suffered as well
with alcohol, so...
- Huh.
- Yeah. I was, I was thinking, um...
maybe it had something
to do with the war, you know?
His way of coping with what
he'd seen over there.
As a mechanic.
How deep you want to go here, son?
Well, I'm here, right?
Your father was not a mechanic.
He was a Staff Sergeant
with Alpha Company's 3rd Squad.
Uh, squad leader, in fact.
And in October 1971,
your dad saved my life.
You two make an adorable couple.
- Oh, we're not serious.
- Really?
So you just casually
went on a long road trip
to track down his father's war buddy?
I have some hang-ups with men.
And he's the first pure alabaster one
I've dated seriously,
- so... Yeah.
- Ah.
Today at the gas station,
the cashier didn't realize
we were together,
and, um, she was rude to me.
Not in the obvious way, just, uh...
- I got it.
- Mm, and, Kevin, he was...
- He didn't get it?
- He didn't even see it.
And it's the little things,
you know, like, this morning,
I forgot my pillowcase
and I realized he thinks I sleep
with a special pillowcase
because I'm fancy.
(LAUGHING): Oh, Lord.
- Did you explain it to him?
- No.
When I start explaining
that I need a silk pillowcase
for my hair, then where does it end?
There's always gonna
be something, right?
And do I really want to spend my time
trying to explain
what it's like to be black
to a white movie star?
Sounds exhausting.
Little bit.
Well, it seems to me,
you need to decide what you can handle.
And if he's worth it to you.
Hm.
Let's get to this key lime pie.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Well, that was an unmitigated disaster.
Five people stayed behind
to talk to you.
They work here, Beth.
- Oh.
- I don't get it, babe.
Every day I hear a new complaint
about quality of life in this district,
and in the next breath they say,
"I'm voting for Sol Brown."
What's that supposed to tell me?
ALBERT: Go back where you belong.
What's that, now?
- I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.
- BETH: Hey, babe.
I said go back where you belong.
Hmm. Where I belong, huh?
And where exactly is that, Mr. Jones?
Oh, please, you tell me
because you would be answering
the great mystery of my life,
I tell you that.
Look, all due respect, sir,
this is a community of good people
who have been totally abandoned,
and I can't fathom why
they're not furious about it.
Because they know the man
who's failing them?
When did complacency
become the best option here?
Blind loyalty the better way?
Man, get the hell on
out of my restaurant.
DORIS: Albert, come on, now.
Who do you think you are,
coming down here
and wagging your finger in our faces?
In 2003,
after owning this place for 21 years,
working our fingers to the bone,
new landlord comes strolling up
in here with his white collar
and his white agenda
to move black folks out.
He raises the rent by a half,
and just like that we were done.
Doris sat down on the floor right there
where you're standing, and she sobbed.
New councilman heard our story,
a skinny young cat named Sol Brown.
He took the landlord to a Phillies game.
Something was decided, I don't
know what, and I don't...
I don't much care, 'cause the next day
the landlord came back up in here,
raised the rent a reasonable rate,
sat down, we broke bread together,
and 15 years later, we still here.
(WHISPERING): So, no.
We don't owe Sol Brown our loyalty.
We owe him our lives.
Am I clear?
Yes, sir.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
MARY: Toby?
Sweetie, uh, your brother
is-is really worried about you.
He-he said that you talked on the phone
and that you said
some pretty scary things.
Have you been outside at all?
Toby, Josie's been gone for months.
- Y-You really need to get up.
- I can't.
Yes, you can. I did.
With the help of a ten-year-old
boy who did impressions.
Listen to me, the joy in you
is as much a part of you
as this sadness.
Do you hear me?
I do think the medication
and our sessions
are having an effect, Toby.
I concur, Doc Feelgood.
Now, if we could only find
somebody who wanted to date
a guy who looks like
he swallowed the Unabomber.
Is that something
that you'd like to attack?
WOMAN: And so I said to myself,
"Tanya, you have lost the weight,
"and now you can help others
be skinny like you."
Oh, thank you, guys. Thank you.
So, who would like to share first?
Come on. Come on, come on, come on.
WOMAN: Seriously, man? You've been
hogging this for an hour.
What are you even talking about?
What time is it?
3:45.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
KEVIN: So, you're saying
my old man was in charge
- of all these guys?
- ROBINSON: Yep.
- And they all loved him.
- All right.
- That sounds about right.
- (CHUCKLES)
Man. You know, I always knew
there was more to his story
than he let on.
You know? Even as a kid,
like, I would ask him questions
or a war movie would come on,
you know, and, um...
I don't know,
something would come over him,
you know, l-like, uh...
like, as if he was haunted.
Well, he wasn't haunted
when I got pulled out.
I, uh, tried writing him.
- Never heard back.
- Hmm.
And then, you know, time.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
And, uh, these guys here,
you know, might they know something?
Uh, him there, that's-that's Townie.
I heard he passed from cancer
about, uh, ten years ago.
And that's Murphy. Died in-country.
And, uh, that man, I don't know him.
- No?
- No.
It says "Pearson" on this guy's shirt.
I'm pretty sure that's my uncle
that died in the war.
- Hmm.
- My dad never talked about him much,
uh, so... You ever cross paths with him?
No, no.
Look, son, I-I know you come a long way,
and I'm sorry I don't have
the answers you're looking for.
But in my experience
with this particular war,
sometimes the answers are so dark
you're better off not having them.
- What are you doing here?
- Fixing your fridge.
I'm almost done. Hey, Randall.
Why are you home so early?
Prom that boring?
Never made it there.
Her dad freaked out when he saw me.
- So...
- (SIGHS)
You know I was born in Puerto Rico?
I, uh, came here to Pittsburgh
when I was eight years old.
And I was determined
to not have an accent
'cause I was gonna be starting
at a new school.
So I studied every American TV show.
I repeated every line from every
commercial all summer long.
And the second...
I walked into class on the first day,
before I could even say a word,
those kids, they gave me a nickname:
Ricky Ricardo. Who's Cuban.
- You know what I did?
- What?
I started entering every room
saying, "Lucy, I'm home."
But you are stronger than I was.
- Even at that age, Randall.
- Thanks.
But I'm-I'm tired,
so I'm gonna go to bed.
I-I feel like my brain's
gonna explode, you know?
I feel like I learned a lot today,
but at the same time, I feel
like I didn't learn anything.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
You order room service?
Uh, delivery for Kevin Pearson?
Oh, that's for you.
- Oh.
- I got the best one I could find.
You got me a pillowcase?
Yeah. It seemed really important
to you, so...
(SIGHS)
Um, Kevin...
Yeah.
The reason I need the silk pillowcase
is because it keeps my hair from drying.
And today, at the gas station,
the clerk was racist.
You're kidding me.
What'd she say to you?
She didn't say anything, but she
assumed we weren't together.
And she was sharp with me
because she was bothered
by a black person invading
a white person's space.
Why are you just now telling me this?
Because I think, God help me,
I think you just might be worth it.
(PIANO PLAYING)
REBECCA: You know,
when I was three years old,
my mom sang me this lullaby, and
once was all I needed to hear it
before I could sing it back.
Music was always in me.
And I put it aside lots of times.
Out of fear and sadness,
and lots of reasons.
It's funny. When Miguel
brought the piano here today,
you said it made the room
look a lot smaller.
And to me, it felt so much bigger.
'Cause music has always represented
this huge, empty room
that I could just walk right in
and let myself pour out.
(REBECCA PLAYS MELODY)
♪ All through the night ♪
♪ I'll be awake ♪
♪ And I'll be with you... ♪
Can you sing that back to me?
Come on.
(HUMMING)
I can't.
Okay. It's okay.
You're not ready.
But one day, I know you're gonna
sit back down at this piano
and start singing again.
'Cause it's gonna be a place
where you can put all of that sadness.
And because it's what
you're meant to do.
(KISSES)
♪ Everybody knows what they want to be ♪
♪ Lately, I've been feeling like ♪
♪ Everyone knows but me ♪
♪ Been keeping my head down ♪
♪ For too long ♪
♪ Now ♪
- Kate?
- ♪ There were... ♪
- Hey.
- Oh, God, hey. Hi, hi.
I am so sorry. I know I'm late. Hi.
The doctor already called.
It worked, baby.
(LAUGHS)
- I'm pregnant.
- Really?
(LAUGHING): Yes. Yes.
(LAUGHS, HYPERVENTILATES)
Okay. Okay. Yeah, yeah. (MUTTERING)
(CRYING)
Hey. Toby, it's okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Give yourself a break.
It was your first day, you know?
You know more now. Seen more
faces, heard more voices.
Yeah. Screaming at me.
Well. Complacent people
don't scream, baby.
I said that, huh?
Yes, you did.
And you'll never say it again.
They grew up with the man, Beth.
They are him, he's them.
I'm gonna have to find a different way.
- Yo. Baby.
- Hmm? Hmm.
Your interview. I didn't ask
you. Tell me, tell me, please.
What's there to say, you know?
- I was a boss.
- Yes. Of course you were.
So when they make you this job
offer, you're gonna take it?
All right, we'll see
about the offer, okay?
We'll see what happens
when the deal comes in.
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
- Meet you at home?
- Yes. I love you.
Drive safe.
Hey, at least you didn't cry.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
See you.
BETH: Yeah, and the Hexpods in New York
really inspired me.
I feel like we can
do something similar here,
just improve upon the idea.
Well, your last boss, Bill,
couldn't rave about you more.
That must've been hard parting ways.
We don't see a lot of résumés
with 12 years at one place.
Yeah. Oh, gosh.
I was there for a long time,
but you know,
budget cuts, and um... but, um, yeah.
Bill and I practically started
that company together.
I was just a kid.
Wide-eyed, and-and,
uh, committed to serving
the underserved.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Sorry. (LAUGHS) It's still a little raw.
Um, what was I saying?
Um... yes.
So, I was there for a while,
and, um, I, uh...
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Beth, are you all right?
Could you give me...
could you give me a minute?
- Of course.
- Okay, thank you.
Thank you. (SNIFFLES)
KATE: I think it's been five weeks
since he's been off of them.
I know, Dr. Weiss.
Okay.
Thank you. Bye.
♪ I lost you a while ago ♪
- ♪ But still I don't know why ♪
- Babe?
I just spoke to the doctor.
They want you
to come in tomorrow and talk
about adjusting your meds.
♪ I can't say your name ♪
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- ♪ Without a crow flying by... ♪
I didn't know what to do with him.
- (KEVIN GROANS)
- It's okay. You were right
to bringing him here, all right?
You go ahead
and take the limo home. I'm
gonna take care of him, okay?
- Okay.
- Come on, Kevin. I got you, buddy.
- I hope you feel better.
- Come on.
Watch the steps.
Hey, it's Miguel.
- I'm not waking you, am I?
- REBECCA: No.
Miguel... (SIGHS)
...you fixed the fridge.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, um,
listen, Kevin's here.
He's fine, but he's had
a little too much to drink.
- Okay. I'm on my way.
- No, no, no, no. It's okay.
I've got him, and he's sleeping,
so, um...
he's fine here, really.
Oh.
Miguel...
thank you...
for all you're doing to help.
You're too good to us.
- (LAUGHS)
- We don't deserve you.
JACK: Hey, Miguel, you gonna
act out the plays for me,
or can I maybe see the TV, too?
(LAUGHS) Here.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
♪ With gatting guns and paint... ♪
- Life insurance?
- Yeah.
- Oof.
- Yeah, I know.
- Pretty bleak stuff, huh?
- Yeah.
Hey, you shouldn't pay for that scam.
- No?
- No. Jack Pearson don't die.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
Hey, but seriously, man...
I get hit by a bus,
you'll look out for 'em, right?
♪ Oh, my brother, be careful ♪
♪ You are drifting away ♪
♪ Throw me a rope ♪
- (ROBINSON CLEARS THROAT)
- ♪ On the rolling tide... ♪
- Hi.
(SIGHS)
You have to understand the Jack I knew
wanted everything from that war
behind him.
But who's to say he
wouldn't have wanted you to
know his story?
♪ The way you made it ♪
♪ That's the way it will be... ♪
I hope these help.
Thank you.
♪ The way you made it ♪
♪ That's the way it will be. ♪
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*