Previously on This Is Us...
I'm Randall Pearson,
and I'm running for councilman
for the 12th District.
- You are not from here, honey.
- Go home.
Beth, there is no easy way to say this.
We have to let you go.
It worked, baby.
I'm pregnant.
The Jack I knew wanted everything
from that war behind him.
But who's to say
he wouldn't have wanted you
to know his story?
Hmm.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- Hey, Mom.
The IVF worked.
I'm pregnant.
What?
I can't believe it!
My sister's having a baby. Beth!
Get in here. It's Kate!
We're getting another Pearson...
Hell yeah.
- You guys deserve this.
- Yo!
- Oh, my...
- Wait, put my man Tobias on the phone.
I want to congratulate him, too.
Toby is actually...
Depressed? About the baby?
No, not about the baby.
He's thrilled about the baby.
Apparently, he went off
his antidepressants
in case the IVF didn't work and
they had to conceive naturally.
Why doesn't he just get back on them?
He did. He's been back on them
for two weeks now.
It's just taking time
for them to kick back in.
So how's Kate doing through it all?
She's hanging in there.
I just wish she wasn't so far away.
Do you want me to come out there?
Oh, that's really sweet, Kev, but...
there's not really anything you can do.
Is Toby feeling any better?
Hi, honey.
How are you feeling?
Oh, just tired.
I was, uh, gonna take Audio on a walk.
Dr. Jasper said I should keep up
with the light exercise,
so maybe we could all go together.
If you're feeling up for it?
Know what? You guys go ahead.
There you go, buddy.
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
- Yes!
- No, no, no.
- Come on, come on.
- Yes! Yes!
- Come on. Oh!
Touchdown!
That's five in a row for me,
you suckable sucker.
- What are you doing?
- How does it feel
- to be not very good at this?
- Mom!
- How does it feel to lose?
- Kevin, get off of me!
- No!
Kevin, MVP of the world!
Kevin, get off your brother. Come on.
Come on, Mom. We're just messing around.
Oh, you're so annoying.
- Hey.
- Hey. Hey, Pearsons.
- Hey, babe.
- Hey, Dad.
What's with the, uh, baseball hat?
Oh, you know, just, uh,
little hometown pride.
- Um, Jack?
- Huh?
- You have a black eye.
- Yeah.
- What?
- I was...
boxing one of the guys at the gym
and just caught a nasty punch. I'm fine.
- You're a boxer?
- Um...
Go set the table, please?
- Go. Go, go, go, go, go. Come on.
- Come on.
Jack, I knew you were using
the punching bag at the gym,
but since when did you start
boxing actual human beings?
I don't do it that often,
just every once in a while,
me and some guys at the gym, we...
spar a little bit. It's no big deal.
Yeah, says my husband
with the black eye.
You know, boxers can get brain damage.
The guy that gave me this, that
tagged me, his name's Stuart.
Okay? Guys named Stuart
don't give you brain damage.
It's dangerous, babe.
Promise me, punching bag only.
I promise.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Hi. This is Beth Pearson,
calling for Kellie.
I was checking to see
if you got the résumé I sent in.
You had asked me to send it last week,
but I hadn't heard anything,
so I thought I'd call.
Uh, which is obvious,
because you're getting
a voice-mail message from me.
So if you could, uh, call me
back, that would be super-duper.
God...
Babe? I need help picking a shirt.
Is it blue or white?
- White.
- Blue.
All right, so it's a draw
between Paul and John.
- Ringo.
- Who's Paul and John?
The hell I'm Ringo.
What happened to the teal?
I thought teal... I don't know,
I was a little concerned
it might make too much
of a statement for church.
It's never too much of a statement
- for black church, Randall.
- Black church.
Why are you going to church
in Philadelphia?
Well, 'cause I'm running
for office in Philly,
so I got to get my Philly on.
Really connect with the people
in the community
that I want to represent.
Maybe after church, I will
treat myself to an authentic
Philly cheesesteak.
Load it up with Cheez Whiz
and everything.
Cheez Whiz is gross.
My beautiful darling gem of a daughter,
if you ever say that within
Philadelphia city limits,
I will be forced to disown you.
Guys, can we talk about us now?
- Okay.
- Sure, yeah.
We're way behind
on Girl Scout cookie sales.
Usually, we go to Mom's office
and sell at least 150 there,
but, uh...
Hey, um, how about tomorrow,
when I have a little bit
more free time...
No. It's fine.
You have stuff to do. I don't.
Uh, you know, we can set up
a table today to sell them.
Right? We-we could make some posters.
Why don't you guys go ask Deja
if she wants to join us?
It's gonna be great.
Great.
Oh, Toby's still not feeling any better?
No. Not really.
But I don't know if I should be
pushing him to get out of bed,
or if I should just...
let him take his time.
I mean, what would you do?
Uh, I think all you can do is
just be patient and supportive.
But you need to be taking care
of yourself, too, Bug.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, I'm really
trying hard to stay chill.
Audio! Mom, I got to go. I got to go.
Audio. My God. Hey.
Hey, hey, let me see.
What did you eat? What's in
your mouth? What did you...
That doesn't look like food.
I really wish I knew
what her name was, you know?
Or anything about her, really.
I mean, she's wearing my dad's necklace.
You listening to me?
Finito, completo.
- What?
- My documentary is done.
All that's left now is to not
obsessively check my e-mail
while I wait to hear back
from the festivals.
Are you kidding me?
Everyone's gonna want it.
You got indie
darling written all over you.
This is great news.
- Ooh, you know what we got to do?
- Hmm?
We got to celebrate.
I've got an in at Le Bernardin.
Just got to text Kimmel
real quick... as in Jimmy Kimmel.
- Jimmy Kimmel, he's my in.
- Um, well, that's really sweet,
but actually, I have this tradition,
that every time I finish
a project, I check into a hotel
for a night of pampering.
Get room service,
spend so long in a hot tub
I turn into a full-on human raisin.
- Human raisin?
- Yeah.
I'm in. Let's do it.
- Uh...
- Oh, gosh.
Um, how do I explain?
I'm going alone.
You're going alone?
- Yes.
- Why?
This tradition is about decompressing.
I can't have your obsession
with that photo raining all over
my 800-thread-count sheet parade.
And, uh, seriously,
stop thinking about the photo.
H-hey, Dad.
I need you to teach me to box.
Randall, you heard your mother.
There's no boxing in this house.
Dad, there's this kid at school.
- Uh-huh.
- His name's Dylan.
He just moved here from New
York, and he's picking on me.
What?
He pushes me into lockers
every time he gets a chance.
Look, we got to tell your mother,
and then we're gonna call your school.
We'll-we'll get it taken care of.
Dad, everybody's gonna make fun
of me for being a snitch.
I won't defend myself
unless I really have to.
It'll just make me feel better
to know I can.
♪ He's got, he's got the whole ♪
♪ He's got the whole world
in his hands ♪
- ♪ He's got the whole ♪
- ♪ He's got the whole world ♪
- ♪ In his hands ♪
- ♪ Oh, he's got the whole ♪
♪ He's got the whole world
in his hands ♪
♪ Whole world in his hands. ♪
- Somebody say amen.
- Amen.
Welcome, friends, on this beautiful day
- that God has given us.
- Yes.
- You may be seated.
Our brother Solomon is going
to read from scripture.
Brother Solomon.
Thank you, Rev.
Blessed day, my brothers and sisters.
Before I share this good word,
I want to make sure we give
a warm welcome to my friend
and first-time visitor...
- Oh, God, please don't.
- Randall Pearson.
Stand up so we can greet you, brother.
Randall is visiting us
all the way from Alpine, New Jersey.
Uh...
Praise the Lord, everyone.
Praise the Lord.
Um, my family and I own
a building on Olney and Third.
It's just a couple blocks away.
So actually, we're very local.
Well, why don't you have
that beautiful family of yours
stand up, too?
Well, unfortunately, they
weren't able to be here today.
- Oh. Maybe next time.
- Yeah.
You know, Randall is the one
running against me for city council.
Now, you might think I wouldn't
welcome him here as a friend,
but, well, he's trying
to do something good.
He cares about people.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
So, Randall,
we welcome you
to our humble neighborhood.
Thank you, my friend.
And thank you all for having me.
And now, I'll be
reading from the Book of Job,
chapter 42.
You're dragging my poster, Mom.
- I'm sorry.
- Why did we park so far away?
Well, because the parking lot was full.
Which is great news for
you guys, because busy store
means lots of customers.
Oh, man.
I-I told you we should've come earlier.
Uh, you know what? It's okay.
We'll just go somewhere else.
Right? Okay?
Okay, come on. Oh...
Hey, Kev.
Hey, uh, listen, you got some time?
I need to talk to you about something.
Actually, I'm in Philly
doing campaign stuff all day.
- I can come to Philly.
- Please, do not come to Philly.
Last thing I need is my white,
movie star brother
coming and destroying what's left of my
already precious-little street cred.
Okay, listen, man, here's the thing.
I know where your office is, okay,
and you know that I don't
respect boundaries, so...
I will... I'll text you
the address of a place
where we can meet.
Cool. It's a date.
Okay, bud, look.
I made bacon, all rubbery,
just like you like it.
Oh, hi. What's up? How are you?
I'm fine. What's wrong with Audio?
- Audio?
- Audio...
Wait, is he...
is he not eating his bacon?
Okay, please don't freak out.
He may have swallowed
something bad at the dog park.
- Why weren't you watching him?
- I was on the phone.
I shouldn't have been on the phone.
I will call the vet right now.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
One... one-two.
Allright.
You know, you got a lot of power
coming out of that left.
You know what, try... sw-switch
up your feet so your...
so your right foot is forward.
Okay? There you go.
Just like that. Same thing, okay?
One-two. Jab, cross.
One more. Jab, cross.
- That feels good.
- Feels really good, right?
Ladies and gents, we've got
a southpaw fighter on our hands.
I'm a southpaw.
- You're a southpaw.
- I'm a southpaw.
All right, let's get
that southpaw in fighting shape.
- Ready. One-two.
- Guys, I'm home.
Hi.
How are you? It's me.
How you doing? Enjoy yourself.
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
- What is this place, huh?
- Ah.
This is where I bring my famous siblings
I can't be seen with.
Ah.
Wow.
This is all...
- a lot.
- Yeah.
I mean, look at that.
Dad's obviously in love
with that woman, right?
I don't know.
I can't read her face. Is it love,
or is it years of poverty
and occupation by foreign governments?
He gave me her necklace, right?
That means something.
Why now?
All of this.
I don't... Do you remember, um...
I don't know, we were,
like, maybe five years old.
There was that-that guest room
that had the wallpaper
with the little blue ships
on it; you remember that?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, okay.
So, you and I were playing
in there one day,
and we discovered this
little spot on the wallpaper
behind the sofa that was peeling, right?
And-and so you and I, we sort of
peeled it a little more.
And then we kept peeling
just because we could.
And the next thing you know,
we had, like,
half of the wallpaper was off the wall.
Do you remember that?
I remember getting a particularly stern
- talking-to from Mom about that.
- Yes.
It-it just blew our little minds
that there was wood paneling
behind the wallpaper.
Like, it had never occurred to us
that there was anything
beneath those ships.
I started peeling.
I'm curious about Dad, too.
But Vietnam...
that was a chapter in his life
he didn't want us to know about.
He made that very clear
while he was still alive.
I know.
Yeah, you know, maybe you're right.
You know, between the V.A. and Robinson,
no one has any answers anyway, so...
Uh, sorry, man, we haven't ordered yet.
Oh. It's on the house.
- Kamsahamnida.
- Oh.
You know what that is?
- No idea.
- The Manny.
Number-one show in South Korea.
I kid you not.
I think I got a K-pop song
named after me.
I'm telling you, that's how
you know you've made it.
Big deal.
Hey, you're free
for the rest of the day, right?
Wow, look at this, man.
You got color-coded maps
and everything up in here,
just like CNN. This is legit.
In the last municipal election
held in this district, only 25%
of registered voters voted.
- 95% of those voted for Brown.
- Okay. So?
About 50% of the Korean
population in this district
aren't registered to vote at all.
I repeat. Okay, so?
Okay, so...
if I can't win over people
in this neighborhood,
where Brown is already so ingrained,
then maybe we can appeal
to people in a neighborhood
where he doesn't set foot at all.
- We? As in the royal "we"?
- Yeah.
You know, sometimes my heart is so big
I can't even stand it.
- What's the game plan?
- I love you.
- I know you do.
- I don't say it enough.
You don't say it enough.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hi, Bug.
How are you?
Terrible.
Audio ate a rock.
What?
The vet said that I have to decide
if we're gonna have surgery
to remove it,
or if I should just take him home
and see if he just... he poops it out.
And if he doesn't poop it out,
it could rupture his intestine.
So it seems like both options
could kill him.
Tell me what to do, Mom.
I...
I think that you should take him home.
You know, you'll feel more
in control that way.
And then, if there's any
sign of distress,
you can just take him
back in immediately.
You know, if my maybe-baby
is a real baby,
I'm gonna have to have you
move into our building.
Mm.
Bug, I love that you are
calling me for advice,
and believe me,
I'm-I'm always happy to give it,
but can I let you in on a little secret?
Toby and Audio and your maybe-baby
that I think is going to
turn into a real baby...
There's gonna be a million
things, a million decisions
you're gonna have to make
for them, and you will.
You'll do exactly what I did.
You're gonna...
take a deep breath...
and make a choice...
and just hope you didn't
screw things up too badly.
- Rebecca, let me explain.
- Okay. Help me out here, Jack.
Help me out.
So, when I said "no boxing,"
what about that says, "I should
teach Randall how to box"?
You know, he's getting
bullied at school.
- What?
- Yeah.
Some new kid is picking on him,
and he's worried that things
are gonna get physical.
But he doesn't want us
to make a big deal about it
because he thinks, and I agree,
that's just gonna make things worse.
He's 12. You can't
blindly follow the wishes
of a 12-year-old.
Especially when it comes to his safety.
Jack, if you feel the need
to go secretly
punch some guys as a stress reliever
for all the things you don't
talk about, that's one thing.
But you cannot keep things from me
when they're about our sons.
You're right. I'm sorry.
We need to call his principal.
No one's here.
Of course not.
Almost all these stores are
out of business.
Oh, there's someone.
- Hi.
Would you like to buy
some Girl Scout cookies?
My daughters used to sell these
a million years ago.
Let me see, um...
I'll take four boxes of the shortbread.
That'll be $16, please.
Oh, I'm sorry. Cash only.
No, we're not.
We just need to use the swiper.
The what, now?
You didn't bring the swiper?
What is the swiper?
The little thing that you put
on your phone and swipe credit cards?
Everyone knows you need a swiper.
I'm sorry, I don't have any cash on me.
Uh, we can...
You know what, you can
give us your credit card number,
and we'll just write it down
on a piece of paper
and tear it up right after we run it.
Um, I don't think so.
Good luck.
Thanks a lot, Mom.
I wish we went with Riley.
She texted that they've already
sold 40 boxes today.
All right, I'm doing my best here, okay?
I'm sorry I'm not as good
as Riley's mom.
Yeah. Me, too.
Riley's mom would have
never forgotten the swiper,
because she doesn't totally suck.
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Come on, let's go.
Come on!
Okay, thank you so much,
Principal Sammartino.
Okay, bye-bye.
- What? What'd he say?
- Um...
there is no one named Dylan
in his class,
and there are no new students
from New York at all.
Wait, that doesn't make any sense.
Why would he make up a bully?
I have no idea.
- But we have to go talk to him.
- You know what, Bec?
Let me talk to him.
No, let me talk to him.
My-my son lied to me.
I need to find out why.
Okay.
- Hey, Bec?
- Huh?
The reason I...
Boxing helps me.
Okay? It...
...helps me with stuff.
Stuff I can't think about.
It... quiets things.
I wish I could explain it.
I don't know any other...
Okay. Okay.
My mom lost a lot of jobs
through the years.
It was always really hard for her.
You know, I was just about
to come talk to you guys.
I am sorry about earlier,
but you really don't
have to worry about me.
You know what Randall told me one time?
He called me exceptional.
And he said it so easy,
like it wasn't a big deal.
I remember thinking,
he must think people have
told me this before.
I bet he's told you before
that you're exceptional,
because you are.
Thanks, Dej.
You know, but I don't know that...
Randall thinks so.
I mean, he loves you like he's
in a Disney movie or something,
like he hears tiny
forest animals singing
or playing kazoos or something
whenever you walk into a room.
But if you're sad,
then you should talk to him.
He'll tell you you're exceptional,
and he'll say it so easy
that you'll believe it.
Wow.
You are really good at these talks.
You live in this house for a while,
you learn your way around a talk.
Oh, come on in, little mamas.
Come on. Everything's okay.
I'm so sorry that I exploded.
Okay?
It was not about you.
- No. I was being a brat.
- Okay.
It was ten percent about you.
90% not.
You got it?
There you go. That's a good one.
Register to vote, it'll last longer.
Okay, you're all set, Mrs. Park.
Hope to see you at the polls. Thank you.
Hey, how you doing, sir?
Randall Pearson.
Hey. Let me see if I have this.
Um, you can't make any inroads
with Sol Brown's base,
so you're getting Koreans to register,
hoping that they'll vote for you
'cause you're related to The Baby-Man.
I'm sorry, The Baby-Man?
Yeah, it's what they call
The Manny in South Korea.
Dude, you are so transparent.
I bet you've never
stepped foot here before,
and if you get elected... if...
you'll never step foot here again.
Hey.
You're right.
You're right, man, I-I've never been
in this neighborhood before,
but I'm here now.
But just on the way in here,
I saw empty storefronts.
I saw badly patched potholes.
I saw a guy carrying his
bicycle tire underneath his arms
because he knew that was the only way
to keep from getting it stolen.
But I don't know what
this community truly wants...
...or truly needs.
But if you'll talk to me, I'll listen.
As long as your kick-ass sister
keeps interpreting for me, that is.
I, uh, I only know one word
in Korean so far.
My brother taught it to me.
Kamsahamnida.
Did I say that right?
- Hey, how's he doing?
- Hey, oh, he's okay.
Just swallowed a little rock.
Just gonna monitor him, and, uh,
he'll be fine as long as he poops.
You got dressed.
You felt good enough to get dressed.
That's huge.
Uh, except that I don't.
- What?
- I-I don't.
I want to, and I-I-I thought
if I went through the motions
that I would, but I don't.
- I'm starting to get worried.
- About what?
That you're gonna leave me.
Not now, but eventually.
Toby, what are you talking about?
You didn't sign up for this.
And you're pregnant.
I'm the one who's supposed
to be taking care of you,
and instead I'm this pathetic burden.
You must be freaking out
that this is what you're stuck with.
Look, I tried
my very hardest today, and...
I'm sorry.
Tobe!
Toby, I think he wants to go out.
I'm gonna take him out. Come with us?
No.
Toby.
I think you should go on a walk with us.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks, Kev. Appreciate it, man.
Yeah, man, these muscles
aren't just for show.
Actually, that's not true at all.
They're mostly just for show.
You know, Randall, you wanted
to find your birth dad,
and you found him,
which led you to his building,
which you bought, which led you
to run for city council.
You want to do something,
you just do it.
Right, you don't... you don't care if it
makes sense to any of us or not. It's...
It's remarkable.
When you have one of those things
inside you, you just go for it.
- Yeah, I guess I do.
- I guess you do.
Randall, I've got one
of those things inside me.
About Dad. I can't let it go.
You need to peel the wallpaper.
I need to peel the wallpaper.
I hope you find what
you're looking for, brother.
Is Mom really mad about the boxing?
No.
She's not so mad,
but we are both confused.
We spoke to your principal, Randall.
We know there is no Dylan.
Yeah. So you...
you lied to me.
I wanted you to teach me how to box,
but I knew you wouldn't
if I didn't have a good reason.
Okay, so you made up a fake bully?
Why did you want to learn so bad?
So I could be more like you.
Randall,
boxing is just one part of me.
Yeah, that Kevin has.
What do you mean by that?
Kevin's good at fighting, Dad,
and he wins everything.
Wait, hold on a second, so you
wanted to learn how to box
- so that you could fight your brother?
- No.
Kevin's tough, and he got that from you,
and I didn't.
Dad, the thing is
that I know I'm your son,
but Kevin is your...
son-son,
and he got DNA stuff
from you that I didn't.
You need to teach me.
I need to learn how
to become a fighter, Dad,
if I'm gonna get anywhere in life.
- No, you don't.
- No, Dad, I just...
No, Randall, no, you don't.
Look, first of all,
you are my son-son.
Okay? And second...
...you've got something even greater
than knowing how to throw a punch.
You-you've got a brain
so smart that you tricked your old man
into thinking that I
had to teach you how to fight.
And that...
is gonna be your
secret weapon, Southpaw.
So, uh, how many voters you register?
About 200.
Ah, well, you only need
around, uh, 20,000 more.
Well, you got to start somewhere.
You know, my grandmother
has spent the last few hours
talking about the black man
with nice hands.
She's got a thing about hands.
Well, tell her thanks.
I, uh... I moisturize.
My grandmother has never voted
once in her life.
In Korea, she didn't
really have the access,
and when she became a citizen over here,
it was always clear to her
that no politician cares
what an old woman from a little
village north of Seoul wants.
But today, she registered to vote,
for the first time in 75 years,
because you made her believe
that you care.
And, plus, the nice hands.
I do care.
I have a master's in poli-sci,
and I was an aide
in a congressional campaign
in Ohio's 13th in 2016.
I know you don't have
a campaign manager.
I want the gig.
I'm sorry, I didn't get
your name earlier.
Jae-won, but most non-Koreans
call me John.
Me and my nice hands are happy
to have you on board, Jae-won.
Okay. All right.
Oh, is that how you do it?
- Kamsahamnida.
- That's good.
- Kamsahamnida. Kamsahamnida.
- That's how you pronounce it. Yeah.
You know, I'm still thinking about it.
You know, I go in there wanting
to ground him for lying to me,
and then when I left,
I wanted to hug him tighter
than humanly possible.
I just...
I can't get my head
around that kid sometimes.
Yeah.
Speaking of heads.
What's that?
I got you this today.
Just a little something, not a big deal.
Is this a test?
It's headgear.
Yeah, I know it's headgear.
If boxing is important to you,
I just want you to be safe, okay?
You know, my brother and I,
we used to box?
Yeah.
There was this local, ancient
boxer in our neighborhood.
Steve Bihuniak, "The Squid."
He had this old pair
of boxing mitts that...
we used to go over there and
we'd each put one of them on.
And-and then we'd roll toilet paper up
and-and stuff it in our teeth
like they were mouth guards,
and, you know, we'd have
these one-handed boxing matches.
Wow.
These are great.
All right, you win.
Win what?
Teach me how to box.
- You want to learn how to box?
- If everybody else knows how.
- Here. Put that on.
- I'm not...
- not wearing this.
- You got to protect your head.
Just put on the gloves.
Here. There's one...
- Uh-huh.
- In there tight. Okay.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Hold on a sec.
Put this second one on...
just, like, push it down.
- There you go. Okay.
- Okay.
Now get them up.
- Is this what I do?
- Oh, wow.
I mean, you in a nightgown
with boxing gloves on,
I mean, that was a fantasy
I didn't even know that I was missing.
Shut up, Jack. How do I do this?
All right, send us one past here.
- Yeah.
- Oof. Throw the other one.
Oh. Yeah.
- Hi.
- That's not so bad.
Thank you.
Yeah. Of course.
Yes, I have the budget proposal
right here.
Mary, let me call you back.
Randall.
Pleasant surprise.
You're good.
At church today, you were gracious,
but you made it very clear
you don't think I belong.
Well played.
Come on, slip, slip, slip.
- Ooh!
- Did you see that?
He gets hit square in the jaw,
spits out blood,
and what does he do? He smiles.
Why would he do that?
Well, uh, I've been at this a while.
Yeah, well, I'm still learning.
He doesn't want his
opponent to know that he's hurt.
There's this thing
that some fighters do.
Okay? If their opponent
hits them really hard,
they just plaster on a big old smile.
Go. Stay on him, stay on him. Go.
I did get a campaign manager.
His name is Jae-won Yoo.
I'm going to win Koreatown.
- Tobe?
- Yeah?
I'm not gonna leave you.
What?
I signed up for better or worse.
Yeah, no, I know. It-it...
It's just that you don't...
you don't how long...
Like, this is gonna be a part
of me for my entire life,
so it's...
Go on.
Babe, better or worse.
Ever since I was a little girl,
I have needed to be taken care of.
First, when I was a little chubby kid,
I needed to be coddled.
And then as a teenager whose dad died,
I needed to be comforted all the time.
I'm 38 years old, and I still
call my mom for advice
when I'm going through
a rough spot, and-and you...
wow, you have talked me off
of more emotional ledges
than I can count.
But the truth is I'm strong.
And the things that I've been through
have made me tough as hell.
So if you think this
is gonna scare me away,
you've got another thing coming.
I'm gonna get you through this, Tobe.
And if you fall again, I will be
right here to pick you back up.
In sickness and health,
for better, for worse.
I'm talking forever.
♪ Days go by
♪ Don't remember...
You're incredible.
- Tobe?
- Yeah?
He's pooping.
- Hey, look at you.
- He's pooping.
All right.
Hi.
- One night, Kevin.
- I know.
- I asked for one night.
- I know, I know, I know, I know.
I know you did, and I'm sorry
to interrupt your raisining,
really, I am, and as penance,
I promise I'm finally
gonna sit down with you
and I'm gonna watch
that documentary Planet Earth,
the one that you can't stop
talking about.
But I really need to talk to you.
Go on.
Okay, uh...
I-I never...
I never really knew
how to ask my dad... things.
Or-or what to ask him, even.
And, um, well, here.
What is this?
Why do people always ask that?
If you open it up,
then you'll know what it is.
That is a visa application
for a trip to Vietnam.
I need to go there, Zoe.
I'm gonna go to the place
where my dad last served,
I'm gonna track down that woman,
and I'm gonna figure out my dad's story.
And I-I know it sounds absolutely crazy,
and it's probably even crazier
that I'm asking you to come with me
because our relationship is brand-new,
and it's fresh and it's fun
and 14 hours on a plane
and sharing a hotel room and a
bathroom with no air freshener,
just gross.
But I just... I-I figured maybe
the documentarian in you
would dig it, you know?
Or maybe the part of you
that digs me would dig it.
I don't know, I just... I feel
like I'm talking way too much,
and I need you to help me stop.
♪ Now not me...
Vietnam, huh?
Yeah.
Really?
- Yeah.
- You want to go?
- Yeah, really?
Beth Pearson.
Love of my life.
I'm so glad you are up,
because I have got the news, baby girl.
Can I get a drumroll, please?
I got a campaign manager.
And a new love for bibimbap.
We got to start adding Korean
to the takeout menu.
That's great to hear, babe.
Nope.
What is it?
What's wrong?
I got fired.
I know. They're idiots.
For the past few weeks,
I've been pretending that I'm fine,
but I'm not, babe.
I'm not fine.
Okay.
I'm really sorry.
Why didn't you say anything?
'Cause I know you're gonna say,
like, any company would be,
you know, lucky to have me,
or that I'm extraordinary
and exceptional... I-I just...
I don't feel
like hearing that right now,
because I don't...
I don't feel like it's true.
Well, you must have been
sipping on crazy juice
if you don't think that's true.
Well, tell that to all the jobs
I sent my résumé to.
Join my campaign.
- No.
- Why not?
- No, I don't want a pity job.
- It's not a pity job.
I... You already have
a campaign manager.
Jae-won says if we want to stand
a chance of winning this thing,
I have to hire a strong team.
And I already got 20 years of
data that says that Beth Pearson
is the best teammate there is.
You are my missing ingredient, baby.
You're the horseradish
in my Bloody Mary.
We pulled all-nighters
in an empty apartment
with the exception of a mattress
to get each other through grad school.
We threw a wedding for $5,000
by negotiating the hell out of
the entire Tri-State Area,
and people are still talking
about them crab puffs.
- Them crab puffs.
- Right?
Anything we take on, we crush.
You swear this is not a pity job?
I wouldn't dare offer you a pity job.
You really do hear
forest animals with kazoos
when you see me, don't you?
What's that?
- Let's win you an election.
- That's what I'm talking about.
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*