Previously on This Is Us...
This is the apartment building
Beth and I bought last year.
It's where I found my biological father.
Our background is complicated.
She will break you, Kevin.
JASPER: I've spoken to colleagues
who have had success with IVF.
At your weight, realistically,
there's about a 90% chance
of failure here.
You've been on
the antidepressant how long?
- TOBY: Uh, six years.
- It's possible they're causing
the decreased sperm count.
KATE: Dad!
DOCTOR: Your husband went
into cardiac arrest.
Mrs. Pearson, your husband has died.
JACK: Come on, Bec.
What's the harm in looking?
Hmm. I've heard that one before.
Mom?
Morning.
(SIGHS)
- Do you want some coffee?
- Yeah.
It's a big day today.
Are we finally gonna pick a
house and get out of this place?
Yeah, if it's the right house.
But that's not why it's a big day.
That came for you this morning.
You know, rejection letters
don't typically weigh three pounds.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Ma, I... Ma, I got-I got in.
- I got into Howard.
- I knew it.
♪
(CRYING) Oh, baby.
(SNIFFLES)
Mom, are-are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good, I'm just,
I'm so happy for you.
- God, get a room.
- (RANDALL CHUCKLES)
Well, good morning to you, too.
You know, your brother
just got into Howard.
Randall, that's great.
Hey, I'm sure you'll hear from
Berklee any time soon now, too.
I was gonna make a veggie omelet for us,
if you want one.
Nah, I'm good.
But, um, we're out of these, by the way.
Okay, I'll go, uh, buy more.
(SIGHS)
I have to go wake up Kevin and tell him.
♪
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
RANDALL: Hey! All right, pack it in.
You three hellions have just completed
your first week of school.
That calls for some celebratory froyo.
Can't. I'm staying after school for TSA.
You're doing airport security training?
It's a Taylor Swift Appreciation club.
I'm staying after, too.
I have my Little Farmers Club.
But froyo.
- Bye.
What about you? Got anything?
Beyhive meeting you got to get to?
- Nope. Don't make this a thing.
- Nothing?
Okay.
Yo, I'm not making this
a thing whatsoever,
but, uh, it's just that it's
your first week at a new school,
and every time we ask you
how your day went,
you've said it was fine.
What? Say it.
It's just, this school
is pretty white, man.
What? White people go to this school?
They got a club for milk
enthusiasts. What is that?
That's my kind of club.
Where do I sign up?
(DEJA LAUGHS)
I miss my drill team at my old school.
Why don't you start one here?
It's not gonna work.
- How do you know unless you...
- Dude.
(GUNFIRE, DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNORING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
What do you got here?
(MAN SPEAKING IN FRENCH OVER EARBUDS)
KEVIN: He's that French guy
you interviewed
- for your documentary, yeah?
- ZOE: Yeah.
Do you even know what he's saying?
Oui.
Je parle français et trois
autres langues.
- Wow. Man. God.
- (LAUGHS)
- You are so hot.
- Oh...
(MOANING)
Hi.
- Mm-mm.
- What?
I have to finish transcribing.
Are you saying I can't compete
with an old French guy?
Uh, no. Not when he's talking about
Earth's dwindling water supply.
- No.
- Right.
Eh, you're probably right.
Hmm.
I was gonna invite you
to my premiere tomorrow night.
But I... it's just, it just,
it's... I... it's too soon.
- It is.
- Yeah.
Plus, you know I'm going
to Chicago in the morning
- to sound mix.
- Right.
I could drive you, tomorrow
morning, to the airport.
- Thanks. You don't have to...
- I don't mind.
- Really, it's, uh, it's okay.
- No, no.
It's no problem.
I'd be killing time, you know?
Um... look, I just, uh,
I, um, I don't want this really nice,
really light, really lovely
thing to be serious, you know?
You know where I'm coming from, right?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Of course.
Ah, I know where you're coming...
I'm the king of casj.
Okay? Casj, like "casual," okay?
- Mm. Oh.
- I'm not the king of cashmere.
Although that's a lie,
I am the king of cashmere.
- (LAUGHS)
- I am. I'm not ashamed of it.
- You'll see. Oh, no, you'll see.
- Of course you are.
(LAUGHS) Okay.
Mm-mm. You're stress snacking?
(CHUCKLES)
It's my co-op kitchen proposal.
I'll work it off at barre class.
No, keep it on.
I like you a little slim thick.
BETH: Mm... oh, that feels good.
- Do not stop.
- Okay.
Just don't keep doing that thing
where you're directing me
the entire time.
Ooh, just a little bit higher.
Oh... I mean, uh, no.
- I'll shut up.
- Uh-huh.
Please don't stop.
This proposal is kicking my ass, babe.
Oh, and I may have
to go into work tomorrow
before the premiere.
- On Saturday?
- Yep.
(INHALES SHARPLY) Just a little
bit lower, more pressure.
I think I'll take Deja to
the rec center by our building.
What for?
There's this girl, Sky.
She's one of the tenant's daughters.
- She's about Deja's age.
- Mm-hmm.
Maybe I can introduce them,
they can hang out.
She may feel more comfortable there.
- Couldn't hurt... ow.
- Sorry. That's...
but you-you said more pressure.
- Yeah, but modulate, baby.
- Right. You got it.
Modulate, but don't stop.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Toby, enough with the knee.
You're driving me crazy.
Sorry. I'm just su... I'm super excited.
I mean, come on.
An NYC premiere? This is too much.
(LAUGHS)
Ooh. (HYPERVENTILATING)
What? What's the matter? What's
the matter? What's the matter?
- Fertility hormone hot flash.
- Oh, I got this.
Hey, man, can you crank the A.C.?
- Oh, that's good.
- Oh, well, that is...
- (EXHALES)
- (TOBY LAUGHS)
Oh, damn, girl.
You look like
you're in a Whitesnake video.
Yeah, you make IVF
look very rock and roll.
- Mm.
- (SNARLS)
Stop, that's my spot. Stop.
- (LAUGHS)
- My gosh.
I'm on the hormones, and you've
been extra frisky lately.
Yeah, well, the idea of you
and me making a mini you and me
makes me and mini me very excited.
Listen, all of this is big news,
and it's still early.
And I-I don't want to talk about risks
or hormone shots with my mom,
so let's not say anything to my family.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Some things are best kept
between a husband and his wife
and his Lyft driver.
Really hope the IVF works for you guys.
- Okay, thanks.
- Thanks.
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
Looks like you could use a hand.
Thank you. I can manage.
Fair enough.
Please, do not touch my things.
I said I can manage.
WILLIAM: I didn't catch your name.
RANDALL: Hey, ChiChi.
Hey, Randall. Is everything okay?
- You got my rent check, right?
- I did. Everything's good.
I just, uh, I wanted
to introduce Deja to Sky.
CHICHI: Sky, over here.
RANDALL: Hey, Sky. This is Deja.
Deja, Sky.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Uh, were ya'll just stepping?
Yeah, you step?
No, but I was on a drill team.
Oh, cool. Come on,
I'll show you what we're doing.
Why is that mattress
up against the wall?
- Because of the hole.
- Well, why is there a hole?
Because of the busted pipe.
Why is there a busted pipe?
Because of the water heater.
Randall, are we going
to play this game all day?
Because I'd like to get back to my book.
Nah.
Why doesn't somebody call
the city or Parks and Rec,
fix this place up?
We call all the time.
It doesn't work.
We don't even have
proper street lighting.
But if you think you can do better
after sitting around
for all of five minutes,
feel free to go to city hall.
Talk to Councilman Brown.
Maybe I will.
Okay.
Maybe I will right now.
(LAUGHS) Okay.
Okay.
I had to tell you guys first,
Ms. Yvette.
We're all here. Go ahead, hon.
Guess who got into H.U.?
KEITH (OVER PHONE): You know!
- (LAUGHING): Yes!
- I told you you'd get in.
RP, you're gonna love the campus, man.
The Greek parties, the step shows.
Yeah, and I'm-a make sure
you pledge, too.
Okay, look, boy, he is going
there for an education.
Hey, I can't wait.
YVETTE: You'll come over
tonight to celebrate.
Isaac is gonna grill and
I'll make my fried okra.
REBECCA: Randall, we're late
to meet the realtor.
I got to go, but tonight sounds good.
I just have to ask my mom first.
Okay and that's the living room.
Let's take a look at the kitchen.
JACK: You got to admit,
this place gets more light than ours.
Yeah, well, light is overrated.
REALTOR: This way.
Now, this house does
only have three bedrooms,
- so if that's an issue...
- No, no, it's fine.
I mean, the boys
can share a room, right?
I mean, Randall,
you're gonna be heading off
to college in the fall
and Kate, fingers crossed,
you'll hear from Berklee any day now.
As for me, I'll be right here.
Me, too.
What do you mean?
I never sent in the tape they asked for
for my callback audition.
- I-I bet you can still
- Nope.
- apply for springtime.
- I'm done.
RANDALL: But if you just explain...
Randall, she said she's done, all right?
Um, have you seen the backyard?
It's like a vacation out there.
That sounds nice.
- Oh, this way. Follow me.
- Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, that was fun.
Kevin.
Kev. Kev, are you hammered right now?
I'm fine.
Okay, so, Megan Markle tiny hat?
Or no tiny hat?
- I don't know.
- I like the tiny hat.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. It's cute.
- Huh? Eh?
- Oh, look at you.
It's Italian. Huh? Made in Pasadena.
- It's very handsome.
- (KATE GIGGLES)
Oh, no, no, no, m'lady.
If you want handsome,
please allow me to introduce
Miguel Rivas!
Huh? Huh?
(WHOOPS)
Guys, we have to go.
Car's all gassed up.
As soon as I grab a snack for the road,
then we can head out, okay?
Ooh! Caramel creme. That's my favorite.
- Oh, and only 80 calories.
- Oh, no, actually, you can't.
- These are Kate's.
- I can't use my own...
I'm a heroin addict.
(BABY CRYING)
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
I know it's loud.
It's too hot. She won't stop crying.
I was wondering if you'd had dinner.
I might've made too much is all
and, uh, you'd be doing me a favor.
(CHUCKLES)
I said I made too much.
I didn't say I made it well.
It's not bad.
It's not good, either.
My food tends to live
somewhere in the margins.
(CHUCKLES)
ChiChi. It's a pretty name.
It's Ibo. I'm Nigerian.
So it's just the two of you here?
I was married.
I married very young.
Me and my husband Emeka
met when I was nine.
(CHUCKLES) He used to come to my house
and my mother would let us
watch karate movies
and Walker, Texas Ranger.
(BOTH LAUGH)
So, when we won visa lottery,
we knew we had to go to Texas,
see the cowboys for ourselves.
Emeka died before we traveled.
I decided to still come...
but not to Texas.
Wouldn't... have been
the same without him.
(SKY CRIES)
My NA group is putting something
together, a little...
celebration for me being
five years clean and sober.
It's at the community center on Fifth.
A lot of people
in the building go there.
Good people.
A lot of them with small kids.
You're welcome to come.
Thank you.
But I'm all right.
Would you like to hold her?
Are you sure?
Uh, I haven't had much practice.
Hello, my sweet.
Sky, meet William.
Hello, Sky. Yeah.
Yeah.
You're a natural.
Hello, Sky.
Hello.
Hey, how's it going?
BETH (OVER PHONE): Swamped.
I might have to meet you
at the premiere.
That's fine. Don't worry about it.
So, uh, I took Deja to this rec
center to hang out with Sky.
Place is a bit of a dump.
Oh, really? So you're thinking
about buying it?
- Ha-ha ha.
- Ha-ha.
But I did go to city hall.
I wanted to speak to the councilman
about fixing the place up.
Apparently, dude is
getting his hair cut.
- So you are...
- Headed to his barbershop.
My man.
Hey, babe, I got to finish up here.
I'm buried in work.
All right. I'll see you tonight.
JACK: You could grow basil for pesto.
When have you ever eaten pesto?
Where are you right now?
What?
Sorry, hon.
I'm right here.
So what do you think of this place?
Have you noticed Kate's eating?
Randall...
You know, and Kevin's
drunk half the time.
But-but you don't seem to care.
I do care.
I'm doing the very best that I can.
They're both grieving.
- What would you like me to do?
- I don't know.
But anything. I mean, you lied.
You said that you'd take care
of everything.
You said we'd be okay,
that you'd step up and make sure of it,
but you lied.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's getting late.
I think we need to go.
MIGUEL: You know, our friend Carol,
she has a daughter who did the in vitro.
- REBECCA: Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- Remember?
The cute, little twins
with the weird names.
- What were they?
- Eloise and Plaza.
- Yeah.
- REBECCA: Mm-hmm.
Terrible names. Yeah.
- Mom.
- Hmm?
- What's up?
- What? Nothing.
Nothing at all, Bug.
This is exactly what
I was trying to avoid.
Just say it.
Kate, have you guys really
considered all of the risks?
Oh, can we not do this?
I'm sure that they've done
the research...
Because I-I did learn a lot
from helping my friend Carol
and I know that
the egg retrieval surgery
is a dangerous procedure for someone...
someone... your size, Kate.
♪
♪ What did I do wrong? ♪
♪ Someone tell me... ♪
Excuse me, Councilman Brown,
may I have a word?
A word? (CHUCKLES)
Hell, you can have a whole paragraph.
My name's Randall Pearson.
I own the property on Olney and Third.
It's the big one,
right next to the laundromat.
Nice to have a black landlord
in this city.
Not many of those.
Councilman Sol Brown.
- 12th District.
- Nice to meet you.
All my pleasure.
My father lived in the building
for several years.
When he passed away,
my wife and I took it as
a personal mission
to turn the place around.
Good for you. Come on, sit.
- Join us.
- Thank you.
So, what's on your mind, Mr. Pearson?
(SIGHS)
I'm actually here about
the rec center on Fifth Street.
The place is falling apart.
I'm talking holes in the wall,
water damage.
The streetlights out front are
either broken or missing.
Yeah, that place isn't what it was.
Kills me.
What part of town do you live in?
Oh, I actually live in New Jersey.
- In the suburbs.
- Oh, good for you.
I grew up in South Philly.
Spent a lot of time at
a rec center myself back then.
Ree's Recreation Center.
- Ever hear of it?
- No, I can't say that I have.
My pops owned the grocery store
right across the street from it.
I think I was in high school
when there was a shooting at Ree's.
The mayor tried to shut it down,
but my pops wasn't having it.
He always said, "Boy,
ain't nothin' worth having
if you ain't willing to fight for it."
He got everybody in the neighborhood
to rally to keep Ree's open.
Your father sounds like
he was the real deal.
He was. He really was.
Last year, I cast the deciding vote
to shut Ree's down.
Eh, it wasn't structurally
sound, became dangerous.
In my position, Mr. Pearson,
I have to make decisions
I don't always love.
Ironic, isn't it?
I got into politics to honor a man
who I'd now be constantly disappointing.
BROWN: Hmm.
I'm adopted.
My adoptive father passed away as well.
So I have two dead fathers
that I'm constantly trying
to make proud.
Tell you what.
I'll have a maintenance crew
come out there today.
I'm gonna be there to make sure.
Hey, you have my word, brother.
Thank you very much, Councilman.
- My pleasure, son.
- Appreciate it.
Thank you, sir.
♪
Hey, all right. Cool.
(IMITATES CROWD CHEERING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Kevin Pearson, brace yourself.
- Really?
- Okay, no, here it is.
I found it, so "doctors
will not even perform IVF
on women over a certain weight
in Australia."
- Because it's that dangerous.
- Hi, everyone.
- Oh, hi, sweetheart.
- Hi. (CHUCKLES)
So proud of you.
Really excited for tonight.
Yeah, no, that's-that's obvious.
What's going on here?
Oh, well, uh, Kate and Toby
are getting in vitro,
and your mother knows everything
there is to know about IVF
because of Eloise and Plaza.
- The book?
- No.
REBECCA: Kate, I'm just saying,
why would you take that risk
when there are
so many other options out there?
Because I want to.
'Cause I want to.
Because I want to look
that baby in his face,
and I want to... I want to see Toby.
I want to see myself. I want to see...
I want to see Dad.
And I'm the only one in the family
who's gonna carry on a piece of Dad.
- What about me?
- Okay, Kev.
"Okay, Kev"? Real...
What's that supposed to mean?
- You're not serious.
- No, no, apparently
I'm not serious ever about anything.
- This is great...
- Okay, enough, enough, enough.
And, Kate, of course a baby
would be cause for celebration.
- But... I... there...
- Why is there a "but"?
How about stop at "celebration"
and just stop there?
I just think it's irresponsible.
- Because of my weight?
- No.
Yeah, you've already
made that really clear.
No, Kate, now you're twisting my words.
Okay, well, for the past 20 years,
you have swallowed every single
comment about my weight,
but now, you want to
bring it up now because
- it's something that I want?
- Kate!
Where do I draw the line?
How do I toe the line, Kate, because...
Shut up! Everyone just shut up!
This is... it's not about you, Rebecca.
It's not about any of you.
This is about me and Kate.
All right? We lost a child,
and now we want to start a family.
And we needed a little help
because we have bad eggs,
and apparently I have really bad sperm.
So we have every expert in town
telling us
how dangerous this is.
And we know it probably won't
work out for us.
So please, for the love of God,
save the asinine commentary
from the cheap seats.
Toby...
I'm sorry. Look, I'm gonna, uh...
I'm gonna go clear my head.
I'll see you guys at the premiere.
Five, six, seven, eight.
WILLIAM: Hi, my name is William,
and I'm an addict.
GROUP: Hi, William.
I've been clean for five years
and... one minute.
(CHUCKLES)
Strange thing to celebrate, huh?
Somehow it feels more special
than my own birthday.
I started using 30 years ago,
when I lost my mother.
The only family I ever really had.
Then I moved a couple of blocks away,
and all that changed.
I met Sam, who drove for Septa
and didn't begrudge me
when I couldn't pay my fare.
And Bernadette, who bested
this old junkie
to a game of chess, and for her prize
asked that I accompany her
to an NA meeting.
And last night I met
this young Nigerian woman named ChiChi.
And she let me hold her beautiful baby.
And she told me I was a natural.
And it might as well have been
my birthday when she said that.
When she gave me that gift.
WILLIAM: Community.
That's a strange word on its own.
The word's not as warm as "family,"
but some people, people like myself,
we don't have family.
But that's okay
because we have each other.
We have this place...
and that's not nothin'.
That's not nothin' at all.
I'm going to Ms. Yvette's.
Okay, sweetheart.
Hey, Ma...
I-I'm sorry.
- You know, about before.
- No, no.
No, you don't have to be.
You shouldn't be.
- Okay.
- Randall...
(SIGHS)
Randall, it's a struggle for me
to get out of bed every morning.
It takes every single ounce
of energy that I have,
and then I have nothing left
for the rest of the day.
Nothing.
And I know that isn't fair to you guys,
but I can't...
seem to stop it.
Huh.
Did you know that your father took me
to look at a new house
a few months before the fire?
Come on, Bec.
What's the harm in looking?
Yeah, I've heard that one before.
Sometimes I think about where
we would all be right now
if we had bought it.
This house does get a lot more light
than our place, right?
Yeah, well, light is overrated.
You could grow anything you want.
Tomatoes, herbs, maybe some...
maybe some basil for pesto.
Uh, when have you ever eaten pesto?
Okay, go.
Have fun with your friends...
college boy.
Go.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Okay... we saw it. Can we go?
- Y-You don't want to see...
- I don't.
I'm sorry, I know I'm being a bad sport,
but I just... I love our house, Jack.
Even if it's old and too small
and doesn't get enough light,
and there isn't any room to grow basil,
it's... it's our house.
Okay, so we're just gonna
stay there forever?
Sounds pretty good to me.
Me, too. Yeah, I just wanted
to hear you say it.
(BOTH LAUGH)
You sure you don't want a ride home?
I bought a bus pass. I'm gonna
get my money's worth.
Fixed the light.
I see that.
One down, 8,000 to go.
RANDALL: I'm gonna stay on him.
We deserve better than this.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
I can't figure you out, Randall.
- What do you mean?
- I loved your father.
He was a good man. We were
his family. He was one of us.
I look at you, Randall,
and oh, my goodness.
I see so much of him in you, so clearly.
It makes me happy. It gives me
a piece of my friend back.
But we are not a we.
You are not one of us.
You brought your daughter
to come play here,
but instead of sitting and chatting
and getting to know the place,
you spent the whole day
seeing its problems,
trying to fix them.
I'm not even sure you know why.
We are not our problems.
I know you're not.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
I got to get going.
I know you do.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Oh, wow.
- This is amazing.
- Yeah.
- Toby's not returning my calls
- or answering my texts.
- Ah. No way he misses a premiere.
He'll be here, trust me.
- Hey, Kev?
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry if I hurt
your feelings earlier.
Oh, no, no. Hey, listen,
it's, it's fine.
Okay? I mean, honestly, the idea
of me having kids
makes me physically nauseous.
It wasn't that, it was, um...
He never saw me act.
He was always the hardest one on me.
And I think it was because he
was the one person in the world
that ever took me seriously.
A-And I always wondered, you know,
if someone actually gave me
a shot, like, a real shot,
to be the man
that he thought I could be,
if I could actually go there,
if I could actually get there.
(IMITATES AUDIENCE CHEERING)
And here we are, you know?
In a couple hours,
we'll find out if I deserve
to be taken seriously, I guess, right?
And now I'm gonna go do
an interview with Mario Lopez.
The world is running out of water.
It's a major human crisis.
MARIO LOPEZ (OVER VIDEO):
Hey, man, I am hearing nothing
- but positive things, Kevin.
- KEVIN: Good. Good to hear.
- There's a lot of great buzz right now.
- KEVIN: Thank you.
- You should be excited.
- KEVIN: Thank you. I am excited.
- Who's joining you here tonight?
- Uh, you know what? My whole family.
What about a special lady friend?
- KEVIN: Uh, I just...
- No?
- Solo tonight. Just me, just me.
- Okay. All right.
KEVIN: Uh, I got to ask you a question.
We want to know how you keep
yourself looking so young?
'Cause you look like
you could walk right back
into Saved by the Bell.
I'm not kidding you.
There you are. Miguel found our seats.
Toby's not here yet.
I don't know what's going on with him.
I'm sure he'll make it.
No, it's time to take my shot.
And he is supposed
- to give it to me.
- And I'm sure he'll make it.
But it... if I don't get it
in time, it's gonna throw off
my whole hormone cycle.
I'm at high risk.
- Okay, Kate, Kate.
- One little slip-up
- is gonna ruin the whole thing.
- Kate.
Do you have it with you?
Just make sure you keep
the site really clean.
I got it. And then
it's just one push, right?
Mm-hmm.
(EXHALES)
You know, Kate,
after your father passed away,
there was a period of time
where I just didn't...
I didn't know if I was
ever gonna make it back.
You know, if I could make it.
MAN (OVER TV): Hey, you okay?
WOMAN (OVER TV): No. Why? Um...
MAN: You're sure?
It doesn't hurt.
So the thought of anything
ever happening to you,
anything, anything
that could ever put you
in any sort of real harm,
is just paralyzing to me.
(REBECCA LAUGHS SOFTLY)
You'll see, when you have kids.
WOMAN (OVER TV):
All I can think about was...
I gained 25 pounds.
WOMAN (OVER TV): You know
what it's like when everything
is suddenly different?
And I should have done more
when you really started
gaining the weight.
I was almost 18.
I should have made better food choices.
Well, we've had a terrible few months.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
- (QUIETLY): Should we do this? Okay.
- Yeah.
Here we go.
(GRUNTS)
- Okay, right there? All right.
- KATE: Mm-hmm.
One, two, three.
- Okay. Is that okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(SNIFFLES)
Okay.
♪ Older chests reveal themselves ♪
♪ Like a crack in a wall... ♪
Thank you.
♪ Starting small ♪
(PHONE CHIMES)
♪ And grow in time ♪
- Hey.
- ♪ And we always seem ♪
♪ To need the help ♪
♪ Of someone else
to mend that shelf... ♪
♪ Too many books... ♪
♪ Read me your favorite line... ♪
♪ Papa went to other lands... ♪
- Hi. Hi, I'm sorry.
- Babe.
I overreacted, and-and then
I lost track of time.
Do you still need your shot?
My mom did it.
Huh.
- Hey, hey. Babe?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I've never seen you
blow up like that. Ever.
What's been going on with you lately?
Yeah, it's probably just jet lag.
You know, I'm okay.
All right. Let's get our seats, yeah?
♪ Some things, they stay the same... ♪
Uh, I'm sorry.
How'd it go at work today?
I kicked that proposal's ass.
That's what's up. Psh...
How'd it go with you?
Uh, it's complicated.
This stuff's always complicated for me.
What is?
Just where I fit in.
How I come off to certain people.
It's either I'm trying too hard
or I'm not trying hard enough.
I can never get it right.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ Mama tried to wash their faces... ♪
I won't have any fun there. (LAUGHS)
All right.
♪ And Daddy lost ♪
♪ At the races too many times ♪
(LAUGHTER)
♪ She broke down the other day ♪
♪ Yeah, you know, some things
in life may change ♪
♪ But some things,
they stay the same... ♪
Hi, um, uh, this message
is for the admissions office.
I'm Randall Pearson,
and I already sent in my form
saying that I'll be
attending Howard this fall,
but I just wanted to call
to say that, actually,
I... actually, I won't be.
I got to, uh, stay,
stay close to home for family.
Thank you for this opportunity.
(BEEPS)
(PHONE CLATTERS)
- KEVIN: Hi.
- Ah.
- My brother, on the big screen.
- Hi.
Damn.
Is this movie gonna make me cry?
Uh, well, you cry
at everything, so probably.
Oh, it's gonna make me
cry buckets, I can tell.
(KEVIN LAUGHS)
What'd I miss?
- Today? Uh...
- Yeah.
You missed quite a bit, actually.
Um, Kate and Toby are doing IVF.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- RANDALL: Good for them.
- I think so. Yeah.
KEVIN: Mom kind of flipped out
a little bit, though.
You know, which upset Kate.
She was like,
"Well, I'm the only one
that's gonna be able to pass on
a piece of Dad," right,
which made me upset, and...
even though, to be honest with
you, it really wasn't about that
for me, you know what I mean? You...
Let me ask you a question.
Do you think serious people
take me seriously?
What? Hey.
No, I... She said she was the only one
who could pass on a piece of Dad?
(WHISPERS): It's starting. Hey.
(20TH CENTURY FOX THEME PLAYING)
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*