[opening theme music playing]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give into her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
-[whimsical music]
-[Ridley] The Trailblazers.
[loud grunting]
[sighing] Can I see my portrait now, Lou?
Not yet. Wait until done.
Sitting still really isn't my thing.
[chuckling] If was,
painting be done by now.
I know,
but I'm an official museum protector.
I need to be out there, protecting.
Keeping my eyes peeled
for people who need help like--
[yelling] This dodo's going down!
Dudley!
[Dudley yelling, grunting]
I have an update.
I still can't fly like an eagle.
[Ridley laughing]
See? I'm crushing it
as an official museum protector.
Less spin. More sit still.
[sighing]
Whoa! I thought I'd seen
every secret hallway in the museum.
This one, extra special secret.
[Ridley] Huh.
That one looks like Grandma,
and this one… Is that Mama?
-My mama?
-It sure is.
Welcome to the Protector Passageway.
It's where we hang portraits
of all the protectors of the museum.
Me, your mama, and now you.
Wow! I look so protectory.
[chuckling] You sure do.
You're the latest museum protector.
Our legacy is to keep everyone safe.
So make us proud. Okay?
Keep everyone safe and make you proud.
I can do that.
It's your best portrait yet, Lou.
I don't know how you do it
with the brush in your mouth.
Where there is will, there is way.
Painting, window to soul.
-Did you do these paintings too?
-Yes.
But from imagination.
Never set foot beyond museum.
Dream of painting sunset
from Serengeti Point.
Serengeti Point?
Huh. I've never been there,
or even heard of it.
It's all the way out here. [chuckling]
Lou would need an official protector
to take him that far. Know any?
[gasping] I can take him there.
We go to Serengeti Point together?
It'd be my honor.
I don't know. Statues not great hikers.
Slow. Top-heavy. Wobbly. No feet.
Don't worry. I'll get you there
and make the past protectors proud.
-What's up?
-Ridley!
-Hey, guys.
-Hey, what's with all the art supplies?
I'm taking Lou to Serengeti Point
to paint the sunset.
First Lou adventure.
Wait, but you weren't gonna go
without us, right?
Plus, that trail is supposed to be
super dangerous.
Sorry, everyone. I kind of got swept away
in my first mission
as an official protector.
Of course, you should come too.
Thanks, but can we circle back
to that dangerous part?
I'm sure it's nothing I can't handle.
I'll keep you all safe.
As someone who never travels light,
who's gonna carry all Lou's stuff?
-Does he have royal subjects too?
-Bummer it won't fit on my board.
[gasping] Houston,
we have a problem solver.
I'll take the supplies in the biplane
and meet you out there.
Thanks, Peaches.
All right, Eyes and Lou,
next stop, the Serengeti.
[biplane roaring]
-How's it going up there, Peaches?
-All good, sunshine.
This is just like all those banana
deliveries I made to the space station.
[Lou gasping]
[Lou] Serengeti Point!
We're going into uncharted territory.
I feel on top of the world, like I…
[inhaling] I got this.
♪ Now that I'm a true protector
The hero I was born to be ♪
♪ I can conquer any challenge ♪
♪ That's my guarantee ♪
♪ When danger strikes, just call me ♪
♪ Who saves the day? It's all me ♪
♪ I'm always there, heroically ♪
♪ It's all me ♪
♪ The stakes are high, but I say YOLO
Charging into the unknown ♪
♪ Flying high and flying solo
I'll do it on my own ♪
-♪ But what about-- ♪
-♪ Just call me ♪
-♪ We're here to help ♪
-♪ It's all me ♪
♪ I thought that teamwork was the key ♪
♪ It's all me ♪
♪ Just wait and see ♪
[song ends]
[Ridley] There it is!
[Fred] Serengeti Point.
[Ridley] Wow, that's pretty steep.
We better get moving if we're gonna
make it to the top before sunset.
[Dante] Let's do this!
Ridley, it's prettier
than banana cream pie up here.
I just unloaded Lou's art supplies.
Want me to do a flyby
and guide you up the trail?
[Ridley] No, I got things covered
down here. We'll see you soon!
Uh, maybe we should
take Peaches up on her offer?
Yeah. All of these boulders
kind of look the same.
Except for the one
that looks like Mrs. Sanchez.
And none of the paths are marked.
Nah, I've got it.
If we just turn this way, we'll hit--
Huh?
-[Dudley] A dead end?
-Just kidding. [chuckling]
I think it's this other trail?
[Ridley] Huh.
-[Fred] Uh…
-[creature growling]
-[all panicking]
-[Ridley] Oh no!
All right, we're back on track now.
We keep moving,
I'm sure we'll make it by sunset.
-[grunting] Oh no.
-[rocks crumbling]
Huh? What is it, Lou?
You're rocking the wrong way.
Trail is small.
Lou is big.
Fall is long!
Lou's right.
It'll take some fancy hoof-work
to get around this cliff.
Or fancy wrap work.
I can tie my wraps around Lou,
and we can all help him keep his balance
by leading him along the trail!
Don't worry. I got this.
It's a dangerous curve,
and I have to keep you all safe.
Go ahead. Lou and I will catch up.
Huh. Catch you on the flip, dudes.
-Here we go.
-[both grunting]
Slow and steady, Lou.
-[Lou grunting]
-And don't look down.
[rocks crumbling]
Uh-oh. Lou look down.
Lou regret looking down.
[Lou wailing]
[gasping]
-[Lou yelling]
-[Ridley screaming]
-[loud crashing]
-[Lou grunting]
Huh? Whew! [chuckling]
See? I got this.
I really hope she does.
[Ridley] Once we cross this bridge,
it's a straight shot to Serengeti Point.
I think.
Rope bridge and giant stone, bad combo.
[grunting]
Too heavy.
Those ropes won't hold for long.
[gasping] We've got a need.
A need for speed!
Here, use my board.
Many thanks, but stones can't skate.
Dude, no worries.
Fred can push you
with their super bisonic strength.
Oh, you bet your horns I can.
And we'll go even faster
if everyone helps me push Lou along.
[Lou grunting]
I don't know. Getting across this bridge
will be tricky and dangerous.
I'll do the pushing myself.
[Ridley grunting]
[bridge creaking]
I'm doing it. [grunting]
Rope and stone don't mix.
We move too slow.
Ridley, we could lend you a hand.
Or a wing, a hoof, a claw.
Anything.
[Dante] Yeah, you need speed. Remember?
It's fine. Just follow my lead.
[creaking, snapping]
-They're breaking!
-Faster, dudes!
I got this. I got this.
-[creaking]
-Yeah, I don't got this!
-[Ridley] Whoa!
-[all yelling]
[crashing, grunting]
-[sighing]
-Everyone okay?
[groaning] Yes.
-Uh-huh.
-Yep.
-Think so.
-I am.
Except for the fact
that there's no way out of here.
[Dante grunting]
This pit, metaphor.
And it's, like, also getting dark.
Sun has set on painting sunset.
What do we do now, Ridley?
Something I've never had to do before.
-[sighing]
-[beeping]
Grandma, I need help.
[biplane roaring]
[whimsical music playing]
Tubular!
Ooh, thanks for coming to save us,
Dr. Jones. That pit was the pits!
Of course! Always happy
to help you Eyes out of a jam.
[Lou] It's okay, Ridley.
We didn't make it,
but Rome not built in day.
I can't believe I…
I failed.
[sad music playing]
-What are you doing, Ridley?
-[Ridley sighing]
Grandma, I couldn't help Lou
or my pals on our trip.
I tried so hard to live up to
the Jones family name
and be a good protector, but…
I failed. I don't think I deserve to
have my portrait up there next to yours.
Being a protector doesn't mean
you don't make mistakes
or have nothing left to learn.
That's the thing about adventuring.
It never stops being an adventure.
And adventures are easier
with the help of your friends.
[gasping] I thought to keep everyone safe,
I had to do everything myself.
A protector is only as strong as her team.
And I have the best team!
I need to make things right with them.
-[Grandma chuckling]
-Thanks, Grandma.
So, I'm really sorry for not listening
to you on our hike yesterday.
I get it now. I need your strength,
your leadership, your caution, your moves,
and your right stuff.
-Oh!
-[Ismat] Of course.
[Fred] Oh, we got you!
Thanks. Now, what do you say
we head out on a new--
Well, do-over adventure? I'll need
all of your help to get us up to the top.
Eyes on three. One, two…
[together] Eyes!
Show us the best way
up to the point, Peaches.
Copy that! Follow my lead!
I think it's a mummy's time to shine!
Oh yeah! On it!
[Lou grunting]
[Fred] Nice!
[Peaches grunting]
The bridge is back, y'all!
-[Fred] Time for this rock to roll.
-[Dante] We've got a need for speed!
-[all grunting]
-[bridge creaking]
[Lou chuckling] Whee!
[cheering, chuckling]
Pipin' hot monkey bread! Y'all made it!
Now take a gander at this view.
-[whistling]
-[all murmuring]
-[Ridley] It's beautiful.
-Better than dream.
Welcome to Serengeti Point, Lou.
Ready to paint?
With all my heart.
-[Fred] It's perfect.
-[Dudley chuckling]
Actually, how do you feel about
painting me a new portrait?
[clearing throat] Let's see.
[triumphant music playing]
[group] That's us!
Lou, you captured exactly
what being a protector means to me.
Adventuring is always an adventure,
but with friends by your side,
you can face anything.
-[whimsical music]
-[Ridley] Moles Shall Overcome.
Our next contestant
on Celebrity Tag-a-Mole
is Ridley Jones!
Taggers are locked and loaded!
Five, four, three, two…
[together] Tag!
[moles giggling]
Whew!
-Yippee!
-Yay, Ridley!
[grunting]
-No!
-[Dante] Cool!
-Gotcha!
-[mole giggling]
[Ridley laughing]
Woo-hoo!
[Ridley giggling]
[snorting] Bisonic job, Ridley!
Who's our next Tag-a Mole tagger?
-[grunting]
-Huh?
[Dudley grunting]
Dudley?
Don't look so surprised.
I've played tag with the best of 'em!
Five, four, three, two…
[together] Tag!
[yelling]
Oh! [grunting]
-[moles giggling]
-[Dudley groaning] Whoa!
Come on, D-Bird.
-I'm gonna get you! Oh!
-[Peaches] Oh boy.
-[moles giggling]
-Oh, come on!
-Stay still!
-[moles giggling]
[Dudley groaning]
-[Dudley sighing]
[muffled] Well,
this isn't my finest moment.
Also not your worst moment.
Uh, do we need to go rescue Dudley?
Your turn. I pulled him out
of the giant nose in the bodies exhibit.
[gasping, sighing]
Who am I kidding?
I'm never gonna tag a mole.
Don't worry, Mr. Dudley.
I've got ya, or my name isn't Maggie.
Nice to meet you,
but careful with the wings when you--
[Dudley groaning]
Agh! Oof! [yelling]
[Dudley yelling, groaning]
Meet my Tag-a-Mole friend Maggie.
-Hi, hi, hi, hi!
-Isn't she cute?
Mama, Dudley got
his very first Tag-a-Mole tag.
Ooh, Tag-a-Mole!
Back in the day, I was the reigning champ.
-Count me down, Peaches.
-Roger that, Captain Jones.
Five, four, three--
-[Peabody] Hurry up, I don't have all day.
-[Lonny] You got it!
It's Mr. Peabody! Everybody hide.
Dudley, hurry!
[Dudley gulping]
[muffled] Uh, dudes, I've got
some good news and some bad news.
[grunting] Okay, just bad news.
I'm righteously stuck!
-[Dante grunting]
-Shh!
Ah, Dr. Jones!
Hi! What a lovely surprise.
Yes, yes, I'm sure
you must be thrilled to see me.
Start putting up that yellow tape.
This mole habitat is hereby closed.
You got it, Mr. Peabody, sir!
You can't close the mole habitat.
That's where we play Tag-a-Mo--
I mean, organize the exhibit because
nothing in it is alive and never will be.
They're tearing it down
to make room for a new coffee shop.
But the museum is for kids like me,
and we don't even drink coffee.
This children's museum isn't for children.
It's for making money.
And a new coffee shop
will make lots of it.
-Lonny, are you done yet?
-Almost done!
[Peabody groaning]
Maybe we could think of a different place
for your coffee shop.
I've grown tired of you Joneses.
This exhibit is closed, and that's final!
If you do get in my way again,
I'd be delighted to fire you.
-Lonny, we're leaving.
-Right behind ya! [chuckling]
Here I come! [grunting]
[straining] Right behind ya.
We can't let Mr. Peabody
close the mole habitat.
[sighing] Sorry, Ridley,
but Peabody sounded serious.
We can't risk him firing us
and kicking us out.
What would the museum do without
the Joneses here as protectors?
[Dante] Keep pulling, my dudes.
My bodacious body's almost free!
[yelling, grunting]
[sighing] Phew!
Yeah, things could get kind of bad
without us around.
You're a protector now, Ridley.
And that means you'll have
to make some tough decisions.
I better go tell everyone that the moles
will need to find somewhere new to live.
That's my girl.
You'll save our exhibit, right?
No. I'm sorry.
Mr. Peabody's mind is made up.
Then what's going to happen to us?
I don't know yet.
But I'm a protector of the museum now.
It's my job to make tough decisions.
I'll figure something out.
-We know you will, Ridley.
-You always do.
[grunting] No! This isn't right.
There's no way you moles
are gonna lose your habitat.
Yeah!
Wait. Mr. Dudley, what's a habitat?
It's a special place
where an animal makes its home
and if an animal loses its habitat…
[gasping] …it might not survive.
[moles gasping]
I won't let you lose your habitat, Maggie.
[dramatically] I won't let you
go the way of the dodo!
-What got into him?
-Maybe some bad bird seed?
[Dudley] Here we go.
Just a little more permanent marker,
and, uh, ta-da!
You look like
you could be my big brother now.
[chuckling]
Well, that's an interesting
fashion choice.
We can't let the moles lose their homes.
Dodos went extinct
mostly because humans took our habitat.
Now, uh… [grunting] …I'm not gonna
let that happen to these guys.
I'm gonna stage a "mole-in."
[yelling] Geronimo!
[muffled chuckling]
I refuse to come out
until we've saved the mole habitat.
These moles will not be whacked!
[chanting] These moles
will not be whacked!
I think it's great
how much you care about the moles,
but I have to do
what's right for the museum.
-[Ridley straining]
-[Dudley grunting]
I'm sorry, I can't come out.
My… [grunting] …conscience won't allow it.
Also, I'm stuck again.
Fred, could you help me
pull Dudley out, please?
Dudley might have a point.
Humans almost wiped out my species too.
[Maggie] We made
extra noses for everybody.
How do I look?
-Believe it or not, tougher!
-Could I get one too?
Long ago, humans hunted mammoths
and that was one reason we went extinct.
Look at me! I'm a star-nosed mammoth!
[trumpeting]
[choking, coughing]
[Nukie snorting, gulping]
Maybe humans didn't,
like, wipe out the dinosaurs,
but I still know that extinction bites!
If we let them take down the mole habitat,
who knows what'll happen next.
Maybe they'll take down the robotic swing
or the butterfly exhibit or Mrs. Sanchez.
A star nose might not be couture,
but this is important!
I've got your six, moles.
Thank you, thank you, everybody.
I don't want the habitat to close either,
but you heard Mr. Peabody.
But even if it ruffles someone's feathers,
you have to stand up and do what's right.
Or in this case, cram yourself
into a tunnel and do what's right?
Dudley, I think…
I think you're right.
For a protector of the museum, being ready
to make tough decisions isn't enough.
You have to be ready
to make the right decisions.
And saving this mole exhibit
is the right decision.
-[cheering]
-Go, Ridley! You're the best!
How's it going?
Figure out where to move the moles?
Aha! What's going on with the noses?
Mama, you know how you said
that I'm a protector of the museum now
and that I have to make decisions?
I remember.
Well, my decision
is to stand with the moles.
We can't let them lose their habitat.
This is important. We have to find a way.
[inspirational music playing]
♪ I see so clearly now
The path that I must choose ♪
♪ My heart is calling
It's a call I can't refuse ♪
♪ We must do what's right for
There are things you have to fight for ♪
♪ And the stakes are
Far too high to lose ♪
♪ We must all stand together ♪
♪ Tail to tail, scale to feather ♪
♪ Take my hand
Because the battle's just begun ♪
♪ If we all stand united ♪
♪ Every wrong will be righted ♪
♪ We can do what must be done ♪
♪ If we stand as one ♪
♪ If some feathers get ruffled ♪
♪ We will never be muffled ♪
♪ We will raise our voices
Till the race is run ♪
♪ We'll be bold and outspoken ♪
♪ With our spirits unbroken ♪
[all] ♪ We will do what must be done ♪
♪ We will stand as one ♪
[song ends]
I am proud of you, Ridley.
I'm proud of all of you.
You reminded me
that it's important to do the right thing.
-Now we need to figure out how.
-That nose looks good on you.
[giggling] Thanks.
It's kinda fun to wear too.
[clicking] Wait. That gives me an idea.
I know how we can save the mole habitat
from Mr. Peabody.
-But I'm gonna need everybody's help.
-You got it!
There's just one problem.
[grunting]
Still stuck!
I think I know how to get ya out.
[inhaling deeply]
[loud trumpeting]
[gasping]
Hey! Look at me, I'm… I'm flying!
I'm a flying dodo! [chuckling]
Whoa! [grunting]
Um… [groaning]
Uh, thanks, Nukie.
Now, let's go save the moles!
Come on, everybody. We have a lot of work
to do before the museum opens tomorrow.
I want to go in now!
-I can't wait!
-Will it open soon?
The museum is about to open.
Everyone's in place.
[gasping] Except me! Gotta go!
[Ridley] Showtime!
-Wow!
-Cool!
Hey, what's your costume?
I'm a star-nosed mole.
-This is so cool!
-Wow!
[child giggling] Huh.
This dinosaur
looks like a star-nosed mole too!
This bison makes a cute mole. [giggling]
-Why's everyone dressed like that?
-I can't really tell you.
I have to show you. Come on.
-Ta-da!
-[children] Whoa!
[child 1] Awesome!
[Ridley] The new and improved
star-nosed mole habitat,
where you can dress up like a mole.
-Wow!
-Cool!
[Ridley] Now when you climb through
the tunnels, you'll feel just like one.
Have fun storming the tunnels!
[child 2] It's so cool!
[children laughing]
Congratulations, Rids.
Looks like the new mole habitat
is a big hit.
-Look at me! I'm a mole!
-[laughing]
[Peabody] Hm. What's all this then?
Well, it looks to me like the mole habitat
has become very popular.
Lonny, what are you
going to do about this?
-Lonny?
-Yes, sir.
[gasping] My cool new nose!
Mr. Peabody, you can't close
the museum's most popular exhibit.
[child 3] Woo-hoo!
[grumbling] I guess you're right.
It can stay open.
Come on, Lonny.
I can't stand being around so much fun.
[Lonny chuckling]
[Dudley squawking]
You can't let the kids see you here.
I know.
I just had to see if we saved the moles.
We did, thanks to you.
But what are we going to do
next time Mr. Pea-bottom
tries to shut down an exhibit?
Simple. We're gonna keep on
fighting against extinction
and fighting to do what's right.
You know what?
Doing what's right feels kinda good.
It sure does.
-This is so cool!
-[children laughing]
[child 4] Can we come back tomorrow?
[closing theme music playing]