[opening theme music playing]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Bison Ball.
-Ready?
-You know I am.
[mystical twinkling]
Whoa! I filled a whole page!
-Next page, here I come.
-Oh, I'm proud of you, kiddo.
You know what? I'm proud of me too.
I'm gonna go show everyone. Bye, Mama.
Ismat, Peaches, Dante, Dudley, Fred!
[gasping] Aw, you guys.
Don't get me wrong,
filling my stamp page is exciting and all,
but you didn't have to do all this.
Good, 'cause we didn't.
Not that your passport stamp
isn't super exciting.
It is. Yay, you!
But this isn't for you.
Right. So, what is it for?
The Paleozoic Prom, of course!
Our yearly chance
to wear our best threads and dance!
[gasping] OM Ra! I forgot!
You've never been to it before!
Nope. Last year, I didn't even know
you guys could move, let alone dance.
Or decorate.
♪ Shake it to the left
Shake it to the right ♪
[Ridley] Looking sparkly, Mrs. Sanchez!
Everyone looks amazing.
Yep, it's the same every year.
-Peaches spruces up her rover.
-That's one good-lookin' rover.
-Ida polishes her armor.
-[Ida blowing] Ah.
And Fred tries to teach Dante and Dudley
their signature Paleozoic Prom dance move.
-Turn to your left, dude.
-Oof!
How 'bout you try your other left?
Hi, Dudley. Hi, Dante. Hey, where's Fred?
Don't know. And gotta say,
trying to dance without them is a bummer.
-[Dudley squawking]
-Turns out, I have two left tails.
I thought Fred'd be bisonically excited
to show off their dance moves
for the prom.
Maybe we should make sure they're okay.
So weird.
I don't see them anywhere.
[Ridley] Uh, Fred?
Fred? Fred who? Never heard of 'em.
Uh, what are you doing in here?
Everyone's getting ready for the prom.
I'm just, uh, catching up on my grazing.
[munching] Yep, grazing.
[gulping]
[sing-song] This fake grass is amazing!
I can't wait to see you dance at the prom!
Oh, thanks!
But I think I'm gonna skip it this year.
-OM Ra! You are not!
-Why?
Why? Because after all this grazing,
I was gonna walk it off
in the geography wing
and take a trip around the world.
But, Fred,
you're always the belle of the ball.
-I know, that's the problem.
-Really?
Look, truth is,
I just don't have anything to wear.
Nothing to wear?
That's so not a problem!
It kinda is, Princess.
This queen happens to be
the best designer this side of the Nile.
I'll find you something. Something
that says, "Guards, seize them!"
I mean, "Own this prom!"
Does that sound okay, Fred?
Um…
Of course it sounds okay.
-Why wouldn't it sound okay?
-Fred?
Why wouldn't I be excited for someone
who loves the words "gaudy" and "gold"
to dress me? No reason.
See? Come on,
let's go to the costume exhibit.
I have so many ideas!
[Ismat clapping]
Uh!
Ismat's gonna find something
perfect for you.
I just know it.
Um…
That seems a little poofy.
Oh, we're just getting started.
A little too Pretty in Pink.
I don't even know
which way you put that on.
Is that much glitter even legal?
So many bows!
It's see-through!
Wow. Just, wow.
I'm sure Ismat has something else.
You have something else, right?
Nope. [sighing]
An entire costume exhibit
and all 67 of my walk-in closets
and not one thing you liked?
There has to be something.
[Fred] Oh, there is!
It's perfect! I love it.
-What is it?
-[Fred] That blue…
-[Ismat] Taffeta dress!
-Wait, what?
-Yippee!
-No!
You're right! It is perfect!
[quietly] Perfectly horrifying.
Go ahead, tell me how mummazing you feel!
And spare no compliments. I can take it.
[uneasy] No problem, Princess.
This dress was just the beginning.
This fur has to go.
Wh-what do you mean, my fur has to—
[gasping]
[spluttering]
-[hairdryer whirring]
-[whimpering]
-[spray hissing]
-[groaning]
-Beautiful!
-A work of art, if I do say so myself.
Dads, thanks for squeezing in
one last fur-do before the prom. [kissing]
No problemo. I usually do wrap blowouts,
but I can do fur too.
Are you ready to see the new Fred?
[Fred] I was pretty happy
with the old Fred.
[mummies] Ta-da!
-[Fred screaming]
-At a loss for words, huh?
Still, the word
you're looking for is "love."
Okay! Dress done, hair did.
Now, you just gotta get
your twinkle toes tappin'.
-[music playing]
-Great idea.
I could use a little help with my moves.
It's a good thing
we got the disco pyramid polished.
[disco music playing]
Okay, follow along. Hoof it to the left.
[Fred panting]
Hoof it to the right. [grunting]
Now, get ready for a finish
that's totally out of sight.
Come on! Give it to us!
Give what to us?
My signature moo-ve.
Spoiler alert! It's mummazing!
That it is.
Okay, here we go.
[grunting, groaning]
Oh, that wasn't it.
[grunting, snorting]
That wasn't it either! [whimpers]
No, not good!
I think all this taffeta might be
getting in the way of my twinkle toes.
[Fred whimpers]
Fred, you just have the pre-prom jitters.
Everyone gets them.
Except queens.
Okay, sometimes we do.
But the point is, as soon as you see
how much everyone loves your new look,
you'll love it too!
I doubt it.
Hot buttered biscuits. Look at you!
[sighing] I really wish you wouldn't.
They look amazing, right?
You all do!
And your lunar rover to the prom awaits.
It's the Paleozoic Prom,
and the stars are out tonight.
Ooh, and now, entering the rotunda
we have the Eyes of the Museum!
Ismat, tell us, who are you wearing?
Vintage couture Cleopatra.
[Mrs. Sanchez] Ridley, looking good
for your first Paleozoic Prom!
You know it, Mrs. S.
[Mrs. Sanchez] Oh, Dante,
Peaches, stylish as always.
And that bow tie, one of a kind.
Just like you, Dudley.
And who is hiding back there?
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
Is that Fred?
[crowd gasping]
Oh, hey. [nervous giggling]
Hi. Uh, just me.
Your dress gets a whale-sized yes from me!
[chanting] Fred! Fred! Fred!
I bow to your magnificent bow.
I have known many a queen,
but none have matched your beauty.
I don't want to be a beauty queen.
I wanna be me.
Well, grits and gravy!
I didn't know you could have
a stampede of one, but there you have it.
Oh, great idea.
Let's do The Stampede.
[disco music playing]
I, like, don't wanna bring everyone down,
but I don't think
that was a dance Fred was doing.
-Then why are you joining in?
-Good question, dude.
We have to go find them.
There you are, Fred.
Why'd you run off?
Yeah, you cute bison.
Don't tell me you suddenly hate to dance.
[groaning] I…
No, seriously. Don't tell me.
Fred, you look as sparkling
as the Sphinx's treasure.
Show it off.
The thing is,
I know you think I look good,
but I don't feel good.
You're sick? Is it contagious?
No. I mean I don't feel like myself.
This dress, I'm uncomfortable in it.
Maybe you need a different size.
I hate when they don't have
the right size space suit for me to wear.
No, it's not about how it fits.
It's just not me.
I think maybe I dressed you
in what I wanted to wear,
not what you wanted to wear.
Sorry, Ismat.
I know you were trying to help.
No, I'm sorry.
Fashion is about feeling good,
and feeling good
is about feeling like yourself.
If you don't feel good,
I didn't do my job.
I don't feel like myself.
Why didn't you just tell us?
I was afraid you'd laugh at me.
Dude, why would we laugh at you?
Because of what I want to wear.
It's kind of different.
But that's exactly why we love you, Fred.
Because you're different
and not afraid to show it.
Come on.
Let's get you ready for the prom your way.
Snazzy!
[Fred] You think?
Take a look.
I look good.
And I feel good! Oh!
I feel like me.
That's what fashion's all about.
-[uplifting music playing]
-♪ When I was just a baby bison ♪
♪ I was always following the herd ♪
♪ Conformity was so enticin' ♪
♪ But something deep inside me
Knew that it was absurd ♪
♪ And now I see ♪
♪ The inner me ♪
♪ I'm steppin' out in my blue suit ♪
♪ I'm now the bison I want to be ♪
♪ I have a passion ♪
♪ For this latest fashion ♪
♪ Without a doubt I'm steppin' out ♪
♪ I feel like me! ♪
♪ Now that I chose ♪
♪ More stylin' clothes ♪
♪ I'm lettin' out what I held in ♪
♪ And now the real me truly shows ♪
♪ No more repressin' ♪
♪ No second-guessin' ♪
♪ Too long I've been keepin' it in ♪
♪ I feel like me ♪
♪ Yeah, these new threads
Are truly Fred's ♪
♪ I feel like me ♪
Yeah!
[song ends]
I think I'm ready to step out.
In style.
-I think you are too.
-Who wants to dance?
[Dudley groaning]
Not me. If you were wondering.
[whistling] Can I get a spotlight?
Oh, I do love a costume change.
That suit is amazing,
and so are you!
[giggling, snorting] I know.
Thanks, Mrs. Sanchez.
Now, who wants to see my signature moo-ve?
[cheering]
[disco music playing]
-Fred, promise me one thing.
-What's that?
Always do you, 'cause you're pretty cool.
I am, aren't I?
You ready to be my dance partner?
I gue-- Whoa!
Ooh! Oh! Woo!
-[disco music playing]
-[laughing]
[whimsical music playing]
[Ridley] Dude, Where's Our Egg?
[Dudley] Follow the soothing sound
of my voice.
Dudley, are you sure
we can't open our eyes yet?
No, that'll ruin the surprise.
We're walking, we're walking…
-[crashing]
-Uh-oh. Hope that wasn't valuable.
Uh, we're in a museum.
Everything is valuable.
I think it's a little dangerous
to have us flying blind, sunshine.
And we're here.
Open your eyes for a big surprise!
[Ismat] Ooh, sand.
Not like I have a ton of that
at home or anything.
Well, without sand, we can't have
our very own Eyes of the Museum Beach Day.
Dun-dun-da-dah!
So, it's not at the beach
or during the day?
-[yelping] Whoa!
-[crashing]
Dudley, we have a real beach upstairs
in the marine biology wing. Remember?
[groaning] I know. But I wanted to
pick a spot close to home…
[sadly] …since you've
all been so busy lately.
[Ismat] Uh-oh. Sad dodo eyes.
Don't look directly at them.
You know, that's true.
No one came to see me
turn the music exhibit into a skate park.
We definitely heard it.
I think a rotunda beach day
sounds like a great idea. How 'bout it?
Um, I wish I could, but I have to do
some spring cleaning with my dads.
And it's not easy watching my subjects
try to get sand out of Egyptian cotton.
Next time for sure, though!
[Dudley sighing]
Sorry.
I've got stomp practice
with the herd all night.
And I'm hosting this month's meetin'
of The Sisterhood of Museum Pilots.
Amelia Earhart begged me to bring
my award-winnin' banana bread.
Don't worry. We can still have
a fun beach day just the three of-- Oh no!
I forgot. I have protector training
with Mom and Grandma.
And tonight's part three
of Booby-Trap Protocol:
Poison darts to rolling boulders.
We'll hang out soon, I promise. Okay?
-[sadly] Yeah, okay.
-Go do you.
Why let a perfectly good beach… uh,
sludge day go to waste? [chuckling sadly]
-Wanna make sand angels?
-Sure.
-[Dudley sighing] Woo.
-Like, yay.
-Oh.
-Huh?
-Whoa.
-[Dante] It's an egg!
-Did you, uh, do that?
-Dude!
Right, right, of course.
This must be someone else's, but who?
Sorry to interrupt your training,
R-dogette,
but this seemed like an emergency.
No, I'm glad you came and got me,
but I've no idea who this egg belongs to.
What we need
is the help of a real eggs-pert.
I know, but the egg joke
was just laying right there.
I see what I did there. Come on.
Hm, well, it's not a penguin egg,
that's for sure.
It must be a hawk egg.
-No, an eagle. Eagle!
-Hawk.
-You don't know what you're squawking--
-I know what it is!
-Dragon egg!
-[Ridley chuckling]
I don't know about that, Pedro,
but I guess it could be
any other type of egg.
So it could be a bird, like me?
Or a tiny little dino dude, like me?
Maybe, and--
Oh! It's an ostrich egg.
You've gotta be yolking.
[yelping]
Oh no!
Whew!
Okay, until we know where this goes,
it'll be safest
if it stays in the rotunda.
No matter what kind of egg it is,
it's fragile and needs to be protected.
Can I count on you to take care of it
while I go to the museum records
to do some research?
-Dude, of course.
-It'll be over easy.
Thanks for your help.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I'll get blankets to make sure
the little one is warm and toasty.
Me too.
Just think,
if that egg hatches and it's a bird…
And it's a dinosaur…
[both] …I'll have my very own
little bro to play with.
[whimsical music playing]
♪ No other pair could be so Jurassic ♪
♪ There on our boards, little dude and I ♪
♪ Our flying lessons will all be classic ♪
♪ As soon as I learn to fly ♪
♪ No longer alone with my sibling in tow ♪
♪ Hangin' with my little bro ♪
♪ Picture us there
In our matching plumage ♪
♪ Using the fan for its flight effects ♪
♪ We skate around at full dino zoomage ♪
♪ A mini-me-saurus rex ♪
♪ The brink of extinction
I'll no longer know ♪
♪ Hanging with my little bro ♪
[both] ♪ Together forever wherever we go ♪
[song ends]
Oh, um…
Well, this is awkward.
You see, I was gonna put the egg
in the dodo exhibit, with me.
What? No way, Dudders.
This egg is gonna love
the open-air plan of the rotunda.
You know, where I live.
What? Dante, Dante, Dante.
[chuckling] Babies are
a huge responsibility.
Why don't I just take this off your hands,
and you can go work on
one of your prehistoric coloring books.
You mean my cave painting?
That does sound relaxing and, uh…
Hey, wait a minute. You're just trying
to get the egg for yourself.
Oh, it's true, it's true.
Dante, I'm sorry. I can't lie to you,
mostly because I'm not very good at it.
[sadly] It's just that
I've been feeling so lonely lately.
Oh, I see the sad dodo eyes.
No fair, dude.
I just wanna take care of the egg
and be a big bro to what hatches.
Well, I feel the same way.
I wanna teach the possible baby dino
ollies and kickflips and…
Whoa! [grunting]
[Dudley yelping]
Okay, ignore that one.
Just the rest of the tricks.
There's only one way to settle this.
A bro-off!
The one who can be
the best big brother is the winner.
We've got some babyproofing over here,
some babyproofing over here,
and egg-cellent!
The sharp corners and edges are now
softer than a brontosaurus's belly.
Yeah, that's all well and good,
but how are you gonna get out?
Oh no!
I made this place Dante-proof too!
Help!
Okay, little Dudley Junior,
are you ready for takeoff?
[gasping] It's working.
[Dante] Whoa!
It worked.
Oh, I've always wanted to pass on
all my flying knowledge.
[sniffling] You're flying.
Ooh, you're flying!
[gasping] Wait, you're flying and I can't.
Agh! Come down!
[panting]
-[Dante] I got it!
-Oh!
[grunting, chuckling]
Okay, I think we know who won the bro-off.
Yours truly.
What? W-with that baby-proofing prison?
No way! Hmph.
The only way to go-go is the dodo.
Dude, I don't think the egg
needs frequent flier miles.
[both grunting]
[giggling]
Hey, check this thing out.
It's the perfect shape, isn't it?
Crikey! It looks just like a rugby ball.
-Keep away!
-[giggling]
Finders lemurs!
[grunting]
[giggling]
Little rascals, time for dinner.
Ooh! Dinner! Yay!
I made a mobile out of cute dodo plushies.
What little guy
wouldn't wanna sleep under that?
Well, I was about to start
to learn how to cook.
I was gonna start with toast,
but gotta be honest, it seems super hard.
Maybe we should just let the egg decide
and see which of us it rolls to.
-Wait, where'd it go?
-Huh?
[Dudley screaming]
-How'd it get up there?
-Dudley, Dante!
So, I did a ton of research
in the museum records,
and I figured out that--
What's wrong?
And where's the egg?
[Dante] Well, um…
We let it out of our sight, and now it's
stuck up there in the treetop! [sobbing]
[confused] In the treetop?
Okay, what happened?
I don't know. We just walked away from it
for a minute or two
because, you know, bro-off.
And then it was gone.
We're so sorry, Ridley.
Please just save Dudley Junior.
Or Dante Junior. It doesn't matter
what we call the little guy.
We just need him to be safe.
It's gonna be all right.
I know that tree like the back of my whip.
Remember?
[grunting]
[groaning] I can't bear to look.
What if the egg falls?
[gasping] Wait, I got it.
But we'll have to work together, lil' bro.
Sorry, Dante. I was so caught up
in who should take care of the egg,
I forgot the most important part:
Just take care of it!
[grunting]
Couldn't've said it better myself.
Now, pull!
If Dudley Junior falls,
we'll be the ones to catch him.
[sighing]
Made it! Come on.
Closer.
-Just a little closer.
-[branch creaking]
No! [grunting]
-Dude! Ridley!
-[Dudley gasping]
-Eggy!
-We've got you!
[Ridley grunting]
You guys saved me! And the egg!
-You're all right!
-We were so worried!
-[cracking]
-[Dante] Uh-oh.
-[Dante] The egg's got a crack in it.
-No way. It was fine when we landed.
Unless it's hatching!
-Is it a bird?
-A dinosaur?
Whoa!
My research was right. A turtle!
A baby girl sea turtle.
Our little bro is a broette?
Aw! Her flippers look like my wings.
And her scales look like my scales.
We're both big bros after all.
[turtle] Mama?
[chuckling] Well, now that we know
what's inside the egg,
we can finally reunite her
with her family.
Yeah, and as the last of my kind,
I can definitely appreciate that.
For sure.
Can I trust you two
to take this little lady
back home to the marine biology wing?
I've got some important
museum protector stuff to do.
-Dude, yes, dude!
-Uh-huh!
Make sure to look both ways
before you cross the ocean.
Catch some gnarly waves for me.
[emotional music playing]
Look at us, we're empty nesters.
[sniffling] They grow up so fast,
don't they?
You know, I just realized something.
Since you and I are each other's big bro,
we'll never be alone,
no matter how busy everyone else gets.
-We're never too busy for you.
-Hey, there!
-Beach day!
-Hi, y'all!
Ridley! Everyone!
So, this was your important
museum protector stuff, huh?
I figured we owed you a beach day.
But you'll always have us too.
Remember? Busy or not.
-Last one in the water's a rotten banana!
-Woo-hoo!
-Tubular!
-This is so fun!
[cheering and laughing]
[Ismat] No splashing!
[closing theme music playing]
[child] No, no! Okay.