[opening theme music playing]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge could get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] A Stamp for Mama.
[rumbling]
Agh! I'm about to be moonstruck!
-[crashing]
-[Dudley yelping]
Wha--
I gotcha, Dudley!
Uh-oh.
[caribou yelping]
[Fred] Time to moo-ve it, folks.
[Ismat] By royal decree,
I demand that you run!
I may have landed on the moon, but I sure
don't want this moon landin' on me!
Yeehaw!
-Doop-de-doop--
-Pedro!
[Pedro] Whee!
[rumbling, crashing]
-[all gasping]
-[Dante] Ooh! Ooh!
Did I get it? Did I hit the piñata?
You hit the moon!
And it made a meteoric mess!
Huh? Dude!
I was wondering
what all that gnarly noise was.
Nice work out there, Ridley.
We saw the whole thing.
Yes, we did.
You almost got smushed back there.
You need to be more careful, sweetheart.
I am careful, Mama. I promise.
You're also one stamp closer
to getting your Compass Eye.
Passport, please.
[mystical twinkling]
[gasps] No way!
I only have one page left to fill!
Wait, what?
You can't be ready for your compass yet.
I haven't seen such a natural protector
since, well, you.
Which is why I think it's time
for her to see what's in this box.
Ooh, what is it?
Ninja stars? The Holy Grail?
-Cheeseburgers?
-Oof!
-[Dudley] A little help, here?
-Oh, man. Sorry, Dudely.
No ninja stars or cheeseburgers in here.
Just a dodo
and things that belonged to your mom and I
when we were young protectors like you.
That pickaxe got me out of lots
of sticky situations back in the day.
Can I have it, Mama? Please?
Sure. I guess
I don't have much use for it now.
Wait a second.
-Is this--
-My old passport.
Wow! I haven't seen that in a long time.
It's just like mine, except… [sneezing]
…dustier. Whoa!
Look at all these stamps.
You must have gone
on a lot of awesome adventures, huh?
-Affirmative.
-Totally!
-Of course!
-You bet we did.
-[Ridley] Is that you?
-Yep, I was your age in that photo.
Your mama was the greatest protector
this museum has ever seen.
She was fearless!
Are you sure we're talking about
the same Mama?
She's always afraid of me getting hurt.
Ah, yeah, I heard that.
She was a very brave little archaeologist.
Even had this cute little thing
she'd say during adventures.
[together] Time to rock it up a notch!
[laughs] That was a long time ago.
I don't recognize that stamp.
What'd you get it for?
Let's see.
Oh! Oh, for fixing a rare artifact.
Now, that was a dangerous adventure.
We were exploring
the ancient Aztec ruins--
[gasps] The stamp! It disappeared!
What?
-[mystical twinkling]
-[gasps]
-Oh my!
-The compass!
What happened?
I've never seen a Compass Eye
disappear before.
How do we get it back?
Something must've happened
in the Aztec exhibit.
-I'll go check it out.
-A mother-daughter museum mission?
Oh, this is gonna be
the most awesome night ever!
I'm sorry, Ridley,
this is a solo Mama mission.
It's too dangerous.
What? Come on,
I can handle a bit of danger.
My middle name's practically danger!
Huh. I always thought it was Sarah.
Ridley is only a couple of steps away
from getting her own compass.
[sighs] Okay. But you need to be
really careful and do everything I say.
Yes, Mama! Thanks, Mama!
I won't let you down.
[adventurous music playing]
[blows]
Well, how do I look?
Like the most adventurous mom ever!
But I think you're missing something.
I've never been down here before.
What is this place?
It's where we keep
the old, retired exhibits
that are no longer safe enough
to be upstairs.
Yeah, like the black hole exhibit.
-That'll suck you right out to space.
-Cool!
I lost way too many bananas to that thing.
I'll never forget you, my banana comrades.
-Whoa!
-[Peaches] Sweet biscuits and gravy!
-That's a moon-sized crater, all right!
-The ruins are old and fragile.
A hit like that could've damaged
a lot of things in there,
including the artifact I fixed.
That's why your stamp must've disappeared.
Which means
I need to fix the artifact again.
Come on, everyone. Stay close.
[Mama grunts]
Your mummy
has some royally awesome adventure skills.
Wait till you see.
My mom? No way.
[Dudley] Snakes!
Why'd it have to be snakes?
They got me. Oh, they got me!
Save yourselves!
[dramatic wailing]
Oh. [chuckling]
I gotcha, Dudely.
[grunting] Thanks.
And, um, let's not mention this
ever again, especially to the eagles.
-I have a reputation to uphold.
-I swear on my scales.
[screeching, flapping]
[all yelping]
[Dudley] Now, those definitely
aren't vines! They're--
-Tiny pterodactyls?
-[squawking]
Aw, come here, you cuties.
Wait, those aren't pterodactyls.
They're bats!
[yelping]
Everyone stay calm.
-I can figure this out.
-Don't move, Ridley, I've got this.
[grunting]
[bats screeching]
Fly away, you scaredy-cats!
-That was awesome!
-Thanks, sweetie.
Guess I still got it, huh?
Come on, we're almost there.
Is the artifact through that door?
Uh-huh. And behind a dangerous booby-trap.
Getting past it is going to be difficult.
Pssh! That booby-trap's got nothing
on us Jones gals!
-Ridley!
-[gasping] Oh!
-[rocks rumbling]
-Ridley!
-Watch out!
-Oh no!
Nobody move!
-I gotta go it alone from here.
-But Mama, I can help.
No, Ridley. This is way more dangerous
than what you're used to.
Ugh! Why doesn't she believe I'm ready
for dangerous adventures like this?
-I can do anything she can do.
-Love the confidence!
But, uh, I don't think
I've ever seen you do that.
[grunting]
[adventurous music playing]
-Whoa!
-Those are some seriously bisonic moves!
I gotta step up my game. [panting]
-Whoa! [grunting]
-[crashing, rumbling]
Those are harder than they look.
And so is this wall.
-Ow.
-[rocks rumbling]
-[gasping]
-Uh-oh.
Take cover!
Mom!
[dramatic music playing]
I can't just stay here while Mom
is out there alone. I gotta help her.
Whoa! Falling rocks! And more falling.
-[grunting]
-[Ridley] Mama!
-Ridley!
-[Ridley] I got you!
[rocks crashing]
Whoa! That was so epic! The ceiling
was like, kssh! Then, we were like, whoa!
And the rocks were like, boom, boom, boom…
You promised you'd do everything I said,
Ridley, but you didn't.
-You could've gotten hurt.
-I'm sorry.
I just wanted to help you. And I did. See?
We made it safely to the… Uh-oh.
The door to the artifact room.
It's completely covered.
This isn't good. [sighing]
-What are we gonna do?
-I don't know. I need to think.
Wait, look.
There's a hole in the rocks.
I think I can fit.
I can crawl through and fix the artifact.
Nope, no way. The booby-trap in there
is way too dangerous.
I'm ready for dangerous adventures, Mama.
I know I am. Why don't you believe me?
[groaning] Ridley.
[emotional music playing]
♪ Although I have an obligation ♪
♪ Protect these treasures
Great and small ♪
♪ Beyond the tests and exploration ♪
♪ There lies an even greater call ♪
♪ My finest feat
Is my crusade as Ridley's mother ♪
♪ That much, my dear, is always true ♪
♪ I have a task
More meaningful than any other ♪
♪ My greatest quest is you ♪
♪ I see you off on each new endeavor ♪
♪ And I'm scared to the bone ♪
♪ Though I know
You're so brave and clever ♪
♪ Still, I'm stunned
By how strong you've grown ♪
♪ I watch you run
Through pyramids and ancient rubble ♪
♪ Ridley, it's hard for me to do ♪
♪ But I've got to trust
You'll overcome all sorts of trouble ♪
♪ My greatest quest is you ♪
[song ends]
I'm sorry, Ridley, I've faced
a lot of scary stuff over the years,
but none of that is as scary
as seeing you in danger.
But--
But I know you're ready.
Wait, really?
Really. So, what do you say?
-You ready to rock it up a notch?
-You know it. Thank you, Mama!
That's gotta be the artifact.
[rumbling]
Whoa!
That's some booby-trap.
Okay, just gotta do what Mama would do.
[grunting]
[grunting] Oh! Ha!
Yes!
Time to rock it up a notch.
[grunting, yelping]
[gasping] That was a close one.
And I'm up really high.
But I know I can do this.
Mama believes in me.
[adventurous music playing]
-[mystical twinkling]
-Woo-hoo!
Oh, thank goodness you're okay!
Okay? I'm more than okay, I'm great!
-No, awesome!
-And the artifact?
Good as new.
You did it! Oh, I am so proud of you!
We did it, Mama.
Here. I don't think you're ready
to give this up just yet.
Looks like it was a successful mission.
You know what that means.
Passports, please.
Oh, right.
I think this is my favorite stamp ever.
-Me too.
-[mystical twinkling]
[gasping] Your compass, Mama.
[Dante] Tubular!
-Goodness gracious!
-Royal!
You know, I think you're just about ready
for one of these.
Only because I learned
from the best protector ever.
And the best mom ever.
Say cheese-asaurus!
-[both] Cheese-asaurus!
-[camera clicks]
[whimsical music]
[Ridley] Fred Steps Up.
-[girl] This way!
-[panting] Karen, wait up!
This game's called Follow the Leader,
not Get Left in the Dust.
Now, do a bison stomp.
[hooves clipping]
Now, shake your tails and do a spin.
My turn! Gotta do as much
Follow the Leader practice as I can.
[scoffing] Why?
Because I'm gonna lead
the entire bison herd one day.
-[laughing] You?
-Lead the herd?
Yup. I can't wait to take y'all
stampeding across the plains,
running toward the horizon.
It's my destiny.
[laughing]
I doubt it! [chuckling]
What's so funny?
No one as small and--
-What's the word I'm looking for, Chad?
-Adorable.
That's it! No one as small and adorable
as you could ever lead a bison herd.
You should probably find a new destiny.
One that's more your size.
-Come on, Chad.
-[giggling]
-[Chad] Lead the herd?
-[laughing]
[pensive music playing]
Do I really not have what it takes
to lead the herd?
[emotional music playing]
♪ I always thought
I was a bison who was born to lead ♪
♪ That I was meant to run out front
And head the whole stampede ♪
♪ My wildest dream was that the team
Was hanging on my every word ♪
♪ I wanna lead the herd ♪
♪ I always thought
I knew exactly what my purpose was ♪
♪ That I had what it takes
To do the things a leader does ♪
♪ All of the hustle and the muscle ♪
♪ No, I wouldn't be deterred ♪
♪ I wanna lead the herd ♪
♪ I always thought
That I was brave and strong ♪
♪ I've been so sure of that
My whole life long ♪
♪ What if I was wrong? ♪
♪ What is the use in introducing dreams
If they just get deferred? ♪
♪ Will I ever lead the herd? ♪
[song ends]
Fred, this is a code red museum mayday.
-Peabody's coming!
-[gasping]
Hi, Mama. Hi, Mr. Peabody…
Um, is that a butterfly on your head?
Indeed, it is, Miss Jones.
This is me getting into the,
uh, spirit of things. [chuckling]
Today is the one day of the year
where the flowers
in the pollination exhibit bloom.
Guests come from all over,
so I'll make a fortune
selling all this flower
and butterfly merchandise! [laughing]
I mean, uh,
I'm going to make many children happy.
It really is a beautiful sight!
Yeah, the butterflies
must love it in there,
or they would
if they were real, that is. [chuckling]
Good thing they're not, because I need you
to move them into the exhibit.
-Now. Step to it, Joneses.
-Okay.
I better check the exhibit and make sure
the flowers have plenty of sunlight.
Why don't you go see the butterflies off?
Sure thing, Mama. One kaleidoscope
of butterflies, coming right up.
-[Dudley grunting]
-Ha!
-Hey, guys.
-'Sup, dudette?
[sadly] Hi.
You okay, Fred?
You seem lower than the gravity on Mars.
Am I too small and adorable
to lead the herd?
[chuckling] Of course not.
Take it from a queen,
rulers come in all shapes and sizes.
The other bison don't seem to think so.
I know what'll cheer you up.
The butterflies
are about to take their yearly flight
to the pollination exhibit.
Wanna see them off?
Stega-dacious idea!
What do you say, Fred?
Ah…
Let's go see some butterflies.
All right, butterflies,
time for your big trip.
-Ooh, yeah!
-Yay!
-The flowers!
-[Ridley] And you're off.
See you at the flowers!
-Fly like the wind!
-See ya!
[butterflies laughing]
Hey, what's this? It won't budge.
It's blocking our way!
The merch booth? Huh.
There's no way around this thing.
You'll have to go
to the exhibit another way.
-But we don't know another way.
-We'll get lost.
-Sounds like you need a tour guide.
-Or a leader.
And I know just the one. Fred.
[snorting] Oh, I don't know.
I'm not sure I've got the hide
or the horns to lead this herd.
Or any herd.
You won't have to do it alone.
We'll help you, Fred.
[uneasy] Uh, okay. I'll do it.
Peaches, can you go to the security room
and get the status of the flowers?
We have to get there
before they all bloom.
Mission accepted!
I'll get my peepers on the petals.
[Fred clears throat] Um…
Hi, everyone.
So, I've never been
a butterfly herd leader before.
-That's okay.
-We've never had a leader before.
So this'll be something new for everyone.
All you have to do
is follow me to the exhibit.
-Think you can do that?
-I hope so.
We'll try!
Pipin' hot monkey bread, Ridley.
The first flower's already startin'
to bloom, which means
Peabody'll be openin' the museum
any minute.
Thanks, Peaches. Ready, Fred?
I guess so.
All right, little flappers,
let's moo-ve out.
-[giggling] Little flappers!
-That means us.
[butterflies giggling]
Now we'll just take this hallway
over here. Got that?
Uh, nope, they don't got that.
[giggling] The colors!
Hey, uh, we don't have time for this.
-[giggling]
-I'm doing art!
We need to get these butterflies moo-vin'.
-What if--
-I know how!
These butterflies have an eye for color.
I love when fashion is the answer!
Cool! Wings!
I already have a pair,
but these are much more glittery!
The butterflies see butterfly wings,
maybe it'll be easier for them
to follow me.
I mean, you. Everyone, strut after me.
[butterflies] Oh, pretty!
I want wings too!
You already have wings.
-Oh!
-So beautiful!
We got them to stop painting,
but they're still distracted.
[groaning] Some leader I am.
Don't give up. We'll find a way
to get the butterflies back in the air.
[Dudley] Let me speak to them,
winged creature to winged creature.
Hey, butterflies!
I need you to line up for me.
Line up? Like, why?
So they can fly in formation.
That's what I would do
if I could actually fly.
You go here, and you over here, and--
Hey, hey, hey,
wings off your brother's antenna.
And, uh, there.
I don't know, Dudley.
The little flappers have a hard enough
time going in the same direction.
Flying in formation is kind of…
advanced, don't you think?
Nah. This couldn't be simpler.
Okay, butterflies, let's get some lift.
Higher. Higher.
Go thataway, butterflies.
No, the other thataway.
This thataway!
-Huh? Which way?
-Oh, I'm so confused!
Okay, I can see how
this might be confusing.
Hello there, little butterflies.
-Hi!
-[happy squealing]
Oh, your wings!
[giggling] They're tickling me!
Oh, I don't think that's such a good idea.
[Mrs. Sanchez sneezes loudly]
[butterflies squealing]
So, they finally leave the rotunda
and end up
in the tundra exhibit? [groaning]
We gotta get them out of there
before Mr. Peabody…
-[Peabody] Joneses?
-…notices that they're gone.
Quick, everyone, freeze.
I've just been to the pollination exhibit.
There isn't a single butterfly in there!
I'm workin' on it, Mr. P.
Well, work on it a little faster.
There are flowers blooming,
and if the guests miss it,
there'll only be you
and your mother to blame.
Honestly, how hard can it be
to move a few butterflies?
Harder than you'd think, actually.
Okay, since we're in a royal time crunch,
I'll lead the butterfly rescue.
I have an idea too,
but we're gonna need a lot of skateboards.
The tundra's not a safe place,
especially for a bunch
of helpless butterflies.
But to save them, we need a good leader.
Know any?
-I used to think that I was one.
-You still are.
Stop letting everyone tell you how
to be a leader and just be Fred.
So, be small and adorable?
And brave and smart and fierce.
All the things that make you you.
Being myself. I haven't tried that yet.
I'll give it a shot.
-[all talking at once]
-[Fred whistling]
Listen up, everyone!
I wanna thank you for all your ideas
on how to herd the butterflies,
but we just need one of us in charge.
And I'm steppin' up to do it.
Woo-hoo!
That's the take-charge Fred I know.
[Fred] Hm, the wind's picking up.
My bison sense says a storm's a-brewin'.
We need to find those butterflies fast!
Stampede after me!
[adventurous music playing]
-[butterflies squealing]
-There they are!
[butterfly] Fred!
We're saved!
Not yet, little flappers.
I need you to listen up.
A storm's about to hit,
but we can outrun it.
You only have to do one thing.
Keep your eyes on me.
-We can do one thing.
-It's true.
Now, let's moo-ve out!
-[butterflies cheering]
-Here we go!
-[butterfly] Fred, wait! Come back!
-[Fred gasping]
-[lightning crackling]
-Come on, little butterflies!
[gasping] We're almost there.
Woo-hoo!
Whoa! Check it out!
Fred's herding those butterflies
like a… like a boss!
-Hooray!
-Go, Fred!
Thanks, everyone.
Next stop, the pollination exhibit!
Well, try as I might, I can't find
a single thing to complain about.
Thanks, Mr. P. The little flappers,
I mean, the butterflies,
look beautiful with the flowers.
Check out that crowd. [gasping]
Maybe I should go sell some merch
to the guests in line! [chuckling]
Nice job today, Ridley. I've got
a little surprise for you. Come on.
For helping getting the butterflies
to the pollination exhibit,
you've earned a stamp.
[mystical twinkling]
You really stepped up today
when the butterflies needed you most.
But only 'cause you helped me see
that to be a great leader,
I just needed to be me.
So, what's your next move,
future herd leader?
[uplifting music]
♪ I've always known
There was a leader deep inside of me ♪
♪ I'll be myself ♪
♪ 'Cause that's the only thing
I need to be ♪
♪ Watch me succeeding as I'm leading
With my dreams all newly stirred ♪
♪ Yes, I'm gonna lead the herd! ♪
[song ends]
[closing theme music playing]
[child] No, no. Okay.