[opening theme music playing]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give into her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Compass Eye of the Storm.
[frog croaking]
[bats screeching]
[dramatic music playing]
[Fred] Don't look down!
[Dudley] That's really… [gulping] …deep!
-[Ridley] Let's go, team!
-[grunting]
[grunting]
[Dudley and Ridley grunting]
[yelping] Couldn't we have made sure
Pedro was lost in the ruins
before we risked life and wing?
Sorry, Dudley.
The Lemurson kids said they saw Pedro
chase his ball in here.
That's good enough for me.
Maybe he already got his ball,
went home to his favorite snuggly,
and is waiting to tell us all about it.
So, uh, we should go back--
Whoa! [yelping]
Dudley!
-[Ridley grunting]
-[Dudley gasping]
If anyone from the museum's in trouble,
I'm here to save them.
I like that motto.
We should get business cards.
[Pedro calling] Ridley! Help!
[Peaches] Any o' y'all afraid of the dark?
Don't worry.
There should be a torch somewhere.
-Aha! Here.
-Nice one, R Jones!
You know this place
like I know the back of my horns.
Well, I have been at this protector
training thing for a while now.
I've been at this constantly-in-danger
thing for a while now too,
but I'm still not used to it.
[Dudley] Oops!
-[rumbling]
-[gasping] I know that sound.
[rock thudding]
Everyone, run!
[Fred] Stampede for your lives!
[dramatic music playing]
-I see a light up ahead!
-Don't go towards it!
Oh, wait. No, in this case,
the light is good. Do go towards it!
Blast off, y'all!
-Is she gonna make it?
-Of course she is!
She's Ridley Jones!
Come hither, Ridley!
[grunting]
[rock thudding]
-[Ridley sighing]
-[cheering]
[Pedro] Hello?
Pedro!
-[gasping, cheering]
-[Ismat] There he is!
Ridley! I'm sorry my ball rolled inside,
so then I followed it,
but then I got lost.
Don't worry. We're coming to get you.
[quietly] Is it just me, or does this kid
get himself into danger every other week?
Shh!
-Yeah, he does.
-[Ridley] Let me handle this.
-[Pedro gasping] Wait.
-[rumbling]
-[gasping]
-[Peaches] Enemy fire!
[arrow twanging]
[Ridley] Okay, new plan.
That walkway is way too narrow.
There's no way I can dodge the arrows
once I'm standing on it.
[gasping] Ridley, not your hat.
-It's your signature look!
-[rumbling]
-[whooshing]
-[grunting, gasping]
-Whoa!
-[arrows whooshing]
-[whooshing]
-Whew.
-Mummazing!
-Yeah!
Are you and your ball ready to go home?
Yes, please.
Don't look back, okay?
-[arrows twanging]
-[gasping]
[dramatic music playing]
-Tubular!
-You did it!
[Pedro] Oh no!
Your hat is ruined.
Hats can always be stitched up.
I'm just glad you're safe.
Now, let's get out of here.
-[Mama] Welcome back, Eyes Team.
-Looks like that was one intense mission.
It was!
But Ridley was out-of-this-world brave!
She even, like, messed up
her bodacious hat to save Pedro.
Wow, that is big, but I'm not surprised.
I'm just glad you're safe.
It wasn't a humongous deal.
I was able to sew it up in the field. See?
Passport, please, Miss Ridley Jones.
[repeated stamping]
Huh?
For leading a ruins rescue mission,
sacrificing something,
and for expert hat repair,
you get three stamps.
-[Ridley gasping]
-Which means…
I filled out my whole passport!
-No way!
-Mummazing!
Congratulations, Ridley.
I-I can't believe it!
After all that work,
studying, adventuring,
I did it.
I did it! Ooh!
That'll be one Compass Eye, please.
-The thing is--
-We can't just give you a Compass Eye.
It's a mysterious artifact
that reveals itself to its protector
when it decides you're worthy.
When you've truly proven yourself,
your passport will be your guide.
-[Ridley sighing]
-Don't worry. I'm sure it'll happen soon.
Just keep on protecting the museum
like you have been.
Like the Jones women before you,
our Jones Compass Eyes
are all connected, you know.
[sighing] Okay,
I just have to wait a little longer.
Even though I feel so ready, already.
[inspirational music playing]
♪ Don't know how long I can wait
To finally realize my fate ♪
♪ 'Cause now the time is drawing near
My Compass Eye will appear ♪
♪ Yeah, it's practically here ♪
♪ I've been so patient 'til now
So, come on Eye, holy cow ♪
♪ I cannot take any more
What else are you waiting for? ♪
♪ 'Cause I know in my core
That I'm ready ♪
♪ Ready to carry the load ♪
♪ Yes, I'm ready
Let's get this show on the road ♪
♪ I've been patiently waiting ♪
♪ Through all of the tests
I've gone through ♪
♪ I have served and protected ♪
♪ So what else do I have to do? ♪
♪ How can I possibly
Prove myself to you? ♪
♪ Prove that I'm ready ♪
♪ I'm jumping out of my skin
'Cause I'm ready ♪
♪ Ready to finally begin ♪
♪ I'm ready ♪
♪ I know it deep in my heart
That I'm ready ♪
♪ For this adventure to start ♪
♪ I'm ready! ♪
[song ends]
[groaning] How long is this
Compass Eye stuff supposed to take?
I've been trying to prove myself
all this time and still nothing!
[Mama] I'm just worried.
Has it ever taken this much time
for a protector to get their Compass Eye?
Not that I know of.
It has been a long time, maybe too long.
[gasping] It's not possible that
Ridley could be the first Jones woman
not to become a protector?
[gasping] Me, not worthy of a Compass Eye?
No, I have to be.
[mystical twinkling]
I can't give up without a fight.
Hot grits and gravy, Ridley!
You finally got your Compass Eye!
Two of them!
A little overkill, if you ask me,
but hey, that's great.
No, they aren't mine.
-I borrowed these from Mama and Grandma.
-Uh, why?
Because the Jones Compass Eyes
are connected.
So, maybe there's a way
to use these two to find mine.
[gasping] Maybe, like, ask it for help.
Uh, worth a try.
Oh, wondrous Compass Eyes,
show me to…
my Compass Eye.
Ooh, I know!
Maybe you just need the right outfit.
Something that screams,
"Museum protector!"
Nah, don't even sweat it.
[grunting] I'll track it down.
[calling] Compass Eye, where are you?
Come out, come out and be--
Whoa! [grunting]
-[Ismat] Ooh.
-Dante!
[Dante] I'm okay.
[Dante chuckling] Whew.
I'm completely stumped.
Maybe, I'm just not cut out
to be a museum protector.
[Mr. Peabody] Lonny! I found your badge
in the cafeteria freezer again.
-You have to be more careful!
-Mr. Peabody and Lonny!
They're still here?
-Everyone, get to your exhibits.
-[Fred] Keep it moo-vin'!
-I could've sworn I heard mooing, again.
-You hear it too?
I think it's the fabled phantom cow
that chews its cud in the night.
Hello!
What's this? I've never seen
anything like these before.
They're beautiful.
So they must be worth a fortune.
[wicked laughing]
Come on!
That was your evilest chuckle yet, sir.
Hm.
Found my toolbox!
It was also in the freezer.
Nothin' like a set of cool tools.
Hm, I can't tell how valuable
these things are unless I open them and--
-[snapping]
-[Mr. Peabody yelping]
Gimme that!
-[clanging]
-[electrical crackling]
-Pierce! Pierce, look.
The portal to the tundra
is goin' all screwy.
-My bird, you're right!
-[electrical zapping]
-[clanging]
-[alarm blaring]
Zounds! Thy portal has gone all…
How do you say it?
Kablooey!
-[electrical crackling]
-[penguins yelping]
Not even a scratch.
Now I know I need to open these up.
What's inside must be really valuable.
Ooh, I know. Stand back!
-[Peabody gasping]
-[Lonny grunting]
[crackling, zapping]
[tense music playing]
What was that?
Warn me the next time
you go swinging a sword around.
This isn't working,
and it's getting pretty late.
Let's try again, first thing tomorrow.
[Lonny] Ooh, I'll bring my power drill.
And a breakfast burrito.
They're both in the freezer.
[crackling, zapping]
Uh, dude, did you, like, hear that?
-Uh-huh.
-[crackling]
[gasping] The exhibits!
Something's making them open and close,
and open and close, and open and--
-Uh, you get it.
-I do.
And it can't be good.
Are you guys okay?
Something weird is going on.
[Ma] Y'all better get to skedaddlin'!
The back wall to the Serengeti
opened on its own,
and a whole bunch of wild animals
are a-coming!
-[elephant trumpeting]
-[Fred] Whoa! Stampede!
Ridley! The entrance
to the Egyptian exhibit suddenly opened,
and a sandstorm
came blowing into the museum!
-[birds squawking]
-[Dante] Whoa!
Okay, team. We might not know
what's causing all these problems,
but it's up to us to keep everyone safe.
We should split up to cover more ground.
Eyes on three.
One, two…
[together] Eyes!
[elephant trumpeting]
Here we go.
Now reaching our destination:
the Serengeti.
-[elephant trumpeting]
-[twinkling]
[crackling]
Is that…
A snowflake?
-[wind blowing]
-[penguins yelping]
-Snowstorm?
-Like, indoors?
The Arctic exhibit portal
must be open too.
-That's where all the snow is coming from.
-We gotta close that door!
Hop on, D-bird.
Let's shred!
[Dante grunting] Whoo!
[crackling, zapping]
[chuckling] Dudley, you ready to fly?
Always! Wait, wha--
[Dudley yelping]
-[crashing]
-[Dudley grunting]
-[confused] We did it?
-Dude! Yes, dude!
Oh no! It's gotten worse.
[crackling]
Don't worry, my loyal subjects.
I command you to trust in me and Ridley.
[Ridley] Grab on!
-[Ridley grunting]
-[wind howling]
-[rope creaking]
-[Ridley grunting]
[grunting]
Okay, now I command all of us
to get out of here!
[Ridley] Run!
[wind howling]
[Ridley gasping]
-[sad music playing]
-[zebras barking]
[grandma gasping]
-Mama! Grandma!
-Ridley, I am so glad you're safe!
What's happening to all the exhibits?
Someone must've messed
with our Compass Eyes.
They control all the magic that opens
and closes the walls to the exhibits.
And both of our Compass Eyes are missing,
so we can't make it stop.
[gasping] The Compass Eyes?
-[zapping]
-Do you know what happened to them?
I… do.
I-I took them. I thought maybe
they could help me find my Compass Eye?
But then I got distracted
and lost track of them.
This is my fault.
No wonder my Compass Eye
doesn't think I'm worthy.
Hey, we're gonna find them.
But until we do,
we need to get everyone out
of their exhibits and into the rotunda.
If the back walls close for good
while someone is on the other side,
they'll be trapped
and never be able to return to the museum.
-Never?
-You hold down the fort here, all right?
Grandma and I will make sure
everyone gets out in time.
[nervously] Okay, y-you got it.
Everyone's confused and scared.
And by everyone, I mean me.
-Someone's gotta step up and be a leader.
-And calm everyone down.
I know just who that someone is.
[Ridley] Me?
[nervously] I don't think I'm…
Lady Ridley, pray tell,
what is going on in the museum?
-We had to grab the kids and flee.
-I'm scared!
Are we gonna be okely-dokely?
Well, see, we just have to…
Um…
I don't have any answers for you,
or a plan.
I'm just not what you need right now.
You need a museum protector
and that's just not me.
I'm sorry.
Eyes Team, I need you to take my place.
You can help Mama and Grandma,
the real protectors,
take care of the museum.
-Wait, but--
-Ridley, no!
I've made up my mind. Okay?
[emotional music playing]
♪ Well, I used to believe ♪
♪ I heard destiny's call ♪
♪ When the time came along ♪
♪ I'd be ready to go
Because I was brave and strong ♪
♪ But I guess I was wrong ♪
♪ They were counting on me ♪
♪ And I let them all down ♪
♪ Gave my very best shot ♪
♪ I felt ready to lead
But I know I'm clearly not ♪
♪ I cannot deny I'm not ready ♪
♪ Now I finally see ♪
♪ I'm not ready ♪
♪ No, the leader they need isn't me ♪
♪ And it won't ever be ♪
♪ I'm not ready ♪
[song ends]
[sadly] I'm on the sidelines,
where I belong.
I'm so not ready.
[Pedro calling] Somebody help me. Please?
[gasping] Oh no! Pedro!
-[wind howling]
-[crackling]
Ridley!
Over here!
[Ida yelling] Charge!
-Hey, Ida! Pedro needs help!
-No time, my lady.
Leading the butterflies
once more unto the breach!
Mr. Lemurson, can you help Pedro?
I've gotta get my kids to safety!
Sorry, Ridley.
Please? Someone!
Pedro needs to be rescued.
[Pedro] Help!
I-I don't know if I can do it.
[sighing] But of course I'll try.
Hold on, Pedro, I'm coming.
It's getting worse.
I'm gonna have to time my jump just right.
Whoa! Dudley, look out!
-[Dudley yelping]
-[grunting] Whoa!
-[crackling]
-[Ridley sighing]
Ridley, what are you doing?
If you go in there,
the back could close for good,
and you'd be trapped on the other side.
-Forever.
-I know.
But I can't just leave Pedro in there
all by himself.
You guys don't need me here.
You have two protectors,
my mother and my grandmother.
-They're the best.
-But so are you, Ridley.
Thanks, but I'm not a protector,
it turns out.
I don't have what it takes.
Huh?
If I don't make it back,
tell everyone I love them.
And I love you too.
I know you usually think of me
as the stoic type, but, uh…
[dramatically] …please, come back, Ridley!
I'd miss you too much!
I'll miss you too,
but I have to go now.
Come on, open. Open.
[whimpering] Can't watch. Oh!
-[yelling] Open!
-[zapping]
-[Ridley grunting]
-[wind blowing]
Ridley, over here!
Hold on, Pedro. I'm coming!
[Pedro calling] Ridley!
[grunting]
[gasping] Ridley, you came!
I did.
And seriously,
we gotta stop meeting like this.
I was scared.
It was noisy in the museum,
so I came here to hide.
I understand wanting to hide.
Then this big branch fell on me.
But now you're here.
I know you can just lasso it up
and get it off of me.
I don't have my rope.
[gasping] Or any of my gear.
[sighing] I didn't deserve it.
Ridley, you're gonna save me, right?
You better believe I am!
[crackling]
But I gotta do it soon
or we're gonna get stuck out here.
[Ridley grunting]
[grunting, groaning]
[sadly] You… you can't do it?
I haven't even begun to try.
[grunting]
Not heavy enough.
[gasping] I know!
[grunting]
[inspirational music playing]
[grunting] Come on, come on!
Here we go! [grunting]
I'm free, I'm free!
Thank you, Ridley Jones!
-[crackling]
-Oh no!
We're gonna get stuck in here.
I have to get you out!
[wind howling]
What do you mean, she went in there?
Why didn't you stop her?
I'm not as big and tough as you are, Fred.
Well, that's true. But still, this is bad.
The portal's already closed!
-[crackling]
-[Dudley] Oh!
Wait! There she is!
-Go with the flow, dude!
-Bring it in for landin'!
The flashing's getting worse.
I don't think we have much time
before it closes for good.
[grunting, sighing]
Pedro, tell my mama I love her.
Everyone else too.
But, Ridley, why don't you tell them…
[yelling] …yourself?
Whee!
-Whoa!
-[all yelling]
Oh, hey, Pedro.
[gasping] No, no, Ridley!
[Mama] No!
Mama!
-Ridley!
-[tense music playing]
[zapping]
Mom!
I know, baby.
There must be some magic
we don't know about yet.
We'll find it.
Someday.
Ridley told me to tell you
she loves you and she'll miss you.
-All of you.
-[Mama gasping]
[sadly] Ridley.
[sadly] Mama.
Dante, Dudley, Ismat, Peaches,
I'll miss you all.
But I did what I had to do.
[mystical twinkling]
A map?
[gasping] What is that?
[mystical twinkling]
[gasping]
[intriguing music playing]
[mystical twinkling]
Is it? [gasping]
It is!
[mystical twinkling]
My Compass Eye! My very own Compass Eye!
I am a protector!
Just like my mama
and my grandma before me.
[gasping] Mama.
[yelling] Mama!
[adventurous music playing]
Come on.
-[mystical twinkling]
-[clicking]
-[gasping]
-[twinkling]
[triumphant music playing]
-Mama!
-Ridley! Oh, Ridley!
-You're back!
-Dreams do come true!
Oh, Ridley!
The Jones women, together again!
The Jones women,
museum protectors, together again.
-Your Compass Eye! You found it!
-And it found you.
-[gasping]
-Wow!
-Ridley!
-I can't believe it!
After I got Pedro back safely,
a map appeared in my passport.
It showed me where to find my Compass Eye.
That was the ultimate act of selflessness.
The sign of a true protector.
Now, let's see
if we can reverse this curse.
[twinkling, zapping]
[triumphant music playing]
[Ismat] I bow down to your greatness!
Oh my! It's almost morning!
Mr. Peabody will be here any minute.
-And everyone's scattered.
-I got this.
But I'm gonna need--
Yeah, you are.
[clicking, twinkling]
Back where it belongs.
Now, you're just missing one thing.
-Ridley, this is yours.
-It is.
Thank you, guys, for keeping these safe.
Everyone, listen.
Mr. Peabody is on his way. We need you all
to get back to your exhibits, quickly!
-[zebras barking]
-[elephant trumpeting]
-[mystical twinkling]
-My compass!
[muttering] My job is always,
"Do this, do that."
-[twinkling]
-That glow!
I think I know where the other two are.
Oh! What are you Joneses doing here?
We live here!
We're missing two artifacts. You haven't
seen them, have you, Mr. Peabody?
[Peabody groaning]
Fine! These are worthless anyway.
Couldn't even get the darn things open
to see what's inside.
Sometimes the power
is in the eye of the beholder.
[chuckling] It's only a matter of time
before I sell the whole museum anyway.
-Then I'll be rolling in dough.
-What did you say?
Uh, what? [hesitating]
No, I can't wait to, uh…
Uh, to roll in the, uh…
the snow!
See? [chuckling] Love to roll in the snow!
In recognition
of her extreme bravery and selflessness
in the face of personal danger,
we hereby declare Ridley Jones
an official protector of the museum!
I couldn't have done this without
my mother, my grandmother, and my friends.
I promise to protect and serve,
for as long as this museum is standing.
-I knew she was a natural.
-You were right.
[camera clicking]
[triumphant music playing]
-Juras-sick!
-[cheering]
Our little Ridley, all grown up.
-[twinkling]
-[upbeat music playing]
♪ I'm ready! ♪
[closing theme music playing]