[opening theme music playing]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge could get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[twinkling]
[Ridley] Northern Lights.
[groaning]
[Dudley] So much snow.
What's wrong? Don't you like snow?
Oh, sure. But when it's this snowy,
hardly anybody visits the museum.
It's like, no funners
when there's no kiddos to entertain.
And if the snow gets bad enough,
a really terrible thing happens.
-What really terrible thing?
-[doors open]
Snow day! Mr. Peabody closed the museum.
That really terrible thing.
[sadly] I was looking forward
to seeing all the visiting kids.
Ooh! I got these sporks
to put in my feathers,
so I can be a space alien! [chuckling]
[imitates alien] Borkle, gorgle, neee.
-Dudley, you know I can't let you do that.
-[groaning]
Kids would think
dodos came from outer space.
What does it matter? There's no kids
coming today anyway. I'm calling it.
-Today is officially a bummer.
-[Dante] Dude.
-[murmurs of agreement]
-Well, not for me.
Snow days are a chance to bust out
the museum's X-57 Snow Slayer,
the most high-voltage snowplow
money can buy.
[imitating snowplow] Brrrrm!
You sure you're gonna be okay
out there in the cold?
Oh, don't worry about me, sweetness.
I used to go out
in the Arctic exhibit with an old friend.
We'd brave the cold
and watch the Northern Lights together.
Uh, Grandma?
Oh, right!
Initiate granny plow mode.
Brrrm!
-Catch, Ridley! In case you need it.
-Thanks, Grandma!
I can already feel the power
of the bummer day
glooping all over me like wet glue!
I reject the power of the bummer!
Bundle up, everyone.
You can't fight a bummer day.
It's all-powerful.
The museum might be closed,
but we can still have an un-bummer day.
[mystical twinkling]
Grandma used to go on Arctic adventures,
and so can we.
With these trays
that I borrowed from the cafeteria,
we will officially conquer
any bummer day bummer-osity!
-[adventurous music playing]
-Woo-hoo!
-[Pedro giggling]
-[Dante cheering]
[Dante] Look at her shredding the gnar!
-Woo-hoo!
-Yeah!
[laughing]
And that's how you beat the bummers.
Right behind you, bummer shredder girl!
Call me a flip-asaurus!
Woo!
[Dante chuckling]
[Pa] Yeehaw!
Last one down is a cowpie!
[Ma] Catch ya at the bottom,
you slowpoke cowpokes!
[Pa] Yahoo!
[Ismat squealing]
Can someone let me know
if I'm goin' in the right direction!
-Gotcha.
-[giggling]
Ooh! Sh-sh. Ooh!
[laughing]
For the glory of the realm!
-[crashing]
-[Ida yelping]
-[Ida grunting]
-[Ismat] Ida!
[gasping]
Are you okay?
I am fine.
Indeed, my armor didst protect me.
You ready to boogie the bummers bye-bye?
I don't know.
Maybe you should, uh, go on without me.
No way, friend.
How 'bout we go together, side by side?
[gulping, nervous laughing]
Go, go, dodo!
[Dudley whimpering]
This is a one-way ride
to total dodo extinction!
[Dudley yelping]
[both squealing]
-[both grunting]
-[Dudley] Ouch.
[wind blowing]
Fred! Dudley!
-[groaning] We're okay.
-Do you see now, Ridley?
See what?
See what? See what?
The power of the bummer day
made us crash, that's what.
Wait, what's that over there?
[intriguing music playing]
-[ice squeaking]
-There's something inside the ice.
[gasping] It's a woolly mammoth!
I thought they went extinct?
-The best of us do.
-True dat.
They did go extinct,
about 4,000 years ago.
This could be a big discovery!
We need to get it back to the museum.
I think we can all agree
that this is a job for Fred.
[Fred groaning]
[grunting, heaving]
This is so cool!
See, your bummer day
is turning into an awesome
find-a-previously-thought-
to-be-extinct-animal day.
I can't seem to move it,
which can only mean it is immovable.
[grunting]
I'm not giving up.
I hope your penguin family's up
for an adventure, Pedro,
'cause I have a plan.
Toodly-doo! A penguin adventure!
[Ridley] On Flipper! On Flapper!
On Pedro and Fred!
We'll have this mammoth
back to the museum in no time!
[Ma] Get along, little mammoth.
The mammoth should unfreeze pretty fast
next to Dante's volcano.
Ooh, but it would be a bummer
if Mr. Peabody came back before it thawed.
-You're right, Dudley.
-I am? Are you sure?
Uh-huh. But I've got an idea
to help things thaw along faster.
[whimsical music playing]
That should speed things up a little.
[robotic drilling]
Or a lot.
[panicking] Huh? W-where am I?
Don't worry.
You're safe here in the museum.
Museum? [gasping]
This can't be my museum.
Everything looks all wrong!
[gasping]
[trumpeting]
[groaning]
[trumpeting, rapid breathing]
Oh, I gotta…
I gotta get out of here! [panting]
He said, "My museum."
He must be a museum exhibit mammoth.
Have any of you ever seen him before?
-Hm.
-Not me.
Mammoth dude must've been before my time.
How long has he been frozen?
-[crashing]
-[trumpeting]
I don't know,
but he looks confused and scared.
We have to stop him
before he hurts himself.
-Let's do this!
-Mummazing!
Halt thy advance, you shaggy brute!
I have no quarrel with thee-- Whoa!
-[Ida grunting]
-You still in there, knightly dudette?
Ah! My armor didst protect me.
[squealing] Stop, mammoth!
Your queen commands you!
-[Peaches chittering]
-[bleeping]
-Whoa!
-[jetpack whooshing]
Woo! Come on!
[Peaches grunting]
[mammoth gasping, trumpeting]
Thanks, Peaches.
Are we really worried about
him hurtin' himself?
It's more like he's gonna hurt us.
Whoa! Oh! Wh-wh-whoa!
[penguins yelping]
-[squealing]
-Oh no! No, no!
-[penguins squealing]
-[musical notes playing]
[trumpeting, rapid breathing]
[breathing slows]
-[Pedro] Whee!
-Pedro!
-[Pedro] Agh!
-[grunting] Gotcha!
[mammoth grunting]
Stay up here. You'll be safe.
-This should slow you down.
-[mammoth groaning]
Well, this is a bummer.
-[rope cracking]
-[Dudley yelping]
[gasping] Thanks, Ridley.
[panicked trumpeting]
[crashing]
This day does feel like a bummer.
Maybe trying to turn a bummer day
into a good day
just made a bad day into a worse day.
Ridley, you can't give up!
Giving up is my thing.
You never give up,
even if it means you might get
trampled flat by a shaggy elephant thing.
[inspirational music playing]
♪ Sure, days can be a bummer ♪
♪ Ooh, like one time in the summer ♪
♪ The spitting camels spat upon my food ♪
♪ Or when my habitation ♪
♪ Is closed for renovation ♪
♪ But you're the one
Who taught me not to brood ♪
♪ I feel so heavy-hearted ♪
♪ When guests have all departed ♪
♪ Or I spill my drink
On Ismat's favorite gown ♪
♪ But there's a little saying ♪
♪ That keeps me from dismaying ♪
♪ Oh, you can't let a bummer
Get you down ♪
♪ The day that I met you, kid ♪
♪ Had started out so blue, kid ♪
♪ But you helped me to overturn my frown ♪
♪ Yes, if a day seems gloomy ♪
♪ All Tutankhamun's tomb-y ♪
♪ Oh, you can't let a bummer
Get you down ♪
♪ No, you can't let a bummer
-[song ends]
-[Dudley gasping]
You're right.
I am? Are you sure?
It's my job to protect the museum,
whether it's from bummer days
or shaggy elephant things.
And that means no giving up, ever.
Wait! Ridley!
I said don't give up,
not volunteer to be smushified!
-Stop! Stop!
-[trumpeting]
-Uh, Mr. Mammoth, please stop.
-[mammoth panting]
-Whoo!
-That was royal!
Hi. I know you must be
really scared and confused,
but the museum
is a safe and wonderful place.
We'll do everything we can
to make you feel welcome. I promise.
You look so familiar.
Oh-ho-ho, I'm sorry
I went a bit shaggy-brained back there.
It's okay. I'm sure waking up
in a strange place
after being frozen in ice
can be pretty weird.
It's mostly because the museum
is so different from what I remember.
[gasping] Nukelik, is that you?
That's my name,
but who are you?
It's me, Sylvia.
S-Sylvia?
[gasping] Sylvia Jones?
Come here, you big muffle monster.
[sighing] You've gotten older.
[chuckling] You've been gone a long time.
Grandma, what's going on?
Back when I was your age,
Nukelik was my best friend
here at the museum.
I called him Nukie.
[both chuckling]
[grandma] Oh-ho-ho!
I helped you gather
most of the stamps in your passport.
We always used to sneak off
through the Arctic exhibit
and watch the Northern Lights together.
But one day, I went out alone.
I fell asleep
and froze into a block of ice.
I searched and searched,
but I never found you.
-[Nukelik] Until now.
-Until now.
Your grandma didn't give up.
No, she's a Jones.
And we don't give up, bummer day or not.
Hi, Nukie, I'm Ridley Jones,
Sylvia's granddaughter.
[Nukelik] Oh-ho-ho!
That's why you look so familiar.
Ah, pleased to meet you, Ridley.
I saw your moves out there. Can see
you got a lot of your grandma in you.
That's as good a compliment
as I could ever get!
I'll introduce you around.
Hopefully, you'll want this
to be your home again.
But for right now, what do you say
we go out and watch the Northern Lights,
just like old times?
[chuckling] I say…
[loud trumpeting]
[grandma] Wow.
So beautiful.
Just like I remember.
[Nukelik sighing]
This brings back memories.
-[all gasping]
-[Peaches] Beautiful!
Thanks for reminding me
not to give up. You were right.
-Hm, are you sure?
-[chuckling] I'm sure.
You know, I have to admit,
today turned out to be
a not bummer day after all.
In fact, it turned out to be pretty great.
[Nukelik trumpeting]
[whimsical music playing]
[Ridley] Slow Place Like Home.
[Lonny grunting]
-Hey, Lonny.
-[yelping]
-What are you working on?
-Oh, Ridley!
Hey, just fixin' a pipe
that's been drippin' all year
and drivin' me bananas.
Which is funny because the other thing
that drives me bananas
is all the banana peels
I find in this place.
Banana peels.
Weird. Need some help?
No, thanks, I'm almost done.
Actually, uh,
I'm kind of the pipe whisperer.
Observe.
[grunting]
[chuckling]
See? Lonny one, leaks zero.
-[rumbling, clanging]
-Do you hear something?
-[water hissing]
-Oh!
Lonny zero,
leaks a hundred!
Ridley, stay calm. I'm gonna run
and grab a replacement thingamajiggy,
so I can shut off the water.
-[Lonny groaning]
-Uh-oh.
-[sloth groaning]
-[slowly] Run.
What does run mean again?
That's not good.
-[laughing]
-Eyes Team, assemble!
[all] Huh?
We've gotta save some sloths!
-Let's do this!
-Let's take 'em.
[adventurous music playing]
[Dudley grunting]
[grunting]
[jetpack whooshes]
[Ismat grunting]
Whew, that's all the sloths.
Now we just gotta stop this flooding
before it messes up anything else.
You got it, Ridley.
But what do we do about them?
-[slowly] Run with me.
-Which way do I go?
[sloths groaning]
We gotta round up these critters
before Lonny sees them.
[Ma] Did someone say
round up these critters?
[Pa] Ooh-wee!
Roundin' up critters
is one of our favorite activities!
It's what we did on our honeymoon.
Thanks, Ma and Pa. You gather the sloths
while we handle the water.
-Hee-ya!
-Giddyup, little slothies!
That's a wrap, thanks to my wraps!
Great! That'll keep the water to a minimum
until Lonny gets back.
[Ismat] Yeah.
[gasping] Museum mayday!
Lonny is coming!
-[panicking]
-[Ma] Scatter!
Ridley, you wrapped that leak
all by yourself?
Yeah, no help whatsoever.
That's good, because it turns out
I don't have a replacement thingamajig
for this pipe.
I gotta order a new one,
which could take a while.
Until then, there's no way
to completely stop the water,
and these little cuties
will have to go into storage.
Uh, I can take care of them. I promise.
There we go.
Blankets, pillows, food, and water.
[slowly] Thank you for everything you've--
[normal] For everything you've done,
is what she's trying to say.
Hi, I'm Julietta.
My parents tell me
I'm the fast talker of the family.
Nice to meet you.
Glad you and your family are okay.
Yeah, me too.
[sighing] Still, I miss
my favorite blankie.
When do y'all think we can go back home?
I don't know. Lonny wasn't sure
how long fixing the pipe would take.
Oh. Okay. Well, thanks.
[pensive music playing]
[sighing softly]
[sighing]
You couldn't sleep either?
Yeah, I just don't feel like
my usual royal self.
I mean, I look fabulous,
as per usual, but--
I just kept thinking about
our sloth friends.
[sighing] Me too.
But don't they have everything they need?
Then why do I feel like we did
something wrong? Let's go check on them.
[door opening]
[sloths snoring]
[yawning, snoring]
This storage room is terrible. I mean,
none of us would wanna live here.
True, there's no room for grazing.
No view of the stars.
No cuddly plush dodos to hug.
The sloths may have
everything they need to survive,
but they don't have a home.
We can do better than this.
[together] Yes!
Come on out, sloths. We're gonna find you
a way better place to stay.
-[sloth] Yeah.
-[Julietta] Thank you, Ridley!
[slowly] Sorry
for getting so overexcited.
[Ridley chuckling]
We need to find
another spot for the sloths.
Any ideas, team?
Hm, what about the Egyptian wing?
The princess has tons of space
and it's way fancier
than some musty old storage closet.
Oh, well, um, I am a royally good hostess.
Julietta, how'd you like to spend
the night in an Egyptian palace?
[gasping] Really?
What's this?
-[Peaches gasping]
-[Dante] Whoa!
-[Fred gasping]
-[slowly] I got it.
[Fred grunting] Phew!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let go of that.
I know a booby-trap when I see one.
[rumbling]
[panicked] Seriously, like,
let go, right now. Please?
[slowly] I'm going as fast as I can.
You gotta go faster.
The room is filling with sand!
This is so soft. It reminds me
of my favorite blankie back home.
Yeah, it's actually a special shawl
that I got from my dads.
I love it because it's fit for a queen,
like me. [chuckling nervously]
Oops. Sorry.
Oh, that's all right.
Would you mind wearing this one instead?
[Ismat laughing awkwardly] Ridley!
As much as I love our sloth friends,
and I do,
I was thinking,
maybe this isn't the right place for them.
You know where might work?
[gulping] Where?
[sloths snoring]
Banana, yum.
[Peaches] Uh, hey, y'all.
Uh, please don't do that, or touch that!
Or go there.
Especially, don't peel that!
[Ridley] How's it goin' in here?
Furrier than I'm used to.
And that's sayin' somethin'.
Sorry, sunshine, I don't think this
is the right place for the sloths either.
But you know where might be good?
[Fred panting]
Nope, not gonna work.
[Fred groaning]
[caribou yelping]
Too many sloths! I can't stampede!
[eagles squawking]
So slippery!
Look out below!
Sorry, Ridley.
[sighing] We tried everywhere.
[slowly] It's hopeless.
Ooh.
Sorry for flying off the handle like that.
-But--
-Thanks anyway, Ridley.
[sadly] My family and I
will just go back to storage.
No, this isn't right.
But there wasn't a single spot
in the museum that was sloth friendly.
That's because
we didn't make it sloth friendly.
We have to give it another shot.
-[whistling]
-[zebras barking]
Hey, everyone, listen up.
I know you all had the sloths
in your exhibits,
and for one reason or another,
it didn't work out.
-No.
-I've got a need to stampede.
There's so much fur.
-Those bananas.
-My royal artifacts.
Think about what the sloths
are going through.
How would you feel if you had to leave
your home and all your stuff?
And not only that,
you had to live in a dark storage room.
-Oh, I'd feel terrible.
-That sounds awful.
We say we tried to help the sloths,
but our hearts weren't in it.
We didn't want our lives to change,
even though theirs changed so much.
I guess we weren't
very good museum neighbors.
All I know is, not in my backyard.
Charlotte, that's the kind of attitude
that got us here.
No, I just mean not in my backyard,
'cause it's full of actual quicksand.
But I agree with Ridley.
Even a queen makes mistakes,
but she also knows when to fix them.
We'll help with the sloths, Ridley.
-Yeah!
-[cheering]
Then let's go stop those sloths
before they go back into storage.
[cheering]
Oh.
Guess they didn't get very far.
[Ismat] Hey, Julietta.
I'm sorry about before.
You and your family
had to give up so much,
so I can give up something too.
Really?
Of course. That's what it means
to be a good neighbor.
[emotional music playing]
♪ It doesn't matter who you are ♪
♪ It doesn't matter where you're from ♪
♪ We're neighbors now
Because you're here ♪
♪ And we're happy that you've come ♪
♪ It's no big deal ♪
♪ Just watch and we'll ♪
♪ Make you feel at home ♪
♪ No matter what, we all are one ♪
♪ Neighbors united in these halls ♪
♪ We'll lend a hand
And we'll welcome you ♪
♪ Instead of building walls ♪
♪ It's no big deal ♪
♪ Just watch and we'll ♪
♪ Make you feel at home ♪
♪ It's no big deal ♪
♪ Just watch and we'll ♪
♪ Make you feel at home ♪
[song ends]
Uh, remind me how to,
like, play this game again.
[chuckling] Dante. I draw,
and you have to guess what the picture is.
Right, right, okay.
Wait, I totally know. It's Ralph.
You got it.
Museum mayday part two!
[groaning] Lonny's coming!
Quick, hide!
Oh, right. You don't do quick.
Hey, Ridley. You'll be happy to know
that I installed the new pipe thingamagee,
and the sloth exhibit's dry
as a dinosaur bone.
-Told you I was the pipe whisperer.
-I never doubted it.
-I better get those sloths from storage.
-Uh, right.
-I'll go get 'em.
-Gee, thanks!
What a helpful kid.
-So, you heard the good news?
-Yes.
We did hear--
The good news! [giggling]
We're excited to go back home!
-Aw, no!
-[sighing]
-Gnarly.
-My nest buddies.
You just got here.
What we're trying to say is,
we'll miss you.
How about one more game?
Okay, one more game.
Dudley, your turn to guess that drawing.
Oh, I know this. Is it a dot?
No, a line. A squiggle. A longer line.
A stick. It's a stick, isn't it?
-[laughing]
-Oh, Dudley.
[closing theme music playing]
[child] No, no. Okay.