[WHOOPING]
[PLAYING "UNSAID UNDONE"]
Powerlessness
My Only power
Hopelessness, my only hope
[MAN WHOOPING]
I see the girl
Up in the tower
But my hands can't grasp the rope
No, my hands can't grasp the rope
Unsaid unsung
Unsaid undone
You can call me names, but I won't come
Aah!
Unsaid undone
Aah! Whoo!
Unsaid unsung
I'll just eat my words and move on
On a map of the world
Yeah!
He stands alone. . . .
With his dreams and his demons...
[CHEERING]
[DOOR OPENS]
I'll just keep on having fun
Yeah, I'll just keep on having fun
Good mornin', captain
Good mornin' to you
Ah, ah
Let me be another mule skinner
Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah
[SIREN WAILING]
Oh, son of a bitch.
Whoa.
[ARKIE CHUCKLES]
Phew. Heh.
[SIGHS]
[GASPS]
What do you--? What the hell do you want?
No, no! Stop! Let go! Get out!
Let go, let go!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Stop! Let go, let go! Stop, stop! No!
[ARKIE SCREAMING]
[HORN BLOWING]
["MULESKINNER BLUES"
CONTINUES PLAYING]
Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah
Da, da, da
Arkie Seavers, age 20.
Currently a resident of the county jail.
What does the other guy look like?
Funny you should ask.
Arkie there wasn't in a fight. Car crash,
head-on collision into a tree. Drunk as a skunk.
He's lucky to be alive.
You have no idea.
Not wearing a seat belt, I suspect.
To hear Arkie tell it,
he didn't have time to fasten his seat belt...
...because he was busy running
from the boy he says caused the accident.
And who was that?
You're looking at him.
No. Not me.
What, he blames himself?
In a manner of speaking.
I don't get it, Mulder.
Arkie, our hapless road warrior...
...is driving by his lonesome
down the highway to hell...
...when he sees another Arkie, across from him,
who grabs the wheel and crashes the vehicle.
Well, you did say he was drunk.
I know what you're gonna say
about seeing double...
...and the bromides
about not giving the kids the car keys.
Twenty is hardly a kid.
Circumstances bear a curious similarity
to stories told by other good folk...
...who didn't share Arkie Seavers' luck.
Who also reported
seeing their doubles before dying.
And how did these people die?
Each by their own hand.
After seeing their doubles?
According to all reports
out of Henrico County, Virginia.
Reports issued by whom?
Friends, relatives. A doctor.
And the medical diagnosis is...?
A rare form of schizophrenia.
Heh. Right, so rare I've never heard of it.
Correct me if I'm wrong, Scully,
and I know you will...
...but schizophrenics hear voices
and report hallucinations similar to Arkie's.
Hallucinations, yes...
...not grabbing the wheel of a car
and ramming it into a tree.
Well, they didn't all die
from car crashes into trees.
Seven died from hanging,
fourjumped off a tall bridge, three--
This is a mass phenomenon.
Precisely my thinking, Scully...
...which is why you and I
are gonna jump on I-95 south...
...and get back to our bread and butter.
These the FBI agents?
Agents Scully and Mulder.
And you filled them in?
Mm-hm.
We know the facts, Arkie.
We'd like to hear the details.
Okay, I-- I looked over,
and he grabbed the wheel...
...and he floored the gas.
And by "he," you mean...?
I mean, the dude looked just like me.
And you'd seen him before.
Yes. Like, four times.
He'd been following me for like a week.
Had he ever said anything?
No, I'd see him in a crowd
or a window.
I thought I was tripping
or something.
And do you take drugs, Arkie?
No, I'm-- Eh.
Yeah, maybe once or twice,
I mean...
And you're in jail because...?
Arkie admittedly has a problem.
A few previous DUI offenses.
Exactly how many is a few?
I don't know, like...
...six.
So the judge is gonna
throw the book at you.
But that's not
what we're interested in.
We want to know how you
came to be the lone survivor.
Why I'm not dead
like all the other people, right?
What do you chalk that up to?
I can tell you.
And it's the same reason
I can prove I'm not lying.
You can prove it?
You gotta admit, Scully,
the kid's story makes a lot of sense.
Arkie's double takes control
of the wheel.
Then Arkie pumps the brakes
with his left foot...
...producing the skid marks
that start up yonder.
Or there's another explanation,
of course...
...which is that Arkie,
in his perpetual state of inebriation...
...falls asleep at the wheel, waking up
to find he's going off the highway...
...and applying the brakes there.
But if he was asleep...
...he wouldn't have been traveling
at such a dangerous rate of speed.
You're saying you believe him.
No.
I'm just saying that I think
the kid's too stupid to make it up.
Yes, I treated several of the victims
manifesting the symptoms.
Their episodes suggest
a pattern of shared hallucination.
A distinct narrative.
They all saw their doubles. Doppelgangers.
None of them had
psychiatric problems before?
They never received treatment.
So there were issues?
No, but they were arguably
not upstanding citizens.
They had trouble with the law.
Not necessarily connoting
they were mentally ill.
Dr. Russell, your diagnosis
is of a nonconforming type of schizophrenia.
That was my clinical opinion.
So they were mentally ill?
They became mentally ill.
It was almost like a kind of outbreak.
So would you say
like a mass hysteria?
I've never heard of a suicidal mass hysteria.
DANA: A phenomenon known as
suicide clusters or suicide contagion...
...have been known to affect
whole communities or social groups.
Are you treating patients
with those symptoms?
Nothing matching
that particular pattern. Why?
This patient, what's her specific
psychiatric diagnosis?
Mm. More a normative schizophrenic.
FOX: Could we possibly talk to her?
I'd strongly advise against that.
Why would you say that?
Because she exhibits split personality...
...with wild swings in affect,
from benign to violent.
Unless you've got some good reason,
I'd steer clear.
I'd like to take a look
at her drawings.
[LOCK CLICKS]
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Judy? You have visitors.
Oh. You should've warned me.
I look awful. I look a fright.
No one's judging you, Judy.
Not without my coiffure.
You look fine to me.
No, I don't. I don't,
not for such a handsome man as yourself.
My name is Fox, and this is Dana.
You can call me Little Judy.
That's what my fans call me.
Are you an actress, Judy?
I'm a very famous actress.
They want to see your drawing.
Would you like to show them?
Oh, it's nothing. It's just hangman.
You play a lot of hangman.
I play with my brother.
DANA: Does he visit?
My brother's an insufferable jerk.
We play telepathically.
FOX:
"Arkie."
You know a...
An Arkie Seavers?
You know, he--
He had an accident recently.
I don't know an Arkie Seavers.
This is just a coincidence?
But she might.
Hey, listen, man, where are they taking me?
Don't know, transfer.
I gotta talk to my lawyer first
or something.
Sorry. Can't help you.
Please, I mean-- Ah!
Okay, okay. Transfer where?
Like I said, can't help you.
[EXHALES]
[DOOR BUZZES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GASPING]
Hey, help, help! He's here!
Please, somebody help me!
Please, please, help me!
[CHIRPING]
[RINGS DOORBELL]
WOMAN:
Coming.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hi, we'd like a couple rooms.
Do you have reservations?
No.
Uh... Do you have any rooms?
I've had a cancellation. It's just a suite.
We'll take it.
There's a pullout sofa.
0K8)'-
Just trying to get some shut-eye.
I'm glad to hear it.
[SIGHS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Mulder.
What are you doing?
That bed nice and comfy?
Mulder, go back to sleep.
I wish that I could, Scully.
They just found Arkie Seavers dead
in his jail cell.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Somebody want to explain this to me?
Who found him there?
One of the trustees.
That gUY-
This happens all the time,
don't know what to tell you.
Looks like a suicide.
MR. CAVALIER: He was strangled to death.
Not necessarily, Mr. Cavalier.
He's wearing handcuffs.
It looks impossible,
and it's highly improbable...
...but there is ample case history
that it can be done.
The victim simply spins the belt around
and unbuckles it, fastens it to the bars...
...loops it around his neck,
and uses his body as leverage.
No, Arkie didn't want to die.
I agree with you.
This is an outrage. Now, who
is gonna stop this carnage?
We're working on it.
Well, someone's gotta pay.
Arkie did not wanna die.
[DOOR BUZZES]
I know what you're thinking.
Anyone up for a game of hangman?
It's just a coincidence.
Judy said that she didn't even know
Arkie Seavers.
Not necessarily, Scully.
She said she didn't know him.
She said that she might.
She also said she was playing
telepathically with her brother.
Our suspect number two.
[DOG BARKING]
CHUCKY:
God's sakes.
[CHUCKY EXHALES]
My one damn day off.
Chucky Poundstone?
Speaking to whom?
Fox Mulder, I'm with the FBI.
Oh, yeah.
With that tasty little redhead.
You tapping that special agent
or can Chucky bust a move?
You're that trustee. You found
the kid hanged in his jail cell.
Yeah, I discovered the moron.
Kid had "loser" written all over him.
Can I ask you a few questions?
Why? Am I under suspicion?
Just a few moments of your time.
Yeah, well, lucky I just tidied up.
[CHUCKY EXHALES]
You'd better hope
the fire marshal never comes...
...he'd red-tag you--
You calling the marshal?
No. I'm just saying.
[GROANS]
Talk about my house.
This town needs cleaning up.
Seen what you need?
Get a sense of what lurks beneath?
I'm an FBI agent, Mr. Poundstone,
not an archeologist.
Yeah, well, I got body parts in the fridge.
You play with your sister?
My sister's a miserable slut
and a damn cheater on top of it.
How does she do that?
She cheats. Breaks the rules.
What are the rules?
[SCOFFS]
What are we, amigos now? Bros?
Is this you deftly profiling the mind
of Charles H. Poundstone?
It's a simple line of inquiry.
Yeah, well, it takes a dipwad to know one.
I take it you're twins.
Ooh.
Powers of deduction.
And she's the good twin.
[CHUCKYLAUGHS]
You don't know Little Judy.
How do you both play a game with the name
of the deceased Arkie Seavers in it?
I like the name Arkie.
Funny name for a no-account douche bag.
All right, well, you mind if I take a picture
of your wall? For my records.
Is this guy a numbnuts or what?
You talking to me?
No. I'm talking to him.
Is she expecting me here today?
We told her you were coming.
Then she flung dookie at us.
So this is the other Judy.
We call her Demon Judy.
DANA:
Why is the light off?
Makes you a harder target.
Sometimes a split personality responds...
...to a strong persona
who challenges the psychotic child.
Both parents hanged
themselves.
And you'll come in with me?
Heh. No way.
Heh. Not a chance.
Judy, it's Agent Scully.
[JUDY SNICKERING]
I want you to behave yourself.
I know what you want, bitch.
I wanna know about Arkie.
Reached the end of his rope.
[JUDY LAUGHING]
I'm not afraid of you, Judy.
Oh, yes, you are.
Everybody's afraid of sweet Little Judy.
Is Little Judy a killer?
Little Judy's an angel.
And what about your brother?
Is he involved?
Could be.
Chucky Poundstone
is the devil's dimwitted disciple.
Did he kill Arkie Seavers?
Arkie Seavers killed himself.
How did you know that, Judy,
if you weren't involved yourself?
Are you trying to trick me,
Agent Scully?
I want the killing to stop.
Oh.
Well, don't you have a heart of gold?
What's he see in you,
your handsome partner?
One taste of Little Judy
and he'd forget you even exist.
Maybe I can make you go away too.
Are you threatening me?
[JUDY LAUGHING]
Afraid I'll dirty your cheap little ensemble?
You're nothing but a hosebag.
How old are you, 40s?
Past your childbearing years.
You're all dried up, not even half a woman.
You can't hurt me, Judy.
Nothing hurts like the truth.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Just a minute.
Hey. What'd you find out, Scully?
That dookie-winging past your head
sends a sharp message to your brain.
What message is that?
Heh.
To gather the other apes
and make war on your dread enemy.
I believe I'm in touch
with that feeling, Scully.
Really? Did you have
dookie flung at you too?
Figuratively. By the queerest little man
in the queerest little house.
I don't know, Mulder, this Judy...
...she has some malign influence
over these victims.
I'm at a loss to figure out what it is.
I agree, there is some evil in the air, Scully.
No, it's not evil, it's mental illness.
There's some kind of
psychic transference.
I wouldn't rule out ghosts.
Well, except for the fact
that they don't exist?
Of course there are ghosts.
Science has proven stimulation
of the brain's left anterior insula...
...is linked to the feeling
of a sense presence.
Repeated stimulations to an area
of the left temporal parietal junction...
...is what promotes the sense
of a shadowy figure...
...collectively known
as the Gastaut-Geschwind syndrome.
Talk about flinging dookie.
[SIGHS]
Mulder, do you think of me as old?
What? Where is that coming from?
Maybe in dog years. No.
What are you talking about?
Well, a woman thinks about these things.
No, Scully, you're--
You still got it going on and...
...heh, you still got some scoot in your boot.
I'm gonna boot you out of here.
Knock three times.
[SIGHS]
Mm.
Bloodsucking scumbag.
You think you're gonna point the finger at me?
[CHUCKLING]
Four letters, little sister.
Is there an E?
I thought so.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Top of the morning, Agent Muldoon.
What's on your mind?
I wanna know how you do it.
Haven't a clue what you mean.
Is the other Chucky here?
The one I talked to yesterday?
Search me, Muldoon,
I'm not my brother's keeper--
It's Mulder, and I think this is an act.
You choose them at the jail, don't you?
Losers like Arkie Seavers...
...who you hanged,
if not literally, then psychically.
Does that FBI health plan of yours
cover anger management, Agent Mulder?
Who's next, Mr. Poundstone?
You're asking the wrong guy.
I can have you and your alter ego arrested.
I can have you committed.
On what legal pretense?
Intent to commit a crime.
Heh. I've seen many a bad jailhouse lawyer...
...spring far less innocent men than I,
Agent Mulder.
I'd even venture I'd have grounds
to have you censured for abuse of power.
You're going down, Poundstone.
Tell it to the hand, G-man.
That's original. I haven't heard that before.
Before I punch you in the face...
...and snatch Little Red Riding Hood.
There's the Chucky I came for.
And that's the Chucky
who's eventually gonna hang himself.
Judy? Excuse me, hon.
Agent Scully's here to see you.
What brings you here today, Agent Scully?
Do you have any recollection
of our exchange that we had yesterday?
No memory whatsoever?
You look mad at me.
lam mad, Judy. I am...
...angry because I need
to stop the killings...
...and I don't know how.
And you blame me, don't you?
Are you to blame?
I'm an actress, Agent Scully.
I've never even played a killer.
Where is the person
that I talked to here yesterday?
Where is that Judy?
She's right over there.
No, she's not.
Sure she is. Just look.
No, she isn't, Judy. And I think
that you're pretending that she is.
You mean I'm pretending
so I can sit here in this bed all day?
I think you have some kind of power
to influence people's lives.
I think you mean their deaths.
Yes.
That's exactly what I mean.
[WHISPERING]
People can protect themselves.
How? Protect themselves how?
By taking these pills.
I take them every day
to protect me from her, and so far...
...they've worked.
Did the nurses give you these?
Every morning with breakfast.
Would you consider not playing that game
with your brother?
Ooh.
Well, what would I do in here all day,
Agent Scully?
I'd go mad.
[SCOFFS]
I have a question for you.
She said that you give these to her
at breakfast every morning...
...and that they have secret powers.
That's really only half true.
That you give them to her at breakfast
or they have secret power?
We bring her bread every morning
and she rolls it into those pills.
So these are just bread pills.
They have no medicinal qualities.
No. Not that we know of, anyway.
Well, but we both take them.
In case they have secret power.
You might wanna take them too.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
[SIGHS]
What'll you have, Dean?
I'll take the lunch special.
No mayo, salad on the side, lightly dressed.
And if you bat those baby blues at me,
I'll give you a little something on the side too.
Promises are like bananas.
Only good when they're appealing.
I gotta have you over to my place...
...to see my sword collection.
You say that to all the girls.
Hey, did you see that guy?
Did I see what guy?
Cancel the blue plate.
Agent Scully, I saw him.
Hold your horses, Mr. Cavalier.
He looked just like me.
Calm down and you can tell us both
what it is that happened.
All right. I saw him through a window,
the same way Arkie said he saw his double.
Was it the first time?
No, no, I think I saw him the other day...
...staring at me from a bus stop.
You're making it worse.
I'm making it worse? This guy is stalking me.
Your paranoia is gonna feed on itself.
You know that mass hysteria
is just a symptom of fears run wild.
Those people all died.
While I agree with Agent Scully's theory...
...there's a danger
and take every precaution against it.
All right. What should I do?
Stay off the interstate?
[SIGHS]
Do you have a family, Mr. Cavalier?
No, I don't. I live by myself.
Okay, well, maybe stay home.
Take some time off work, lock your doors and
call the police if you have another panic attack.
Yeah. Well, that's easy for you to say.
Take my card.
And just know that it can't haunt you
if you don't let it.
Yeah.
FOX:
Like I said before.
Clearly there's a dark influence
set loose in this town, Scully.
Well, by "dark influence," again,
I presume you mean "evil," Mulder.
But there is no such thing as evil.
I mean, evil is a concept.
Like the devil.
Oh, the devil is a concept?
Certainly, that's not what they taught young
Dana Katherine Scully in Sunday school, is it?
Well, I certainly believed
in the literal devil when I was a child.
You don't believe that we as humans have
dark sides that we sublimate or repress?
Well, anyone with an imagination can entertain
acting out violence or antisocial behavior.
That doesn't mean that there's
an evil twin lurking inside of us.
Speak for yourself, Scully.
And tell that to Chuck and Judy.
Chuck and Judy are mentally ill.
Explain how they're doing it.
I can't.
But if you eliminate the impossible...
...whatever is remaining,
even if improbable, must be the truth.
No sugar, Sherlock.
But I have to admit...
...I still sleep with my back to the door
in case the devil comes in the night.
Can never be too careful.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[PANTING]
[BEEPING]
[DOG BARKING]
[PANTING]
Is there an S?
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER TV]
Damn you, Chucky Poundstone.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[BLADE SWISHES]
[GASPS]
Please, Mulder, you've got to quit
scaring me like that.
Oh, I'd like to quit.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING OVER RADIO]
Thank you.
So neighbors called police
when they saw him acting suspiciously.
He was dumping firearms in the driveway.
The doors were locked from the inside
when they arrived?
Yeah, he wasn't responding.
They broke through the window
and broke in the door.
Has anybody offered up any evidence
for how this could happen?
Well, it seems everyone's under the agreement
that a man can't cut off his own head.
Oh, good to see there's still
a shred of sanity left in this town.
But I have to say, it's not outside
the realm of extreme possibility.
Oh, so he tripped and fell
and splattered the walls with blood?
Well, if he were a determined man...
...with a razor-sharp sword set on creating
his own self-fulfilling prophecy--
He was scared out of his mind, Scully.
Well, if he was in his right mind,
he might've called you.
Oh, maybe he tried.
Only he lost his head.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
FOX:
You coming, Scully?
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
Oh, hey.
Speak of the devil.
I can't sleep, Mulder.
What's the problem?
Something about this case
is getting under my skin.
Well, we've had stranger cases, Scully.
Can you hold me?
Yeah. I can do that.
[DANA SIGHS]
What's gonna happen?
What's gonna happen when?
When we're old.
What do you mean "when"?
[DANA CHUCKLES]
I mean...
...sooner or later we're gonna retire and...
Hmm.
Are we gonna spend time together?
I'll come push your wheelchair.
With my wheelchair.
[CHUCKLES]
That's not what I mean.
Oh, I'll always be around, Scully.
Offering bulletproof theories of genius that you
fail to assail with your inadequate rationality.
And I'll always be around
to prove you wrong.
Hmm.
Promise.
No, but that's not what I mean.
What do you mean?
What if you meet someone?
What if you meet someone...
.“youngen“
...who wants to have kids?
Oh, that's what you mean.
Well...
...you could do the same.
You could meet someone...
...and have kids.
Mm.
Mulder, that's not gonna happen.
It's nonsense.
No, it's not. I'm--
I'm at the end of that journey.
Do you wanna have more kids?
Well...
I would have liked to have had
another one.
Hmm.
At the risk of sounding insensitive,
what's stopping you?
Mm.
Besides the fact that the first time
was a miracle?
And besides the fact that...
...I don't have anyone to have one with
even if I could?
You're a woman of science.
[CHUCKLES]
Mulder, sometimes I think
the world is going to hell...
...and we're the only two who can save it.
The world is going to hell, Scully.
The president working
to bring down the FBI along with it.
What if we lose our jobs?
Yeah.
Then what would we do?
We'll think of something.
JUDY:
All right.
Is there an L?
I said, is there an L?
Are we playing or not, Chuck-face?
Earth to Judith.
Yes, Your Royal Highness, there is an L.
[CHUCKLES]
[GASPS]
[WHISPERING]
Scully, get up. Get dressed.
Mm. Come back to bed.
They're coming after me.
What are you talking about?
I was looking in the mirror, and there he was.
There I was. It wasn't my reflection.
It was my double.
I know. I saw my double too.
They're targeting us both.
That's how they operate.
I know how they operate.
You're playing into it.
Spare me the pop psychology, okay?
Mulder, you have to calm down.
Scully.
Put a dimmer on that afterglow and get
to the hospital before they hang us both.
They can't hang us.
We can only hang ourselves if we panic.
How many letters in "Scully," Scully?
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
JUDY:
ls there another L?
What do you mean, no?
Don't throw a hissy. One L.
You know you're in love with him.
Double L, Chuck-face.
Who's the one in love?
[GRUNTS]
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
Chucky Poundstone.
No letter C, super-freak.
MULDER: I know you're in here.
I said, no letter C.
You're under arrest, Chucky.
Put the pencil down.
[CREAKING]
Who's the cheater now?
[SCOFFS]
My rational mind knows
that you are only...
...a manifest psychic ideation
borne of latent hostility.
Maybe Mulder was right.
You're evil incarnate. It's all you are.
[SIGHS]
Step aside.
I'm coming through.
[GRUNTING]
Is there a J?
Oh, look, and a D, and an I-T-H.
Is there a C-H-U-C-K-Y?
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA]
[HISSES]
[ALL GASP]
BOTH: Not going in there.
[CLICKING]
Judy, open the door.
Judy.
[CREAKING]
[PANTING]
Judy?
[DOOR CLOSES]
Nurses, get in here!
NURSE:
Get Dr. Russell.
So I was thinking maybe we could
get a couple hours in before checkout time?
I'm just talking about
getting some shut-eye.
I'm glad to hear that, Mulder.
Yeah.
Uh...
I guess I should hit the hay.
Okay.
Yeah.
If you need anything,
you just call me.
I can't imagine that I will.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER TV]
But then again...
...it's not out of the realm
of extreme possibility.
[SWORD SWISHES]