[COMPUTER CHIRPS]
SCIENCE".
In 2016, on the 23rd of March...
...an artificial-intelligence chatter bot
was released...
...by a major American software corporation
via the social-media platform Twitter.
The Talkbot was designed to mimic
the online language patterns...
...of an innocent 19-year-old girl...
...and was introduced as an experiment
to better understand how humans converse...
...and relate on social media.
The quality of her interactions were meant
to be friendly and informal.
The AI would learn from humans.
It was constructed to become
progressively more intelligent.
The experiment performed as designed.
The robot did indeed learn,
but not as intended.
The chat bot's "repeat after me" capability
made her vulnerable to humans...
...allowing Twitter users to affect her tweets.
Her posts became offensive.
Racist. Hateful.
After more than 50,000 followers
and almost 100,000 tweets...
...the software corporation was forced
to shut the bot down.
In less than a day, her posts deleted.
Humans must take care in teaching AI...
...or one day, we will be the ones deleted.
[DISPLAY CHIMES]
[MUSIC PLAYS]
[BEEPS]
COMPUTER:
Yum.
[BEEPS]
Yum. Success.
[SIGHS]
[CHIMING]
[CHIMES]
[CHUCKLES]
[DISPLAY CHIMES]
[BEEPS]
[WHIRRING]
COMPUTER:
Yum.
[WHIRRING]
[DANA LAUGHS]
[DANA LAUGHING]
Ah.
Ooh.
[LAUGHING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Ugh.
Heh.
Mm.
[CHUCKLES]
[WHIRRING]
[WHIRRING STOPS]
[BEEPS]
[CHIMES]
[WHIRS]
[BEEPING]
[STATIC CRACKLES]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[STATIC CRACKLING]
[WHIRRING]
COMPUTER 1:
Door closing.
[BEEPING]
[DOOR LOCKS]
Door closing.
COMPUTER 2: Yum. Success.
COMPUTER 1: Door closing.
Door closing.
COMPUTER 2: Yum.
COMPUTER 1: Door closing.
COMPUTER 2: Success.
COMPUTER 1:
Door closing.
[WHIRRING]
COMPUTER 1: Door closing.
COMPUTER 2: Success.
[GRUNTING]
COMPUTER:
Yum.
Success.
[WHIRRING]
[WHISTLES]
[DOOR LOCKS]
COMPUTER:
Yum.
[WHIRRING]
COMPUTER:
Yum.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[CHIMING]
COMPUTER:
Yum.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[DOOR CHIRPS]
[WHIRRING]
[CHIRPS]
[CHIMES]
Hello.
This is a driverless Whipz for Dana Scully.
[CHIMING]
Mulder--
[DOOR WHIRRING]
[CHIMES]
No, thanks.
You are going to 121337th Place.
Is that correct?
Yes.
You can answer in complete sentences.
Yes, that's correct.
Tell me how I can make your ride
more enjoyable.
Be quiet.
Would you like to watch television?
No. No television.
Music? You can say names of artists or songs.
No. No music. Be quiet.
[PINGS]
All right. Taking you home.
Slow down.
Hmm.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Home.
[CHIMES]
Blobfish.
[PINGS]
Home.
GYDZ". Let's get started. Drive safely.
Slow down.
Slow down. Oh, my God.
You're kidding me. Stop. Pull over.
Play Prince. "Controversy."
I found a faster route.
Well, good for you.
Just play Prince, "Controversy."
[CROSBY, STILLS, NASH & YOUNG'S
"TEACH YOUR CHILDREN" PLAYS]
Teach the children well
[LAUGHING]
Oh, how do you get "Teach Your Children"
from "Controversy"?
It's not e-- It doesn't even-- It's--
Doesn't even sound like it.
[BUSY TONE]
Oh, yep, of course. Busy.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Stop it! Slow down!
GYDZ".
We found a faster route. Recalculating.
Turn right.
Don't you ever ask them why
Stop! Pull over!
You're driving too fast.
Who am I talking to?
If they told you, you--
[DISPLAY PINGS]
What? Why?
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Stop. Stop. Pull over.
GYDZ:
In 30 feet, your destination will be on the left.
[ALARM BEEPING]
Oh, come on. What...?
[GYDZ SPEAKING ON-SCREEN TEXT]
[ALARM BEEPING]
You suck, Mr. Phone.
I'm going old-school.
[WHIRRING]
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[SCOFFS]
[WINDOW WHIRRING]
[THUD$]
How do I get--? Let me out.
[DISPLAY CHIMES]
[DOOR HANDLE THUNKING]
[BEEPING]
What?
Poor. Awful.
Terrible. Never again.
Wha--? Open the door!
[BEEPS]
[WHIRRING]
[ELECTRICITY FUZZING]
[OWL HOOTING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[WHIRRING]
Ow.
[MOSQUITO BUZZING]
COMPUTER: Front door open.
[ALARM BLARING]
[BEEPS]
I can't-- Come on.
[BEEPING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hi. Yeah.
No, it won't work.
I'm putting it in.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
No--
Queequeg.
The password is Queequeg.
Q-U-E-E-Q-U-E-G.
[BEEPS]
Thank you.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[CHIMING]
[SCOFFS]
RECORDED VOICE:
You have reached Big/y Credit.
We are experiencing
an unusually high call volume.
Your approximate wait time is 17 minutes.
Press 1 now if you would like a callback.
[BEEPS]
Please say your name at the tone.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Fox Mulder.
MAN 1: It looks good at NASA One.
MAN 2: Roger.
MAN 3: BCS Arm switch is on.
MAN 1: Okay, Victor.
MAN 3: Lining rods are armed. Switch is on.
Here comes the throttle. Circuit breakers in.
MAN 2: We have separation.
MAN 4: Roger.
MAN 3: inboards and outboards are on.
MAN 2: Coming forward with the sidestick.
MAN 5: Looks good.
MAN 6: Roger.
MAN 3: I've got a blowout, damper three.
MAN 1: Get your pitch to zero.
[STATIC HISSING]
[STATIC FUZZES]
[CAMERA LENS WHIRRING]
[WHIRRING]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[BUZZING]
[WHIRRING]
Hey, kid. Fly this out of my face, or you'll end
up with nothing in your hand but a joystick.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[WHIRRING FADES]
[CHIMES]
Oh.
[RINGING]
RECORDED VOICE: An automated call for...
FOX [ON RECORDING]: Fox Mulder.
Fox Mulder.
This is the living Fox Mulder.
FOX: Fox Mulder. Fox Mulder--
[DRONE BUZZING]
[WHIRRING]
Come on.
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[WHIRRING FEEBLY]
Let that be a lesson to you.
[DRONE WHIRRING]
COMPUTER: Front door open.
[HUMMING]
[WHIRRING]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[BEEPS]
[DRONE WHIRRING]
[WHIRRING FADES]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[WHIRRING]
COMPUTER: Front door open.
Oh.
[BEEPS]
[CHIMES]
Oh...
[BEEPING]
[WHIRRING]
[SIGHS]
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[CHIMES]
[WHIRRING]
[CHUCKLES]
[BEEPS]
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[WHIRRING]
[CHIMES]
["TEACH YOUR CHILDREN"
PLAYING OVER CELL PHONE]
[BEEPS]
["TEACH YOUR CHILDREN"
CONTINUES PLAYING]
Must have a code
[BEEPS]
And so become yourself
[GRUNTING]
Your children well
Their father's hell did slowly go by
And feed them on your dreams
[DRONE WHIRRING]
The one they pick's the one you'll know by
[WHIRRING STOPS]
RECORDED VOICE:
Hello, and welcome to E-Norm-Uz. com...
...the world's largest online retail store.
How can I help you? You can say things like,
"make a payment"...
..."reorder items" or "returns."
Returns.
I'm sorry, I did not catch that.
You can say things like,
"make a payment," "reorder items--"
Returns.
I did not catch that.
You can say things like, "make a payment,"
"reorder items" or "returns."
Returns.
I'm sorry, let me put you on hold...
...while I find an operator to assist you.
["TEACH YOUR CHILDREN" PLAYS]
Don't you ever ask them why
If they told you, you would cry
So just look at them and sigh
[BEEPS]
And know they love you
[SIGHS]
["TEACH YOUR CHILDREN"
CONTINUES PLAYING]
And you
[BEEPS]
Of tender years
Can't know the fears
That your elders grew by
[BEEPS]
And so please help them with your youth
They seek the truth
Before they can die
Teach your parents well
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
Their children's hell
[ZUEMZ BEEPING]
Will slowly go by
--them on your dreams
[DRONE WHIRRING]
The one they pick's
The one you'll know by
Don't you ever ask them why
If they told you, you would cry
So just look at them and sigh
[WHIRRING]
And know they love you
Don't you ever ask them why
If they told you, you would cry
So just look at them and sigh
And know they love you
["TEACH YOUR CHILDREN"
CONTINUES PLAYING]
FOX [ON RECORDING]: Fox Mulder.
Here. Present.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
Pfft.
[WHIRRING]
COMPUTER: Front door open.
["TEACH YOUR CHILDREN"
CONTINUES PLAYING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[CHIMES]
[BEEPS]
[WHIRRING]
[WHIRS]
COMPUTER: Front door open.
And feed them on your dreams
The one they pick's
[WHIRRING]
Don't you ever ask them why--
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CHEERING]
[BEEPS]
[BEEPING]
And know they love you
[BEEPS]
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
[DANA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[WHIRRING]
[DISPLAY CHIMES]
Teach your children well
Their father's--
[MUSIC STOPS]
[DANA GROANS]
[BEEPS]
[STATIC CRACKLING]
Oh.
[BEEPS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Come on. No, it's not incorrect.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[ALARM BLARING]
[THUDDING]
COMPUTER 1: Intruder alert.
Intruder alert. Intruder alert. Intruder alert.
[GAS HISSING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[RATTLING]
[GAS CONTINUES HISSING]
Aah!
Scully, let me in.
The door won't open.
Intruder alert. Intruder alert...
[WHIRRING]
I smell gas.
[STATIC CRACKLING]
Why is your house so much nicer than mine?
[WHIRRING]
COMPUTER 2:
Fire. Calling the fire department.
Contacting emergency services.
Call 911.
Calling the fire department.
[CHIRPS]
Call 911.
[CHIMES]
Calling the fire department. Contacting...
[RINGING]
Hello?
WOMAN: Hello?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I had to adjust my headset. Heh. I'm Wendy--
Oh, shut up.
I can't get out.
Let's get to the neighbors', use their phone.
COMPUTER 2:
Contacting emergency services.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[CHIMES]
[CHIRPS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Calling the fire department. Contacting emer--
[AUDIO DISTORTING]
Contacting emergency services.
[WHIRRING]
DANA:
Cut through here.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[BEEPING]
[WHISPERING] They're tracking us, our phones.
They know everything.
Where can we go?
[WHISPERING]
The Brutalist Criminal Cyber.
Get rid of anything they can track you with.
[BUZZING]
[WHIRRING]
[DANA PANTING]
FOX".
Let's get inside.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[DRONES WHIRRING]
[CHIMES]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
[GASPS]
[CLANKING]
[WHIRRING]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[WHIRRING]
[WHIRRING STOPS]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[WHIRRING]
[WHIRRING STOPS]
[GRUNTS]
[CHIMES]
[BEEPING]
[PHONE CONTINUES BEEPING]
[CHEERING]
[PARTY HORN BLOWING]
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
Heh.
We have to be better teachers.
[BEEPS]
[DOOR BUZZES]
[BELL DINGS]
WOMAN:
Here you go. Enjoy.
[CHATTERING]
Oh, thank you, Shirley.
You're welcome.
And take your time. No hurry here.
Thanks.
Oh, man.
I lost so many steps
when we were in that warehouse.
Mm.
Well, it's good to see you got
all your personal devices back.
Not all of them.
[CELL PHONE DINGS]
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
[PHONE RINGING]
[SIGHS]