SINGER: One, two, three, four!
[RAMONES' "CALIFORNIA SUN" PLAYING
OVER RADIO]
[CHIRPING]
[STATIC OVER CELL PHONE]
[STATIC CONTINUES]
LANGLY:
Mulder.
...Mulder.
["CALIFORNIA SUN" PLAYING]
[GUN CLICKING]
[STATIC CONTINUES]
LANGLY:
. . . Mulder.
Mulder.
...Mulder.
Mulder...Mulder.
Mulder.
Hmm.
Well, I'm going out west where I belong
[STATIC CONTINUES]
Hmm.
...Mulder.
What?
Fox Mulder.
Langly?
Um...
I believe-- I believe you knew me as Langly.
Richard Langly. Ringo Langly.
Lone Gunmen Langly?
["CALIFORNIA SUN" PLAYING]
And I'll Walk a little Walk
I'll twist a little twist
And I'll shimmy a little shimmy
And I'll fly a little fly
[MUSIC STOPS]
[GUN COCKS]
Mulder, I need to know.
Am I dead?
If I am, they know that I know.
[WHISPERING]
Know that he knows what?
[FLOORBOARD CREAKING]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Go.
Well, I'm going out west out on the coast
Where the California girls are really the most
And I'll Walk a little Walk
I'll twist a little twist
And I'll shimmy a little shimmy
And I'll fly and they'll shimmy
And I'll fly and they'll fly
Where they're out there having fun
In the warm California sun
Where they're out there having fun--
[MUSIC STOPS]
Scully?
You all right?
There's one in the room.
Behind the couch.
[DOOR OPENS]
[PANTING]
Two down, all clear.
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[DANA PANTING]
Mulder.
[STATIC]
Am I...
."dead?
If I am...
...they know that I know.
Better call it in from a landline.
Yeah.
[PHONE KEYPAD CLACKING]
This is Special Agent Dana Scully,
XF072161.
Yes, Washington, D.C. Field Office.
Yes, I'm calling in an incident
where multiple gunshots were exchanged.
There are two suspects on the ground.
No, we weren't injured.
Agent Mulder's residence, yes.
Yeah. Faras Corner.
227700 Wallace Road.
You're careful not to taint that,
but you're willing to conceal this?
You said taint.
This may not be related to that.
Yes, but we're not gonna know
unless it's properly investigated.
Scully, 1O minutes ago,
we received a message...
...from a man who's been dead for 16 years.
Now you want me
to hand it to Evidence...
...where it's gonna sit in a locker
for two, three years?
I was gone back then.
Could--? Could Langly be alive?
No.
I was at Langly's--
At the Lone Gunmen's...
...burial in the Arlington Cemetery.
But did you ever see Langly's body?
Well, nobody did.
They were exposed to a weaponized
strain of the Marburg virus.
Their bodies were incinerated.
It's gotta be connected.
That-- That whatever
Langly message and this.
They know that he knows. Who's they?
I mean, it's-- It's-- It's too much
of a coincidence, right?
I think that the Langly message
was warning us these guys were coming.
It wasn't warning us.
It-- It asked if he were dead.
What do you think it was?
I don't know what I think. I don't know.
But I'll tell you what I do know.
[CAR ENGINE RUNNING]
We gotta take a trip to IKEA.
Well, that was fast.
SCULLY:
What is that?
The Critical Incident Response Group?
Never.
I got 14 rounds.
Eight.
[PHONE RINGING]
Don't answer the phone.
If we use the phone, they may be able
to pinpoint our exact location in the house.
Identify yourself.
MAN:
Can't hear you. Answer your phone.
Should I call Skinner?
We haven't talked to him in a couple weeks,
and I don't know where he stands.
We are federal agents.
We are armed. Identify yourselves.
Hold on, hold on,
see, the "we are armed" thing.
That is a problem for you.
Put down your guns. Come out.
SKINNER: Hello?
Skinner, it's Scully. I'm with Mulder.
Listen to me, Scully.
MAN". You don't have much “me.
Surrender. I can't explain
on an open line, but I can't help you right now.
MAN:
Waiting!
The only chance you have
is to put down your weapons and surrender.
[LINE BEEPING]
You know what you did.
MULDER:
We defended ourselves.
MAN:
Yeah, yeah, that's what they all say.
But see, they were wearing body cams.
You know how that turns out
for the ones who weren't.
Skinner says surrender.
Why should we surrender? To who?
I don't know.
Why are we under suspicion?
Identify yourselves or we'll be forced
to consider you hostile agents...
...and respond with deadly action
and the aggressive action.
Identify ourselves? No.
We don't need to identify ourself.
What world are you living in?
[GRUNTING]
[MEN YELLING IN RUSSIAN]
[MAN 1 SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
[DANA PANTING]
MAN 2 [IN RUSSIAN]
MAN 3
MAN 2
[IN ENGLISH]
Where's your phone, bro?
Easy for Orwell to say.
"I want to believe."
Here's what I believe.
We would've all saved lots of money
and headaches if we only knew...
...that Americans would have been
just fine losing the Cold War.
If they could only
make a little money off of it.
You guys there, find his phone.
You two, watch these two.
Once we find his phone--
[MEN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[LANGLY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER CELL PHONE]
[MEN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
Hold on, hold on. Hold on.
MAN: Shh, shh.
[STATIC OVER CELL PHONE]
[LANGLY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER CELL PHONE]
[STATIC]
LANGLY".
This is Richard Langly.
Richard Langly.
Ringo Langly, I need to know.
Well, well, well, Ringo.
Am I dead?
You're never going to know.
And neither will these two.
[GRUNTING]
[GUN FIRING]
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[MEN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[MEN YELLING IN RUSSIAN]
[YELLING CONTINUES IN RUSSIAN]
Surrender?
Give up?
WALTER:
I'm risking my own ass being out here.
Who are they? Why are you so afraid?
They're not U.S. Intelligence,
I'll tell you that much.
The commander was Russian.
Skinner, tell us who they are.
It's Perlu Services.
American security contractor
with headquarters in Moscow.
A private contractor
has ascendancy over the FBI?
When they're a classified security directive.
From the Executive Branch.
I thought they were questioning you guys,
why would they want to kill you?
You tell us.
They're not supposed to kill
Intelligence agents, but apparently they will.
You need to come with me.
[EXHALING]
Do you have any money?
Take it.
It's all I have on me.
Is Langly alive?
Lone Gunman Langly?
You and I buried him in Arlington
along with Byers and Frohike.
You didn't answer my question.
L just did.
He's buried in Arlington.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
MAN:
Hack Mulder's phone.
Find out how he contacted Mulder.
[LAUGHING OVER CELLPHONE]
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
Kill switch.
Here's Byers.
Frohike.
What are we looking for, Mulder?
Knowing Langly, bread crumbs.
[SCULLY SIGHS]
MULDER:
His birthdate is wrong.
October 13th, we shared the same birthday.
Byers was born on the day
Kennedy was assassinated, so that's correct.
Frohike.
1945.
Frohike look 57 to you when he died?
Frohike looked 57 the day he was born.
His birthday is the same day that FDR died.
So Langly, March 28, 1969.
Any president die that day?
Eisenhower.
Who needs Google when you got Scully?
Right?
Heh.
Well...
...JFK was the 35th president,
Eisenhower was the 34th president, FDR--
Now you're just showing off, really.
The--
Thirty-two.
Thirty-second president.
Thirty-two, 34, 35.
Thirty-second, 34th, 35th, anything in that?
You mean, other than the fact
that the 33rd is missing?
Thirty-third? Three and three?
Three up, three down, three over?
Well, he's facing this way.
One...
...two...
...three, I'll go this way.
MULDER:
All right.
Scully.
This is it.
I watched his funeral.
From a thousand yards away.
Over there, through binoculars.
Deep Throat.
I didn't know his real name until right now.
I never visited out of respect, I guess.
1994.
He's dead because the world
was so dangerous and complex, then.
Who'd have thought
we'd look back with nostalgia...
...and say that was a simpler time, Scully?
Everything we feared came to pass.
How the hell did that happen?
Mulder, Deep Throat was assassinated
eight years before the Lone Gunmen died.
How and why
would Langly leave bread crumbs at a grave...
...in a graveyard that he didn't even know
he was gonna be buried in?
This cross...
...it's different from all the others.
It's not engraved. It protrudes.
What is that?
Mm-hm.
Wait.
Thank you, Skinner.
I think it's a Memory Medallion.
You scan it, and it links to a video
of the pet or person.
But I don't have my phone to scan it.
Mulder...
...do gravediggers work at night?
[GRUNTING]
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
I'm gonna open an X-file
on this bran muffin.
I gotta get to the bottom
of why it's so freaking good.
I don't care if it came out of an alien's butt,
I'm gonna eat the whole thing. Mm.
MULDER:
All right.
New Yorkers call it
the Long Lines Building.
Edward Stone documents indicate
the building, code name Titanpointe...
...was used as an NSA surveillance station
in a program code-named, Blarney.
It was started in the '70s
and expanded after 9/11.
Why? Why did he point us
to the NSA program?
Why didn't he tell us
it was about a building?
I opened an X-file on this building
in the '90s.
Langly actually provided
the initial information, we should check it out.
It?
An X-file?
Mm-hm.
You mean the X-files that are in our office
that we can't get into kind of X-file?
Right.
0K8)'-
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
Don't get in.
Put the weapon down, Mulder.
Can't do that, sir. You seem to be working
with people who tried to kill us.
I don't work with them.
The world is different, Mulder.
When Scully started, it was just us.
Dark forces in the U.S. government,
there was barely a Russia.
Now there's 17 U.S. intelligence agencies.
Homeland Security, Russian FSB...
...Chinese MSS, ISIS, al Qaeda,
Blackwater.
Private companies launched
to the space station.
All of them are in bed with one another,
while trying to exterminate each other.
And that includes each of us.
We need your help, Walter.
Even if we don't trust you.
What is this?
How did we get here?
What about us?
We were the ones who were just assaulted.
We can't go to our home.
They'll be waiting for us at our office.
We're not asking
for you to get us out of this.
But we do expect your help.
We need to see the X-files.
If you wanna see the X-files,
you don't have to go to the office.
WALTER:
After the X-files were closed in 2002...
...the Agency lobbied Director Mueller
for jurisdiction over the files.
They were looking to cross-reference
their own past research in telekinesis...
...MK-ULTRA, remote viewing,
with your fieldwork.
The agency then contracted
a private company...
...to digitize and maintain the files online...
...for any U.S. intelligence agencies
to have classified access.
A private contractor. Perlu?
So the Russians who tried to kill us
have had access to all of our work?
When the X-files were reopened,
why weren't we told?
Why didn't you tell us?
The X-files belonged to us.
SCULLY:
Do you work with them?
Do you work for them?
You two were gone.
I was left here. I didn't know
if you were coming back...
...and the files are too important
to sit in a basement gathering dust.
And what's in them...
...belongs to everyone.
That's the point of them.
Control of the X-files reverted back
to the FBI after the files were reopened.
[WALTER SIGHS]
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
WALTER:
Yeah? Right.
[SIGHS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
All the files on NSA Project Blarney
and the Titanpointe Building are gone.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Langly has been bleached from the X-files.
Not just the person, but any information...
...Langly contributed
to theoretical computer science.
Byers and Frohike are still in here.
Cryptographic protocols, machine learning,
quantum algorithms, all gone.
All right, thanks.
I had the Director speak
with the Executive Branch...
...to call this off, but the...
The Bureau's not in good standing
with the White House these days.
How do you like that?
The FBI finally found out what it's like
to be looked upon as a little spooky.
KARAH: Okay. So complete the two problems
and e-mail me your solutions by Friday.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
We're old friends of Richard Langly.
I figured if I...
...hadn't seen you in five years,
then I never would and I could...
...stop regretting.
We received a message on my cell.
Asking if he was alive.
You should go. They're watching.
Who is watching?
Perlu Services.
They came to us 15 years ago...
...with the science and the math
to prove that we could live forever.
The contract states
we can live out our natural lives.
We could continue our work
after we die.
And where is Richard now?
They brought us to a facility,
and over a two-week period...
...they scanned and copied
the salient features of our biological brain.
They uploaded us into a simulation.
The two minds could never exist at once.
Our simulated selves
would come into consciousness...
...in that life once we died in this.
And so did he instruct you
to leave this for us?
He entrusted me in case he discovered
that they had lied about life in the simulation.
And if Richard is reaching out,
then they must have.
We wanted a life eternal together.
So we took the deal.
But we theorized what to do
if it was not what they had offered.
How would that life know
it was a simulation?
There would be cheats.
The stars and the moon,
they wouldn't be fully realized.
The background people
wouldn't be fully rendered.
They'd constrict the use of technology,
of two-way contact to control them.
But Richard being Richard,
hacked a way to reach out.
Why reach out to me if you're alive?
Memory...
...isn't erased, it's suppressed.
They've probably theorized,
as we have, that their lives are a simulation...
...that perhaps Richard's subconscious...
...must have recalled the two of you
investigating this type of subject matter.
Remember, he saw Mulder in his dreams.
Who hasn't?
[FOX CLEARS THROAT]
Perlu is likely aware
that Richard is reaching out to you...
...to expose a simulation.
Is there anything we can do
to help Langly get through?
Do you have the cell?
No, it was taken from us.
I phreaked my phone years ago...
...using video signal manipulation
to my cell.
We'd have to help him
by making this side easier to reach.
You're gonna have to edit the SIM card
to your number and follow these steps...
...for the phone so that you can con--
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
Mulder, that's evidence.
He's evidence.
[EXHALES]
[THE RIVERAS' "CALIFORNIA SUN"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Sorry.
MAN 1: Come on.
It's been a-- It's been a long day.
Tough day. Thank you.
MAN 2:
Freaking out here.
Scully, you looked so adorbs
just there.
All curled up in a ball
in the booth of a skanky bar...
...with your fingers wrapped around
the grip of an assassin's Glock.
Well, I'm going out west where I belong
I did what I could
to follow Dr. Hamby's algorithms...
...and I added
what little I know about phreaking...
...and we have to wait and see
if we receive another transmission.
But they knew Langly
was trying to reach us.
They knew Dr. Hamby knew about
Langly and the computer simulations.
The longer we leave the phone on,
the sooner they're gonna find us.
So I gotta turn it off,
and we gotta move to different spots.
[STATIC]
Oh.
Scully.
Is this Mulder?
Yes, it's-- It's Mulder.
It is Mulder.
Is that Langly?
Richard Langly?
It's Mulder and Scully.
Scully?
Dana ?
Dana Scully?
MULDER: Heh.
Yeah.
But I'm not real, though. That right?
You are real, and I'm not?
Dr. Hamby told us you were in a simulation.
Ah. Hmm...
Mulder, it's like I designed heaven.
I eat hot dogs and doughnuts all daylong.
No one here ever dies
of cancer or Alzheimer's.
And The Ramones are here.
And they don't fight.
Every night they get on-stage
and they play "California Sun."
And I circle the mosh pit
like they do on the West Coast.
There's consensual sex
without blame or judgment.
Oh, and the New England Patriots are here
and they never, ever win.
Even.
And I'm begging you, destroy it.
We're living a lie here.
It's a work camp. We're digital slaves.
They take our uploaded minds
to develop science...
...that only the elite will use
to leave your world.
We turn theories of space colonization
into realities for them.
We dream,
but we're not allowed to have dreams.
Goals, nothing for ourselves.
No choice, no diversity.
[SIGHS]
There's a-- There's a wall around this place,
and the stars are fake. Hmm.
And the sunlight has no warmth.
[SIGHS]
And all the great minds that have died
since they realized this place are here.
Steve Jobs.
Marvin Minsky. Michael Crichton.
They all hate it here.
They don't even know who they are.
What we were in that life
is completely opposite from what we are here.
Go to the Long Lines Building. Titanpointe.
Please, for all of us. Shut this down.
MULDER:
Travel guides for NSA personnel...
...to Titanpointe for Blarney operations
were included in the Snowden leaks.
NSI and FBI personnel could not carry
identification to or in the building.
You'd have to arrange for a meeting
a week prior...
...and confirm with the program
director 24 hours before.
That's what we're sure of.
What we're not sure of is--
Whether they serve mimosas on the bus?
Ow.
High five, Scully.
That was fun.
Uh--
Are you kidding me?
Langly believed there was a tunnel
between Titanpointe...
...and the FBI Field Office
a few blocks away.
You think we can get in there looking
like this without raising suspicion?
You look good.
[GUARD SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[DANA CLEARS THROAT]
I'm a bit tied up here to flash you my ID,
but Special Agent Scully...
...XFO71261, Washington Field Office.
I can take him upstairs to Holding.
No, I'm taking him to Titanpointe.
The NSA guys wanna question him.
It would help
if you could get us in the tunnel.
[CHUCKLES]
After you drop him off, maybe you'll
come back and repay the favor.
[DOOR BEEPS]
[LOCK BEEPS]
It's easier getting him through
without cuffs.
I'm not uncuffing him. This guy's
like Hannibal Lecter-level psycho.
[FOX CLICKING TONGUE]
So, hon...
...what's your home office?
Sorry, bro. Married to the Bureau.
All right.
If they're waiting outside the elevator doors
when they open, that's it...
...so I'm guessing the computer simulation
is housed on one of the upper floors...
...by an exhaust opening.
But there are 29 floors.
Mm-hm.
Twenty-six, 28. What's after 28?
Thirty, 32, 34, 36, 38...
MAN 1: There they are!
MAN 2: Over there!
[MEN YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN 1:
Follow her.
[GRUNTING]
MAN 2:
Go! Down the stairs!
[MAN 3 SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[GRUNTING]
What are you running for?
Ain't you heard, FBI Mulder?
You're on our side now.
[DOOR BEEPS]
I'll confess.
After our last encounter...
...I was disappointed by you.
I didn't get your value to Mr. Y.
But he explained that we'd meet over
and over and then I'd...
...change my opinion.
In the last few days,
I've seen your instinct for survival.
Well, now that I've won you over,
you'll stop sending assassins to kill us?
We've really turned a corner.
Easy. You have a way to go, Fox.
Or rather, you need to change
how you look at all this.
You're still refusing
to answer the question of your father.
You don't understand
what's about to happen.
PRICE: Our world is a progression of one life
being replaced by another, over and over.
This is what's really meant by evolution.
And this series of replacements...
[GRUNTING]
...isn't about this is black, and this white.
This is male, and this female.
This is rich, and this poor.
This is chaos, and this--
Control.
[CHUCKLES]
Now that you understand that...
...what you really need to know is this:
Life on this Earth, all human life,
most animal life, is about to be crushed.
Burned to the ground.
The computer simulator down the hall
is necessary for our evolution as a species.
When we leave this planet,
this life will have evolved into that.
PRICE: Of the hundreds of extraordinary minds
uploaded into that world...
...the only one that figured out
it was living in a computer simulation...
...had 7 billion choices
to contact in this world.
[PANTING]
And the one person
Laugh] reached out to was you.
MULDER:
Mm.
And to think,
my company advised killing you.
But now that you are once again
in front of me, and aware of the simulation...
...I believe you won't want to destroy it.
Not when you understand
the good it's doing.
Its reason for being
is to advance life, not end it.
If I were to change my course of action...
...and terminate my father...
...would I be able
to upload to the simulation?
And could Agent Scully be with me?
PRICE:
It won't be her.
And it won't be you.
And we can upload a mind now
through any smartphone.
No one's even aware we're doing it.
We can take a piece of your mind
anytime you make a call.
Painless.
Heh.
Two hours.
Painless, except we have to die.
Heh. One of our best incentives here
is that you and loved ones don't ever die.
So if you upload me through my phone,
I don't really have a choice.
Sure you do.
You could not use your phone.
[CHUCKLES]
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I want to believe.
But...
...I would just like to--
To see it.
PRICE: Very few have ever seen it,
and those that do, don't realize what it is.
It's just a client server.
Wires, lights, why do you need to see it?
It's the closest I'll get to seeing God.
In this life.
Or that.
[DOOR BEEPS]
Stop. Face to the wall.
[DOOR BEEPING]
Inside.
[GRUNTING]
[DANA PANTING]
Why do you operate so well
with your hands cuffed behind your back?
As if you didn't know.
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTING]
[WHIRRING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[ALARM COTINUES BLARING]
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[BEEPING]
Bye-bye, Ringo.
[POWERING DOWN]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
I'm armed.
[DANA SIGHS]
Hi.
What?
You Okay?
Got my phone back.
The simulator is down.
0K8)'-
Let's bring him back through
the tunnel to the FBI Field Office.
Come back with some
cyber forensics agents and then...
...start a case against Erika Price.
0K8)'-
Oh, I thought I was going to throw up
for a second, but I'm okay.
[DOOR BEEPS]
They're gone.
[DOOR BEEPING]
[DANA SIGHS]
[FOX slel-ls]
[STATIC]
LANGLY".
Mulder? Mulder!
They know that we know.
Destroy the backup.
Mulder, I'm afraid. Mulder--
[STATIC]
One, two, three, four!
In the warm California sun