[EKG BEEPING]
DOCTOR:
He was just brought in, 3O minutes ago.
Nine fifteen p.m., respiration 17,
body temp 97.6.
Heart rate--
Just give me a 22 scalpel.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
They are dosing us, folks.
I know what you're asking.
Why would they dose us?
Why would they use these planes?
It's the same reason that chemtrails...
[EKG BEEPING]
[RETRACTOR CREAKING]
[FLATLINING]
Lord Jesus Christ, son of God,
have mercy on me, a sinner.
Wait, pancreas looks bad.
It might be infected.
Just leave it.
[SNIFFS]
Shame to waste a good pancreas.
It's ready.
[JULIET GRUNTS]
Those who love me, I will deliver.
[GRUNTS]
Go, go, go!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Tell me where they are.
I don't know. I'm not part of them.
[BONE CRACKS]
I need medical attention.
Ugh.
Whosoever commits sin is the servant of sin.
Last chance to save your soul.
Where are they?
I told you. I don't know.
Those who love me, I will deliver.
Ugh!
[SIREN WAILING]
Oh, jeez.
[CHOIR SINGING IN LATIN]
PRIEST: We break this bread
to share in the body of Christ.
We being many are one body
for we all share in one bread.
These are the gifts of God.
For the people of God.
Whoever eats my flesh
and drinks my blood has eternal life...
...and I will raise them up at the last day.
For my flesh is true food...
...and my blood is true drink.
Whoever eats my flesh
and drinks my blood remains in me...
...and I in them.
ALL:
Praise be to God.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
PRIEST:
Go in the peace of Christ.
And may Almighty God bless you.
The Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
[SOBBING]
Special Agent Dana Scully.
This is Special Agent Fox Mulder.
We didn't request help
from the Washington Bureau.
Well, we found reasons to become interested.
Look, we know your reputation.
You come into a case,
take over, turn it upside down.
No, we like to think we uncover facets
that would otherwise go unnoticed.
You guys ID this gentleman?
His name is Robert Jenkins, 23.
Trainer at Brooklyn Heights Fitness.
He was abducted after work.
Roommate hadn't seen him in 18 hours.
Both victims have metal dowels
impaled through their sternums.
Staked through the heart, you mean?
I would've expected the weapon
to be made of wood.
A combination of the three types
used in Christ's crucifixion cross:
Cypress, cedar and pine.
That would imbue it with the holy properties
necessary to defeat evil.
Looks like you guys are up to speed.
We've got our own stuff we need to attend to.
We'll leave you to it.
You did that on purpose.
You think?
But there are multiple cases here, Scully.
This victim was murdered by these two.
Who, in turn, were murdered
by someone else in a style...
...familiar to fans of Hammer horror films.
Of which, I am one, guilty.
The question is why
were the organs harvested?
There were about three-quarters
of a million dollars' worth of organs...
...left in the cooler
outside the emergency room.
Which tells me that whoever killed these two
did not do it for material gain.
"I will repay" was written on the cooler.
Sounds like a motive.
Yeah.
But whoever took the organs
is not familiar with transplant procedures.
That no hospital is gonna take those organs.
But maybe we can find a use for them.
Someone went to a lot of trouble
just to let them go.
The cooler that was left at the hospital
was missing the liver and pancreas.
A liver has a "need to use" time limit on it.
I'll run a check on hospitals doing liver
transplants over the next seven to 20 hours.
I'll go on some onion sites
and see if any organs were put up for auction.
Are those new?
Bifocals?
They're not bifocals.
They're progressives.
They're called progressive lenses.
No need to get defensive.
I'm not defensive.
Presbyopia is a natural part...
...of the aging process.
We're all gonna go through it, Mulder.
Just wait till you get gout.
Gout.
You know, sometimes I wonder
why we keep doing it, Scully...
...in the face of all this indifference
and presbyopia.
Did you get your hair cut?
Are you kidding me?
[WOMAN PRAYING IN SPANISH]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[WOMAN SOBBING]
[WOMAN CONTINUES PRAYING
IN SPANISH]
[WOMAN CONTINUES SOBBING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING OVER TV]
[WOMAN CHUCKLES]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[MOANING SOFTLY]
[FAN WHIRRING]
[MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]:
It's The Barbara Beaumont Show.
Tonight's episode, "The Lion Tamer."
I love this episode.
[AUDIENCE CLAPPING ON TV]
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
It's as funny now as it was 5O years ago.
A simple misunderstanding.
Uh-huh.
I can explain everything.
JOE". Honey, is this gonna take long?
I'm trying to finish this book.
Well, I can start in the middle.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING ON TV]
JOE".
Start at the end.
BARBARA: All right.
All right.
We owe the city $20G...
...for creating a public nuisance...
...the lion tamer $75 for the sick lion...
...the grocer $5 for the 1O pounds of meat...
...and the shoe shine boy a stick of gum.
[LAUGHING]
Do you wanna hear the details?
JOE".
I'm afraid I do.
Thought you might.
No. I mean...
...that's what I should've been afraid of
when I said "I do."
Oh, honey, you can't live without me.
I can barely afford to live with you.
I just have one question, Barbara. Why?
Well, like I said, it's simple, really.
I do it just for kicks.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
[MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
Well, like I said, it's simple, really.
I do it just for kicks.
[BELL TOLLING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Well, I didn't burst into flames
when I crossed the threshold...
...so I guess they really do forgive a lot.
In the last 24 hours,
there have been 12 liver transplants...
...in a 450-mile radius,
all of the donors have been accounted for.
Well, I checked the dark web
and there's no organs for sale in this region.
But the dead surgeon, uh...
...Doctor-- Oh, God, help me.
Sorry.
Rednon. Dr. David Rednon
had his medical license revoked for...
...over-prescribing opioids
to bratski krug drug dealers.
Russian mob.
And the kid that was with him
was a street-level gangster.
I think we should hand this over
to the NYC Organized Crime division, Mulder.
I don't think this is an X-File.
I'm gonna need some time here.
I can meet up with you later,
or you can wait for me.
PRIEST:
Juliet.
Yes.
[SIGHS]
Uh... Where's the rest of it?
Where's the rest of it?
[ALL GASP]
Cat got your tongues?
You were all broken when I found you.
Crippled, malformed.
And I gave you hope.
What do you see when you look at me?
ALL:
Beauty and light.
And what do I see when I look at you?
ALL: Ugliness and pain.
No.
I see love and obedience.
I see the promise of what will be.
We have all worked too hard...
...and sacrificed so much.
Each one of us, transformed by the genius...
...of Dr. Luvenis.
That's why we should all
be so disappointed.
Where is my heart?
Where are my lungs?
There was a problem at the harvest.
Someone attacked us.
She killed Dr. Dave with a metal stake.
I escaped with what I could.
I'm sure you did the best you could.
[WHIMPERS]
I need a word with you.
PRIEST:
You have to have faith, Juliet.
Faith that through Him,
your sister Olivia will return to you.
I'll pray for her.
And you.
No, Father.
Prayers aren't enough.
I will make mine arrows drunk with blood,
and my sword shall devour flesh...
...and that with the blood of the slain
and of the captives...
...from the beginning of revenges
upon the enemy.
Juliet--
Look at this, Scully. Today's scripture,
Romans 12:19.
"Vengeance is mine, I will repay."
That's what was on the organ cooler.
Well, it's a common biblical passage.
Did I ever tell you
how I came to believe in God?
No.
When my brother Charlie was a baby...
...he got seriously ill.
I think I was about 4.
I later learned that it was rheumatic fever.
Hmm.
Every night, Morn would tell us
to get on our knees and pray for his recovery.
Your prayers were answered. He lived.
Only, after the first couple nights,
I wasn't praying for him.
I was praying for a puppy.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
And we got one that Christmas.
I thought God had performed a miracle.
I finally know why I'm not a Christian, Scully.
My parents never got me a puppy.
So are you praying for another miracle now?
I don't know if I believe in miracles.
But I do know the power of faith.
I saw it in my morn,
the strength that she received.
I could use some of that strength now.
[SIGHS]
I need what you have.
You always bear north, Mulder.
No matter which way
or how hard the wind blows against you.
I think all I have...
...all any of us have...
...are the results
of all the choices that we've made.
And at the end of the day,
we just hope that we made the right one.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Mulder, it's locked.
I will repay.
There's three bars missing.
Someone is literally using the church
to exact vengeance.
[GROANS]
One day without my dinnie, and look at me.
I can already see the lines.
I wanna cry.
You look perfectly beautiful.
Not a day over 33,
when I first fell in love with you.
That's sweet.
[MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
You don't look bad for an 85-year-old.
All thanks to Kayla.
She's my angel.
You're my addiction, Dr. Luvenis.
I will be a worthy companion to you
in no time.
I'm beginning to wonder.
No one could've predicted
what happened last night.
But I have a friend at the hospital.
He's heard rumors about recovered organs,
organs they can't use.
Our organs.
Your excuses...
...don't solve the problem.
I will find them.
Attached to Kayla? Heh-heh.
I don't think so.
Barbara--
I think you'll agree...
...that failure should not be rewarded.
Kayla...
...I think you're ready to ascend.
I am?
Mm-hm.
Do you trust me?
Have I ever lied to you?
No.
You're living proof.
That's right.
Close your eyes.
Barbara, please.
Tell me your dream.
I wanna be beautiful like you.
All right, my ugly duckling...
...prepare to be a swan.
[SIGHS]
[KAYLA GASPING AND CHOKING]
[GRUNTS]
[LUVENIS EXHALES]
LUVENIS:
Hmm.
There. She looks better than ever.
We'll eat her for now.
Her organs are already depleted.
So find me what I need...
...before we both start looking our age.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Mrs. Bocanegra? I'm Special Agent Fox Mulder,
this is Special Agent Scully.
We're from the FBI.
We'd like to ask a few questions.
You have news about my Olivia?
We spoke to Father Hardy at St. Joseph's.
He said your daughter has been missing
for almost two months?
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
If we can come in, we might find something
that would help us find your daughter.
No. You can't come in.
Sorry, but we're trying to help.
Olivia doesn't wanna be found.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Mom, the truth is Olivia couldn't stand looking
at that girl staring back at her in the mirror.
She rejected her family and God.
She joined a cult.
If she's being held against her will...
...we can investigate and try and extract her.
I know my sister. All right?
She doesn't want our life.
To her, we're monsters.
She thinks she can change who she is
and become something she will never be.
I've given up on her.
Have you?
Or Will you repay?
The cult your sister's in may be involved
in illegal trafficking of human organs...
...or using them for unnatural purposes.
I believe you know that.
That's why you're trying to find her.
You wanna save her.
You have to leave.
Father Hardy was afraid somebody might be
tempted to take the law into their own hands.
Become an avenger.
I want her to be found...
...so my mother will stop crying.
That's all.
DANA:
You think she's involved?
FOX:
I think she is. My gut tells me she is.
My gut doesn't need glasses.
[CAR DOORS CLOSE]
[GRUNTS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
There was nothing in her.
No sustenance. No nutrients.
You ruined her.
Kayla was as good as junk food.
Look at me. Hmm?
What do you see?
You look as beautiful as ever.
Liar!
Barbara, this a dark time.
No one is eating well.
We need healthy organs.
Why can't we use one of them?
These children are our seeds.
You don't eat the seeds,
you eat the fruit from the trees.
Stop talking to me like I'm an idiot.
You know I'm not a scientist.
LUVENIS:
But I am. Barbara, we've talked about this.
The blood and organs in these children
is being restructured...
...every time they drink their dinnie.
But cell adhesion is not yet complete.
Their morphogenesis is not finished.
But then when they're ready...
...and they are surgically attached to you...
...then you are gonna reap the benefits
of reverse aging.
Hmm.
Remember? Remember Dylan
when he was attached to you?
Mm.
You glowed like a 20-year-old.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, I remember Dylan.
He wouldn't shut up.
I'm glad we ate him.
All of this is for you.
Don't do anything rash.
I have a lead on the organs
left at the hospital.
I'm gonna go get them for you.
Mm.
I saw marionette lines in the mirror.
WARREN:
Barbara?
I hate to see you down.
You make us happy.
I was hideous,
but you saved me, gave me joy.
I wanna make you happy.
I'll be dinnie.
Because if I'm in you...
...I will always be happy.
Oh, Warren. Warren, Warren.
Oh.
You are such a beautiful person.
Because of what you have offered me...
...I'm going to do something
very, very special.
For you.
Come on.
I am going to perform my favorite song.
I sang this song
on the Sonny and Cher Comedy Hour in 1973.
And they told me that at the time
it was the highest-rated show they'd ever had.
Higher than Charo or Muhammad Ali.
[CHUCKLES]
It also won an Academy Award that year.
Maureen McGovern made it famous...
...but people tell me
that they like my version better.
And so, Warren, to you I say...
There's got to be a morning after
If we can hold on through the night
We have a chance to find the sunshine
So keep on looking for the light
[SCREAMING]
Oh, can't you see the morning after?
It's waiting right outside the storm
Why don't we cross the bridge together?
And find a place that's safe and warm
[WARREN GASPING]
It's not too late
We should be giving...
[BLENDER WHIRRING]
We're moving closer to the shore
I've got to be there by tomorrow
And we'll escape the darkness
We won't be searching anymore
[GULPING]
There's got to be a morning after
JOE: Whoops.
BARBARA: Aah.
You're in an awful hurry this morning, Joe.
Honey, I'm in a pickle.
I forgot it's Mr. Morris' birthday.
I don't want to be a suck-up...
You're interrupting my prep.
I have to memorize my lines.
"Double Trouble."
You've seen this a thousand times.
[GASPS]
How dare you?
I had to break in to the cold storage
at the hospital to get this.
You did that for me?
Everything I do.
Well, I know exactly what you need.
Olivia.
It's your day to be beautiful.
FOX:
They're here, Scully.
The organs are somewhere inside.
You were right. They need those organs.
It was easy enough
to put a tracker in the heart.
But harder to get the hospital
to loosen their security so they could steal it.
MAN:
No vacancy.
Open the door. Federal agents.
[LOCKS CLICKING]
[EKG BEEPING]
Olivia, if you can hear me,
I want you to count backwards from 100.
One hundred.
Ninety-nine.
Ninety-eight.
All right, Calvin, you may begin.
Cut the back to expose
the descending aorta.
The only people living here
are on the fourth floor.
What do you know about the tenants?
The only person I know is Barbara Beaumont.
She's owned this building
for over 4O years.
Barbara...
[GROANING]
Barbara Bea Beaumont. Child actor.
Our Gang shorts.
Gentlemen Prefer Blondes.
TV Westerns. Dragnet.
The Barbara Beaumont Show, 1967.
Then, um...
...nothing much ever again.
So at 85, does she need assistance?
I don't know. Look, I've never met her.
Never even seen her.
Once a while I get a note to go up and fix stuff.
I never see nobody when I go up there.
But I know they're there.
Just from the smell.
Husband of 22 years died of leukemia,
1970.
Joined a Life Extension "commune"
in northern California.
Married a Dr. Randolph...
...Luvenis, Luvenis, Luvenis.
How long have you been a super here?
Seven years.
Seven years, and you've never talked to her?
All right, it's weird.
But this is the Bronx.
There's an envelope full of money
in my mailbox every two weeks.
First time there's been a problem.
Seven years and you've never crossed paths?
She don't go out the front.
What about the people on the fourth floor?
They ever leave?
This building is 1890s.
It's got, like, a dumb waiter system.
It's been modified, long before I ever got here.
Like trap doors and ladders.
It goes out the basement,
then the sewers and the subway.
These people never see the light of day.
Every room's got one.
[EKG BEEPING]
Now connect the two valves and sew us up.
[WHIRRING]
[MOANING]
Miss Barbara Beaumont? Federal agents.
We have reason to believe
someone inside...
...may be in possession
of contraband human organs.
We tracked a signal to this apartment.
I guess we'll go away
and get a search warrant.
We'll be back.
[LOCK CLICKS]
BARBARA: Hello.
FOX: Hello.
I'm Special Agent Mulder,
this is Special Agent Scully with the FBI.
Oh.
And you are?
Well, you tell me.
I'm sorry. Can you tell us your name?
Haven't you seen
The Barbara Beaumont Show?
Gentlemen Prefer Blondes?
Loved you on Dragnet.
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
Everyone says
that was their favorite episode.
Did you know Jack Webb?
I did not.
I'm sorry, but we're looking
for Barbara Beaumont.
[CHUCKLING]
Don't-- You--
You--
You really don't recognize me? It's--
I'm Barbara. I'm Barbara Beaumont.
We're looking for an 85-year-old woman.
Yes, well...
...I look good for my age, don't I? Heh.
I keep it dark in here,
not because I'm trying to hide anything.
I believe women should have
a little bit of mystery.
Sunlight is strictly verboten.
It's terrible for the skin.
You should be careful, darling.
If it's not already too late.
DANA:
Okay.
We're also looking for this woman,
Olivia Bocanegra.
Is she a Netflix executive?
[BARBARA CHUCKLES]
Oh, yes, let's get our selfie
and then you can be on your way.
DANA:
This is her. Have you seen this woman?
No. No.
Scully.
No.
No, no, no!
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
Scully!
[SCREAMING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Those who love me, I will deliver.
No!
[SCREAMS]
[GASPING]
MAN:
No! Barbara!
Run! Run!
[PANTING]
I did repay.
My sister is here.
Scully! Scully!
Scully?
Scully!
Scully.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[DOOR CREAKING]
Let her go.
She's a part of me of her own volition.
You can ask her yourself if you like.
You've surgically attached yourself to the girl?
We're helping each other.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
LUVENIS: Have you ever asked yourself
what could be achieved...
...what would be possible if we were free
from government restraints...
...and regulations?
What have you achieved?
I found a cure for the greatest disease
to afflict mankind.
Every human being has a time bomb
built into their genes. I defused it.
Sarcopenia. Cardiomyopathy.
Presbyopia.
These are all just symptoms.
But through heterochronic parabiosis,
I have reversed time.
Olivia is my parabiont.
And together we are gonna cure
this horrible disease.
Age isn't a disease,
it's a natural progression.
I don't accept the premise
that we have to grow old.
She's having a seizure.
We gotta get you to the hospital.
This is what we want.
Your experiment is over.
Not unless you want her to die first.
The genie is out of the bottle.
We are all running out of time.
No!
I will deliver.
[OLIVIA PANTING]
JULIET: Olivia.
Juliet?
What are you doing here?
I came for you.
[BANGING]
FOX:
Scully?
DANA: Mulder.
Scully.
[GROANS]
Whew.
You stink.
Thanks, Mulder.
[SIGHS]
My fall was broken
by decade's worth of trash.
But I'm okay.
Don't feel sorry for me.
I know I'm going to prison...
...but I made a choice, it was mine.
I'd gladly trade my lifetime here
for an eternity in heaven.
[MRS. BOCANEGRA PRAYING IN SPANISH]
[CONTINUES PRAYING IN SPANISH]
[ORGAN PLAYING]
That must be a sign.
I'm all out of miracles.
Turn back. Give up.
Accept your place in the numbing embrace
of the status quo.
Mm-mm.
I will relight your candle...
...and extend your prayers through mine.
What prayers?
I can't tell you, they won't come true.
It's a prayer candle, Mulder,
not a birthday cake.
Mm-hm. Heh.
Prayers aren't meant to be sentiment.
It's a conversation.
You can do it like a meditation.
Or if your needs exceed your grasp...
...you can ask God to act on your behalf.
But you don't believe in God.
So you'd essentially be talking to yourself.
I may not believe in God,
but I believe in you.
Therefore, I speak to him through you.
So it's a transitive property of equality.
lfA equals B and B equals C...
...therefore A equals C.
Reason and faith in harmony.
Isn't that why we're so good together?
Are we together?
You know, I believed I could protect our son.
And I failed.
I believed that we could live together.
And I fled.
I gave up on that too.
If only you had fled earlier.
Do you know how many times
I've envisioned that scenario...
...where you left that basement office
before I even needed glasses?
You'd have your health...
...your dog...
...your sister.
You'd be Kersh's boss at the FBI.
You'd be married to some brain surgeon...
...and have a bunch of kids
that you wouldn't have to give up.
Mulder, I don't begrudge you
any of those things.
That's not what I was talking about.
What are you talking about, Scully?
Because I don't know if any God is listening,
but I am standing right here.
And I'm listening.
Right beside you.
I'm all ears.
That's my choice.
[CHOIR SINGING IN LATIN]
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
That's not my 4-year-old self
looking for a miracle.
That's my leap of faith forward.
And I'd like to do it together.
I've always wondered
how this was gonna end.