[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[MURMURING INDISTINCTLY]
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER RADIO]
For the next few hours,
this crate is all that matters.
Protect it like your Mama's in it.
Clear?
BOTH: Yes, sir!
Do not drop it, do not scratch it,
do not peek inside of it.
And for God's sakes,
you do not lose sight of it.
Is that clear?
BOTH: Yes, sir!
Quon will guide you to a site
east of Hill 862...
...where you're gonna deliver
this crate to Bravo Company.
Is that clear?
BOTH: Yes, sir!
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER RADIO]
MAN 1:
Three o'clock. Three o'clock.
Rendezvous back at the drop site
at approximately 1900 hours.
Is that clear?
[GUNS FIRING]
MAN 2: Now! Let's go!
Go! Go! Go!
[GRUNTS]
[GUNS FIRING]
[FIRING CONTINUES]
[WHIRRING]
You all right, John?
I'm scared as hell, man!
[BULLET WHIZZING]
Dude, look at me. Look at me.
Everybody's scared.
I got your back, and you got mine, okay?
Okay. Okay.
We go.
There's a village in there. Go.
WALTER:
Damn!
Go! GO!
[ALL SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Quon!
What are you doing?
He's been hit! I gotta go help him!
No, we gotta stay with the crate!
Please.
Stay put.
[GRUNTS]
[MAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GUNFIRE]
[MEN SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Quon.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
[YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE
CONTINUES]
WALTER: John.
John, where are you?
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
John?
Monsters.
John--
John. John, it's me.
John, it's me. It's Skinner!
Deputy Director Kersh.
I'm gonna ask you once and only once.
Where is he?
Sir, of whom are we speaking?
Cut the crap, agents.
Have you ever wondered why...
...after 35 years in the Bureau...
...Walter Skinner isn't sitting
on this side of the desk...
...or even perhaps running
this whole damn agency, for that matter?
Are you looking for Skinner?
Let me be unambiguous...
...in the event that there are any questions
about this in your conspiracy-addled minds.
Walter Skinner's stalled career...
...has everything to do
with his blind loyalty to the both of you...
...and your misguided search
for some imaginary truth.
Sir, what is this about?
Skinner's gone AWOL, Agent Mulder,
without warning or explanation.
And, frankly, I don't buy your naiveté,
not even a moment.
He hasn't been the same
since the two of you returned to the Bureau.
Sir, has anyone checked his apartment?
Could he have had a medical emergency?
The director's asking questions
about Skinner's activities that I can't answer.
There's some implication
that he recently started poking around...
...in places he shouldn't be poking.
What sort of places?
I couldn't say. But if you truly care
about his future in the FBI...
...I suggest you bring him back here
while he still has a future to return to.
What happened to the old reliable Skinner
we knew and loved?
Well, based on his behavior
the past couple months...
...it's safe to say
the old Skinner has left the building.
Mulder, do you think his disappearance
actually has to do with us?
Or something to do with William
or that business with the Purlieu Services?
There's no way of telling
what Skinner's been up to recently.
But I'll keep my eyes peeled
for cigarette butts.
Maybe he's out
meeting with an interior decorator.
No, I noticed this
the last time that we were here.
There are no personal items.
No mementos, no knickknacks...
...no family photographs.
It occurs to me
that even after all these years...
...we know precious little about
Walter Sergei Skinner beyond the professional.
It appears he may suffer
from moderate to severe constipation.
I'm sorry to be a wimp, Mulder,
but this just feels wrong.
This feels like a real invasion of his privacy.
Well, it's not like Skinner to just disappear
without telling anyone. You know?
As much as I don't trust the guy
right now...
...if he's gotten into a dangerous situation,
he's gonna forgive us this little trespass.
Look at this, Mulder.
"Lance Corporal Walter Skinner.
Third Battalion, Third Marines,
United States Marine Corps."
That's a peculiar way
to address it.
There's no return address.
Aah!
Is that a--?
Desiccated human ear.
There's a note.
"The monsters are here."
Monsters, Mulder.
Does that get your juices flowing?
As much as I appreciate any reference
to myjuices, Scully...
...my only concern here is for Skinner.
But now I'm worried about him.
Me, too.
FOX:
"The Mud Lick Messenger."
Mud Lick?
Well, this is strange. Based on the way
that package was addressed...
...I requested some basic information
about Skinner and his platoon in Vietnam...
...like names of his fellow Marines, et cetera...
Uh-huh.
...and I've just received word
that I've been denied access by the Bureau.
That the information is classified top secret.
Well, the sheriff here in Mud Lick says
he's got a body in the morgue minus an ear.
I'll bet you that that victim turns out
to be one of Skinner's platoon mates...
...from that classified list.
You ain't gonna find no kitten.
What?
Ain't no kitten out there.
No. All right.
SHERIFF: Doctor Matthew Wegweiser.
The victim was a medical doctor?
That's correct, ma'am. Doc Wegweiser is--
Was our one and only town doctor.
Terrific guy. Beloved.
Went out for a hike Thursday last,
never to return.
Mrs. Wegweiser told us he hiked
the same route several times a week.
We found him on the trail, got himself snared
in some kind of hunting trap.
A hunting trap?
How do you account for the severed ear?
Well, I can't, honestly.
And the missing teeth?
Missing teeth?
The autopsy says that he was missing...
...several upper and lower molars
...and a couple of bicuspids.
But there's no evidence
of advanced tooth decay or periodontitis.
No evidence of manual extraction.
FOX:
That mean something to you?
It's funny because I just happened to have lost
two teeth in the past month myself.
And my wife lost one yesterday.
We were puzzling over it at breakfast.
FOX:
Hmm.
The autopsy also says that
there were wood splinters inside the wound.
This hunting trap, did it have
some kind of a spear or stake element?
Yes, ma'am. It was a primitive whip trap.
It's a bent piece of bamboo
held by a trip wire.
There's a sharpened spear attached at the end.
It's a punji stick.
Pardon?
It's a simple spear
made of wood or bamboo.
It was used in Vietnam in any one
of a number of insidious traps or weapons.
Was Dr. Wegweiser here
by any chance a Vietnam vet?
I don't believe he was, no.
Are there any other Vietnam vets in town
that you know of?
Oh, sure. Yeah, there's an institution
outside of town called Glazebrook.
Lot of guys were sent up there after the war.
Lot of them stuck around when they got out.
I think we passed one on our way in.
Old Trigger Davis. He's harmless.
Trigger?
Is Glazebrook a mental hospital?
Right, ma'am, a government-run facility.
I'd like to see a list of past and current patients.
Do you have access to that?
Probably not.
They run a tight ship up there.
But I'll see what I can drum up.
Thank you, sheriff.
Anything to dispel the craziness
everyone in town is buzzing about.
What kind of craziness is that?
People are swearing they seen
some kind of monster out in the woods.
FOX:
Hmm.
[WHIMPERING]
[TWIGS RUSTLE]
[DOG BARKING]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
Pippet?
[DOG WHIMPERING]
Pippet. What is it, girl?
What is it?
[YELPS]
[DOG WHIMPERING]
SHERIFF:
Tell them what you told me, Ed.
Well, Banjo called me up and said he saw
a damn monster out here in his woods...
...and could I come with him
and look around.
We was having that look around
when he just straight disappeared.
Did you say Banjo?
Ozzy Krager. Friends call him Banjo.
This is his property.
Did he describe this monster?
Well, first he thought it was a bear,
shh, shh, shh, but then he saw big old horns.
And it was walking on two feet.
Same as people in town was talking about.
But Mr. Krager, I mean, Banjo,
was he a Vietnam vet?
Yeah, he was.
This may seem like an odd question,
but was he missing any teeth?
Yeah, he was.
He'd just keep losing them,
like he's an old man or something.
Well, I can't make much fun of him
because I been losing some, too.
What's this?
That's, uh, that's one of them deer cams.
Hunters use them for game surveillance.
They send an alert to your phone
when they detect movement.
Can we review what's on it?
Should be able to see it on a computer
back at the station.
Something about that camera
that's troubling you, sir?
Banjo don't have no deer cams.
I mean, at least none that I seen,
and I hunt with him, like, every week.
The camera is motion activated...
...so it shouldn't take terribly long
to find what we're looking for.
DANA:
Oh.
FOX:
There.
SHERIFF:
I don't believe it.
There's our killer.
Why do I get the distinct feeling
you two know who that man is?
That how it's gonna be?
I've been nothing but courteous to y'all,
and I don't appreciate being played a fool.
Excuse me. I gotta go tell my people
we found their monster.
Sheriff, that man is our boss.
Assistant Director Walter Skinner
of the FBI.
Well, what in the hell was he doing
at my crime scene last night?
That's what we're here to find out.
You're telling me you knew
that man was here all along?
Walter Skinner didn't do this.
He's a good man. He's a smart man.
He's been at the FBI for over 30 years,
and this murder's sloppy.
I mean, not that he's capable of murder.
But if he was, he certainly wouldn't get himself
caught on camera at a crime scene.
So tell me, what's your good man doing...
...standing over a dead body in the woods
in the middle of the night?
A body which he neglected to call in
to any law enforcement agency...
...including his own?
Well, I know it looks bad, sheriff,
but I assure you, he's not your man.
You can assure me all you want.
I'll decide who my man is...
...when I get a chance to bring him in
and have a conversation with him.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I gotta go
put out an APB for this Walter Skinner.
What are you doing?
There's more on that tape, Scully.
Put down an out all-points bulletin
for a Walter Skinner, white male, glasses...
Hurry up.
You're gonna get us run out of town.
SHERIFF:
--armed and dangerous.
[BEEPING]
What did we just see, Mulder?
We find that monster, we find Skinner.
Tell me you don't think that was some real,
actual monster we just saw.
For once, we agree.
Monsters don't dig pits and set traps.
That was a man in a mask.
I'm more concerned
about Skinner's state of mind right now.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Maybe Skinner's experiencing a delayed form
of PTSD from his time in Vietnam.
That's, uh, not without precedent.
And even the shock of receiving that ear
in the mail is a pretty plausible trigger.
What?
You said trigger.
Trigger. Banjo.
Kitten?
I already told you.
Yeah, you said I wouldn't find Kitten.
But is Kitten a person?
Is that somebody's nickname?
I told the eagle where to find Kitten's kitten.
The eagle. Hmm.
Is the eagle bald?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Hello?
Anybody here?
[CHUCKLES]
So I unload into this ditch, right?
And they're deader than a bag of tent stakes,
the whole lot.
And I kneel down next to this little one.
He's gotta be no more than 10, 12 years old.
And I'm about to add another
little adorable charm to my necklace.
I take out my Ka-Bar...
...I slice this little monster's ear off
like a hunk of Wisconsin cheddar.
SOLDIER 1:
Oh, man, Kitten.
But all of a sudden, he opens his eyes.
Screams like a banshee!
Takes off into the trees,
hollering the whole way!
[LAUGHING]
Uh.
You're bleeding, man.
SOLDIER 2 & 3:
Oh.
Dang. That's the third one this week.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, they got a tooth fairy in 'Nam?
WALTER: Get down!
Aah!
JOHN: Speak of the devil. Ha-ha-ha.
Whoo!
MAN:
What are you doing in my house?
John, is that you?
[CHUCKLES]
John.
I'm not John. I'm Davey.
Davey.
Well, you're John's son.
You're Walter Skinner.
That's right.
Father sure talks a lot about you.
Your father and I, heh,
we went through a lot together.
Calls you baby killer.
Where is your father, Davey?
Father says it's your fault
the way our life turned out.
Because of your testimony against him
after the war...
...Father spent 38 years in Glazebrook.
Until I got a letter from him last week,
I thought he was dead.
I spent years searching for him
after his trial, but they vanished him.
His records were sealed, even from me.
Who vanished him?
The same people responsible for turning him
from the good man he was into...
Into what?
I only wanna help him.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry, I don't believe he wants
your help, Walter Skinner.
Father told me all the stories
about his time in Vietnam.
DAVEY".
There were monsters in that jungle.
Because of his exposure
to an experimental weaponized gas...
[YELLING]
He wasn't crazy like you said
at his court-martial, but no one believed him.
Not even Mother.
No one except me.
Listen, Davey, I know what he saw.
I got a glimpse of it myself,
but it wasn't real.
It was the gas
using his own fear against him.
Your dad was exposed to a lot more of it
than I was, and it changed him.
I watched it happen.
And yet, you said nothing about that gas
at his trial?
Did you?
They'd let me visit him sometimes
up at Glazebrook.
I had to sign
all manner of non-disclosure documents.
Do you realize how painful it was for me...
...to see my father wasting away
at that sanitarium?
They kept him behind glass the whole time.
I couldn't even touch him.
I couldn't touch my own father.
How could you let that happen
to your friend?
I was forbidden to speak about the gas
at his court-martial.
I was following orders, doing
what my superiors commanded me to do.
I'm not saying it's right.
It's not.
And I have lived with the guilt
of that decision every moment since.
I think about him every day.
But you gotta understand,
your dad murdered innocent people.
And I know it was because of the gas.
I knew who he was before.
But the man it changed him into...
He was dangerous, Davey.
People are getting hurt again,
and we can stop it.
But you've got to believe
that I am here to help him.
I only wanna make things right.
Please...
...take me to him, Davey.
0K8)'-
I'll take you to him.
His name is John "Kitten" James.
He is or was, in fact,
a patient at Glazebrook Hospital.
But his military files, like the other files
I've tried to access, are classified.
You think it's true, Scully, what Kersh said?
What's that?
That we're the sole reason Skinner's career
hasn't advanced in 30-some years?
I hope not.
I'd like to believe that his choice
to stay loyal to us was exactly that, a choice.
But if there's one thing I know
about Walter Skinner...
...is he's a man ruled by his moral compass
above all else.
There was a time I would have
agreed with that unequivocally.
I realize that his conduct
has been strange...
...but don't you think we should give him
the benefit of the doubt...
...after everything we've been through?
I mean, especially in light of what we now
understand he may have sacrificed for us.
[SIREN WAILING]
Let's just hope we find him
before somebody else does.
WALTER: Where are we going, Davey?
It's not far now.
This is what they drove him to.
Oh, God. No, John, what have you done?
John.
[GRUNTS]
[CHUCKLES]
[WALTER GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
Now who sees monsters?
[DOG BARKING]
Help me! ls somebody out there?
Help!
Why ?
No!
DAVEY: Can I help you?
Special Agent Mulder.
Special Agent Dana Scully.
Are you related to John James?
I'm his son, Davey.
We're looking for a man who we believe
may be in the area...
...and may have served with your father
in Vietnam. Walter Skinner.
I don't believe
I've heard that name before, no.
Is your father home?
No, I'm sorry. I haven't a clue where he is.
I haven't seen him in weeks.
Is it okay if we come inside
for a brief moment?
We'd like to get some insight on a few things.
By all means.
Right this way.
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
Help!
I've never met real live FBI agents before.
Please.
Father said there's two refuges in life
from sorrow...
...music...
[CHUCKLES]
...and cats.
But I think cats are creepy.
[JOHN CALE'S
"FEAR ls A MAN'S BEST FRIEND" PLAYING]
Can I offer you some tea or something?
No, no, I'm good.
No, thank you.
Um... Mr. James, we understand
that your father was a patient at Glazebrook?
Yes, uh, that's right.
For many years.
And when was he released?
He was released one month ago.
On what grounds?
Sorry?
Why was he released after he had been
confined for so many years?
They determined that he was no longer
a danger to himself or anyone else.
Not that he ever was.
Well, I guess he was a threat to someone.
Is this your mother?
My mother died many years ago.
Father's incarceration was very hard on her.
Do you mind if I ask how she died?
Yes.
Mr. James, a minute ago you said
that your father was a threat to someone.
What did you mean?
Father had secrets.
Secrets?
About the government.
DAVEY: Father was poisoned
by an experimental weaponized gas in Vietnam.
Because of his exposure,
they continued to do tests on him...
...and other soldiers
for many years at Glazebrook.
What kind of tests?
Chemical and biological.
They were trying to learn
how to control human behavior.
Harnessing our fears
to manipulate us into violence.
[GRUNTING]
Using this weaponized gas?
The gas in the war
was still in the experimental stage.
And they still haven't perfected it.
But after years of testing it and honing it...
...they are getting close.
To what end?
Imagine the power of a government
that could literally control the minds...
...of millions of its citizens.
Influence every choice and decision they made
simply by exposing them to this poison.
You'll have to forgive me, Mr. James,
but this sounds like a dystopian novel.
It's happening right now
in the United States of America.
Do you honestly believe that after 3O years
of research and development...
...and decades of experimenting
on American heroes like my father...
...they would just be thrown in the trash?
Never to be utilized?
Unlikely. The DoD and the CIA
have been working on various incarnations...
...of mind-control projects since the '50s.
Project Bluebird, MK-ULTRA,
MK-DELTA.
Well, those programs were supposedly ended
in the early 1980s.
Supposedly.
My father believed he was part
of the program MK-NAOMI...
...which was a successor to MK-ULTRA.
We don't know how they're using
this chemical now, but we know that they are.
Maybe they're poisoning our water
or the food supply.
Maybe they're putting it in those chemtrails
behind all those commercial jets...
...that fly over our country every single day.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you, Mr. James.
[DOOR OPENS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
You drive.
What's going on, Mulder?
Let's just get in the car and drive away.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR DOORS CLOSE]
Mulder, you wanna tell me
what's going on?
He claims not to know who Skinner is,
but in the photo album...
...there were photos of his dad and Skinner
like they were BFFs.
And did you check out that SUV
parked beside the cabin?
Yeah, that definitely wasn't his.
Skinner could be back there.
Then why the hell are we driving away?
Just pull over here.
Get somewhere with cell reception,
call the sheriff...
...and get every available officer
down here.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna do for Skinner
what I'd hope he would do for us.
Mulder.
[MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
[NEEDLE SKIPPING]
WALTER:
Help!
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Come on.
Damn it.
WALTER:
ls somebody out there?
Hello?
Mulder?
Skinner.
[PANTING]
Get me the hell out of here.
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[FOX EXHALES]
I'll boost you up.
I'll boost you, you're good.
Here we go.
Davey. Davey, please. Let us out.
Let's do this quickly.
Come on.
[WALTER GRUNTING]
Gas. Ugh.
Davey. You don't have to do this.
[GUNSHOT]
Scully.
Where's Davey?
Go. Go!
[GASPS]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[DANA GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[WALTER PANTING]
[DANA SIGHS]
Thank you.
Ambulance is on its way.
I would call Kersh
as soon as you get cell reception.
Something you wanna share?
Kersh indicated to us
that we were responsible...
...for your lack of upward mobility
in the Bureau.
If it wasn't for you two,
I wouldn't be here right now.
And I'm not talking about the fact
that you showed up here today.
[GRUNTS]
I enlisted in the Marine Corps
the day that I turned 18.
I was a kid.
Full of callow self-confidence,
and faith, and this...
This kind of uncorrupted belief
that I was doing the right thing.
But John James...
...he didn't enlist.
He was drafted.
And his whole life
was completely upended...
...by a war that he really,
truly didn't even understand.
And he was so afraid all the time.
I felt like I had to protect him.
But I didn't.
I couldn't.
That experience in Vietnam with John...
...it put a dent in that blind faith
that I had in my government.
It planted seeds of mistrust.
I tried for years to suppress that mistrust,
but it gnawed at me.
[SCOFFS]
Then you two.
You two came along
and you taught me not to hide from it...
...but to have the guts to shine a light
directly into the darkest corners.
And if given the choice
between advancing my career...
...by being blindly loyal to some faceless
puppeteers pulling strings from the shadows...
...or to throw in with you two,
make no mistake about it...
...I'd make the same decision
every single damn time.
So I'm gonna go back,
I'm gonna kiss the ring.
But I intend to do right by this man...
...and that means finding the truth
of what the hell it was they used him for.
No matter the cost.
I owe him that.
[SCOFFS]
I owe myself that.
[GROANS]
[SIGHS]
Skinner.
We're with you.
DAVEY: Imagine the power of a government
that can literally control the minds...
...of millions and millions of its citizens,
simply by exposing them to this poison.
It's happening. It's happening right now.