[SCREAMS]
[METAL GRATING]
Hello?
GIRL:
[METAL THUMPS]
Who is that?
[PANTING]
[RATS SQUEAKING]
Are you Ghouli?
No.
You are.
No--
I'm not, I swear.
That's what Ghouli would say.
You're trying to trick me.
Look, I can prove it.
Just stay where you are. I'll come find you.
Not if I find you first.
[METAL THUDS]
[SCREAMS]
[CREATU RE SQUEAKING]
[SCREAMING]
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
[KNIFE SLASHING]
[GROWLING]
GIRL 1; No! Aah!
GIRL 2; Ugh.
[GIRLS COUGHING]
[GIRLS BREATHING HEAVILY]
DANA: Most people believe
there are two states of consciousness:
sleep and wakefulness.
But there is a third state, hypnagogia...
...characterized by dreamlike visions
and strange sensory perceptions.
It was in this borderland
that I found myself frozen on a stranger's bed.
[MOANING]
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[PANTING]
What the hell is going on?
Sounds like sleep paralysis.
REM atonia.
Did you hear hissing or buzzing? Did you feel
an electric current running through your body?
No, it was different, Mulder.
I mean, after the initial jolt of fear,
I felt compelled to follow the dark figure.
Dark figures are usually meant to be avoided.
Where was it leading you?
There.
That's the same boat.
That's an open X-file, Scully.
Chimera.
"Dreams are today's answers
to tomorrow's questions."
That's a quote from Edgar Cayce.
He was called The Sleeping Prophet.
Like you, he received visions
in a hypnagogic state.
He believed those visions were messages sent.
He also believed in the lost city of Atlantis.
Another reason to love the guy.
You've been receiving visions through seizure.
Maybe this is an evolution of the form.
No, but you're onto something, Scully,
I'm sure of it.
We're being followed. Since the airport.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Detective Costa.
Agent Scully.
Agent Mulder.
Pleasure.
So the victims and the perpetrators
were two female high school seniors.
Different schools, no past criminal history.
They were good students.
We talked to their families
and checked their social media.
No indications that the girls knew each other
before the attack.
Crime scene photos indicate that the wounds
were made with a sharp blade.
We found two knives at the scene.
They cut each other up pretty bad.
What's the condition of the girls now?
Both lost a lot of blood.
The one, Brianna Stapleton, was a millimeter
away from having her carotid artery severed.
Both girls are unconscious in the hospital,
but doctors are confident they'll pull through.
FOX:
Who reported the attack?
DET. COSTA:
Anonymous 911 call. Didn't leave a name.
But the voice was male,
and sounded panicked.
Forensics has a complete workup
with pictures and measurements...
...but this was left otherwise untouched.
There's no blood leading to or from the spot
where they were discovered.
Seems like once they started,
they were gonna finish.
FOX:
Hmm.
DANA: Mulder, the way they attacked each
other indicates an extreme emotional response.
It suggests that they did know each other.
If they didn't know each other, that response
could be an indication of extreme fear...
...like a lizard brain thing.
Either way, this meeting
was surely not a coincidence.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
All right. Okay, thanks.
Hey, guys, there was one other thing.
The EMT said that he heard something
when he was treating the victims.
He said that the girls asked him
if he found Ghouli.
FOX:
Is that Ghouli with an H?
It looks typical. The teeth, the mucous.
Ghouli probably feeds on human flesh.
Yawn.
DANA: The site's only been active
for the last couple of months.
Mostly fan fiction.
This is my problem with modern day monsters.
There's no emotional investment.
You know, like Frankenstein
or the Wolf Man.
Not only did they inspire bowel-clenching fear,
but there was pathos.
Frankenstein, he was afraid of fire
and he just wanted a friend. You know?
There's a lot of money to be made
in scaring people.
Maybe the girls were manipulated
to attack each other in order to goose traffic.
Most of the stories are written
by an @Rever.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
Oh. The girls have regained consciousness.
We can talk to them at the hospital now.
Bob. Double shot cappuccino, extra foam.
Thank you.
No worries, buddy.
Bob?
Like I wanted to explain "Fox"
for the millionth time.
Ghouli's real.
I saw it. It was closer than you are to me.
I was scared. I had to defend myself.
The thing was an inch from my face.
So close, I could smell its breath.
It had rows of sharp teeth,
and this goo was dripping from its mouth.
What did it smell like, its breath?
Like...cinnamon.
And how did you find this Ghouli?
I fell into this hole into its lair, I guess.
I heard something jump down,
and when I turned around, it was screaming.
What about Brianna Stapleton?
I didn't see anybody else.
She was on the floor, next to you.
Also injured.
I don't know any Sarah.
Okay? All I saw was Ghouli.
So how did you know to go to the ferry?
You're gonna think I'm crazy.
I had a dream.
But it wasn't a dream.
It felt real, like I was really living it.
At first it was scary because I couldn't move.
Like I was in bed, but it wasn't my own bed.
Someone was next to me.
I couldn't see him. It was a dark figure.
And I jumped out of bed and chased him.
It wasn't even my own house.
I would run through the hallways
and try to get to the living room to get outside.
I would just end up back inside again.
Like a maze.
Where no matter which door you open,
you end up in the same place.
Was there something
you were supposed to see?
A souvenir.
Yeah. You shake it and it snows.
What was inside your snow globe?
A ferry.
Everybody knew where it was.
Kids would get stoned on it
in the summer. Not me.
Have you ever experienced
a dream like that before?
Kind of. My boyfriend and I
did this fun house thing at the fair.
You have a boyfriend?
I'm not supposed to.
My parents don't approve.
They're really lame, but he's cool.
What's his name?
Jackson Van de Kamp.
The sleep paralysis, the labyrinth,
the snow globe. You share the same story.
And the girls apparently the same boyfriend.
Jackson Van de Kamp.
Scully.
I know.
Mulder, it has to be a coincidence.
No, it's not. You were sent here.
We are meant to be here.
We gotta find out where this kid lives.
I feel like I'm gonna fall off a cliff.
[GUNSHOTS]
Mulder, this is the house in my vision.
MULDER: The door's open.
Scully.
[GUNSHOT]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
DET. COSTA:
All right, so you said you heard three shots?
Murder-suicide.
Jackson Van de Kamp killed his parents.
When he heard you and Scully
break into the house...
...he realized he was gonna get caught
and killed himself.
That's a rather convenient explanation.
The kid had two girlfriends
who tried to kill each other.
There's something dirty in the water.
The back door was open.
Maybe he left it open.
I don't think you worry about those details...
...when you're looking
to commit murder-suicide.
I mean, you were here.
There was nobody else when he killed himself.
I appreciate your expertise, but I think you're
trying to answer questions nobody is asking.
I appreciate your input.
Scully?
[SIGHS]
This is his room.
I recognize it from my dream.
You were right, Mulder.
Whoever he is, he wanted me to be here.
Look.
Birthday, Halloween, vacation.
Baseball.
It's a whole life.
It's full. And still cold.
Odd choice to crack open a can of soda
before you decide to kill your parents.
Look at this.
The Pick Up Artist:
Memoirs of a Wolf in Sheep's Clothing.
At least he had his priorities straight.
He was troubled. Maybe even schizophrenic.
He was seeing a psychiatrist.
Clozapine. That's an antipsychotic,
and Diazepam is to treat seizures.
They were prescribed two months ago,
and they're still full...
...so he was off his medication.
I have grave doubts about what appears
to have happened here, Scully.
Aha.
Malcolm X.
"The future belongs to those
who prepare for it today."
Was that his hero?
We don't know
that that body is William, Scully.
DANA:
Mm.
Malcolm Little took the last name X...
...because he wouldn't take the slave name
given to his ancestral family.
Was Jackson's identity so adrift...
...that he couldn't see himself
as being a part of a family?
Is that why he killed his parents
and then himself?
Why would he call you here
just to see him die?
I need to get proof of his identity, Mulder.
I need answers.
[CAR DOORS CLOSE]
I'll get you one.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Who are you with,
and why are you following me?
Take it easy. Nobody's following you.
We're just curious onlookers.
We saw the police cars.
Something bad happened here.
What agency are you with?
Judging by your crappy rental car,
I'm guessing the DOD.
You make a lot of assumptions.
I also assume it's no coincidence you're here
on the night the Van de Kamps are killed.
Wow. Three bodies. What a tragedy.
Yeah.
Keep cracking wise.
You have no idea my state of mind.
[SIGHS]
[GASPS]
I don't know if you are
who I think you might be.
But if you are William...
...this is what I'd say.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry...
...that I didn't get a chance to know you.
Or you get a chance to know me,
or your father.
I gave you up for adoption
not because I didn't want you...
...or because you were any less loved.
I was trying to keep you safe.
I hope you know that.
And maybe...
Maybe I should have had the courage
to stand by you.
But I thought I was being strong, because
it was the hardest thing I have ever done.
I mean...
To let go...
...and to know
that I was gonna miss your whole life.
But it turns out that this is the hardest thing.
To see the outcome.
And how I failed you.
[SOBBING]
I need you to know that I never forgot you.
And I thought...
...I felt...
...even recently
that we were gonna somehow be reunited.
I wish I could have been there
to ease your pain.
Oh, my God, this is so inadequate.
[EXHALES]
I'm just so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[SOBBING]
[SIGHS]
Have you been there the whole time?
No, but I heard enough.
You have nothing to apologize for.
[DANA SIGHS]
[SOBS]
[WHISPERS] This is torture, Mulder.
I need to get the results.
0K8)'-
We can get a DNA comparison at the lab here.
Okay.
We'll be back in two hours.
Yeah.
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
[BONES CRACKLING]
WOMAN [OVER PA]:
Respiratory therapist to the ICU.
Any available respiratory therapist
to the ICU, stat.
[GASPS]
William.
[PANTING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[WHISPERING] Is this a message for me?
Or am I sending a message to you?
MAN:
Agent Scully?
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
I'm Dr. Harris, the coroner.
Where did you put the body?
There's no sign anyone was ever in here.
Scully, can I have a word?
[WHISPERING]
It's okay, Mulder.
It's not good news.
I know. It's William.
His body's missing.
There's no way anyone
could've taken the body out of here.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Are there any windows anywhere?
No sign of damage on the outside.
That window is always locked.
Well, then it must've been opened
from the inside.
Scully.
Can I talk to you?
[WHISPERING] Yeah.
[WHISPERING]
I know what you're thinking.
And I want him to be alive,
every bit as much as you do.
And in my heart, I never thought
that we'd have to face this moment.
But here we are.
And hope is not a fact.
And I'm always the first to jump to extreme
possibilities, but this is not as simple as that.
Mulder, I had another vision.
And I saw this.
Did you take that from his room?
I don't know why I did.
I just needed to hold on
to something tangible.
All right, I'll check
the video surveillance.
But this doesn't change anything.
Not yet.
He wants us to find him, Mulder.
I know it.
DANA: Oh. Aah! I'm sorry.
MAN: Aah! Oh.
MAN:
I'm sorry.
It cracked. The stuff leaked out.
No, it's my fault. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You were distracted.
You like windmills?
I like this one.
Who are you?
Don't give up on the bigger picture.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Nothing on the surveillance cameras
and nothing here.
No history on ghouli.net, no porn.
How many 17-year-olds with two girlfriends
have a search history that clean?
Maybe he wiped his history.
I got this from the dark web.
It retrieves the browser history
from the hard drive.
If we can find the right computer.
He's hiding it here somewhere.
[SIREN WAILS]
I think our investigation
is about to get hijacked.
DANA:
Got it.
Teenage girls have secrets too.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
FOX:
Look at that. Hundreds of posts to ghouli.net.
And a back door to some
files at the DOD.
MAN:
Agents Mulder and Scully.
We are commanding you to cease all activity
and exit the property immediately.
The FBI has jurisdiction
over this investigation.
I suggest you leave the premises until I can get
an order from a countermanding authority.
That's straight from the DOJ.
Now scram.
MAN:
Step away from the desk.
Everything in this house is now
under the jurisdiction of the DOD.
Oh! Never a good idea
to keep an open beverage by electronics.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Mulder, how is it the only updates
I've received about what you're doing...
...come through complaints
by other agencies in the government?
Let me guess, the DOD.
WALTER: And the DOJ.
They filed a memo documenting
obstruction and tampering with evidence.
Nothing will come of those complaints...
...because the DOD is involved
in a conspiracy they're trying to cover up.
Does it have anything to do with a missing
dead body, a Jackson Van de Kamp?
I'll tell you more when I know more.
You need to come back
so we can discuss your activities.
No, actually you're gonna need to come here.
I'm not going to Norfolk.
BARISTA: Bob?
Skinner, you're breaking up. I can't--
Bob?
Mulder. ...
Double cappuccino, extra foam?
Yeah. Yeah.
Mulder, I can hear you perfectly.
I'm gonna have to call you back
when I get a better connection. Hello?
Mulder?
Mulder is close.
I suspect he'll be interested
in Project Crossroads.
We'll be able to find
what we've been looking for.
Mulder, why did you wanna meet out here?
It's cold and it smells.
This is where it all started.
When two young girls were attacked
by a monster only they could see.
You're wrong. This is the end of the road.
It started decades ago.
When they decided to combine
alien and human DNA to create hybrids.
Listen to me, I came out here
to warn you and Scully.
Drop this investigation.
I'm listening.
After the crash at Roswell...
...our government's interest in alien
technology exploded in all directions.
And finally, in the '70s, our science
caught up to our ambition.
A eugenics program was initiated
by a Dr. Masao Matsumoto...
...using components of alien
technology, hybrid DNA.
Project Crossroads.
I read the report.
It was ultimately deemed a failure
because they couldn't predict...
...what attributes the test subjects
would get from the hybrid DNA.
That's correct. The project
was defunded 15 years ago.
Dr. Matsumoto burned all the files
pertaining to the subjects to save their lives...
...and then he disappeared.
The DOD has tried to track
them down ever since.
That's why they were following us.
We found one of their own for them.
Jackson Van de Kamp.
Now do you understand?
Jackson Van de Kamp was our son,
Skinner.
He was named William
before he was adopted.
I checked his DNA
against Scully's.
Oh, my God. I am so sorry. Mulder, I--
Thank you.
For your warning.
It just came too late.
DR. SCHOLZ: I find it hard to believe Jackson
would harm anyone, much less his parents.
He loved them very much.
And we never discussed any suicidal ideation.
Your claims don't describe the patient I know.
You prescribed medication for seizures.
Jackson had symptoms that coincided
with extreme electrical activity in the brain.
But can you tell me, did he have...
...visions?
What he saw was specific and detailed.
That's all I'm willing to say, Agent Scully,
unless you come back with a court order.
His visions were apocalyptic.
A pandemic was spreading
across America.
Hospitals were overwhelmed.
People were panicking.
A vaccine was needed.
One that had to be created
with a combination of human and alien DNA.
And Jackson himself was the key.
It ends with a UFO,
hovering over the 14th Street Bridge.
That's what he saw, Dr. Scholz.
How is it possible you know?
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
So you think a shared vision
means that it's more likely to come true?
What if I didn't get a glimpse of the future?
What if I was just a receptacle
for his message to me?
Just like my dream to come here.
BARISTA:
Hey, Bob.
[DANA CHUCKLES]
It's an alternate reality.
Fox doesn't exist in coffee shops.
No.
It's a false reality, Scully.
Just like everything we've seen so far.
I've been going over the forensics
of the case.
The police think Jackson killed his parents,
then himself.
But the spatter pattern tells me different.
It tells me there were two shooters.
[SCREAMS]
Her body was moved after she was shot
to make it look like there was one shooter.
Scully, I believe that through
the Smoking Man...
...you were an unwitting participant in a
eugenics program called Project Crossroads...
...spearheaded by Dr. Masao Matsumoto.
He disappeared two years
after William was born.
I believe our son
was one of his test subjects.
[BANGING]
Let's go.
FOX: Jackson knew he was being hunted.
So he hid the only way he knew how.
He created an alternate reality playing dead.
So he made us hear the shot...
...and see the hole in his head.
Yes. And those two girls thought
they saw a monster.
And so, Mulder?
[FOX slel-ls]
Where is he now?
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BRIANNA GASPS, THEN MOANS]
Heh. Jackson.
Thank God.
They told me you were dead.
Not yet.
Oh, babe.
These look sick.
It's horrible. I'm so sorry.
Where have you been?
I've been hiding.
There's these people, they're after me. I--
Look, I just came to apologize.
I didn't mean for any of this to happen.
I didn't think anyone would get hurt.
I thought it'd be funny.
Like a prank. Like, you'd see the Ghouli
and you just run away.
Are you Ghouli?
No. There's no such thing as Ghouli.
I made up everything on the website.
No, Jackson.
That thing attacked me.
And the other girl.
You attacked each other.
You saw what I projected into your head.
All right, it's like...
...this...
This power,
I was learning to control it, okay?
I just couldn't stop it in time.
There was so much blood.
It was all just a blur.
That's really messed up.
It is.
All right, it started
when I had my seizures. I--
I'd see things.
Terrifying things like UFOs.
And it Would hurt like hell.
And...
But when I was in pain, I could share it.
Kind of. Like mentally.
With Who?
This woman. I don't know, she was...
...maybe my birth mother.
Look, I came back, because...
...everyone around me is in danger.
My parents are dead, Bree.
[WHIMPERS]
But I wanted to say goodbye. Okay?
0K8)'-
[SIREN WAILING]
[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
Oh, no.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
They found me.
Take it easy, agents. You guys can relax.
You can relax. It's under control.
You have Jackson Van de Kamp in custody?
Not yet.
I don't understand how a dead guy
can be up on his feet.
But he's in there, exits are covered.
How do you know he's inside?
I got a text from Sarah Turner. That's him.
I'd like to ask you to keep your officers outside
so we can be the first to go in.
Agents from the Department of Defense
are already inside.
Excuse me.
Gee, Sarah.
You were kissing her.
So I wanted to hurt you.
So I-- And I texted them.
I'm so sorry.
I should be the one saying sorry.
Are you gonna be in trouble?
They-- They wanna kill me.
SARAH:
It's my fault.
This is-- This is all my fault.
No, no, no. Look.
I'm gonna be all right. Okay?
[GASPS]
He's coming your way.
[ALL GRUNTING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[PANTING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[GROWLING]
[GUNSHOTS]
Evacuate the floor.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Subject is heading your way.
[PANTING]
Hey, don't move.
[CLAMORING]
MAN:
Move!
FBI. Put your weapon down.
Stay out of my way.
I know you're here, boy.
[EXHALES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
DANA:
Stop.
[BOTH GRUNT]
[GASPS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
They shot each other.
Well, who were they shooting at'?
He's here.
Jackson. It's safe. It's over.
Jackson, we just wanna talk to you.
Make sure you're okay.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Anything?
He's disappeared.
Oh, boy.
MAN:
Yeah, I'm sorry...
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING CONTINUES]
Do we need gas?
I could use a bathroom.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Mm.
Are you following me?
Hey.
Didn't I see you at the hospital?
It must be kismet. Heh.
But I doubt we'll be seeing each other again.
I'm driving across country.
Oh. Anywhere in particular?
No. I just wanna see the world.
Things are about to change.
Hey-
Are you Dr. Masao Matsumoto?
A doctor?
Heh. No. I never finished high school.
You seemed like a nice person.
I wish I could know you better.
Well, safe travels.
If you don't stand for something...
...you'll fall for anything.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Who's that?
DANA: Just a friendly old guy.
But he seems so familiar.
The Pick Up Artist.
What are you talking about?
That book in Jackson's room.
I think he's the author.
What did he say?
He gave me a piece of advice. He said...
He said, "if you don't stand for something,
you'll fall for anything."
That's a Malcolm X quote, Scully.
Scully.
We need to see your surveillance video now.
DANA:
Right there.
DANA".
Are you Dr. Masao Matsumoto?
JACKSON:
A doctor? No, I never finished high school.
You seemed like a nice person. Heh.
I wish I could know you better.
DANA". Well, safe travels.