[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Come in.
What do you think?
This is yours?
Well, only 15 percent of us
actually live in
the neighbourhoods we patrol.
[CHUCKLES]
Uh, taming the frontier
isn't enough for you?
Well, I'm thinking of
staking a claim.
Seemed like a good idea a month ago
when I put down the deposit,
but now, with everything heating up,
Antwon Mitchell...
maybe it's not such a good idea.
Get extra patrols,
undercover units to look after you.
I can't divert police resources
for my own protection.
I mean, that would defeat
the purpose of living in the 'hood.
Why am I here?
You want me to find
a couple of code violations,
sweat your landlord
and get your deposit back?
I didn't sell you out.
Everyone in L.A. saw you
on that tape
grabbing that kid in the church
and smiling.
I had to ask you
to take a step back.
A back seat.
Let me guess.
Either you're with Vic Mackey,
or you're against him, right?
Keeps things simple.
I'm with you.
But I expect you to be with me.
Wherever your head is these days,
just don't start cutting me out
or going around me like you did
with Aceveda.
Keeps things simple.
Hey, man,
where the hell you been?
Taking care of some things.
I hope you're talking about Shane.
We need to stick together.
I don't need babysitters.
Antwon's got Shane out to kill you.
What the hell are we doing about it?
I'm watching my back.
Really? Out there in the open?
Could be setting you up,
could be a drive-by,
waiting for you at your house.
LEM:
He and Army are off the grid.
You seen them at all today?
We went by Shane's truck to pick up
the latest tape, they're nowhere.
Come on, let's get out there, man.
Come straight at them.
Don't worry. When the time's right.
Why'd you change your hair?
It was a whim.
It's like seeing
a stranger in the mirror.
That's a bit drastic.
I wish you would've asked me first.
I could've offered an opinion.
You don't like it?
I'll get used to it.
[PHONE RINGING]
What? What is it?
My sister's having a meltdown.
Her asshole boss fired her today.
I'm sure your sister will be fine.
She wants to come over.
You told her it's not a good time.
Look, I wouldn't do this. It's just
she's really on edge, depressed.
We can hurry.
[SIGHS]
I'll make it up to you, I promise.
SARA:
Hey. Come on in.
MAN:
Thanks. Looking beautiful.
BILLINGS:
Mitch Robville, 33, throat slashed,
was supposed to pick up
a friend for work, never showed.
Should have used a safety razor.
Did you say Mitch Robville?
You know him?
He's one of our informants.
He tipped us about
the crackhouse on Rivermore.
Took the money and ran.
Idiot shouldn't have turned down
our offer to move him.
Tip leads to a seizure,
and this is what happens.
We have to assume
the same thing happened to Angie.
Yeah, that's one way to make sure
the snitch well runs dry.
Very first roll call, I said that we would
protect the people who helped us.
Now we've lost two of them.
You giving me the wheel,
or am I still in the back seat?
I want who did this.
Police!
Antwon, get your ass out here!
You better
have a warrant.
Warrant?
I just saw your door busted wide open.
Wanted to make sure you were okay.
You okay?
One-Niners got a campaign
against police informants?
I'm done with this.
You think you can
just go after anyone?
You think
you're indestructible?
I don't know what you spitting.
[CROWBAR CLANGS]
If you've given the word,
and some informant
or some citizen
or some cop gets hurt,
you're gonna be spitting teeth.
I'm going back to bed.
Make sure you get that door fixed.
Anyone could just walk right in.
[###]
The other players on Rivermore
all got the same inter-ghetto memo.
Word's out our dead guy was our tip.
Tried to take every precaution with our
seizure C.I.'s since Angie disappeared.
Pull in the rest of the tipsters
until we get a handle on this.
Pulling in C.I.'s is only gonna
expose them more, ratchet things up.
They're all at risk. Could be
Antwon Mitchell sending out
a hell of a signal.
I'll see about
sending him one back.
I'm also calling in IAD.
Seizures are stirring things up.
Could be getting ourselves all worked
up about a leak that doesn't exist.
Then let them prove that.
Do you really wanna give
Aceveda more ammunition
to shut this thing down?
Give me one last chance
to find the leak, plug it.
Okay.
But first, solve this murder.
Somebody killed one of our rats.
I'm running it down.
Where do you want us?
VIC:
Captain's digging deeper into our leak.
Get the info from Billings,
compare to Angie's,
see what they have in common.
Why bother, man? Shane and Antwon
are responsible for Angie.
We can't tell that to the captain,
can we?
LEM: What about Shane?
VIC: This again?
You just want us to sit on our asses?
I mean, do you have a plan?
Are you gonna tell us what it is?
Shane's cell phone.
I palmed it from his locker yesterday.
Keep an eye on it, see who calls.
That's it? That's the master plan?
Part of it.
LEM:
What are we doing to end this?
I appreciate you two
having my back.
But I don't need it.
Meet me on the other side
in three minutes.
Your unfinished business
kicked down my door last night.
Well, it's complicated.
He's a smart guy, I gotta do it right.
He's coming
straight at me, man.
And I'm not gonna lose no more sleep
over this asshole, you feel me?
Tomorrow morning's news will have
a big picture of Mackey's kids
crying their eyes out.
Or a picture of your son,
crying his.
You don't wanna make that threat.
Your wife still sell
real estate? Hm?
Still show those open houses?
Yeah.
Playtime is over.
Get it done tonight.
I'm on my way.
BILLINGS:
Ken Gibbin, science teacher.
Been at this high school seven years.
RAWLING:
He's not one of our C.I.'s.
Maybe he dropped a dime
on one of his students.
This ain't exactly
finishing school.
BILLINGS:
I ran his name.
It's coming up dry.
RAWLING:
Keep checking.
Grab the class rosters.
Run the names of the principal,
see he's not on the dean's list.
He may or may not be connected.
Sure the throat's cut,
but it could be a copycat.
You have a different way
to go?
You have a lead on the first murder
that I'm not aware of?
Are all the other snitches
in safe houses yet?
I just finished that.
Call in the next shift OT.
Increase their protection.
You don't think the one shift's
got it covered?
No. I don't.
VIC:
He's been doing 15 months
for possession.
Only 14 months to go.
Someone planted all that weight
in my locker.
Mr. Gibbin?
Your old teacher?
Somebody cut him, ear to ear.
That your idea of payback?
Gibbs? No, Gibbs wasn't no rat.
He was always trying
to keep me straight.
I'd screw up, and we'd talk.
But he'd never take it to 5-0.
They cut him?
Head almost completely off.
VIC:
Sheriff tells me the kid didn't have
any colours before he hit juvie,
but to stay alive,
he had to claim Spookstreet.
Could be covering for his crew.
Spookstreet supplied rock to the house
our victim gave up on Rivermore.
Uh-huh.
Puts them in the middle
of both killings.
And off of Antwon's plate.
Not necessarily.
Pull in all the unis assigned
to Spookstreet.
I'll do you one better. Danny's
baby mama C.I. is a Spookstreet ho.
She's watching cable
in a safe house on our dime.
What, the one with the 2-year-old?
All her tips have been on One-Niners.
She'd never give up her own.
Danny knows her pretty well,
she thinks she might have a soft spot.
It's worth a shot. Bring her in here.
I have a theory.
About the leaks.
Isn't Aceveda's office reviewing
every one of the seizures?
I thought of that.
I see him pulling political moves, not
moves that get people's throats cut.
I'm not pointing any fingers.
Just a notion.
You've given us some great intel
on the One-Niners.
And you pay good money
for the things I hear.
VIC:
Anyone in Spookstreet taking it
upon themselves
to pay back people
they think might be rats?
Everyone wants to know
who's been talking.
Getting the cops
to take their houses and shit.
It's a good thing
I keep my mouth shut.
But Spookstreet is in the middle
of both killings.
You must've heard something?
I can't help you.
Sure you can.
How much is it gonna cost us?
Money's for One-Niner shit only.
Spookstreet's my blood.
I ain't spilling.
DANNY:
Let me talk to her?
CLAUDETTE:
What did he look like?
He already said
he doesn't remember.
He was black.
I got that.
Any identifying features?
Guy beat my head with a bottle.
I was unconscious.
I'm lucky I remember my own name.
CLAUDETTE:
How much he get away with?
At this hour, maybe 300.
DUTCH:
We need you to check
the receipts, tally a total.
So black guy comes in,
attacks you,
and next thing you remember
is a different guy dialling 911 for help?
You ever try writing this shit down?
Come on, we got his statement.
I was by my car pumping gas. I look
up, I see somebody hitting the clerk.
You got a good look inside the station?
Not really.
It wasn't until he came outside
that I got a look at him.
Hot off the press.
DUTCH:
You should work that
up into a flyer.
I thought he'd get
another look at it again first.
Looks great to me.
Right?
How do you know?
You never saw the guy.
That's him.
I've a good eye for detail.
DUTCH:
We appreciate it. We need
anything else, we'll call you.
Okay.
Hey, Julien.
Captain got you riding a desk?
Yeah. Until my complaint's addressed.
The stand you're taking
sets a great example.
Let me know if you need anything.
Hey, listen, since I've got you.
A Jag dinged Aurora's car
in the Gelson's parking lot
and took off without stopping.
Do me a favour, run the plates.
Sure.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming down.
Sure.
So, uh... how can I help?
We're afraid our seizure C.I. list
has been compromised.
Is there any chance
there's a leak on your end?
My end? That's ridiculous.
You just took office.
You sure you vetted everyone
on staff properly?
They've got confidential police
documents running across their desks.
I'll call IAD myself.
We've got nothing to hide.
What'd they say
about this place?
I'm still investigating.
Oh, so you haven't had IAD in here?
You haven't run Mackey?
Vic may have a hard-on
for authority,
but he would never
put innocents at risk.
He's not the leak.
Have IAD here
in the morning.
My staff will be happy to speak with
them, as soon as they finish with Vic.
You know you're safe here.
But you also know that living the way
you do, one foot in with the bangers,
one foot trying to get out,
it's never gonna work.
I got no place to go.
Well, that's what the money's for.
It's a big world out there.
Single black mom, I just pick up
and move to Beverly Hills?
Staying half in is gonna
get you killed. Or Malcolm.
Maybe not now, maybe not next year,
but somewhere down the line.
I'm safe with Spookstreet.
If I go off on my own,
who am I gonna count on?
You think you can count
on those assholes?
Those guys and their ho's
will slash your neck
if they found out that you ratted
on the One-Niners.
Come on. Why don't
we just take the baby right now?
We'll go get him inked with gang tats.
So it's a done deal, isn't it?
He's gonna wear colours,
you're gonna wear black to his funeral.
She says that if any one of
the Spookstreeter did the slashings,
they'd get a brand
before the day's out.
Some guy named Skitch
is doing them all now.
Check it out.
He comes in for looseys.
Two, three times a week.
What's a loosey?
You don't know
what a loosey is?
A single loose cigarette.
Loosey.
CLAUDETTE:
You sure it's the same guy?
MAN:
He makes me break a pack.
I'm not supposed to, but he winds up
buying it one smoke at a time.
What else
can you tell us?
He comes in for looseys
two, three times a week.
Looks just like that. Sorry.
He comes in again,
give us a call, all right?
Where you going?
Guy was standing out there
like he was waiting for us to clear out.
That's a buck 20.
DUTCH:
Hey, hey! Police!
Don't throw that coffee.
Shit.
Stay down. Stay down!
You're under arrest.
You okay?
Yeah. You?
We just caught
the big bad coffee bandit.
We've been looking for you, Starbuck.
I told you to wear your vest.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Yo, Skitch, we're looking
to skin some Spookstreet hide.
You brand any today?
Nope.
None? No one came in here looking
for a Grim Reaper on their ass?
I'd have remembered that. I can heat up
a swastika for you though, Adolph.
Hey, Vic, why don't I wait in the car,
I'll let the two of you
maybe talk in private?
Works for me.
Don't mind any strange noises
emanating from this area.
Okay. Okay, I see how we're doing it.
Maybe there were two other guys
around here.
But you keep my name out of it though.
These guys ain't too fond of snitches.
Okay. This is Hook. This is Cutter-10.
A plainclothes unit has them spotted
on Blythe and Fountain.
Uh, Curtis, I need you to take point.
Uh, Billings and I
have been working this.
You're staying.
[SIGHS]
Real estate between me
and anything seizure-related?
You did a great job
finding these assholes,
and you'll get a chance
to interrogate them
when the others bring them in,
but you cannot be
the arresting officer.
Mm-hmm.
I appreciate you understanding.
LEM:
Go, go.
MAN:
Get your hands where I can see them.
DANNY:
Police! Out of the car now!
Get out of the car.
Get out of the car!
Hey, get out!
Get out of the car right now!
RONNIE:
You heard the lady.
Got something.
MAN: Come on, man.
Shut up.
VIC:
Victim's blood, your fingerprints.
Somebody should have branded
"dumbshit" on your forehead.
MAN:
But it took a whole fleet of blue
to bring me in, didn't it?
What's your reason
for killing anyone helping us?
I ain't got no problem with the po-po
cleaning up the streets.
That's what white law gets paid for.
You just don't like anyone
cooperating with us.
Come on, man, some dick
buys himself a brand-new Caddy,
he ride around
like he some kind of mack.
People gonna thank me
for doing him.
As a matter of fact, you make sure the
pen hears all about it before I sit down.
What about the teacher?
You looking to make your bones
with the kids in detention?
No. No, he was
a snitch's snitch, man.
Everybody knew that he the one
that gave up the One-Niners drug den.
We'll show you the books.
He wasn't our informant on anything.
What kind of cred's killing some
innocent dude buy you in the can?
He wasn't innocent, man.
He was a rat bigtime, man.
Everybody knew he was ratting.
You got played, man.
People found out you got
all worked up about snitches,
just gave you a name,
settle some personal score.
RAWLING:
We'll make sure they hear
about that in the pen too.
Someone punked you like that,
you're not gonna let them
share the pain?
Some breezy,
she one of his students.
Tracy something.
She on the drill team.
I'm not admitting
to anything.
Sure, whatever. We're bringing
in the other clerks to identify you.
They're pissed.
They'll remember.
You know, every once in a while,
somebody commits a crime
that we cops have to smile at.
Yeah. A hot cup of coffee,
no other weapon. Brilliant.
Pour it, pay for it, bam. You're back
home before they guy's washing off.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Any dumbshit criminal
can use a gun.
Where'd you think
of that idea?
Some broad threw
coffee in my face.
I remember thinking to myself,
I'm lucky this isn't hot.
[ALL LAUGHING]
After that,
it all came together.
Well, I heard you took one
in the line of duty.
The coffee bandit
is now in custody.
Dutch did a great job.
It was a team thing.
Congratulations.
We'll pay to have
your suit dry-cleaned.
Thanks.
Anything on the gas-station assault
that put you there in the first place?
Suspect's a part-time smoker.
He'd go into the gas station
a couple times a week for looseys.
I used to pay a dime for mine.
Ah, the good old days.
You were both smokers, huh?
The suspect's sketch has been put
in every gas station in the area.
So if he lives nearby,
maybe he'll hit another one.
Good work.
A meeting got cancelled.
I figured I'd take a chance.
Expecting someone?
No.
But you need to call first.
You know you can't just drop by.
Right. I might run into your sister.
How is she?
This isn't how it works.
Please leave now.
Go.
This place, your clothes,
your hair.
Must all add up, huh?
That's why you
bring the gifts.
As nice as Dell Rossetti's?
Did you forget I'm a police officer?
Your bullshit lies don't work on me.
He's a friend.
You don't have friends.
You have clients.
I'm guessing Rossetti's
a generous one.
But then again,
he showed up empty-handed.
Maybe we're standing in his gift.
He the reason
you changed your hair?
He prefer blonds?
I told you a lie
to keep our lie alive.
You wanna puncture that balloon,
that's your deal.
Yeah? Well, what's
this guy's flavour, huh?
Up the ass? Shitting on you?
You don't get to talk to me like that.
Not even when I'm on the clock.
Well, Rossetti can certainly afford
the all-access pass.
He's got condos going up
all over the city.
We don't talk business.
And from what I can tell,
he cuts corners.
Which could land him in some
serious trouble with the authorities.
I don't know what shit you're
trying to work through with me,
but it's not working.
You know, he got married
a couple of years ago.
The wife has any brains, she put
a cheating clause in the pre-nup.
You gonna call her?
Sort of a bitch move,
don't you think?
I don't think she'd see it that way.
Or I could call my friends
in the DA's office.
I could call my friends
in the PD, hit him
with a dozen different shitstorms,
and my fingerprints
wouldn't be on any of them.
You've got a wife too.
Should I let her know how
to make you happy at home?
Oh, you wouldn't do that. Not to me.
Because you're so powerful,
right?
You wanna see the things I can do?
[SIGHS]
Look, David.
I like our time together.
Let's not screw it up
over something stupid.
Just tell me what you want.
I don't come second to anyone.
You're working today.
Yeah. What are you doing here?
I'm just trying to catch Vic. Kid stuff.
What happened to your suit?
A takedown got pretty messy.
It's no problem. We got the guy.
We'll celebrate later.
There's Vic. Listen, I've got a robbery
I'm working on, so I'll talk to you later.
Hey, I got a pretty full plate.
What's going on?
I heard back from that clinical trial
that I signed Megan up for.
Uh-huh?
She's not eligible.
Shit. Come on.
She's under 3 years old,
second kid in the family with autism.
Isn't that what they wanted?
It's not Megan. It's us. Our lawsuit.
Pyren Pharmaceuticals
excludes anyone with
pending legal action against them.
First, these are the people who make
the vaccines that make our kids sick.
Then they're the gatekeepers
of the ones who get better?
I spoke to Mamyn. We can
drop out of the lawsuit if we want.
It's just the money
that we've sunk...
We're not eating 15 grand.
These clinical trials. I've seen video
of kids who, they haven't even talked.
And now they're playing,
and they're laughing.
That'll never be Matthew,
but Megan still has a chance.
Or she could end up
being the one eating the sugar pill.
She shouldn't miss out.
But this lawsuit was our one chance
for financial security for Matthew.
[WHIMPERS]
I don't know what to do.
I'll take care of it.
SHANE:
There he is. Hey!
Hey, I been looking for you all day.
I don't know why the helping-out-kids
angle wasn't my first stop.
Hop in. I have something
you're gonna wanna hear.
I'll hear right here, man.
I ain't forgot what happened last time
I conferenced with you two.
I got you and the 4-H Club
a new road to heroin.
You should take this ride.
Come on.
Let's go.
Little Pop, Los Mag OG
owes me a favour.
They got a Nogales customs agent
on payroll.
Tar slips over the Arizona border.
Just a Sunday drive away.
Antwon's beefing with the wetbacks.
That's why we used the El Salvadorans.
That's where the deal
gets interesting though.
We know you were next in line
to be the One-Niner Don.
Antwon got sprung,
decided to reclaim his crown.
Things change, you know?
You wanna live, you change with them.
Well, it's time for
another change, brother.
Los Mags are willing to work
with a new One-Niners boss.
That's you. Ain't a smiling matter.
Antwon keeps playing
his Malcolm X games,
the heat's gonna cripple you guys.
Already is.
He didn't give a shit
about the One-Niners.
He's just using his old set
to climb back on top.
You didn't come up with him.
You got no loyalty to him.
Say what you gotta say, man.
I've negotiated a deal
between you and the Los Mags.
One condition,
Antwon goes away.
Clean, simple.
Look, he's beefing
with enough people,
it's an easy pin.
You step up, you earn your crew's
respect with this new product.
With Antwon gone, our captain,
she loses her hard-on, PD backs off,
the injunctions... go away.
ARMY:
Brothers get back
to making money.
Everybody wins.
What you win?
That little girl's body.
No. I don't need to be
the head nigga in charge, man.
Antwon, he can have the limelight
and the heat. I'm a pass.
Come on, man. You know
that's thinking like a pussy.
Pussy, someone who's willing
to off a partner to cover his ass.
We're not talking about that.
ARMY: Kill what partner?
Don't worry, Pablo, it ain't you.
Not yet, anyway.
[LAUGHING]
Antwon wants you to kill Mackey?
No, Antwon
wants a lot of things.
The question is,
is what does this guy want.
Now, I got a deal on the table.
It's in your best interests.
That's your opinion.
I'll tell Antwon we chatted.
Where you going?
You stay right there!
What the hell you doing?
You control your boy.
That's not the way to handle this.
Then how do we do this, boss?
He downloads to Antwon, and we're
deep in dead girls and bullets.
Yo, handle this shit!
Put it away.
Put that thing away, okay?
Los Mags think
that I've been dealing in your name.
Back out of this, they're not gonna...
[GUNSHOT]
I didn't mean that.
Jesus Christ!
I didn't mean it!
That asshole shot me, man!
What the hell are you thinking?
That asshole shot me.
What's wrong with y'all?
Holy shit.
Why didn't you tell me about Vic?
Now's not the time.
WOMAN:
6-Paul-24, 6-Paul-24, come in.
What the hell have you gotten us into?
I said shut up!
Everyone, just shut up.
Jesus.
All right.
Where's that little girl's body?
I ain't saying shit.
Look, I can drop you at a hospital,
or I can let you bleed out in the desert.
Now, where did Antwon put her?
Okay, fine. Fine.
Next stop, Joshua Tree.
RAWLING:
We heard that your teacher
failed you for cutting class.
You think I slit his throat?
I'm half his size.
Everyone knows you busted Hook
and Cutter-10 already.
I ain't scared of you.
We need to know who else
you've been talking trash about?
If you've been shooting your mouth,
your lynch mob might go after them.
Why you ain't out arresting Dynamite?
That nigga running girls on a track.
Or my mail-lady,
she running numbers.
So the code of silence
is for everyone else?
Everybody got their own code.
That's the only law out there.
You all just something
to get around.
You're not getting around us today.
We're booking you for
conspiracy to commit murder,
reckless endangerment,
and anything else that we can think of.
Bullshit charges
will never fly.
I'm supposed
to let her walk?
No law against trash talking.
She knew the climate out there.
She used it to get
a schoolteacher killed.
You'll never prove intent.
It's a loser.
She's tuned in to what's going on
out there. We're not.
I am sick of being blindsided by it.
I'm gonna move into that house.
You want to drop yourself in the middle
of all that crap? Good luck.
The only way to be a real catalyst
for change is to leap in the mix,
show them you're right there
with them.
They won't give a shit.
Not at first.
Good work closing this one.
Zerkow,
how are we on patrols tonight?
Short. Why?
Captain's moving into the 'hood.
You're kidding.
I wish.
Point of pride with her, she won't
order up extra patrols for herself,
but we gotta make sure
no assholes get any cute ideas.
I'll put it
in effect tomorrow.
Thanks.
I'll look in on her tonight.
Heard you were right
in the thick of things out there.
I shouldn't have broken
that damn window.
It's bullshit
you couldn't be with us.
Next time.
Hey, wanna grab a beer or something?
Bust like that, I could blow off steam.
I can't. Got something
with the kids and a stakeout.
If you want some company
for the stakeout, give me a call.
I'm still a little wired.
Okay.
SHANE:
Wake up. Where is she?
She's in the crapper on the right.
She's buried underneath,
wrapped in plastic.
Not only did you kill her,
you gotta shit on her too?!
Methane helps hide
the death smell.
Gotta get me some help.
What time does this place shut down?
It don't shut down.
The shelter's got guards 24l7, man.
How we gonna get her out?
I don't know.
What are you doing?
I send units to recover that body, you
and Antwon'll be waist-deep in shit too.
Try to move it, I'll nail it in transit.
We can't just leave him here.
You tell Antwon I'm done
with his shit, all of it.
He tries to come after us,
my family or Vic,
I'll walk up to him, and I'll put
a bullet in his head. You got that?
You got that?!
SHANE:
Move. Get out of my way.
SARA:
I'm sorry...
MAN:
Who you talking too?
I'm sorry.
All right.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Was that like you wanted?
Ah! That's too hard.
[GRUNTING]
You're too powerful!
No.
It's so big.
WOMAN:
Hey, detective. Did you talk
to that guy who was looking for you?
What guy?
He said something
about a mini-mart?
Where is he?
You looking for me?
MAN:
You the one handling
the gas-station beatings?
Yeah.
Yeah. That was me.
You... You're here
to turn yourself in?
After I finish this,
I'll tell you all about it.
Take your time.
All I needed was one cigarette,
then I'm good.
I buy a pack.
CLAUDETTE:
You smoke them all.
So, what happened in the store?
This new idiot was working.
I told him the other clerk always busts
a pack for me, but he wouldn't do it.
I told him, I said, "I'm trying to quit."
I'm begging him, "Show me some love."
But he wanted to be an asshole, and...
I lost it.
Just... Just one cigarette.
And $300.
What?
You stole $300 from the register.
Maybe now,
you can afford the whole pack.
No. I came here to admit my wrong.
I shouldn't have hit that man.
And I take my punishment.
But I'm not a thief.
Police intel's making its way
into the street.
Thought those slashings
was a girl playing witch-hunt?
Yeah, they were,
but we never did find
our missing C.I., Angie.
We never determined
who tipped off that warehouse raid
when DEA was in town.
Sounds like plain old bad intel.
I thought all you guys
took cynical pills.
Are you IAD or not?
At your service. What's my cover?
I'm gonna put you in as part
of the Gang Task Force.
You'll be working with Vic Mackey.
Oh, his name's run across our desks
a few times. You think he's involved?
No. But I need to prove
to someone that he's not.
I told you, we don't
have to decide tonight.
What's going on?
You need to take this.
You've been hiding money from me?
This isn't about ducking alimony.
I wanna take care of my children.
Where did this come from?
Where did you get this?
The money's clean.
Just make sure you don't deposit more
than 5 grand every couple of months.
Do it.
Don't bring this in the house.
I don't want it.
You wanna drop the lawsuit,
get Megan into that clinical trial.
This is how you do it.
Use this for Matty.
I wanna go kiss the kids good night.
They're asleep.
I'm not gonna wake them up.
Why did you have me
take Cassidy tonight?
Are you okay?
Nothing I can't handle.
I wanna say good night to the kids.
It feels like goodbye.
Vic.
[DOOR SHUTS]
You're pretty quiet tonight.
Anything you wanna talk about?
Think the captain is dumb
or brave for doing this?
Gang Task Force
is a pretty good idea.
Sure as hell keeps me from spinning
my wheels out there, you know.
Thanks for putting me
up for that.
So you wanna call it?
No.
Oh, Jesus. Come here.
[BOTH PANTING]
Oh, yeah. Like that.
[DANNY MOANING]
DUTCH:
We just, uh, need a few more details
for your statement.
After the suspect ran out, how long
did it take you to get to the victim?
A few seconds.
Once the thief drove off, I ran in,
found him unconscious, called 911.
Uh, anybody else there?
I don't think so. Place was empty.
Probably why he robbed it then.
Or why you robbed it then.
I called this in, remember, guys?
You might be smart,
but you're not criminal smart.
And you're a terrible liar.
I've never done anything
like this before.
You always need more.
Rent goes up. Alimony.
You feel so stretched, and there was
some cash just sitting there.
I'm really sorry.
You're sorry you got caught.
If you were really sorry,
you would have turned yourself in.
[CHUCKLES]
Come on. Who the hell would do that?
Shit. I can't get
ahold of his machine.
What kind of plan is this?
We can't even reach Shane.
I don't feel right at all.
Part of me wants it to go down
tonight, get this all over with.
But we can't let Vic go alone. If Shane
shows up, brings Army, it's two on one.
I know, I know...
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey. Where the hell is Vic?
I've been looking for him everywhere.
We haven't seen him for a while.
Hey, that's my cell.
Yeah, watch commander found it.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Your phone was here.
What was I supposed to call?
Never mind.
Hey. It's the way Vic wants it.
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
SHANE: Hey. Hey, I've been
trying to reach you.
Look, uh...
Look, I need your help
with something.
Can you meet me? Just you?
Yeah. Sure, where?
[WHISTLE BLARING]
SHANE:
Hey.
Thanks for coming. Uh...
Look, uh...
I'm in some serious shit.
Hey. Hey, what the hell are you doing?
What the hell's the matter with you?
Bugged your car.
It's you or me, right?
I guess it's you.
No. No, no, no, look, I'm explaining.
Please, listen to me.
Goddamn it, listen to me!
Look, Antwon killed Angie
right in front of me and Army.
He did it with our guns.
That's what I came
to talk to you about!
Thought you had nothing to do
with Antwon.
That's nothing
that we haven't done before.
Look, he's squeezing us.
He says the body will turn up
if I don't...
But I would never do that.
Never. You know that!
Look, I was just bluffing him
to buy time.
We... We took a run at Halpern, he
showed us where Angie's body was,
but we can't get to it
just the two of us.
Army's gun went off. It...
Halpern's still alive,
but once Antwon finds out, I'm dead.
I got Mara and Jackson
out of town, but I'm...
Look, I'm... I'm in trouble, man.
I don't know how it got this deep.
You got one shot.
Take it.
No.
I would never choose him over you.
We let that money-train bullshit
get in the way, but...
Come on, you're my friend.
Look, I need you.
Will you help me?
[###]