Carl and Scooby were murdered.
Stabbed to death in a sewer.
LUCAS: Now Antwon cuts a deal
with DEA and just walks?
RAWLING:
The deal was made behind my back.
ASHER: That shithead killed two of us.
RAWLING: I know.
I am assured that
Antwon's cooperation will
lead to numerous arrests.
LUCAS: Except the prick who
organized it. We should've put a bullet
in him when we had the chance.
RAWLING:
The feeling is understandable,
but I need everyone
to be professional in the street.
This is as painful to me
as it is to you.
Hood's happy. Kill a cop,
cut a deal with DEA and skate.
RAWLING: The department's
looking into that arrangement.
We're gonna do everything
we can to make sure this
doesn't happen again.
PAULA: So the ship's sailed?
Antwon's free?
And there's nothing
we can do about it.
Is it true that they're pulling
the plug on the seizure policy?
The policy's being discussed
by Pol Com tomorrow.
No decision's been made yet.
We're dropping like damn flies
and nobody's paying for it.
We are really hurting
and angry right now.
But we've got
a job to do.
So let's do it.
We have got to undermine
Antwon's deal with DEA.
The same thought's been
ringing in our ear too.
What about Aceveda
and Phillips? You're hanging
from a pretty thin rope.
Yeah, well, they disagree with me
about a couple of things.
But there's one thing
we don't disagree on,
and that's wanting to see Antwon
in a short stay on death row.
Even so, brass will never
sign off
on us undercutting
a DEA investigation.
That's why they can't find out
about it until after we pull it off.
JULIEN:
Help Danny through this trial.
Guide her, Lord.
Give her strength in adversity.
Oh, Jesus, Julien.
Amen.
How you doing?
I'm okay.
I just can't handle all the
"save her, Lord" stuff
right now. You know, it's...
Anyway, he already did, right?
Look, I was just waiting
for you to wake up.
I thought I'd say a prayer.
As long as you're talking to the man
upstairs, just ask him for a Vicodin.
Thanks for your prayers.
I'll come back later.
I'll help you home.
That'd be great.
Thanks.
Anything?
Checked into Aceveda and Antwon.
Aceveda only visited Antwon
one time. No phone calls, no letters.
Aceveda visited another inmate
before that, though.
Who?
RONNIE: Juan Lozano.
VIC: Who's that?
You mean who was that.
Byz Lat who grabbed
Aceveda's gun, then got busted
by him for armed robbery.
What happened to him?
Took a 40-pound dumbbell
to the back of the head in county.
Bled out in his cell.
So Aceveda meets with Juan,
then with Antwon.
Antwon gets a deal, Juan gets killed.
What the hell is up with that?
What?
I heard you visited Juan Lozano
in county the other day.
Here's your doll, okay?
Go play, I'll be right there.
Yeah, he's filed an appeal.
Claims that I forced
his confession.
Lucky for you
he had a little sports injury.
Somebody in county went
Mr. Universe on his skull.
Guy's dead.
Can't say the world
will miss him.
He seems to have
a lot of enemies.
Especially you.
Been going over the paperwork
for his arrest last year.
First he assaults you,
takes your gun,
then you make the collar,
put him away,
go visit him at county,
next thing you know, he's dead.
Well, he's not the first person
to piss off the wrong inmate in jail.
Instead of rehashing the past,
I was hoping
that you could help us
with the future.
In what way?
Your boy Juan,
he have a relationship
with Antwon Mitchell?
Maybe Antwon was
the inmate he pissed off.
Well, Juan seemed pretty desperate.
He lost his juice up in Terminal Island.
Maybe he thought going
after Antwon would get
him back his street cred.
Antwon found out,
struck first?
If Juan was bludgeoned
after Antwon made his deal
with the DEA,
it could kill his immunity.
That's where you come in.
I'm sorry I ever gave
those guys a hand.
Then for Antwon to be responsible
for our cops' deaths,
now maybe this Juan too.
Now, give me some time.
I'll look into it.
Nice to have you on board.
ANTWON:
Bonilla?
He's the solo gatekeeper between
U.S. dirt and El Salvador, man.
And old-school crazy.
You know, a technophobe.
No cell phone, no e-mail.
Everything gets
hand-delivered to him.
Now, I say everything,
I mean everything.
Shipments, distribution,
slaughter crews.
They all go through him.
And him only.
That's why you guys keep
coming up with these dead ends.
GROSSMAN:
He's the only one
that deals directly with...
Here's the rest of what
we have on Mitchell.
Hope it helps.
LAMBERTl: We could've sent an
agent over to pick these up.
I wanted to see him for one last time
before you sent him off to Shangri-la.
GROSSMAN:
You know his full name?
I only know him as Bonilla.
You know, cat's got to be
about 50, 60 years old.
He's given us more in a day
than we got in a year.
But the deal's only good
if his testimony leads to arrests
and convictions.
LAMBERTl:
Only reason we'd do it.
It's gonna be huge.
ANTWON:
They get the messages to him.
LAMBERTl:
I know it's painful.
You have no idea.
ANTWON: Lik e I've been saying,
this Bonilla's the k ey to them all.
[###]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
I just came from the DEA safe house
where they're keeping Antwon.
Hope Mr. Mitchell's
comfortable.
The key target he's giving up
is an El Salvadoran named Bonilla.
Name ring a bell?
No.
He's either lying or this Bonilla's
way high on the food chain.
So we got half a Latino name
in a city of 4 million Latinos?
We should rattle
our boy Gusano.
Shake the Salvadoran tree,
see if Bonilla falls out.
Yeah, this guy is
Antwon's biggest chit.
If we can take down that asshole first,
we blow Mitchell's leverage.
Then we can barter with the DEA.
Bonilla for Antwon,
straight up.
MAN 1:
Check out this fool, homes.
MAN 2:
No way.
[CRASH]
SHANE:
Hands in the air!
VIC: Stay right there,
don't move. Shut up.
What the hell do you want?
Oh, we smelled smoke, thought
the whole place might burn down.
But since we're already here...
Bullshit. Get out of here.
Tear the place apart.
You got it, man.
Hey, hey!
Looking for a big fish
named Bonilla.
I don't know no Bonilla.
Get the crowbars. Pull up
every goddamn floorboard.
LEM: You got it.
Hey, hey, okay!
All right, look,
check the flower store.
Eighth and Western.
You babysit them.
All right.
We're gonna go check this out.
LEM: Yup.
Get them down.
Proud of yourself?
Stood up to Billings, Vic.
No more pranks or jokes since.
Damn straight, I'm proud.
Men, doesn't matter
if they're 5 or 65,
it's all about the pecking order
on the playground.
You're just figuring that out?
Wedding?
CLAUDETTE: Quinceañera, probably.
It's a Latin coming-out party.
They present the girl as a
woman when she turns 15.
Get them while you can.
CLAUDETTE:
Well, it looks like this guy got his.
Everything was fine
until her boyfriend showed up.
It wasn't his fault.
He wasn't supposed to come.
Papi told you.
What's your boyfriend's name?
Alejandro.
My papi hated him.
He told Xylina
to keep him away.
Did Alejandro shoot him?
No.
Then who did?
When my father saw her going to
the parking lot to talk to Alejandro,
he went over there
to tell him to leave.
There was someone else with him.
I heard arguing, then the shots.
Did you see
the other person?
Too many cars.
But she knows.
You're gonna protect the person
who murdered your father?
You're 15. You're supposed
to be a woman.
Start acting like one.
RONNIE:
Unis are rolling up.
The captain said Bonilla
was old, like 50 or 60.
These guys just
got out of diapers.
Hey.
It's tar.
Where you from, ése?
Jalisco, Mexico.
Mexico?
Gusano humped us.
He sent us to bust
his competition.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
Gusano sent us
on a wild-goose chase.
No shit?
Yeah, gave us a Mexican tar house.
You still got them?
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Yeah. Hey, shut up.
Yeah, we're coming back
to have a little chat.
Hey, shut up. English only.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Hey, hey, hey, sit down, sit down.
Lem, what's happening?
Go ahead, shoot.
Get your asses down!
You'll never find Bonilla.
Goddamn it!
Lem? Lem?
I said sit down!
[GRUNTING]
Shots fired. Hold it.
Officer needs assistance.
[TYRES SCREECH]
SHANE: Hey, hey, hey.
VIC: All right, all right.
SHANE: Hey.
VIC: Lem.
You all right?
Yeah.
Where's Gusano,
man?
He got away.
Hey, hey, hey.
[SIRENS WAILING]
What the hell happened?
My fault.
I left him alone.
Lem kicked some serious ass.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, fine.
We got a lead
from our guy Gusano.
We left Lem to watch him
while we checked it out.
He took down two of them,
but Gusano bolted.
Way to take care of yourself.
LEM: Thanks.
What about the lead?
Turned out to be bullshit.
You still think Gusano
can take us to Bonilla?
Emolia's a CI of mine.
She worked as an H-cutter
for a lowlife named Pittario.
He was our initial contact
for Gusano.
Hello. I'm Captain Rawling.
We've lost track of Gusano.
Any help you can give us finding him
would be extremely valuable.
I don't know much.
I talked to him on the phone.
Saw him a couple of times
when he stopped at Pittario's.
How did Pittario
get in touch with him?
Called him.
I never knew the number.
Do you know anyone
else connected with him?
Any friends, associates?
Have you ever heard
of a guy called Bonilla?
I met Gusano's girlfriend.
She knew I had a kid.
So I babysat for her
a couple of times.
Where'd you babysit?
At her place.
Rosaria? Get out.
[LATIN MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[ROSARIA SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
RONNIE:
Clear.
Looks like a little family vacation.
Oh, hey, check this out.
Found it by the phone.
Directions to Industrial
Discount Clothing.
It's off Rampart.
I shop there.
That explains a few things.
Come on, brother, let's go get you
the arresting officer's discount.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
This where you gonna go
meet Gusano?
No means yes.
CLAUDETTE:
This must be horrible for you.
Your father killed
on your quinceañera.
Look, we believe you
when you say he didn't do it.
But he knows who did.
And if we can't
clear Alejandro,
that makes your boyfriend
an accessory to murder.
But he didn't shoot him.
But he's protecting
the killer.
Your boyfriend's friend
murdered your father.
My father tried
to throw them both out.
Why'd he have to do that?
It was my quinceañera.
Alejandro's scared,
and he should be.
He'll go to prison.
But if you don't mind waiting...
Twenty, 30 years sound good?
Boy's name is Miguel.
He's crazy.
Always on drugs.
Alejandro is not like that.
Gusano.
See if there's an entrance
in the back.
Get out of here.
[LATIN MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[MEN SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
RONNIE: Police!
Get on the ground right now!
Get down right now!
[ALL SHOUTING]
[GRUNTING]
Bitch.
Dealing, concealed weapon,
dealing.
Dealing again. All kicked down.
Must have some powerful
connections, Gusano.
Somebody's paying
for the lawyer.
I guess they'll pick up the tab
for you and your idiots trying
to kill a police officer.
You're lucky. We don't want you.
Even luckier, you hook us up,
you can help yourself.
Look, let me talk to him,
man to scum.
Give us up Bonilla,
I'll get my guy to drop the charges.
We'll go our separate ways.
No one will know we ever met.
Yeah, except I'm still out
a key of tar, thanks to you, puta.
You listen to me, shithead.
I did you a favour
by getting that tar back to you.
Whatever that crap was,
it wasn't tar.
I tried to pass that fake shit
down to one of my hookups.
Looked like I was
trying to play his ass.
I had to kick him down with
two keys just to make it right.
So don't think I owe you a favour.
Don't dick me around.
You left me holding a pile of shit.
Gusano claims the dope
we returned was bogus.
Is that possible?
Pittario sometimes had me
thin out his supply.
Not thin, fake.
EMOLIA:
I don't know nothing about that.
Gusano thinks I'm in on it?
We'll keep you hidden.
Vic, check this out.
Gusano's phone.
All regular numbers, no names.
But look at these.
They're coded?
RONNIE: Yeah, third-grade code.
Instead of 213,
he's got 324.
Dipshit's adding one to every number.
Let me see that.
Hey, Vic.
I looked into this possible
relationship between Juan
Lozano and Antwon Mitchell.
There's no connection.
Except you visited
both of them in prison
the day that
Lozano was killed.
Look, Juan was killed
before Antwon made his deal.
So there's no violation.
So basically, you got zero.
Yeah.
Maybe I should do some digging
into what got this Juan killed.
Why do I get the feeling
that you're actually working
another angle?
Maybe I should do
some digging to see
what you're up to today.
If we can bust the main target
of the DEA's case, this Bonilla,
we can kill Antwon's deal,
get him to pay for Carl and Scooby.
I'm taking a chance
telling you this.
But we may need you to help the feds
swallow the pill when the time's right.
Now, why would
I want to assist
on an unauthorized investigation
that could blow up in all of our faces?
Why would I wanna
look the other way
on this whole weird
Juan-Antwon-Aceveda triangle?
I want Antwon
for those murders.
Dig all you want,
I've got nothing to hide.
But I'm still gonna
help you, if you need it,
because I want justice
for Carl and Scooby too.
Either way, I'm good.
You got a lot of friends
in funny area codes.
434, that's Virginia.
324, that doesn't even exist.
You better start talking
or we're gonna call a few.
Don't forget to subtract
one from every number.
Huh?
Yeah, 324, that's really 213.
Really?
434, that's really 323,
right here in Los Angeles.
Nice job, windtalker.
If the Germans had you
in World War II,
we could've stopped
that thing before it started.
[PHONE DIALLING]
All right.
[RINGING]
[MAN SPEAKS IN SPANISH
OVER PHONE]
Hello, who's this? Alberto?
MAN: Alberto.
This is Detective Mackey.
I'm at the station with your
friend Gusano.
Yeah, he thinks you have
some information you'd
like to share with us.
Hello?
Alberto doesn't care to share.
We keep letting
our fingers do the walking,
won't be long till we're talking
to Bonilla or one of his goons.
Better think about
helping us, quick.
Bonilla loves music.
He's got a club on 8th.
That his corporate headquarters?
Place where he warehouses
his product?
No. He just hangs out there.
He loves music,
poppies, black whores.
Who doesn't?
SHANE: Looks like a goddamn
Viagra convention.
Hanging with the Depends crowd
keeps Bonilla under the radar.
I get that low-pro, you tie off my
colostomy bag and you call it a day.
Man, you're gonna be
on wife number, what, six by then?
Five.
[ALL LAUGHING]
VIC:
This better be our guy.
Antwon's kissing fed ass
and we're losing time.
SHANE:
Hey.
Gusano says he likes to burn coal.
Yeah, well, three hotties like that,
you tell Santa I been naughty.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Captain. We nailed the shooter
in the quinceañera murder.
Kid named Miguel.
RAWLING: Good.
There's something else.
You're gonna wanna hear this.
Kid's a pill freak. Found
some scrip bottles in his car
when we picked him up.
CLAUDETTE:
All from the same place.
The foster home
Joya was assaulted in.
Was there a date
on those bottles?
CLAUDETTE:
One of them's only a few days old.
According to Family Services,
there's some new kids in that
house, teenagers.
One of them goes to school
with our shooter.
That place was supposed
to be shut down.
What the hell
is Family Services doing?
Anything else you need?
No. I'm just gonna...
Thanks... . watch some TV
and probably fall asleep.
All right, I'll check in later.
Hey, Julien.
Yeah.
I've been thinking
a lot about
the head-butting and everything
that went on between us,
you know, with the injunctions
and the seizures and everything.
Now you're the only one
taking care of me.
You'd do the same for me.
I'm glad you know that.
Why are the Walkers
still supervising children?
Their foster-care licence
is under appeal.
They have a right
to operate until a final
decision has been made.
We have criminal charges
pending against them.
Misdemeanour charges,
and they're presumed innocent.
Two months since that little girl had
drain cleaner forced down her throat,
one of their kids
is selling prescription
meds out of that house.
When do you get mad?
Give me the name of the kid
dealing and I'll handle it.
What I'll give you is notification.
We're seizing the Walkers' house.
What?
If you won't shut it down, I will.
Isn't that a little bit out of your realm?
Excuse me, I'm done talking to you.
Round up some unis.
We're seizing the Walkers' house.
I thought there was
a moratorium on seizures.
I'm making an exception.
They're having a meeting
about it tomorrow.
If you throw this in their face now,
it doesn't help the policy or you.
Well, this was the Walkers'
second strike, I'm not gonna
give them a third. So do it.
I'll take the heat.
If she's gonna hang herself,
there's nothing you can do
about it.
We just have to be careful
we don't get caught in the
middle again.
I'm not sticking
my nose anywhere.
You know, if she goes,
they'll come to you
to take over.
They don't want me.
They'll get some company
yes-man jellyfish from outside
that'll keep us all in line.
Black Betty's taking a little stroll.
This hood,
we better protect her.
[BAND PLAYING]
Hey, darling. How much
for a blowjob?
I ain't no ho.
VIC: No.
You just joined grandpa's
harem for the free paella.
Oh, man, come on.
I just need a smoke.
Looks more like you need
a nap. What are you on?
Nothing.
Sister's oozing O.P.
What you want?
VIC: Bonilla.
You've been
with him all day?
He in town,
I'm with him every day.
Anybody drop by his club?
Tipping him off about the cops, huh?
He don't tell me shit.
I don't have time for this.
VIC:
Oh, shit.
[BOOGIE COUGHING]
God, are you all right?
LEM:
There's some blood in that.
Looks like an ulcer. If you don't
get that thing treated for...
It'll kill me, I know.
That's the plan.
Here's a new plan. I'm gonna get
the city to pay for your medical bills.
We're gonna fix up your gut,
you're gonna answer a few
questions, all right?
Please don't be
screwing with me.
I'm not.
One of his soldiers passed
a message, really pissed him off.
You know, more than usual.
Something about the stuff
being moved to la cueva.
The cave. What's that?
Don't know.
Just passed on the message.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
[RINGING]
Yeah. You still got Gusano?
RAWLING [OVER PHONE]:
Antwon gave up Gusano to DEA.
Lamberti and Phillips are taking
him away in about two minutes.
We only need him for one.
Get his phone.
You have time for one
phone call. Make it now.
Get Bonilla on
the phone now!
SHANE:
Guy who doesn't like to use
cell phones, must be important.
El Asshole better talk fast.
Yeah, I got busted.
They think
I'm talking to my attorney.
They're asking me
about la cueva.
VIC: So much for age and wisdom.
Shithead's going for it.
[BONILLA SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[MAN WHISTLES]
Shit. Spotters.
[GUNSHOTS]
[MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
RONNIE:
Go.
VIC:
I got Bonilla!
Stop!
[MAN YELLS]
LEM: Get your ass over here.
Get over here.
Shane, get it out.
Hurry up!
Shit.
Come on, buddy.
Little light reading for the DEA?
Jesus Christ.
Shipping receipts, distribution
charts. Pretty meticulous.
We got names
from D.C. to San Salvador.
This will put the Salvadorans
back two years. Nice work.
Number one on our most wanted.
Some coincidence.
Yeah, well, my guys were
working a routine sting and
they just stumbled across this.
And you just happened
to nail the one godfather
with the Salvadoran Rolodex.
The one Antwon Mitchell's
been telling us all about.
Sometimes you just get lucky.
LAMBERTl:
I'm taking him and those files.
Right after he gets processed
for attempted murder.
His guys took shots
at my officers.
We'll also need to log
all that stuff into evidence.
You do that,
his organization will have time
to learn about his capture
and seal off the damage.
RAWLING:
I got him fair and square.
He's a goddamn whale to us.
You really expect
that I'd let him go?
What do you want?
I want Antwon Mitchell.
I'll run it up the ladder.
Cover things here. I'm leading
a seizure down the road.
What? What seizure?
A kid selling scrips from
that abusive foster home
a couple of months back.
Pol Com's meeting tomorrow.
A seizure's the worst thing
you can do.
We just busted Bonilla,
snagged Antwon.
I think I just bought myself
a little cover.
Or we can quit
while we're ahead.
Duly noted.
Again, nice work.
All right, come on.
Why do I have to go?
I didn't do anything.
CLAUDETTE:
You sure about this?
We busted the actual
dealer, 14-year-old.
Assigned to the house
three weeks after Joya's rape.
You still have some doubts?
Glad you could make it.
I'm glad too.
You're out of control.
And now everyone can see that.
I'll take these
children now.
That scares
the shit out of me.
These kids will end up
sleeping in my office tonight.
At least it won't be here.
And now you've shut down this home.
Congratulations.
You think it's about
shutting down one home?
This system fails
thousands of kids every year.
This is about not putting up
with this shit anymore.
Cass?
Cassidy?
What are you doing here?
Dad had to work late.
And I'm taking you home.
Grab whatever you need
and let's go.
Hello.
We were studying.
We didn't hear the door.
Who are you?
Evan.
Nice to meet you,
Mrs. Mackey.
Where are your books?
VIC:
What's going on?
I saw something when
I went to get Cassidy
at your apartment.
What?
She was there with a boy.
Evan something.
He lives in your building.
It took them a long time
to get to that door.
What were they doing?
She says studying,
but there were no books.
She's been lying to me lately,
and when she's not lying to me,
she's shutting me out.
You know what they say,
11 's the new 13.
No shit.
Mom tells me
you had a friend over.
She makes a big deal
out of everything.
Well, that's her job, right?
Come on, Cass, you know
you're not supposed to have
anyone over there alone
without Carmen or I there,
let alone some cute boy, right?
We weren't doing anything.
Okay.
Has he been over there before?
No.
Who is he?
Evan. He lives in 3A.
His folks know
he's been over there studying?
He's cool. Just like you.
Me?
Yeah.
Other kids like him
and he doesn't take
shit from anyone.
Cassidy.
No. No.
You understand there's
more important things
to being a person, right?
Like being honest,
trustworthy.
Someone caring about you.
I like him.
Why did Mom have to say anything?
She didn't get you
and now she doesn't get me.
Stupid.
I had every reason
to seize that house.
Neglected, unsupervised
foster kids selling
prescription drugs
that contributed to a murder.
It's a PR win for us.
This isn't about seizures.
Then why the executioner looks?
The Department of Justice
has been on the phone with
the mayor ever since
you twisted DEA's arm
to hand over Mitchell.
They're threatening to pull
federal funds for everything
from law enforcement
to drug treatment.
I gave them Bonilla.
They got what they wanted.
You made them eat shit. And now
they're making the mayor eat it.
If you think he's gonna let them
yank tens of millions of dollars
from this city...
I'll apologise.
ACEVEDA: The DEA chief
doesn't want your apology.
He wants your job.
And now the mayor wants it too.
Pol Com's recommending
you be relieved of duty.
PHILLIPS:
And the chief's decided
to act on the request.
And no one's
gonna fight for me?
Cops watching
each other's backs?
I tried. I explained the situation
to my colleagues.
I got DEA to hand
Antwon over to us.
But that's where
my juice stops.
So now you're letting
DEA buy my job?
I'm sorry it ended like this.
You'll fight for me,
right, Roy?
The chief too.
Because you know that Farmington
is better off now then when I found it.
Because the seizures
were working.
Because I made sure
that Antwon Mitchell paid
for what he did
to our two cops.
I looked after them,
now you'll look after me, right?
I don't have much time.
What is it?
You were right
about the Strike Team.
Emolia, come in here.
Emolia's one of our Cls.
She's made money
in the past by giving up tips
on El Salvadoran runners.
Now, on the sixth of this month,
she was cutting H
for her dealer, Pittario,
when Detective Curtis Lemansky
had words with him,
assaulted him and confiscated
a kilo of tar heroin.
Now, those drugs were
never logged into evidence.
When was this reported?
GINO:
Emolia called in one of my
colleagues immediately.
They were able to ID Lemansky
from her description,
searched his vehicle
while he was sleeping,
procured the heroin and replaced it
with a non-narcotic substance.
I thought you were Vic's CI.
Whoever's got the money.
Are you moving on Lemansky?
Not yet.
My boss wants to use this
to net the whole team.
Vic likes me
and my boy.
He wants to
take care of us.
We can use that.
I just lost my job.
This is someone else's problem.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[DOOR OPENS]
You are gonna appeal, right?
If I lose, they take my pension.
I've had my run.
I never got to put this up.
Carl and Scooby's.
Families said
I could frame them.
Make sure this gets hung in a place
where everyone can see them.
I will.
Ma'am, Assistant Chief
Phillips sent us over.
We're to escort you
out of the building.
VIC: Hey, guys,
she's a captain, not a criminal.
We're just carrying out
our assignment.
Well, not tonight.
We're waiting for Antwon Mitchell
to be remanded into our custody.
The captain has to make that arrest.
OFFICER:
As long as it's not too long.
All right, Cass,
get in the car.
I love you.
I've gotta get back
to Matt and Megan.
Are you done here?
Not yet.
But everything's
squared away with Cassidy.
No more hanging around
with boys in empty apartments.
I guess she listens to you.
Yeah.
Listen, uh...
Maybe she should
move back in with you.
Are you serious?
Well, she's getting to be that age.
She needs her mom.
This is because
of what happened?
It's a lot of things.
There's gonna be more boys,
other stuff.
You can keep an eye on her
better than I can.
You sure?
Positive.
Thanks.
Antwon Mitchell.
You're under arrest
for conspiracy
to commit the murders
of officers Carl Miller
and Wayne Haimes.
[GATE CLOSES]
Right over there's great.
Okay.
Thanks.
I signed a six-month lease.
Only now, not only do the
neighbours not want me here,
neither does
the department.
I guess that means
you're staying.
Yeah. Might be fun.
I like the place.
It was good working with you.
What's gonna happen to you now?
What do you mean?
I feel like I started something
with you, but I didn't get to finish it.
We got Antwon Mitchell.
Yeah.
You ever think about
how it's all gonna
end up for you?
I'll take things as they come.
Promise me you'll take a good look
at where you're going.
And you take care of yourself.
As long as you promise
to do the same.
Yeah.
Good luck.
You too.
Wagenbach.
Yes, sir.
Don't know if you heard what
happened, but your captain's
been relieved of duty.
Yeah.
We need someone to cover
in an interim capacity.
Claudette's the best person.
She's learned...
I'd like you to step up.
Me?
There's no guarantees,
but if it works out,
it could be permanent.
I'm sorry, I can't.
Not that I'm not honoured,
flattered.
But can't leave my partner.
More valuable to you on the street.
Well, I'd like you upstairs.
To be honest, if you think
I'm the kind of guy you're
looking for,
you've made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
What was that about?
He asked me to be the
company yes-man jellyfish.
I told him to shove it.
Sometimes you have to take
the moral high ground.
One day you'll understand.
We're all heading over to Jamie's
to celebrate nailing Antwon
and closing Carl and Scooby's case.
You wanna join?
I'm sure we could all use a few.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
MAN:
You and me, for crying out loud.
RONNIE: It's Danny.
VIC: Hey, hey, hey.
[ALL CHEERING AND SHOUTING]
Hey.
VIC:
Let the hero sit down.
All right.
You want a beer?
No, I'm still
on pain medication.
Anybody got a glass?
[ALL LAUGHING]
Hey, hey, get them up,
get them up. Come on.
To Carl and Scooby,
a couple of good cops.
ALL:
Cheers.
Right?
[LEM SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[ALL CHATTERING AND LAUGHING]
[ALL CHEERING AND SHOUTING]
Get a room.
[###]