Nice to see you, man.
How was your week?
It was okay. How was yours?
ANTWON: Smooth.
Matter of fact, I hit a trifecta.
Lost a half a million dollars
in product in the church seizure.
Six of my top soldiers
got busted, but the highlight...
was the El Salvadorans
cut off my supply.
Well, you'll find a
new pipeline to tap.
ANTWON:
Yeah, but in the meantime,
how are we gonna get back
all that money I lost.
You're a drug dealer.
Why don't you consider it
the cost of doing business?
ANTWON:
So you're saying
my business model's flawed?
Maybe I need a new partner.
Buy in's 20 grand, cash.
My hands by tomorrow.
Thought you didn't smoke
the shit you sold. Come on, man.
I don't have that kind
of cash lying around.
Look, man, I know
you been skimming.
Consider it a cost
of doing business.
[SIGHS]
Plus one more thing.
What?
That's Kozodav?
Man, he doesn't look all that.
Don't let him fool you.
His enemies are all fish food
in the L.A. river.
That's Kozodav's car?
VIC: Yup.
Cover me while I replace
the hard drive underneath.
Man, dudes are 30 feet away.
Can't we do it later?
The hard drive's full and Kozodav's
been talking about something big.
If something's on that disk,
we gotta know pronto.
Forget what these guys
have been talking about.
What's Shane been saying to Antwon?
VIC:
Nothing incriminating.
You've seen the tapes?
Well, Ronnie has.
Don't worry about it.
We're watching.
Oh, shit.
The Russians are coming.
Hurry up.
[MAN SPEAKING
IN RUSSIAN]
Evening, gentlemen.
Can I help you, officer?
I thought the Moscow
ballet was in town and
then I saw the ink.
New policy says I gotta get
name, rank and serial number,
comrade. Let's go.
Save the shakedowns
for the niggers and spics.
I got a Jew lawyer.
His name is Paul Hirschheimer.
You wanna talk with me, call him.
LEM:
Got a gun.
VIC:
Coping an attitude's one thing.
Coping a Glock is another.
Might be time
to get that Jew on the phone.
He's a bodyguard.
He's got a permit to carry.
[SIGHS]
Well, I'm afraid I owe you
gentlemen an apology.
You won't be
bothered again.
Video transfer of the hard drive we
pulled from Kozodav's car last night.
He hired someone
to torch a building to
pay off an insurance scam.
Mention when?
No, but the contract's out.
Could happen as early as today.
Know the arsonist's name
or the target?
Nothing. Sounds residential.
Shithead joked
there were only
Mexicans living there.
If we arrest him right now,
how bad can we hurt him?
We've got over 10 counts
of extortion, racketeering,
grand theft.
He'll do a minimum 20.
So we bring him in,
use that as leverage to get
him to give up the arsonist.
It's time we shut this down,
declare victory.
I'll call the chief.
Get a team together, bring him in.
RAWLING:
Vic.
I had some doubts about
you handling both the
seizures and the garage sting.
But great work.
I couldn't have done it
without Ronnie.
Nice work.
Big chief.
Vic need him new driving machine,
so he can catch him bad guys.
Knew you had some Spanish,
didn't know you knew smoke signals.
Hey, there's a criminal somewhere
out there driving my new ride.
I got two Laker tickets
for the one who seizes it first.
Yeah, what do you have in mind?
VIC:
Hey, Dutchboy!
What are you driving these days?
Subaru.
Anything but a Subaru.
[OFFICERS CHUCKLING]
All right, we'll have you
riding in style in no time.
Something fast. I can't take down
these ROC assholes
doing zero to 60 in four minutes.
RAWLING:
Let's find the big guy
a new car.
LEM:
So we gonna bust these
Russians or what?
Captain's running late.
Can't start without her.
[WHISPERING]
Bringing him back
wasn't my idea.
Captain wanted someone
from Juvie in house.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
VIC:
You people all know
your assignments.
Take up positions in 20 minutes.
RAWLING: Hold off, everyone.
VIC: What's going on?
Change in plans.
ACEVEDA:
That church you raided last week?
[PEOPLE SHOUTING ON TV]
VIC [ON TV]:
Hold it, Muncelle.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING ON TV]
RAWLING:
That is not how it went down.
People were not screaming.
This tape has been edited.
Where's the untouched version?
This is the version the
local news stations have.
It hits the air tonight at 6.
RAWLING: Where'd we get it from?
My press secretary had it slipped
to him as a favour by a reporter.
Does he have the original?
I don't think so, but I'd
worry more about how you're
gonna spin this nightmare.
I have 12 kls. of heroin
in my evidence room.
That's all the spin that I need.
PHILLIPS:
Public Relations is working
on our response.
In the meantime, the
Organized Crime Unit is gonna
handle the Kozodav sweep.
This is John Sullivan,
their team leader.
Congratulations. You guys
did a hell of a job.
Put together a great case.
Yeah. Our goddamn case.
We worked long and hard
on this case, Roy.
We deserve to make this bust.
PHILLIPS:
Getting Kozodav is a big win for us.
We can't risk tainting it by having
the arresting officer and his captain
plastered all over the news
the same day.
He has been pissing on
this policy from day one.
Last quarter's numbers. For all
the great work you've been doing
crime is actually up
4 percent in this district.
I promised my constituents
that I would review
all of these seizures
on a one-by-one basis.
And I expect full access
to all of your files.
PHILLIPS:
Detective Mackey will get
you up to speed on the op.
Provide you any
support you need.
All clear?
Crystal.
[###]
I'll look into the tape.
Try and track down the original.
We'll get through this.
In the meantime,
Shane brought over a case from Vice.
Work it with him.
VIC: What is it?
He found a Byz Lat in the state pen
willing to act as an informant
in return for early release.
Prison Bureau almost
never grants early release.
Yeah. Well, the chief went
to bat with the Bureau himself.
Shane's informant is banger
buddies with Ernesto Dienta,
Byz Lat contraband king.
Guns, drugs,
you name it, he gets it.
Not for long.
RAWLING: Use Lemansky.
I'd like to see how your old
Strike Team works together.
Great.
Any progress on Lem's missing girl?
Still working on it.
I'm not feeling a happy ending
to that story.
Captain, I got a call
from Mission Cross.
Little girl was just brought
into the ER with burns to
her throat and face.
What happened?
DUTCH: They think she was forced
to drink some acid.
Doctors are treating her now.
How old is she?
According to the foster dad, 7.
RAWLING: She's a foster kid?
Yeah.
Give me a minute, I'll join you.
This is Hielo Gutierrez.
Did a nickel in Chino
for armed robbery.
SHANE:
Covered his Byz Lat homeys'
asses when he got pinched.
Thanked him by only visiting him
once during his entire stretch.
That's more than I'll be seeing
those fools when they're behind bars.
Payback's gonna taste sweeter
than teenage booty.
He's only been a citizen
for a month.
His buddy Ernesto's
integrating him back into the fold.
Ready?
Where we headed?
Echo Park. Ernesto and Hielo
have a meeting with a busboy
who works on an Indian
reservation in Cabazon.
What's the grift?
SHANE: Cigarettes.
Indians buy them tax-free.
Byz Lats turn them around
for face value, tax is pure profit.
Crossing state lines.
That makes it a federal beef.
When it comes time to make
the busts, we can RICO their asses.
Sweep up half
the Byz Lats.
I learned from the best.
Vic and me will ride together.
You ride with Armie and Hielo.
Ready? Let's go.
Stay cool. Play the
good soldier, all right?
The guy with Hielo, that's Ernesto.
He's the Byz Lat contraband king.
Guess he's gonna have to run
his kingdom from a cell in Chino.
The other Mexican, that's Garcia.
He's the one who works
on the Indian reservation.
GARCIA:
I've been known to get
my hands on a pack or two.
ERNESTO:
I need cartons. Lots of them.
GARCIA:
I can get 300
cartons a month.
ERNESTO:
How much?
GARCIA:
Ten thousand in cash,
on delivery.
Got him hooked,
about to get booked.
That was quick. Hey, hope you
didn't mind me calling your cell phone.
Not at all. Corrine Mackey,
this is Capt. Monica Rawling.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. How's the girl?
Joya's unconscious.
Her oesophagus is badly burned
and there's stomach damage.
She's been put on a ventilator.
DUTCH: Where are the parents?
That's her foster father
over there. He brought her in.
There are also signs
of a sexual assault.
Waiting for the results
of the rape kit.
What did she swallow?
Some sort of household cleaner.
Should have killed her. It still might.
Can we see her?
RAWLING:
Child Services?
Sending over a case worker now.
Yeah, that'll fix everything.
Was Joya in a private
or group home?
CORRINE:
I don't know.
Could be an attempt by the rapist
to destroy DNA evidence.
If the sexual assault extended
to an oral nature.
Thanks for calling right away.
Bring the foster care father
back to the Barn. Get his take
on what happened.
We'll run by his house,
see what we can learn.
You're splitting us up?
I'm just marshalling our resources.
Hi, come on in.
RAWLING: Captain Rawling.
LIZ: Hi.
CLAUDETTE: Claudette Wyms.
Hi. How's Joya?
She's suffered a lot of damage.
It's terrible. These children
have so many problems.
They experience violence
so they get violent.
Hi.
RAWLING: Who was home?
Uh, all the kids. We have seven
with us now. Frank was here.
I was out getting groceries.
And he called me on his way
to the hospital.
Hi. What's your name?
Bibi.
We need to see all the children.
LIZ: Okay.
Gather everybody.
Bring them to the living room.
Can you show us where
your husband found Joya?
Sure. This way.
Uh, this is the kids' bathroom.
Over here.
Sorry about the smell.
Joya threw up.
You found an empty bottle
of drain cleaner. Where is it?
I'll ask Bibi, she's the oldest.
She looks out for the younger ones.
CLAUDETTE:
These meds belong
to all the kids?
LIZ:
Yeah. They're all
taking something.
Like I said, they
have problems.
RAWLING:
Why is a padlock on this door?
Oh. The closet is our safe place.
RAWLING:
Safe for who?
CLAUDETTE:
You lock the kids up in there?
LIZ:
Yeah, we give them time-outs
on occasion.
Most of them
have behavioural disorders.
This lets them calm down.
Keeps the other kids safe.
You realise you've admitted
to child endangerment?
LIZ:
My husband says it's not.
I mean, people send kids
to their rooms, right?
This is the only space we have.
Any of the kids
capable of attacking Joya?
Making her drink Drano?
Take your pick.
Got an update?
Yeah, the prelim just came back.
Joya wasn't raped this
morning. The healing
looks to be 24 to 48 hours.
What about the father?
DUTCH: Definitely a control freak.
So the closet-o'-horrors
doesn't surprise me.
Not sure he's a rapist though.
Files from the foster care kids?
Yeah, Child Services just
sent them over. They read
like the Marquis de Sade.
One of them's
probably our liquid plumber.
So we have six suspects.
DUTCH: You mean seven.
Well, I'm not counting Joya.
Neither am I.
There were six kids.
We met them all.
Not according
to these CS documents.
Uh-huh.
"Darnell Garry. Age 17.
Bipolar, history of violence."
So where is he?
Tell us about Darnell Garry.
He was the oldest.
Ran away about three months ago.
RAWLING:
You never called
Children's Services?
FRANK:
I did. Also sent an e-mail.
I can print it out for you.
They never wrote or called
to check on the status?
No. Trust me, lady,
I've been working
for the county a long time.
I know how to cover my ass.
You kept cashing Darnell's cheques
after he left.
How're you gonna cover your ass
on that one?
My wife handles the books.
We get a lot of cheques
for these kids. It's hard
to know the difference.
We caught the mistake
last month.
Sent them an e-mail to bill us.
You don't seem too broken up
Darnell took off.
FRANK:
Darnell was uncontrollable.
Belonged in a hospital
or a prison, not my house.
Sounds like your closet
therapy didn't take, huh?
Child endangerment's a crime.
RAWLING:
Consider your
foster care licence gone.
How hard we press charges?
That's in your court.
When was the last time
you saw Darnell?
Couple weeks ago.
Caught him in the house
when he thought Liz and I were gone.
Stealing groceries,
other kids' prescriptions.
DUTCH:
Any idea where he went after that?
Try his mom. She's a junkie.
Him too, probably.
Only meds he didn't take were the
ones that actually might help him.
RAWLING:
The dad reported
Darnell Garry left months ago.
How come someone didn't file
a missing person's report with us?
There's no record of him
being missing.
This is a copy
of the e-mail he sent you.
He's been gone for three months.
How many visits have you had
there since then?
Two.
And you didn't notice that
one of the kids was missing?
Cheques were never stopped. Darnell
was never flagged for a follow-up.
You know who ends up doing
that follow-up? My cops or the ME.
Half these kids are gonna
end up in the penal system.
They're time bombs.
We shuffle them around from
place to place, lose track of them...
until they explode.
Look, I'm here as a courtesy.
If you wanna lecture
about the foster care system,
teach an extension
class at UCLA.
You know, I understand
the difficulties and limitations.
I deal with my own,
but we have got to do better.
No, you mean
I've got to do better.
If we got a missing teen,
stop taking it out on me
and do something to find him.
In Domestic, I had to watch
you people on a daily basis.
I saw more concern
for filling federally funded beds
than in helping
reunite families.
We've got tens of thousands
of kids to care for.
This is one mistake.
This is a kid.
So is the one in the hospital
with half a throat.
You don't like my job performance,
call my supervisor.
Fine. I'll explain
why you've been arrested.
Hey, for what?
Negligence, child endangerment.
You were assigned to that
household, so I'm holding
you responsible. Officer, take him.
SANDERSEN:
You gotta be kidding me.
What's she doing?
RAWLING: Hey!
Standing on her soapbox.
She have her own
or you let her borrow yours?
[###]
VASCO:
What's the problem, officer?
Your plates are expired, Illinois.
Licence, registration.
You boys are enjoying the party.
I smell marijuana.
All right, get out of the car.
Step out now, all of you. Move it.
VASCO:
Come on,
we just seeing the sights.
DANNY:
Put your hands on top of your head
and turn around.
JULIEN: Come on, step forward.
DANNY: Boys affiliated?
VASCO: What?
Gang ink. You got any?
Hey.
Eighth street. What is that,
your Boy Scout troop?
We ain't got no business here.
We just visiting my cousin, that's it.
I'll let your cousin know
when your visiting hours are.
Danny.
DANNY:
Hey, Vic.
I think we got your new
official department issue ride.
Oh!
DANNY: Chicago homeboys
with too much narcotics.
You make that stick,
those tickets are all yours.
Oh, leather seats.
Fully loaded.
For you, I'll even throw in dinner.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
VIC:
What happened?
OCU sat on Kozi cabs for two hours.
Half the Russian mob showed.
Kozodav didn't. Sullivan
made the call to go in anyway.
Kozodav's in the wind?
Yeah, well, Sullivan
said he had no choice.
A residential building
is about to be torched.
He figured he'd press the soldiers,
use them to give Kozodav's location.
Well, they're all asking for lawyers.
Monica got you up to speed?
She gave me the ABC's.
Good. We need your help.
I'll get my team together,
start digging into Kozodav's haunts.
PHILLIPS:
Not for field work.
What do you want my man for?
To help transcribe video tapes.
You oversaw the operation.
If there's any clue to Kozodav's
whereabouts, we need to know.
Where are you going?
Every second I stay here,
Kozodav gets further away.
My boss just gave you an order.
Follow it.
VIC:
You got a minute?
Building full of people is about
ready to burn down, a minute's
about all I got.
Look, I know this church tape
is a problem for you.
But, I should be the
one looking for this guy.
It's OCU's case.
Hey, we've got years, Roy.
Something's up.
All I'm asking
is to shoot me straight.
Whatever you did to piss
off Aceveda? It worked.
He's got leverage with chief
and he's using it.
I'm keeping my nose clean,
I'm doing what I'm told. I'm delivering.
Yeah, you've been doing good lately,
but you got a damaged jacket.
I'm fixing that.
Do yourself and your family a favour.
Whatever you need to do
to make sure Rawling succeeds, do it.
Because the shot
she's giving you,
it may be the last one
you've got in this department.
CLAUDETTE:
We're looking for your son.
Darnell?
You Child Services?
No, we're police.
There was an incident at Darnell's
foster home. He may be a witness.
Whatever it was, he probably did it.
CLAUDETTE: Why'd you say that?
That boy's no good.
Comes around, steals my stuff,
sells it for drug money.
RAWLING: Where does he score?
All over.
I can tell you how he earns his pay.
CLAUDETTE: He's got a job?
Just blowjobs.
He sucks fag dick
on 4th Street.
Tell him I said hey.
I didn't mess with Joya
or make her drink anything.
We'd love to take your word for it
but we're gonna take a DNA sample,
compare it with the semen
we found, just in case.
I ain't giving you
permission for that.
Frank is still technically
your legal guardian.
We have your permission?
Of course.
I may have done some shit.
But what about him? You ain't
gonna let him go free, are you?
DUTCH:
So you did rape Joya?
DARNELL:
You see what I gotta do
on the street to survive.
When am I gonna get me some?
When am I gonna get to bust a nut?
She's 7.
I hope you fry.
This is his fault.
Locking us up in a closet and shit!
A few minutes
to calm you down, you animal!
More like hours!
Sit down.
DARNELL:
He called it the hole.
Put the oldest one in charge,
make them keep order.
Little ones in there crying
and wailing for hours in that closet.
And as for the Drano,
that ain't me.
Sounds like Bibi trying
to keep the peace
so she don't get locked up
in Frank's hole.
SHANE: We need to get Ernesto
to admit that he's selling the
cigarettes across state lines.
But let him say it.
Don't get overeager,
tip your hat.
Don't worry about it, bro.
He thinks of me like a brother.
He won't see nothing coming.
Before I went away,
I banged his 14 year-old sister.
Took her virginity.
Fool didn't have a clue.
Told him I was helping her
with her history homework.
Try the history
of popping cherries.
Why don't you keep it
to yourself, man?
What's your problem, superstar?
If there's grass on the field,
you gotta play ball, right?
Hey, cut it out, man. Cut it out.
LEM: Guy's a dick.
Yeah, well he's my CI
Okay, this is my run.
So just follow my orders.
First one is to give him
and me a little room.
Okay?
All right, showtime,
lover boy.
ERNESTO [ON RADIO]:
Garcia called with the drop point
for the goods.
Doing good, bro.
There's more where this came from
when the smokes get to St. Louis?
Told you not to push it,
you skid mark.
Should've emphasized
the point.
ERNESTO:
Relax. Enough business.
[WHISTLES]
Got you a present
for all your hard work.
Puta's all dressed up
with no one to blow.
Mami's gonna mak e papi happy.
RAWLING:
I looked into the video tape.
the woman who shot it,
her nephew works at
Antwon Mitchell's rec centre.
You think Antwon edited the tape?
Sent it to the press?
I know it's not an accurate depiction
of what happened there.
Help me bury this.
I know the press.
You can't unring this bell.
I'll be handing these seizure cases
over to the police committee.
The rest seem fine.
I also looked into the crime stats.
The numbers are up
because you manipulated yours
to make things look better.
I'm getting punished because
I reported mine accurately.
Sounds to me like now's a good time
to start formulating an exit strategy
for this seizure policy.
The only person who could
take me off this is the chief.
And not without
one hell of a fight from me.
Well, then, I'd start training.
I just spoke to him.
He's still blue in the face from having
to explain to the ACLU lawyers
why you put a cop like Vic in charge
of such a controversial programme.
That's what all this is about.
Mackey.
Starting tonight,
Vic's the face of that church invasion.
Pulling him off the street
might buy you some slack.
He's working. I stand by my choice.
You just won't take help, will you?
Help from you? Sure.
Orders, no.
If Mackey's off the table,
I'm gonna have to set my sights
on the policy in general.
That was an illegal U-turn, right?
DANNY: That's right.
I'm sorry.
I don't know this part of town too well.
And I've been looking for 5 Freeway
for like 20 minutes and in the rain,
it's brutal.
DANNY: It sucks, doesn't it?
MAN: Yeah, it does.
Three blocks, make a right on Prince.
Thank you.
DANNY:
Let me see your licence
and registration, please.
Right.
That an open container?
No. It's corked.
JULIEN:
It's been opened.
That's illegal.
It's from lunch.
Dude, it's a $400 bottle of Pomerol.
I wasn't gonna leave it
for the busboys.
Get out, please.
I had a glass of wine with a client
like three hours ago.
Man, I'm not impaired.
I said out of the car, sir.
All right. Do it?
All right. You heard the officer.
Come on, get out of the car.
Step to the back of the car.
Step up against
the car, please.
Bootleg DVD's.
You intend to sell these?
No, it's for me.
Guy on Olvera sells them cheap.
You affiliated?
What?
With a gang. I see the ink.
Pull up your shirt.
What's your deal, man?
Get your hands off...
Hey.
Ow! Aah! Back off, man!
Take it easy.
All right, look, look.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, officer.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm gonna document his ink,
I'm gonna tow his car in.
If his lawyer can't prove
that he didn't intend
to sell those DVD's,
we'll seize his vehicle.
That's what we do, right?
Might even get me
some Laker tickets.
Hey, Vic. You need to see this.
VIC: Later, okay?
No. Now.
Lock the doors.
This surveillance tape's
from Shane's car last night.
ANTWON [ON TV]:
One more thing.
SHANE:
What?
How would you lik e to get
that little girl's body back?
Your bullets and all.
SHANE: How?
Trade.
Body for a body.
SHANE:
Who?
Vic Mack ey.
His body for hers.
You been telling me
he's behind all my misery.
And he ain't gonna stop
coming after me so...
No way.
Look, man.
I'm offering you a chance
at liberation.
Freedom from the shackles
that bind you.
SHANE:
Know what? I don't give a shit.
You send her goddamn body
to the cops.
Sure you do.
I mean, I send her body
to the po-po, you go to jail.
You go to jail...
who's gonna protect
that pretty little wife
and son of yours?
Body for a body.
Last time I offer.
Let me know when it's done.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Uh, one sec.
RAWLING:
It's Capt. Rawling.
[WHISPERING] Stash it. Nobody
does anything or says anything
about this until I say so, all right?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was locked.
What's up?
Excuse me.
I, uh...
I need you to
take a step back.
Temporarily.
I can't have you heading up
the seizure policy right now.
What are you talking about?
Well, the church raid
stirred up a shit storm.
So you're offering me up
as a sacrifice?
I'm not taking you off it.
I just need you in
a less visible role.
I worked hard for this.
What happened to you
having my back?
I'm protecting the policy.
Protecting your own ass.
I am getting us time to regroup.
Aceveda has the chief's ear.
The guy has got it
out for you and...
And you're too much of a coward
to stand up to him?
Don't make this personal.
Only difference
between you and Aceveda
is you fooled me into
thinking you actually
had a goddamn backbone!
You were the redheaded stepchild
when I arrived here.
I put my ass on the line to
give you a second chance
when nobody else would.
I gave you power.
I gave you respect.
So keep your mouth shut
before you lose both.
I know this is hard,
but I need you to look
at the bigger picture.
[SIGHING]
Hielo's ready to make the buy.
You ready to kick some ass?
Hell, yeah.
Then, good. Let's go.
We found Darnell.
He admitted raping Joya
while you were in charge
at the house.
That true?
CLAUDETTE:
What happened?
RAWLING:
It's okay.
We know about the closet.
It's not his fault.
He's not gonna hurt
you anymore, honey.
I'm sorry. I tried to stop Darnell.
I couldn't.
Then Joya was gonna tell.
You poisoned Joya?
Tried to kill her?
She said that she was
gonna tell her teacher
at school what Darnell did.
We'd all be pulled out of there,
sent somewhere else.
I couldn't take the chance.
Chance at what?
Going someplace worse.
Frank isn't so bad.
Other homes I been at...
At least he doesn't touch me.
DANNY: Oh, come on,
take that shit down.
Guy broke the law.
Yeah, you proved your point.
Not everyone gets treated the same.
You know, shaking down
the white guy might have evened
some intellectural score for you.
But this stunt you pulled this
afternoon, doesn't help anyone.
So what are we
supposed to do, huh?
Sweep everything black and brown
into the same garbage pile?
There was enough drugs in that car
to qualify for an intent to distribute.
They weren't drug dealers.
They were just partying too much.
So being young and stupid
buys them a pass?
No. They broke the law,
they should make restitution.
But how many shifts do you think
this guy had to work in order to
cover the payments on that car?
Give me a break.
After lockup,
how's he supposed to drive
to a job?
So now he starts selling drugs.
All we did was create
another drug dealer.
Look, if it hadn't been for church,
that would've been me 10 years ago.
The streets have changed
a lot in 10 years.
I can't know how you feel every time
you arrest a young black man.
No, ma'am, you can't.
I respect the conflict.
But you became a cop, Julien.
It's clear you won't get
behind this programme.
At the end of the day, I don't give
a shit about race, colour or creed.
Either you're blue or you're gone.
I'll put through
the administrative transfer.
Let the brass decide
where to put you.
Ma'am...
Garcia's van just pulled in.
They're ready to make the buy.
All right. Vic and I are going
in to make sure our CI's safe.
You and Lem stay with
the van, you keep listening.
We don't know we can
trust this Hielo guy, right?
I'm going in too.
Look, I told you to stay.
It's my operation.
Come on. Let's go.
[MEN CHATTERING IN SPANISH]
GARCIA:
Here are the cartons
just like I promised.
Let's see the cash.
ERNESTO:
It's all there.
GARCIA:
It's good.
[CHATTERING IN SPANISH]
LUCY: Are you the captain
who arrested my caseworker?
You must be his supervisor.
Who the hell do you think you are?
He had nothing to do with this crime.
His job was to monitor that family.
These caseworkers are
overstretched. They're not liable.
You don't remember me,
do you?
Monica Rawling,
Domestic Abuse.
You remember
Lisa Rodriguez?
Her father put her
mother in a hospital,
said it was an old boyfriend.
We worked the case together.
What's your point?
Do you remember promising me
you'd get the kids out of that house...
then being overstretched then too?
I want my worker released right now.
I promised Lisa that Daddy
would never hurt her again.
But you let Daddy go home.
He beat her with a golf club.
Two years later, she's still in a coma.
Remember now?
Yeah.
His psych history didn't come out
till the attack.
I warned you about him.
And I had rules and
regulations to follow.
You want perfection? Clean up
your streets before sticking
your nose in my houses.
A raped and poisoned 7-year-old
took me to one of your houses today.
Which had nothing to do
with my caseworker.
It wasn't his fault.
Then whose is it?
I signed off on his work.
If you got a problem with him,
you got a problem with me.
Oh, well, there we agree.
I'll release him.
But the next case of neglect I see,
that worker spends a night in county.
One after that, you'll be
sharing the cell next door.
Pass it on.
I'll follow the van, set up
on the buyers in St. Louis,
we'll bust them both.
This is getting to be a hell of a bust
by the time this thing's through.
Yeah, no shit.
This guy's cold.
Played his pal like no CI.
I've ever seen.
We're gonna ride him all the
way to the Vice hall of fame.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
ARMANDO: Drinks on me tonight.
Yeah?
RONNIE [ON PHONE]:
Kozodav mentioned
a coyote on a tape.
Referred to him as El Callado.
VIC: The quiet one?
Used him a couple times to ferry
soldiers back to St. Petersburg.
You tell OCU yet?
Shit, no.
VIC:
Kozodav's coyote
have a real name?
RONNIE:
Just used a street tag.
All right, you give me one hour,
and then you pass it on to Sullivan.
I'm gonna have to take a rain check
on the cocktails.
SHANE:
What's up?
My boss wants me to fill out
some paperwork.
Another time.
Count on it.
Need a ride?
I'm gonna walk.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
I told you to come alone.
And I don't know you.
VIC:
Maybe.
But I know a member
of your organization
is acting as a criminal informant.
Don't jerk me off, man, all right?
I'm willing to give you his name.
But I'll need something in return.
What's that?
You know a coyote
named El Callado?
Heard of him.
Works for the grande jugados.
The cartels mostly.
He's moving a Russian
mobster named Alex Kozodav
out of the States.
I need to stop him.
This coyote's not Byz Lat.
I'd have to call a lot of favours
just to get a message to him.
How do I know what you're
telling me is worth a shit?
You get him to give me Kozodav.
I'll give you the informant's name.
And I'll make sure that van full
of cigarettes doesn't get busted
on its way to St. Louis.
The Russian's at this address.
Alone or with company?
Alone. Just waiting to get picked up.
Who's the informant?
Hielo Gutierrez.
No. Uh-uh.
You tell me it's Hielo,
I can't believe that.
He's like a brother to me, all right?
He bragged he popped
your sister's cherry
when she was 14.
Said it was so tight
he thought it was her asshole.
Told you he was just helping her
with some history homework.
You do whatever you feel
is appropriate with that info.
I'll make sure
it doesn't blow back on you.
[GRUNTING]
Son of a...
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
You hired an arsonist
to torch a building.
I need his name.
I need an address.
Who is this?
Next word out of your mouth
isn't a name.
I pull the trigger.
Gregor. Gregor Barinat.
I didn't think anybody'd
be here to look over her.
Makes two of us.
Any changes?
RAWLING:
They say she's a little better.
You think I lost it
a little bit today.
We've all got burrs
under our saddle.
RAWLING:
My, uh...
Best friend growing up,
had a father.
Used to knock her around
pretty regularly.
I knew what was happening,
what she was enduring...
but I couldn't.
I just felt helpless.
Feels worse now.
If you're here to take the second shift,
I've got some seizure paperwork
I've gotta prepare
for Aceveda's eyes, so...
Guess who's here, Alex.
It's Gregor.
You were about to torch
those Mexicans in that
apartment, huh?
[GUN COCKS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOTS]
KOZADAV:
Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
I'm not a great cook, sorry.
I thought it was terrific.
CORRINE: Thanks.
You okay?
Yeah.
It's just that little girl, Joya.
I don't know...
Dead bodies, you get used to them,
doesn't affect you.
But there's something about a kid,
you know, hanging on, fighting.
Yeah. I know.
Hey.
DUTCH: Hey.
You want me to read that
to you again?
Come here.
Oh.
Big Buddy Bear.
"Buddy was a big brown bear.
A bumbling, stumbling,
sweet as honey bear."
Goddamn it.
What's up?
Been trying to get in touch
with Hielo for the last hour.
Not answering his cell or at home.
He's probably getting laid.
I spent five years in prison,
you wouldn't get my face
out of snatch for a month.
Chief already made promises to the
Bureau of Prisons to spring him early.
Look, this guy ghosts,
I'm gonna look like an asshole.
ARMANDO:
No worries. He'll show.
RAWLING:
Kozodav?
And the arsonist.
How'd you track him?
Some unis responded
to a shots-fired call.
These two were there
when they arrived.
Cuffed and gagged.
I'll take it any way I can get it.
[###]
Hey.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
ON POLICE RADIO]
I'm a cop
so get that light out of my face
and get out of here.
[###]