CARL:
Wait. Then the guy was just screaming,
so I look down,
and I see in his hand
his nipple ring and his nipple.
[LAUGHTER]
It's all true.
Fortunately, the guy was drunk.
DANNY:
Yeah, but sooner or later,
you sober up,
and you're still
missing your nipple.
DANNY:
How'd you guys log that
into evidence anyway?
Oh, shit, with gloves on.
[LAUGHTER]
I'll be in the car.
Thought he got benched?
His PBA rep appealed,
he's on the street till the hearing.
CARL:
He's pissing a lot a lot of people
off, not being onboard with the captain.
DANNY:
Come on, he's got a right
to take a stand.
He's also got the right
to remain silent.
Okay.
You with me, Scoob?
SCOOBY:
Damn straight.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
1-Tango-17, 242 just occurred.
762 Whitney Avenue, code two.
[MAN GROANS]
DANNY: Talk to you later.
Yeah, I guess
second roll call's over.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
Look, you had a gun
to his head. He's gonna tell you
anything you wanna hear.
It wasn't like that.
How can you know what's in his mind?
If Shane wasn't telling me the truth,
you trust me,
things would've gone down differently.
He was never coming after me.
He's been lying to us for months,
leaking all that intel to Antwon.
He didn't get Angie killed.
Her own mother gave her up to Antwon
before she OD'd.
He had to watch Antwon shoot her
for chrissakes. He's sick about it.
Yeah, so sick all he's worried about
is covering his own ass.
I told him he has to
come clean with everything
that happened with Antwon.
Will that buy him some trust?
We should hear him out.
Boys.
SHANE:
And once he had us on the hook
for Angie, he twisted us pretty hard.
You've already seen the highlights.
And after that, everything else
seemed like small potatoes.
We tipped off the El Salvadorans
in that church raid.
Muled some China White
from San Pedro to L.A.
Antwon was pretty pissed off you
took down those drug dens of his.
And to help ease the pain,
we busted his competitors,
you know,
gave him half the product.
And that's most of it.
Antwon have any relationships
I should know about?
Not many that work.
Beaners hate his ass.
El Salvadorans are losing faith.
ROC, they ignore him.
Asians tolerate him.
Outside the brothers,
he ain't too popular.
These injunctions and seizures
are hitting him harder
than he wants folks to know.
That's why he needed me.
LEM:
What about Army?
He follows my lead.
So he won't blind-side us?
No, no, he's down.
Look, I'm sorry about that little girl.
But it's not too late to get her back,
to give her a proper burial.
So basically you need
our help. Right?
He came clean.
Now, it's time for us to do our part.
ARMY: What?
SHANE: I told them everything.
What everything?
All of it.
How about bouncing that shit off me?
I don't know these guys.
Well, I do.
And we can't handle this alone.
All right. Banger spotters
are there around the clock.
Lost souls usually shuffle in after dark.
Place closes down around midnight.
Find an excuse to roust them out,
bring them to the Barn.
They're One-Niners,
we'll just bust them.
How are you planning
on get Angie's body?
We wait till it's dark. I just don't
know how deep she's buried.
If they planned on having the shithouse
on top, probably not very deep.
We dig her up,
extract our bullets.
Find a really good place to bury her.
Once we have the girl's body, Antwon
doesn't have anymore leverage.
We go at him hard,
put him away for good.
Or we shoot him for resisting.
This is bullshit, man.
Or we can do this,
just the four of us.
No. He's good.
Don't worry. Let's go.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
1-Tango-13, roger.
Respond to 4556 Alexandria Circle,
Apartment 7.
1-Tango-17 has been code six
on a domestic dispute for a while now.
And not responding.
JULIEN:
Roger, this is 1 -Tango-13.
We're on the scene.
DANNY:
Ma'am, are you the one
that made the 911 call?
Yeah, but I told them other cops
they missed him.
How long ago
did the other officers come by?
About a half hour ago.
Why'd you call?
Gideon Mazell,
my ex's kid,
he was trying to break in.
Said he was gonna rape me.
Asshole's been trying to get at me
since I dumped his old man.
Did you see where the other officers
went after they left here?
WOMAN:
Figured they went
looking for Gideon.
JULIEN:
I have to take a look.
1 -Tango-17, you copy?
Carl, Scooby,
you guys on foot?
Anything?
Canvassed the whole area.
There's nothing.
RAWLING:
Shit.
JULIEN:
Half the people
weren't answering their door.
The other half were sleeping.
Use your radio.
Staff, 9-Tango.
I'm code six on Alexandria Circle.
Be advised we have
two officers unaccounted for,
requesting a tac alert.
All watches will be held over.
WOMAN:
Copy that.
We should notify the families.
Carl and Scooby have been missing
at least an hour.
I'm on my way over there right now.
Could be the same hunt.
Antwon sending a message.
Well, if that's true,
they aren't just missing.
Retribution for not killing
the cop he wanted.
Yeah, we know where he likes
to bury bodies.
Jesus Christ.
All right. You, Army and Ronnie
stick to the plan.
Find our missing cops.
We also gotta get a 20 on Antwon.
So we can scoop him up
soon as we find the girl's body.
You come with me.
Let's go.
Want you to go to the end
of the block and keep knocking
till you wake people up.
JULIEN: Yes, ma'am.
CLAUDETTE: Where do you want us?
We're tracking down Gideon Mazell,
he's the subject of the 911 calls.
Steve Billings is on his way down,
so pass on to him what you find.
Captain, Steve's good at what he does.
But we've got officers missing.
If they're alive, they won't be for long,
and your best detectives are here now.
You haven't seen our best game
because of the whole DA thing.
This is too important.
Okay, you're the primaries.
We'll contact the sheriff.
See if they can loan us
some bloodhounds.
Tracking Gideon Mazell.
No, Danny talked to the woman
he was threatening.
So you guys get together. Vic and
his people can work the gang angle.
DUTCH: Where is she?
DANNY: Number 7, upstairs.
Julien, I want you to be
department liaison. Sit with Carl's wife.
I heard what happened.
I wanna help.
Tonight your reserve duty?
No. But I'm still part of this family.
Who can I ride with?
I'll see who's available.
Captain, I knew both those guys.
I should be out there looking for them.
Well, I'm comfortable
if you're at Carl's house.
I don't have time to worry
about whether you'll follow orders.
Danny, I want you to take Aceveda
on patrol with you.
If there are problems,
I wanna hear about it.
Absolutely.
You eve consider this might be
Antwon Mitchell's work?
It's his hood, isn't it?
Yeah, I sent some unis
to pick him up.
Call them back.
I'm all over it. He's MIA.
With our two cops,
that's convenient.
Give me those unis.
I'll sweep up some of his crew,
maybe find Antwon or our guys.
I can only spare
a couple of bodies.
Look, if I wasn't put in
the backseat on this, I could've
stopped this from happening.
You did what you had to do.
I know that.
I just wanna find these guys.
Okay. I'll have Zerkow call them back,
assign them to you.
Appreciate that.
I'd like to help out.
You got any gaps here?
Yeah, check with Dutch and Claudette.
They're over there.
We wanna talk to Antwon.
Yo, he ain't here.
What do you assholes know
about two missing cops, huh?
What's up, man?
Can I see?
You know there's
an injunction, boys.
Ain't no violation, man.
Franklin here's a citizen.
He ain't claiming.
Really?
WOMAN: That's ain't right.
MAN:
Sweating him for Twon.
What are you gonna do,
drop my drawers too, faggot?
MAN:
Hey, Vic!
VIC:
Take this piece of shit punk-ass.
Get them inside, out of sight.
Okay, go to work.
Back in the Barn in an hour.
DUTCH:
Gideon Mazell's address.
Captain... I mean, councilman.
It's just officer tonight.
What can we do?
Pick Gideon up.
And take plenty of backup.
Don't worry, we'll be careful.
MAN:
Detective!
I just talked to a neighbour who called
911 an hour before the other call.
What was
the complaint?
Homeless man
rooting through the trash.
When they tried to run him off,
he seemed unstable,
threatened violence.
Get a description.
He's homeless, he's not far.
I'll tip it up, you push it up
and over, okay?
Okay.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Oh. Goddamn it.
That is rank.
You can do the digging.
Okay, fine.
No sign of our cops,
and the girl's body wasn't there.
What do you mean?
Shallow grave, empty.
Somebody moved her.
Halpern tipped Antwon.
No way. We've been taking turns
watching that place around the clock
since he showed it to us.
Halpern lied?
Maybe the body was never there.
Ah, he moved it
and didn't tell him about it.
Well, now what?
Can't find the Don,
you go visit Fredo.
VIC:
Yo, what are you working?
Same as you.
Captain talked to Dutch and Claudette
and put him onto Antwon.
They got me tracking him down.
Hear something,
give us a heads up.
Yeah.
Look, I'm trying,
he's not making it easy.
Keep trying.
Why you got me locked down?
Officers who brought you in
said you got a little physical.
'Cause I didn't do
nothing to deserve this.
Twice arrested for intent
to distribute steroids.
That your One-Niner connection?
You and them run into two
of our police officers tonight?
Shit, no.
You went over to Lydia Qualls's
looking to get a little physical.
She's the one trying
to get physical with me.
With you?
Yeah.
She's dating your father.
Left him.
Thinking she could have 2005 model.
I told her I was straight.
If she's the one chasing you,
how come she's calling 911 trying to
stop you from breaking into her house?
What you talking about?
Officers respond,
they go missing.
Takes somebody pretty strong
to corral the two of them.
What time we talking?
CLAUDETTE: Few hours ago.
No, no, I was over
at Greg Hockler's place all night.
Shooting up with stanozol.
Steroids?
Got fresh track marks in my ass
to prove it.
[CHUCKLES]
Looks like you could use
a little juice, buddy.
DUTCH:
You lied to us Lydia.
CLAUDETTE:
We have two officers missing.
So we don't have time
for goddamn liars.
Gideon was nowhere near your place
when you called 911.
You lured those officers there,
you told them some bullshit story
about some guy harassing you.
And when you left your place,
there was somebody else
waiting for them.
No.
Where are they, Lydia?
We are gonna lock that fat ass of yours
in a cage for the rest of your life,
unless you tell us right now.
I didn't lure no one.
I was just trying to set up Gideon.
Figured if I got him
into some trouble with the law,
then he'd have to talk with me.
And I'd drop the charges
if he got a little friendlier, you know?
I was looking to get the man in my bed,
not mess with no cops.
Thank you. We'll return the favour
if you ever need it. Goodbye.
Sheriff's office is sending
over six more officers.
What'd you get upstairs?
The bodybuilder and his paramour
weren't involved.
So we're back to square one?
No. We've ruled
some people out.
We have to rule some people in.
We knew whoever did this
had a reason for being on that block.
Mm-hmm.
Statements from neighbours?
Oh, yeah.
Look, I've been over this,
nothing stands out.
I was gonna go through them again.
RAWLING:
Well, do it in person.
Knock on the doors yourself.
We might have something.
Like I told
the other law enforcement agents,
one was tall, African-American.
The shorter of the two
appeared white initially.
Then, I realised he was Asian.
Marco Polo.
Did you see the officers go
into the apartment building?
Yes, ma'am.
Did you see them
come out?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Can you answer
the question, Roger?
May I see a badge number, please?
Did you see the officers come out
of the building, yes or no?
I am going to need one of those
before I can be debriefed
in the category.
Civilians don't have badges.
When I get my badge,
all things will be made known.
Peace officer to peace officer.
Hey, Corrine.
Hi. What's going on?
VIC:
We're looking for a black banger,
20's, came in here last night.
This tied
to those missing cops?
Might be. You got
any gunshot wounds in here?
Only about a hundred.
Check for a Halpern White.
Give me a sec.
Gunshot wound to the shoulder.
Lost lots of blood.
Stabilized this morning,
moved to the fourth floor.
VIC: Talking?
On a morphine drip.
He's happy, not sure
how much talking he's doing.
So any word on those missing men?
No, but we could use
a favour with that.
That felt creepy.
It's for a good cause.
Thank you. Thank you.
SHANE:
Hey, see you got that lift to the ER.
MAN:
The hell you want?
Did you say Angie's body
was under the outhouse?
It is.
No, it ain't. We looked.
Antwon must've hauled it out.
Ow.
Question is, where to?
Same place
he's stashing the two cops?
What cops?
You best be coming up
with some answers
or a copy of this CI contract
you just signed
gets nailed to the door
of Antwon's community centre.
Next time you sign insurance waivers,
you should read the fine print.
Some paper, signed or not, ain't
gonna make my clique turn against me.
You just took a bullet,
almost died.
Now, you found Jesus,
saw the error of your ways.
Started giving it up to Mr. Man,
get a fresh start.
You know the thug code.
Trust no one.
Kill your buddy before he kills you.
That's what
separates us from you.
Antwon wouldn't use his own crew
for that kind of shit. Farms it out.
I got a contract
with the El Salvadorans.
VIC:
With you laid up,
who'd he reach out with?
Doubt he went direct.
I don't know who he'd use
as a middleman.
Whoa, whoa. Yo, hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You won't be able to make
any phone calls.
But you won't care.
Oh.
Would you do the honours?
DUTCH:
What happened after the officers
came out of the apartment building?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Uh...
The officers in question were
approached by a series of individuals.
CLAUDETTE:
How many?
Three to seven.
Difficult to say with accuracy,
low luminous environment.
Where were you in relation
to the police car?
Oh, I'd say 40 metres
east-southwest.
CLAUDETTE:
What were you doing there?
Uh, routine surveillance.
Um, monitoring bursts of non-visible
light in the 800 angstrom range.
High dispersion and so forth.
I need you to be honest with me.
Detective to detective.
Did you have anything
to do with this?
No, sir, I did not.
What happened
to those police officers?
Hm.
DUTCH:
These men have families...
that are very worried about them.
We all have level three clearance
here, correct?
CLAUDETTE:
No.
I'm still at level two.
Roger...
[WHISPERS]
level three.
Foreign operatives are...
using the fault lines
to destabilize the gravity shelf.
9l11 all over again.
So these people you saw,
they were, uh, foreign agents?
Uh, they travel along the fault lines
to evade detection.
There are easier ways
to knock down a skyscraper
than flying aircraft into it.
Subduction, slip-strike manipulation,
mantle failure and so forth.
That building is coming down.
It's coming down all right.
Got it.
Officer, deploy the swing shift
without roll call.
Everyone on the street.
No petty busts.
I don't want anybody holed up
with paperwork.
MAN: Yes, ma'am.
So he give us anything?
Alien abduction in the hood
is more plausible
than anything he had to say.
He studied string theory at Cal Tech
before going off the deep end.
Send him to County for observation.
One thing we do know is he saw
our cops. We should keep him here.
The man's psychotic.
He's our only witness.
When does INS send your ass back?
Supposed to be three days ago.
Behind schedule. Why?
I can keep you off that bus.
Keep you in the U.S.
Two cops have gone missing.
INS is helping the police.
What do you need me for?
Information. Antwon Mitchell.
If he wanted to grab some cops,
who'd he use from your set?
You can really get me out of here?
Free pass comes right
from the top.
Chief signed it himself.
Name's Pitarrio.
Knew Antwon in prison.
He's his go-to on all the ugly shit.
Where can I find him?
I need to look for him.
You need to stay here
in case Carl calls.
You know, he's been...
coming home every night,
talking about how things
are more dangerous out there.
I mean, what did your captain think
would happen?
You push people long enough,
they push back.
Things weren't working before.
She's just trying something different.
Things were working fine before.
Carl came home every night.
He's out there.
Alive.
I can feel it.
Then we'll find him.
What's up, Queenie?
Daddy, am I glad you here.
Ducked in the alley for a quick bowl.
Mm, you know, take the edge off.
Dude grabs me from behind,
puts a knife to me,
tells me to dime po-po
and give y'all an address.
What is it?
Sister needs to be about her paper.
That blade on this pretty face
scared my ass to death.
Here.
2711 Heliotrope.
What am I gonna find there?
Didn't say.
What's the guy look like?
Told me if I turned around,
he's gonna cut out my implants.
Did he sound black or white?
Honey, I wasn't trying to know.
I just finished paying
for my new kitty-cats.
Another dub,
buy you some bomb-ass skully.
You know, I'm gonna
take care of your piece
better than any other female.
I'm gonna have to take your word for it.
VIC:
Go.
Oh, Jesus.
ACEVEDA:
[MAN GROANS]
MAN:
Oh, sh...
Everyone outside
until the detectives get here.
MAN:
Come on. All right, let's go.
Let's go. Come on, let's go.
DANNY: Stay behind the line.
MAN: Can you tell us the names?
MAN: As soon as I get down there.
MAN 2: All right, it's okay.
MAN:
Out of the way.
They were killed somewhere else,
dumped here.
Forensics' job just got harder by half.
Gotta find the murder scene.
We seized this house last month.
Somebody's certainly
making his point.
Antwon Mitchell's
hit the hardest.
Partnered with the Salvadorans
at Lompoc.
Likes to use them
for the dirty stuff.
You remember that Salvadoran broker,
Spider, from the church bust?
I had a little chat with him.
The INS hasn't sent him
back to El Salvador yet?
They're not
the most efficient bunch.
But anyway, he put me onto a guy
who does dirty work for Antwon.
Let me know.
Yeah.
VIC:
It's a foursome.
Easy way to wash drug money.
Yeah, bottles come in the front,
the big faces come out the back.
Go around.
Yeah.
Freeze! Hands on the table!
Don't move!
VIC:
Which one of you is Pitarrio?
Pitarrio?
Pitarrio.
Pitarrio? Talk!
[MUTTERS IN SPANISH]
SHANE:
Get out. Get out!
Who paid you to kill the cops?
I didn't kill no cops.
Antwon Mitchell
gave you the order.
No. I didn't do no cops. Ahhh!
VIC:
Spider says you did.
I was at the movies last night.
Ticket's in my jacket.
Sylmar. Eight-thirty show last night.
Shit.
No.
[PITARRIO YELLS]
You didn't kill the cops, but you did
something for Mitchell! What was it?
What?
The body.
Antwon told me to move a body.
Cops?
No. I think it was a girl.
Where?
Where?!
Griffith Park, man. By the horses.
CLAUDETTE:
Need to interview
the suspect Billings brought in.
MAN:
Psst!
Psst, psst.
[SIGHS]
Surveillance
has been non-productive thus far.
I have been monitoring
the chatter and so forth.
Sorry to hear
about those two officers.
They deserved better
than getting dragged down like that.
Why don't you start without me?
What do you mean dragged down?
I need you to really concentrate
on everything you saw last night.
See it in your mind
like it's a movie.
And you're looking at it one frame
at a time. Can you do that for me?
I'll try. I've got one of those brains
that skips around a lot.
Uh, my condolences
to the Marco Polo family.
The cavern.
In a canyon.
Excavating.
For a mine.
# Dwells a miner
Forty-niner #
# And his daughter #
# Clementine #
CLAUDETTE:
I'm in a hurry,
so I won't waste your time.
I'll do the same.
People say not a lot happens on
your block if you don't sign off on it.
I look after my peoples.
We had two cops murdered and
dumped in the house on your street.
That had to have been outsiders.
Really?
Mean you and your neighbours
weren't pissed off
the police seized that house
on your street?
Wasn't my house.
Owners cooked meth.
Street's been safer
since you done it.
We need to do another canvass
of this whole area.
Figure out how Carl
and Scooby disappeared.
What are we looking for?
I'm not sure.
But it may involve a geological
anomaly in the earth's crust.
Just something to keep in mind
as you do your search.
Vonda, I'm Captain Monica Rawling.
He's dead.
I'm so sorry.
He believed in what you're doing.
He was proud to put on
his uniform every day.
But what you're doing here
in Farmington is what got him killed.
You need to know that.
Carl was a hero.
I need you to leave now.
Both of you.
Please, just go.
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[METAL RATTLES]
Hey, uh, give me a hand with this.
Here.
LEM:
Yeah, Southwest. That's cool.
All right, we'll pick him up.
Thanks, man,
we owe you one.
Was that about Antwon?
Well?
Yeah, that was Walon Burke,
Decoy Squad.
I know Walon.
What did he give you?
FBI pal of his in Westwood
just got a hit on Antwon's credit card.
He charged a plane ticket from Vegas.
Due into LAX at 7:30. Southwest.
I'll send some unis
to pick him up. Nice work.
DUTCH:
I got something.
Found at the bottom of a manhole
near our original crime scene.
There's blood everywhere
down there.
How do you get two cops
in a sewer?
"Officer, my daughter fell
down there, can you help me?"
Blinged-out dog tag
the hip-hop kids wear. Initials, J.P.
Found it in the blood.
It's too untarnished to have
been down there long.
Get the owner,
got a killer.
So how many guys do you think
it took, you know, to get Carl
and Scooby down there?
A few. There's a lot of anger
about what's going on.
Yeah, well, they're angry
because it's working.
A lot of us are
behind the captain.
That's understandable.
Sometimes street level
isn't the best vantage point to...
[OBJECT THUMPS METAL]
What the hell was that?
Holy shit.
CLAUDETTE:
This look familiar to you, Yancy?
Don't think so.
It was ripped from the neck
of one of the people
who killed two cops last night,
whose bodies were found
on your block.
You're hip-deep in this shit.
Now, you're the mayor on that block.
You either did it or you know about it.
Don't come near me with that.
Oh, you've never seen
this jewellery before?
Name's Yancy Backus, remember?
J.P. belongs to somebody else.
So it belongs to one of your friends
you did the killing with.
Y'all took my cell phone downstairs.
Check my friends and family.
Or you could check
with Leimert Jewellers...
the people who made this,
see who they sold it to.
[MEN CLAMOURING]
MAN: He didn't even do nothing.
MAN 2: He didn't do nothing.
MAN:
What's wrong with you?
Who wrote this?
Man, he ain't seen nothing.
He was out back unloading the truck.
Yeah, bullshit.
What's bullshit, brothers here dying,
ain't none of you turning over.
One of these cops was a brother!
A cop ain't a brother.
Maybe you saw something then, huh?
Man, get the...
MAN 3:
Hey, come here.
Get your ass over here.
MAN 4:
Where you going? Come here.
[ACEVEDA GROANS]
MAN 5:
We need to get
this bastard down here.
You okay?
[GROANS]
You know, you might wanna
get that x-rayed.
I got the wind knocked out of me is all.
Comes with the territory.
Along with getting shot at.
Don't single yourself out.
Three other officers
got their cars fired on today.
Everybody okay?
Thank God.
Not that you're asking,
but I've lost cops under my command.
It's easy to shit your pants,
but it accomplishes nothing.
I wasn't going down that road.
What I'm saying is, a thing like this,
especially if there's no good news
right away, can paralyse you.
Those people out there need to feel
your confidence.
RAWLING:
Vic...
you're empty-handed.
Where's the guy who does all
of Antwon's dirty work?
He had an airtight alibi.
Well, it's going around.
Antwon just happened
to be in Vegas last night.
Got his flight info.
I have some unis posted at LAX
to grab him when he gets off the plane.
Some good news, finally.
Yeah, well, conversations with Mitchell
tend to go around in circles.
I don't want to keep the community
waiting while I find the straight line.
Dutch and Claudette
have come up empty too.
Maybe it's time to, um...
bring in
a person of interest.
Lay it off on someone?
Just a couple of days.
Give us a chance to try
to squeeze the truth out of Antwon.
Makes people think twice
before they take a shot at a uni.
Have anyone in mind?
No.
Just so long as he fills the bill.
One unsympathetic asshole
coming right up.
Captain's arranged
a welcome waggon for Antwon.
He's flying into LAX tonight.
So I hear.
You knew?
What part of us getting information
first didn't you understand?
Captain was standing right there
when I got the call. I had to tell her.
She doesn't have anything on Antwon.
No. But he's got plenty on them.
We haul in Antwon,
push the wrong buttons,
how long's it gonna take him
to point a finger at me and Army?
I'll make sure it takes long enough
for us to get our leverage back.
Look, we gotta find a goat to pin
these murders on, calm the streets
before another cop gets killed.
This captain won't go for that.
It's her idea.
All we need is a face and a name.
Anyone in Antwon's circle fit that bill?
Well, there is this young cat.
Earned his cred by supplying
clean guns to the black sets.
Whatever he was doing,
it wasn't legal.
Guppy got a name?
Street name's Urkel.
Swear to God.
All right, good.
You and Ronnie go pick up
our cop killer.
Now you want us to haul
in an innocent guy?
No, he'll have a car full of guns.
Bring him in for that.
We'll figure the rest out later.
Let's go.
Rise and shine, big pimpin'.
[GASPS]
Better get ahold of our thick friend.
Give him a heads-up.
About what?
Our captain likes him
for killing those cops.
Sending a blue crew
to LAX to pick him up.
SHANE:
He needs to fly
into Burbank instead.
We'll surprise him there, tell him
how to play this out with our bosses.
You think he's gonna drop
his black ass into whatever
jackpot you got planned?
No more games. No more threats.
We wanna stop beef and start
doing business the right way.
This guy wants you dead.
He ain't getting into a car with you.
Not gonna have a choice.
Now, make the damn call.
Hell, yeah, that's my shit.
So you're admitting you were present
at a crime scene last night, Jamal?
Crime scene?
CLAUDETTE: Those two dead cops.
DUTCH: Friends of ours, actually.
J AMAL: No, I was not there.
But your necklace was?
How do you explain that?
Necklace got itself stolen.
Right. When?
Six, seven months ago.
They took the TV too.
You, uh, report it?
I spent three G's getting
this thing custom-made.
You best believe your ass I reported it.
Go check your records.
Police have any idea who took it?
I kept trying to check back
with you cops every couple weeks,
see if they heard anything new.
No one seemed real interested.
Y'all real interested now,
though, huh?
RAWLING:
Dutch.
You two come up, please.
So the trail just stops?
DUTCH:
Well, even with the necklace
stolen, we're thinking
it probably ended up
in the hands of somebody
with the initials J.P.
RAWLING:
That's reaching.
What else do we have?
No witnesses,
but we're waiting for lab work.
So that's the plan? We just get lucky,
something falls in our laps?
DUTCH:
It's only the first day.
RAWLING:
Every day will just get harder.
Meanwhile, I've had
four different squad cars shot at.
Two brawls with civilians
and officers, and one instance
in which my own men lost control.
It's gotta stop.
Vic and his guys have brought
in a suspect.
Great. What do we have on him?
Carload of stolen guns.
Our guys were stabbed.
He's a gang member,
we've got him on weapons charges.
But nothing related to our murders?
I want you to make the press believe
that we have a killer in custody.
Oh, you're kidding me.
You want us to lie?
Save your high and mighties for when
the lives of my cops aren't at stake.
You've had a chance to solve this.
It's only been one day.
And you've been doing your best,
but we're not far enough.
You tell the community
that we have a killer,
it sends a message that there's
a price to pay for coming after us.
Makes whoever really did it cocky,
gets them laughing with their friends
about what idiots we are,
and if they tell their friends...
Their friends tell someone
who tells us.
You wanted the case.
So take the bad with the good.
ANTWON:
So five-0 was waiting for me at LAX?
How's this an improvement?
My little gift to you,
running interference.
I didn't know
I made your Christmas list.
We want a truce.
You know there's a much bigger upside
for you, me being alive and kicking.
I don't see it.
Truth is, my captain's made
a serious dent in your business.
How long before someone
in your organization decides
to play king of the hill?
Nobody's taking me down.
Not without my backing.
You been stepping on my game
since day one.
That earns you dead.
Yeah, that didn't happen.
My boys saw you gaffing me up
at the airport, so...
Now, what?
You back off me and mine,
Shane and his family.
We work out fair percentages,
you get to do business uninterrupted.
That's the deal.
Either you smoking crack,
or you think I am.
Our captain pulled him off lead on the
gang task force. He lost his pay bump.
There's no upside for me to play
by their rules anymore.
I got two sick kids. I gotta earn.
And I ain't got time to hear no more
of this crackerwood bullshit.
Look, I know you've been looking
for a new tar importer
ever since you lost that cul-de-sac,
the El Salvadorans.
VIC:
I got a hookup
with a Jamaican crew out of Miami.
They call themselves
the Splash Posse.
Yeah, I heard of them niggas.
They're looking to move weight out
of the West Coast.
I'm their broker.
We need a retail outlet.
So you a... baller all
of a sudden now, huh?
Always was.
But I just took a step back
from the game for a little while.
So, what's your captain
gonna sweat me on, huh?
These dead cops?
I don't kill for no reason.
And I don't know nothing
about mercing no police.
SHANE:
They got nothing on you.
They'll hold you for a few hours,
then cut you loose.
I'll be in the room.
I'll steer the questioning away
from anything sensitive.
That is, if we're working together.
You lucky your boy
got mad love for you.
Yeah.
We're all about mad love.
[CHUCKLES]
The suspect's name
is Donzell Prince.
And you've arrested him
for the murders
of Officers Haimes and Miller?
DUTCH:
He's being held on weapon charges,
but we're confident we have our man.
MAN:
If you're so confident,
why don't you file on murder?
Because we don't wanna
make any mistakes.
No one wants to take any chances.
MAN 2:
Do you believe
he acted alone?
Doesn't the crime itself suggest
that there were multiple assailants?
I really can't go into our theory
of the crime at this time.
Has the suspect indicated
any accomplices?
I can't talk about the specifics
of what the suspect revealed.
All I can say is
our investigation is bearing fruit.
And we'll have more for you
in the coming days. Thank you.
WOMAN:
Could you tell us
what lead you to Mr. Prince?
[REPORTERS CHATTERING]
Danny, bring him up to 1.
DANNY: Sure.
We frisked him, he's clean.
All right.
He gave us the slip at LAX.
How'd you find him?
One of his crew told us
he got a heads-up.
Only had one of two choices
left, Burbank or L.B.
We got him at Bob Hope.
Nice.
Don't know what we're gonna
throw at him yet.
I have a couple of aces
up my sleeve.
See you up there.
Yeah.
Help yourself.
All known city gang members
with the initials J and P.
I hope you got
a four-leaf clover in your pocket.
We should start with One-Niners.
In Farmington.
Want some dinner?
I had dinner four hours ago.
Yeah, I mean another dinner.
Whatever you want's fine with me.
We have nothing
to charge Antwon with.
We can only hold him
for 12 hours.
She's buried in Griffith Park,
somewhere near the horses.
In three holes.
Christ.
I'll tie up Mitchell, make sure he does
not dime anyone to move her again.
You three have to find the graves.
Yeah.
LEM:
I'll do it too.
Look for fresh digging.
Let's find her.
Don't need that.
Thanks for coming in, Antwon.
[###]