[WOMAN SCREAMING]
WOMAN:
No, no!
Please, no. No.
No, God.
Don't... No, don't do this!
No, let me go, let me go.
Don't do this.
MAN:
Shut up. Shut up!
Oh, God! Let me go!
Oh, God.
Oh, God, you're hurting!
You're hurting... No, no!
You're hurting! No, no!
No, no, no, God!
No, no, no!
Not so hard. I told you, no bruises.
Stop. Oh, God.
Please, don't do this!
Please, don't do this. No.
[WHIMPERING]
No. Oh, God, don't do this!
Please. No.
SARA:
You wanna say Thursday?
I'm not sure.
Oh, uh
Before I forget.
I love Neiman's.
[LAUGHS]
I have the perfect pair of shoes
to go with this.
From now on though,
get a gift receipt.
Um
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
What we do together is important.
Whatever it is or why,
that energy has to come out.
Buying into the shame is what's wrong.
Not what we do in there.
In there is what the gifts are for.
Not the small talk.
Next Thursday's fine.
RAWLING:
I don't need to tell you what
drugs are doing to our streets.
You live with it every day.
The purpose of this meeting
is to outline new initiatives
that we're taking to change things.
To lay out the facts,
dispel rumours and get your input.
I mean, if any of you have
any ideas of how we can
be more effective, I'm listening.
So, what are you gonna do
so different?
I mean, because all these years,
I heard a lot of talking.
[PEOPLE MURMUR]
And all I see
is more sidewalk chalking.
CROWD:
Yeah.
Right.
RAWLING: I agree with you.
For every dealer and banger we put
in jail, three more take his place.
It's because the culture of wealth that's
been created by the sale of drugs
has sent a very clear message
to our kids: "Now hiring."
Putting more officers on the street
will make it harder to do business.
Increased gang intervention.
Restored and expanded
after-school programmes.
Kids have to have a place to go to.
They have to have things to do.
Also more aggressive
drug education.
It all can work,
it just requires patience.
How long we supposed to wait?
CROWD: Yeah.
MAN: That's right.
We didn't have the resources before
that we have now.
These new policies allow us
to confiscate property
that's been paid for
with drug money.
We're taking the dealers' profits
and using it
against them
to improve your lives.
I think it's time
that they pay the bill
for all the pain and suffering
that they've caused.
MAN: Right?
MAN 2: That's right.
BILLINGS:
Romeo Barnes.
Took a head shot,
close range.
VIC:
Romeo, poor Romeo.
Witness here works
at the methadone clinic.
Says he saw our victim
and a black female
arguing with another black male.
Few minutes later, heard shots.
Saw the shooter take off
on a motorcycle.
Let's start up a canvass.
Have DWP check the storm drains
in case he tossed his piece.
Let's talk to methadone man.
So you saw the shooter book?
Yeah, I know I said that earlier,
but just to be clear here
I didn't actually see anybody
do any shooting.
Right. Recognise the guy
driving off on the bike?
Never seen him before.
What about the woman
he was arguing with?
Never seen her before.
Victim?
Never seen him before.
Hope you're not counting on me
to be more helpful than that.
Wouldn't dream of it.
God bless you.
And thank you for cracking down
on these gangsters,
so my kids can go to school one day
without being afraid of getting shot.
MAN: Yeah.
WOMAN: That's right.
[APPLAUSE]
But aren't we creating
a bigger problem?
White police officers
have been swarming
on our neighbourhood
since day one.
MAN: Yeah.
And now they wanna take the black
and the brown man's property
if they think he's up to no good.
Now, it should be noted that
Mr. Mitchell is a convicted felon
who spent 13 years in prison
for distributing crack cocaine.
Excuse me. So you don't
believe in rehabilitation?
What you're saying is the police
can change, but a brother can't?
Rehabilitation presumes that
a person's behaviour has changed.
Tried and convicted again
by judge and jury.
See, but the problem with this is
the police aren't a jury of our peers.
I grew up in Farmington.
It was an okay place to live
until the summer of 1984.
That is when
the crack-cocaine epidemic hit.
WOMAN:
Yeah.
Turned this place
into something else overnight.
That's why
I became a peace officer.
To help to bring Farmington back
to the place that I remember.
Now, look, with God's help
and your support,
law enforcement is a solution.
We are not the problem.
WOMAN: Sell out.
MAN: What are you talking about?
David Aceveda,
city councilman for this district.
When someone is arrested,
the law says innocent
until proven guilty.
The reason for that
is people make mistakes.
Under this policy,
that burden falls on you, sir.
And you, and you.
To prove that you didn't buy
your house by selling contraband.
Otherwise, they can take your property,
sell it to the highest bidder.
And they keep the money.
Which we funnel back
into neighbourhood programmes
and into making
this community safer.
There's been abuse and corruption
in nearly every city
that this policy has been tried.
Which is why I cannot support it
without strict regulations.
You're trying to fix something
that isn't broken.
No. No, it's my duty to put the best
interests of Farmington
ahead of a social experiment,
however well-intentioned.
[APPLAUSE]
RAWLING:
Councilman.
Getting me up there under the pretext
of soliciting public support
and then undermining me?
Thanks for the crash course
in sandbagging.
I came willing to be convinced.
I wasn't.
Congratulations, you pushed half that
crowd into Antwon Mitchell's hands.
That's a slippery slope.
Using the bogeyman to ride
roughshod over people's rights.
Don't you have enough to do
on city council?
Or is this some power trip,
doing my job as well?
Actually, my job duties now include
vice-chairing the police committee.
Helping oversee how
these seizures are implemented.
Well... I guess we'll need to figure out
how to get along, then.
Learn to do what I say,
and we'll be just fine.
[###]
VIC:
Romeo did time for moving crack,
possession, assault.
He was clean the last 10 years.
Doesn't sound like he got shot
for minding his own business.
[CHUCKLES]
Anything else
on the motorcycle gunman?
Not the most cooperative block.
That's gonna change.
Pull in Vendrell to help you.
Shane?
Yeah, you're the one
who sold me on his credentials.
Like I said, Shane's a good cop.
Maybe Shane's vice intel gets us
to Antwon Mitchell.
We won't find Antwon anywhere
near anything this low-level.
Small world.
Even 12 degrees of separation
between this and him
will get us closer.
VIC:
Hey. New girlfriend?
I got socks older than her.
Look, she gave me something
on that meth whack you're working.
She reliable?
Yeah, I know her.
Talk to her regularly.
Bust her every couple weeks
for petty stuff like shoplifting.
She's just trying to keep her
and her mom fed.
VIC:
So tell us about Romeo.
GIRL:
Romeo wasn't using no more.
He's my mom's NA sponsor.
Her slanger was trying
to get her back on the H.
Romeo's been stepping to him hard,
to leave her be.
What's this dealer's name?
All's I know, he ride
a loud-ass motorcycle.
It shake the house.
Where's your mom now?
Probably tricking to get low.
Five or six places
I usually find her at.
You think you can show us?
Can I get some Starbursts first?
I thought the deal was
we'd be working our own shit.
Captain knows you got the street
hookups. Smart to bring you in.
VIC:
But first,
you gotta check this out, man.
We borrowed one
of our Garage Sting hidden cameras
for a little personal use.
Ladies and gentlemen, the man who put
the pimp in pimp juice.
SHANE:
Who's the babe?
VIC:
Friend of Claudette's. Blind date.
We'll spare you the awkward hellos and
skip straight to the painful goodbyes.
Excellent.
You still cold?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry again about cranking
the air conditioning.
Oh, it's all right.
I guess cooler climes
are just hardwired
to my northern European DNA.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Oh, this is me.
Listen, we should
get together again.
Maybe, uh, this week end?
I'm...
I'm gonna be in Kansas city.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
Well, call me
when you get back.
Sure.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Bye. Bye.
Yeah, okay. See you.
Looks like his next date's gonna be
with some hand cream.
No, no, wait. This is the big finish.
[DURAN DURAN'S "HUNGRY LIKE
THE WOLF" PLAYING O VER RADIO]
# Hungry lik e the wolf #
# Straddle the line
In discord and rhyme #
# I'm on the hunt
I'm after you #
# My mouth is alive #
DNA like that, his parents should have
chlorinated the gene pool.
# Hungry lik e the wolf #
VIC:
Come on, all right.
All right, look.
We're looking for a horse dealer.
Works by the methadone clinic
over on Seymour.
Wondered if you guys
could track down a name
while we chase the junkie mom
who witnesses the killing.
Know anything else about this dealer?
Rides a wink-bike.
Loud.
He was whacked by some slanger,
he works off a motorcycle.
Street soldiers are a little below
my need-to-know, man.
Sound like Freebo.
He got a rice rocket.
Temper too.
Yeah, where can I find him?
Why?
To lock his ass up on this shooting.
Hey, we gave you a name
to keep our boy clear of this,
not so you can take him down.
Now remember, you're paid
to protect my business.
Look some smoke goes and kills
a fellow asshole, I got no issue.
But he grudge-whacked
a drug counsellor.
That shit ain't right.
Also, I'll make sure
the investigation seals off with him.
Doesn't work its way up the food chain
to the big fish.
Someone else gives him up,
there's no guarantee of that.
I'll make a couple calls,
try and locate that cat.
Good boy. Holler.
Holler.
RAWLING:
I got a murder for you two.
Sixty-five-year-old white female.
Shot during a home invasion.
Run it through Vic.
We're reporting to Mackey?
On this one.
Looks gang-related.
His domain.
That a problem?
Of course not. I just...
I know he's got his hands full.
CLAUDETTE:
I understand you're confiscating
Maurice Webster's house
over those three pot plants.
He was distributing drugs,
selling them out of that house.
I guess even a hummer bust like this
brings in a chunk of change
for you and the DA's office
to divvy up.
Why don't you and I go somewhere?
RAWLING:
Can we have the room
for a minute please?
MAN:
Sure.
Debate's fine,
insubordination isn't.
The DA doesn't call over
to ask for a detective anymore
than you can tell them
what prosecutor to use.
Why were we put
on the Webster case?
I've enough on my plate
without second-guessing
the DA's mood swings.
If I'm part of some back-room deal,
why don't you just lay it out for me?
Does my office down there
look like a back room?
All that manpower thrown at a case,
the guy turns out to be a nobody.
But they grab his house anyway.
Detective in me wonders,
who benefits?
Well, maybe the detective in you
should get down
to your assigned crime scene
before a reprimand hits your desk.
Either she's lying
or the DA's office is
or they both are.
So it's not that
she's another woman who took
the job you're supposed to have?
No.
Just checking.
DANNY:
Shot in the back twice.
There's no sign of forced entry.
DUTCH:
Who found the body?
DANNY: The husband and daughter.
DUTCH: Over there.
DUTCH:
Detective Wagenbach,
Detective Wyms.
CLAUDETTE:
Our condolences.
Could we ask a few questions?
DUTCH: You found the body?
GIRL: My father and me.
I picked him up at the library.
[SOBBING]
And we came home and...
What time was that?
Around 11.
Tell them
about the car.
Oh, oh.
This morning when we left,
I saw a car full of Mexican kids
parked across the street.
They looked like
gang members.
DUTCH:
What kind of car?
I don't know.
It was so old and beat up.
Grey spray paint. I got a good look
at the driver though.
Daddy. Daddy, are you okay?
I'm just a little dizzy.
Go on, I'll be okay.
We have to get him to a hospital.
He's got heart problems.
One of our unis can drop him off
at Mission Cross. We can do this later.
I'll come with you.
WOMAN:
Oh. My, my.
GIRL:
Mama, these folks
wanna talk to you.
GIRL: Mama.
WOMAN: Sons of bitches, eat my ass.
RAWLING:
Angie, come here.
Do you have other family you go to
when she's like this?
She's like this all the time.
Someone's gotta look out for her.
We'll get her into treatment.
Last time I called,
it was like a half a year wait.
Me calling might make a difference.
WOMAN:
Stop getting at me, man!
VIC:
Hoda, come on. Come on.
Where you score your heyron from?
Come on, I got a sick friend.
All right, I can take me
some grey dick.
Hey, hey, listen. I can't help you
score if I can't reach your main man.
VIC:
You got a name
and number for me?
Any of them houses on the cul-de-sac
got a big bag.
What cul-de-sac?
Hoda? Hoda?
Leave her be.
Mama, you talking about the houses
on Hoover?
Used to party and play over there.
You know that dead end by the steps?
I know some kids over there.
Saw Mama copping a couple times.
Check this out.
House on the left.
VIC:
Reinforced steel doors,
blacked-out windows.
Same as the place next door.
Gotta be the house
Angie was talking about.
Yeah.
No smoker traffic.
Ain't no rock house,
but it's something big.
Check out the guy over there.
Spotter.
Another one over there.
Homeboy's doing more than keeping
the flat screen from getting jacked.
I think it's warrant time.
I'm gonna call my captain.
This was my tip.
You're not assigned to Farmington.
Look, after we close the book
on this case and Angie...
You got Shane
back in the house.
Having you there is gonna
drive him further away.
I need him close,
and you know why.
Yeah. Yeah.
Look, I know you want back in.
[SIGHS]
Look...
You keep showing up at the Barn
with juvie intel on all my cases,
I appreciate it.
Shane's still an issue.
There's still a lot of history there.
Neighbours say they're nice people.
You know, keep to themselves.
Well, there's been a bunch of home
invasions in this neighbourhood.
Yeah, we answered
one of those.
DUTCH:
Hey. Take a look at this.
Uh, find out if there was
a car parked across the street
with a bunch of male Hispanics
around 9:30 this morning.
Go to the trouble of killing someone,
you leave the good stuff in plain sight?
Yeah. Not a very thorough
home invasion.
Unless the victim put up
a struggle, got herself shot,
they panicked, took off.
I had a case. Two guys on crank.
Took multiple stab wounds
from an 80-year-old
whose birdbath they
were trying to swipe.
Old and stubborn. I guess all you look
for is a good fight sometimes, huh?
Daughter makes it sound
like a home invasion.
Something off
with the family though.
Neighbourhood's Byz Lat turf.
You should get with the OGs.
Scooby and Lucas
are talking to them now.
Esé crews run a bunch
of gank-and-goes over there lately.
Four in the last month.
Did you look
at the witness statements?
Read the reports,
witnesses are being reinterviewed.
You got something big going down?
Yeah.
Have you run
a canvass of the area?
You know, I have run
a murder investigation before.
Right, and I couldn't be happier
having a seasoned
law enforcement professional
such as yourself
working the case under me.
Just attack it.
Like you're hungry. Like the wolf.
RAWLING:
Okay, everyone.
The target looks like
a drug distribution centre.
Two neighbouring houses that have
security and communications.
One of their spotters
calls himself TEC-9.
So we can assume the firepower
lives up to the name.
RAWLING:
We also want you to be aware
that we're looking for a suspect
in an ongoing murder investigation
who operates out of this area.
Rides a motorcycle,
street name is Freebo.
High-risk warrant like this,
shouldn't we be going in at night?
Well, the bad guys have imbedded
themselves in a residential area
where there's a lot of kids.
We hit while they're in school,
minimise the risk.
The trade-off is we lose the element of
surprise, which makes our job harder.
This will be a success
if and only if
every one of you
comes back in one piece,
and no civilians are hurt.
So let's do it right.
VIC:
All right.
Team assignments and target 20.
Shane, you're going in with me.
Army with Ronnie
and Lemie's group.
Jesus Christ.
This is part of
Antwon's operation?
Yeah, this block.
Yeah, it's gotta be.
Well, this is major,
we gotta give him a heads-up.
Just take it easy, all right?
RAWLING: No cell phones.
Yeah, I just gotta let my wife...
RAWLING: Operational security.
SHANE: Right, okay.
VIC:
Shane, let's move out.
I wouldn't.
Put your hands on your head.
MAN:
Take another sweep.
Pick up, pick up, it's the cops, man.
MAN 2:
Police. Stay on the ground.
Don't move. Don't move.
MAN 3: Right to left.
MAN 4:
Let's bring it around back.
[COOL HIP-HOP PLAYING]
MAN: All right.
[EXPLOSION THUDS]
MAN 2:
Freeze. Police.
MAN 3: Police.
Don't move.
VIC:
Stay right there.
MAN 4:
Hands above your head. Stay here.
MAN: Pick it up, pick it up.
MAN 2: Police.
MAN 3: Away from the window.
MAN 4: Hands up, boy.
MAN: On the wall.
MAN 2: Look at the wall.
MAN 3: You got him?
MAN: Yeah.
MAN: Clear.
MAN 2: Clear.
SHANE: Clear.
MAN 4: Hey.
LEM:
Jesus.
I wish we had
this kind of shit in Iraq.
Holy cow.
Well.
What I got here buys
each of you entrepreneurs
a hard 20 in Pelican Bay.
Now, I'm looking for the dealer
who capped a brother
over on Seymour last night.
Name's Freebo.
He rides a rice burner.
One of you citizens
gives us a real name,
you walk away clean.
SHANE:
Up. Up.
Freebo was just here.
Real name's Freddie Bokamp.
Smart man. How long ago?
Half an hour maybe.
I heard his bike.
Hey, hey, shit, no, man.
Take me down with everybody else.
Feed your ear there.
All right.
MAN:
I got a strong chemical odour
coming from the back
of that building. Could be ether.
RAWLING:
Possible meth lab.
Let's get HAZMAT down here.
Got a lead on Freebo.
Frederick Bokamp,
this is his DMV.
Where is he?
Well, if he didn't split
before we locked this place down,
he could be in any of those buildings,
but pulling a new warrant takes time.
This HAZMAT situation,
I think we better evacuate the block.
That's a good idea. A crank lab,
the whole place could blow.
DANNY [OVER MEGAPHONE]:
Attention all residents,
this is a mandatory evacuation order.
You must leave
the premises immediately.
Again I repeat, please leave
Okay, sir, step on out.
I need you to evacuate the premises.
My son's got pneumonia.
We'll get him
medical attention.
You can't stay here though.
You can't just come in here like this.
DANNY:
Come on, sir, step outside.
What the hell you doing, man?
We'll take him to the hospital.
You need to clear out of here though.
There's hazardous material in the area.
You need to clear out.
Put him down, goddamn it.
[MAN GRUNTING]
MAN:
Stop resisting.
WOMAN:
That's cold.
Did your mother
have any enemies that you know of?
No. And she was my stepmother.
My mom passed nine years ago
next month.
It was like déjà vu
finding Margo's body.
How's that?
Uh, my dad and I found my mom
in the same room.
We'd just come back from running
errands, and she was lying there.
CLAUDETTE: How'd she die?
WOMAN: Stroke.
My Dad had a heart attack
the next week.
Guess that happens sometimes when
people have been together a long time.
We found a jewellery box
in your bedroom, just beautiful pieces.
Oh, yeah, my mother's.
Thieves only took
your stepmother's jewellery.
You know, I'm just...
I'm worried about my dad having
to go through this all over again.
I really need to get back
to the hospital, be with him.
We can call over there,
see how he's doing.
Send a car over
if he's ready to go.
Hell of a day.
Wouldn't be a bad month.
Evacuation didn't
turn up Freebo.
But I'm not done yet.
Last chance for any of you cupcakes
if you ever wanna smell pussy again.
MAN:
I can smell yours from here, bitch.
MAN 2: Yeah.
MAN 3: Shit.
You get to come with me.
Easy, man.
I was, like, acting down there.
You know, for the homeys.
Yeah, well, if you don't tell me
where Freebo is,
you're gonna be acting
like a guy doing life in prison.
Hard to say. Brother gets around
on those wheels, man.
He a free spirit.
MAN:
Come on!
What you doing, man?
Acting for the homeys.
You think they got the message,
or do we need a second act?
Freebo stays
with his twin brother, Weebo.
Freebo and Weebo?
Got a line on Freebo.
Hey, press conference
hasn't started yet.
Still got plenty of time to figure out
how to take credit for all this.
7661 Anholt. That's Freebo's crib.
Come back us up. He's a shooter.
An impressive bust
from what I hear. Congratulations.
Why do I get the feeling
that's the last compliment
I'll get in this conversation?
I just came from the crime scene.
You've got a lot of unhappy people
out in the street.
HAZMAT's finishing up
a threat assessment.
Why weren't arrangements
made for emergency shelter?
We weren't anticipating
having to evacuate the area.
Next time you have an operation
this size, you should let me know.
I can put the resources of my office
at your disposal.
Head off little snafus like these.
You say snafu, I say the biggest
drug bust in Farmington
in the last 10 years.
Dutch, we're sure
the murder weapon was a.38?
Pending confirmation
from Ballistics.
They found a box of.38 ammo
in the husband's closet.
Find a gun?
Turned the place upside down.
Neighbours said gangs
have been a problem,
but no one saw this car
full of Mexicans.
Take a gun and not the ammo.
Swipe the cheap jewellery,
leave the good stuff.
How much convincing would it take
to move you off this home invasion?
I'm not loving it. Which leaves
the husband and daughter.
Doesn't strike me
he wanted out of the marriage.
So, what was in it
for daddy's little girl?
I think you just answered
your own question.
Do you own a handgun, Warren?
.38 Smith and Wesson.
Why?
DUTCH:
We're looking into the possibility
it could've been the murder weapon.
Where do you keep it?
On a shelf in the bedroom closet.
But it... It's not loaded.
I make it a point to keep
the bullets in the drawer.
So it should be
in the closet there now?
Sure.
Because we've had our people go
all through the place, we can't find it.
DUTCH:
Margo and Donna get along?
They ever argue?
They had opinions.
You tell me, all the time
Donna's spent taking care of you,
she wasn't upset,
Margo wanting you to pull up stakes,
move you to another state?
Uh...
Excuse me,
I'm having a senior moment. Um...
We had another break-in
a little while back.
I didn't wanna tell Donna about it
because I knew she'd worry.
It's what she does best.
My gun was stolen.
You report the burglary
to the police?
No. Uh, that was probably
a mistake, wasn't it?
Captain, I need your officer
to testify in this assault case,
and I am having trouble
serving the subpoena.
He's on vacation.
He gets back on duty tomorrow.
I'll make sure he gets it.
I appreciate it.
Question for you.
How did your office decide to file
in the Webster case?
Oh, it's still in play.
Trying to make a plea bargain?
Oh, I don't know where it is exactly.
I don't have the file in front of me.
Is there someone in your office
I can call? To check on it.
The case is in the system.
What's the urgency?
We're moving
to seize the property.
And this won't fly if it gets kicked
down to a misdemeanour.
Look...
I'm not at liberty
to discuss specifics right now.
As soon as I know something,
I will get back to you.
Thanks again.
You're welcome.
You got some explaining to do.
SHANE:
Hey, I was double-blind.
You didn't tell me
what you had going.
Mackey threw this
into high gear behind my back.
I didn't know it was going down
till it was too late.
Hey, two rules:
don't complain and don't explain.
The only rule
is that you don't set the rules.
And you need to explain to your people
that it's bad business
to whack a citizen
in front of a witness.
Now, there's a manhunt
for your boy Freebo.
You had better hope
I'm the one who brings him in.
I got four layers of nigs
don't know who they work for
insulating me from that cul-de-sac.
Yeah, as long as your crew
hangs tight.
One of your boys decides to roll on
one of your other boys to get out
from underneath a murder,
you got a big hole in that insulation.
I'm still the best friend you got.
I appreciate the help.
It's what I'm here for.
And if you'd start listening,
this whole thing would go
a lot easier on the both of us.
You know what?
I think the two of us should
work on our communication skills.
That way shit lik e this
doesn't happen again.
I'll let you know when.
VIC:
Where the hell is Shane?
LEM:
Which one's Weebo
and which one's Freebo? They're twins.
VIC:
Shit, they're running.
Somebody tipped them off.
What if they take off
in different directions?
We only got one car.
Where the hell is he?
We gotta go.
Yeah, they're splitting up.
Damn it.
RONNIE:
Police. Move away
from the bikes, now!
VIC: Hands on your head!
LEM: Gun.
VIC:
Get down on the ground now!
Put your hands on your head!
Get down. Get down.
Get down.
You all right?
Yeah.
WOMAN:
This is 911 emergency.
This is Detective Lemansky,
badge number 27228.
I've been involved in
a shooting at 7661 Anholt.
Notify paramedics
and a supervisor.
Where have you been?
What happened?
Goddamn it, we needed you.
You, call for backup.
LEM: Look, I got this.
VIC: Your hands behind your back.
FREEBO:
Look what you did to my brother, pigs!
VIC:
Shut up.
Look, man, we got here as quick
as we could.
Nice try, Freebo.
Dutch says it's breaking different
than home invasion.
Yeah, looks like the daughter.
We just have to trap her.
I've stopped the forfeiture proceedings
in the Webster case.
I did some digging.
Webster was on the witness list for
the defence in a separate murder trial.
The DA had other interests in that
pot bust beyond enforcing the statute.
Like ruining his credibility
on the stand.
Well, it worked. He was
dropped from the witness list.
The defendant pled.
You just find this out?
You smelled horseshit, turned out
there was a pony in the Barn.
Well, I appreciate your digging.
You know, what I don't get...
is why did the DA choose
the two of you in the first place.
I mean, shady tactics like this,
I think you'd be the last ones
they'd trust to make it work.
I guess we'll never know.
As far as it goes between us,
I expect a sea change in your attitude.
Can you hook Freebo into Antwon?
He's a little tweaked about losing
his brother. It's twin shit.
Can I pull a favour?
Have you talk to IAD about
this officer-involved shooting thing.
Well, Lemansky's not under
my command.
You know his CI broke this case for us.
The whole cul-de-sac.
He had permission
from his supervisor to roll with me.
Their first question's gonna be
the same as mine.
Murder suspect,
armed and dangerous.
Where was your backup?
Shane got stuck in traffic.
The brothers were taking flight.
We had no way of knowing
which one was Freebo. We had to roll.
Write up a report.
I'll take a look at it.
I got you for killing Romeo Barnes.
We go for special circumstances,
you'll be
seeing your brother again.
Don't talk like that, man,
that boy was my heart.
You give up Antwon Mitchell.
That'll buy you a day pass
to ID your brother's body.
Jesus, man,
I don't even know the cat.
I'm trying to k eep your ass
off death row.
If I had something,
I'd give it up.
DUTCH:
We may have caught a break.
CLAUDETTE:
We've got a suspect in custody
apprehended for ripping off
a house down the block.
Multiple convictions for grand theft,
history of violence.
You think he's involved?
You tell us.
Is this one of the men you saw
in the car outside your house?
Yeah, that's him. He was the driver.
Take your time.
We need to be sure.
It was definitely him.
You're positive?
A hundred percent. I remember
he was wearing that shirt.
This man's a police officer.
He was patrolling with his partner
when you shot your stepmother.
You... think that I killed Margo?
You dropped your dad off at the library,
went back and shot her.
No!
Then you picked up your dad,
brought him home,
two of you discovered her body.
Same choreography as when
you found your mother.
See, that was the last time
you had him all to yourself.
You tried to recapture that moment
in time when he needed you,
when it was just the two of you
against the world.
You wanna trick me into admitting
something that I did not do!
We've already got your father lying
about what you did.
Any more, he's gonna be
an accessory to murder after the fact.
If you confess now, we won't give him
the chance to lie himself into a jail cell.
[SIGHS]
[GROANS]
If he moved to Arizona,
he'd be dead in six months.
I cook his food.
l... I drive him to the doctor.
I make sure he has all 17 of his pills
at the right time each day.
She didn't care about him.
[SOBBING]
Not like...
Not like my mother.
Not like me.
She said
that they were going
to Arizona alone.
After all I've done.
She just turned her back on me,
and so I...
Shot her in hers.
What'd you do with the gun
and the jewellery?
I just threw it away.
DUTCH:
Where?
If I tell you...
will you let me say goodbye to him?
So I'm in the can, and I look over
and I see two dreadlocks
hanging out of the cabinet of the sink.
MAN:
This bad boy had to be 6'3".
How he folded his ass
into a space like yay:
Living in a 6-by-9
with three soul brothers
for a few years
ought to be a cake walk.
Everyone, you have
reason to be proud.
Today's raid netted
the largest cache
of black tar heroin
in Farmington history.
[APPLAUSE]
RAWLING:
The chief asked me
to convey his thanks.
Each of you will receive
a letter of commendation
from him personally.
So keep up the outstanding work.
[APPLAUSE]
This citizen that we took
to the hospital, what did you see?
The individual was informed
of the evacuation order.
He responded in a belligerent manner,
was restrained by the other officers.
RAWLING:
Anything to add?
That's pretty much
how it went down.
He isn't even out of the ER,
he's already threatening a law suit.
I'll make it clear to the city attorney
that his case has no merit.
Good work.
Thanks a lot.
Next time those guys
get to party,
over busting some soul brother,
better be out of my earshot.
They're just blowing off steam.
Everybody's just happy
to be in one piece.
Why is everybody treating this
like we just won the big game?
Because that raid
was a home run.
Yeah, well, I'm having a hard time
mustering team spirit
over a beat down.
Get real, Julien, you were there.
You saw what happened.
He was minding his own business
until we showed up
and started dragging him
and everybody else out of their homes.
Well, if those folks were interested
in getting the thugs off the streets,
instead of turning us
into the enemy.
Yeah, well, why are we
only doing this in Farmington?
What about Brentwood,
where the crooked drug lawyers live?
And the bankers who wash
the dirty money?
Why aren't we taking their houses?
If you think it's such a rotten idea,
why'd you help the captain
sell it on that panel?
DUTCH:
Got the gun, missing jewellery.
Three homicides we've caught the past
two weeks. Three for three.
You must be thrilled
to be back in the saddle.
Aren't you?
Wonder what changed?
What do you mean?
I've been the DA's leper for months.
All of a sudden,
I'm back in his good books.
You certainly did your time.
These are not the type of people
to let go of a grudge.
And I know I never apologized.
Well, maybe they finally realized
there was no upside
in benching
their two best detectives.
The buzz is that taking down
Maurice Webster
gave the prosecution
a win in some murder trial.
Where'd you hear that?
Ooh, that would explain
the sudden change in attitude.
That would also suggests
a quid pro quo.
I gotta get with Ballistics.
Confirm this is our murder weapon.
CLAUDETTE: Ballistics can wait.
DUTCH: I'm busy.
And stop treating me like a suspect.
Did you have a chat with Beth Insardi?
If we carried the Webster case, maybe
they'd let us out of the doghouse.
Something along those lines?
Fine. I confess.
At least now we're getting
confessions from other people too.
Real criminals. Killers.
What other errands do you have us
running for the DA?!
Nothing.
DUTCH:
One of us needed
to mend fences.
You went behind my back.
After being ignored head-on
for six months, you bet I did.
That wasn't your deal to make.
You're the best partner I ever had.
I hung in with you,
waiting for you to see this through.
Instead, you just dug
yourself in further.
I wasn't gonna sit on my hands
and watch you wreck
your career and mine along with it.
I got dinged pretty good in this too.
This was my fight.
And you lost.
So I threw in the towel with the DA.
And I'd do it again.
And if you wanna be pissed at me,
fine, go ahead.
RAWLING:
You put one of my guys on ice
then used that leverage
to turn him into your lapdog.
You do not wanna mess
with my people again.
A new captain is in
no position to make threats.
Assistant DA's are judged
by their conviction rate.
How's yours gonna look
when my people show up
an hour late in court,
give witnesses wiggle room
on their statements,
misplace evidence
only on your cases?
Either our offices are working
against each other or working together.
Which is it gonna be?
Together.
Good.
I keep hearing how good
these seizures are
for the neighbourhood.
Can't help wondering
if they're making things worse.
Okay.
This is where people live.
They're raising their kids.
We're treating it's some battleground.
How far is too far?
Okay.
So why are you
coming to me?
To get you to weigh in.
With your seniority.
You have got a very popular new
captain who's got the chief's support,
coming off a big success today.
Besides... my opinion doesn't seem
to mean jackshit around here.
If people thought like you
back in the day...
Don't lecture me
about the struggle, son.
I am the struggle.
Breaking down black folks' doors
to make the world safer
is not a new concept.
The difference is now you're
the one with the boot on your foot.
You got an opinion.
You got a voice.
Use it or lose it.
Hey, I'm getting my nuts twisted
by IAD on account of you.
Oh, easy, Quick Draw.
You stay out of this.
You and I don't have shit to talk
about on any subject.
Hey, hey. Easy.
Unis just found Angie's mother.
Dead from an overdose.
LEM:
Aw, shit.
Angie's given Social Services the slip.
She's probably out there
looking for her mom.
I gotta go find her.
Hang on, I'll come with.
Look, they may have grabbed your shit,
but the investigation is sealed off.
No roads lead back to you.
Just say thank you, Antwon.
Do you know how much
you cost me today, huh?
In product and in manpower?
Do you?
Well, if you'd kept me
in the loop on your tar castle,
then maybe I could have
kept an eye out for you, homey.
[ALL YELLING]
ANTWON:
Grab his piece. Grab his piece.
Give me both their guns.
Payback, bitch!
I don't get played,
and I ain't your homey.
Oh, man, you're gonna get...
[YELLS]
Shut up, bitch.
You knew they were taking down
my shit.
My niggas saw you faggots
on the goddamn raid.
So how you trying to tell me now
there was nothing that you could do?
Huh?!
You think you was ever making
the rules around here?
[GUN COCKS]
You're not stupid enough to bring
that kind of heat down on your ass.
Had a talk with her moms.
Amazing what a bitch
will give up for a little rush.
Or in this case, a big rush.
Jesus. You killed her mother.
This is the little whore
that gave up my block.
[SOBBING]
She's just a kid.
I know.
And you two...
should be ashamed of yourselves.
ANTWON:
You found her on the street.
Tried to bring her in for foster care.
But she didn't wanna go.
So she offered you a mouth bribe.
One thing led to another.
And then when she threatened
to tell your boss.
SHANE: No!
ARMY: No, no!
ANTWON:
Give him to me.
You got rid of your problem.
And I got rid of mine.
Now...
her body...
shows up...
with bullets in it...
from your two gats.
And your card
in her burnt little pocket.
One time, doing time,
for a long, long time.
[CHUCKLES]
From now on...
I say, "Suck my dick,"
you say,
"You want me
to lick your balls, Daddy?"
[GASPING]
[COUGHING]
[###]