JULIAN: Get back, let's go.
Get back, now, move!
[WILD HIP-HOP PLAYING]
MAN:
What's up with my legs, man?
My legs ain't moving, man!
WOMAN:
I think that's Betty Johnson's boy.
Hey, somebody wanna
turn that crap off?
MAN:
What's up with my legs, man?!
[HIP-HOP SILENCES]
My leg!
Drive-by in the hood. That's original.
Well, you know,
if it ain't broke,
don't fix it.
Victims are
all decked out Spookstreet.
Driver was gone, must have fled.
Found a half key of tar heroin
hidden in the back seat.
What's with him?
Just babbling.
DANNY:
Paramedics say
he's not gonna make it.
BILLINGS:
Witnesses?
Oh, yeah, they're just falling
all over themselves.
See no evil. Hear no evil.
[COOL ROCK PLAYING,
INDISTINCT CHATTER]
So, what are you hearing in Juvie
about Antwon Mitchell?
Besides building parks
and holding freedom rallies,
he's moving tar heroin
on the street.
Shane's been cozying up
to the guy lately.
He might be in business with him.
Well, he's not my problem.
We all have a stake in making sure
Shane stays out of IAD's headlights.
Gets in over his head, gets pinched,
we're his best chance of getting a deal.
No. Shane wouldn't.
He was ready to go to jail for Mara
when she almost killed Tavon.
He's a father now.
You'd be surprised
what you'd do for your kids.
RONNIE:
It never goddamn ends.
We need to get back close to him.
Make sure if there's a problem,
we can fix it before it's too late.
I haven't talked since it went down.
VIC:
I'll deal with him one on one.
Look, I spoke to your CO.
I want you to ride
with Danny and Julien tomorrow.
They've been assigned
to tap into the One-Niners.
If anyone's running their mouth
about Shane, I wanna hear it
before anybody else.
[ALL CHATTERING]
WOMAN: Good morning.
RAWLING: Morning.
MAN: I'll talk to you about it later.
MAN 2: All right.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[CHATTER SILENCES]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[ALL LAUGH]
Morning.
Um...
I think I've had a chance to meet
and speak with all of you.
But this is my first opportunity
as your captain.
[APPLAUSE]
In the, uh...
[CLEARS THROAT]
In, uh, the two plus years
since this substation's inception,
the Farmington district has had
its share of successes and failures.
The difficulties are well-known.
Unfortunately, the successes
are mostly known only in this house.
I see a lot of wonderful people
determined to make a difference.
I wouldn't have taken this job
if I didn't.
[RAWLING CLEARS THROAT]
Actually, I'm better one on one
than in front of a big crowd.
VIC:
They say you should imagine
your audience naked,
but with this crowd
I wouldn't suggest it.
[LAUGHTER]
Look...
I know what it's like out there.
I worked this neighbourhood.
You put
your life on the line every day.
The people that you protect
don't thank you enough for that,
so let me thank you for them.
The problems here
aren't about personnel.
They're about policy.
And that is what I'm here to change.
We...
[APPLAUSE]
We police a largely minority district.
They're universally poor.
Most of them don't speak the language.
They look one direction,
see financial skyscrapers.
They look in the other direction,
they see the Hollywood sign.
In between is the L.A. they know.
Gangs, drugs... fear.
We're not miracle workers.
We don't have
any hidden tricks up our sleeves.
We can't make fathers
want to stay in their kids' lives.
We can't solve poverty.
We can't take the addiction
out of heroin or cocaine.
Our job is to distinguish
between the criminals and the citizens.
It's been too hard
for the good people.
And too easy for the assholes,
and we are gonna change that.
We are gonna turn that around.
[CROWD CHATTERING & APPLAUSE]
Last night... Last night three members
of the Spookstreet Souljahs
were killed in a drive-by.
Three hours later,
they struck back at their rival gang.
The Farmington One-Niners.
Two more dead.
Five hours, five lives gone.
Uh, Steve, you're lead on the case.
What do we know?
Well, not much.
We're currently looking
for the owner of the car, but he's
AWOL.
RAWLING: Witnesses?
BILLINGS: None that are cooperating.
Starting today...
all drug and gang-related homicides
will go through Vic Mackey.
I've posted a list of 10 detectives and
20 unis who'll work directly under Vic.
He'll be leading a task force
designed to learn everything we can
about the roughly 50 gangs
who operate on our turf.
Their membership, their businesses,
chains of command.
Federal asset forfeiture laws
will now be enforced in Farmington.
A drug dealer uses a car
to distribute drugs,
we're gonna seize that vehicle.
A gang sells crack out of their back
room, we're gonna take that home.
Stereo equipment, plasma TV's.
Everything bought with drug money.
We're gonna take those assets,
auction them off.
The DA's office will get a third
to help finance further prosecutions.
A third will be funnelled back
into the community.
For a better Social Services,
for safe playgrounds.
For after-school programmes.
We want these people to know
we're about more
than just throwing their men into jail.
The rest of the proceeds
are gonna be used to help you.
Now, besides the grand reopening
of the men's room...
[LAUGHTER & APPLAUSE]
I'm gonna hire more cops.
I'm gonna authorise overtime when you
tell me that you need it to close a case.
I'm gonna purchase equipment
that actually works.
[LAUGHTER & APPLAUSE]
I'm going to encourage informants
to come forward
by giving them a cut
of assets we seize.
Citizens whose fear and silence
the gangs depend on.
We are gonna make them a better deal
than the bangers.
It'll sting at first.
People usually don't like change.
And I still wouldn't expect
any thank-yous.
But we will make things better.
VIC:
There's been another retaliation.
One dead
and two critical on Alvarado.
The job's impossible.
I can't do it without you.
So let's get started. Thank you.
[CHEERING & APPLAUSE]
[###]
I didn't think you could top
fixing the men's john.
But I gotta give that speech
four flushes.
Don't be too impressed.
I still haven't gotten
my voice mail to work.
A gang war's
the last thing I need right now.
I'll serve all open warrants.
Double up patrols in Spookstreet
and One-Niner territory.
Get as many of these guys
off the streets as possible.
What's the average life cycle
of days-of-rage in the Farm?
I've seen them as short as a week,
as long as a year.
Look, dealing with these gang beefs
can take time. They're complicated.
Bunch of kids shooting at each other.
Stop it, so we can move forward.
I don't know. What do you think?
Sherman's march through the hood.
Sounds like one step forward,
two steps back.
Aceveda's old office
is now our command post.
VIC:
Courtesy of our new captain.
These all outline
all known gang turf in Farmington.
Each of you has been assigned
a territory to map.
When you're not answering 911 calls,
get to know it like home.
Take a Polaroid with you.
You see a shithead, engage him.
Take his picture. Document his ink.
Get his name, street tag.
Bring it all back here.
Danny, Julien, this little sliver
of milk and honey is
Farmington One-Niner territory.
VIC:
Now it's your piece of paradise.
Spookstreet and One-Niners
are warring.
I want you to get in their face,
find out what they're fighting about.
Lem's gonna ride with you two today,
get you guys up to speed.
DANNY:
Thought you were
working Juvie.
Well, half the Niners are under 17.
I mixed it up with the other half
on the Strike Team.
We're especially interested
in an O.G. named Antwon Mitchell.
Seems like he's back in action. If you
hear anything about him, let me know.
VIC: Everybody clear?
MAN: Absolutely.
VIC: Hit the road.
RAWLING: Thank you.
RONNIE: Vic.
VIC: What's up?
Owner of the shot-up Escalade's
rap sheet. Street name's Choppa.
We got unis posted
at his apartment and known hangouts.
All right, put patrols at
his girlfriend's house, mother's too.
Trouble hits, these assholes
always run one of two ways.
To the pussy they're getting into
or the pussy they came out of.
Find Stank, he runs the One-Niners.
Call me if something pops.
Yup.
[COOL HIP-HOP PLAYING]
Tough getting up in the morning
without a prison guard
banging on your cell door?
Rough night.
VIC:
Too busy running a gang war,
Antwon?
Too busy trying to find out
what started it.
Shootings scare away
customers, huh?
Slows down
your drug trade?
Somebody's gotta
keep the peace.
Trust me. I'm on top of it.
I'm sleeping better already.
Why you here?
Figure out how we're
gonna keep that peace.
I don't even know
what they're warring about, man.
If I did, maybe I could stop it,
but I don't.
Today's the one day
I don't give a shit
whether you're Pablo Escobar
or Bishop Tutu.
We both want the same thing.
So as info pours in,
you let me know.
And I'll let you know
what you can do about it.
LEM:
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
DANNY:
Farmington One-Niners.
LEM:
Hey, what's up, Big Crane?
CRANE: Just walking.
LEM: Yeah?
JULIEN:
You wouldn't be just walking
to beef with Spookstreet, would you?
CRANE: Just walking, homey.
LEM: What's the word out there?
Word is watch for gats
on the roll, man.
JULIEN: Mind if we take your picture?
CRANE: For what?
For dressing like you're representing.
New policy.
They just threads, man.
Come on, man. Don't make trouble.
All right, show us the ink.
LEM:
All the way.
DANNY:
That's an awful lot of artwork for
someone who's not banging, Big Crane.
What's your real name?
You mean my slave name?
Tremaine Harris.
Who you rolling with, Tremaine?
ARMANDO:
The Vice king strikes again.
This guy could smell the sin
out of a nun's crack.
We all learn from the best.
It's all about the intel, brother.
How you choose it, how you use it.
Missed you at Gilroy's funeral.
Had more pressing problems to bury.
But I'll send Nancy a fruit cake
if it'll make you feel better.
Vice keeping you busy?
Wetbacks making book
out of a roach coach.
Good thing I ordered first.
Little, uh, beef, bean and cash burrito.
You want a taste?
No thanks.
Trying to earn
that Eagle Scout badge, huh?
Look, this war between the Niners
and Spookstreet's running hot.
Since these things
are almost always drug-related,
I figured you'd lend a hand.
Army and I got a full load.
I had your back with
that BlackBerry you pocketed
over at Dead-Eye's the other night.
No professional courtesy in return?
I'll ask around.
This Choppa's
mom's house?
BILLINGS:
Yeah. He went inside 10 minutes ago.
[VIC KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Yeah?
We're looking for your son, Al.
His car was involved in an accident.
He ain't around.
You know where
we can find your brother?
Don't be talking to him, D.
If you don't tell us,
he's gonna go to jail, do you?
You don't want that?
He's in his room.
[MAN LAUGHING,
FUNKY HIP-HOP PLAYING]
Assume the position, ladies.
Hands on your head right now.
Hands on your head!
BILLINGS: Turn around.
Since when
is niggas kicking it a crime?
Aw, yeah, that's right,
since around forever.
Aw, chilling's cool.
Those teeth are a felony though.
MAN:
Gun.
You plotting retribution? Huh?
No, man.
We got a circle jerk jumping off.
Why don't you grab
some Vaseline and join in?
Who shot up your car
and your friends last night, Choppa?
Don't know. Wasn't there.
Where are your clothes?
You don't live here.
Come here.
MAN:
Keep your ass right there.
Stand right there.
WOMAN:
Those are my linens.
Told you to wash my shirt, Mama.
Started the sheets first.
Always separate your blood stains
from your delicates, asshole.
Armed robbery with a deadly weapon
at a convenience store on Baxter.
Victim's at Mission Cross.
What happened?
Shot, stabbed?
Splashed,
with a really hot cup of coffee.
Don't you think it's a waste of time
to give us a case a uni could handle
when there's a gang war
going on out there?
I would love to use you both
for more important things.
Apologized to the DA yet?
Let me know when you do.
Impressive.
Only six months into
our unflinching moral stand,
already the results
are devastatingly effective.
CHOPPA: I was at a light,
they rolled up on the passenger
side and started blasting.
VIC:
Did you see
who the other shooters were?
My black ass was out the door
the second I heard it jumping off.
So you running
had nothing to do
with the half kilo of tar
we found in your car?
That shit wasn't mine.
Belonged to my homeboy, Shank.
Right. Blame it on the guy
who didn't make it out alive.
Shit's unfortunate.
But I'd do it for him
if I'd taken the bullet, so.
RAWLING:
Come on, you know who shot at you.
You told your crew.
How else would they know
who to retaliate against?
Apologise to the DA already.
You made your point.
I deserve
out of the doghouse.
People deserve our expertise
solving serious crimes.
I'm not apologizing.
You don't have to mean it.
DANNY:
Okay, Rodrigo,
tell them what happened.
I was working the register
when this man came in.
He asked me if the coffee was fresh.
I said I just brewed it.
He got a cup.
He gave me a five.
I went to open the register
to make change,
and then he threw
the coffee in my face.
He grabbed the cash,
and he ran...
[GUNSHOTS]
Shots fired.
Call for backup!
[GUNSHOTS]
WOMAN:
Shots fired inside the ER
at Mission Cross.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Room's clear!
MAN:
Shooters took off, man.
Hurts like a bitch.
You're in the right place.
Hey, where's Corrine?
DUTCH: She was off duty.
RAWLING: What happened?
Harold Pinker.
Spookstreeter nicknamed Oink.
He was treated for a broken finger.
Nurses say two teens
sporting One-Niner colours
came in to see a friend,
saw Oink, went right for him.
DUTCH:
Rent-a-cop chased the shooters
out. Took a slug for his troubles.
There are no metal detectors?
VIC: They can't afford thermometers.
You want us to follow up on this?
Vic's on it. Get back to your case.
We've got good news, bad news
and worse news.
How about a refill on my beverage?
VIC: Oh, Sure.
Refreshed?
The bad news is your cousin, Oink,
was admitted to the ER.
The worse news is
the One-Niners found him there
and killed him.
Good news is,
off the tar we found in your truck,
we searched your apartment
and found enough hell dust
to earn you stripes in Chino.
These pricks killed two of your friends.
Slaughtered your cousin.
Tell us who started this
so we can stop it.
CHOPPA:
You want me to rat out names?
So you can stick us all in the same
cage and get me smoked?
If you don't, they hit back,
you end up in the same prison anyway.
No, me and my boys gonna handle this
in the streets. Believe that.
SHANE:
Sorry to interrupt.
But I bet you didn't know that
your suspect also goes by "Goldie G."
Bona fide triple-X rap mogul.
Oh, you gotta be shitting me.
Monica Rawling.
This is Shane Vendrell.
I hear you're making
quite a name for yourself over in Vice.
Miss our Barn?
Place wasn't without its charms,
but like they say, uh,
off to bigger and better.
Couple of pros at a video shoot
saw a hood rat
with One-Niner ink playing
hide the bone with Choppa.
Thought it might be related
to your gang war out there.
Army's looking into who made it.
[WILD HIP-HOP PLAYING,
WOMAN MO ANING]
[RAPPING WILDLY]
Never thought of myself as a prude,
but... might be time to reconsider.
Met the guys,
get ready for their better halves.
Heck of a place
for a mommy and me class.
LEM:
How you doing, Tanika?
Be a lot better if you'd brought
this fine brother around here earlier.
Wouldn't be the baby mama
of some broke-ass nigga.
Do you know anything
about these shootings?
Just our men getting shot up.
Antwon Mitchell
have anything to do with it?
No, Antwon's straight up.
He built this park.
You know him?
No, but I know
three of his baby mamas.
How many has he got?
Why? You looking to get knocked up?
Who's the skank?
Caught the booty,
didn't catch the name.
Bet you caught something else.
You know your leading lady
is One-Niner property?
Why you think I was claiming my set?
VIC:
So what?
All this shooting's over her?
CHOOPA:
We don't throw down over bitches.
Look, all's I know is
the One-Niners shot up my ride
and killed three of my niggas.
What's with the video?
CHOPPA:
It's a demo.
Y'all always jawing
about getting a job.
That's my résumé.
So this is gonna
launch your career?
[LAUGHS]
Yeah. Check it out.
I'm gonna get my freak on with this ho.
Six people are dead.
Why are you smiling?
You can't buy
this type of street cred.
It takes time.
I don't have time.
Everyone has a pressure point.
Find his.
You wanted a second chance.
I gave it to you.
Now get it done.
Wow, looks like fun to be a cop here.
Pretend this guy isn't a coffee thrower.
Let's say he killed three people.
Well, now you're just
getting me aroused.
Okay, uh, he escaped on foot.
Means he probably lives in the area.
His M.O.'s simple, yet effective.
I'd say he's had priors,
learned from his mistakes.
Let's start there.
VIC:
This is Stank, One-Niner captain.
Captain Rawling.
Call me Monica,
if we're gonna do business,
we should be on a first-name basis.
We didn't start a thing.
Of course, you didn't.
You know who did?
Come on upstairs. I got something
might jog your memory.
Oh, here comes
the good part.
Who is she?
Just some skank-ass ho.
He knows the girl.
I'll find her.
SHANE:
Hey.
Followed up on that video.
Company called
Ghetto Bang Productions made it.
Owner's name is Terrence Ross.
Army and I'll track him down.
I appreciate your help,
but you're not under my command.
This is our investigation.
I'll join him.
RAWLING:
Fine.
Army and me
can handle it.
VIC:
I'll back you up anyway.
You wanna tag along,
tag along.
Terrence Ross?
Who are you?
VIC:
The pussy police.
I'd tell you to spread them,
but looks like she beat you to it.
SHANE:
What's up with that?
Hung brothers, old mothers.
It's the next big thing.
I'm more interested
in Choppa.
Hey, man, that cat's straight thug.
I got a family.
You want us going through
your hard drive?
Checking the IDs
of every chickenhead in your movies?
Choppa needed a demo.
I'm a one-stop shop.
Got the cameras, girls, Viagra.
What, Samuel Goldwyn
meets Seymore Butts.
I do weddings
and confirmations too...
Who's the One-Niner
Spinner was riding bareback?
Name's Bounce. She's a video ho.
Looking to hook up with the next Nelly,
get herself out of the hood.
VIC: Where can we find her?
She lives in the jungles.
I think I got her
address around here.
Here you go.
Keep it, I was looking to hit that,
but after seeing Choppa bust raw,
I'll save myself a trip to the free clinic,
you know what I mean?
[SPEAKING IN
FOREIGN LANGU AGE]
My uncle says a man came in
and threw hot coffee in his face
and robbed him.
Yeah, yeah.
Can he give us a description
of the assailant?
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGU AGE]
Okay, okay. Calm down.
This is an investigation,
not a goddamn jihad.
Might not recognise Bounce
with her clothes on.
RAWLING:
Oh, but I do.
I don't do porn, I was dancing.
Tomato, tomato.
Thanks for your help.
Just like old times, brother.
Yeah.
Well, see you around.
RAWLING:
Who gave you your black eye?
I ain't no snitch. He'll kill me.
You have a newborn, right?
Ten months.
You violated your parole.
You do another bid in Chowchilla,
Child Services is gonna
take that baby away.
I don't want that.
I ain't violating nothing.
It's called consorting
with a known felon.
Peter hit me.
Who's Peter?
Puppethead. My baby daddy.
He saw the video. He got jealous.
Just because I suck his dick
don't make him my man.
VIC:
Puppethead's a One-Niner?
This war, it's about you?
[CHUCKLES]
I guess I'm the bomb, huh?
DUTCH:
We're investigating
a convenience-store robbery.
I don't do those anymore.
Well, forgive me if I'm sceptical, Kyle,
but we've got your prints on file.
We're running them
against the coffee cup.
Coffee cup?
Yeah, guy threw coffee in the clerk's
face while he was making change.
Cleaned out the register.
I always used a knife.
Can I get a moment with you, please?
Sure.
I by no means meant to offend you,
your ethnic background,
or your religion in any way.
I apologise profusely.
His comments were not reflective
of this department, whatsoever.
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGU AGE]
[MAN SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGU AGE]
He asks if you caught the guy yet.
Not yet. But I assure you I won't
let him rest until he does.
RAWLING:
If you ever have a problem
in the future, call me directly.
WOMAN:
Thank you. Good day.
Borderline racism aside,
I don't have time for this nonsense.
I'm sorry. I was distracted.
It's not easy being cut out
of all the action here.
It's my first day,
I'm already tired of hearing it.
[WHISPERING]
Puppethead will be on edge,
worried about some street retaliation.
So be careful.
Right.
[MAN WHISTLES]
VIC:
Spotters! He's running, let's go.
[DOG BARKING]
You wanna go over? Go over.
[MAN YELLS, THUD]
[DOG BARKS]
You know,
Puppethead started this war
because he didn't like Choppa
inside his woman's cooch.
PUPPETHEAD:
Spookstreet tried to take me out.
VIC:
Oh, yeah?
Where'd they take shots at you?
I'll send unis over there,
look for bullet holes.
I saw the video, bitch.
VIC:
I know you started this war.
RAWLING:
Is that the guy who shot up your car?
Do you even worry about yourself?
About being killed?
When it's time, it's time.
Well, that's a way of looking at it.
I got a witness
saw you tak e the shots.
Help yourself out and cooperate.
You got a witness, huh?
Let me hear what he got to spit.
What other leverage do we have?
VIC:
I had Ronnie look
into Choppa's finances.
He rents an apartment on Baxter.
But he also owns a house.
How'd he pay for it?
Cash down payment.
Makes the mortgages
with money orders.
Drug money. Who lives there?
His mom, her two other kids.
And we don't have anything else.
Mother know
how he paid for the house?
She knows
he's never held down a job.
Can we make a solid connection
between the house payments
and drug money?
You're gonna tell Choppa
we're taking his mom's house?
He's tough,
he could call our bluff.
What if it isn't a bluff?
He doesn't ID the shooters,
help us stop this, we take the house.
I love it.
How old are the kids?
Young.
Be a huge PR nightmare.
Tossing two kids out onto the street
is not exactly the cleanest example
of how I want this to work.
Taking the house
is the only leverage we have.
Yeah, this policy got
a shitload of resistance
when I pitched it to Pol Com.
Chief bit because
nothing else has worked.
The last thing I want
is to give the naysayers any ammo
to shut this down
before it gets a chance to take off.
VIC:
Rise and shine.
Still playing, huh?
Who shot at you?
Last time I'm asking.
Good, because I'm sick
of you barking.
Okay, take the house.
With pleasure.
What house?
The one you bought your mother
by dealing dope.
Yeah, right. You can't take shit.
Come with me. I'll show you.
Do you know what federal
asset-forfeiture laws are, Chopper?
Skipped that course
at Harvard, huh?
It means any property
bought with drug money
or used to facilitate the drug trade
can be seized.
I ain't falling for no bullshit.
No bullshit.
Unless you prove
you bought the house legitamately,
it's ours to put up for auction.
RAWLING:
We're not required to provide
you a defence either.
You wanna fight this?
Then hire a lawyer on your own dime.
Quit clowning. This is America.
Turns out a One-Niner named
Puppethead started this war.
His shortie had a thing
for a Souljah's pogo stick.
That right?
This is all about
a jealous boyfriend.
I see my tax dollars
are being well-spent.
What do you want from me?
I got the guy who started this.
I just need you to keep
these assholes out on the street
from shooting each other
for me to show the neighbourhood
that things are changing.
And we got things under control.
What makes you think
they'll listen to me?
I've seen you work a room.
Even convinced a few people
that you're on the straight and narrow.
Feel free to confess
that you're a piece-of-shit gangster.
Thanks for the help.
Detective Wyms.
MAN: Thanks for coming.
DUTCH: What happened?
Guy bought a cup of coffee.
I opened the register, he splashed me.
Grabbed my cash and ran.
I'm lucky, coffee wasn't hot.
CLAUDETTE:
Surveillance camera working?
I got him on my cell phone.
Didn't you talk to that guy today?
Yeah, he had a rock-solid alibi.
Aw, man. Aw, man.
This is entrapment.
CLAUDETE: How do you figure?
I'm a thief, he's telling me about asking
for change, then throwing coffee.
It's like giving a junkie a syringe.
I was done robbing
until he put it back in my head.
That's our guy?
Uh, actually, we inadvertently
slipped a few details
to one of our other suspects.
Kind of created a copycat.
But we got him.
Still working on the original guy.
Way to go.
Get assigned a simple robbery,
cause a crime wave.
Remind me never to put you guys
on a murder case.
Hope you're happy.
Keys. Thanks.
Hey, called your dentist.
Paid for your choppers with cash.
Tooth fairy wants them back.
Man, I ain't giving you my fronts.
Either you take them out yourself,
or I get a pair of pliers.
Thanks, honey.
LEM:
Vic.
What's up?
One thing we know about Antwon is
he don't like to strap his shit up.
What'd you hear?
Guy's fathered a dozen children
from six different mothers.
Knocked up a couple from behind bars
by sneaking his sperm out.
Holy shit.
You hit up that many women,
you're bound to leave
some serious scorn behind.
All right, let's find out their names.
Anything about Shane?
Nope, not a word.
All right, keep listening.
Aloicious? Aloicious,
what have you got us into?
It's okay, Mama.
They just trying to scare me.
It ain't gonna work though.
It's working on me.
It's working on me, Aloicious.
Are you crazy?
Excuse me, can I help you?
Let go of me.
Calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down.
Who's in charge?
Who put my babies on the street?
I'm Captain Rawling.
You did this?
You're taking my house?
I've reserved shelter space
for the three of you.
What the hell am I supposed to do
with shelter space?
The department of Social
and Human Services
can help you find
permanent residence.
You wanna help?
You give me my home back.
I can't do that.
You got no right throwing children
out of their beds.
RAWLING:
All your son has to do
is cooperate with our investigation.
He does that,
he will help us save a lot of lives.
My boy got shot at. He's innocent.
Your boy bought your home
using drug money.
You knew where that money came from,
and you chose to look the other way.
You don't know
what it's like living here.
You think I can just pick
and choose how to go about surviving?
You don't have children,
do you?
Do you?! Because if you did,
you couldn't do this.
No mother could do this.
Six children are dead.
How do you think those mothers...?
You don't have kids of your own,
so you're throwing mine out.
Just be glad that all you lost today
was your home, and not your son.
Shut up!
You just shut up!
These are recruiters.
Newbies just got their stripes.
They find the next generation
to bring in.
What's up, Lil Bull?
Hey, man, I got some people here
wanna take you guys' pictures.
Gonna make you all famous,
all right?
Go ahead, man, say cheese.
JULIEN:
What's your name, son?
Run, stupid, run!
Come here, when a police officer
gives you an instruction, you listen.
You understand?
I don't want
my picture taken.
All right, then why are you
hanging out with gangs? Hey.
What are you,
my mama now?
Go.
VIC:
Look, this lawsuit's
gonna bury us financially.
But can you afford not to sue?
The money I'm asking you to put up
for medical tests is peanuts
compared to what two autistic kids
are gonna need over their lifetimes.
I work at a hospital.
What if I pulled some strings and found
a way to get the tests done there?
The doctors I use are experts.
They're expensive,
but their testimony carries weight.
Her friend Gail
is the head of Paediatrics.
That expert enough for you?
Talk to her.
If she's willing to testify and can
provide the credentials I need,
I guess I can live with it.
Good.
Can I at least
eat dinner in peace?
You know, this isn't about right
and wrong with you anymore.
It's about pride.
Can't psychoanalyze killers anymore,
so you're giving me the once over?
Okay, uh, maybe it's easier
to shoot yourself in the foot
be a martyr than to be a captain
and make tough decisions.
You can always get
another partner, Dutch.
I don't want that.
What do you expect me to do?
You... You're not giving me any choice.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
I thought your shift ended
an hour ago.
I'm just finishing up
some paperwork.
Captain, I wanted to thank you
for including me in all this.
It feels really good
to have a mission,
not just out answering
drunk and disorderlies.
Thank Vic. He recommended you.
WOMAN:
There's no reliable evidence
to prove a causal link
between Thimerosal and autism.
I won't do the testing because
I won't be a party to this lawsuit.
What about
the 300 percent rise in cases
since they increased
the vaccines for children?
Could just mean we're getting
better at diagnosing autism.
There aren't enough case studies
to prove anything.
They're shooting our kids up
with mercury.
You're saying that
it's a coincidence
they're sick?
What would you do, Gail?
You love your children
for who they are.
Just get out of the suit,
save your money.
Why? Because lawsuits like these
cost doctors like you a few bucks?
CORRINE: Vic.
No.
How many shots of Thimerosal
have you prescribed to kids?
Saying that
they've been poisoning our kids
is like admitting you've been
doing it all along, right?
I've devoted my life
to caring for children.
I'm a cop
who looks out for other cops.
Don't you tell me that doctors
don't look out for other doctors.
You know, helping them out.
Making sure that they hide the truth
from people like us.
The only difference is,
what I do
doesn't screw kids up
for the rest of their lives.
Corrine, please. Just talk to him.
If you don't wanna help us,
we're gonna find
someone else who will.
It's not like that.
This isn't who my children
were supposed to be.
It cost me my marriage,
their future.
And you're wrong.
My mom's at work.
I came to ask you
what to do with this?
These pictures, they go up
on a wall in our Station House.
Once they're up, they only come down
for one of two reasons.
Either you die, or you go to jail.
Do I need to put this up or will you
consider making some other choices?
Like what?
I grew up around here. There are
other ways to go, Church, sports.
Nah, I ain't into that stuff.
What about
the Explorer's Programme?
What's that?
We take young men like you.
We teach them about law enforcement.
I don't wanna be like you.
Look, when we took your picture,
you ran.
That means you're scared.
You're scared
because you know it's wrong.
You need to chill, Oprah.
I ain't never gonna be no sellout cop.
I just needed to know what to do
with this picture.
Now I know.
Hey, not too bad for day one, huh?
We're gonna need a bigger room.
I just got off the phone with Central.
Puppethead was
bailed out last night.
He had a quarter million dollar bail.
Antwon Mitchell
put up 25 grand cash bond.
Goddamn it.
Guess you're thinking
what I'm thinking.
Puppethead isn't long
for this world.
He might be gone already.
VIC:
Hey.
Where's Puppethead?
People saying he's dead.
MAN: Where...?
RAWLING: Who's saying that?
Antwon gave him up to Spookstreet
so they'd end this war.
And I heard they whipped him,
chained him to the back of a car and
dragged him till his skin peeled off.
Nothing like that's been reported.
Well, that's what they're saying.
RAWLING:
Antwon got a set
to give up one of their own.
You believe that?
Well... we won't know for sure
unless a body shows up.
It'll show.
He'll want his bail money back.
Yeah.
Chenille Jenkins never went
to the shelter with her kids.
Taking the house
didn't get Choppa to cooperate.
The war's over,
why does it feel like we lost?
Well, we did.
Antwon showed the street
that he's got more juice than we do.
Look, we got our shooters,
we made the peace.
Nothing says you can't give that house
back to Chenille and the two kids.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Surprise.
For your boy.
Uh, thanks, man.
Better late than never, huh?
Yeah.
Cute kid.
Yeah, he's got
his mother's looks.
Thank God.
Nice place.
Yeah, the last one barely held
two of us, let alone a third.
Hello, Vic.
I think it's warm enough.
SHANE:
Okay.
[BABY COOING]
Is she all right?
Yeah. Just a little postpartum,
you know.
Still adjusting.
It's a... It's a lot, you know?
So, what's up?
We did pretty good
on this thing, you know.
Stopped the war.
These seizures are real.
Farmington's gonna be the place...
One second, buddy.
[BABY SOBBING]
Hold on, it's coming,
it's coming.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's okay.
I know, I know, it's coming.
If it wasn't warm enough,
why didn't you say so?
It's okay, I got it.
SHANE:
Come on, get dressed, all
right? I'll make you some lunch.
So, what, uh?
What about the seizures?
I'll need the best people
to make it happen.
Our differences aside,
you're one of them.
I got a good thing on Vice.
My own boss,
my own way of doing things.
What exactly are you doing?
I'm getting what I need done.
I hope you're using protection.
You lecturing me?
Man, you killed our team, not me.
You're right.
I made some mistakes. I'll own that.
I'm past working for you, Vic.
You wouldn't be.
I got the watch,
but the only person you'd be
taking orders from is the captain.
You still get to do things your way.
Well, I got a partner
I trust now.
I really like
running with this guy, man.
Well, I'll try to bring him in too.
You know, working out of the Barn
will make things easier on the family.
Consistent hours.
Plenty of overtime if you need it.
Shane's doing great without you.
He's making a lot of arrests.
Well, you both did
a great job with this one.
He's beautiful.
Thanks.
Look, I'II, uh...
I'll think about it.
Good.
I don't trust him.
It's not about trust anymore, baby.
It's not.
[SIGHS]
Lady.
Don't throw my peoples
on the street.
I'll tell you everything.
Too late now. The guy we wanted you
to ID is on the loose. Probably dead.
So, what's gonna happen
to my mama's house?
You ain't even sorry, are you?
We're done talking.
You a white bitch!
You threw children on the street!
You a crackerwood ho!
You hear me, bitch?
Hey, shut up.
You a white bitch too.
Hey, easy.
What you looking at?
Can I help you, detective?
My partner and I have been on your
office shit list for six months.
Oh, I must have missed that memo.
It needs to end.
You need
to divorce your partner.
What's it gonna take
to get the DA off her ass?
Going into his office,
getting on her hands and knees
and begging for his forgiveness.
She's not gonna do that.
Then you're both in
for a long winter.
I got work to do.
Well, what if I, uh?
What if I promise to control her?
Are you sure
you can do that?
I wouldn't be here if I couldn't.
She listens to me.
Would that be enough?
This office needs favours
from time to time.
I'd expect you to deliver them
when I ask.
You got a deal.
I was told we're moving this stuff out.
All we need's a signature.
Now this guy inside says
we might not?
What's going on, captain?
Give me a minute, okay?
We swept the place.
No drugs, I'm checking the inventory.
Everything's still here.
Explain to me why taking this house
was the right thing to do yesterday,
but the wrong thing today.
Yesterday, we had to stop
the shootings.
This house was bought
with drug money.
The mother knew it.
You said
it would be a PR nightmare.
Either it works,
or it doesn't.
To make exceptions
to put a prettier face on it...
sounds more like Aceveda
than me.
Take it.
[###]