SHANE: Nice smile, ace.
LEM: Yeah.
[ALL LAUGHING]
VIC:
The Russians are on the move.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
VIC:
Tall blond guy's Tretiak.
ROC captain.
He's the asshole that Carl
and Scooby slapped with
that reckless-driving ticket.
RONNIE:
Who's the girl?
LEM:
Must be one of his whores.
VIC:
Oh, shit.
[TRETIAK AND IRINA
SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
Oh, this guy...
Hey, we got a job to do here, okay?
Yeah, smacking a hooker around
is not gonna give us any leverage
to twist this guy.
Why don't we turn over his office,
find something real to pin on him.
Yeah, I got it.
RONNIE:
Looks like invoices for
the restaurant over here.
Go through them all.
Show me anything that
doesn't look aboveboard.
Gotta find something
to hold over this guy's head.
MAN [ON TAPE]
Tell Phillip that James and Peter
are meeting us at the dance hall.
[MAN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN
ON TAPE]
English for Russian Dummies.
LEM: Check this out, man.
Looks like a lot of their
shipments get delivered
to a warehouse
at the Alameda railyard.
According to this, he gets beef
shipped there twice a month.
So it's a steak-and-blowjob joint.
RONNIE:
The warehouse is for dry goods.
What kind of steak
doesn't need refrigeration?
I usually just order
the blowjob.
Can we talk someplace?
I'm good here.
The chief's made the decision
to shelf the asset-forfeiture policy.
I'm sorry. It wasn't
an easy decision.
You were the eyes and ears
of the chief on this project.
Who's really the one with
his finger on the kill switch?
We have two dead cops,
allegations of corruption,
and a community on fire.
We said from the start
it would be a trial.
Cops in other divisions
are expressing concerns...
They haven't seen firsthand
how this is working.
Look, I called you out
in front of Aceveda.
Said some things
I shouldn't have.
I apologise.
We know how invested
you are in this policy.
That's why we want you to draught
the department's statement,
explaining why
we're suspending it.
Sell it to the press however
you deem appropriate.
Well, Phillips is hoping I'll just quit.
He wants you to take one for the blue.
I've been taking one for the blue
for over 20 goddamn years.
When are they
gonna take one for me?
The seizures are making a difference.
You keep trying to make that case,
but the crime stats say otherwise.
Those stats are
three months behind.
I see a difference
in our caseloads every day.
Less violent crime,
less gang activity.
Those numbers catch up,
they'll show that I'm right.
Not if they shut
you down now.
Well, it's not a done deal
until Pol Com signs off on it.
They're assuming your committee
will just rubber-stamp it.
The next session
is in three days.
I know how much you've got
invested in the Barn.
It's your legacy.
I also know how you'd
like the city council
to have more influence
on how the department operates.
Us working together
is the last thing that
downtown will suspect.
I mean, Mitchell's in jail.
We ride out this rough spot.
We keep the seizures going.
Crime goes down, revenue
continues. It's a win-win.
Farmington becomes a model
for other districts.
And you get to hang your
mayoral hat on a big success.
And where do we stand with
the murders of Scooby and Carl?
Have you been able to prove
that they're not seizure-related?
Not yet.
Well, that would be helpful.
Well, whoever's behind them
is our main priority.
SHANE: So, what do you think
is in the commie lunch box?
VIC: Coke and a sandwich?
SHANE: Yeah, or china white.
It's too milky to be tar.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
SHANE:
Looks like the girl's translating.
Hey, the guy with the Russians
is driving a pickup that says
Holbalt Construction.
He's alone.
SHANE: They just leave
the drugs sitting there?
LEM:
What's that about, man?
I don't know, man.
But I'm gonna get a closer look.
Oh, shit.
What's up?
VIC: Jesus Christ!
LEM: Heads up, dude.
What the hell was that?
RONNIE: Jesus Christ.
C-4.
[###]
Hey, can you do me a favour?
PERRY: Yeah, what do you need?
I need you to remain silent, because
anything you say might get you shot.
I got behind on my book.
Ponies, mostly.
I started paying Tretiak back
in supplies.
Lumber, cement...
Explosives?
The Russians asked me to get C-4.
I told them it was too risky.
The government keeps
pretty close tabs on that shit.
They threatened
to tell my boss.
So I forged the ATF papers.
Getting it from
a plant in Arkansas.
Shipment comes in today.
What are they using it for?
I don't know. They're shipping
a ton of it back to Kamchatka.
Shit. Everyone in this country's
so worried about what's getting
smuggled in.
Nobody's watching
what's getting shipped out.
That clay hits Russian soil,
ROC can distribute it to any
major terrorist organization.
What size shipment
are we talking about?
A ton.
Tell ATF it went down too fast to call.
We'll let them haul it away.
Yeah, I'll get SWAT
and the bomb crew to back us up.
Great, us?
I'm riding with you
and your guys on this.
Hey, wait. This is real
breach-and-bang stuff.
It's not a great time to babysit.
In three days, Phillips
is gonna recommend to
the police commission
that they kill our
seizure policy.
We need to prove that these
cop killings aren't seizure-related.
That gives us a lifeline.
What we need is to find
everyone who was involved
in killing Carl and Scooby.
Which is why
I'm coming with.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
So how do you wanna do this?
Well, C-4's pretty harmless
without a cap, but I wouldn't
wanna risk any gunplay.
Let them lock up the container.
Have the sharpshooters take point
on the bridge.
My guys will be the first wave.
Have SWAT take tactical watch.
Back us up with unis.
Okay.
You find Tretiak?
He's back at the restaurant.
Guess he doesn't
like heavy lifting.
VIC: Yeah, saving his strength
for hooker beating.
When we're done here,
you two peel off,
pick up Tretiak
and his lieutenant.
And grab the hooker too,
we're gonna need a translator.
I know these Russians.
Once they get into custody,
they turn into stone.
Tired of our leads
dead-ending.
We're gonna bleed Tretiak
for everything he knows
about Carl and Scooby.
We're all set.
Us too.
SHANE:
Hands in the air, right now!
Right now, buddy!
Right there, on the ground!
Let's go, Boris.
SHANE: Right now!
You, buddy. on the ground!
Get down, right now!
VIC: Goddamn it!
[GRUNTING]
Get down!
[SIRENS WAILING]
OFFICER: Let's go.
Cold War's over, boys.
No sign of a struggle.
No buckshot through the hands.
He never saw it coming.
That better or worse?
Either way, it's worse.
TERESA: SID tech found this
and a 12-gauge shell.
Looks like the victim's wallet.
Gill Prue. Local.
Amex, ATM card, about 40 bucks.
CLAUDETTE: If he wasn't robbed,
why get blasted at point blank range?
Hummer gone bad?
Gang execution?
Dr. Grohl, rage-management classes,
one-on-one counselling.
Maybe he ran into someone
who flunked that class.
I know a shotgun to the
genitals always brings me
to my happy place.
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
He's never gonna hurt you again.
You understand that?
Never again.
This is right?
You are police?
Yes, yes, we can protect you.
[SCREAMING]
Relax, relax! Easy.
I will help.
Good.
Now you ask him why they hired
the Nigerians to kill those cops?
[IRINA SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[TRETIAK SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
Jesus. We're gonna
need a different plan.
Our victim just got out of Chino
two weeks ago. It's his third run.
He was a high school
phys. ed. teacher.
Coached baseball.
His latest stretch was for nearly
beating his shortstop to death.
It is America's
favourite past time.
Don't let them know it's eating you,
they'll never lay off.
Two cops are dead.
You'd think harassing me
about dating Vic's wife
wouldn't be a priority.
Well, you're the distraction
keeping them from thinking
about dead cops.
Forget about it.
DUTCH:
You were tired of the life.
Constant beatings,
embarrassment. Ridicule.
He got out of Chino, came home,
just couldn't take it anymore.
CLAUDETTE: Sold your car
last week for $8700.
Maybe you hired someone
to stop Gill from hurting you?
The cash was for fake ID,
forged reference letters.
He knew no school was gonna
hire him with his record.
Is that why he was in that
part of town? Getting a fake ID?
HEIDl:
Could have been.
You didn't go with him?
No, I was at my 6:30 AA meeting.
CLAUDETTE: Is there anyone else
who knew he had the money?
That he was
getting a fake ID?
What, dear?
I've been sharing about it
in my morning meeting.
One of the newcomers,
guy in a wheelchair, Bumper.
He caught me in the parking lot
after a meeting.
Told me he knew someone
could help get Gill the IDs.
[TRETIAK GRUNTING]
Relax.
Make that look real. These guys
know how shit that works.
Don't worry, Olga.
We're just gonna scare the
borscht out of your buddy.
Get him a little chatty.
What's the Russian
for "all wired up"?
Let's go.
You tell him he's got 30 seconds to
tell us why they hired the Nigerians.
And who else was involved
in killing our cops.
Or we blow his boss
to red heaven. And then him.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[OSIP SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Tell him to relax
or he's gonna flip that goddamn chair.
[SHOUTS IN RUSSIAN]
SHANE:
Hey, hey, hey. Vic...
Jesus Christ. You okay?
[OSIP SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
SHANE:
Shut up. Shut up.
LEM: Jesus.
Holy shit.
LEM:
Man, that was loud, brother.
What the hell are we gonna do?
LEM: Holy shit.
Oh, my God.
All right.
Get our shit, grab the Russians.
Let's get out of here.
Go!
Move!
LEM: Let's get out of here.
Go, go, go!
Come on, let's go.
[OSIP SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
That's far enough.
He says he doesn't know why.
Tretiak just told him to hire
Nigerians to kill police.
The black cop gave
Tretiak a ticket.
Is that why he killed him
and his partner?
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
He doesn't think so.
Said he was crazy, not stupid.
Shit! Apparently, the only
person who knew anything
just blew himself up.
He says there was a young
black with the Nigerians, driving.
A third black guy, three?
He says he saw him once before.
He brought language tapes to Tretiak.
Get her keys
to the restaurant.
Go get those tapes.
Yeah.
You have someplace safe
you can go?
ACEVEDA:
Nina, we're gonna grab
some coffee at Ivid's.
Be back in a few.
This subpoena was just delivered.
ACEVEDA:
All right.
What is it?
It's nothing. Judge wants me
to sign some affidavits.
I always get these.
You ready, mamas?
[DOOR BUZZES]
Glad you could
find time to visit.
Thought you were up
in Terminal Island.
I'm in county this week.
Waiting for the judge
to consider my appeal.
Appeal, on what grounds?
Innocence.
I didn't rob that market.
Three witnesses
including myself saw you.
Well, Ricky, he went in for food.
Next thing I know, I hear gunshots.
Ran in to see what happened,
you pointed a finger at me.
So your lawyer'll actually think that
a judge will buy that bullshit story?
Oh, that's not
gonna happen.
They're gonna drop the charges
when you take the stand
and admit that you
forced my confession.
Otherwise, I'm just gonna
tell the whole courtroom
what went down with us.
I ain't got nothing to lose.
No one's gonna believe you.
Well, I got the picture
to prove it.
Oh, you know, on your knees.
My dick in your mouth.
Shut up, shut up.
You forget the 50 ways
that I can screw you
and your loved ones to death
if you open your mouth?
My grandma,
she died last month.
Had that throat cancer.
My mom, she got tired
of wiping rich kids' ass
and moved back to Mexico.
You don't have a picture.
And neither does your girlfriend.
Oh, believe what you want.
Believe what you want.
But you will get on that stand,
and say you violated my rights.
Or you'll pull some strings
and get me out of here, power man.
Show me what
you could do.
Show it to me.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Found Tretiak.
Damn.
Must have mishandled
his merchandise.
Our best lead to these
cop killers just got blown to hell.
Well, if he was involved,
smells like justice to me.
We'll go through the restaurant,
see if it gives us anything.
We traced some books on tape
in Tretiak's office
to the UC Northridge
language library.
Checked out by a Jason Porter. J.P.
Ring a bell?
Yeah, Dutch found a J.P.
necklace in the sewer, next
to Carl and Scooby's bodies.
SHANE:
This kid's a foreign-language major.
Spanish, Korean, Russian.
Clean record, got his dad's address.
Department head says he's been MIA
from classes for the last two weeks.
Since Carl and Scooby
were killed.
[KNOCKING]
We're looking for Jason Porter.
So am I. Haven't seen
my boy in two weeks.
Come on in.
Look around if you like.
Do you have any idea
where he might be?
Oh, he's an adult. Road trips
to Northern California all the time.
College buddies.
Why you looking for him?
He may know a couple of Nigerians
involved in a shooting.
We need to talk to him.
No, doesn't sound like
Jason's friends.
LEM:
Oh, shit. Hey, check this out.
That's Jason.
This guy always show up
at your picnics?
Antwon Mitchell.
Jason's half-brother.
You're not Antwon's
biological father.
No. Jason and Antwon
share the same mother.
Antwon and I
are no relation.
You were a correctional officer
at Chowchilla, weren't you?
Yeah.
Knocked up Antwon's
incarcerated mother.
Cost you your job.
Got into security work
and raised Jason on my own.
If you know where your son is,
you need to tell us.
Places he goes? His friends?
Guess I didn't ask
enough questions
about where he goes
and who he hangs out with.
I'm sorry about that.
DUTCH: I cross-referenced
Bumper with DUIs.
Francis Valverde, a.k.a. Bumper.
Various gang stuff.
Took a bullet in a drive-by two years
ago, left him wheelchair-bound.
He's been clean ever since.
Paula and Carlos
are scooping him up now.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Well, if the pad fits...
Yeah, I packed the napkins.
Forgot the sandwich.
Hey. Hey, hey.
You find out who's pulling this shit?
No, not yet.
Did you ask around?
Look, I've been working an
assault that's got me spinning.
But I'm on to it.
I promise, okay?
RAWLING:
Think this kid's capable
of murdering two cops?
Antwon's blood.
Wouldn't surprise me.
He could be hiding anywhere.
How do we find him?
I got a C.I., works a pawn shop.
He can put the word out on the street
that PD never found the necklace.
That it's just sitting there
at his shop.
That's an expensive piece of ice.
I'm hoping that greed wins out
over smarts and he comes to claim it.
TAYLOR: Listen, man,
I'm the BNOC, brother, okay?
I spread the word
from Crenshaw to Northridge.
If he's in town, he got the memo.
The video recorders are all on.
Just step on this power strip,
they'll all kick in.
You can't just sell him the
necklace. You gotta make
him prove that it's his.
No, no, no. I'm well versed
in the conversational arts.
Good. Here's for
your education.
There's another hundred
if you don't screw it up.
I call the police, I don't
know exactly, six or seven
times a month.
I've stopped keeping track.
Harassment can be hard to prove.
Random, unpredictable.
It's as if they think it's my fault,
or it's all in my head.
The phone calls, the rotten eggs
on my car, the bleach on my lawn.
Tell me about the call today.
It was from a man
who has called before,
who says I deserve to suffer
the way Will's victims suffered.
Said he was gonna rape you?
Kill you, used those words?
He said he watched me come home.
He knew what I was wearing.
The police are not
gonna protect me.
I thought you could help me
get a carry permit.
For a gun?
Do you have one?
What choice did I have?
Listen, most of the time,
threats are just threats.
Somebody trying to feel powerful
by making you afraid.
Well, it's working.
Hey, Dutch, we have Joanna Faulks'
phone records from the last month.
It's a pretty short list.
Thanks.
She received like 15 calls.
Eleven were from telemarketers.
So much for the
friends-and-family plan.
Aside from the 911,
the numbers she dialled mostly
were pizza and Chinese places.
Shit.
She left me a message
a couple months ago.
It's been a pretty rough time
around here for all of us.
Yeah.
Check the names of the callers
against a list of the Cuddler's victims.
See if there's a connection.
Okay.
SHANE:
That's him, buddy.
[PHONE RINGS]
Horus' Trade.
VIC: Yo, that's him.
LEM:
Come on, man, let me check it out.
TAYLOR:
Yeah, okay. Will do, bye.
What's going on, brother?
How you living?
Heard you got your hands
on a necklace.
Initials J.P.
Yeah, yeah.
No, you know, I keep it
locked up, you know.
It's a real fine
dog tag here, man.
Check it out.
How much?
You know what,
I'm in a charitable mood today.
I'll give it to you
on the cheap, 15 grand.
You smoking crack, brother?
Nigga, that is platinum, okay?
With half carats all around.
Necklace is worth 10 G's.
So, what you do,
you the bling king now?
I know how much it's
worth because I'm J.P.
It's mine.
My brother gave it to me.
Listen, a homeless dude
came in here.
He told me
that he found it in the gutter.
That's where I lost it.
My brother's Antwon Mitchell.
You really want that kind of trouble?
VIC:
Go, go, go.
No, I don't.
Listen, I have heard
of Antwon, okay?
All I'm saying...
VIC: Freeze, police!
[ALL SHOUTING]
SHANE:
Turn around, right now! Shut up!
VIC:
Shut up!
TAYLOR:
I have receipts for everything.
What happened?
She came home, found
the back door unlocked.
Reported a break-in.
You know where you leave
things. Someone was in here.
Maybe it's possible that you left
the back door unlocked yourself?
Why, with everything
that's happening to me,
would I leave
the door unlocked?
You can go, officers, thank you.
Sure thing, detective.
The carry permit.
I'd still like to get that.
Honestly,
I don't think it's a good idea.
Listen, I owe you
an apology.
You left a message,
I meant to call you back.
When Will was arrested,
I was angry. At him, and you.
Nothing made sense.
I called because I thought
perhaps I could cook you dinner.
By way of apologizing.
Oh. Ah...
That's not necessary.
But thanks.
Listen, I really have to get back.
Murder case.
I'll keep the unis coming by,
checking on you.
You're gonna be fine.
Remember me, Mr. Mayor?
Juan's girlfriend?
The one you kidnapped.
Juan says you think we're bluffing,
that we don't have the picture.
I'm sorry, I don't
know who you are.
You can't put hands on...
What's this?
ACEVEDA [ON TAPE]:
- don't know who you are.
If you really had a picture,
you wouldn't need me on this
admitting one exists.
You'll see it when
Juan shows it in the court.
Or maybe we can
mail it to the Times.
Look, I might be able to do
something, but it takes time.
So you need to convince
your boyfriend to be patient.
No way, he's only in county this week,
and he's not going back to TI.
You know what Juan did to you.
And soon everyone will know
unless you get him out of there.
SOPHIA: Chimney.
Chimney.
AURORA:
Now let's make one for Daddy, okay?
SOPHIA:
That's a flower without petals.
[AURORA LAUGHS
AND KISSES]
SOPHIA: Let's have a Christmas tree.
AURORA: Okay.
I gotta go finish
some things up.
It's Antwon Mitchell's half-brother?
How did you miss the connection?
RAWLING:
This kid's on the dean's list.
No record, no gang ties.
Doesn't seem like the type
to go 187. Why are you here?
Heard you got a break
on our cop killings.
Jason might be
our Antwon connection.
Which means the murders
are seizure-related.
We don't know what it means yet.
RAWLING:
Nice ice. You should have
seen it when we found it.
Covered in the blood
of two dead cops.
I lost it on my way home
from school.
Before or after
the dog ate your homework?
That's the truth.
We know you were with
the Nigerians when they
killed our guys.
We also know
you have a bright future.
No way you'd be stupid enough
to do something like this
without your brother
Antwon telling you to.
Barely know Antwon.
These are cheques for your
tuition at UC Northridge.
That's Antwon's signature.
So he pays some bills,
doesn't mean it's a love fest.
VIC:
Antwon paid for your college.
You killing two cops sounds lik e
the love being paid back in full.
Antwon didn't have
anything to do with that.
He's a leader. A visionary.
His incarceration's a crime
against this community and
all people of colour.
VIC:
Let's stick to your crimes.
You're an accomplice
to the murders of two cops.
We have a Nigerian in custody
who's anxious to make a deal.
And your bling
at the crime scene.
Covering up for Antwon
is gonna do you no good.
And if this is about you
cozying up with him at Lompoc.
Ain't gonna happen.
I met one of the Russians
at school.
They knew who I was,
thought I might be willing to help.
I arranged the deal
with the Nigerians.
That night, I helped
communicate the plan.
I did it to prove to Antwon
that I can play in his league.
He didn't know anything about it.
So it sounds like
Antwon's clean on this one.
You really think
the Fresh Prince in there
brokered a high-powered
deal between the Russians
and the Nigerians?
He admitted to his
part in the murders.
Antwon's already in jail.
Sometimes you have to take
"I did it" for an answer.
It's bullshit.
This kid is Antwon's tool.
You know it.
Look, I know pinning
this on Antwon
puts these murders
on the seizures.
That's a bad thing
for us, I understand.
I just want to find out the
whole truth, wherever it leads.
[GRUNTING]
DUTCH: Whoa!
BUMPER: Aah!
CLAUDETTE: Jesus.
DUTCH: Sorry, sorry.
Shithead!
Come on, get him up.
Let's get him up, I got it.
Okay, we're okay.
We're okay now.
DUTCH: Tell us about Nokey.
Nokey.
This ID guy I used to roll with.
All puns intended.
Did good work.
I gave Gill his number.
Anything in it for you?
Commissions, kickbacks?
Just a chance to be of service.
You happen to have
Nokey's number handy?
Sorry. I lost it.
We'll get it from Gill's house.
We'll be back.
I'm not going anywhere.
Visitor this late at night?
Must be important.
I've got some friends in Justice
who might be interested in you.
Lot of people
interested in me.
These friends can offer you
witness protection.
You're monitored, but you're free.
I ain't a rat.
You got loyalties
to the Salvadorans?
The DEA can't make their case,
and they're looking for
any help they can get.
Well, if the feds want my love,
why the hell am I talking to you?
They know the havoc
you left in Farmington.
They won't push this through
without some local cover.
And that's me.
Now, I can go tell Justice
you're interested...
If what?
If you're willing to give some
serious intel on the Salvadorans.
Now, you gotta give
them the names at the top.
Names that matter.
All the locals in charge.
People in Central America
that they answer to.
That's a tall order, man.
Well, that's the only way this works.
And I assume there's some sort
of broker's fee for you.
No. Nothing for me.
Call Justice.
Tell them I'm interested.
I will.
In the meantime, there's
an inmate here in county.
Name's Juan Lozano.
He's due to testify
this week.
Could upset a case
that the DEA's working on.
This could be your chance to show
that you're a team player.
Convince Juan
to miss his court date.
I'll see what I can do.
I'll call Justice.
You do that.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Two, three, seven, got it, thanks.
I'll get back to you.
[ALL LAUGHING]
CLAUDETTE:
You okay?
They're bringing in Nokey.
Let's talk to him.
Dutch. Come on.
We found Nokey.
I don't think he likes you anymore.
He confessed.
To making the fake IDs.
He said Gill was supposed
to come by, pick them up,
pay off the $6500 balance.
Claims he didn't murder him, though.
DUTCH: We believe him.
Blowing off a guy's nads
and stealing his money.
That's just bad business.
You knew Gill had the cash.
You took him down a quiet alley,
put two rounds of buckshot
in his privates.
In that chair, you'd have been
face to balls with the guy.
CLAUDETTE:
And then rolled away with the cash.
That's pretty ambitious
for a cripple.
You mean a person
with a disability?
I'm a goddamned cripple.
I own that.
You also own
a brand-new handicap ramp.
Contractor just emailed me
the work order, $6000.
You paid cash.
This afternoon.
I test those wheels, I'm gonna find
shotgun residue and Gill's blood.
I should probably get a lawyer.
I didn't threaten to rape anyone.
I have a wife and two kids.
How do you explain
the calls
made from your house
to Joanna Faulks'?
Maybe one of my kids
dialled the wrong umber.
Her husband was convicted
of raping and killing several
women last year.
Your mother lives two doors down
from one of the victims, Dory Smythe.
Police interviewed her
at the time of the crime...
My mom's still scared
shitless because of it.
What does that
have to do with me?
DANNY: Okay, this asshole did it,
but he's just not gonna confess.
He's actually trying
to pawn it off on his sons.
Take the recording over
to Joanna's house in the morning.
See if she can ID the voice.
All right, sure.
DUTCH:
I cover your ass last week.
I ask you for a simple favour.
Not only do you not
help me out, you pile on.
You gotta unwind
a little bit, Dutch.
All I see is you laughing
right along with everybody else.
Maybe I ought to set an
example, starting with you.
BILLINGS:
You don't wanna get into this.
It's not so funny now?
What are you gonna do?
Turn off the hose and hide?
Hey.
LEM: Check it out, Billings and Dutch.
SHANE:
Cat fight.
[ALL SHOUTING AND CHEERING]
I got 20 on the geek.
That's even money.
LEM: Get him around,
get him around, baby.
MAN 1: Come on.
MAN 2: Stay away from the hair.
Stop pulling hair.
SHANE: Come on.
Kick his ass, brother.
MAN 3: Billings, he's getting at the tie.
MAN 4: He's getting it.
How many slapfests
do I have to break up today?
Goddamn it!
Come on, let's just finish this.
Come on, asshole!
Let's go. Yeah, you, Vic.
Come on, you too.
You want to keep riding me?
You wanna mess with my chair?
Let's finish this, let's just do it...
Two of our own are dead!
Rise and shine. You have to
give us another name.
Apparently, Antwon's lawyer
thinks helping you
is a conflict of interests.
I don't understand.
Means your big brother doesn't
give a shit about where you end up.
Which makes me wonder why
you're trying so hard to protect him.
Antwon is just looking out for me.
Then why'd he make
such a big show
about that custom necklace
he got for you?
Couple of his boys
picked it up in a robbery.
The original owner has confirmed
that it was stolen.
Antwon's always got my back.
Ever since I was a shorty.
Helps with groceries.
Covers the mortgage
when my dad's out of work.
You're all just trying to screw
with me because I'm tired.
Get me to say something stupid.
I'm sure Antwon's briefed
you about the Farmington
asset-forfeiture policy.
Him being a known drug dealer,
that statement means
we can get a warrant.
Look into your father's finances.
The statement before the one
about you saying something stupid.
The mortgage payments
made with drug proceeds.
We can take your father's house.
Or you can tell the truth.
Keep your daddy
from moving into a shelter.
Nobody touches
my dad's house.
I don't want to go
someplace far away.
We can connect you
to the murder of two cops.
You go wherever
we say you go.
Or I can talk to the DA,
get the death penalty off the table.
Make sure they put you
into protective custody.
You stay alive.
Dad still enjoys retirement
rocking on the front porch.
I need to see the deal
on paper.
Then I'll tell you
how it went down.
This is all your stuff.
Thanks.
Can we just...?
For a minute?
The kids are getting
ready for school.
And I don't want them
to see your face like that.
Listen, when I said before
this started because of Vic...
That's not the only reason.
It's the only one that matters.
See, no. It isn't.
Because there's
something here.
I know you want to
believe that now.
But Vic got under your skin,
and I was a way to get back at him.
Maybe he's still
under your skin.
Maybe you even thought
you could get back at him a little.
Show him
you've moved on.
Men have time for pissing
contests. Mothers don't.
You want me to forgive you?
You're forgiven.
Listen, I didn't
tell you about Vic,
because I was afraid
you wouldn't go out with me.
Then I was afraid to tell you
because things were going so well.
Being afraid ruined it.
Yeah, it did.
Well, I'm not afraid anymore.
So at some point,
look past my bad start,
give me another chance.
Let me know.
Antwon saw the coming tide.
Black and white's days
are numbered.
It's all about making peace
with the red, yellow and brown.
He paid for your education,
made sure someone in his
organization
could speak the languages
so he wouldn't be left behind.
RAWLING:
Goodwill ambassador.
Only instead of brokering
peace, you broker drug deals,
gang alliances.
How did Antwon get the Russians
and Nigerians together?
The Russians had a beef with PD.
Because we took down Kozodav?
Antwon was plugged into that.
He offered Tretiak the Nigerians
as hired help.
Why were Officers Haimes
and Miller targeted?
Tretiak's idea.
The black cop pissed him off.
Gave him a speeding ticket.
And you?
I translated. Drove.
Made sure the Nigerians had what
they needed to get the job done.
Antwon's emissary.
J ASON: Russians have
an international pipeline.
Need them in your corner
if you wanna play outside the States.
Killing the cops
was a handshake.
Antwon knew if they did this,
they'd be tied.
There'd be trust.
An oath in blood.
Police.
Mrs. Faulks?
JULIEN:
I hear a TV.
[MAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
Shit. She said the intruder
came through the back the last time.
Mrs. Faulks, police.
You in there?
[GUNSHOT]
Ow! Damn it, shit!
One-Tango-13. Shots fired.
Officer down.
Oh, God.
Let me see your hands.
Put that gun down,
put the gun down!
Drop it!
JOANNA: I thought you were...
Put it down!
I didn't know, I'm so sorry.
Put your hands on your head!
I heard them outside, I thought you...
DANNY: Oh, God.
Step down, move, now!
I'm so sorry.
PHILLIPS:
Give us a minute. Now!
DEA just requested all
departmental files on
Antwon Mitchell.
Shit, are they thinking
of making a deal?
Witness protection, immunity.
I hear it's done.
What? We've got to get it
off the table. We just linked
him to the two cop murders.
How?
His half-brother gave him up.
Antwon's gonna walk.
You and your boy really did it.
Me?
And Aceveda.
I know all about the dance
you two are planning for
the Pol Com session.
You help him navigate
this Mitchell deal?
What the hell
are you talking about?
Aceveda brokered the deal
between Mitchell and DEA?
A woman like you? Figured
you'd get to know your bedmates
before you lay down with them.
Shit.
RAWLING: The deal is off.
J ASON: What?
Big brother struck a better one,
which leaves you shit out of luck.
You can't do that.
You're gonna take a lethal injection
for the killing
of two cops.
And I'm gonna
be there to watch.
Put him back in the cage.
What the hell happened?
Aceveda shit all over us.
Brokered Antwon to the DEA.
Witness protection.
They're letting him go?
Excuse me, the councilman's...
ACEVEDA: It's all right.
Where the hell do you get off
cutting a deal for Antwon Mitchell?
Hey, it's the DEA's deal.
They asked me to approach him.
Antwon ordered the hit on our cops.
His half-brother just gave him up.
You just set a cop killer free,
you dick.
The kid said
he acted alone.
That family has a little bit
of trouble with the truth.
VIC:
He lied.
Call the deal off.
I can't.
It's in DEA's hands now.
Carl and Scooby were
stabbed over and over again.
Probably alive long enough
to feel most of it.
ACEVEDA: I was there when
the bodies were carried out.
I'm the one who found them.
I'm still a cop.
Bullshit. Cops want only one thing,
Antwon executed for what he did.
Look, the DEA cannot make a case
against the Salvadoran cartel.
Mitchell is willing to
give up the entire pipeline.
All right, this is huge.
You and your council buddies
get a few favours from Sacramento.
Do you think I care about a DEA win?
Carl and Scooby were my men.
You're the one who came
crawling to me, asking for a lifeline.
And I was an asshole to think
you were an option.
Watch it, you still need me.
I need shit from you.
You can take
your backroom handshakes,
your DEA cronies and your
self-serving cop-killer deals
and you can shove
them up your ass.
You're not a cop.
You never were.
[###]