SMITTY:
Now, I need you to tell the truth.
Absolutely.
SMITTY:
Is your name Shane Vendrell?
Yes.
SMITTY:
Are you currently the mayor
of New York City?
SHANE:
No.
Have you ever lied
to keep yourself out of trouble?
SHANE:
Yes.
SMITTY:
Have you ever won the gold medal
in women's gymnastics?
No.
SMITTY: Are you married?
SHANE:
Yeah.
SMITTY: Do you have children?
SHANE: Yes.
SMITTY:
Have you ever been unfaithful
to your wife?
SHANE:
No.
Eating ain't cheating.
I've been fielding calls all day
by people very angry that we
put away Antwon Mitchell.
He confessed to murdering
a teenage girl.
Mitchell's always claimed
we were targeting him. Now
he's screaming Vendrell's dirty.
People think
we're trying to cover our ass.
That's bullshit.
I know.
I just need you
to explain it to them.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
I'd be a little nervous.
VIC: Yeah.
ARMANDO:
So how we supposed
to beat this thing?
Well, it's easier if you're
a pathological liar or a narcissist.
All right, so Shane's safe.
What do we do about Army?
I heard something about
putting a tack in your shoe
messes up the results.
VIC: Yeah, along with your foot.
SMITTY: Tack in your shoe.
Bar of soap under the armpit.
No proof they work.
Plus, if they catch you,
they know you're lying.
Come on, Smitty, what do we do?
All right, you be the interrogator.
Ask me about
some crime you think I did.
You like little Asian boys?
Let's say I did.
I do what they call a substitution.
I replace your question in my mind
with another question
to which the truthful answer
is no.
I might ask myself,
do I have $10 million in the bank?
I answer no.
The polygraph records
the response as truthful.
That really works?
You do it right, yeah.
Oh.
VIC: Got no choice.
Captain's got a spotlight
on all of us until you two
pass that lie detector test.
We got a few days to practice.
We can do it.
RAWLING:
The officer Mitchell
propositioned was undercover.
We heard he was corrupt.
That's Mitchell's allegation.
We're investigating.
WOMAN:
I was at your first town meeting.
RAWLING:
Yes, I remember.
WOMAN:
That councilman said these seizures
breed police corruption.
I have the officers involved
taking a polygraph test.
I will be happy
to make those results public.
We also hear you're trying to blame
Antwon for those dead police.
RAWLING:
We're investigating all leads.
Investigate yourself.
Taking people's houses
is what got those cops killed.
Now you're trying to hide it.
How much longer you gonna
let these seizures go on?
RAWLING:
We don't know
what got those officers killed.
But attacking the seizure policy
isn't gonna help us find it.
We're re-evaluating
the seizures entirely.
This department is not
interested in any policy
that inflames the community
or leads to cops' deaths.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
OFFICER:
Here. The files
you were looking for.
Nailing Antwon's
really shaken things up.
What's the fallout on the street?
Well, naturally, decapitating
the One-Niners has created
a power vacuum.
Now a few of his sloppy seconds
wanna try on the crown.
So how do we take advantage?
Hit them up for info on our two
dead cops before the dust settles.
Or at least until Antwon
sets up shop in prison and
circles the wagons again.
You think Antwon's lying,
One-Niners are responsible?
Don't you?
Hit them hard.
Fine.
But I need Shane and Army.
Not until they clear the polygraph.
That's not until next week.
I need guys now.
Just let them work on who killed
Carl and Scooby. Nothing else.
They only work the cops' murders.
Anything goes sideways
with them, it is on you.
Got it.
[###]
SHANE: Looks like Antwon Mitchell
isn't the only One-Niner on his
lawyer's buddy list.
I knew that shylock was dirty.
Officer of the court running
errands for Antwon Mitchell?
Gives us a good card
to play with Halpern.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
Lighting up.
No, no. No, you're not.
I finally got something nice where
the A.C. actually works. Toss it.
I'll blow the smoke out the window.
Or you can blow me.
I want this to smell like rich
Corinthian leather, not an ashtray.
Come on.
[CHUCKLES]
I heard what happened this morning.
Phillips threw you to the wolves.
Yeah, he hauled me in front
of Antwon's true believers
and promised them that
he'd re-evaluate the seizure policy.
It's a real shame you weren't there
to witness your handiwork.
He's linking it to Carl and Scooby
getting killed. Is it?
[SIGHS]
We don't know.
If you can prove the killings
had nothing to do with the seizures...
However it breaks, it breaks.
I'm not suggesting slanting evidence.
I'm offering you an olive branch.
High enough to hang myself from?
I don't like people capitalizing
on cop killings.
I'm willing to talk to the chief on your
behalf, on behalf of the seizures.
lf?
If you agree to a few modifications.
Such as no auctioning properties until
the suspects are actually convicted.
That leaves money in
escrow accounts for years,
instead of in the community
where we need it.
It's an olive branch.
Thanks for your offer.
I think I can take
care of Phillips.
HALPERN: And listen, anybody
gives you shit, you come find me.
Get on the horn and you call me.
VIC: Go get your nails done.
We need some quality time
with big poppa. Screw.
What? You already got Antwon
sitting down.
That deal we were discussing
prior to your accident,
it's back on the table.
What is it with you guys? I look like
I got a pork chop around my neck?
Antwon's lawyer just went
straight from the men's Jail
to a meet and greet
with a cat named Weed.
You know him?
Yeah.
ARMANDO:
I thought you
were next in line.
White smoke coming out
of Antwon's cell, man.
Means he's anointing Weed
as his new pope of dope.
We're trying to figure out
whose side we're on.
You fools still playing
that dirty cop shit?
Hey, shithead, we don't wanna
get into business with you.
We're looking for the guys
who killed our cops.
I already gave you the El Salvadorans.
No one specific.
And all we got to was that
street-level asshole, Pitarrio.
You're out of ICU.
You're reconnected to the street.
You must've heard
something new.
VIC:
This guy's not a player.
Let's go talk to Weed.
HALPERN:
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
When Antwon got
with the Salvadorans,
he only talked to one guy.
Cat named Gusano.
Where do I find this maggot Gusano?
He deals to Pitarrio.
Now, how you gonna
handle Weed for me, huh?
You're looking at a bunch
of bona fide weedwackers.
SHANE:
Hey, Weed.
You wanna hang up
the phone there, superstar?
VIC: Grab some skull, dickhead.
You know, it's funny, man.
I see your mouth moving,
but I don't hear you saying nothing.
Yeah? Can you hear me now?
Any of you guys smell
the sickening-sweet
odour of ganja?
Oh.
Yeah, all right.
Come on, man,
it's the 21 st century.
That old school trickery,
it ain't gonna fly in these last days.
You'll be locked up a week
before the judge drops the charges.
Antwon's gone, man.
One-Niners
are deciding who's got next.
Can you really afford
to be benched for that long?
SHANE:
Especially with Halpern
on the campaign trail.
Look, check this out.
Quit beating me in my
head conversation.
What do y'all want?
You give us something
that gets us our cop killers,
I guarantee you
Halpern goes down in the polls.
WEED:
All right. Word on the street,
some kids' running their mouth,
talking about some
dead cop's gun.
Where'd you hear that shit?
Nigger named Jamani.
He stay down on Grape Street.
He run guns, you know,
to the street struggle.
So Halpern really wants
to squabble, huh?
You got my back, right?
Hey, this tip pans out,
the street will be kissing
your ring before you know it.
[###]
I'm going to Giovanni's.
You want lunch?
Chicken parm. You need cash?
No, get me later.
What about him?
Dutch hates Giovanni's.
I'll pick up some wine on the way.
CORRINE [ON PHONE]: I can do it.
You've got such a long day.
I don't mind. Chardonnay, right?
CORRINE: My fav ourite.
DUTCH: I know what you lik e.
Uh, I gotta go. I'Il...
I'll see you tonight.
See you then.
Bye.
Captain?
Where are you on Scooby and Carl?
We've talked to the neighbours twice.
We've papered the town with fliers.
Latest crime scene reports
haven't turned up anything new.
I want you back
in regular rotation.
You're taking us
off the cop killers?
RAWLING:
You still can provide support.
But I can't let this
trail get any colder.
This case will break. May take
six months, it may take six hours,
you know that.
Six months is
good enough for you?
Every spare moment you have,
work on Scooby and Carl.
But I've got Vic looking into it,
so bring him up to speed.
[###]
[MEN SHOUTING
IN SPANISH]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TYRES SCREECHING]
Oh, shit.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I was on my way home from work.
Oh.
And I really need
to tell you something.
Everything all right?
Yeah.
Actually, I've been
seeing someone.
Well, I've seen a few people
since the separation. We're allowed.
You kind of work
with this person.
Who?
Dutch.
You're kidding me.
No.
How the hell did that happen?
It just did.
You just said dating was allowed.
It is.
Just know that this guy's
a first-rate asshole.
No, he's not.
We're always riding this prick.
He's got a bug up
his ass about me.
He just wants to get
back at me through you.
That's ridiculous.
I'm just telling you the truth.
You do whatever you want with it.
I'm not gonna do anything with it.
Fine.
You didn't tell him
about the money
I gave you, did you?
No, of course not. I didn't tell anyone.
Good. Don't.
I gotta go.
Wait a minute.
You're not gonna do
anything, are you?
What would I do?
Please, don't get in the middle
of this. Forget I said anything.
Fine. Kiss the kids, will you?
Okay, bye.
Got an address on Weed's tip.
The guy who was bragging
about the cop gun.
All right, go pick him up. We'll try to
find Gusano, trace it back to Antwon.
RONNIE:
Not your most ingenious prank.
VIC:
Yeah, but it felt good.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Police.
Pitarrio, get out here!
Pitarrio.
WOMAN: I have a gun, I'll shoot.
We're the police.
WOMAN: Bullshit. I know who you are.
We're coming in.
We'll shoot.
WOMAN: Me too.
Stop.
VIC: Where's Pitarrio?
Gone.
Where to?
He lost something he was holding.
He knew the Salvadorans
would come to kill him.
VIC:
What did he lose?
Heroin, a kilo.
Shit.
Where'd he lose this kilo?
Look, we're not
here to bust you.
[SIGHS]
I'm Pitarrio's cut-up girl.
The Salvadorans can't find him,
they'll come after me next.
I thought you were them.
Then why'd you
come back here?
Thought maybe I could grab
some product, or some tools to sell...
Pitarrio left without paying me.
I got nothing for us.
Who's got you and Pitarrio
so scared?
[CRIES]
Dealer named Gusano.
You know where
we could find him?
LEM:
Hey, hey. Come here.
[WHISPERING]
She was here when I roughed Pitarrio
up and took that heroin as collateral.
So if she's running,
it's because of me.
She see you take it?
I don't know.
Come on, let's just get out of here.
And leave her hanging? No way.
SHANE:
What do we do with them?
Pack a bag.
Pack a bag, let's go.
What exactly...?
What exactly did you tell him?
I told him
that we were seeing each other.
Yeah, how'd he take it?
CORRINE:
He said that you two weren't exactly
the strangers you said you were.
Well, we've... We've bumped
heads over a case or two.
But you know Vic.
We need to talk about this.
DUTCH:
Listen, I hate to do this to you.
But I'm looking at a dead body
right now. I've got to go.
Okay, I'll still see you at 8?
Sure. If this case wraps up, sure.
Okay.
CLAUDETTE:
Louis Saldera, 21.
Took four shots at close range.
Do we know the car yet?
Saldera's registered owner
of a 2003 Honda.
Still wet. Maybe there's a witness.
Somebody was here recently.
You're not gonna wash your car
with a body right next door.
Yeah, don't be so sure.
I'll post a squad car out front.
But trust me,
no one's gonna find you.
Gusano thinks I know where
Pitarrio is, or that I have the heroin.
Last woman he thought
crossed him?
His man held her down, stuck a rat
in her pussy till she bled to death.
VIC:
That's a street fairy tale
cholos have been spinning for years.
Well, something happens to me
make sure
somebody takes care of my boy.
Nothing's happening.
You let me take care of Gusano.
After that, things can change.
I'm out of a job.
Can't exactly collect unemployment.
And H-cutter don't look good
on no résumé.
You could clean up your act.
[SCOFFS]
Start fresh.
I don't see where
you have much of a choice.
I'm helping you this time.
Next time, I'll be arresting you.
Besides, how old is this kid?
What, 2, 3?
Four.
He seems small.
We take care of ourselves.
RONNIE: But the good
news is, this gun guy,
Jamani, works alone.
LEM:
Come on, dude,
put that shit out.
This is my car.
Okay, this guy deals in filed-down
guns and sawed-off shotguns.
Gotta be careful.
We'll try not to get your hair
messed up.
[CHUCKLING]
I can't go through
with this lie detector.
SHANE:
That's just jitters. We'll get you back
to Smitty's, get you strapped in.
Hey, we got three
days to practice.
I mean, we're gonna beat
this thing based off the tips
of a goddamned locksmith?
Smitty was Army intelligence
for 12 years before he got into keys.
Dude, I was in the service.
A.I. means he was carrying
extra batteries for the field radio.
Look, man, Vic put his
ass on the line for us.
So did these guys.
We just need to be calm
and concentrate.
Answer these questions
that we ask ourselves.
We're gonna get through this.
Bro, l...
Don't "bro" me.
Now, this is a team.
And it all comes down
to us delivering.
We're not gonna let
these guys down.
Let's go find this asshole
and see what he knows.
We hear you fix guns
for Grape Street, Jamani.
RAWLING:
Anyone approach you
with a slain officer's gun?
Looks like you got
some bad information.
We found three silencers
and a stash of unregistered
handguns in your crib.
Unless you wanna hone
your legal skills in Soledad,
better tell us about the gun
you heard about.
African cat stepped to me with it.
Told me he needed
the numbers filed off.
What kind of piece?
It was a Beretta 92F.
J AMANl:
I told Kunta Kinte he could take
that business somewhere else.
He came in acting all arrogant,
high and mighty and shit.
Dude called me a nigger,
like G-E-R.
RAWLING: What's his name?
I don't know.
We'll need you to look
at some mug books.
No. Later for that. l...
I didn't even get a good look at him.
Hey, man, this guy's
great, great, great grandpappy
sold one of your ancestors
to the man.
You really wanna let him get away
with acting like he's better than you?
TRACY:
I heard something loud.
Came over to the window
to see what it was.
What'd you see?
No one's gonna know your name.
I only saw one car.
It was dark blue and old.
This was about a minute
after the shots.
1990's? '80's?
I'm really not good with cars.
Older, I think. Like a classic.
We're just back from the car wash.
Victim was a Latino.
Killed during a carjacking.
DUTCH: Girl heard the shots.
She didn't see the killer,
but saw a witness.
The shooter had Los Mag
gang tats, drove the stolen car.
Two other Latino males
followed him in a black BMW.
Sounds like your witness
called in. Wouldn't give a name,
but he caught a lot of detail.
911 get his number?
No, called the switchboard.
He knew how to keep
his name and voice out of it.
LEM:
Hey, man, what you got?
Unis papered the neighbourhood for
the Nigerian named Ade Achebe.
Lives here. He was trying
to clean a cop's gun.
From the make, it looks like Carl's.
LEM: Any connection to the Niners?
Haven't seen one. But he's
on a Homeland Security watch list.
So is every African that's entered
the country since 9l11.
What's the big deal?
You can fit them
all in a phone booth.
[WHISPERS]
Ronnie, Army, take the back.
LEM: Hey, man, we got a warrant?
Just my winning smile.
Anybody else hear
those cries for help?
Police.
Clear.
Here we go. Here.
[DOG BARKING]
[ECHOING]
Six-Paul-Eleven.
That's another radio.
Hit it again.
Keep hitting it.
[ECHOING] Six-Paul-Eleven.
Six-Paul-Eleven.
Test, one, two.
SHANE:
Hey.
Scooby's.
RONNIE [ON RADIO]: Test, one, two.
Shit.
So somebody executed our best lead?
VIC: Found Scooby's radio.
Any guns?
VIC: Nope.
RAWLING:
Well, he could have bought
that radio in a pawnshop.
VIC:
Or took it from him
after he killed him.
This guy couldn't subdue
Carl and Scooby.
The whole neighbourhood knew
we were looking for a Nigerian.
Maybe his accomplices heard
too and tried to tie things up.
Feels like it's moving away
from Antwon.
Might not even be seizure related.
I wouldn't rule him out just yet.
We haven't found
his Salvadoran hookup, Gusano.
This reads mob to me.
The neighbours are screaming
blue justice.
Payback for one of our own.
Let them stick their fingers up
his ass. He's been cold for hours.
We just got here.
We just need to get a fix
on what direction this is going.
El Salvadorans, Nigerians.
Just get me answers.
We should talk to Vic.
Maybe he could find out if our dead
guy was beefing with another gang.
We can do anything he can do.
Including dating his wife?
Ex-wife. And we're friends.
You wanna keep secrets,
go ahead.
But when it starts interfering
with our investigations, give it up.
It's just weird timing right now.
Maybe you should be the one
to talk to him.
CLAUDETTE:
Where are you going?
Blue classic car.
Well-maintained.
That's a classic?
It is to Billings.
You're not serious.
Witness knew enough to call
the switchboard instead of 911.
You're just mad at him
because he took our cases.
Witness with a spot-on
knowledge of gang tattoos?
I'm still not there yet.
That's dried soap. I thought he was
supposed to be getting you lunch.
So, what's up?
DUTCH:
We're stuck on this
carjacking murder.
Thought you might be able
to help us out.
BILLINGS: Sure.
Anything you wanna tell us about it?
What do you mean?
The anonymous caller
who witnessed the shooting
provided a lot of detail.
Very thorough.
DUTCH: Called the switchboard.
Recognized gang tats.
CLAUDETTE:
Your car is streaked
with dried soap
like you rushed out of there
without having time to rinse.
Dried soap? We had Nicole's blood
in O.J.'s bedroom
and look at what good that did us.
Give me a break.
DUTCH:
We got the bills back
from the car wash.
Your fingerprints
were on some of them.
You guys must've
broken the world record.
I can't get anything back
from those lab rats in a day.
So it'll take a day. But when it does
come back, we gonna find yours?
All right, I was there.
And now I'm here because I didn't
feel like committing suicide today.
Come on, I was 15 feet from
two armed bangers who
already had their guns out.
That's not being a coward.
That's living to fight another day.
Why didn't you report it?
I called in and told them what I saw.
Every detail.
If I didn't care,
would I have done that?
You should've called us instead.
Why? So the people here could think
I didn't do something to stop it?
Did you?
I was outnumbered and outgunned.
Come on. You know you can't
show weakness in this house.
You saw how they treated Reynolds
when they caught him bawling
his eyes out in the locker room.
Or Lowe, when his boyfriend
threw a hissy fit.
They still make fag
jokes behind his back.
It wouldn't be like that.
After what happened to Carl
and Scoob, everybody's
looking over their shoulder.
They give us this
badge and a gun.
And they expect us
to act like Superman.
Like I'm not a middle-aged guy
who could use a few more hours
a week on the treadmill.
You're both smart.
You got the facts.
I gotta work with the people here.
Keep me out of this?
What are you doing?
I'm practicing for the damn polygraph.
Listen, dude, you're gonna pass it.
And after you do,
you should get out.
For real?
Look, this team gets into a lot of shit.
You're telling me now?
We always say that we're through.
Okay, but if you're not in
a hundred percent...
split while the going's good.
Because you're either built for it
or you're not.
SHANE:
Hey, techies pulled a slug
out of that dead guy's wall.
Ballistics don't match Carl
or Scooby's guns.
INS gave us his roommate off
an expired visa.
Ididsa Okoye.
It's Okoye with me,
if it's Okoye with you?
Sponsored by a family
out of Long Beach.
If Okoye executed his roomie,
he's gonna need a place to
hide for the next few days.
So grab your swimsuits,
we're heading to Long Beach.
Lem, Ronnie, go around back.
You got it, man.
Come on, Ronnie,
let's go down the side.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Ididsa Okoye, is he here?
Is he inside?
SHANE: You speak English?
[SPEAKING IN NIGERIAN]
Ididsa, Ididsa.
Down.
[GUNSHOTS]
[WOMAN AND KIDS
SCREAMING]
VIC:
Get them out of here.
SHANE:
Army.
Army, get these kids out of here.
VIC: Police.
Come on, buddy.
All right, come here.
SHANE: Come on.
[GUNSHOT]
[MAN SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
Sounds Russian.
You ready? Go.
Yeah.
[GUNSHOTS]
Cover.
Let's go, he's empty.
[GRUNTING]
Don't move.
You all right?
[WOMAN CRYING]
[GUNSHOT]
[THUD]
He's down. He's down.
Shit.
Vic.
Hey, thank you.
Yeah.
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Vic.
OFFICER: Don't move.
SHANE: Hey, hey. We're cops.
RONNIE:
We're cops. Farmington P.D.
VIC:
You wanna shoot somebody,
I volunteer this guy.
[SIREN WAILS]
When we responded to shots fired, we
found this guy fleeing from the scene.
He involved in the shooting?
No, that's Ididsa Okoye.
His sister lives here.
Yeah, well, we found this on him.
It's Carl's.
Hey, man, you just snagged
yourself a cop killer.
Where's your partner?
He's in the restroom.
I've got a murder
I could use some help on.
VIC:
I'll be with you in a second.
I heard you're banging my ex.
Trying to get my attention?
No, it's...
I hope you're
thinking that through.
By the way...
we just picked up one of the guys
who killed Carl and Scooby.
That's great.
Yeah.
Weren't you primary on that?
Yeah, well, we're all here
to help each other out, right?
Right?
RAWLING:
You are in deep shit.
We know you killed
two police officers.
I didn't kill anybody.
Why were two Russians
holding your family
hostage, waiting for you?
Let's start with the cops.
Did Antwon Mitchell
hire you to kill them?
Who?
Why were the bodies left
in a seized house?
Look, I don't know how it works
back home in lion country,
but here, you get the
needle for killing cops.
Give yourself a chance,
you start talking.
Naming names.
You say I killed someone?
I say you are wrong.
VIC:
They found the police
radio in your apartment.
You had one of their guns on you
when they picked you up.
Both were taken off the bodies
after they were killed.
I am tired now.
I'm going to take a nap.
RAWLING:
Okay. Settle down.
Now, even cop killers
have rights.
Sleeping just isn't one of them.
This guy doesn't even know
to ask for a lawyer.
Give me the night. I'll get him
to own up to stabbing our guys.
It just doesn't add up.
Why are the Russians involved?
We'll figure it out.
It looks like it has nothing
to do with the seizures.
Well, isn't that a good thing?
Yes.
The Russian guy from the house
won't say a word...
but I tied him
to Carl and Scooby.
Pulled his boss over
a few weeks back. Clocked
him doing 50 in a school zone.
They got into some kind
of argument,
and they tossed the guy
in lockup overnight.
What?
Carl liked to get in people's faces.
They got killed
over a speeding ticket?
DUTCH:
We need you to ID
the shooter on the record.
BILLINGS:
Why?
CLAUDETTE:
Unis pulled over the stolen car.
He was Los Mag,
long rap sheet.
So why do you need me?
Because he's not talking.
We don't know his accomplices.
And we didn't find a murder weapon.
You're the best detectives.
Tell him you've got 10 witnesses.
Break this asshole
and get him to confess.
We tried.
You're our only eyewitness.
CLAUDETTE:
I know you're scared.
BILLINGS:
Come on.
Can you honestly say that you
wouldn't have done the same thing?
I know I'm an
asshole for asking.
But please, take another
crack at this guy. I'm begging.
Well, don't.
Ever heard of Andrei Tretiak?
He's Russian Organized Crime.
Same as the comrades who were
holding your family hostage.
RAWLING:
You're safe and sound here
in the police station.
But what about them?
VIC:
They've already
killed your roommate.
And we stopped them
before they raped and
tortured your family.
Next time,
they'll be quick.
They might let the kids live...
but only if they cut their eyes out
so they can't be identified.
RAWLING: I mean, it's over
for you. It was over the moment
you killed our two officers.
But I'm giving you a chance
to save the lives of your sister
and the rest of them.
How would you protect them?
We'd move them out of state.
But you have to give us a
statement and leave nothing out.
VIC:
Did Tretiak hire you?
I can't say.
Achebe arranged everything.
Well, while we're gluing his brains
back together...
you give us something
on these Russians.
Just did what Achebe asked.
RAWLING: And what was that?
Well, he was given names
and pictures.
We followed them, your officers,
and we waited
for our opportunity.
Then they went into an apartment,
so we opened a manhole cover.
When they came back...
we told them
we heard a child below.
So they bent down to look.
That's when I stabbed
the Asian one
in the back of the neck.
He was paralyzed.
Couldn't move his arm.
But the other one,
the black one,
he fought hard.
So I went to help Achebe.
We stabbed him,
we kept stabbing him,
but he wouldn't die.
And then we...
We heard the Asian one.
He was still breathing.
So I went, took him down
and finished him as well.
Cut him here.
And then we carried them
to the building.
The one you had stolen.
Just as Achebe
was instructed.
VIC: We straight?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
VIC:
Yeah.
Hey, I just wanted to say that
it really means a lot to everyone
that you guys nailed those assholes
who killed Carl and Scooby.
This old team
still has a few new moves.
We still gotta get the Russian
string-pullers.
Also, we got a lead on Antwon's
Salvadoran connection.
A guy named Gusano.
You still think Antwon's involved?
Well, we think
he might be connected somehow.
We're on the way over there now.
Shane and Army
have other business first.
Polygraph in 10 minutes.
Gang Central.
VIC:
I thought that was next week.
You know the public pressure
we're getting on this.
If I'm to stand up for this
team, I need assurances.
And I need them now.
If you can put it off till tomorrow,
this Salvadoran
might fill in some blanks for us.
These two are staying.
Anyway, good work.
Did you have to get
such a pretty tester?
Try and relax.
I'm just saying
you got my heart rate up.
Could you take a few points
off for me, darling?
I'm gonna ask you
a series of questions first.
Just to make sure
the machine's working properly.
Make your answers
accurate and honest.
Is your name Shane Vendrell?
Yes.
Gusano?
What's up?
VIC:
I'm here to talk about Pitarrio
and his heroin cutter,
Emolia Melendez.
Cops?
Yo, man, it's a friendly visit.
GUSANO:
Since when have cops
been friendly?
Pitarrio lost
something of yours.
Emolia was worried
that you might blame her too.
I helped her to get it back.
Now I'm helping to make it right.
Here.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Tell her to relax,
don't even trip.
As soon as I tell you to stay
the hell away from her and her kid.
SHANE:
Thank you very much.
It was very nice to meet you.
Hey, it's not that bad.
RAWNLING: Army, let's get started.
I'm not taking it.
You're what?
I talked to my PBA rep
and he said I can refuse to take it.
But we got...
We got nothing to hide.
And I can't get penalized for it.
He said polygraphs are subjective
and the results aren't worth shit.
And that's why
they're not admissible in court.
This isn't about
covering your own ass.
We have to prove
that we didn't set up Antwon.
If people believe that,
they'll think we framed
our cop killer.
Everything will fall apart.
I'm sorry, that's not my problem.
It is about everyone in here...
and how people think of us
out there.
You are screwing
every single cop in this building.
This has nothing to do
with anybody else.
This is about
taking care of me.
Look, the guy's just nervous. I can...
No, it's too late!
Injunctions are keeping the gangs
indoors. I'm surprised to say it, Roy.
But Monica's policies are
really starting to take an effect.
The public sees us
as having our boot on their neck.
When does the press
get good on this?
RAWLING:
We're seeing a difference.
Somebody just has to report it.
Don't shut it down now.
ACEVEDA:
She brought down
Antwon Mitchell for chrissakes.
You've been pissing on her policies.
Why the change?
I'm allowed to re-evaluate
my position. As long as
she's willing to also.
I really think there's a middle
ground that we can all be happy with.
Like what?
No.
Compromise, retreat
is the worst thing that we can do.
You'd be abandoning the memory
of those two dead cops
and all that they fought for.
PHILLIPS:
Don't play that card with me.
Most people in this town still
think they were killed because
of your seizure policy.
Well, they weren't.
It seems there was a traffic dispute.
ACEVEDA:
Do we know that for sure?
Is there any proof that we
can put in front of the people?
I'll find it.
As for the seizures,
they stay or I go.
Then you can tell the brass how you
lost one of L.A.'s two female captains
because she was too tough
on crime.
VIC:
Hey.
l...
I took care of Gusano.
He's not gonna be a threat
to you anymore.
You can stay here
for a few more days
but after that, I can only fudge
the paperwork for so long.
We'll be fine.
How's this little guy?
Has he been to a doctor?
Sure.
What did they say?
I gotta make him eat.
Try to get him into a preschool.
He used to talk more,
but some of the stuff he's seen...
I'd keep my mouth shut too.
I'll go pick up a few things to make
you guys a little more comfortable.
Maybe that'll get
him back to talking.
Thanks.
He confessed.
Kept your name out of it.
Thanks, really.
CLAUDETTE: You're welcome.
How about I buy you both a beer?
No, thanks.
Can't. I gotta be somewhere.
Vic's put me through hell but
never anything this malicious.
He just said that to hurt us.
So you're not trying
to get close to me just
to get back at him?
No. Absolutely not.
Maybe at first, a little.
But I really like you now.
Look, I put up
with Vic's shit every day.
So was asking you out a perk?
Sure, but Vic...
Vic's an asshole.
He's the father of my children.
That makes him my
asshole, not yours.
It's not where we started,
it's where we are now.
We started with a lie.
I don't even know
where we are now.
I'm sorry.
You think this is easy
for me? Dating again?
I told you it was a bad idea,
but you kept pushing it.
What about my kids now?
I love your kids.
You weren't honest with me before.
How can I even trust you
with them now?
Or trust myself to you?
Corrine...
You can leave, okay?
l... I am sorry.
It was nothing you couldn't
handle. I told you that.
I don't have to handle it.
The PBA guy told me...
You trust him before us?
Damn right.
I mean he may not be as
well-versed in these things
as an ex-Army locksmith,
but I'll take my chances.
You stupid shit.
Hey, hey.
Your PBA genius,
he gonna get you your next job?
He's gonna keep me out of court.
Well, you toss your
career if you want.
You made us all look guilty
when you blew off that test.
You are guilty.
SHANE: Shh!
Who's the one who lost it
and shot Halpern?
I know I didn't.
Which makes me guilty too.
VIC:
Hey.
Maybe Army's right.
This is as good a time
as any for him to jump.
No reason we can't
leave as friends.
Captain's right.
You are screwing people over.
You're screwing this team over.
ARMANDO: This team?
Look, that bullshit never worked
for me when I was pulling sand
out of my ass in the desert,
it's not working for me now.
I didn't take a bullet over there,
I'm not gonna take a bullet here.
Not for you guys.
I appreciate your honesty.
Let's go.
I vouched for him. I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
We have to shake
the Russians.
Figure out how this all
comes back to Antwon.
You think it does?
There's only one guy
who can get El Salvadorans,
Russians, Africans
and One-Niners all in the same bed.
Antwon.
We just got out from underneath
Antwon's shadow. Why shake
a stick at a hornet's nest?
Because anyone who had
anything to do with killing
Carl and Scooby has to pay.
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Plus, I got eight months of kicking
ass with you guys to make up for.
[MOTOR REVING]
[###]