[FOOTSTEPS]
LEM:
So how big is this rock
we're looking for anyways?
SHANE:
It's big, man. It's landmark-like.
RONNIE: Nothing.
ARMY: Me either.
Are we sure that's
the stables back there?
I got the horseshit
on my shoes to prove it.
SHANE:
Pitarrio said the girl's body's buried
200 yards south of the horses.
ARMY:
Which way's south?
RONNIE: We are south.
This is supposed to be the place.
SHANE:
I don't know. This doesn't feel right.
LEM:
Jesus Christ. This is bullshit.
You got something to say?
LEM: Nope.
I'm just looking for a dead girl's
body to keep your ass clean.
You don't wanna be here, don't be.
I'm not here for you. I'm here for her.
[HORSE NEIGHS NEARBY]
Couldn't pass up a police escort.
I felt like the mayor of cracker town.
VIC: Enjoy it now.
Your next police escort
might not be a round trip.
ANTWON:
I thought we were being friendly.
Times like this, a community
needs to come together.
Here's the waiver. Says you agree
to talk to us without the presence
of an attorney.
Waive my constitutional rights?
Let it be said that Antwon Mitchell
is all about the help.
Who killed our cops?
Way people feeling about y'all
these days, could've been anybody.
You've been speaking out
against the seizures.
Our dead cops were found
in a seized house.
You sure that wasn't your
idea of a protest song?
This may come
as a big surprise to you,
but there's a lot of shit
that goes on out there
I ain't privy to.
That house is in Niner territory.
You're king of the One-Niners.
You're telling me
you didn't order the hit?
Hear about it afterwards?
I just got off a plane.
I ain't even been back
to the castle yet.
Yeah, that was
convenient.
Out of town just long enough
for two cops to get murdered?
You know what happens now,
don't you?
Investigation never ends.
Ever.
Did you hear about Antwon's son,
Donald III?
He's in county, isn't he?
Turns out Don's been
a bad boy in lockup.
The surveillance camera caught him
in the bathroom with another inmate.
Guards say that he wasn't forced.
Did you know that your son
was gay, Antwon?
I didn't know your crew
was so friendly with the Mexicans.
Makes me kind of wonder what would
happen if I pulled a few strings
and had him transferred
to Folsom.
Little Tijuana?
VIC: He'd have a line of
boyfriends outside his cell.
I wanna know
who killed our cops.
When I come back,
you help me with that,
we'll talk about how
I can help your son.
[WHISPERING]
I'll take care of that.
I didn't know about the kid.
You goddamn busted him.
Check yourself.
No.
You better check her.
Don't forget,
I got cards to play here too.
[###]
If you've got any more bombs
to drop, give me a heads-up now.
You're doing great.
I'd do better if you
let me in on your intel.
No time.
We've only got him for 12 hours.
I wanna get back in there.
I don't think that going after
Antwon's family is the best way...
Somebody killed two of ours.
He knows who.
[DOOR OPENS]
Who killed our cops?
More yearbook
photos?
These are the Mexi OG's
who are running gen pop at Folsom.
They all have one thing in common.
They want you dead.
Now, they've got something else.
You some kind of special, lady.
Guess he's gonna have to learn
how to watch his own ass now.
He ain't my problem.
RAWLING: I don't believe that.
I bet you're feeling like a real
bad dad for not being there
during the wonder years.
I mean, just think, if you hadn't
been away doing time,
maybe junior wouldn't be
in the pokey doing dick.
I don't wanna see anything
happen to your son.
It's bad enough having you
for a father.
So tell me about my cops,
and Donald will stay right
where he is.
You ain't got much regard
for a man's family, do you?
I don't think much of you.
I wasn't talking about me.
I was talking about Rich Nelson.
You used to work together,
right? Way back when.
This ain't about
history, jerkoff.
It's all about history.
Couldn't have much respect
for his wife and kids either,
you screwing him and all.
I said, shut your face.
She ain't the only one
that went to the library.
Don't you wanna hear
my book report?
Say what
you gotta say.
When I was away, I heard that
you and Rich had a thing.
But I guess
it didn't work out.
He went back home
to his unhappy family.
Got the cancer.
And you moved on to take care
of mommas and their babies.
Now look at you.
Threatening to have my son
raped and killed.
How would your old boyfriend
like the new you, huh?
Oh, he'd like me fine.
He had you put away,
remember?
Oh, yeah,
but I'm back now,
and he's long dead gone.
Get me a cup of water.
Room temperature.
This ain't it. Body's not here.
Well, the ground was torn up, man.
I mean, you saw it.
ARMY:
By a mountain lion or something.
We're west of the stables, man.
The body's supposed to be south
of the stables.
This is where the rock is, man.
Know what, I'm calling Vic.
Come on, he's got his
hands full keeping Antwon
and Monica under control.
Instead of locking Antwon up.
That shit's on you, just like all
this other stuff.
Why'd you bring him into this?
Vic did that.
Probably wanted someone
around who wasn't thinking
about killing him.
I never would've done that.
Yeah, we'll never know that
because Vic got the drop
on you first.
Screw him.
DUTCH: We can rule this guy out.
What's the latest?
We're still following up
on the stolen J.P. necklace.
Pulled these from
Gang Central.
Went all the way back to '98.
Slim pickings.
Team's cleared over 60 people
so far. Tips keep coming.
Two cops dead, everybody
wants a taste of the action.
RAWLING: No one's taking
the claim? Bragging to their
buddies on the street?
Not yet. Our best lead's upstairs.
For now, Billings is gonna take
the lead on Scooby and Carl.
DUTCH: You can't take us off this...
Just temporarily.
Kleavon Gardner, your possible
serial killer from San Antonio.
You know this guy.
DUTCH:
What happened?
Young female, black,
was grabbed on DuPont
and strangled in the vacant lot
on Houseman.
A couple interrupted the attack
but she died on the way
to Mission Cross.
CLAUDETTE:
How'd we get onto my friend?
Was seen in the area, couple
gave a description close enough.
So unis are bringing him in.
We close Kleavon, you move us
back to Carl and Scooby?
Maybe I can solve that
while you solve this.
Looks like we've got him this time.
Yeah. One victim too late.
You've got Antwon Mitchell
upstairs? What's his connection
with the gun supplier you arrested?
RAWLING:
It's not clear yet.
But they're both involved in Carl
and Scooby's murders?
Yeah, I'd rather not discuss it
till we know more.
Oh, so you announce
you have your guy,
keep the streets quiet until
you get a lead on the real thing.
Smart call.
You look terrible.
Thanks. So do you.
You should go home,
get some sleep.
So should you.
Thanks for your help.
Is Antwon keeping his mouth shut?
Captain's pushing him
pretty hard.
Meaning he's about
to start pushing back?
And all we got is a rock
in the middle of a pretty
damn big woods.
Department's got a metal detector.
Girl was buried with earrings,
a belt buckle, it'll pick that up.
Or Shane's bullets?
I don't know. Maybe we should
just step away from this thing.
You mean away from Shane?
If I gotta choose taking down Antwon
and covering for Shane...
We're not there yet.
You and I both been living straight
and now we're in deeper than ever
because of him.
If we hadn't allowed ourselves
to get pulled apart,
stopped looking out for
each other, Shane wouldn't
have been in this mess.
It's time for us
to turn that around.
Like it or not, Shane's family.
[DOOR OPENS]
You going home?
Yeah.
Hey, nice getting shot at
with you today.
Maybe next time
two cops get murdered,
we'll be paired up again.
Maybe.
Hey, could be worse.
Could be Carl and Scooby
making bad jokes about us.
You found them, huh?
Yeah.
Did they?
You know, were they...?
I don't think they suffered much.
Really?
I heard it was pretty bad.
They had each been stabbed
several times.
But they had been moved
from another scene,
so the blood was minimal.
You know what? On second
thought, I don't wanna know.
Yeah.
Me either.
Thanks for riding with me.
You're lucky, you know.
You got family at home waiting
for you to walk through the door.
Take care, Danny.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
About time.
Who killed our cops?
Donald gets transferred out
to Folsom next Tuesday.
I suggest you arrange
a visit to say goodbye.
And I suggest you come down
out of that tower, ivory.
We all just taking a run
at something feels better,
using the power in our hands.
Rich Nelson.
He was using his power.
Screwing you wasn't his
only indiscretion, was it?
He planted that blow in my car
and trumped up
those trafficking charges.
Because just like you all,
he had shit on me.
You had to know it.
Your boyfriend,
he cheated that evidence.
So, what does that make him, huh?
You, for knowing?
Do you wanna talk
about indiscretions?
Secrets in the dark?
How about when
you were a kid, 13, 14?
Fat, not very popular.
Burying your head
under the covers
to drown out the screams
of your baby sister.
Your 6-year-old sister
that your daddy raped
night after night.
And you couldn't stop it,
could you?
Too much of a coward to confront
your old man, but not your mama.
She emptied two loads
of buckshot into his gut.
So daddy's dead, baby sister's
in the psych ward and your mama,
she's doing life in Chino.
All because you couldn't come out
from under the covers.
But, oh, boy are you making up
for it now. Yeah, you're street tough.
You're a gangster,
full of cop-killing rage.
But you're still too much of a coward
to even save your own son.
Cuff him.
End this now, man.
Give us a name.
Somewhere
we can look.
Maybe you ought to
take this out there.
Ask around your own house.
RAWLING:
What the hell does that mean?
Heard a lot of street chatter
about a little girl, got herself killed
because she was tangled up
with a dirty cop.
If I heard it, maybe
the murdered cops heard it too.
Got dead because of it.
VIC:
Bullshit.
For you to figure out.
In the meantime,
I want my lawyer.
Now.
DANNY:
Hey, Julien.
Watch commander wants us
to cover the cage tonight.
I won't be able to sleep anyway.
I'll let Vanessa know.
I saw Carl's wife before.
How's she doing?
She's upset.
She's thinking about
suing the department.
You're kidding.
This didn't have to happen.
She sees that.
She sees that?
Or you put it in her head?
It wasn't like that.
Okay, I'll be in the cage.
Take your time getting there.
You saw a black male, 30s,
running from the scene?
He was about 6 feet. Wearing jeans.
No. He was wearing a track suit.
MORGAN: Since when's
a track suit made of denim?
Don't tell me
what I saw, Morgan.
Can you describe anything else?
Hair? Distinguishing marks?
Just your average
shifty-Iooking black dude.
MORGAN: No offence.
Thank you.
He was clean-cut. The kind
you'd bring home to mom.
At least from a distance.
Sounds like you wanna bone the guy.
I don't think she meant it...
No, trust me, she meant it.
He thinks it's funny
making me feel like shit.
DUTCH: Think you could
pick out the man you saw?
I could. She's useless.
He's right. I have a terrible
track record picking out men.
MORGAN:
It's too bad that psycho
didn't cross your path.
Oh, you are so...
Aah! Arrest her.
TRINA: Arrest me?
Okay, all right, let's just calm down.
If it was me smacking her around,
you'd lock me up.
Asshole.
Bitch.
DUTCH:
Okay, take her away.
This is bullshit.
He's the one you should arrest.
JULIEN: Watch your step.
TRINA: He's stealing our cable.
Lady, two officers were killed
today, all right? Boosted cable's
just not a priority.
Looking good, Trina.
Looking real good.
Sir, step away from the cage.
Come on.
How about the stolen car parts
in our garage?
Think you could make that a priority?
She's lying.
Real crime is how small his dick is.
Afraid that one's not
in the penal code.
Then search our garage,
get him on grand theft.
I'll give you permission
to search our house.
Dead victim.
No physical evidence.
Two witnesses who failed
to pick Kleavon out of a six-pack.
We got nothing.
Kleavon's logged more
hours in interrogation
than the two of us.
He's guilty.
He's not gonna crack unless he's
under some serious pressure.
Well, the M.E.'s initial report
says that the girl was strangled
face to face...
What are you doing?
I only have a hundred.
I'm getting change.
I need some cash.
For gas.
If Kleavon thinks that girl's alive,
he'd know she could ID him.
He might want a deal.
If we offer one, he'll smell weakness.
Then we gotta get him to ask
for one. Let me get a run at it.
He's got a thing
for us black girls.
Young woman was rushed
to Mission Cross for surgery.
They say she's a fighter.
Fifty-fifty she makes it.
Glad to hear it.
Sloppy work.
Not by me.
You're jittery. Afraid of what
she'll say when she comes to?
Why should I be?
I was home watching the game.
Ask my sister.
I will.
Then do it. Get me out of here.
Last time you were here,
you were so calm
because you were innocent.
What's different about tonight?
Out of patience.
Seems like every time somebody shits
around here, y'all smell my ass.
Witnesses put you at
the scene. You sure you
didn't leave your house?
Went out for soda.
You changed your story.
You were watching the game
or you went out? Which is it?
I never been arrested, never tried,
never convicted, never on probation.
Come and go as I please.
Look, I'm sorry
that girl got her neck wrung.
It ain't my problem.
He wasn't gone long,
not more than five, 10 minutes.
Barely long enough
to get the sodas.
We have two witnesses who saw him
attack this girl. They chased him off.
They're wrong.
He has a habit of being in the
vicinity of murdered black girls.
That's what
the San Antonio police said.
And they've convinced you
of the same thing.
I know it's hard to believe this
of your own brother.
FATIMA:
Kleavon is not a killer.
If he was, I'm his sister.
Believe me, I'd know it.
We had a woman in here last year
whose husband was a serial rapist.
She had no idea.
He said he was at work, even took
a job that suited his other career.
I don't think she really even
believed it when he confessed.
Then I'll pray for her.
But Kleavon was home with me.
He left for only
a few minutes.
Is that enough time for him
to get the sodas,
stalk some girl
he doesn't even know,
drag her to a lot and strangle her?
Is it?
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
SARA:
Nice place.
What are we doing here?
I was driving by, it felt right.
After last time, I think we need
to go over the rules again.
No bruising,
no ripping out hair.
When I say stop, stop.
I heard on the news
about those two cops.
Died in the bottom
of some sewer.
Assholes overpowered them.
Let me make you feel better.
I don't wanna feel better.
My client and I need
to speak in private.
I'm surprised your client
can afford your services.
From ex-con to millionaire
rec-centre owner.
It's quite a leap.
Earn your 500 an hour,
asswipe.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Let me know when they're done.
Will do.
They can only hold you
six more hours. No reason
to say one word more.
I need you to do me a favour
while I'm stuck here.
What?
Cover that camera first.
Our conversations are privileged.
They're not allowed to watch.
Humour me, Tom.
ANTWON:
Call Bobcat.
Tell him it's time
to let the police find that girl.
RENNEL:
I don't wanna hear any more.
ANTWON:
Fine. Just get him the message.
[DOOR OPENS]
What? What now?
Pitarrio. He screwed us, man.
We've been north, south, east,
west of those damn stables.
What?
Captain's been digging
into Donald III.
Antwon's kid?
Turns out the kid's a cum burper.
Grabbing his ankles
for Mexi inmates.
Sent Antwon over the edge.
He's got his piece-of-shit mouthpiece
setting things into motion.
He's dropping the body?
Anonymous tip
could come in any time.
SHANE:
Okay, uh...
Okay, we gotta
go back to Pitarrio.
Have him be real damn clear
this time where Angie's body is.
Split up. One to his place,
one to the recycling centre.
Recycling centre. It's on Lexington.
There are like four of them altogether.
Forget it, you take the cut-house.
Make sure you get collateral
this time, so we know that
he's telling the truth.
SHANE: Okay.
VIC: Hey.
We still got time.
Yeah, all right.
No! Please, no! No! No! No!
Please, don't!
[SARA GRUNTING]
Come here. Get on your knees.
Not so hard.
Open up, sweetheart.
I said, not so hard.
Let me see that pretty mouth, huh?
Stop!
You ever suck a dick?
Like a cell bitch, huh?
I said, stop it!
[BOTH PANTING]
Did somebody do that to you?
Put a gun at your head...?
Shut up.
Just...
[HEAVING]
Look, whoever did
whatever to you...
You didn't know
they wouldn't pull the trigger.
You probably knew they would.
If you'd fought it, you'd be dead.
It's not your fault.
You're not like that.
You're a good person.
A good person
wouldn't be here with you.
I don't wanna
ever see you again.
Get out.
I said get out. Get out!
Leave.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Your sister says you were
gone about half an hour.
No. She knows it was five,
10 minutes.
Her statement puts
your alibi in jeopardy.
KLEAVON: Those Texas boys
were good at locking up
they coloured folks
on bullshit charges.
Somehow I don't think you two
run the same scam.
If you needed a soda, there was
a convenience store two blocks away.
But you went a half a mile further
to a more expensive supermarket.
That convenience store
don't always stock my drink.
Didn't wanna miss the game
so I just went straight to the market.
The same grocery near
the victim's bus stop?
She passes it every
Tuesday and Thursday
on her way home from
teaching night school.
But you've been stalking her
for weeks, haven't you?
No, sir.
Our witnesses are here.
Ready to stand in the line-up?
That's him, officer.
CLAUDETTE [ON TV]:
Number four.
You're out of luck.
Dutch, you ready
with that second witness?
Four, k eep your number up.
[MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[WHISPERING]
Psst. Get your hands up. Shh.
You want Pitarrio?
Yeah, Pitarrio.
Good. I got too much to do
today to get hauled in.
Put your hands down.
He's in the other room.
All right, let's go.
Shut up and keep it down.
Better go and get out of here.
Go.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Get up.
Shit.
Who are you?
You met my friends yesterday.
Asked about a little girl's
body you buried.
I told them.
Directions didn't work out.
Try again. No bullshit this time.
South of the horses, man...
You like lying about dead girls
as much as you like burying them?
Man, screw you...
Goddamn it.
Shit.
Wipe it up.
Look, you tell me
where the girl's buried.
And do not say the stables.
What stables?
You said the stables.
No, no, horses, man.
That go up and down.
The merry-go-round?
Yeah.
The goddamn
merry-go-round? Christ.
Where's your stash?
Where's your stash?!
Ain't got no stash...
How many teeth you wanna lose?
All right.
Where is it?
It's in there.
Get up. Get your ass up. Where?
It's in there, man.
All right.
Don't move.
We find the dead girl's body,
you get this back.
It's your last chance
to change your story.
Two hundred yards south of the
merry-go-round. By the big rock, man.
[TYRES SCREECHING]
Body's by the merry-go-round.
He said horses. He said horses,
so we've been in the wrong spot
all night?
Lem's on the way.
I'll meet him there.
Good morning.
You're back.
Hey, sweetie.
I missed you.
SOPHIA: I missed you too.
Those two officers...
Did they find out who did it?
No. Not yet.
It was a long night.
The dry-wall guy's
coming today.
Can you leave a check
before you go into the office?
Sure.
Actually, I was, uh...
I was thinking maybe
I wouldn't go in today.
Maybe we could take Sophia
to the beach.
Oh, I don't wanna get her off
her preschool schedule.
I found them.
Stabbed, tortured.
Jesus, David.
Well, we should try and do
something for their families.
I'm sorry.
For everything.
I've made mistakes.
Trying to get out of this hole.
Okay. Please, don't.
Just don't.
Those two men lying
on that ground...
I don't wanna spend another day
losing you and Sophia.
I spent the whole night worried
something happened to you.
You didn't even call.
I know. l...
I'll change things.
I'll get better.
It's over.
I swear.
[AURORA CRYING]
I swear to God.
SHANE:
Oh, shit.
RONNIE:
There's overturned dirt
about 100 yards back.
And just as we started digging,
cops rolled up.
Wetback says horses, we go
to the real goddamn horses.
What do you think, an hour
before they find that body?
I don't know.
Sorry, man. We tried our best.
Yeah.
Two witnesses. Two different
line-ups. They both went right
for you.
Your witnesses, they're white.
Figured. You know witness IDs
across race lines don't hold up
in court.
DUTCH: You're a DA now, huh?
Something I read once.
Whitey think we all look
the same. Isn't it true?
Same as us not knowing
one Chinaman from another.
The word of two white people
against one black man.
Isn't that enough
for any jury?
Not this time.
I wasn't there.
The doctors at Mission Cross called.
The victim came to.
She ID'd your brother
as her assailant.
It's gotta be a mistake.
You go to church regularly?
Every Sunday.
Never miss a service.
You said your brother left at 8.
Came back 10 minutes later.
Five to 10.
Would you be willing to put
your hand on the Bible in court
and swear to God on it?
Maybe it wasn't
exactly 10 minutes.
But it didn't seem
like much longer.
My goddamn card is in her pocket.
I mean, how long you think
it's gonna take for the captain
to come straight at me?
About five minutes
before she comes at me.
VIC:
They haven't even found the body yet.
LEM:
As far as we know.
ARMY:
Goddamn it.
SHANE:
Look, man, I've been
involved in shootings.
My ballistics are on record.
Yours aren't.
Maybe you swap out your gun.
You can get out of this.
They gotta bring the body
to the coroner.
Maybe we can't get in there
during the day, but maybe tonight...
Come on, that's bullshit,
and you know it.
RONNIE:
Cameras all over the place.
Look, someone say it.
I'm going away.
We're gonna think
of something.
Me going to jail and Antwon walking
out of here, that's not gonna happen.
I saw him shoot
that little girl four times.
So if I'm gonna go to jail for murder,
it may as well be for his.
Don't be a dumb shit.
SHANE: He killed Angie.
Probably our two cops.
This guy, he's evil.
I put a bullet in his brain,
at least there's some justice.
ARMY:
We ain't deep enough?
They're gonna find
that body any minute.
I won't have another chance.
VIC: No.
SHANE:
This is my mess.
You guys did everything that you
could for me and I appreciate it, but...
It's time for me
to take care of business myself.
We're not giving up to this guy,
not to this guy.
Let him do it.
Shut up.
Antwon's a problem
Shane can make go away.
Putting himself on the line
to protect us,
make sure Mitchell
gets what he deserves...
It's the first good thing
you've done in a while.
VIC:
Now's not the time, Lem. Let it go.
SHANE:
Oh, come on, man.
Lem's right.
I'm the one who got us
mixed up with Antwon.
I let him back me into a corner
that I didn't know how to
get out of. Well, now I do.
This one's on me.
Yeah.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
You and me, we're gonna chat.
I ain't chatting without my lawyer.
This ain't about lawyers.
This is about you and me.
Stand up. I wanna
look you in the eye.
Stand up.
You're not gonna get away
with killing that little girl.
What little girl, detective?
You know,
you got it all, don't you?
You got money,
you got power, respect.
The hillbilly's been
listening to my speeches.
It's too bad about
your son though.
Tell you what, my little boy
turned out to be a fag,
I don't know what I would do.
They say you're born that way.
You doing his mother up the ass
when you knocked her up?
One time, doing time,
for a long time.
That poor little kid.
He's gonna be found
face down in a shower
with a back full of shiv
and an ass full of cum.
Word hits the street,
what's that gonna
make you look like, huh?
Your people don't cotton
to the homo vibe.
My people ain't your worry.
Yeah?
But you know what, man?
With all that money, all that power,
at the end of the day,
you're still just a nigger.
With a faggot nigger son.
And where's the respect in that?
Huh? Where's the respect in that?
Now...
what were you saying
about my nigger faggot son?
Talk to you for a minute?
You don't get out of this
by getting dirtier.
You come clean.
To the captain, both of you.
No. Come on, that's not gonna fly.
VIC: We tell her the truth.
Antwon grabbed you up,
took your guns, he beat you.
Killed Angie,
used it to blackmail you
into working for him.
And we've got the proof on tape.
ARMY: There's a lot of other shit.
VIC: Not on that video.
I can sell it.
We've got him on tape soliciting
one cop to kill another cop.
No.
No, then it implicates you and
Ronnie for not coming clean sooner.
Army gets dragged into this...
VIC:
We do this right, nobody goes down.
Don't underestimate
how much she wants Antwon.
LEM:
Maybe...
Yeah.
Look, I can't ask you to do that.
I'm offering.
SHANE:
Look, you know how this works.
Captain doesn't buy it, they will
drag in anybody that is close to me.
So we survive it together
or not at all.
One more thing.
SHANE:
What?
ANTWON:
How'd you lik e to get
that little girl's body back?
Your bullets and all.
Jesus Christ.
ANTWON: Trade.
Body for a body.
SHANE: Who?
ANTWON:
Vic Mack ey.
His body for hers.
Shane and Army
killed Angie?
No. No.
Antwon did it.
Took their weapons,
beat the shit out of them.
Then he shot Angie with
their guns. He's had them
on the hook ever since.
How did you get the tape?
You asked me to find
the leak when the drug
warehouse came up empty.
I knew it wasn't Shane,
but I wasn't sure about Army.
So I bugged
their department vehicle.
Without my authorization?
One word from you
that I had authorization
to instal that camera,
it's all good.
You told me to find the leak.
And when you did, you kept it
from me. For how long?
Couple of days. That's all.
Ronnie and l...
Gardocki too?
What about Lemansky?
Are all you guys working
things behind my back?
No. We had to go through hours
of video before we found that.
I confronted Shane.
We've been working it out.
I had to have time
to wrap my brain around it.
Find a way to get Shane and
Army out from under Antwon
without them
losing their careers.
This isn't about careers.
He put a hit out on a cop.
You didn't come forward when
Carl and Scooby were killed.
I guess I wasn't thinking straight.
Not until we're minutes away
from digging up Angie's body
with your guy's bullets in it.
Anonymous tip gives us
the location of that girl
with Antwon in our house?
You're gonna find Shane's
card in that girl's pocket.
Now, if this wasn't a setup,
you think that Shane would've
left that behind?
Antwon's the bad guy here.
And you guys
are supposed to be the cops.
Shane needed my help.
His back was against the wall.
What would you have done
if it were Rich Nelson?
You goddamn leave him out of this.
Tell them I wanna
talk to them.
ANTWON:
You've been telling me
he's behind all my misery.
You're a regular Auto Zone,
Morgan.
You're such a bitch.
Takes one to know one,
asshole.
JULIEN:
You, over there. You, over there.
MAN:
Walk him to the back now.
Move.
It sucks to be stuck
with the wrong person, huh?
RAWLING:
Sit down.
One whiff of bullshit
and my next call is IAD.
So explain to me
how Antwon got to you.
When that cul-de-sac
got busted, we...
Tried to tip him about that?
No.
But after it went down, Army and I
figured that the girl going missing
was his way
of sending a message.
So you went
after him alone?
Well, there were two of us.
I thought we had a handle.
I was wrong.
Not coming to me immediately
is a fireable offence.
He said he would
hurt my family.
I have a 3-month-old son.
I have a wife
who shows open houses all day.
What was I supposed to do?
Carl had a wife.
Scooby has a mother.
He was her only son.
What did you
do for Antwon?
I tipped him
about the drug warehouse.
I busted a couple
of rival dealers.
But when Mitchell asked me
to put a bullet into Vic,
I knew I had to come clean.
So you went to Mackey?
Well, he came to me
before I had a chance.
You'll take a polygraph.
I'll do whatever you need.
RAWLING:
Army.
Have a seat.
[KNOCKS]
Yeah.
Well?
They'll take a lie detector.
I'll decide after that.
I was wrong not coming to you
right away.
But don't punish two good cops
because of it.
You think they're good cops.
You're a good cop.
I get helping friends,
it's just...
I asked you repeatedly
to find that leak and when
you did, you hid it from me.
You can use that tape
to get Antwon Mitchell off the street
for the rest of his life,
or you can use it to hang me
and the rest of my guys.
Or I could do both.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Your sister rescinded bail.
What? Why?
She wasn't too thrilled
when she found out about the stuff
you stole out of your mother's
house after she died.
You told them that?
Wanted the company.
The officers will be by to check out
the items in your attic later.
You can thank him
for giving us permission to search.
You know, he's into kiddie porn.
Hey, "barely legal"
is exactly what it says, legal.
Pretty detailed
and reliable for white folk.
Am I under arrest?
As soon as the
statement's processed.
We spoke to your sister again.
I wanna talk to her.
Can't let you do that.
You may taint her testimony.
She said you weren't watching
the game. You were watching
the news.
CLAUDETTE:
A report on the cop killings.
Bet that gave you
the itch, didn't it?
We were watching the game.
They kept breaking in with
bulletins about those dead cops.
DUTCH:
Let me ask you something.
Why would somebody kill them?
Ask them.
We're really stumped on this.
Hypothetically,
why would somebody
kill a cop?
Why would you?
I didn't kill no cop.
Hypothetically.
Tell you want I think.
I think people are tired
of being treated like criminals.
Tired of being hauled
into rooms like this.
Asked a million questions
they don't know the answer to.
Where were you last night?
How'd you know the victim?
Why'd you do it?
What made you kill?
You don't know
nothing about me.
I know I make you feel small.
Detectives, doctors
called from Mission Cross.
Your victim's awake.
Was that all right?
Yeah, thanks.
He was responding to you.
No. I lost him.
Because you
stopped pushing.
I don't see the point in burying
myself deeper in his mind,
there's nothing useful there.
What's wrong? You all right?
I'm fine.
Then go in there
and close him.
Van will be by later.
Can you make him stop looking at me?
Back up.
There's a rumour going around
that the money in that donation
jar's for a legal fund.
To hire a lawyer to sue
the department.
It is for whatever they need.
Same as when any officer dies.
People are really raw
around here, you know it.
It's not the time to start
rubbing salt into a wound.
Look, I didn't choose the timing.
I was your TO.
You did not learn this from me.
Screwing the department?
Disobeying the captain?
I understand that you're on edge
because of what happened.
But maybe what's really
bothering you is knowing that
if people had listened to me,
Carl and Scooby might be alive.
You may not be a cop killer,
Kleavon,
but you definitely tried to kill
that girl last night.
Lana's talking.
She's ID'd you
as her assailant.
You bought a case of soda
and two packs of Kools.
Grocery clerk said
you were in a hurry to leave.
An opportunity caught your eye.
She got off the MTA bus, walked
across wearing her headphones.
You put your soda in
the car, followed her,
waiting for your moment.
You came at her head on.
You wore latex gloves to avoid
prints, but also for a surer grip.
Her neck was thin, weak.
Her panic excited you.
That's the whole point.
All you can think about
is finishing.
Her carotid artery pulses.
Needs to pump oxygen to the brain.
Her throat pops.
Her urine splashes the ground.
She cries, all the fight is gone.
Her eyes roll back in her head.
It's over.
You look into those eyes
and all you can see is darkness.
And almost immediately,
you feel guilty.
Wrong.
Shut your mouth.
She told us what you did.
You expect me to believe
that girl got strangled,
then came out of a coma
pointing a finger at me?
Well, that's what happened.
Is she in a coma or is she
in surgery? It ain't both.
She was in a coma.
She went into surgery to open
an airway to fix her crushed trachea.
No. I don't think you two
got your stories straight.
I think I'll wait,
visit her at the hospital,
and see if she can point me out.
ANTWON [ON TV]:
How would you lik e to get
that little girl's body back?
Your bullets and all.
SHANE: How?
ANTWON: Trade.
Body for a body.
Who?
ANTWON:
Vic Mack ey. His body for hers.
This is entrapment.
Good luck on selling that one.
It's an illegal recording.
Camera was placed
in a department-issue vehicle.
On my authorization.
The Supreme Court says
that we're golden.
Plus our two officers
are willing to testify
that you shot Angie Stubbs
with their weapons.
That and a murder-for-hire charge.
Next time you arrange a cop killing,
don't do it in a cop car.
[ANTWON GRUNTING]
Stop. Don't move.
Do you wanna tell us
who killed our two men now?
Death penalty's off the table?
I go back to Lompoc, right?
My son
coming with me?
You think there's anything I get
out here I don't get on the inside?
Girls.
Cold brew.
You saw how
I was living.
Life for me
won't change.
Well, it'll be different
enough for us.
Who killed our two cops?
I don't know.
RAWLING:
Who has their guns and radios?
Don't know.
This deal is no good
unless you give us everything.
Look, I told you I killed
the girl. Bang, bang.
The bitch deserved it.
Put a hit out on Mackey.
But I ain't had nothing to do with
two dead cops. You barking up
the wrong tree with that one.
And while we're on the subject of
truth, you ought to know something.
Vendrell and that
burrito boy he rolls with,
they were dirty way
before I got anything on them.
So you can tell them
I'll see them on the inside.
[ANTWON CHUCKLING]
It's bullshit.
He's just trying to take down
as many of us as he can.
You gonna let him
have his way?
They pass the lie detector,
they'll be fine.
[DOOR OPENS]
We're releasing your brother.
The girl's dead.
Deep down,
you know we're right.
There's something wrong with him,
you just don't wanna see it.
But now that you know,
things will add up.
If I'm living
with a killer,
why hasn't
he killed me?
He feels safe
with you.
You've never suspected him.
So, what do I do now?
Just act as if
everything's normal.
But be careful.
KLEAVON:
Fatima.
She's scared.
CLAUDETTE: Good.
First sleepless night,
we'll be her first call.
Money jar's gone.
Someone took it.
I guess someone has
a problem with the idea
of suing the department.
Excuse us, we're ready to go.
We worked it all out.
We'd like to drop the charges.
Well, you can just express
your undying affection to the judge.
You're not letting us go?
Not till the van shows up
to take you downtown.
Asshole.
Bitch.
[DOOR OPENS]
Captain showed Mitchell
our little home video.
Got him to confess to soliciting
my death and for killing Angie.
[ALL SIGH]
Barely put up a fight.
Hallelujah.
What about Carl and Scooby?
Didn't give us anything on that one,
but we all get to go home.
Antwon's going to jail.
What about the lie detector?
After what we pulled off today,
polygraph's a piece of cake.
Couple of Vicodin, you'll have them
believing that you don't jerk off.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Rawling will
back you up.
That and all the back slapping
over getting Antwon...
It's over.
VIC:
Free and clear.
Couldn't have gone down
better if we planned it.
Thank you.
Look, I know
you didn't want to, but...
Maybe this is just who we are.
Me too.
VIC:
No, it isn't.
We had a problem,
we came together, solved it.
That's who we are.
Now on, we got
nothing over us.
We got one thing to do.
Hit the streets, find the bad guys,
show them who's in charge.
Strike Team style.
VIC: Starting with the pricks
who stabbed Scooby and Carl.
When the time comes, we'll be there
to see them get the needle.
LEM:
I'll sweat the baby bangers,
threaten to take away their PSPs,
they hold out on intel.
Anybody that owes me a favour,
I'll just be real damn clear that
it's way past due.
One-Niners will be
a lot more talkative.
SHANE:
I tell you what, man, this whole thing,
this is gonna shake up the street.
ARMY:
Bangers won't know which way
to turn. Then, bam, there we'll be.
Mackey's coming up clean
the past six months.
You've been through
the seizure files?
Sloppy paperwork,
but it all reads fine.
How about the evidence room?
Nothing's missing
or out of order.
Look, I've been asking around
the street as much as I can
without attracting attention.
I thought this
would be good news.
Stay on Mackey.
All of his guys.
You sure?
I wish I wasn't.
Here he comes.
VIC:
We got it, fellas.
Guess it's time for you
to lick my balls, daddy.
Captain's not buying
your tall tales, Antwon.
She bought the one about
me knowing nothing about
them dead cops.
You think some shit like that
goes down without my okay?
Who?
Who what?
We're just whispering here.
Those kind of whispers
violate your deal.
Yeah. Not unless
you got them on tape.
You'll never find out
who offed them pigs.
I'll go to sleep every night
smiling on that one.
You go to sleep every night
in a 6-by-12, asshole.
OFFICER:
Let's go.
Get in the van.
We'll find out
who killed our boys,
and we're gonna wipe
that smile off his goddamn face.
[VAN ENGINE STARTS]
[###]