The police department
can change.
But trust me, it's not gonna
happen from the inside.
Well, what's that have to do
with the city council?
These property seizures
are targeting my constituents
now, someday yours too.
That's not our problem?
You just started, David.
Take a breath. Give yourself
a chance to get settled in.
This policy's led to
increased corruption
in other cities.
Locals fighting for profits,
rises in police-brutality complaints.
What do you want, exactly?
A leadership position
on the police committee.
I can steer policy,
protect the council's interests.
Look, Bill,
I know how it works there.
I know what needs to be done,
I just need the authority to do it.
That's what
the other councilmen
are afraid of.
Think you might try
to shove something
down their throat.
No, that won't happen.
It's how I can serve best.
It just makes sense.
ACEVEDA:
I got it.
WOMAN:
Thanks.
I'm Sara.
David.
You mind?
[SIGHS]
Having a good time?
Just making an effort
to meet people.
But I don't remember
seeing you in here before.
But your friend looked familiar.
I hope, for his wife's sake,
he wasn't a john.
You're a cop.
I need to get my radar checked.
How's business?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Look, I'm just here
to have a cigarette,
not to make an arrest.
So where you from?
Phoenix.
Been here long?
No.
Just came out.
I like it, though.
There's a lot to like.
It was nice to meet you, David.
You been on vacation,
or you just working
on white people's time?
Where the hell is Antwon?
Every cop with a Kodak is hassling
brothers, seizing cars and shit.
Antwon's shit.
So?
So you best remember why you're here.
Antwon ain't posing for no po-po.
Look, I told you last time,
I don't deal with scrubs.
And just so we're clear, I'm the one
that's supposed to be getting tips.
You're a week behind.
So you tell Antwon
to come back himself
and don't forget
to bring me gifts.
You tripping, huh?
Or you forget
just how much you up in for Antwon?
'Cause it just takes
one anonymous call to 911.
You feel me?
Oh, yeah, I feel you.
You gotta figure out how
to stop the bleeding.
Or I'm gonna
have to drop a dime on your ass.
One second. Come here.
SHANE:
We'll work this out.
He's gonna drop a dime?
Are we involved in
some shit beyond hookers
that I don't know about?
This is just a little quid-pro-quo thing,
only Antwon's a little slow on the quo.
Hey, this is not a big deal.
These guys always try this to see
if they can own you.
Now, as long as we handle
this right, it's not a problem.
So you just sit on
the other guy. Okay?
All right? Okay.
I think I might've come
up with something.
My nigga.
ARMY: Hey, hey.
ARMY:
Step back, asshole.
[GRUNTING]
SHANE:
You gonna drop a dime on us, huh?
What we got here?
Come here.
Hit him.
Do it, asshole!
No.
I told you to do something,
you dumb shit.
ARMY:
Harder!
I thought you two were tight.
[CHUCKLES]
Know what?
Tell Antwon
there's a new scoop law
come pick up his dog shit.
It's safer if we talk out here.
Whatever.
Listen, I need you to look at a guy.
A drug dealer
named Maurice Webster.
Claudette and I don't
usually handle drug cases.
From what you've been telling me,
it's a step up.
I should write this down.
No, stop. I'll send the file.
Get it from your captain.
This is all we have to do
to make things straight
between us and the DA again?
No. But it's a start.
Now, my source says
that Maurice is a major player.
Let's see what you
and your partner can whip up.
VIC: Hey.
CORRINE: Hey.
We've gotta go, the realtor's inside.
She's taking her sweet time.
They're interested. Gretchen thinks
they're gonna make us an offer.
Why does Mom have to move?
We talked about that, Cassidy.
I want to.
What about my friends?
When I'm here?
CASSID Y:
Can I go to my room?
We have to go while they're here.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hold on. Yeah.
[MOUTHS] You gotta leave.
I'll hold.
All my stuff is in my room.
No one's gonna touch your things.
VIC:
All right, I'll be there.
I gotta go to work.
Give me a kiss.
VIC [SIGHS]:
All right, let's get
out of their way.
Look, I appreciate the call,
but rape's not usually my thing.
Fugitive recovery is.
Oscar Ruiz was at
the courthouse this morning
for a prelim on his three
sexual-assault charges.
They think he found
an unlocked window.
VIC:
Picked the wrong guy to let escape.
They figure he got loose around 7:30.
We didn't hear about it until 9:30,
after he raped again.
JOE [OVER MACHINE]:
Myrna, are you there?
You said it was an emergency.
MYRNA: Joe.
JOE: Yeah, what's wrong?
MYRNA: I slept with him.
JOE: What?
MYRNA:
I suck ed his dick,
and then he did me from behind.
JOE:
What the hell's going on?
MYRNA:
He's better than you are.
He's a real man, not a pussy lik e you.
JOE:
Myrna. Myrna, Myrna,
is somebody there?
MYRNA [WHIMPERS]:
He's so big.
JOE: Who's there, Myrna?
MYRNA: He's the best I ever had.
JOE: Is he making you say this?
I want him to do it to me again
in the ass
while you listen.
Myrna, I'm calling the police.
I'm on my way home.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
Wanna get this guy?
Yeah.
[###]
DUTCH:
Oscar Ruiz,
the stay-at-home rapist.
Forcing his victims to call the husband
or the boyfriend is his standard m.o.
It's a neat spin on things.
Come for the rape.
Stay for the humiliation.
That's a list of his known friends.
Anyone interesting?
Got a fiancée living in Farmington.
Talk to her.
So Ruiz left the rape scene at 9: 15 with
a gun and clothes from their closet.
That makes two hours
since anyone's heard from him.
A smart guy would run
as far and as fast as he could.
RAWLING:
He raped again
right out of the box.
Which means
he knows we'll catch him.
He's gonna binge until we do.
Ruiz poses as a flower-shop
delivery guy, then he forces his way in.
I'll get his picture to the shop owners,
and I'll talk to this roommate.
"Stay-at-home rapist"?
It's just something I coined.
Yeah, well, the women stay at home.
This guy goes out and rapes.
Nicknames are meant to be catchy,
not literal.
You want us to throw in on Ruiz?
No, Vic's got it.
I'm Captain Rawling.
This is Detective Mackey.
Emily, right?
Yeah, Emily Mischner.
Thank you for coming in.
I apologise for what happened.
We can put you in a department
safe house until this is resolved.
Until what's resolved?
EMILY:
Why am I here?
Oscar Ruiz escaped
from sheriff's custody this morning.
Oh, my God.
That's... That's what the commotion
at court was about?
RAWLING:
We're gonna find him.
But you shouldn't go home alone
until we do.
I have been alone.
I went home right after
they delayed that hearing.
He already raped me once.
Why didn't somebody here tell me?
The sheriff's department thought they
had him contained in a downtown area.
Took a couple of hours before they
realised that he had gotten past them.
So he's out there?
Listen, we have a lot of resources
dedicated to this thing.
In the meantime, a couple of officers
could take you home and stand guard.
EMILY:
I...
I'd rather stay here
until you catch him.
VIC:
Yo.
You seen this guy?
You are Blinky, right?
In here, I'm Felix.
What's going on?
Oscar Ruiz, your roommate.
He's in prison.
VIC: He got escaped.
No shit?
So you don't know that he raped
another woman this morning either?
They were about to lay
a life sentence on this prick.
Know what they're gonna do
when they find out you helped him?
Yo, I didn't help him escape.
All right?
I didn't even know he was out
till he showed up this morning.
When did he get here?
He was out back
when I got here to work.
Look, he said
he was innocent.
So I gave him a few dollars to get
to Mexico. I just wanted him gone.
He didn't go to Tijuana.
He went out and raped
another woman.
Used your money to buy the flowers
that got him in the front door.
VIC:
He know how to get
into your apartment?
Hey, he knows
where I keep the spare key.
Hey, man, I'm sorry.
Save it.
Gonna park your ass right here
with an officer
in case Ruiz shows up again.
SHANE:
Antwon Mitchell.
As I live and breathe.
SHANE:
Run on inside, kids.
ANTWON:
Man, you've got to be crazy,
showing your face around here.
Especially after that shit
you pulled last night.
I didn't wanna play hard, but your boy
was threatening to own us.
Question is, what's next for us?
Halpern was out of line.
That shit won't happen again.
Yeah, well,
that's not good enough, partner.
I don't know if
you got a hard-on for jail,
or you just like pissing off cops.
But me and my boy are looking
at the door on this unless
you convince me otherwise.
Come on, shit on them, man.
Hey, don't go sideways on me.
Paid in full.
With a little extra
to make everything all right.
Okay, player?
Good.
But I like making busts too,
so step up the tips.
I'll make sure
you get by same as before.
Things ain't the same
as before, man.
We got these cops coming after us
like storm troopers.
Well, I'm your Luke Skywalker.
The seizures...
I'm close to the cop
who's running it.
How close you to him?
I'm as close as I need to be.
Okay.
Get at me, then.
See, you gotta bring me
some news I can use.
Then the clock starts running
on your protection.
Hey, captain. Back already?
City business.
A multiple rapist walked out
of the courthouse this morning,
attacked another woman.
I need to reschedule.
Anything I can do?
No. Sorry to inconvenience you.
A lot of people have been
talking to me about
these police seizures.
I think we should talk today.
It's important.
Can you wait a few minutes?
Yeah, a few.
Beth Insardi just called.
There's a drug dealer
they wanna make a case against.
She specifically asked
for the two of you.
Really.
CLAUDETTE: You sure she meant us?
Must be the bottom of the barrel.
Doesn't sound it.
His name is Maurice Webster.
He's a big dope fish in our little pond,
so try to wrap a net around him.
Drug sting?
Isn't that more Vic's rhythm?
Vic's busy, so I'd take whatever
olive branch the DA's offering.
Beth says there's a time issue,
so don't waste any.
Maybe they're ready
to take the leash off, huh?
RONNIE:
His picture's out there.
Flower shops, supermarkets,
we even covered the on-ramp slingers.
VIC: Anything on the fiancée?
RONNIE: No, nothing.
VIC:
All right, gather around.
This is Ruiz's old apartment.
We'll start from here and spread out.
Let's hope he's feeling homesick.
Let's go.
Hey. Any luck on your rapist?
Yeah, all his.
You got something to run by me?
Yeah, I just found a crack
in Antwon Mitchell's family seal.
His oldest son, Donald III,
has been moving fake IDs
out of the back of his van
in the DMV parking lot.
I thought Antwon
kept all of his kids straight.
Well, this one dumped private school
for the family business.
Uh, do me a favour, don't move
on this punk for a day or two.
Why not?
I gotta test a theory.
Someone just spotted Ruiz.
Seventh and Vermont.
So about the seizures.
I understand coming on strong
in the beginning to set a tone.
But maybe you're pushing too hard.
You have a suggestion?
Reach out to the community.
Visit some churches,
community watch programmes.
Put on a friendly face. If these people
don't know you, they won't trust you.
When they see us pulling bangers
off their corners, I think
they'll give us a second look.
And what they'll see
is you targeting blacks and Latinos.
That's who's here.
We target the criminals.
Most of their victims
are black and Latino.
They're smart enough...
I'm not trying to kill it.
Maybe with some modifications,
this plan could be
a little more civilian-friendly, that's all.
This coming from a councilman
or a police captain?
Both. And you should know
there's a chance
that I could be overseeing these
seizures on the police committee.
We don't answer
to the police committee on this.
Not yet.
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
VIC: We just missed him.
What happened?
Flower-shop owner saw him, called in.
We missed him by five minutes.
What do you need?
As many bodies as you can spare.
I gotta blanket the area.
Okay.
Excuse me.
JULIEN:
Raga's who our boss is interested in.
Sees the tag in a dozen places
every day on her way into work.
He's the main tagger
for the One-Niners.
"Raga paints." P is for Po Boys,
ain't, S stands for shit.
"Po Boys Ain't Shit." Cute.
So does this have anything to do
with the territory being disputed?
This is the front line,
which is why Raga
keeps hitting this sign.
Raga just gets the word out.
But if we can get him,
we can find who's giving the orders.
Yeah, look for hoodies or skullies,
and a backpack to carry the paints.
I've been trying to get you guys
onto taggers for a long time.
What changed?
We got a new captain.
So, what's the chance
of this guy hitting again tonight?
Sometimes it's hard to tell if ours
is even dry before they tag over it.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
Possible man down.
That's us. Thanks.
Have you looked at his file?
DUTCH: Glanced at it.
Sixty-year-old drug dealer
that's never been arrested?
Late bloomer?
There's a possession charge in '89.
A citation.
We've got unis staking out a guy
who got a ticket for having a joint.
Maybe he's careful.
You said he was a late bloomer.
DA says he's important.
I think they're trying to jerk us off.
They requested us.
Yeah. Because everybody else
is out hunting a rapist.
Take yes for an answer.
Please.
VIC:
Ruiz ran out of here
less than 20 minutes ago.
Where do you want us?
Start a couple up on Bonnie Brae.
Work your way north.
MAN:
Okay.
Hey, Vic.
Ruiz just called his fiancée.
She tipped him the cops are there.
Tell me we got a trace.
MAN:
They're gonna take care of you.
WOMAN:
I need you with me.
MAN:
I'll be right behind you. I promise.
[MAN GRUNTS,
OBJECTS CLATTER]
Look, sir, come on, calm down.
It's his house.
[SOBBING]
Neighbourhood canvass
came up empty.
He's got family in Fresno.
Unis are at the train and bus stations.
What's your next move?
I'm on the fiancée
and the friend.
We're gonna expand
the neighbourhood search.
Ruiz didn't sling,
he wasn't a member of a gang.
And maybe you should
talk to Dutch.
He's a little more plugged in
to this guy's psychology than you are.
It's time to get creative.
[WHISTLES]
Five-0.
VIC:
Suvuto.
How'd you and your thorns
like to play deputy for a day?
God's work ain't cop's work, homey.
I think Jesus'll loan you out
for this one.
RONNIE:
Name's Oscar Ruiz.
He who persecutes my brother
persecutes me.
Yeah? Well, how about
he who rapes my mother or my sister?
At least five that we know about.
After he's done, he makes them call
their husband or boyfriend,
tell them how good he was.
Ruiz escaped
in your 'hood this morning.
We'll check it out.
VIC: Good.
Look for flowers. He poses
as a delivery guy to get in the house.
All right, homes.
Someone sees him, I want a call.
Hey. Aren't you gonna
swear us all in?
Blessed is he
who delivers this asshole unto me.
DUTCH:
What do you got, Carl?
Pulled him over for rolling a stop sign.
Barely. I mean,
come on.
Hey, somebody
tell you to talk?
When he opened the window,
I noticed a strong marijuana odour
emanating from inside the vehicle.
Which gave you
probable cause to search.
Yes, sir.
We found these.
DUTCH:
Good work, officers.
Don't you have anything
more important to do?
I'm sorry you don't think
buying illegal drugs is important.
Fortunately, the courts do.
Have you heard about
the asset seizures
we've been doing around here?
We caught you with illegal drugs,
that means we can take your car.
We find any weed in your house,
you can kiss that goodbye too.
You can't do that.
Watch us.
He's not lying.
DUTCH:
You've never been to prison,
have you, Slick?
Of course not.
Forty years old. You really
wanna start down that road now?
Look, it was just
a couple of reefer sticks. Come on.
You've got one chance
to help yourself.
After that, it's out of my hands.
Now, who's your dealer?
Maurice, but he's not a dealer.
He's just a friend, hooks me up.
Got a few plants in his backyard,
enough for him and a few others.
Three plants in his backyard?
That's just his version.
The DA's office is trying
to make us look like idiots.
Why would they do that?
Somebody is lying to somebody.
Right now, Slick's
the only person I believe.
RAWLING:
How was the interview?
Oh, our major drug dealer
is looking a little minor.
Slick's ready to cooperate.
Hey, if the DA's willing to
pull you two out of mothballs,
there's plenty I could use you for.
Vic talk to you yet?
No.
He will.
Ohhh. Crushing crime
one blunt at a time.
Find what you need?
I've been meeting with people
about staff jobs for my district office.
I was just checking records.
Resources are for
law-enforcement personnel.
Well, I'm a reservist,
so technically I am personnel.
Fell short of your 10-year pension,
did you?
Being a cop gets in your blood.
So does being a politician,
from what I hear.
If I can stay connected to the force
a couple of nights a month,
then I'm happy to serve.
I need some fresh air.
The effectiveness and fairness
of these seizures aside,
you're doing a bad job
selling them.
And you'd like to be my publicist?
Forcing property forfeitures
and seizures
on a community
that's already decimated?
That's the current spin.
If this is about council getting a cut
of seized property, it's not my area.
No, I'm just making
a suggestion.
I've been where you are.
And I've learned
there's always a compromise.
The policy still needs
time to breathe.
If I set up a public forum
where you can present your plan,
answer questions, will you come?
Sure.
You want a tip?
Well, I got one for you.
Heard about some éses running
some wetbacks over the border.
I can eat lunch downtown,
trip over one or two
on my way in the door.
Shit, my mom's got
half a dozen sleeping
in the backroom any given night.
Yeah, well, these Mexicans,
they check in, they don't check out.
ARMY:
What does that mean?
They gotta find a family member
willing to pay a 5-grand relocation fee.
I got some credit now?
Yeah.
If the cheque clears.
Hey. I heard about that rapist.
Think you're close?
I could use a break.
What are you into?
Got a line on a coyote farm.
Getting ready to move,
thought you might wanna hop on.
Could use a break, not charity.
Peace offering, that's all.
You remember
Shane Vendrell.
He's got something brewing
in our backyard.
Got word on a coyote farm. Hoping
maybe you could give us some backup.
They're housing illegal aliens?
Until the family can pay
to spring them.
Just when they think they're free
and clear, boom, final bill comes due.
All my officers
are tied up chasing Ruiz.
So I guess we're on our own.
Well, let me know
when you're in position.
See what I can spare.
SHANE:
Thank you.
Ah, so how's the hunt?
I got some things
worth looking into.
Look what the rat dragged in.
Uh...
He's got a line on something.
Some One-Niner
dropping stolen airbags
at a garage on Third.
Think I'll cut out the back.
So, what's going on with Webster?
You tell me.
Are you saying
you don't have anything yet?
No. We hear he's got three
marijuana plants in his backyard.
Oh, well,
three is enough for us.
You said he was a major drug dealer.
He's selling drugs, isn't he?
What aren't you telling me?
I'm not gonna push this any further.
Webster's about to testify
for the defence in a murder trial,
and we'd like to
undermine his credibility.
You had us target a guy
to keep him off the witness stand?
That's bullshit.
You wanted out of the doghouse,
remember? You came to me.
And you knew if you laid it out for me,
I wouldn't go for it.
It's not illegal.
What, just immoral?
Not the way I see things.
My partner doesn't like the smell of it.
Fortunately, you promised
to keep her under control.
But if you don't like
the way the deal is anymore,
we can go back
to the way things were.
So you'll go under with Slick, right?
Do me a favour.
Get somebody else.
It's our case.
Well, I'd rather not.
Well, that's great.
That's fantastic.
Hey. Hey, don't you
walk away from me.
Not after I've had your back
every day for the last six months.
Look.
This is our way
to get back into the rotation, okay?
He'll never buy me in this world.
It has to be you.
DANNY: Hey. Get back!
[ALL CLAMOURING]
Get on the sidewalk now!
MAN: Back off!
DANNY:
Drop the stick right now. Drop it.
VIC:
Holy shit.
MAN: Back off.
They think it's your guy.
They started chasing him,
he called 911.
VIC:
Hey, hey. Back off.
Back off!
He's not the rapist.
He's Chinese, for chrissake.
What's wrong with you people?
Hey. What happened
to calling me first?
They thought they got him.
They got excited.
If he's a Chinaman
driving an actual floral truck,
then feel free to assume
he's not our escaped Hispanic rapist.
Hey, all you said
was flowers, man.
I asked for eyes on the street,
not a lynch mob.
And trust me, you find him,
he won't enjoy the process.
For chrissake.
What happened?
Ah, running down Ruiz
has everyone a little on edge.
On edge?
You put a street gang on payroll?
Look, I was just going for intel.
These guys follow the Messiah,
not Suge Knight.
We're lucky they didn't kill him.
It's under control.
I got the genie back in the bottle.
Maybe you should've asked
the genie for three wishes.
About as realistic
as expecting a street gang
to do your policing for you.
Yeah, I get it.
Are you gonna burn me, Vic?
No, I'm gonna catch this guy.
A lot of people warned me about
using you. Maybe I should've listened.
You told me to get creative.
That doesn't always go smoothly.
She's been sitting there all day
because she's afraid to go home.
Talked to Dutch?
Enjoying the show?
Deputizing vigilantes.
I gotta write that one down.
Yeah, well, the point is to find
this prick before he rapes again.
Which is the only reason
I'd ask your opinion.
Shoot.
Ruiz had a roommate.
Got a hundred bucks off him.
Worked once, it can work twice.
I'm on him.
We know about the fiancée.
No family in town.
You watching the border?
I got the street stuff covered.
I need you to drop
some profile bullshit on me.
Preferably something useful.
He used to rape
once every two or three months.
He's raped twice today already.
As I predicted, he's bingeing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're a genius.
What else does he binge on?
At the end of the day,
these guys are all Ioners.
And Ioners become
creatures of habit. They have to.
Prison's forced depravation.
Now he can indulge.
So, what else does he like
besides raping?
Kicking soccer balls,
watching video games,
the same porn movie,
whatever it is,
he's been missing it.
You're welcome, asshole.
[MELLOW J AZZ PLAYING]
So, uh... Slick says your mama's ill.
I swear, I don't know which is worse,
the chemo or the cancer.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
Weed's the only thing seems to help.
Wait right here, Claudette.
It's not chronic, but it is fire.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
It's usually $20 a bag.
But the second one,
for your mama, is gratis.
Hey, thanks, man.
That's great of you.
Yeah. God bless.
I talked to you at the Continental.
SARA: I remember.
How did you get my home number?
I can get any number I want.
All right, look, I'm gonna hang up.
No, please don't.
I'm interested in getting together.
But I need to be more careful
than most people.
There's some precautions
we need to take.
All right.
Why don't you come over
to my place tonight,
and we'll talk about them?
Okay.
What did Ruiz like to do
before he went away?
I don't know.
Where did he spend his time?
In his room.
Doing what?
I didn't even wanna know.
Okay, you know what? I got this.
This guy did something
besides raping all day.
What was it?
He'd get his takeout and close
his door. All day, every day.
What kind of takeout?
Chicken pot pie, man.
Same thing, same place.
The chicken pot pie at Clucky's.
Clucky's.
Good.
I just waited on him.
This guy?
Hour ago.
I do something wrong?
Did you talk to him?
Of course.
I live off tips. Seemed nice.
He was looking for a car,
asked me what I drove.
He asked me out too,
but I told him I had a fiancé.
Jimmied.
Where's your registration?
Glove compartment.
That's funny.
Not really.
Vic!
He's going for the street.
Police!
VIC:
Stay with him.
Stop!
[SIREN WHOOPS,
TYRES SCREECH]
VIC:
Come on. He's close.
MAN:
Hold on.
[BARKING]
MAN:
What's up, boy? What's up?
Send him.
MAN: Take him!
[RUIZ SCREAMING]
Should I call him back?
Not yet.
Ruiz, throw out your gun.
Throw out your gun right now.
He lost the gun.
Call the dog back?
This guy raped five women,
two today.
Yeah, he might
still be packing.
RUIZ:
Get him off of me!
Get off of me!
Okay.
Sounds like he's
ready to give up.
MAN:
Aus, enough.
Emily.
Yeah.
We got him.
One of our officers
can take you home now.
Is he in jail?
He's in the hospital.
They used a police dog
to subdue him.
Ruptured one of his testicles.
They say dogs are a good judge
of character.
SHANE:
Hey, that was a nice tip today.
Rescued over 80 illegals,
made six arrests.
That worked out real good.
No doubt.
Look, I'm not unreasonable.
You work with me,
I'm gonna work with you.
Keep both our asses
in the clear.
It's good to give,
but it's nice to receive.
Mackey's got his eye
on this garage on Third.
Dropping stolen airbags
or something.
Yeah, okay.
But the seizure thing, man.
How's that gonna play out?
I'm working on getting close for you.
Good looking.
Told you.
This could be
a beginning thing.
If the cheque clears.
MAN:
Hey, what's up?
Man, I don't make trouble.
I don't hurt anybody.
I don't sell to kids.
I keep to myself.
But y'all act like
I'm out there...
killing people.
I was looking out
for your mama, wasn't I?
Now y'all wanna lock me up.
For three plants!
That ain't right.
[KNOCKS ON DOORS]
Can I talk to you outside?
Beth is gonna take over from here.
DUTCH:
He's all yours.
What happened?
Went by the tyre store.
The airbag guy definitely
pulled up stakes and moved on.
Shane tipped him off.
All right.
Good news is we know about it.
So from now on,
watch what you say around him.
You're a part of this now.
Well, I got a choice?
All right, what do I gotta do?
Shane thinks he knows
all our moves...
so let's throw him a curve ball.
Pick up Antwon's kid.
Let's let this guy feel the heat.
Which guy? Antwon or Shane?
Both.
[GENTLE POP PLAYING]
You can smoke if you like.
I might.
I'm glad you wanted to see me.
I need to work some things out.
Me too.
I need you to proposition me
so I know I'm safe.
I, uh...
wanna be with you.
Sexually.
I'll pay you. Just tell me how much.
You're different, David.
I can tell.
I like you.
Next time, you should bring me a gift
to show me that you like me too.
Anything you want, but nice.
Six hundred dollars' worth.
I can't wait to see
what you pick out.
What are you doing?
I'm undressing you.
Ow.
I'll undress you.
Okay. That hurts.
[SIGHS]
You can slap...
but you can't leave bruises.
Anywhere.
No scratching
and absolutely no blood.
You can pull hair
as long as you don't pull it out.
And you can choke
if it doesn't hurt too much.
I'll show you a safe signal
in case I think it's going too far.
Didn't we see her before?
Raga's a girl.
Let me see your hands.
Sorry to ruin your masterpiece.
JULIEN:
Not worth it. Just come down
the way you went up.
Come on.
You've cost this city tens of
thousands of dollars in cleanup.
Send me the bill.
RAWLING:
We will.
But you tell me who's planning
this war with the Po Boys,
who's giving you these messages,
I can make things better.
Bring her something to eat
while she thinks it over.
Hamburger and fries.
Settle a bet first.
What's Raga stand for?
Righteous angel, gorgeous ass.
I don't admire the artwork,
but I got to admire the confidence.
VIC:
How's Pops?
MAN: I don't know.
[VIC CHUCKLES]
If he's king, asshole,
that make you prince?
I get some juice on the street.
But I get problems too.
Lot of guys wanna take me down
for being his blood.
Hell, yeah.
You're walking around
with a bull's-eye on your chest.
And where's Antwon?
Oh, yeah, that's right,
he's got 10 other kids to look in on.
I hardly know the cat.
Just hear the lectures about
going on the straight and narrow.
He should take his own advice, right?
I got an idea how to get him back
for all those sad Christmas mornings.
Back up, man.
I don't like the dude.
But I ain't gonna help the white
occupation take him down either.
SHANE:
Look, I heard about the garage,
I passed on the info.
But I'm not gonna guarantee
these things.
I don't give a shit
about that garage.
Then what the hell's
your problem?
They busted my son.
You hear about that?
Huh?
They come around here
looking for help when they want it.
And then they go and bust my son.
They bust my kid, man.
You think that shit is just bad luck?
I'll find out what I can.
They're coming to get me
through my blood, man.
That's what this shit is about.
He said he'll look into it.
Damn it, look in too,
because that's what you're here for.
You're starting to sound
a lot like Halpern.
Maybe you're thinking about
dropping a dime too?
It's cool, brother.
It's cool.
I thought you said you were
close to the seizures dude.
I will be.
Right.
Then I'm waiting on you,
white shadow.
You been holding my daughter
all night for a little graffiti?
Your daughter tags for one of
the most violent gangs in the city.
Not my daughter.
Hi, Mom.
So where should we send the bill?
Still working the garage sting.
Love that.
So I want back in.
Really?
Yeah, you're right.
This new captain,
Farm's where the action is.
But I'll need Army too.
We come as a package.
I can't promise anything,
but I'll grease her wheels.
Thanks.
But that being said, things are
gonna be different now, right?
I'll report to you...
but I answer to her,
just like we talked about.
I can probably make that work.
RAWLING:
Beth Insardi just called.
The DA wants the two of you
on a fresh double murder.
Great. Where are the bodies?
Is the DA's office
assigning cases now?
I expected a smile or two.
What did we do
to deserve this promotion?
I don't catch your meaning.
Whose agenda
were we servicing
by targeting and rolling
a three-plant drug kingpin?
I'm not aware of any agenda.
Right.
VIC:
Shane Vendrell.
The guy who rolled those coyotes.
Yeah.
VIC:
I know we're taking on
new personnel.
Truth is, I could really use
someone like him
working the drug angle
with these gangs.
He made a nice bust today.
But I don't know him very well
other than what's on paper.
A lot of that's bad.
Aceveda hated Shane
as much as he hates me.
That's what that is.
Didn't you two have some problems
bigger than Aceveda?
Well, brothers fight.
Who do you trust more?
So you're vouching for him?
Yeah. He's a great cop.
Okay.
[###]