[BELL JINGLES]
Hey. Take a break.
SHANE:
You ready?
Hey.
Shh.
SHANE:
Is Cromo strapped? Let's find out.
We'll let you take
the first round, sweetheart.
WOMAN:
Yeah. He got a gun,
and it's loaded.
How do you wanna
do this, boss?
SHANE:
Cuff them to something outside.
MAN:
Got it.
Right here, ladies.
[WOMAN MO ANING]
[DEVICE BEEPING]
MAN:
This better be important,
you stupid goddamn bitch.
Sure is,
Let's go.
Hands on your head,
behind your head now.
Come on, corn row, let's go.
You okay?
Two minutes later,
I would've been doing a lot better.
Raping a minor. Doesn't that break
some pimp code of ethics?
Man, she bragged she was 18.
You see, she wanted it.
It's like a Kobe thing.
Yeah?
Looks like you just lost
your endorsement deal.
Let's go, Kobe.
VIC:
What the hell happened, man?
Ah, it's just a scrape.
I'll be okay.
Hey, I miss you
and your guys coming in here.
[LAUGHS]
I figured with all the free meals,
you'd be happy to be rid of us.
I need a favour. Remember Cyril,
the kid that works for me?
Hasn't shown up in a couple of weeks
until this morning.
He ripped off your payroll?
Yeah, I tried to stop him.
Shoved me out of the way.
He only got 30 bucks.
He a rockhead?
Come on, Cal.
Only one thing that turns a good kid
into a thief that fast.
I didn't wanna lead with that.
I was afraid you wouldn't wanna help
if you knew about the drugs.
Oh, and this one I should?
I just thought maybe
you could help me
put him on the straight.
Excuse me. There's a shipment for you.
A bunch of Polaroid cameras.
Oh, uh, stack them
on that desk over there.
RAWLING:
Danny, right?
Yeah. We haven't officially met.
Now we have.
I'm Monica Rawling.
So can I ask
what the cameras are for?
David needs to push
the transition meeting.
Okay.
I didn't see any paperwork
for cameras.
You're leaving
with David, right?
Of course. Why?
No reason.
What are you doing in here?
I'm, uh...
Our... Our men's room doesn't work.
We all share this one.
No, we don't.
Yeah, we... We do. We...
You mean, we don't share with you?
[CHUCKLES]
Uh, somebody in there.
Hey, Dutch Boy's been promoted
to bathroom monitor.
It's a shitty job,
but someone's gotta do it.
[PEOPLE LAUGH]
Big man,
pass these out to the unis.
Seventeen-year-old base chaser.
Anybody sees him,
call me.
All yours.
I got a teenager on a drug tear.
Friend of a friend.
I'll track him down
before he does any damage.
I wanna give you
the heads-up.
You should tell your CO.
Like I said,
I wanna give you a heads-up.
I'm not in charge yet.
Seriously, tell Aceveda.
All right, Social Services
is on the way,
so just wait in the other room,
sweetheart.
Ohhh.
Such a fine line, isn't it?
Amen, brother.
Book him with two of those
and pocket the other one.
It's currency on the street.
We use the blow to buy intel
on the next asshole.
Hm.
You serious?
How'd you think I got Night Train
to give up this place?
Look, it's old school Vice, baby.
Use the world to bust the world.
Hm.
All right.
Hey...
it's all good in the 'hood,
brother.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
Sorry, Nance.
The Mexican authorities
sent him back.
I got the call this morning.
Can I help you?
Yeah, we're here
to ID Ben Gilroy.
You family?
Wife and, uh, friend.
Give me a minute.
[CLEARS THROAT]
How are the girls taking it?
Haven't told them yet.
They can barely wrap their brains
around him leaving the first time.
Yeah.
Follow me, please.
Nance, you don't have
to see him this way.
I just don't wanna feel sorry
for the piece of shit.
Federales found him with a bunch
of fake Mexican IDs
and an expired
California driver's licence.
Benjamin Wescott Gilroy?
Shit.
That a positive ID?
How'd he die?
Take your pick.
Cirrhosis, malnutrition.
Official cause was suffocation.
Aspirated on his own vomit.
Christ, this guy
was the assistant police chief?
What happened?
Take your pick.
[###]
SHANE:
Hai-yee!
[SOUTHERN ACCENT]
Pimp's in the Barn,
and we having a ho down!
[PEOPLE LAUGH]
MAN:
It is the lord of the Vice.
Just here to brighten up your day,
you bunch of sad little desk monkeys.
RAWLING:
Who's the cowboy?
A guy I used to run with. He jumped
over to Vice, Central Bureau.
Guessing by the look on your face,
it ended shit-side up.
No, just haven't seen him
for a while.
How's that new partner
working out?
It clicks.
Yeah, I gotta get back to this.
Yeah, get to it.
Cyril's got two juvie hearings
pending.
One for crack cocaine
and the other's for public lewdness.
Getting head
on a bench in Griffith Park.
The head attached to a name?
Oh, she fled.
Cops got a description.
Uh...
Slight, blond,
piercings, early 20s.
You know what?
I spoke
to the Jesus-whacked mom.
Her address is different
than the one he gave
when he got busted in the park,
could be the blond's place.
Phew.
You know,
it's strange.
Clubhouse
being this way.
Yeah. Thanks for unsealing this.
It's cool.
Hey, heard about Gilroy.
Yeah, burial's tomorrow.
It'd be great if you could make it.
I'm trying to give him
a decent send off.
Is, uh, Shane going?
I don't know.
WOMAN:
211 in progress,
Darmond Wash 'n' Go. 612 Ames Street.
MAN:
Hands up!
MAN 2:
Untangled 13. Code 6.
[GUNSHOTS]
MAN: Stop! Police!
MAN 3: Don't move. Don't move.
MAN: Second shooter ran out the back.
Cover this.
On the ground now.
Hang on. Okay, stay still.
Just stay still.
I have an update on the Garage Sting
that I think you two might wanna hear.
Who's that with him?
Lewis Sperling,
guy we flipped to give us the sting.
Other than a few busts
in the first month,
our cameras haven't
turned up anything.
No major deals,
no major connections.
I can't control
what folks say and do.
ACEVEDA:
You played us, Lewis.
Set up another corporation
in your daughter's name.
That's a violation of the terms
of your deal.
I got two ex-wives, five kids.
I can't mak e a living with
you guys perpetually up my ass.
Maybe Mackey couldn't figure out
how you were end-running us, but I did.
You tipped off big-fish clients.
They gave you seed money
to start a new company.
You got your income back,
they got a new place to launder cash.
Jesus...
how'd you miss this?
I'll give you
more names.
From the new business.
Bigger guys.
I don't think so, Lewis.
It's over.
And now you're going to jail.
[SIGHS]
Six months and thousands
of tax dollars pissed away.
At least now we know why.
I dropped the ball.
Little late
for the humble-servant routine.
I'll set up the collars on the ones
we have, make sure it gets done right.
Oh, and you're the man
to do it right?
Just let him fix
the problem, okay?
Sir, there are two people dead
at that laundromat robbery.
One of them's
an officer-involved shooting.
Shit. What do we know?
Two suspects. Looks like
a Hispanic male and a white female.
Do we have a description
of the shooters?
Just the girl, she's one of the DOAs.
Blond, pierced nose, 120 pounds.
What?
This shooting might have something
to do with the kid that I'm looking for.
Your wayward juvie's
tied in with a 187?
If you're trying to win me over,
it's not working.
Little Bonnie and Clyde
shot and killed the manager
for $11 in quarters.
The boy got away.
You pull a name and address
on the girl?
Hope Anthony. 9246 East Olympic.
Goddamn it.
Problem?
You got that Xerox picture
of Cyril on you?
DANNY: Yeah.
Run it by the witnesses.
Hey, I, uh, think the other shooter's
this kid I've been looking for.
Unbelievable. Putting cops at risk
by running this off the grid?
I didn't have all the facts...
Well, at least you're consistent.
Give information
on the kid to Billings
and finish closing out
the Garage Sting.
It sounded like you had something
more you wanted to share up there.
What if I did? Who are you?
Captain Rawling.
Aceveda's on his way out.
I'll be deciding
what happens in the Barn.
Well, I got a name will spin
your pretty little head around.
Well, my pretty little head
doesn't spin that easy.
Who is it?
I want my deal back in place.
No jail time.
That deal got flushed
with your corporate switcheroo.
You gotta put something real
on the table,
or the DA won't even take my call.
No deal, no name.
No problem then.
There he is.
Yeah.
It's me.
I just messengered you a package.
Is it ticking?
Sort of.
It's a class-action lawsuit against
Pyren Merril Pharmaceutical Company.
What's that got to do with us?
Well, it claims that the rise in autism
is due to a vaccine preservative.
Vaccines that both Matthew
and Megan got when they were 2.
Well, that was right around when...
I know. I know.
There's a deadline. We need
to sit down, talk with the lawyer.
Okay. How about tomorrow morning
when I drop off Cassy?
Great. I'll set it up,
and I will see you then. Bye.
Armando Renta, this is Vic Mackey.
Good to meet you.
Army's fresh off a 14-month roll
in Shock and Awe.
Gave those sand pigs a little taste
of the red, white and brown.
Mission accomplished?
That's what they told us.
So it must be true.
How you like running with Wild Bill?
Beats going door to door
in Baghdad.
Now it's hick and the spic.
That's clever.
Can you give us a minute?
So, um, what's up?
We need to know who's running crack
in Ashmore Heights these days.
That's hard to say. Last few weeks,
someone's flooded the market.
Every pusher in the hood's rock-heavy,
scrambling to unload product.
Since when do you need help
powder tracking?
You hear about Gilroy?
What, is he back in town?
Yeah, spilling his guts
at the morgue.
Drank himself to death.
They're gonna bury him tomorrow,
you should be there.
I wanted the guy dead.
Well, you got your wish.
This is about his wife and kids now.
You forgetting he threatened
your family? He hung you out to IAD?
Money and pussy
make man do evil shit.
But before all that,
he was a friend.
Some bodies in blue
should show respect.
I'll see if I can
shake myself free.
So we, uh, done?
I, uh...
I got some worries about what I saw
over at Dead-Eye's the other night.
Well, stop worrying.
Dead-Eye was about to start
C.I. duties for me.
Tracking Antwon Mitchell's new game,
until someone tapped his mute button.
Now I'm watching Antwon.
So if you got
any kind of relationship...
I got no relationship with him.
Then I got no problem.
ARMANDO:
Everything cool?
Yeah, it's all good. You ready?
It's gonna take two, maybe three days
to lay a new piece of pipe.
Get started.
I wanna hear flushing in 48 hours.
What's going on?
Having the men's room repaired.
I didn't fix the men's room
'cause it would've chewed up
35% of our budget.
That's my worry now.
Plumbing crews, cameras.
Either you're completely naïve
about our financial constraints,
which I doubt,
or you've got something planned.
I'm instituting seizures...
across the board:
cars, houses, businesses.
Anything drug or gang-related.
Asset forfeiture?
The chief will never go...
It's already signed on.
Pol Com too.
Citizens here can't afford lawyers
to fight seized assets.
He's not worried
about pissing off dealers
'cause we swiped
their pimp rides.
We're gonna target
the right people.
And you're thinking of
using Mackey for this?
[SCOFFS]
I'm still deciding.
I mean, your letter
made him untradeable.
I have to use him somewhere.
Keep him parked inside.
Anything else is dangerous.
Trust me.
Appreciate your input.
MAN:
I need a signature to start the work.
ACEVEDA:
So why is this the first
I'm hearing about all this?
Oh, it happened fast. Thanks.
Anyway, after tomorrow
it's mine to win or lose.
She was unconscious when they
brought her in. Fishnets, spandex.
I don't think
she was out walking her dog.
Hooker rape?
The name she put on her form
is Olive Martini.
This is the only thing
that she had on her.
Ralph's card. That's official.
She's in 6.
I'll go see if she's shaken or stirred.
Oh, you know what? Test results aren't
gonna be in until this afternoon.
I usually, uh, grab a taco
across the street.
From Rullio's?
We treat at least four cases of food
poisoning a week from that place.
It got an A in the window.
Stands for acute gastritis.
CLAUDETTE:
Did you say Room 6?
Olive has left the building.
DUTCH:
Okay.
James has got a family friend,
thinks you two would hit it off.
Really?
She does public-affairs work. Smart.
For some reason,
she likes cops.
What's she look like?
Petite, dark-skinned, attractive.
She black?
Never mind.
What?
l... I dated a black girl in college.
Quarter black.
I mean, you could definitely tell.
Forget it. What's on the raped
hooker's grocery card?
Uh... No address, bogus phone number.
Hey, if James
thinks we should...
What hooker?
Paramedics took her over
to Mission Cross.
She was beaten,
sexually assaulted.
Gave a fake name
and disappeared.
Did you have hospital personnel
go through the mug books?
No.
Where did
the attack happen?
We don't know yet.
Is there anything
you do know?
Last week, she bought 3 gallons
of Chablis and 11 boxes of condoms.
If she's pissed off a pimp,
her life could be in danger.
Why don't you see
if anyone's called it in to 911?
Transport's running late.
You'll miss lunch call at county.
You think my price
is a couple of candy bars?
Maybe you think better
on a full stomach.
I'm thinking fine.
I called the DA.
They won't budge
without a name first.
Looks like we got ourselves
an old-fashioned stalemate.
Yeah, I guess so.
Except I'm going home
to a warm bed tonight.
You go home to them.
Got a 911 call came in
from a payphone outside
a Korean bakery.
They were robbed 11 times
last year. They installed
state-of-the-art surveillance.
Cameras picked this up
early this morning.
[MAN GRUNTING,
WOMAN WHIMPERING]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
We have the face of our victim.
And the back of a rapist's head.
Make some dubs of that tape.
The DA's gonna need a copy.
And let me know
when you locate her.
ANTWON:
Clear that out...
VIC:
Hey, yo.
What are you building,
Antwon?
You here to pitch in?
Forgot my tool belt at home.
Still got my cuffs though.
Ah. House was in foreclosure.
Crackheads took it over,
so we took it back.
Helped the owners
get back on their feet.
MLK to Jimmy Carter.
You got all your bases covered,
don't you?
I got work to do, man.
Hey, we're looking
for this kid.
Put the word out to your dealers.
Give me a heads-up if he tries to score.
I run a rec centre.
Just because you pound nails
into some poor slob's house
doesn't mean shit to me.
We both know you run drugs,
not a rec centre.
All right.
My next step,
I start sweating the slangers.
Those pussies always give up
chain of command.
I wanna eradicate the crack epidemic
as much as you, man,
but my relationship to...
[PHONE RINGS]
Hold that lie.
Yeah?
Beauty. Hang on.
Lem may have a lead
on Cyril's drug dealer.
That gives you 20 minutes to find me
a short cut to this missing kid
before I start twisting the truth
out of his dealer.
There he is on the black bike.
Right there.
BO Y:
Cops!
You little dick!
Park the Schwinn, shithead.
This is why
you should always wear a helmet.
VIC:
Where'd he go? Where?
Ran out the back.
Hey, put that shit down.
Goddamn it. He swallowed.
Shit. Come here.
[GRUNTING]
Goddamn it.
You sell to him? Did you?
Did you?
You know what,
he seems a little bound up.
He bought a crumb from me
a couple hours ago.
Asshole paid in quarters.
Where's he now?
Don't know,
never sold to him before.
VIC: Bullshit.
He ain't a regular. That's the truth.
I swear to God, man.
I swear. I swear.
Get on your feet.
Hey, clean up, Aisle 4.
You're really gonna set up
your office down here.
I feel more at home on the floor
with the grunts.
For someone
who's supposed to be observing,
you sure are awfully active.
I saw you chatting
with Lewis Sperling.
Just trying to talk some sense
into him while he's still ours.
I closed down the Garage Sting.
Your instincts
six months ago were right.
It's got great potential.
It just took a wrong turn.
It's been compromised.
It's dead.
The AG C angle, yes.
But the new business
that Lewis set up is untainted.
You got a good system in place,
we own the spyware.
We get the bugs in the cars.
We're back in business.
Yeah. You don't have the authority yet
to be interviewing suspects,
getting the goddamn toilet fixed
or overturning my decisions.
So until you're actually
in my office... observe.
ACEVEDA:
That the kid you almost choked out
with a bottle mustard?
Who ratted, the condiment weasel?
Kid's a novice.
He was swallowing open jums of crack.
I induced vomiting.
Saved his goddamn life.
I'm still allowed
to save lives, right?
I want a complete report.
Oh, sure. Have one for you
the day after tomorrow.
Oh, that's right. You'll be gone.
I'll mail one to you.
We can't post these in the Barn.
Looks like the department sanctioned
people to attend the funeral.
It's just a flier.
LEM:
Cyril forged you this cheque
from his boss's restaurant.
This bounced, man.
Kid didn't even write this anyway.
It was this blond t-girl.
She said she worked there.
VIC:
Is this her?
Shit.
VIC: That's her?
Yeah.
She's a tranny?
She tried to blow me to cover it.
I ain't down with
that "chicks with dicks" shit.
So I said no,
she came with the cheque.
So where did he-she score from you?
I ain't saying no more, man.
You saw what I could do
with a bottle of mustard.
You imagine me with
the butt of a gun. Huh?
Underhell.
Underhell?
Under the tile factory
by the freeway.
VIC:
All right, thanks.
Coroner just confirmed it.
Hope had a rope.
Here we go.
MAN: Jesus.
MAN 2: There's a cop.
There!
MAN: Gun!
Hold on, hold your fire.
He's dry firing, the gun's empty.
Cyril, drop the gun, kid. Cyril!
Cyril! Put the gun down, kid.
All right, Cyril, that's it.
It's over, come on.
On your feet. Get up.
Come on, kid.
[SOBBING]
Look, I done nothing wrong.
I don't know why Barbie and Skipper
hauled my ass down here.
DUTCH:
They... found you tricking.
We just wanna know
what happened to you.
Yeah, like you're real concerned.
I was walking to the market.
Someone jumped me.
Woke up in the ER.
We have security tape
that shows the assault, Olive.
Then go arrest the prick.
We can't identify him.
Me either, then.
DUTCH:
Hey, Olive's prints came back.
Real name, Olivia Kenshaw.
She's mapped.
Restricted from the zone
where she was raped.
And she's HIV positive.
How long
have you been tricking sick?
I don't know. Ten months.
Risk is hype.
Make all my customers strap up.
What about the guy who raped you?
Was he using a condom?
He wanted it. He got it.
What about all the innocent people
he could infect?
Please.
They should all die sore and ugly.
We just need his name
or a description.
And I just need a pussy
ain't so stretched.
You've been mapped with HIV, Olivia.
State considers that
attempted murder.
You'll do real time.
CLAUDETTE:
Do you know how hard it is
to get the cocktail inside?
If I give him up,
I want the other charges dropped.
I could ask the DA.
I want some kind of guarantee,
and I want it in writing.
DA will never go for it. She's got
a four-page sheet, mapped with HIV.
You mean, the DA will never go for it
because it's our case.
Well, that doesn't help.
I'll go play good cop.
I already played good cop.
I'll play better cop.
What's that about?
Captain-hooker confidentiality.
[SCOFFS]
So, uh, what's James' friend's name?
Forget it.
Just because I asked if she was black,
doesn't mean I'm a racist.
And there are plenty of sisters
I think are hot.
Halle Berry, uh, Tyra Banks.
Beyoncé.
[LAUGHING]
What?
VIC:
Cyril, who put you on the rock,
Cyril? Who's your main score?
Fat Benish.
Where can I find
Fat Benish?
Where, Cyril?
Above Pip's Quick Lube.
Ronnie, Cyril's dealer
is a cat named Benish.
He lives above the Quick Lube
on Hauser. Get a warrant.
Is he making sense yet?
Eh, he's pretty doped up.
He's detoxing.
Cop downstairs said it was
the other shooter that killed
the woman at the laundromat.
That clears Cyril.
He was part of the robbery.
Makes it his murder too.
He didn't know what he was doing.
It's that shit rock. What about
the guy that sold him the crack?
I'm taking care of his dealer.
Look, he's gonna be asleep for a while.
Why don't you go home, get some rest?
I wanna be here when he wakes up.
I think you're in a lot of pain.
I don't need pity.
Not pity.
Compassion.
Even if you don't think
you're worthy of it.
We're guilty of
perpetuating that.
Letting the streets
take care of themselves.
[SCOFFS]
Got that right.
Can you tell me
what happened?
You seen the tape.
I did.
And I am so sorry.
He was at the end
of an all-nighter.
Paid for a suck.
Got me in the back alley.
Threw the first punch
before I could hit my knees.
[TEARFULLY]
It was all about the hurt
with this guy.
Hey, I see you got our ho basket.
ARMANDO:
It's a nice addition to your stable.
Don't know if they worth a thing.
SHANE:
Let me tell you how this works.
You and the syphilis brigade
see anything, hear anything,
new players, new product,
anything happens on the street,
I'm your first call.
Got that?
SHANE:
All right, Venus, you come with us.
What for?
To suck his big Latin dick.
[SHANE LAUGHS]
This ain't for real.
It's the only way to establish
dominance with these slit mongers.
Tail's the only currency they know.
Then let her suck you off.
Come on, man, I'm married.
Look, you got an ED thing
happening, just say so.
Blow me.
I'll let her. Come on, sweetheart.
Now just sit back and relax, all right?
Enjoy the ride.
You getting some back-alley Clinton
is really gonna help the cause.
Two's a mouthful,
three's a crowd.
Yeah.
Man, Venus is going at it
like she's taking rust off a low-rider.
That's some Boss Hogg bullshit,
man.
Let's talk percentages.
Percentages?
Yeah.
Keeping you and your girls
out of lockup is gonna
require additional man hours.
That's gonna cost you 10 percent.
That wasn't part of the deal.
Yeah, well, make no mistake.
There is no deal here.
This is you doing what I say,
or else you getting a cap
in the back of your ear
and something we like to call
"in the line of duty."
Now, sit back down.
If you're dicking us around again,
not only won't you get your deal,
we'll make sure
you do your time in Solano.
Warden's a friend of mine.
You think the inmates are bad?
Wait till you spend some happy time
with the guards.
[VIC CHUCKLING]
Alex Kozodav.
The taxi king?
VIC:
Old school Russian mob.
Any other cab tries to pick up
a fare in Farmington,
both car and driver end up
stolen and chopped.
SPERLING:
Ever since the Armenian money train
got jacked,
the Russians have been looking
for another place to launder their cash.
And you've been
more than willing to help for a fee.
I'm also putting radios in his cars.
You ever see Taxicab Confessions?
Kozi cabs
are the Russian's favourites.
A lot of potential marks.
Well, I'll see
if there's a deal to be made.
Signed, sealed and deceitful.
Bring him in, you can release her.
Bust her again, it's attempted murder.
Make sure she's clear on that.
Got it.
CLAUDETTE:
Thanks for running interference for us.
My pleasure.
Another win for Billings.
Okay, Olivia, let's take a look
at some of our mug shots
of known sexual offenders.
He's white, pierced tongue,
delivers pizza.
Has one of those pizza-shack things
on the top of his car.
I just talked with Lewis.
Apparently, his ride
left without him?
Lewis' name.
Alex Kozodav.
L.A. boss,
Russian organized crime.
This guy's
on everybody's top 10 list.
The DA wants to play ball.
I think you are making decisions
to settle a grudge.
Decisions I'm gonna
have to live with.
These property seizures
that you want to impose,
who's gonna have to live
with those decisions?
I could've let Lewis get lost
in the system for a couple of days,
taken the credit
when you were gone.
But you've earned this.
I figured we could... present it
to the chief together.
I'll take a look at it.
[SIRENS WAILING]
VIC:
Shit!
God!
Somebody torched Benish's place.
God.
Hey, chief.
Hey, I got a warrant to search upstairs.
Pretty hot in there right now.
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
Any way of putting it down?
I doubt it.
We've already lost
a couple of blowers.
All right. Thanks.
Hey, who owns the bikes?
Fat guy. He lives there.
You sure?
You don't forget
a 300-pound dude on a scooter.
VIC:
Check the plates.
MAN:
Oh, man.
VIC:
What's the matter, fat man?
You got insurance, don't you?
MAN:
Yeah, I'm in real good hands.
VIC:
It's too bad about your little
crack factory upstairs.
What's that smell? Oh, yeah.
You got smoke.
[LAUGHS]
I ran the VIN numbers
on your scooters.
Stolen the same night
six other bikes got jacked.
I got grand theft.
Antwon Mitchell, he the one filling
the cesspool with new rock?
Rumour is, Mr. Mitchell's
walking the straight and narrow now.
Oh, it's gonna be hard
maintaining that edge in the joint
when gen pop finds out
you're the little red scooter bandit.
There's been a crack flood 'cause
everybody's dumping what they got.
Why?
It's getting pushed out.
Crack's bad business.
Cluckers all crazy, die fast,
strip a hood of its potential.
Pushed out for what?
Tar.
Heroin?
Sleepers hold a job.
Less crime, less heat,
everybody wins.
Antwon the one
enforcing that mandate?
That part of
his community salvation?
Ain't no salvation here.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah?
SHANE:
Look ed into Ashmore.
Niners used to have the lion's share,
but since this new product hit town,
it's real messy.
It ain't new product.
It's old.
The street's dumping all their crack
to make way for tar heroin.
Who told you that?
A guy with weight.
I'll see you.
Try to mak e it to the funeral.
Vic, inspector says it started
with a grease fire.
What? Engine grease?
Cooking grease.
Shit.
VIC:
How many more pictures of this kid
I might find if I start opening drawers?
What are you talking about?
I care about him.
Guy dealing to Cyril,
his place got torched tonight.
Fire was started
with cooking grease.
You're not a very good criminal, Cal.
I smell the smoke.
Please don't make me
search the place.
You screwing this kid?
Don't say that.
Are you?
He slept here.
But I never laid a hand on him.
He wanted to get the operation
when he turned 18.
I told him I'd pay for it.
We were... We were gonna be together.
Jesus Christ!
[TEARFULLY]
I'm sorry.
l... I know it was wrong.
You could've hurt someone
setting that fire, Cal!
Nobody was home.
That dealer took away
the only thing I love.
You know what that feels like?
[SNIFFLING]
[SIGHS]
Call a lawyer.
When the detectives come,
don't say anything.
Get rid of the photos.
The dresses too.
MAN:
Thimerosal has been used as
a vaccine preservative since the '30s,
even though
it's 49 percent mercury.
Which is extremely toxic,
especially with children under 3.
And you think this mercury
in the vaccine is the missing link?
The increase
in the rate of autism
parallels the rise
in thimerosal exposure,
all broken down
in the science there.
Wha...? They're just
figuring this out now?
Look, forgive the hard press,
but the statute of limitations
is running out on Matthew.
You have only three years
from the time of diagnosis to file a suit.
Okay.
There's no legal fees, Mr. Mackey.
We only collect if we win the case.
But expert witness costs
are expensive.
Ten to $15,000 per child.
[SCOFFS]
Jesus.
MAN:
Yeah. Well, you got a lot
to think about,
so, uh, why don't you take some time
and let me know what you decide?
I know someone should pay.
ACEVEDA:
And that's it.
I can't think of anything else
I need to tell you.
You seem to have strong opinions
on how you wanna do things.
Okay.
Well...
we can tell the bosses
we had our transition meeting.
Thanks.
Oh, there is one more thing.
I spoke to Chief Bankston.
He seems to be excited
at the prospect
of netting Alex Kozodav.
So the Garage Sting
will stay up and running.
Did my name come up?
Oh, I don't believe so.
But Vic's name did.
Chief wants him running the project,
which keeps him on a tight leash.
You'll thank me for that.
[BAGPIPES PLAYING
"AMAZING GRACE"]
[WOMAN SOBBING]
Sorry for your loss.
Excuse me.
You didn't have to come.
I knew Ben a little...
in better years.
Yeah, me too.
Puts everyday bullshit
in perspective.
I told Aceveda about Kozodav.
He went behind my back,
got the chief pregnant on the idea.
Took credit,
covered his ass.
He also convinced the chief
that you should still run the Sting.
Means I gotta find someone else
to head up the task force.
I can do both.
Look... Ronnie knows the drill,
he can handle the Garage stuff.
Put me back on the street
with the unis.
Nobody knows the bangers
better than I do.
Please.
Put me somewhere
where I can make a dent.
The only way
I can sell that to the chief
is I give Internal Affairs
full access to the Barn.
Open house.
Means you can play hard, but...
I get it.
IAD gets a whiff of anything dirty
near these seizures,
me, this policy, everything,
it's dead in the water.
I'll do it right.
Okay.
NANCE [TEARFULLY]:
Go to the car. Go on.
I know that, uh, you're the one
that got this turnout.
Means a lot to my girls.
He was my oldest friend.
You doing okay?
I hope he was scared and alone
and in a lot of pain.
He had his demons, Nance.
He had a dick he couldn't keep
in his pants.
Threw away 20 years on the job.
He shit all over this family.
[###]
[DROPKICK MURPHYS'
"AMAZING GRACE" PLAYING]
RAWLING:
Just right there.
That's really nice.
Have one.
ACEVEDA:
Hey.
Thank you.
MAN: All right.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[CHEERING & APPLAUSE]
MAN:
We gave you Cromo
and his underage hit.
But the girls, that was Antwon
paying back a favour.
You, you taking a piece,
that makes him look the fool.
Yeah? You tell the great reformist
that's the cost of doing business.
Doesn't work that way.
What doesn't work
is me finding out second-hand
about dealers dumping crack
to make room for tar.
I don't know nothing
about that, man.
Yeah, course you wouldn't.
You're just his slow-witted bitch.
What?
Oh, shit.
Just relax, policeman.
Chill.
It's just a beeper.
Just a beeper, all right?
From now on, it's me and you
face-to-face or nothing at all,
you got that?
You got that?!
[###]