MAN 1:
Lot number 149.
2004 Cadillac Escalade EXT.
Black, leather interior.
Bidding starts at $22,000.
MAN 2: Twenty-two.
AUCTIONEER: Twenty-two. I have 23?
Anybody say 24? Twenty-four.
How about 25? I have 25.
Twenty-six? Twenty-six. How about 27?
Twenty-seven, 27.
Twenty-seven. How about 28,
28, 28, 28? Twenty-nine, 29?
VIC:
Sucks I didn't bring my chequebook.
AUCTIONEER:
How about thirty, 30?
Laverneous'd pop if he knew
all these whiteys were
scoping out his ride.
I put ads in El Clasificado,
and The Sentinel.
But apparently only the Times
crowd was interested.
AUCTIONEER:
Who wants to go 31?
Thirty-one? Going, going.
Sold. Thirty-one thousand dollars.
Okay, now we have lot number 611.
I did a little show and tell
for the city attorney
last night.
She sign off on the injunctions?
One-Niners are
Antwon Mitchell's
foot soldiers.
And these injunctions
are gonna keep them off
the street pushing dope.
He's gonna feel
the pressure.
Well, he's already feeling it.
This is gonna jack up the pain.
AUCTIONEER:
Seventeen thousand dollars.
Okay, next item. Lot number 684.
Yamaha motorcycle,
minimal damage.
SHANE:
All right, let's make this quick.
We gotta clock in to the boss.
You forget
I'm your boss?
What do you need?
This address.
Chink heron dealer.
Hear a shipment came in
last night.
And you don't
like competitors.
You know, Bill Gates has his hit,
I got mine.
Yeah, and busting dealers
is ours, so sure.
All right,
we'll pay a visit.
Do our part
to keep the, uh, black tar
monopoly safe.
Plus, I'm gonna need
half his inventory.
We're good on demand,
but light on supply
because of your intel failure.
We give you information,
we don't move product,
get hung up in your shit.
Hey.
I'll beep you when
we got the stuff.
Bitch with a badge
doing my bidding.
It's a wonderful day.
[ANTWON CHUCKLING]
MONICA: As you know,
we had our first auction
this morning.
Try to keep your jaws off the floor.
We raised over $900,000.
I guess taking houses
is profitable.
That's money out of
the bad guys' hands,
and back into the community.
Yeah, and a third
comes to us.
Now, that's not the
only good news.
Officers Sofer and Lowe
have done a fantastic job
documenting the One-Niners.
Thanks to their hard work,
we got injunctions.
After we serve these, you see
two or more One-Niners
together in Farmington,
that's called congregating
in groups, and that's jail time.
One-Niners are just the beginning,
so let's get these served
by the end of the day.
Match the glamour shots
to the injunctions.
You have any questions,
get in touch with Danny
or Julien.
Can't find them,
come to me.
MONICA:
Thanks, everyone.
VIC:
Any word on the girl?
Talked to Angie's friends,
kids at school. No one's
seen her, off the map.
Her mom goes
in the ground tomorrow.
Girl checks in once a week.
Now nothing.
Talking about Angie?
Yeah.
You speak to the family
in Georgia?
She, um, she hasn't been back
to her apartment,
didn't, um, pack any bags.
What if Antwon Mitchell
found out Angie gave up
the cul-de-sac bust?
That would have
to come from here.
You ran that.
Is there any chance
that word got out?
None.
I'm glad to hear IAD cleared
you on the shooting.
LEMONHEAD:
Yeah. Thanks for the word you put in.
Your CO's anxious
to get you back.
I took personal time
the rest of the week
to look for Angie.
Let me know what you find.
All right.
Come here.
What the hell was that?
Shane is slipping
inside info to Antwon.
Angie goes missing the night
we take his distribution centre.
She fingered.
And I'm supposed to pretend
those two things aren't related?
Shane wouldn't give up
a girl to that.
He's down for stealing,
planting evidence...
We're all part of that.
But he would have been down.
We hadn't been there
to rein in his shit.
On his own,
we got no idea
what he would do.
We're keeping Shane
out of trouble. Making noises
to my boss doesn't help.
He didn't do this.
I'll look around
and make sure of it.
You keep looking
for Angie.
[###]
MAN 1: Catch the ball.
MAN 2: Come on, that's right.
[SIREN WAILS]
VIC:
Oh, you knuckleheads
make it way too easy.
RONNIE:
Game's over. Against the fence.
Get against the fence right now.
Move. Move your ass.
RONNIE: You.
VIC: Face me.
We was just balling.
Yeah?
Well, from now on, T-Gun,
a cop sees you so much
as playing with your own dicks
in the same room,
you're going to County.
Oh, this one's for you, Notch.
It's called an injunction.
You're all documented
members of a known
criminal organization.
Judge thinks you're
domestic terrorists, ladies.
I ain't no sheet-head.
Yeah, just a shithead.
Injunctions are
zero tolerance.
That means no associating
with known bangers.
No hanging with homeys,
no riding together.
REX:
Wait, hold on,
hold on, hold on.
So you trying to say
it's illegal for me to hang out
with my own brother?
He your real brother?
FROGG Y: Yeah.
Like we came out
the same vagina.
Well, the court says
you're One-Niners first.
I mean, what you all think,
we banging 24l7?
JULIEN:
It's not up to me.
VIC:
All right, see who we got.
I'll tell the bartender
his One-Niner clientele's
banned.
Yo, all right, police,
you know the dance.
You know the dance.
Buy me a damn drink!
VIC: Jesus, shit.
MAN: Let's go.
You're gonna buy me a drink, bitch.
Break it up. Break it up.
I'm DEA.
What?
I'm undercover.
You bust this place,
you're gonna screw it up.
Get off me, pig!
Hold it right there!
VIC: Don't shoot. I got him.
He should be here and let go!
I got him.
Ah!
It's okay. This is the guy
that Billings was looking for
on that 211.
All right, come on,
asshole. Come on.
Hospital says that alky
you knocked around
barely has a bruise.
Drunks are like
super balls.
Bounce them off the floors,
they never get a scratch.
I'll have to remember that one.
Credentials cleared.
Agent Hendricks
say what he was doing
at Lucky's?
Couldn't tell you
if I wanted to.
How long you been
on the One-Niners?
A while.
Obviously, we're tilling
the same ground.
One-Niner heroin trade,
probably Antwon Mitchell too.
I'm just a guy on the street.
Say I talked to the guy
in the corner office?
HENDRICKS:
You'd have to be
pretty convincing.
Give me a name.
I'll work on my sales pitch.
Federal investigations
take precedence.
We say keep away
from that bar,
you better do it.
We can help you.
You don't even have working lights.
I'm bringing the place
into the 21 st century.
Rewiring, high-speed internet.
VIC:
Meanwhile, here's
the low-tech version.
You guys are into the One-Niners.
We know everything about them.
Ink, homeys, drug dens.
MONICA:
The bangers know
we're plugged into them.
We do the bust for you,
get the heroin off the street.
You get closer to Antwon Mitchell,
and your agent's cover
isn't compromised.
You're making
a lot of assumptions.
The DEA's set up
on a One-Niner bar.
One-Niners are front
and centre in the tar trade.
I'm a local, not a moron.
Antwon never sees the light
of day again, I host the party.
LAMBERTl:
One-Niners have been trading
stolen cars for tar heroin.
Pipeline runs between L.A.
and El Salvador.
VIC:
Tar comes from Mexico.
LAMBERTl:
It's grown there,
imported through El Salvador.
Salvadoran named Spider's
the go-between with the bangers.
Has a garage of stolen Camrys
on Broadway.
How'd the El Salvadorans
get hooked up
with the One-Niners?
Antwon. Back in Lompoc,
he took advantage
of some bad blood.
Made an alliance
with the Salvadorans
against the Mexicans.
They are still tight.
You know where he unloads?
Four months, no clue.
Slips us every time
we get close.
MONICA:
So we use my people
to bust the garage,
convince Spider to share
where he takes the drugs.
Work up the chain
from there.
I'll have some unis
round up Spider's family
for leverage.
It's a good bet most
of them are illegals.
So we're clear.
This is my op.
You screw it up...
Wouldn't do that to you.
Antwon was some
Iraqi National Guard
general,
we'd wait till he was
all tucked in bed
having a real nice dream,
and then cluster bomb his ass.
Worst thing we could do
is take a straight shot.
Not till we know where
he's keeping that girl's body.
No, we gotta be patient.
[DOOR OPENS]
Captain's got something
cooking with DEA.
Wants us all on it.
Fed bullshit?
No, I think we'll pass.
Captain's orders.
You wanna skate,
you talk to her yourself.
Hey, Vic,
your nanny is here.
Cass, everything okay?
You still feeling sick, kid?
Mr. Vic,
I'm very sorry.
My girl,
she's having a baby.
I thought that was next month?
Baby come early.
Problems, I think.
Do you understand,
right?
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
It's okay.
Thank you.
VIC:
Come on, honey.
CASSID Y:
Sorry, Dad.
VIC:
No, that's okay, sweetie.
Not your fault.
Who's this?
Cassidy. She's feeling
a little under the weather.
This is my boss,
Captain Rawling.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Why don't you take
her home?
I'll have Shane take the lead
on Spider.
No, no, no,
I got it covered.
I just have to call
my backup sitter.
Your dad is
very dedicated.
ANTWON:
Why are you letting
that bald cracker-ass
run my boys off they corners
with this injunction shit, huh?
They ain't hardly
earning.
I can only wrap my arms
around so much.
Injunctions are coming
from the top.
Maybe a brick of China white
will ease the pain.
Fresh from
your Asian friends.
I don't touch
the stuff.
There is something else.
An El Salvadoran named Spider
showed up on the radar.
So you got business with him,
shut it down.
Cat named Verdice may show up
on the same radar.
Make sure you shut
that down.
All right.
Pick up your trash.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
SHANE [ON PHONE]: It's me.
VIC:
Where the hell have you been?
SHANE:
Checking out
Spider's casita.
VIC: What, for the last half hour?
It takes as long as it takes.
All right, well, Spider drove up
about 10 minutes ago.
Feel like doing some work?
Let's tear down
the web then.
Let's go.
Hey, get down!
Drop the bag!
Get down right now!
Get down!
Don't move.
Clear!
MAN: Clear!
VIC:
Whoa! Spider send in more than
just cars back to the homeland.
You get a shit load
a tar with those.
El Salvador, they got AK's
up the ass, all the guerrillas.
But handguns, they're like
tight pussy. Rare and precious.
VIC:
All right, let's pop the trunks,
see what else we can find.
SHANE:
Here.
Nothing.
Hey.
Wetback's got
some greenbacks.
Holy shit.
RONNIE:
How much you
think that is?
VIC:
Hundred grand
or more.
Let's call it in.
You know, you have
to talk to me eventually.
Victim was Raine Powell.
Worked down the street
at Electronics Emporium.
What's this?
SCOOBY: Just what it looks like.
Wasn't us. Talk to him.
I knew you'd wanna see
where the body was,
so I drew her for you.
Where the body was?
You moved her?
Yeah, the way people come
speeding through,
she would have been a pancake.
Did it ever occur to you
to redirect traffic?
Hey, I used up half
my kid's chalk.
I don't need a thank you,
but how about you get up
off my ass?
CLAUDETTE:
And this is?
BOBO:
Oh, I had to move
the pocketbook too.
You were a big help
in the community meeting
last week.
I mean, a real asset.
JULIEN:
I believed in
what I was saying.
MONICA:
Well, I hope you
still do.
I've heard things.
Maybe some of the minority
officers here aren't so thrilled
with my policies.
Maybe you're one
of them.
Some people feel
like it all sounds good.
But the reality out there
seems a little bit different.
We're arresting bad guys,
just like always.
The way seizures work,
everyone is guilty
until proven innocent.
If we take the wrong car,
it's not like people here
can afford a lawyer.
Well, maybe you can
do something about that.
Look into using seizure money
to start a legal fund.
I guess so. Sure.
It's a work in progress.
This policy isn't
the usual Band-Aid.
Your guys got a location
on Verdice's drug stash.
Grab your partner,
come with.
CLAUDETTE:
Raine have any problems
that you know of?
Man trouble
or money trouble?
No, she was a good girl,
you know.
What about boyfriends?
Just Bear,
but he wouldn't
have done this.
DUTCH: So you saw Raine last night?
BRUCE: I was overseeing a shipment.
She was stuck behind
her computer screen,
like always.
Type A personality.
Familiar.
BRUCE: I told her not to park
down here, but the girl was
a stickler for the policy.
The policy?
Rules say employees can't park
at the store lot. Raine's the only
who ever listened.
She lives with Cornelius Aimes,
a.k.a. Bear, over on Parmer.
Check it out.
See? You're talking to me.
To the extent necessary
to solve this case, yes.
Spider says he dropped off
two keys last night
to a guy named Verdice.
Gonna have dogs
and shooters,
so stay awake. Let's go.
MONICA:
They're in position.
Go when ready.
MAN 1: Clear.
MAN 2: Clear.
Shit.
LAMBERTl:
You sold me on this.
Spider gave us the right location.
This guy, Verdice, got lucky, bailed.
Bullshit. Somebody couldn't
keep their mouth shut,
which is why we don't work
with people like you.
No one leaked anything.
We go to Spider, we find what...
I'm not letting you
near my guy again.
VIC:
I need to borrow this asshole.
Come here.
You got about 30 seconds
to spill your guts.
How tough are you gonna be
when your little brother's
being hacked to pieces?
I don't got no little brother.
Then it must be some
other Juan Emilio I got
back at the station.
It's gonna be bad
when they have to deport
him down south.
You got a lot of enemies.
La Colonia doesn't get him,
the Mexicans will.
Twenty seconds.
Tar that comes to me,
I bring it here.
Most of it Verdice gets
at the church.
The church?
Verdice is a believer, man.
Stuff comes in there,
he takes what he needs.
Keeps the rest safe
with Jesus.
I'm gonna have to scrap
the whole operation,
pull my agent.
Couple of months,
put in a new face.
Where's my informant?
VIC:
Right here, sir.
Thought he might need
to stretch his legs before
he took his ride.
MONICA:
First, Angie fell off our radar.
Now this guy clears out
like he's been tipped off
after I give my word
I'm not gonna screw this up.
What the hell's going on?
Maybe the wrong person
saw us nab Spider,
spread the word.
Doesn't explain
Angie's disappearance.
These were both your operations.
Both of them were successes.
Verdice and the heroin
are still missing, so is Angie.
Lem's out looking for her.
We can still salvage this one.
Spider gave up
his One-Niner contact.
Do I wanna know
how you managed that?
We brought his family in
for leverage, I used it.
If you ask me,
they probably packed up.
You know, cook houses
move all the time.
What did you get
from Spider?
The El Salvadorans
are shipping their drugs
to a church on Avon.
Verdice is a member.
Has his guys as good God-fearing folk.
You're kidding me.
Sounds like Spider sold you a load.
He's not risking his family.
It's the real thing.
I'll work on a warrant.
Let's keep this contained.
The three of us, Army, Ronnie.
That's it, just the people we trust.
All right.
Here,
take this.
CLAUDETTE:
Occurred to me to take that down.
I see Vic's humour
grows more sophisticated
by the day.
Boyfriend wasn't home,
I grabbed Raine's diary.
Seems there were bumps
along the relationship road.
CLAUDETTE:
Detective Huarez in San Antonio's
got a different angle.
He's been tracking murders
in the L.A. area.
Because there aren't
enough in Texas?
Because his suspect
relocated to Farmington
a month ago.
Hey, exposed dick?
Thanks for the warning,
Dutchboy.
CLAUDETTE: Kleavon Gardner,
questioned in four separate
homicides.
Suspected him on two murders
three days apart, then nothing
for six months.
Witnesses placed him
at a couple of the scenes.
But detectives in San Antonio
weren't able to make
anything stick.
Well, what's the connection
to our body?
All the victims were young
black women in public places.
Raine was killed seven blocks
from where Kleavon's sister lives.
Are we gonna be like this
from now on?
Huarez tried to warn
somebody in this department
a few weeks ago
that we had a thrill killer
on our hands.
Thrill killers need the juice,
they take chances.
This guy's patient,
an opportunity killer.
No wonder San Antonio PD
screwed it up.
Get your profiles right,
people.
Whatever he is,
I'm going to
introduce myself.
Oh, what?
I'm not coming with?
Stick to your
True Confessions.
San Antonio police interviewed
you 11 times.
They got you killing everybody
but Osama.
What I don't get is,
why you? They got no DNA,
they got no prints.
Any excuse to fry
a brother.
Justice, Texas-style?
You said it.
He send you after me?
Huarez. Got a real hard-on.
Why is that?
Might have mentioned
he don't know how to screw
his wife too well.
Shouldn't have done that,
but he just got me worked up.
You get angry a lot,
Kleavon?
Nah, no more than usual.
About how long is this gonna take?
Twelve hours was the limit in Texas.
Where were you last night, Bear?
Little after midnight?
Driving.
Around, collecting
my nighttime thoughts.
Nighttime thoughts,
about what?
Life shit.
Think better at night.
Found this in, uh,
Raine's underwear drawer.
She mentioned you.
Man, she's gone, why you wanna dig...?
"Dear Diary,
This job is just
a stepping stone.
I'm going places, but I'm
not sure Cornelius is
ready to go with me."
Then she talks about you
and a girl named, uh, Janelle.
Janelle's just some white chick.
Raine find out about
you two?
You read where she talks
about that collage
I did for her birthday?
What kind of grown-ass man
does collages,
and kills his woman?
You read this?
I saw her put it away like
a hundred times. What was
I supposed to do, bro?
See, man, I knew
this shit looked bad.
Where were you last night?
At Janelle's,
but it wasn't like that.
We were in the bed,
but the clothes were on.
It was platonic.
You were sleeping
together, but you weren't
sleeping together?
Yeah, there you go.
BROCK:
Bless this child, Father.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Ghost,
I say amen.
PARISHIONERS:
Amen.
[ORGAN PLAYING]
WILLIAM:
We thank you, Lord,
for bringing this child...
Reverend, I'm Captain Rawling.
I need a moment.
Oh, all right,
must be some kind
of problem.
They sending
a captain.
Well, uh, we believe
a few of your members
are using this church
to import illegal drugs.
That's not possible.
I'm sure it's without your knowledge.
Are these three boys here
right now?
Muncelle's car is in your lot.
He's known to hang out
with the other two.
They were making
sandwiches in the kitchen
about a half an hour ago.
Those boys volunteer.
Their criminal days
are in the past.
They are tagged One-Niners.
Just being here together's
is against the law.
I know about
those injunctions.
You find them out on the street,
they're all yours.
But this is a house of the Lord.
We have a warrant on the way.
We just need to talk to the boys,
do a search of the premises.
We'll be very respectful.
RONNIE:
How do you think it's going in there?
I'm more worried about
what's going on over there.
I mean, they snag him and
he gets caught, I don't wanna
hear what Antwon's gonna say.
Damnit, here he is now.
Verdice is walking right
into an arrest.
[TYRES SCREECHING]
Get out of here.
Shit.
VIC: Yo, that's Verdice's ride.
RONNIE:
He's coming for a pick-up?
Not coming for the wine.
RONNIE: He's running.
Asshole's gonna try to split.
[TYRES SCREECHING]
What are you doing?
Army, what the hell
are you doing?!
[HORN HONKING]
Get out of the car!
Come here.
You talk,
Antwon will know.
You keep your mouth shut,
you get out of this alive.
Take it easy. Let's go, get up.
What the hell was that?
Hands behind your back.
Guy was gonna bail.
BROCK: Stay out of my church.
SHANE: Yo, get up.
Reading the good parts?
Looking for more clues.
It's a real window
into the mind.
How things going
with your Texas
chainsaw murderer?
Says he's the victim
of the good old boys network.
But something's off
about him.
Maybe you'll have a take.
So we're back?
No, but I can put up
with you long enough
to put someone like this
behind bars.
I been telling my partner
about how you were
harassed in Texas.
Can we get you
something to drink?
So you can stop me
from going to the can
when my bladder fills up?
No thanks.
So, uh, witnesses spotting you
near those crime scenes
was just dumb luck, huh?
Just happened by.
No law against that.
Why'd you leave
San Antonio,
Kleavon?
KLEAVON:
Just got sick
of The Alamo.
Kind of feels like
we're wasting our time.
His too.
Probably got somewhere
you need to be.
Job? Girlfriend?
Like we established,
I'm new in town.
DUTCH:
Must have a lot of free time.
What do you like to do?
People watch.
Tell us where you were last night,
we can end this now.
KLEAVON:
Oh, I was home.
I know, give us a rundown
of the whole night.
So you can go over
my statement 50 times,
try to trip me up? No thanks.
Woman named Raine Powell
was murdered last night.
Bludgeoned to death.
Maybe you, uh, happened
by this crime scene too.
Yeah, I didn't kill her.
He didn't even blink
at those photos.
Classic sociopathic
non-reaction.
I don't know.
He seems pretty confident
we won't come up with something.
He's already gotten away
with at least four others.
What else do we got?
Raine's diary mentions, uh,
some beef with a co-worker,
a friend she lent
her bingo winnings to.
I'll have the unis
pick him up.
Have to admit it felt good
in there. Two of us clicking.
Dutch, do you know where Vic is?
DUTCH: No, why?
He's got me watching his sick kid.
My shift ended and
the sitter never showed.
Did you try his cell phone?
No answer.
I know the mom,
she works at Mission Cross.
Uh, I can call her.
How's she doing?
Good. Thanks again.
Vic had a uni with her
the whole time. It wasn't like
he left her totally alone.
I can't believe
he didn't call me.
Divorce is tough.
Mine was a while ago.
Anyway, thanks again.
It was really nice of you.
You're welcome.
Listen, um, wanna have
dinner some time?
Dinner?
Why not?
Three kids, a job,
selling our house.
I don't have time. I don't know.
We'll work around your schedule.
I don't know. You work with Vic.
We barely see each other.
I tried it with a cop once.
Vic and I could not
be more different.
Reverend, I have
a signed search warrant.
You must open the door.
This is a house of worship.
There's an easier way
to do this.
There are no drugs here.
Except for the heroin.
Reverend, I have
the legal right to come inside.
Use force if I have to.
Neither of us wants that.
Then let the Lord be
your judge.
We could pack it up,
come back tonight.
Yeah, give them time
to flush the tar?
We already look
like assholes.
Go in now, at least
we have something
in hand to show for it.
You believe in your intel,
right?
VIC:
Oh, yeah.
Okay, people.
Let's go.
You know who
we're looking for.
Remember that this is a church.
There are civilians inside.
So do your jobs,
but use extra care.
VIC: All right, who's got the hawk?
We do.
Good. Four teams,
two in the front, one on the side,
one in the back. Let's do it.
Captain, I'm not breaking down
a church door.
Just think of it as a drug
warehouse, because that's
what it is today.
We shouldn't be going
in like this.
Get in the back,
both of you.
What the hell are you doing?
You're knocking us out of this?
All right, Reverend,
last chance.
Open the door.
Do it.
BROCK:
The Lord is the stronghold of my life.
Of whom then should I go in dread?
When evildoers close in on me
to devour me...
Hold it, Muncelle!
BROCK:
It is my enemies
who stumble and fall.
VIC: Don't you move.
BROCK: An army should encamp me.
You all right?
BROCK: My heart does not fear.
Sofer and Lowe got the other ones
coming out the back.
BROCK:
My heart does not fear.
Though wars are waged against me.
Even then do I trust...
[CHURCH BELL RINGING]
Any drugs?
JULIEN: Nothing here.
DANNY:
Just the.38.
We're gonna have to search
the whole church
and everyone in it.
Just be gentle.
Hey, hey, all that fast
and furious shit,
you're sending smoke signals
to Vic and the captain.
What they gonna do,
reprimand me?
Look, we gotta find
that heroin first,
show him we're not
Antwon's butt buddies.
I told you,
that's temporary.
Ah!
You got something?
Yeah, botulism,
residue.
K9 could do this
in five minutes.
Yeah, if they'd ever show up.
Hey, just found a receipt
in the good
reverend's office.
Church candles are imported
from El Salvador.
Okay.
Yeah.
BROCK:
Oh, heaven help them.
Vic.
Get these sinners baptized.
What's up?
LEMONHEAD:
I got the toxies on Angie's mom.
Levels indicate she had
over 500 bucks of heroin
in her system.
Jesus. Even a frat boy
knows not to shoot
that much poison.
Yeah, this was a junkie
who could barely scrape enough
together for a dime bag.
Somebody made sure she
copped till she dropped.
Well, I'm connecting
the dots, and all
I'm seeing
is a picture of Shane
with Antwon Mitchell.
SCOOBY:
Hey, did Paula find you?
She was trying to call.
Shit. I had it on silent
for the bust.
Something about Detective
Wagenbach taking your daughter
to the hospital?
We'll do this later.
She's sick, you brought her
to the station?
Carmen dropped a bomb
on me, backup sitter blew
a tyre.
What was I to do? I had it.
Should've called. Obviously not.
Otherwise you wouldn't have
dumped her with a uni.
Christ, the first time
in seven months
there's been a problem.
Come on, Cass,
let's go.
CASSID Y:
Maybe I should stay
with Mom.
She's gotta work,
sweetie.
Genine's waiting for us.
Let's go.
Go with your father.
I'll see you tomorrow.
One time thing, that's it.
You were, uh, pretty broken up
about Raine earlier.
How are you doing now?
Bunch of us from the store
set up a shrine.
Teddy bears, flowers.
That's nice.
You know, your boss found
those order forms
you've been changing.
I sold a few DVD players,
a couple of Xboxes
on the side.
I was gonna tell you
all about it.
Raine know about your enterprise?
No way.
Really? Her diary,
it says she
confronted you.
Said she was gonna go
to your manager.
I know, you were gonna
tell me all about it.
Now, when Raine confronted
you, what happened?
You probably tried
to reason with her.
Look, if it were up to me,
I'd pin this on a real killer.
Some asshole
who murders for fun.
Problem is, the unis eyeballed
your car with what looks
to be blood inside.
You didn't plan this.
Second degree murder.
You can get out one day,
but we need to know
the truth.
I offered her a cut.
But she pulled the moral high ground
shit on you, didn't she?
One thing I hate,
it's a self-righteous bitch.
DUTCH:
Tell me about it.
You did what you had to do.
She left you no choice.
So much for San Antonio
eating our dust.
He's innocent.
Of murdering Raine.
Guy's still a stone cold killer.
And he just pitched a tent
in our backyard.
We got a suspect, but no victim.
That's new.
It bites we don't
live in a dictatorship.
Put the guy in a hole
and forget about him.
Well, there's an impulse
I can understand.
We can't turn Kleavon
over to SIS until he commits
a crime in L.A.
You know, I thought I hated
being on the DA's shit list,
but this is actually worse.
I can't believe
you're still freezing me out.
you sold me out.
Officer Lowe.
I think you should stick
to desk duty the next
few days.
See if you can find your way
into what we're doing here.
If not,
I understand.
But you should consider
putting in for a transfer.
I wasn't gonna break
into a church.
There was heroin
in the holy candles.
This time.
VIC:
Altar boys pin you
as the head honcho.
We can't make a deal,
you're eating roadkill goulash
over at Lompoc.
Where's my spoon then?
You wanna be a barrio martyr,
that's fine with me.
But why not serve up
Antwon instead?
Antwon who?
We can put you into relocation,
keep you safe.
[WHISPERING] Lone Ranger
and Tonto, they hauled
your ass out of that car.
What did they say to you?
They told me get out the car,
and put my hands on my head.
And that's the last I'm saying.
[PHONE RINGING]
Dutchboy.
Hero of the hour.
Your daughter was sick.
Wanted her mother.
You can't take a joke,
so you make me look
like a prick in front of my ex.
I'm sure your ex doesn't need
any help seeing what kind of
prick you are.
Just saw Angie's mother's tox report.
Lem have any news on Angie?
I don't know.
Well, find him.
I wanna hear
what he's got.
ANTWON:
Used to be bad cops
was good business.
But now I got a stash gone,
a whole crew locked up
and sellers who can't sell.
You wanna tell how
the world got upside-down
on your watch?
SHANE: Seeing as you
were misusing a house
of the Lord,
I'd say
divine intervention.
He must really
hate you.
Only reason he'd talk
to me like that
because he wants
to see y'all dead or in jail.
Vic Mackey wants you gone.
We're the only thing standing
in his way.
You think I need your ass,
you're wrong.
You think you don't,
Look, protecting you
is a full-time gig
plus overtime.
So you can either tell me
what you're into,
or I can keep
chasing Vic's tail.
Some days we'll catch it.
Some days we won't.
I'll think about it.
Yeah, you do that.
ARMY: Antwon's gonna drop the body.
He's not that stupid.
Him being stupid is
not what I'm worried about.
Well, I didn't hear you complaining
about my leadership skills
when I got you blown.
This isn't doing favours
to get intel on bad guys.
You got me taking it up the ass
from Antwon Mitchell.
Ramming cars to keep us
out of prison.
I've dealt with guys
like this before.
You or Mackey? Do you even
have a clue how we're
getting out of this?
Look, I'm getting
us close.
This guy thinks he can kill
this little girl right
in front of us?
We're gonna find
that little girl, we're gonna
give her a proper burial.
Then when the time
is right
we're gonna shove a stick
of dynamite up his ass.
MONICA: Dr. Alvin Bernard's
clinic has been providing
free pre-natal care
to Farmington's poor
for 21 years,
which is why I'm so pleased,
Al, to give you
this cheque for $10,000.
REPORTER 1:
Is that money
from seizures?
Part of my promise to give
a third of what we get
from asset-forfeitures
back to the community.
How does that community
feel about your decision
to invade a church?
I wouldn't characterise it
quite that way.
We found 12 kilos of
tar heroin inside there.
I'd say they're pretty
damn happy.
REPORTER 1: Any plans to seize it?
No.
REPORTER 2:
Is the reverend under arrest?
The only people under arrest
are known drug dealers
with affiliations
to Farmington One-Niners.
So you'd interrupt another baptism
to put away a gang member?
I'd interrupt
my grandmother's funeral
if it meant taking
dangerous narcotics off the streets
our children walk on.
But don't tell that
to my grandma,
because she's still full of piss
and vinegar in Tarzana.
Reporters were tough today.
We keep storming churches,
they're gonna get tougher.
You were all for it earlier.
I was. I am.
It's just this thing's to good to blow...
Hoda Stubbs was killed.
Angie too, I'm guessing.
I plan on finding who did it.
When you do, ask about the leak
at the warehouse today.
We don't know
if there was a leak.
Even if there was, we don't
know they're related.
Could be accidental.
Stop bullshitting me.
You vouched for Shane.
What about Army?
He seems like a good kid.
I don't think...
I don't care what you think.
What do you know?
Is there a reason you don't
wanna dig deeper on this?
I'm not about witch hunts.
I've been on the other side
of a few.
I chose you for this job because
I needed somebody as hungry
as me to make it work.
And I'm getting it done.
Why are you riding me?
Because shit is falling
through the cracks.
Pressure on the seizure
programme is only gonna
get more intense.
And when it does, that shit
is gonna rise straight
to the surface.
If you can't withstand
scrutiny about anything,
I need you to step aside.
I don't step aside. I step up.
Which is the other reason
I chose you.
Find the leak.
ARMY:
I mean, that's some
cold ass shit.
Can't tell the Iraqi insurgents
from the plain old Iraqi idiots.
Yeah, and no difference here.
Somebody gets in the way,
we keep rolling. I'm just saying.
Maybe that's the way
we gotta look at things.
What's up?
Son of a bitch, what did...?
She was 14.
SHANE:
What the hell's
your problem?
LEMONHEAD:
You bring Angie
to Antwon Mitchell yourself, huh?
Hand her with a bow,
or just tell him where
to find her?
No. No.
No? Where is she then?!
Back off. Just back off.
I got it, okay? I got it.
Where is she then,
Shane?
Where's Angie?
What are you asking me for, man?
You telling me you're not
in bed with Antwon Mitchell?
You told him Angie gave up
that cul-de-sac bust.
No, man,
I would never do that.
What happened to her, Shane?
What happened to her then?
I don't know.
Dude, she was 14.
She just wanted
to get her mom clean.
You tell me what you did!
Nothing! Nothing!
Look, you know
that I would never...
You know I would
never hurt a kid.
Look, I got one
of my own now, man.
Yeah, I know you.
I know you're lying.
I didn't kill that girl.
And I didn't give her name up
to Antwon.
So you just stay
out of my face.
I lose that one percent
of doubt I got, we'll be
mixing it up again.
Captain says she wants
to hear your opinions,
but only hers is right.
DAVID: Agendas have
a way of creating
tunnel vision.
She said I could put in for a transfer.
Sure.
Stock the pond
with true believers,
make implied threats
to get rid of ones who aren't.
You don't think
I should leave?
I think if you wanted to,
you wouldn't have
called me.
I grew up in Farmington.
I don't wanna see it
torn more apart.
What is it you want
me to do, Julien?
You've got power.
Help us to stop her.
Going after a police captain
is no walk in the park.
I should know.
There are other officers
of colour that agree with me.
We wouldn't be alone.
I remember the last time
you and I went down
this path.
Things got messy,
and you left me
twisting in the wind.
Not this time.
Vic Mackey, he's got
a lot invested in this policy.
He'll come after you.
Could dredge up the past.
I can handle it.
I'm a different man now.
RONNIE:
Russian taxi king's
expanded his realm.
Added three more cabs to the fleet.
Alex the Conqueror.
How many cabs we got
wired so far?
Even dozen, even managed
to get one in his personal ride.
Sweet.
LEMONHEAD:
Yeah, what do you want?
What the hell you think you're doing
going after Shane?
He ran right back
and told you, huh?
You got suspicions, fine.
We all agreed we'd keep
them to ourselves.
Look, there's a 14-year-old girl
rotting out there someplace.
Are you in on that too?
What?
You saying
you gotta keep Shane close.
Maybe you gotta keep me
far away because you're back
to business as usual.
Riding in Mitchell's pocket
with Shane.
I wanna bring down Antwon
and find that girl
as much as you do.
Really?
Prove it.
Let me back in.
It's complicated.
You gotta do things my way.
Oh, you mean, I agree
to protect Shane
like always, right?
Right?
We added another car
in the garage sting.
Shane didn't tell me
you came after him. I saw it.
Jesus Christ.
Lem's one crazy-ass
white boy.
You really used
to be tight?
SHANE:
Yeah.
Lifetime ago.
What does he know
about us?
Nothing. He's just guessing,
he can't prove anything.
I'll handle him.
Look, you're just gonna
have to trust me.
I'm gonna handle
all this shit.
It's not about
protecting Shane anymore.
It's about stopping him.
[###]