I'm not gonna be a superhero.
What else ya gonna do as a Hulk?
(HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(BURPS)
JENNIFER: Previously, on my show...
Remember my date
with the guy with the fetish?
Did you call me a specimen?
As a compliment.
I wanna see the supersuit
that Luke made you.
JENNIFER: Why? I won't wear it.
You didn't tell me you were nominated
for Female Lawyer of the Year.
Do we get to go to a gala?
My friend sent me a link to
a video post on that site, Intelligencia.
- JENNIFER: I met a guy.
- I'm Josh.
We went on a few dates,
it was going great.
And I haven't heard from him.
WRECKER: You were ghosted.
EMIL: Next time you think of Josh,
everyone we meet,
no matter how much they hurt you,
is a lesson learned.
ROBBER 1: Is this OLED or QLED?
My online research tells me
OLED is better for
color resolution and picture quality.
Funny enough,
I actually read the article... (GROANS)
LEAPFROG: The store might be closed,
but you forgot about
the Guard Frog.
(EXCLAIMS)
The hell is a Guard Frog?
ROBBER 2: I think it's his name.
My name is Leapfrog.
I'm just acting like I'm the Guard Frog
in this particular instance.
"The Guard Frog"?
Yeah, but my name is Leapfrog.
Yes, that has been noted several times,
Mr. Patilio.
- Cool.
- So, your defective suit...
LEAPFROG: Right. So, I was surrounded
by these huge guys.
- Twisting toe jam!
-(GROANS)
Although I was outnumbered,
I could tell they were afraid of me.
So, in order to de-escalate the situation,
I shouted my signature catchphrase.
Time to ribbit and rip it!
(LEAPFROG SCREAMING)
And then next thing I know,
my inflammable suit
with a 900-degree threshold is on fire.
And, you guessed it, I have
third-degree burns all over my legs.
I mean, I deserve justice.
And compensation for all of
my pain, mental anguish and...
Stuff.
Well, this does seem to be a pretty clear
case of manufacturer's defect,
negligence, strict liability,
and breach of warranty.
- Yes?
- I do believe
you are owed compensatory damages.
Yeah! Whoo!
What is the name of the manufacturer?
Luke Jacobson.
He specializes in supersuits.
Oh, shit.
Jacobson is the only tailor I can go to
because of my unique physique.
Do you think maybe
Pug could take this one?
Mr. Patilio is one of our biggest clients.
The guy dressed as a frog?
Mr. Patilio, Sr.
Look, it's very important
that we keep the Patilios happy.
Eugene is also very excited
to have a Hulk on the case.
And they're willing to sign
a conflict waiver
to have you, Ms. Walters.
But I believe I would be
ethically compromised
in representing a client against Jacobson.
I like my nice clothes
and I don't wanna piss him off.
You've handled a client
who had to sign a conflict waiver before,
in a case one would argue
is a lot more personal than this one.
Yes, and I would love
not to be in that position again.
Also, he's making me a dress for the gala.
Very well, Ms. Walters.
I suggest that you try to
come to an agreement with Mr. Jacobson
so then a filing would
not be necessary. Understood?
(PHONE RINGS)
- Ribbit and rip it.
- Yes, ribbit and rip it indeed.
Jennifer, do not rush me.
I told you
your dress will not be ready until Friday.
You wanna look good
for your lawyer award, right?
Uh, yes. Well, Luke,
I am here under some
unpleasant business.
I have been retained by a client
who suffered serious injuries
due to a dysfunctional suit
that you sold him.
Nothing has been filed.
I think we can come to some kind of...
Excuse me?
How dare you.
I have never made a defective suit
in all my life. My work is impeccable.
Obviously, I know that firsthand. And I...
Trust me, I'm not happy to be doing this.
I'm not trusting you
after you just lumbered in here
and stabbed me in the back.
Well, there's no lawsuit yet.
And there won't be
if you just take some responsibility
for some of my client's injuries.
I do not make suits that malfunction.
My work speaks for itself.
Oh, excuse me. What did you say?
She wants to tell me something, hold on.
"She-Hulk will never get another suit
by Luke Jacobson ever again?"
-(GASPS)
- Oh!
Hey, I pre-paid for that!
Then you shouldn't have betrayed me.
You are blocked, blacklisted and reported!
Now, I am gonna take you down.
Well, I hope it's not down to wherever
it is you get your ugly clothes from.
See you in court!
Can you...
LUKE: Goodbye, tragedy.
JUDGE PRICE: Mr. Jacobson,
I see you are presently without counsel.
Are you representing yourself?
(CHUCKLES) Representing himself?
Start planning
how you're gonna spend all your new money.
Mr. Jacobson?
Of course I'm not representing myself,
Your Honor. I'm not a fool.
JUDGE: Then where is your counsel?
I'm here.
Apologies for the tardiness, Your Honor.
I had trouble finding parking.
I'm just kidding. My driver got lost.
-(CHUCKLES)
- My name is Matthew Murdock.
I'll be representing Mr. Jacobson
in this case.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
As a first point of order,
I'd like to ask that
the motion to compel production of
the defendant's client list be rejected
as it's not relevant to the litigation.
Who's this asshole?
Your Honor, I believe
this information to be incredibly relevant
given the nature of the complaint.
There could be multiple instances
of Mr. Jacobson's other clients
sustaining injuries
from faulty merchandise.
I believe Ms. Walters will find that
Mr. Jacobson's record
as it pertains to customer satisfaction
to be spotless.
If the defendant has nothing to hide,
then why not hear from his clients?
That's an invasion of privacy
based on a very shaky "what if."
This is a very common procedure
in product liability lawsuits.
It is material to the case whether
this type of malfunction
has affected other people.
There is no inherent right to privacy
when employing
Mr. Jacobson's tailoring services.
We're not just
talking about a product here.
The very nature
of Mr. Jacobson's line of work,
making suits exclusively for superheroes,
necessitates anonymity.
May I remind you that
the Sokovia Accords have been repealed.
Superheroes operate in the public eye.
As public figures, it is assumed that
there will be some loss of privacy.
We're not talking about celebrities,
but superheroes who have
enemies who will try to harm them,
and people close to them.
The ones who didn't ask
to be a part of this life.
Ms. Walters chose
to have her identity be public,
but she can't choose for everyone else.
This isn't about
privacy for privacy's sake.
If this information is not protected,
not only would it ruin my client's career,
it could put a lot of people
in a lot of danger,
and all over one man's misuse of a suit.
JUDGE PRICE: I'm in agreement
with Mr. Murdock.
Motion to compel discovery is denied.
Wait. Does that mean
I don't get a new suit?
Sit down!
What, no... Look at this thing!
How am I supposed to wear this?
(SNIFFS)
Mr. Patilio, what kind of fuel
did you use in your boosters?
Jet fuel.
Wait a minute,
you used jet fuel in your boosters?
Because that's not
what my instructions said.
What?
Uh... (CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
No, I didn't.
He's lying.
Don't ask me how I know, I just know.
Yes, we can all tell he's lying,
Mr. Murdock.
If the plaintiff ignored
the manufacturer's explicit instructions,
then the defendant
is absolved of all liability.
I'm dismissing this case.
Am I gonna go to jail?
No, but I would like you to.
- And Luke, Luke.
- Yes, clown?
I just wanted to apologize for...
For daring to question my craftsmanship?
Is there any way that we could
go back to you being my tailor?
Jennifer, Jenny, Jen.
No. Because I hate you now.
(SIGHS)
What's this?
It's from that guy over there.
An appletini? Cute.
Mind if I join you?
Sure.
Would you mind?
I wanted to extend a peace offering.
Ugh! I hate it when people
take the high road.
So, what's your story, Matt Murdock?
You're from New York
but you flew all the way out here
for a product liability case?
Luke Jacobson made a couple of
new suits for me, so I owed him one.
Doesn't really look like it.
(CHUCKLES) That's a low blow
insulting a blind man's clothes.
-(CHUCKLES)
- I'm wearing pants, right?
(JENNIFER LAUGHS)
You have your own practice, right?
Ms. Walters,
have you been checking up on me?
Yeah. Can you blame me?
You came out of nowhere
and you made my dumb client admit
to being even dumber
than I thought he was in court.
How did you know about the jet fuel?
A hunch.
What is his deal, by the way?
- Well, I'll give you one guess.
- Okay.
It rhymes with "rich parents."
-(CHUCKLES)
- Wait, I said it was rich parents.
His dad is a very important client,
so he is a very important client.
Well, you know the expression,
"One for them, one for us"?
Yeah.
Well, I run my practice in Hell's Kitchen,
and we mostly do pro bono work.
The "us" part.
But I do on occasion
take a job with a bigger client
when the bills start piling up.
The "them" part.
Wow. Secret double lives of Matt Murdock,
how does he do it?
As someone who works for "them" full-time,
I really don't have any gas in the tank
for anything else.
Yeah, you say that,
but I think you're in a unique position
to do some real good.
You see, the way I see it,
Jen Walters can use the law to help people
when society fails them.
And She-Hulk can help people
when the law fails them.
So, you can, if you choose...
Be the best of both worlds.
- Excuse me for a moment.
- Yeah.
We're all feeling this, right,
it's not just me?
-(PHONE CHIMES)
-(GROANS)
Ugh! You remember Todd, that gross
tech bro with the She-Hulk fetish?
Ugh!
Hey, do you wanna get another round?
Jen, I am so sorry, I have to go.
Something has just come up with work.
Oh, yeah. Totally. I got work, too.
- Yeah.
- Um...
Uh, yeah, it was really...
(CHUCKLES)
It was nice meeting you.
Yeah, you, too.
(PHONE CHIMES)
Okay.
Mr. Phelps.
Mr... It's Todd.
(CHUCKLES POLITELY)
So, what is the urgent matter
that you wanted to discuss with me?
Oh, yeah... So, I was at
an auction recently buying art
and then, get this, they had
an authentic Wakandan war spear.
So, I, of course, win the auction.
A millie. (CHUCKLES)
It's (CLEARS THROAT) a million.
- Dollars.
- I got that.
Yeah. So...
I mean, you gotta see it, right?
(CHUCKLES) So, here it is. Check this out.
Boom. How cool is that?
I mean, I own that now.
God, no one is collecting African shit
on my level.
I love it. I love Wakanda.
You know, I actually studied abroad there.
Really?
Wakanda Forever!
Ooh! I... That makes me uncomfortable.
So, is there a legal issue
with your purchase?
No, no. Well, okay, they want it back
because apparently
it was stolen by colonizers,
but whatever. I mean, I got the receipts.
You know, listen, babe.
Let's just drop the whole coy thing
-'cause I don't play games, okay?
-(CHUCKLES)
And I can feel it
and I can tell that we're both feeling it.
Ugh! No!
- Oh!
-(PATRONS GASPING)
Goodbye. Oh, and I'm billing you
for the whole hour.
What?
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Oh, God.
- Hello?
- Thank God! Ms. Walters, it's Leapfrog.
Listen, you gotta help me.
I think I'm being attacked.
Legally or physically?
Definitely physically.
But, I mean, maybe legally, too.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to the Lily Pad.
Is that a place I'm supposed to know?
Yeah. It's my famous secret lair.
(GASPS) Yeah,
I just need to find my friends.
Okay, I'm gonna try to lose him
in this parking lot.
- I'm gonna lose ya.
- You're close.
I'm heading to you.
We'll meet in the middle.
Hurry!
Whoa!
My car!
You need to back off.
And waste this outfit?
Eugene, get out of here.
Dope supersuit!
You're making a mistake.
You made a mistake
when you messed with my client!
'Cause now I'm gonna whoop your ass.
(CHUCKLES AND GRUNTS)
Huh. My ass remains unwhooped.
Yeah? Let's fix that.
LEAPFROG: Ribbit and rip it!
(LAUGHS)
Where are you going? We're not done.
You're very persistent, aren't you?
And you're very annoying.
(GRUNTS)
LEAPFROG: See you later!
(LAUGHS)
Come on!
(CAR ALARMS BLARING)
-(GROANS)
- Gotcha.
Whoa, whoa! Jen!
Matt?
Wait. Do you pretend to be blind, man?
'Cause that is really problematic.
No. No, no, I'm blind, I'm blind.
Relax. I...
I have a spatial method that I use to see.
Oh, like echolocation?
Yeah, kind of. It's...
Basically I have really good hearing.
Or at least I did.
Wait, why were you attacking my client?
Leapfrog is the bad guy here.
He kidnapped Luke Jacobson.
He's holding him hostage.
Why didn't you tell me that
before we fought?
Why didn't you ask me
before trying to whoop my ass?
I'm sorry that I assumed the guy
dressed as the devil was the bad one.
Yeah, that's a fair point.
So, are you, like, a superhero?
Like the Gold Devil?
I'm Daredevil.
It is very daring to use ketchup
and mustard as your color scheme.
How 'bout I tell Luke?
No! No, please don't.
Okay. Well, if you're done making fun,
I need to save my client from your client.
Okay, yeah, let's go.
You ever destroy a parking lot before?
JENNIFER: Crap. I'll go leave a note.
Hmm. Subtle.
For version two, we gotta go all out.
I'm talking bulletproof shields,
fancy AI
with a British voice that talks to you.
Oh, snap! And some of those poison darts,
like the tree frogs.
I don't know who told you
that you could pull off this color,
but you should go back to them
and shoot them.
Look, I know you're just being mean
because I kidnapped you,
but words hurt, man.
Guys, what do we think
about the name "Leap Squad"?
You know, like, "Leap Squad!"
JENNIFER: I can't believe this dodo
has henchmen.
Actually, I can.
I bet these goons work for his dad.
Nah, see, that's where you're wrong.
Goons and henchmen
are two completely different animals.
Henchmen believe in the cause,
goons are just there for the paycheck.
Henchmen, goons, whatever.
There are 25 goons in the building.
Seven below us, eight in the front,
and 10 in the hallway.
How do you know that?
I can hear their heartbeats.
You can hear their heartbeats?
Come on, that's a little far-fetched.
(HEART BEATING)
I can hear yours, too.
Your heart's beating pretty fast.
What?
What? No, it's not. I'm healthy.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
I'll sneak in
and take out the goons in the back.
It'll take me 15 seconds for each one.
So, wait here until I've gotten all 10.
I'm not gonna sit here for half an hour
while you pick off goons one by one.
That's not how that math works out.
I'm a Hulk.
How about I just smash our way in?
They have weapons, Jennifer.
Yeah, good thing
She-Hulk is indestructible, Matthew.
Stealth's the way to go.
I've done this a million times.
Have you broken into
a warehouse full of goons?
Remind me again
who has the superpowers here?
I'm pointing at myself.
Oh, yeah, I know.
I have echolocation, remember?
Just let me do my thing.
Yeah, and I will do my thing.
(SCOFFS) You... You don't have a thing.
You don't ever do this.
Just follow my lead.
Okay, I guess that's pretty cool.
So, I said I respect that
you wanna dress up like a frog,
but that doesn't mean
I'm cool with being a baby frog.
Wait, I thought he wanted
to call us "Tadpoles."
Yeah, man.
- How do you not know what...
-(THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GOON 1 GROANS)
GOON 2 ON WALKIE:
Tadpole five, come in.
We need backup at the rear entrance.
We got...
Tadpole five, repeat.
Hang tight, backup's on the way.
(ALL YELLING)
(GOONS GROAN)
She-Hulk smash.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Ugh! More hench-goons?
How about we don't?
Whoa! Hey! That's vintage!
(GOONS CLAMORING)
LEAPFROG: Hey, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be helping me.
JENNIFER: I am helping you.
I'm stopping you from getting
into even more trouble.
Go call the police.
Don't you yell at me.
I'm already very stressed out.
JENNIFER: Eugene,
let me give you some legal advice.
Stop now, before you rack up
even more serious charges.
Legally speaking, we could say
this is an episode of mania...
Temporary insanity is murky,
but it's not a bad strategy.
I'd angle this more as a form of traumatic
expression due to undiagnosed PTSD.
So, the devil ninja guy, he's a lawyer?
No. I'm just a big fan of legal dramas.
This guy's really kinda doing it for me.
(GOON 5 YELLS)
It's sad that you thought that would work.
(YELLS)
No shame in retreat.
Ribbit and rip it! Oh!
(LEAPFROG SCREAMS)
(LEAPFROG GROANING)
Well, well, well, I suppose
we're even now. You're forgiven.
So, you'll make my gala dress?
- Yes, of course. I'm not a monster.
-(EXCLAIMS EXCITEDLY)
Try not to get too bloated
between now and then.
Great to be strained
professional acquaintances again.
LUKE: Uh-huh.
Are you gonna
give a statement to the cops?
I'm not really a stick around
and talk to the cops kinda guy.
- Oh, so brooding.
-(CHUCKLES)
More of a secret identity thing.
- You wouldn't understand.
- Mmm-hmm.
Thanks for your help with all of this.
Thanks for your help.
No. You're the one who helped me.
No. I was the lead superhero on this.
Uh, you were they guy
who wanted to spend half an hour
- picking off each goon, one by one.
-(CHUCKLES)
You were the woman
who caused excessive property damage.
And you still can't get that math right.
When do you head to New York?
- Tomorrow.
- Oh... Well...
Hey, maybe next time I'm in town,
I can take you out to dinner.
Yeah, or maybe we can
skip all of that and just...
(KISSING AND MOANING)
JENNIFER: That's all right.
That's okay.
MATT: Wait, you have to...
All right, here you go.
Okay. Let's go.
(WHISTLING)
Good morning.
(HUMMING)
It's weird you guys are still here.
Doesn't it feel like
this episode should be over?
Hello! Uh...
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I thought that you were dead.
I had to break and enter. By the way,
there's some guy outside
dressed in a devil costume
and he's doing the walk of shame
'cause he's...
Oh. You did... With the...
Yes.
Oh, all right. And we're happy?
- Oh, we're happy.
- Okay.
- All right. You're the devil.
-(BOTH LAUGH)
Seriously, what is this scene?
This episode already came to
a very satisfying conclusion. Trust me.
Come on! We gotta go.
Tell me about it later.
We have to do your hair and your makeup.
Where is the gown from Luke?
Oh, for the gala?
Wait, we're doing the gala?
That doesn't feel right.
Is next episode the finale?
- Come on. Let's go.
-(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Just like a tacked-on set piece
near the end of the season.
This is the big twist, isn't it?
But the question is,
is it the kind of twist that's like,
"There's another Hulk,
but this one's red,"
or like, "I'm getting fridged?"
We gotta make you look amazing.
Whatever. I'm game.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Sweetheart. You didn't bring a jacket?
What if you get cold?
She can wear mine, Elaine.
We are so proud of you.
- Thank you, Dad.
- Your jacket won't fit her, Morris.
NIKKI: You can't cover up a
Luke Jacobson-Zuhair Murad collaboration.
ELAINE: Nikki!
MORRIS: That's certainly a mouthful.
(CHUCKLES) I'm a little nervous.
Okay. Let's find our table.
- Yeah. There he is. Hi!
- Let's go. Come on.
Come on.
Educated.
Accomplished.
Beautiful.
And doing everything regular lawyers do,
except backwards,
and in high heels. (CHUCKLES)
This year's Female Lawyer of the Year
award goes to...
Jennifer "She-Hulk" Walters!
- Let's go!
-(ALL APPLAUDING)
Kara Hunter.
Alice Chen.
Joanne Torres.
Barbara Wells.
Mallory Book.
Now tell us,
what's it like being a female lawyer?
So special and empowering. I love it.
Twice the work, half the recognition,
and you're constantly being asked
what it's like being a female lawyer.
- Yeah.
-(SNAPPING)
Yeah. I'd actually like to take this time
to thank my parents.
And my friends, and my esteemed colleagues
without whom I wouldn't be here today.
DISTORTED VOICE: Do you want to see
who She-Hulk really is?
Uh, my identity is not a secret.
This is busted.
This is the truth
presented by Intelligencia.
She-Hulk does not deserve your attention.
She does not deserve your praise.
She does not deserve
the power she stole from the Hulk.
What the hell this?
Can somebody cut this off?
Can we turn this off, please?
Okay, let's... Can we stop this?
- And she's a slut.
- Can you stop it?
JOSH: Yeah, maybe you should lie down.
Excuse me! Can you turn this off?
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
Don't do it, Jen.
Don't do it.
(SCREAMS)
(ALL GASPING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
-(SNARLS)
- Don't move!
Jen! No!
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)