KING THE LAND
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
As long as you feel at ease now.
Thank you
for bringing me all the way here.
Yes.
They're together.
The photos will look nice.
Don't worry.
I always protect my informants.
EPISODE 14
It's Tiger Balm.
Apply it to alleviate any type of pain.
That's nice.
Mr. Han, you should try this.
It's from Won. It's nice and cooling.
- Sir.
- Yes?
The media wish to report on Mr. Gu Won.
They should.
Of course they should.
For the first time in Korea,
our hotel will launch a global chain.
They won't find a better story than that.
It's not that.
It's a love scandal.
- Love scandal?
- Yes.
Chairman Han
must have leaked the story first.
It's all right.
They'll get married soon.
That's not the story.
Please take a look.
3RD-GEN CHAEBOL'S SECRET LOVE AFFAIR,
KING HOTEL SUCCESSOR AND ORDINARY WOMAN
It'll be published online soon.
Stop it immediately.
Offer to buy ads
or threaten to pull them out.
Stop it at any cost.
Yes, sir.
He'll offer to buy ads
or threaten to pull them out,
but I'll double
whatever my father proposes.
So publish the article.
Doesn't our cafeteria taste awful
after we outsourced the catering?
Right?
When we had full-time caterers,
I always looked forward to lunch at work.
Do you come to work to eat?
Learn to be thankful
for getting lunch vouchers.
You'll only learn
once you start paying for your lunch.
My gosh!
You surprised me.
Why? What is it?
There's an article on Mr. Gu.
- What?
- What surprised you so much?
My gosh!
"Third-generation chaebol's
secret love affair."
That's a feisty title.
She's an ordinary woman.
He's in love regardless
of her social status. How cool.
I always knew he was manly.
It says she's ordinary,
but she must be
a daughter of a small business.
It's a different world.
Even so, don't you envy her?
Her status just skyrocketed.
- Yes.
- Right.
People like us
wouldn't even have a chance.
Why would you envy her?
Don't even dream about it.
We're still free to dream.
- Isn't that so, Sa-rang?
- Sorry?
Why do you ask me that?
Aren't I allowed to ask?
Everyone is too uptight.
But wait.
The woman who got blurred out
kind of looks like Sa-rang.
What do you mean?
No, not at all.
No, she reminds me of you.
Yes, she has a similar vibe.
- I think so too.
- Right?
- That looks like her.
- The vibe.
- It looks just like her.
- Yes.
- They do look alike.
They're similar.
It's not like it's a Magic Eye.
She's all blurred out,
so how could you know if I look like her?
- But it looks like her.
- Yes.
It can't be Sa-rang.
- Right.
- No way.
- I think it's her.
- Maybe.
Anyway, Sa-rang.
Where are you going?
To the restroom.
It's that way.
I feel like going to the one
that's far away over there.
I get it.
- It makes no sense.
- No.
- It's her.
- It's nonsense.
Are you busy? Were you leaving?
Did you see it?
Yes, just now.
I got worried,
so I was coming over.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Did we do something wrong?
No, not at all.
Exactly.
It's nothing wrong, so don't be sorry.
But the article went out.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm not sure yet. I'm still out of it.
But I came to tell you I'm fine
and that you shouldn't worry.
You were worried about me?
Of course. You're the one I love the most.
If something ever happens again,
don't hesitate to come find me,
just as you did now.
If you can't come, you can call me.
If I do, will you come over right away?
Of course I will.
I'll run over right away.
Whenever it is, wherever you are.
Mr. Gu, this is bad!
My gosh, things are worse in here.
Sa-rang, you were here.
Knock first. This isn't your office.
Why are you two here together
in the midst of this turmoil?
Only I get the urgency.
- I get it, so leave for a moment.
- No.
I can't. This is a total emergency.
I'll go.
I have to go back to my shift.
Goodbye, Mr. Yoo.
I mean, Mr. No.
Okay, thanks.
Please take a seat.
What's happened has happened,
so our priority
is to resolve this scandal wisely.
Such a term only applies to gossip.
This isn't a scandal. These were facts.
Anyway,
make sure Sa-rang's identity
isn't revealed.
I don't care about me,
- but she must be protected.
- Yes.
I met with the head of the PR team.
They'll do whatever they can
to make sure
there aren't more articles on this.
You don't have to worry about that.
The problem is
that this won't be the end of it.
What do you mean?
Why was this article released
at this point in time?
I kept thinking about it
and concluded that it had to be Ms. Gu.
- No Sang-sik.
- Yes.
Don't jump to conclusions
unless you're sure.
I said it because
I have reason to be suspicious.
A few days ago,
Ms. Gu
summoned me.
Mr. No, you're with me from now on.
Make sure you report
everything related to Mr. Gu to me.
What do you mean by everything?
Everything.
From his professional life
to his personal life.
Report everything back to me.
Do not leave anything out.
In that case,
how high can I go by helping you?
How's head manager?
Doesn't that sound like a good deal?
Head manager?
That's nowhere near enough.
What?
I thought you'd offer to make me
president of a subsidiary company.
The head manager's position isn't enough
for me to betray my friend.
That trivial friendship?
To me,
he's too good of a friend
to call him trivial.
I'll pretend I never heard this.
I'm sorry.
She offered me your job
if I reported on your personal life.
When I wasn't shaken,
I suppose
she had someone else dig up dirt on you.
Why didn't you accept it?
Exactly. I should've accepted it.
I was just too loyal.
You lost that great chance
over some loyalty?
Exactly, it was a huge miscalculation.
I must be insane.
No Sang-sik, you crazy man. You fool.
You should've accepted it.
I must be crazy.
Thanks.
Sorry?
Forget it if you missed it.
"Thanks." I heard you.
I can't believe I lived long enough
to hear you thank me.
I knew it.
Isn't love great?
Good grief. Get out of here.
I will, but promise me one thing.
Once you become the president,
make me the head manager.
Of course, I know you'll do that.
Okay.
And Mr. Gu?
I'm more grateful.
He told you not to worry,
that the PR team will stop this.
Yes, he did.
It'll be fine, right?
The PR team of a major firm
must be well-equipped.
- They'll handle it.
- Of course.
Preventing articles
isn't a big deal for them.
What is this?
Why? What is it?
Oh my gosh.
"King Group's second Cinderella."
"Will the tragic love story
repeat itself?"
Let me see.
"Chairman Gu Il-hun married
a regular employee of his company,
but it ended in a divorce."
"His son, Head Manager Gu Won,
embarks on the same journey."
"His father's romance didn't end happily."
"Will his son be able
to turn this into a happy ending?"
Who wrote this article?
Is something wrong?
No.
I love it.
I wrote the draft.
It's getting lots of attention.
Release more articles
to keep the public's interest aroused.
That family's history
is quite interesting.
I mean, Reporter.
You can't publish her photo
without permission!
She has her portrait rights!
Another article just popped up.
Me?
I told you I'm her friend.
Her best friend.
I'm stepping in because she's a friend!
Water, please.
Okay.
How many pictures did they take?
You can't upload unblurred photos
of an ordinary person like this.
You need to take it down now.
We won't condone this!
No way.
It's still on the main page.
He's not even a celebrity.
Why are these articles flooding out?
It seems like a bigger deal
than celebrity news.
A story like this
is easy to get the people gossiping.
Anyway,
I wonder if he's okay.
Who? Mr. Exclamation Mark?
Yes.
Excuse me.
You should worry about yourself.
You're the one in a pickle right now.
Well, why should I worry?
It's already out there.
- Worrying won't change anything.
- But this is a relief.
The photos look great.
Yes, they do.
It's like a scene from a drama.
Guys, is that so important to you
in this situation?
Hey, people are going on and on
about how you're a Cinderella.
It'd be worse if they bashed your looks.
Sure, they'll insult you anyway,
so one less insult is better.
Why should I be insulted?
Is dating someone
something to be insulted over?
People feel sour when someone does better.
They're probably already
betting on when you'll break up.
She's right.
It's easy to sympathize
with someone worse off,
but it's not easy to applaud
someone better off.
Yes.
On that note,
let's give a round of applause!
Congrats.
I'm glad I have you two
who will gladly applaud me.
KING GROUP'S SECOND CINDERELLA?!
Stay away from social media for a while.
- And don't read the comments.
- Right.
Don't mind
what these nameless strangers say.
Yes, okay.
What do you want for lunch?
- Black bean noodles?
- I'm on a diet.
That's her, right? Mr. Gu's girl.
She's not much. Hey, you're better.
Of course. Don't even.
She has nothing on you.
I always knew Cheon Sa-rang
was up to no good from day one.
She was always flirting with him.
Look what happened.
Really?
Yes, didn't you see
her big smile with the flowers
at the inaugural ceremony?
I saw it.
It seemed like
she was determined to get him.
I feel so bad for Mr. Gu.
How did he end up
falling for someone like her?
It won't last long anyway.
Of course. A month at the longest.
Just wait and see.
Hey, Sa-rang.
Get in.
Hello.
Good for you, Sa-rang.
- Sorry?
- Your social status skyrocketed.
What's it like to be on that rocket?
It's not like that.
Don't try to pull that.
You approached him with a motive.
You can be honest with me.
How did you pick him up?
Share your secrets.
It's not like that.
Please don't make
such careless comments about my business.
Don't deny it.
I read everything on the news.
I hit on her.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
I went after her.
I hit on her first.
Well, not literally hitting.
So if you want to know some secrets,
you can come to me.
I'll give you a special lesson.
No, it's a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding or not, remember this.
I'm the one who liked her first.
Got it?
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
Let's go.
From now on,
say confidently that I hit on you first.
Okay?
Let's see if you have some good moves.
Not everyone can do that.
What do you take me for?
I'm a very deliberate person.
I made a decision to go after you
and planned out my moves.
You didn't know?
I see.
I'm sorry.
Who would believe you?
They'll say I'm a nobody.
A nobody?
From the day I met you,
my world has been
full of you.
Stop it.
So don't say things like that.
I don't deserve someone like you.
Okay?
Why didn't you do your job?
I'm sorry, sir.
Tell them to write
as many articles as they want.
But take down all articles
that mention Won's mother.
Tell them that I won't let it slide
not just as the group,
but on a personal level.
Yes, sir.
What about Mr. Gu and Ms. Cheon?
What can I do?
They're in love.
- Sorry?
- Let them be.
They'll have to learn
that what they're doing is meaningless.
Yes, sir.
KING GROUP'S SECOND CINDERELLA.
WILL THE TRAGIC LOVE STORY REPEAT ITSELF?
Ro-un.
I got two tickets to a musical.
Want to go over the weekend?
I'm okay.
You know I have feelings for you, right?
I'm sorry. I like someone else.
Is it Pyeong-hwa?
Do I have to answer you?
I want to know exactly why
you're turning me down.
Yes, it's her.
As I expected.
Okay.
Have you all heard?
One of my colleagues got divorced,
but pretended she was never married
to get promoted and got busted.
So it caused a big scene.
My gosh, I can't believe
anyone would do that.
Do they have to go that far
just for a promotion?
Isn't it weirder to penalize someone
for getting divorced?
Divorce isn't a crime.
Even so, they still lied.
Don't they feel guilty?
What a fraud.
I can't believe that.
How can a team lie to each other?
I'm glad our team
doesn't have someone like that.
What? Yes we do.
What? On our team?
Really? No one knows?
Pyeong-hwa, you didn't tell them?
Wait, was your divorce a secret?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought everyone knew.
You don't have a kid though, do you?
Or do you?
Having fun?
Why are you so mad?
I was just sharing a fact.
It's all true.
And I know I was your junior,
but you shouldn't use that tone
to the purser.
This is just like you.
Wait.
Wait, Pyeong-hwa.
Will you please just go?
I'm incredibly embarrassed right now.
Sa-rang.
Yes, Ha-na.
You should take a break.
You don't have to try so hard around us.
No, it's all right.
She's right.
We got this. You should take a break.
Okay?
I'm fine.
You aren't fine.
This is a huge scandal.
Everyone talks about you
no matter where you go.
How could you be okay?
The article wasn't written properly.
The article was incorrect.
It's not a scandal.
It's a love story.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- No, I should apologize.
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
Don't say that.
- Please take these.
- Me?
Thank you.
Please be nice to my girlfriend.
I'm asking you as her boyfriend,
not as the head manager.
Please share these.
Are you already helping her?
Hey.
Mr. Gu, may I share a word?
Yes, please.
Sa-rang is part of King the Land,
and she's our dear family.
Even without your request,
we'll look after her
and make sure she isn't hurt.
You don't have to worry so much.
Thank you.
Bye.
He's so cool.
He's such a romantic.
You must be so happy.
Even a man would fall for him.
- Thanks, Sa-rang.
- Thank you.
Thanks, Sa-rang.
This looks delicious.
It really does.
Did you all see the articles?
What do you think?
I thought it was quite serious.
It wasn't just a regular scandal.
She's our staff.
I met with a few reporters,
and it's highly likely
for the story to take a worse turn.
What do you mean?
That the hotel's successor…
is a player who seduces his staff members.
I agree with him.
No matter what the facts are,
this did have an impact
on the image of our hotel.
I even saw an awful comment that said,
"Is King Hotel
more like a motel for couples?"
We, the board of directors,
decided to come together
and oppose Mr. Gu's promotion
to president.
We should do that.
If the public doesn't approve of him,
our stock price will drop.
Why are you all here together?
I see.
You were having a meeting
without telling me.
Yes.
The hotel is in trouble.
So? Did the emergency meeting go well?
Yes.
The board members
have something to share with you, sir.
- Really?
- Yes, sir.
Because of Mr. Gu's recent scandal…
Hold that thought.
I have something to say too.
May I go first?
Yes, sir.
The articles…
were your doing, weren't they?
A reporter asked,
so I just shared the truth.
Did you think
this would make me disappointed in Won
and give everything to you?
Don't get ahead of yourself, Father.
You have caused greater damage
just for your personal gain!
Get your facts straight.
I'm not the one who damaged the hotel.
It's Won.
Politics suit you better
than business management.
You're to give up
every position you hold here
and leave King Hotel.
Father.
Yes, my daughter.
If you want to say something, go ahead.
This was your plan all along.
Everything was your son's.
Your honesty is way overdue.
If you have more to say, go ahead.
Like that would change anything.
You don't care about me anyway.
From a long time ago until now,
you've never cared about me,
not even once.
CERTIFICATE OF ACHIEVEMENT
GU HWA-RAN
- Hello, Ms. Hwa-ran.
- Where's Dad?
He's on the second floor.
Good job.
Now pass it to your mom. Okay.
All right! Good.
- Go.
- Nice.
You can do it this time, Won.
You shoot this time.
- Go, Won.
- It's my turn to block you.
Looking good.
Shoot! Great!
- Won, head it.
- Pass!
- Head it!
Nice job.
I'm going to score, okay?
Get ready.
Block it, Won. That's right.
Why don't you try shooting?
Hey, it's a goal!
Great job.
Well done.
Honey.
Grandma, we're here.
You two aren't even married.
- Don't say "we."
- Ma'am.
Your grandson-in-law is here.
You're here.
Grandson-in-law candidate number one.
Our relationship got on the news,
so please leave out "candidate."
That's what you want.
Why are you in such high spirits?
Looks like you're the one
who published them.
No.
It wasn't me.
I know you did that
to tell everyone
because I wouldn't approve.
I'm not that crafty.
You already know he wouldn't.
Goodness, you're already taking his side?
Do you like him that much?
My gosh.
Well, I'll be.
Come this way.
If you ever make Sa-rang cry,
I'm going to kill you.
That will be the last day of your life,
so remember that.
I will never let that happen
and be good to her.
Stop smiling.
Don't. You might grow on me.
What should I begin with?
Peeling onions?
If you're dying to help,
get changed first.
- Yes.
- I saw a car parked outside.
Is your rich grandson-in-law…
He is here.
I had no idea
you were such an established man.
I should've noticed back then.
One moment.
Have one. Drink up.
Thank you.
He's here.
Do you even have to ask?
Our town's rich grandson-in-law.
Please take this.
Sa-rang is such a big shot now.
Okay.
Take a nice picture.
- A photo?
- Yes.
Why do you want a picture?
He's just a candidate.
Candidate or not,
it's my first time
seeing a chaebol in real life.
- Take it.
- Just one?
One, two, three.
- Okay.
- One more.
Just take one. We're all waiting.
Yes, one per person.
You know me, right?
The ginseng chicken soup.
Yes.
Give me your autograph.
I'll put it on the wall.
I don't have an autograph.
It's simple. Write out
three syllables of your name.
- Come on.
- I only have two syllables.
Yes, two.
And write down, "The soup is savory
and the meat is amazing."
Just do it.
- "The soup is…"
- Savory.
The meat is amazing.
"The meat is…"
- He's so handsome.
- His penmanship is impressive too.
- Okay, a selfie.
- Me too.
You look great.
- My gosh.
- My turn.
- Mine too.
- Give me one too.
Your autograph.
Sign here.
- Write "I love you."
- Here.
Aunties.
That's enough.
Then you should line up.
- Do one for me.
- Me too.
What autograph?
Why are you frowning?
Let's make the picture look good.
Do it quickly.
I have to open for business.
One, two.
- I'm taking it.
- Okay.
Move aside.
As soon as I get a job, it's over for you.
You should've been good to Mom
while she was nice.
You reap what you sow.
It's your punishment.
- Where did you learn those words?
- You always said that to Mom.
Dad.
You should wipe that place too.
Make it look sparkling clean.
Darn it!
There's no end to these chores!
That's the thing with chores.
Your work doesn't really show,
and no one gives you credit.
What are you doing?
Cho-rong told you to wipe there.
Cho-rong, Grandma is home.
Mom.
- Mom.
- What's going on?
Why is my son holding a rag?
You're home, Mother.
Forget your greetings.
Why is the head of this household
holding a rag in his hand?
I can't believe
I lived long enough to see this nonsense.
I must've lived for too long.
Good grief.
This house is such a mess.
Father, Mother,
I have something to say to you.
As if.
- Gosh.
- I want coffee.
Red ginseng honey tea
for Father and Mother.
Look at her.
My son
- really did that?
- Yes.
Your son did that.
He didn't tell us that he quit his job,
used up his severance pay,
and even took out a loan.
It wasn't a loan. It was a cash advance.
You punk. Shut your mouth.
Mom, indoor golf.
- Nice shot!
- Right.
He even played golf with that money.
Da-eul, listen up.
You are no longer our daughter-in-law.
You're the head of our household.
Dad.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
The head of our household can't go hungry!
What are you doing?
The head of our household hasn't eaten.
Get cooking.
Me?
Mom!
Will you clean the house all day?
Go cook!
The head of the household must eat well
for our home to be in great condition.
Whatever. You do it, Mom.
You punk.
Grandma, nice shot!
Go make dinner!
Stop pestering me about food!
As for the hotel chain business,
handle every step yourself.
Yes, I plan on doing that.
Don't send your staff overseas.
You should go abroad yourself.
Yes.
Okay.
I need to get some rest.
Why…
won't you ask me anything?
If I do, will anything change?
No.
There are high expectations
for the chain business.
That also means
many are jealous of you.
Bring back good results
without making mistakes.
Yes, I'll do that.
Our best talent. Have you been well?
Yes, sir. Have you been well too?
It's always the same for me.
Allow me to serve your meal.
Okay.
When will your other party join you?
Should I warm up the rice and soup later?
Sit down.
That's your seat.
- Me?
- I came here to treat
our best talent to a meal.
Why? Do you feel uncomfortable?
No, sir.
You do know you're very dear to me, right?
Yes, sir. I'm always grateful for that.
I understand why Won likes you.
And it's scarier because of that.
You two aren't kids,
so I won't tell you to break up.
Instead,
go somewhere quiet
until things settle down.
Is this a request or an order?
It's an order
as the chairman of King Hotel.
If it's your order, I must do as you say.
Once you think things over away from him,
you'll realize what the best decision is.
I'm sorry. Let's eat.
It's getting cold.
My gosh.
- Did I keep you waiting?
- No.
Your face is cold.
I told you to wait somewhere warm.
The breeze was refreshing.
Is something going on?
No.
But you look so…
Why?
Do I look that ugly?
What kind of nonsense is that?
It's so cozy and nice.
I agree.
Anyway,
we can't meet for a while.
I have a business trip abroad.
For how long?
About three weeks.
That's not so bad.
I just said three weeks.
That's almost a month.
You're okay with that?
I already miss you to death.
You're leaving to work.
Go do a great job.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
But still,
since we can't meet for a while,
don't go home tonight.
What are we going to do?
Let's go somewhere.
At this hour?
Where?
See? I told you.
I knew it'd be closed.
You're right. It's closed.
Let's go.
Wait.
Ta-da.
Did you rent out the entire place?
Wait.
I rented out the entire place.
Why? Do you not like amusement parks?
No, I love them!
It's so pretty.
Let's go.
Our night has just begun.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Why would anyone ride that?
Why would you come here
if not to go on the rides?
Well, you just come for the vibe.
What are you talking about?
We're already here,
so we have to go on the rides.
Let's go.
Wait, are you scared?
I'm a guy who doesn't know
what getting scared means.
- But you look scared.
- Come on.
I even go skydiving.
That's so cool. So let's go.
What now?
I thought about it,
and I should stay down here
to take pictures of you.
Don't get on if you're scared.
I can go alone.
Wait.
Let's go.
Not here.
- Are you crying?
- No.
Don't go on rides if you're scared.
I'm not scared.
I was just that thirsty.
If you go skydiving,
why are you scared of this?
That's very different.
Up there, I make the choice to jump.
But leaving my life
in the hands of that machine
is a totally different story.
It's different.
Thank you
for trying to do everything with me.
Of course I should.
I'll always do everything with you.
Good luck with your business trip.
If you miss me, tell me right away.
I'll give up everything and fly back.
Okay?
Don't worry about me.
Finish your job and take your time.
Okay.
- Let's go if you're done.
- What?
- Already?
- Yes.
- We have many more to ride.
- I'm not done yet.
I'm not done yet. Let's take a break.
Get up now.
Yes, ma'am!
Attaboy.
I'm on my flight.
I'll be back.
I love you.
Have a nice trip.
I love you too.
KING TOURIST HOTEL
MANAGEMENT POLICY
CUSTOMER SATISFACTION
Hello.
- Bo-yeon.
- What?
It's you, Cheon Sa-rang.
- Have you been well?
- Why are you here?
I was appointed here.
Stop talking nonsense.
This isn't a place for people like you.
Who are people like me?
Big shots like you.
You made it to King the Land, didn't you?
Only the worst transgressors end up here.
Is this that…
Yes, you're right.
The place you can't escape
once you get in,
the infamous place of exile,
King Tourist Hotel.
Why are you here?
Don't ask. It breaks my heart.
Someone else got fired
from the room inspection team.
Again? Why?
For being fat.
That's why I told everyone
to stay out of Ms. Gu's way
when she shows up.
They never get the hang of it.
But Ms. Gu's too much too.
She wants to fit everyone
in a certain size.
Hello, ma'am!
Get rid of her.
Follow me.
You know that a tourist hotel
is different from a regular hotel, right?
Yes.
Hotels abide by the Public Health Act
as a lodging business,
but tourist hotels are
tourist accommodation businesses
under the Tourism Promotion Act.
You have the answer to everything,
just as you always do.
It's because I was taught well
from the very best when I began.
It's all thanks to you.
You've become good with words
while I was gone.
This is the lowest subsidiary
among King Group,
but there is one good thing
about this place.
Board and lodging for staff.
Use the bed by the window.
There's a uniform in the closet,
so get changed and come to the lobby.
Okay.
Sa-rang.
I saw the news.
I saw it too.
Everyone here was kicked out,
so we're like family here.
You don't have to worry.
CHEON SA-RANG
Hermès.
Are you okay? Is everything fine?
Pretty much, other than the fact
that my entire team knows now.
But you know, secrets don't last forever.
I was always worried
about when it would get out.
I think this is for the better.
Byeong-gu will stop blackmailing me too.
What about Ro-un?
He's just a junior.
What about you?
Is Chung-jae looking for a job?
No idea. He'll figure it out on his own.
He stopped going to indoor golf though.
Cho-rong says people never change,
but what can I do?
She said that?
Hey, she's better than me.
Sa-rang loves this.
Seriously.
I wonder if she's eating all right.
Should we call her?
She's too busy. She rarely picks up.
It's been two weeks,
and she hasn't visited Seoul.
She'll return soon, right?
No idea.
I have a feeling something is going on.
What is this?
Are you moving?
No, a business trip.
How long could that be
for you to pack so much?
I wonder. When will I come back?
What is it?
I'll be back.
Let's talk then.
She said she'd tell us
when she's back, so let's wait.
Right, she's not the type
who shares these things.
Exactly.
I'm sure she's troubled alone,
pretending to be fine.
Why don't we go see her?
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- When is your day off?
- What about you?
One second.
KING TOURIST HOTEL
You're checked in. Enjoy your stay.
- Sa-rang.
- Yes?
The restaurant needs backup
and called for help.
You should go.
All right.
Hey, miss!
Yes?
We stayed here for over three hours
and refilled our coffee twice.
Is there anything on the house?
What kind of hotel is this?
You didn't order anything else,
but just coffee?
Why?
Coffee is enough.
What more are you trying to sell?
Good grief, you charge 10,000 won
for this bitter coffee
just because you call yourself a hotel.
Where's your conscience? Isn't that so?
Exactly.
Your stomach must hurt so much
from drinking just bitter coffee.
I'll bring some hot water
and a few cookies in secret.
It must be because she's from Seoul.
There's some talking to her.
You are
very clever.
Please give me a moment.
I missed the smell of Seoul.
This is so nice.
Wait.
Are you calling Sa-rang?
I should tell her I'm here.
You're going to call her
after three weeks?
You should just show up and surprise her.
Every moment of a relationship
should be special.
How did you start dating her
without knowing a thing?
You can talk to me again
once you try dating.
Who says I've never dated?
Everyone at the hotel knows.
Really?
The person you have called is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
I arrived at the airport.
I miss you.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
How was your business trip?
Good. Where's Sa-rang?
She was reappointed.
- Reappointed?
- Yes.
I only heard it from my manager.
To where?
I'm not so sure.
Ha-na.
When I first came to this hotel,
I said something like this.
That from now on,
I'll make this hotel
a place without fake smiles.
Is that smile…
genuine?
I'm sorry, Mr. Gu.
We were ordered
not to share a word regarding Sa-rang.
Where is Ms. Cheon Sa-rang?
Who reappointed her?
We do not know who reappointed her.
I just know
she went to King Tourist Hotel.
- King Tourist Hotel?
- Yes.
It's been about three weeks.
Three weeks?
- Is something going on?
- No.
Don't worry about me.
Finish your job and take your time.
Okay. Thank you.
Won.
This…
is a pocket watch.
Don't lose it.
Okay.
Always keep it on you.
Of course.
Mom, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Won.
It's me, Mom.
KING THE LAND
I'm sorry I'm late.
You should be in King the Land.
Let's go back now.
Don't drive Won into a corner anymore.
Let him live his life the way he wants to.
What did you do?
This is why you can't be loved.
It is a design
that symbolizes unchanging love.
I have something I want to say today.
I gave her money and she left on her own.
What cheap love.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs