KING THE LAND
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Are you still mad?
I'm sorry. I won't do that again.
Do you know what you did wrong?
Of course I do. I'm really sorry.
What are you sorry for?
Everything.
I'm sorry for all of it,
no matter what it is.
Forget it.
You're bound to repeat the same mistakes.
I have zero hope in you.
No, I'll never do that again.
I'll be good to you.
Once my schedule slows down,
we can go on a trip in two or three weeks.
You wanted to go to Gangneung.
No, Sokcho.
Yes, Sokcho.
You wanted the spicy noodle soup there.
Potato dumpling soup.
Right.
Come with me, okay?
Let's go somewhere quiet.
I have something to tell you.
- What is it?
- We'll talk when we get there.
Can't you just tell me now?
Why?
I'm meeting my club members.
It's an important occasion.
So you're here
not to actually apologize to me
but to clear your conscience
before meeting with your friends.
Don't say it like that.
I had to push the time back
to wait for you.
I tried to be understanding
since no one is perfect.
I wanted to try my best
with the person I chose to be with.
But…
it's pointless to be considerate
to someone who doesn't value me.
You don't deserve it.
Okay.
I'll tell them I'll be late,
so let's go eat something.
Something simple like gimbap?
Let's go.
What's wrong? Don't you want gimbap?
It's over.
I feel too sorry for myself
to keep seeing you.
All of a sudden?
When one person always humors another,
that person gets ruined.
I think I ruined you.
I came all the way here for you.
I can't believe you're this selfish.
One second.
Hey, is everyone there?
Go ahead and get started.
No, I'm almost done. I'll leave soon.
Something came up.
I'll hang up soon. Hold on.
Order whatever.
We're splitting the bill anyway.
I'll call you back.
Sa-rang!
Wait!
There's no way
I'm feeling jealous
or something like that.
Me?
I can't believe this.
You just littered.
Driver's license, please.
Here.
Sir, you have to pick that up.
Please throw this out.
We don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Was that for your girlfriend?
No.
You got it as a gift for her,
but you threw it out.
Something happened.
I said no.
Your girlfriend must've had another man.
We can tell right away
when we see a situation.
This isn't the first time.
She must be pretty.
Well,
sure.
I'd say she is
quite pretty.
And smiles often.
That's a part of her job.
She's pretty and she smiles a lot?
A woman like that will
have you in her grasp before you know it.
So don't get played and snap out of it.
Pull yourself together.
She's not like that!
She already has you.
No, forget it.
It's fine.
Here. You can just go.
What do you mean?
Just give me that ticket.
I just feel bad for you.
You saved money today,
so buy yourself a drink and wake up.
- Okay?
- It's not like that!
Why are you such a softie?
I know this because I've been there.
Forget it.
Nothing I say will get through to you.
Just go.
Go let her toy with you.
You'll regret it once you're hurt.
Then you'll remember what I said.
Go.
Man.
Just go.
Go!
Listen to what I'm about to say, my man.
How many relationships have you had?
With friends?
With women.
I'm a busy man.
Okay.
Not much dating experience,
but you seem to have some money.
That makes you the perfect prey, right?
And what drives you more insane
is that you don't even know
how you really feel.
"Do I really like her?
Am I just curious about her?"
"Am I in love?"
It gets so confusing!
Right?
And how do I know?
My woman was very pretty too.
Her face was the vision of love itself.
- Love?
- By any chance,
do you know that song?
Your eyes, nose, lips
The way you caressed me
Even all those tiniest touches
I can never forget her.
I thought I could die
a hundred times over for her.
I should've held onto her.
I should've screamed,
"I'm your man, not him!"
After that one moment of hesitation,
after turning away like that…
I've been tormented ever since.
Buck up.
Jeez.
What am I doing in front of a stranger?
Bye!
Your call cannot be completed.
You will be redirected…
PAENG
RECENT CALLS
GRANDMA
Grandma.
Of course I had dinner. It's late.
What about you?
Can I come over tomorrow?
Yes, it's my day off.
I want to eat your food.
Of course. Your food is the best.
Yes.
Your food is my favorite.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I'll bring some tomorrow.
EPISODE 4
KETTLE-COOKED COW'S HEAD GUKBAP
My daughter-in-law.
Two bottles of soju, please.
Okay, coming. Two bottles of soju.
Goodness.
They'll be even sweeter
coming from my daughter-in-law.
This is the last round.
You should go home and sleep.
I'll sleep as long as I want
once I'm dead.
That again!
Don't have too much.
My daughter-in-law,
some more radish kimchi.
Okay, radish kimchi!
Grandma's got it.
All of you.
Why do you call my granddaughter
"my daughter-in-law"?
I called over my kind daughter-in-law.
What's this mean granny doing here?
Cut your crap!
You two don't even have sons.
Don't let me catch you
calling my granddaughter
your daughter-in-law again.
Got it?
My daughter-in-law.
- A bottle of rice wine, please.
- Why you…
Okay, your daughter-in-law is coming!
Goodness.
Here.
Is something
going on with you?
What do you mean?
I just came to see you.
Your food is the best.
If you're concerned about me,
you should get married soon.
Da-eul already has a big kid.
You always say that.
Is that all you have to say to me?
She got married early.
Pyeong-hwa is single too.
Don't get me started on Pyeong-hwa.
She's impossible.
The thought of marriage
isn't entering your head
because you two stick together.
Kick her out soon.
I should leave before you nag me more.
Wait.
I'll pack some side dishes for you.
Go give some to that guy
Yu-nam or whatever.
Don't.
Why not?
We broke up.
We just did.
Good.
I'm glad.
That rotten jerk.
It's his loss.
You don't even know the reason.
I know you.
I'm sure he's the one at fault.
Forget about money.
You should be with a man
who's good to you.
I'm glad things ended.
Yeah.
Me too.
Also,
when you feel upset in the future,
don't hold it in and just tell people.
Okay?
Throw a fit if you want to.
If you want to be a crybaby, be one too.
And you can tell me everything.
Okay. I'll do that.
This is so nice.
Grandma, you're the best.
Goodness, my dear little girl.
Great job.
I'm glad you did that.
First Royal Hotel's LVIP Lounge
just became the top of the industry
surpassing King the Land of King Hotel!
Chairman Han, your wish finally came true.
It's been a lifelong dream of yours
to surpass King Hotel.
It's just the lounge.
Don't make such a big fuss.
Do you want to make a bet?
It was just the lounge this time,
but will it end with just that?
You should make a bet
with your hotels at stake.
Our hotels aren't on the same level.
I hear you spent a fortune
to become number one.
Can you handle it?
It's called an investment.
My victory over King Hotel
after years of losses
already gives me
a different outlook on business.
All right.
You can try your best to catch up.
Okay!
What does revenue from the lounge mean
in hotel management?
Since the clientele is mostly VIPs,
the higher the revenue,
the more sophisticated
and classy the hotel is.
That's why competing hotels
compare the lounge revenue,
not the overall sales.
If you knew that,
why did First Royal Hotel
take first place?
I trusted you two
and left you to work together.
What have you done?
They only increased
their short-term revenue
with excessive promotions…
Such complacent thoughts
are the shortcut to rock bottom.
It may be the lounge this time,
but that doesn't mean it'll end there.
Work together and do whatever it takes
to reclaim first place in lounge revenue.
Yes, Dad.
The same goes for Distribution and Air.
Climb up so high that First Royal Hotel
won't even dream of competing with us.
I'll see what you two can do
and decide if I'll bequeath
the whole group
or split it between you two.
Understood?
Yes.
What's your plan?
He told us to join forces,
but you have no power.
Not yet.
And in the future too.
So don't try to meddle with anything
and sit this one out.
I'll handle this.
So this must be how it feels.
What?
Getting looked down on.
It's not even news.
Did you think you were a big shot?
Someone said…
All people are the same.
That means
everyone should be treated equally.
…that everyone
should be treated with equal respect.
You're an exception.
You're an upstart nobody.
I know.
So don't be scared of me.
Thank you for everything.
I'll head upstairs then.
As you already know…
No.
You have no idea
what King the Land is like.
I'm sure the chairman put you there
because he doesn't know any better.
You'll get kicked out soon,
so don't try too hard.
Okay.
It's been a while, Su-mi.
Hello, Ms. Jeon.
Hey.
Ms. Cheon Sa-rang?
Yes.
I'm the manager of King the Land.
I'm here to take you there.
Hello, my name is Cheon Sa-rang.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Let's get along.
Ms. Jeon.
She went to a two-year college.
Okay.
Let's go upstairs.
I'll give you a tour.
Most of our guests here are chairpersons
who are ranked within the top 30
in the business world.
One VVVIP guest often spends
more than the hotel's daily revenue.
That's why we call this place
the hotel's first class.
It's a dream for all concierges
to work up here,
but in reality,
not everyone gets to do that.
I never imagined
that I'd get to work on this floor.
It honestly doesn't feel real.
I'll do my best not to become
a nuisance to King the Land.
Any takes on this piece?
I don't know much about art,
but it looks great.
Right?
The chairman got this himself in New York.
He has an eye for art, doesn't he?
Yes, I think so.
He also recruited you here himself.
I'm sure he has a reason.
I trust his judgment.
So don't mind those
who talk behind your back.
You must respect yourself first
before others do.
Okay.
Let's go. Your uniform is ready.
Hello, my name is Cheon Sa-rang.
Have you thought about it?
Yes.
All night.
And even now.
What will you do?
I should've held onto her.
I should've screamed,
"I'm your man, not him!"
I'm thinking.
Again?
You're still thinking?
How will that help reclaim
the first in revenue for King the Land?
What?
Revenue?
Do you know
how First Royal Hotel took first place?
For months, they followed
some ginseng diggers around
and got a hold of wild ginseng.
They sold that with wine
for 100 million won.
I'm 100% sure that's what Ms. Gu will do.
That's why
- we should do it first.
- And copy them?
No, we're only following the trend.
But money should be earned honestly.
Says who?
Who said that to you?
I doubt they were rich.
That's a classic line from the poor.
Why are you so passionate today?
You be the head manager!
I'll end up as a nobody
if I just trust you and sit around.
You got a full-time job here.
That's all. There's nothing after that.
I must have sided with
the wrong guy.
Go. It's not too late.
Get out of here.
"I'll take King Group for myself!"
Do you not have such manly ambitions?
Why would I?
You don't want anything
and can't be bothered.
Right. You know me.
That's because you have too much,
for insufficiency brings desire.
You can throw out your fortune
and position to me.
I'll gladly become your trash can.
Whatever.
I'll be one for you. Here, throw them out.
Feel free.
Dump them here.
Among the things I have,
the thing I want to dump the most…
is you.
Get out of here.
I don't want to go.
- Not until you dump something.
- Get out.
No way. Give me something.
Get out of…
The new staff of King the Land
is here to greet you.
Hello.
I'm Cheon Sa-rang,
and it's my first day at King the Land.
Our kind Ms. Sa-rang,
you finally got here. Congrats.
I hear King the Land
is staffed with our best employees.
Yes, we all work there with pride.
But she's now a part of your staff?
I know her a little.
You'll need to give
extra attention and training
to enlighten her on the sophistication
and basic manners
befitting King the Land, Ms. Jeon.
Yes, sir.
As per your words,
I'll do my best to be more sophisticated
as I learn basic manners
befitting King the Land.
Yes, you will.
- You may go.
- Yes, Mr. Gu.
Excuse us.
Yearly business plan.
Our annual revenue last year was…
Why were you like that to her?
What?
As if you like our kind Ms. Sa-rang.
What is it? What's going on?
Like a pathetic little kid.
What?
- "Pathetic"?
- Yes.
- "Little kid"?
You like her,
but you can't tell her.
You want to get her attention,
but you have no idea what to do.
That's why you pick on her and act rudely.
That's what kids do.
I don't like her!
She's such a phony.
She's totally not my type.
Why did you get so angry over a joke,
as if I saw right through you?
I'm sorry, Mr. Gu.
You have no sense of humor,
no consideration, and no popularity.
That's why you're not seeing anyone.
Hello, Ms. Jeon.
Everyone say hello.
Ms. Cheon Sa-rang
will join us starting today.
Nice to meet you.
We're all like family here,
so you'll fit in soon.
Learn a lot from your experienced seniors,
and tell me if there's trouble.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll teach her well.
Let her sign the NDA first.
I need to go to the office.
Goodbye.
Ms. Jeon is nice, isn't she?
Yes, she seems wonderful.
You're right.
She's kind to everyone
without any prejudice,
and she's warmhearted too.
But I'm not like her.
I believe distinctions must exist.
We all graduated
from well-known universities in Seoul.
The fact that a two-year college graduate
like you made it here
belittles the time and effort we put in
to get to this place.
If you wish to be accepted,
you must prove you have what it takes
to be here against our tradition.
You can try hard, but it'll be tough.
Brace yourself.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Follow me.
Du-ri.
Is this place for anybody now?
Hey, the chairman put her here.
I knew it.
I know girls like her very well.
She's the type we don't want on our turf.
The guests we receive here
are in the top 0.0001% of the nation.
This says you must not disclose
who you saw here
and the conversations they had.
If you disclose anything about this place,
you'll be held liable
and must compensate for any damages.
Sign it.
Okay.
Are you on social media?
- Yes.
- Delete your accounts.
It's a breach of contract
to upload any photos of this place.
Can I just not take photos while up here?
Then you can go back to your old post.
I'll delete them.
SIGNED BY CHEON SA-RANG
KING MALL
Is this store the top in sales?
Yes, ma'am.
Who's in charge?
Hello.
I'm the supervisor, Do Ra-hee.
Which stores do you work with?
The airports in Incheon, Gimpo, Jeju,
as well as shops downtown.
Work here from tomorrow.
Keep this shop as our main focus
and double the sales.
Can you do that?
Yes, I can.
Ms. Do is going to start working here?
She's the most infamous witch
among the old witches.
What will happen to us now?
She's that bad?
Her name already rhymes with crazy…
Manager Do Ra-hee.
It's okay.
We'll do the actual work anyway.
Let's go.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
You couldn't meet their eyes.
- Hello.
Is this the team with the lowest number
for in-flight duty-free sales?
There are three teams in the lowest rank,
and this is one of them.
Purser?
Yes, ma'am.
What's your plan?
We'll do our best.
Which you haven't done so far?
No, ma'am.
We'll do our best to bring up the sales.
Any specific plans?
We'll push the sales more
so that none of our guests
leave the flight empty-handed.
That means you can easily
double the sales compared to now.
We'll do our best.
Don't let me down.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye!
Who is she?
I've never seen--
You must've been shocked.
- The managing director.
- That almost killed me.
You do realize the Chinese restaurant
has the highest sales in every hotel?
Yes, I'm aware of that.
So what's going on here?
I'm going to try the dishes myself,
so change your old recipes
and make new dishes by this week.
By this week, ma'am?
You can't?
No, I can do that.
- Get rid of him.
- Yes, ma'am.
Get rid of him.
Yes, ma'am.
I prepared a meeting with the staff
regarding our revenue.
Why should I go to something you prepared?
Look at Ms. Gu.
She visited every single department
and gave them a new sales goal.
Great.
I won't have to do a thing.
She already fired two people today.
"Get rid of him. And him."
She was so scary too.
One of them was too fat,
the other was too messy.
The staff?
Of course. Why would she fire the board?
What if all of the employees
of King the Land get fired?
And most importantly,
what if I get kicked out?
I did nothing wrong.
This may not be a big deal to you,
but a mere employee like me
can get fired over this.
You might work
at daddy's company as a hobby,
but some people work hard
just to make ends meet.
Does this meeting
include the staff
of King the Land as well?
Of course. Especially if you're attending.
Let's go.
Mr. Gu is holding a meeting with the staff
regarding the hotel's revenue.
A special promotional event for our VIPs
would be the most effective way
to increase short-term revenue.
Go ahead and do that.
If you don't like that,
we can increase the per-transaction sales
by having premium wine
or limited-edition whiskey
as our main liquor.
Okay.
If you don't like any of those methods,
please let me know
the direction you are looking for.
It's not that I don't like them.
As someone on the ground,
you must know better than me,
so I want to follow your suggestions.
What's the most effective method?
To be frank, pushing incentives.
Then let's do that.
However, providing just 30,000 won
in incentives like last time
for selling a liquor set
worth 40 million won
won't have a huge impact.
What?
You got only 30,000 won in incentives
for selling a product
worth 40 million won?
It's my first time hearing this.
Yes.
Make it big enough to have an impact.
Let me know your sales goal.
I'll look over it
and implement it right away.
Thank you.
We'll do our best.
That's all for the meeting.
PHONY CHEON
CALL
MESSAGE
I need to talk to you after work.
Okay.
Is she still at work?
Did she not see it?
How could she not see it?
Is she still working?
Is she working overtime?
Do I not have signal?
Seven. Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
One, two, three…
Just until this hourglass runs out.
It hasn't run out yet.
PHONY CHEON
MISSED CALL
Ms. Gu came by today and it was like war.
She came by Da-eul's store as well.
I heard she did that at the hotel too.
No idea.
- You don't know?
- No.
A few of the employees were exiled.
Why were they exiled? To where?
How would I know?
I hear your hotel
has a special place for the exiles.
I don't know.
Who is it?
Well,
I don't need to know their place of exile
when I'm about to get axed.
Why? Did you do something wrong?
She wants us to double the sales.
If we make low in-flight sales,
we'll become traitors.
How can you double them?
If they keep pestering the staff,
we'll somehow bring in sales,
so they'll pester us
until the point of death.
Didn't they discuss sales with you?
We get incentives for pushing sales.
Really?
Your team is the best off.
How much?
No idea.
It's not like the incentives
or the lack thereof
will make me work more or less.
I'm just going to do my job.
But I'm not getting anywhere
although I'm doing more than my job.
I'm suffocated in the middle,
pushed around by my seniors and juniors.
If you need help, ask Da-eul for a lesson.
Her shop had the top sales.
I really should.
Good for Da-eul.
She's the manager,
the best salesperson, married,
and has an adorable daughter.
She has it all.
I'm jealous!
I'm home.
- Mom's here.
- Hey, Cho-rong.
What did you draw?
You're home.
Make dinner. I'm hungry.
Okay.
Look at that.
What's with them?
Mother, I need to go grocery shopping.
There's no food.
Why didn't you go beforehand?
It'll take forever for us to eat.
I made braised short ribs
and pollack soup this morning,
but a thief must've come and eaten it all.
That's why you should make
more than enough when you cook.
Don't be so stingy with food.
Grandma.
Don't be mean to Mom.
Aunt, Uncle, and that darned family
came and finished everything.
Who taught you such a phrase?
Don't use such words.
While you're at it,
get some oxtail and make a hearty broth.
I must be low on energy.
- I haven't had an appetite.
- Jeez.
You cleared three bowls of rice
without an appetite?
I only had three bowls
because I had no appetite.
What are you waiting for?
Go get the groceries.
Okay, I'll be back soon.
Cho-rong, come with Mom.
Look at that.
Mom, our home isn't a restaurant.
Why does Aunt always come
and eat at our place?
I guess my food is much better.
She always comes and eats for free,
never even does the dishes,
and steals everything good
from our fridge.
Should we report her to the police?
Let's say it's because I'm a good cook
and give her a break.
Cho-rong, do you want a doll?
Hello? Where are you?
Can you come to the grocery store?
I have too much stuff.
Sorry, I'm out having dinner
with a client.
Still? Can't you sneak out?
How can I do that?
It's a part of work.
Okay. Make sure you eat well.
- Don't strain yourself.
- Okay.
You too.
Don't strain yourself and get a good rest.
I'll be late tonight,
so you should go to sleep first.
Bye.
I need to talk to you.
Would you like to order?
I asked to see you yesterday.
What? When?
Didn't you see the text?
I called you too.
- Do you know my number?
- Of course.
It's in your personnel record.
Don't you know mine, Phony Cheon?
I have no access to your personnel record.
Here.
That's my number. Save it.
So what did you want to say to me?
I must
ask you something.
Ask away.
Let's talk over dinner after work.
Wait.
Can't you just tell me now?
You treated me to juice
on Gapado last time.
I'd like to return the favor,
so I'll see you then.
No, it's okay.
I'm not okay.
I simply can't stand
owing someone a favor.
But I'm okay with it.
Is it too much
for you
to just say yes this once?
Well,
isn't it proper manners to check
if I have a prior engagement
before asking me to dinner?
Ms. Phony Cheon.
Do you have
plans for dinner
tonight?
No, I don't.
In that case,
would you like
to have dinner
with me?
I don't want to.
Why not? Why do you say no to me?
I didn't say no to you.
I said no to dinner.
Then Ms. Phony Cheon,
what do you like other than dinner?
It's just that it'd be so awkward
to eat alone with you.
So you won't order?
I won't.
I'm not eating!
What's with him?
Next.
And next.
You must choose a photo today.
They all look the same to me.
So much so that it's almost scary.
Please make your call.
I've decided.
Thank you. Which one?
I simply must have
dinner with her tonight.
Make dinner plans
with Ms. Cheon Sa-rang after work.
Make sure she comes.
Why? Is something going on?
- Tell her it's a welcome dinner.
- A welcome dinner?
Where at?
The hotel's
Japanese restaurant.
After the welcome dinner,
you must choose a photo, okay?
You have to. Please?
Hello, it's been a while.
A strong cup of coffee, please.
I'll bring it to the cockpit.
No, I'd like to have it here with you
in this cozy galley.
I'll bring it to you.
You're still as feisty as ever.
Eat dinner with me after the flight.
It's been a while.
No.
Here's your cozy cup of coffee.
Please excuse me.
Don't be so cheeky.
Who do you think will suffer
if I start acting nasty?
Do you still think I'm a joke?
No.
I still want you.
Hello.
Would you like something?
What? No.
I already got it.
Keep it up.
Did something happen?
It's not a big deal.
Do you have plans tonight?
I'm just going to rest.
How about having a beer with me?
No, I'm tired. I'm not in the mood.
My mom told me to treat you
and thank you for her scarf.
It's okay. I wanted to thank you first.
Well, I'm using her as an excuse.
I want to have dinner with you.
Let's get dinner together.
This is nice.
I think so too.
Don't you love it here?
The waves and the wind.
I love seeing you so happy.
Thank you for your help last time.
How could I not act
after seeing my senior
run for her life like that?
I was just doing you a favor
to make my life easier at work.
You don't have to thank me.
If that's the reason, I'm sorry.
Why?
You picked the wrong senior.
I'm the only one among my peers
who didn't make assistant purser.
If I don't get promoted next year,
people will know that I've been left out.
That'll be the end of me.
What about it?
What do you mean?
You won't benefit in any way
if you befriend me.
So stay away.
So what if I can't get promoted?
It hurts too much to fall from high-up.
I prefer the low and long haul.
Sounds great.
I'll have to be
one of your close associates.
You'll regret it later.
I never will.
What do you think about Mi-na?
She's a great girl.
She's very curious about you.
What about you?
What?
I'm very curious about you.
This way, please.
- Hello, Mr. Gu.
- Why?
- What is this?
A welcome dinner.
- Why?
- To welcome Ms. Cheon.
You told me to put a dinner together.
Is this really…
You're…
- They can eat and go.
- Don't be so shy.
Please go inside.
- Hello, Mr. Gu.
Let's take a group photo before we eat.
Okay, Hermès.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Look at that. You look great.
Cheers. Congrats.
Thank you.
Mr. Gu.
Thank you for sparing your time
for our rookie, sir.
Please eat.
- Maybe a toast?
- Let's just eat.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Ms. Cheon.
Is it not to your liking?
No, it's good.
How would you know without having any?
Do you not eat raw fish?
I'm fine.
Mr. No, prepare a steak for her.
It's a Japanese restaurant.
I know. I meant next door.
No, I'm fine, really.
Let me know
if any of you can't eat raw fish.
I'm fine. I'm not picky.
Me too. I like raw fish.
- Should I go?
- I'll be right back.
I thought that was the door.
I'm Edward Jung, the head chef
of King Hotel's Western restaurant.
This is an Angus sirloin steak,
a prime T-bone steak,
and an Australian lamb chop steak.
Have a lovely dinner.
Thank you.
Eat before it gets cold.
Will do.
Where are my manners?
Mr. No, cut it for her.
- Yes, sir.
- No, I can do it!
Can you feed yourself?
- Do you need help?
- No.
I'm fine.
Please eat.
Why did you call me out here?
Are you trying to put me in a tough spot?
Why would I?
I didn't ask for a welcome dinner.
And what was that huge steak?
Did you want to kill me?
I didn't…
This wasn't what I had in mind.
I saw that you couldn't eat raw fish,
so I got you steak.
Why are you angry over that?
You've never had to mind anyone.
Of course not.
You probably lived like a king
among servants.
I feel like I'm on pins and needles
because of your unnecessary kindness.
I already feel self-conscious enough.
Why do you feel self-conscious?
I was showing consideration
for this dinner I arranged.
That wasn't consideration.
It was more like a bomb.
From now on,
just pretend like you don't know me.
I don't need your consideration.
Please.
What went wrong?
GONG YU-NAM
Sa-rang!
- Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday.
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, dear Sa-rang
Am I allowed to be this happy?
No, you should be even happier.
This isn't enough.
Yes, so wish for bigger happiness
as you blow these out.
CHEON SA-RANG'S BIRTHDAY
Happy birthday!
You made all this?
Sure, I'm a seasoned homemaker.
Thank you.
I'm a seasoned eater.
Okay.
Here, open your present.
We picked it out together.
Gosh, thank you.
Let's see.
- What is this?
- Your birthday is tomorrow.
You can hang out with us today,
then have a wild night
with your boyfriend tomorrow.
He won't forget your birthday, right?
He did last year.
Didn't I tell you?
We broke up a while ago.
What? Why haven't you told us until now?
Sorry, I forgot.
I've been too busy lately.
How can you forget that?
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I actually feel relieved,
almost to the point
where I wonder if I even had a boyfriend.
I guess that was it.
Will you get back with him?
Never.
I'll get the beer. Turn on the music.
This is great. It's a party.
Sa-rang, get up.
Get up and show us.
Get up.
Let's go!
HEAD MANAGER GU WON
Do I seem like a guy
who hasn't had to consider others
because I was born into the right family?
A bit.
But who dared to tell you such a fact?
How brave of them.
Don't mind it though.
You were born this way.
I'm only jealous.
Please go inside, Mr. Gu.
I'll stop by King the Land first.
Why?
It's our kind Ms. Sa-rang's birthday,
so I got her our buffet voucher.
One of the employee benefits.
Look at you, showing your teeth.
Just leave me alone.
- You might bite me soon.
- I'm not doing anything
not because I can't fight,
but because I don't want to.
You say you don't want to fight,
yet you went behind my back
and had a strategy meeting.
I'm in charge of King the Land.
And you're under my charge at work.
Didn't you know you needed
my permission and approval
no matter what you do?
I didn't know.
I didn't look at the organizational chart.
I don't know why you came to work here,
but you'll have to fight me for life.
If you need money,
I'll give you what you want,
so leave.
I have plenty of money.
I'm telling you for your sake.
Don't end up like your mom.
See?
Nobody remembers her.
Both you and me.
That's life for a loser.
Okay?
And throw out that pocket watch.
How childish of you.
Are you looking for this?
- Give it back.
- I don't want to.
Give it back. It's mine.
She left because she didn't want you.
So forget about her.
No!
No…
I'll be the main server.
You can stand quietly in the back.
Don't meddle
and try to sell something expensive.
Yes, I understand.
I'd like some wine recommendations.
We recently got nice vintages
of Charrier Margaux and Zeña.
Which would go better with today's meal?
Let me get the sommelier
to provide a more detailed suggestion.
We can't wait that long.
Give us a suggestion.
Any bottle will go nicely
with the meal we have today.
You're that best talent, right?
Hello, sir.
She still has a great smile.
In that case,
let's get a suggestion
from the best talent of King Hotel.
In that case, may I suggest the Zeña?
It's a premium wine from Chile.
The smell of blackcurrant
and blackberries mixes nicely
with the smell of vanilla
from the oak barrel,
and you'll feel the fine-grained tannins
with the elegance of full-bodied wine.
I believe it'll go nicely
with your lamb chop steak.
You're well-versed in wine,
almost like an expert.
I'm a certified sommelier.
I knew I had a discerning eye for people.
I really want to recruit her.
I'll pay you twice as much.
Come work at my hotel.
I'm flattered, sir.
My goodness.
Should we get the meal ready?
Sa-rang, what are you doing?
There's a single-malt package
worth 40 million.
Why did you recommend wine?
You should've made him order whiskey.
This is why we say
you don't have the basics.
But the chairman asked
for a wine recommendation.
And you suggested wine too.
Whatever.
Make sure to sell more expensive items.
Try upselling.
Remember that.
Got it?
Yes, I'll remember that.
PERSONNEL RECORD
Mr. Gu.
If you tell me who you're looking for,
I'll look it up.
Can a record be left out of the server?
No, we typed in everyone since year one
as we digitized our system.
So why can't I find it?
It has to be there.
Our payroll and severance pay
are on our accounting system,
so nobody can delete the records.
Is that everything from 1989?
Yes.
Who are you looking for if I may ask?
Never mind.
Surprise! Happy birthday.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
I made reservations at a nice spot.
Are you still sulking?
We broke up.
I said I never wanted to see you again.
You weren't sulking over the gimbap?
That's why I made a reservation
at a high-end fine dining restaurant.
Don't sulk over some food.
Hey.
Do you think
I broke up with you over that?
If I had, I would've dumped you
hundreds of times already.
What do you take me for
to take what I said that way?
I'm sorry.
I'll be really good from now on.
I'm so sorry.
Stop saying you're sorry!
If you were really sorry,
you wouldn't have acted this way
to begin with.
I'm sick and tired of you.
Let's end this.
You're really harsh.
And you're selfish.
You can't make the call alone.
I can.
My love is over,
so do whatever you want with yours.
I never want to see you again.
Have you always been this harsh?
Are you the Sa-rang I know?
Let go of me.
We're now strangers.
This is my spot.
Excuse me?
This is
my spot.
KING THE LAND
Your outfit…
You two look so good together.
I knew it.
Who are you to…
She doesn't want to see you anymore.
- Why are you here?
- Why didn't you reply?
- Reply to what?
- My text.
- I did.
- And I replied to your reply.
I'm working right now.
I was just acting startled.
Look, it's a heart.
It's good.
Your favorite food, your favorite weather,
your favorite color.
Tell me everything you like.
Why do you want to know that?
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs