KING THE LAND
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Are you not going to tell me?
Do you want to see me die of frustration?
It's just…
I have a lot on my mind.
I'm wondering if the work I'm doing now
is what I really wanted to do at a hotel.
This isn't what I dreamed of.
I know.
I should be thankful for my job there
instead of complaining.
Goodness.
My baby has finally learned
to grumble and whine.
I always wondered
if I'd be able to see you do this
before I passed away.
What are you saying?
You should be telling me off,
saying that I can't have it all
and to just do my job.
No matter how well-known a restaurant is,
it's no use if it's not to your liking.
Who cares about the hotel?
You only live once.
You should do what you really want to do.
Don't mind other people,
and don't hesitate either.
Do everything you want to.
If it isn't the way,
you can take a detour.
If you fall off a cliff,
you can climb up again.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, Grandma.
You'll be fine.
I'm here for you,
so do whatever you want to do.
You deserve it.
Okay.
I'll do that.
Good.
I'm done.
I want to leave.
What do you exactly mean…
by leaving?
I want to quit my job at the hotel.
Was there a specific reason
that made you want to quit?
To me, a hotel was a place of happiness.
And that's why I became a concierge.
I wanted to provide the happiest day
to every guest who stayed at the hotel.
But what I'm doing right now
seems far from that.
Although King the Land may be fancy,
and I may make a lot of money
in the Dream Team,
it's not the life I want.
I also…
want to write my own story.
It sounded like a tough decision,
but it was a happy resolution.
That's true.
I want to make a hotel of my own,
no matter how tiny it is.
I want to try it on my own.
One second.
It's me.
Please cancel the event.
Thank you.
What did you just cancel?
It was something important.
But I'll do it later.
I'm sorry.
I must've startled you.
Don't be.
Congratulations.
You found what you really wanted to do,
and you're determined to try it.
Congratulations.
Perhaps that was
what I most wanted to hear from you.
Thank you
for sharing
your honest feelings.
But promise me one thing.
What is it?
When you work alone,
you'll face many difficulties.
You'll come across things
that are tough for you to bear alone.
When that happens, don't hesitate…
and call me.
I'll run over right away.
You're the prettiest today
since the day we first met.
You're dazzling.
I was going to blow my nose,
but I can't now that you said that.
Just blow your nose.
Even that looks pretty to me.
So what did you want to say to me?
Oh.
No matter where you are,
no matter what you do,
I'll always be on your side.
I wanted to tell you that.
Thank you.
Me too.
I'll always be on your side.
Excuse me.
May I take a photo of you two?
Sure.
You look great.
I'll take the photo now.
One, two, three.
Could you take one more?
Okay, one more time.
One, two, three.
FINALE
Thank you for seeing me today.
How could I turn down your offer
to treat me to a meal?
Are you trying to
kill your enemy with kindness?
I wanted to tell you something.
Yes, I'm sure you have lots to say.
I'm listening.
Well…
I would like to quit.
I came to tell you that.
May I ask
the reason?
I want to quit
and date him out in the open.
If I stay here,
I'd have to continue
following your orders.
Did you come to declare war?
I came to a realization
after spending time away from him.
I love him so much
that I can't live without him.
You may not be happy with me,
but I know I won't disappoint you.
This is exactly why I like you!
I apologize for my immaturity
and for not separating the personal
from the professional.
When it comes to my children,
I become rather ambitious.
It's all right. I understand.
Thanks to you,
I reached the highest position possible
and found out what I truly wanted.
So thank you.
That's why I'm going to do something
I really want to do.
I see.
I'm sure you'll do a great job,
no matter what it is.
Thank you.
It's my treat today, so please enjoy.
All right.
Thank you.
I'll enjoy it.
So delicious.
Sa-rang, thank you for your hard work.
This is for you. It's from all of us.
Thank you.
I learned so much from everyone.
Don't forget us no matter where you go.
I hope you'll always be happy.
Thank you, everyone.
I'll miss you all.
And Ms. Jeon,
you always helped me greatly.
I'll never forget that.
You've done well.
I want to hug her too.
Me too.
- Sa-rang.
- Don't go.
- Great work.
- Gosh.
You'll stay in touch, right?
- Yes.
- Don't forget us.
"President Gu Won."
Sa-rang.
- Hello.
- It's your last day.
It is.
Mr. Gu went out to work.
It's okay.
Anyway, with our kind Ms. Sa-rang gone,
who will watch over King Hotel?
The talented Mr. No is here,
so why are you worried?
That's true, right?
But with you gone,
my life will be too tiresome.
I must deal with his temper alone.
Don't say that.
He's very considerate of you.
Please take good care of him.
So he said that behind my back?
We should all get together soon
for a drink.
Okay, let's meet up.
Sounds good.
Good work.
Thank you.
I'll root for you.
Wait, why are you crying?
I am?
- Come on.
- I'll leave.
- What's with you?
- Are you staying? Bye.
CHEON SA-RANG
Wait, how did you find me here?
Congrats on your new chapter.
Thank you.
One second.
They say good shoes
take you to good places.
They're so pretty.
Thank you
for all of your hard work…
at King Hotel.
I get to leave with great memories
thanks to you.
Thank you.
Good work,
our number one best talent.
I was happy here,
President Gu Won.
You're always welcome to visit.
We'll have you as our VVIP guest.
It's an honor.
Please make me the VVVVVVIP.
Of course.
- Shall we?
- Okay.
- Can you give me 1,000 won?
- What?
I hear I need to get money
after giving shoes as a gift.
Only then will you not run away.
You're right. You knew that?
I can give you 1,000 won.
Wait, my wallet!
- Where is it?
- We left everything at the bus stop.
Sir, stop the car!
These chores never end.
I'll end up developing hand eczema.
- Put these on.
- Are you a wolf in sheep's clothing?
Thanks a lot.
I'm about to cry tears of gratitude.
If you have to do it anyway,
try to enjoy it.
But this isn't enjoyable!
I have no pleasure in life,
stuck at home all day!
It's your day off. You're leaving?
I signed up for a workout.
What? Are you out of your mind?
You need to help me out at home
on your day off!
Get a job within the month,
or I'm really done with you.
Do the dishes and clean the bathroom too.
Why am I the only one who has to do this?
Don't worry and go, Mom.
I'll keep my eyes on him.
Cho-rong, what's this?
An army drill sergeant.
These guys are the scariest.
You've got ten minutes.
Finish up in ten minutes. Understood?
No, I don't understand.
Then bunny hop until you get it!
Great job, Cho-rong.
Keep an eye on him. I'll be quick.
Okay, be careful of the traffic.
Yes, ma'am!
Thank you.
Please.
What do you think?
It does smell quite different.
It tastes completely different.
We know that too,
but I don't think it's necessary
to place premium coffee machines
used in junior suites and higher
in standard rooms as well.
I agree.
It blurs the service differentiation
between room types.
The standard room
is our most popular unit, right?
- Yes.
- Do you think it's a waste
to provide better coffee and services
to the majority of our guests?
They won't notice.
Is this change necessary?
It all tastes the same.
These small changes are what set us apart.
Our hotel has a simple principle.
Regardless of the room they're staying in,
we consider every single guest
at our hotel a VIP.
That is our new principle.
Well then.
Then we'll change the water too.
Thank you.
May we move on to the next item?
Yes.
The next item
is breaking into the European market.
According to market research,
tourists have increased,
but the revenues of global hotel chains
continue to drop.
The needs of guests continue to grow
more detailed and diverse.
We won't break into the market
as a large-scale hotel chain.
Focus on purchasing luxury mansions
that can accommodate up to 20 rooms.
A single chain with a thousand styles.
That's our strategy
for the European market.
So this will turn into our staff lounge?
I'm telling you. Why won't you believe me?
We'll really get massage chairs too?
And a nap room too.
No way.
Then we can truly relax
when we go on breaks, right?
Sure.
It's all thanks to Mr. Gu.
You should be grateful,
work harder when you work,
and rest well on breaks. Okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Jeez, what are you doing?
- New cologne?
- It's what I always use.
What's this?
Pull your arm out. You're gross.
A new position, a new scent.
How charming.
When will I get promoted
to a position worthy of such a scent?
I really wonder.
We need to talk.
- This is for me?
- Yes.
- It looks bad.
- This is good.
Why are you suddenly so nice to me?
It doesn't suit you.
This actually tastes good.
It's good.
Is that for me?
What could it be?
Should I open it?
Business cards?
I still have lots left.
NO SANG-SIK
STRATEGIC PLANNING DEPARTMENT MANAGER
I'm a department manager?
- You are.
- I'm a department manager!
I'm a department manager!
Are you that happy about it?
Why am I not the head manager?
What?
Ms. Gu said she would make me
the head manager.
I should have switched over then.
I shouldn't have stayed loyal.
There's no reward.
This is such a shame.
I honestly thought
you'd make me the head manager.
You don't like
department manager?
It's not that.
It's just a bummer
that there's no head manager.
It'd be wonderful
to change this to "head."
"Head Manager No Sang-sik."
In that case…
I guess you won't need this either.
What is this?
May I open it? I'm doing it.
You said you didn't need it.
It's a watch.
Mr. Gu, your generosity knows no bounds.
Not only are you handsome,
but you're also charming and cool.
That's why you're dating someone.
You didn't want it. Give it back.
No takebacks. You gave it to me.
- Bring it here.
- No.
I will work here until my death.
Thanks a lot.
You didn't want it. Give it back.
Thank you for the promotion!
We go hard! Let's go!
Thanks!
Thank you!
It is I, Department Manager No!
HOUSING LISTINGS
Did you find a place?
I'm still looking.
What's your theme?
Let's look it up together.
That's a secret.
Come on, don't be like that.
I found one.
I'll call you back.
Hello, I saw one of your listings online.
May I see the building?
Right, the listing number is 15017.
Hello, I'm calling
about one of your listings.
Not this one.
I don't think this is it.
Not this one either.
I'm calling about listing number 10591.
I see.
I wanted to see a building you have.
All right.
I finally found it!
Congratulations.
CHEON SA-RANG
-You're opening your business
-Congratulations, dear Sa-rang
FINALLY A BOSS
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
I'm so proud of you.
There's finally a boss among us.
An owner of a hotel, at that.
Who cares if I'm the owner
when I'm the only staff?
Girls like her are the scariest.
She said she never wanted much,
but now she owns a hotel!
I took out a huge mortgage,
and there's only one room.
And that single room is a suite.
Of course, all rooms are suites.
The cream of the crop.
Thank you always
for seeing things in a better light.
I'm so happy I'm friends with you two.
You two are the best!
You realized that just now?
Of course we're the best.
Now, let me mix some drinks.
Sounds great. Okay.
KETTLE-COOKED COW'S HEAD GUKBAP
CHA SUN-HUI
Hey, Sa-rang.
Cheon Sa-rang?
I'm busy, Grandma.
Come here.
What is it? I'm busy.
I still have a ton of dishes left.
Did something good happen?
What's this?
All of your daily wages.
You gave me pocket money each time.
Think of it as severance pay.
I wasn't even a full-time employee.
How much is this?
One, two, three, four, five, six…
Grandma!
Thanks for helping me out
even with your busy schedule.
No, I can't take this. It's yours.
And this here
is the money from selling
the wild ginseng you dug up
from Mount Jiri or whatever.
Why did you sell it?
I told you to have it yourself.
Jeez.
Wait, 150 million won?
That little thing was
apparently over 100 years old
and valued at over 100 million.
I was really shocked.
What would you have done
if I ate that precious thing?
That's why I wanted you to have it.
Goodness, home-cooked meals
are better than wild ginseng.
I'm perfectly healthy,
so don't worry about me.
And this.
I saved up some money to give to you
for when you found something
you really wanted to do.
It's not much.
Gosh, this is too much.
I saved up money too, Grandma.
Don't let money stop you
from doing whatever you want.
If it's a hotel,
it should look pretty
no matter how small it is.
No matter what hotel you run,
make something that resembles you.
Then it'll be
the prettiest hotel in this world.
- Thank you, Grandma.
- Sure.
My precious girl.
Thank you for letting me
do my part as your grandmother.
All right.
SUITE
OFFICE
You're going to the US tomorrow?
He has an early flight.
Why don't you come back and live here?
It's okay, Grandpa.
I want to go back to school
and see my friends too.
Really?
I thought you'd prefer living here
with Mom and Grandpa.
That sounds great,
but I should go back to where I should be.
You're not old enough
to be acting so grown up.
You've matured too early.
I'm sad to see you go.
I'll be back.
Okay. Let's eat.
Ji-hu.
If you want to stay, you can stay longer.
If you don't want to go, don't.
No, I want to go now.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Please say goodbye to Sa-rang for me.
Let's fly kites again next time,
Uncle Won.
Okay.
Let's hang out again
the next time you visit.
Okay.
We need to talk.
Talk.
Don't let Ji-hu…
live like we did.
Don't say "we."
It makes us sound like family.
You already know
Ji-hu is going back to the US for you.
He thinks that if he stays,
he'll only be a nuisance.
That small kid
is trying so hard to protect
someone dear to him.
As the adults,
we need to do our part.
I…
have a favor to ask of you.
Sure, anything.
Don't get smart with me.
Let me ask you one too.
Don't.
Don't live such a lonely life anymore.
I'll escort him safely, Ms. Gu.
I'll go now.
Take care.
Have a safe trip.
I love you
so, so much.
I'll see you again.
Mom.
Where are we going?
We're going home.
- Home?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Thank you for coming.
Let us begin.
You just took over King Hotel,
yet you're already about to open
hotel chains in 16 different countries.
What gave you that push
to turn your domestic hotel
into a global chain?
I looked back
on the past 100 years of King Hotel.
There were times
when we were desperate to survive.
At other times,
we were drunk on our success.
Over those years,
only one thing remained constant.
It was the heart of those
who took care of this hotel.
Such people kept our hotel together.
I only stood on the shoulder of that giant
to look out at the world.
You've moved on from a local hotel
to become a global chain.
What are your next steps?
We'll make our way to Europe,
where many chains have failed.
You're going to see new, innovative hotels
previously unseen from existing chains.
Your management style
is rather aggressive.
Is it your goal to make King Hotel
the best in the world?
On the day I was appointed
as the head manager,
I said,
"I'll make King Hotel
a place without fake smiles."
I used to think
most people's smiles were fake.
However, I met someone
who could smile with all her heart,
and I came to realize
how beautiful a smile could be.
King Hotel's goal
isn't to be the best in the world.
It's to become a hotel
where everyone can smile from their heart.
That
is the goal of King Hotel.
GUIDE TO HOTEL AMOR
Where love begins. Hotel Amor.
We'll open for reservations tonight.
All done.
Everything's ready.
I just finished getting ready to open.
I miss you so much.
He must be busy.
I need a nap.
I'm so tired.
Just for a moment.
You'll be there alone.
For emergencies.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
What's going on?
I missed you so much.
It's wonderful to see you here.
I missed you too, so I ran over.
What's all this?
They're so pretty!
I'm glad you like them.
I wanted to give these to you.
Thank you.
Did you do this all by yourself?
You have such great taste.
I guess you know your stuff.
Do you want to sell this hotel?
I'd like to buy it out.
This is a five-S hotel,
so it's quite expensive.
I've heard of five-star hotels,
but never a five-S hotel.
Five smiles.
That's why it's a five-smile hotel.
"Where love begins."
- Hence, Hotel Amor?
- Yes.
This is a wonderful place,
full of romance.
I remembered the bed and breakfast
we stayed at in Gapado.
We detested each other so much,
yet we were so close on that day.
In a way, that was the place
our journey began.
That's why
I wanted to create a place
where love starts to bloom.
Are you talking about
the most luxurious hotel
and the best restaurant in Gapado?
Yes.
The Chinese bushclover wine was delicious.
I'm craving it.
I had fun riding a bike together.
I want to do it again.
We should go back.
- Should we?
- Yes.
Let's do that.
One second.
ONE RESERVATION CONFIRMED
It's a reservation!
Let me see. Really?
Hey, you got a reservation
as soon as you opened.
Ms. Cheon, how impressive.
Yes, that's me.
Only you could pull this off.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
It's pretty late. Shouldn't you go?
You have work tomorrow.
Just a little longer.
I mean,
if you leave too late,
you'll be sleepy and tired.
Do you want to spend the night?
It's even prettier in the morning.
Here.
One, two, three.
Right, Sa-rang's hotel.
- Hotel Amor.
- Yes.
- I couldn't get a reservation again.
- Really?
I failed too.
The six of us said
we'd meet up over a month ago.
Right?
But I'm glad her hotel is fully booked.
I should go over and help her out soon.
Where are we going?
To meet Mom.
Mom?
Whose mom?
Who do you think?
You gave me a scarf
to give to my mom, remember?
Yes, I did.
Since that day,
she's been asking me to bring you over.
What? No, I can't.
I'm not dressed properly,
and my hair's a mess.
I need to fix my makeup too.
You already look great.
I'm not ready to meet her yet.
And I don't have a present.
I can't go empty-handed.
Anyway, I can't. Turn the car around.
I'm not turning around.
We'll be there soon.
Gosh, you should have told me.
I didn't even bring my makeup bag.
Mom, Pyeong-hwa is here.
Say hi to her.
This is my mom.
Hello.
My name is Oh Pyeong-hwa.
Mom,
she's my girlfriend.
What do you think?
Isn't she pretty?
Not only is she pretty,
but she also has a big heart.
We will be…
happy together for a long time.
Please watch over us.
Let me know if you need anything.
- Okay, thank you.
- Sure.
I'm hungry.
When did you come?
Right now.
You must be hungry. Late-night snacks?
My gosh!
- What?
- Move aside. It's dangerous.
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
Why are you here again?
I was just passing by.
That makes no sense.
I saw the lights off as I passed by.
Stop lying.
You should call me for help.
Aren't you tired?
I should get some rest.
I knew you would do this.
I said I'd throw out the food waste.
Give me.
These are recyclables.
- You're right.
- Why are you here again?
To take out the garbage. Where is it?
Over there?
Where? Outside?
- Outside.
- Here?
No, outside. Out there.
You were out of toilet paper last time.
- Toilet paper?
- Yes.
Toilet paper?
Toilet paper.
So there's the toilet paper.
Why do you have so much?
We need to talk.
Hey.
You're not close by.
You can't come visit me every day.
I'm not tired. I'm fine.
Have you looked at yourself in the mirror?
Have you even seen your eyes?
Your dark circles
have reached your cheekbones.
My gosh.
Stop coming over.
I'll come to you when I'm free.
You're fully booked this month.
How can you manage alone?
I already uploaded a job ad.
I'll find a part-timer. Don't worry.
A…
A part-timer?
Are you being serious?
I'm doing this
because I'm worried about you.
Promise me.
Promise that you won't come over
every single day.
You're busy enough already.
Now.
Fine.
I won't come.
Do you mean it? You promised.
Okay.
And this too.
Good.
Can you start right away?
May I work on weekdays?
I'm looking for someone
to work weekends right now.
I have to hang out on weekends.
I cover your food, lodging,
and transportation expenses.
Is it still too difficult?
Of course it is.
Isn't doing my job enough?
Why am I forced to smile?
Wouldn't our guests be happier
if you welcome them with a smile?
Well,
can I be in charge of the office
instead of cleaning and stuff?
I looked over your résumé.
Can you really work weekends
when you already have a full-time job?
I'm always free on weekends.
On top of that, I'm very fit,
so it won't be a problem.
And everyone has two jobs now.
I should work hard too.
The president of King Hotel
doesn't need two jobs.
You're busy as it is.
That's why I should work even harder.
I heard the president here
used to be the hotel's best talent.
I'd like to learn from you.
Please hire me.
No. Please leave.
Yes. Please take me.
In that case,
show me your smile.
Gosh.
You aren't ready to smile wholeheartedly.
Disqualified!
One second. Give me another chance.
Let me try again.
Please
hire me.
Is that a real smile?
Yes.
Not a fake one?
No.
You can start next week.
Thank you, Ms. Cheon. I'll do my best.
That's a given. You have to do well.
- Can you do that?
- Yes, I can!
Excellent.
That's all for the interview.
Come to work next week.
I still have to pass
the most important interview.
Sorry?
I want to be with you forever.
Will you marry me?
I love you.
I love you more.
Everything is ready. Come on out.
Okay. We're coming.
- Please have a seat.
- Okay.
She looks great.
You look so pretty, Grandma.
What is this?
I'm scared someone may see me.
No, you could compete in pageants.
What?
Everyone does this now.
You're like a princess.
Goodness.
How can this old woman be a princess?
If you aren't the princess,
you must be the queen.
Your Majesty the Queen, happy birthday.
- Two, three.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Grandma
Blow them out.
Okay. Come closer and do it with me.
Should we?
- One, two, three.
Goodness, this is embarrassing.
All right.
Let me try it first.
It's so good.
Of course. I made this.
Ma'am, please try some.
So are you sure people can eat this?
Of course. What do you take me for?
I'm asking because I know you.
Let's see.
Here we go.
Perfectly seasoned.
- Not so bad.
- I'm good at everything.
Did you make this too?
I bought that.
I knew it. This was the most delicious.
And picking up nice food
is also a great skill.
You always have a way with words.
My gosh.
I'd like to tell you something.
Yes? What is it?
You're very serious.
Did you do something wrong?
We'd like to get married.
We'll always cherish each other
and live a happy life.
I think I'll always be happy with him.
Yes.
So you should.
That's wonderful.
Grandma, why are you crying?
We'll be happy.
Yes, you should be.
Does he pass?
Yes, he does.
I do, right?
It's Uncle Won.
You must be Ji-hu.
Yes, my name is Yoon Ji-hu.
Who are you?
I'm Uncle Won's mom.
That makes you…
my grandma?
Are you my grandma?
You're very smart, just like your mom.
May I…
give you a hug?
Yes.
You've raised him beautifully.
You did a great job.
Let's go and find your auntie.
There she is.
- Cho-rong.
- Hello.
Yes, hello.
Hello, you must be Cho-rong.
Is he your boyfriend?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
He's so cool, like a prince.
You pass!
Goodness, thank you for giving me a pass.
Hello.
You must be Cho-rong.
It's a no for you. You don't pass.
What's with the rejection?
Why don't I pass?
You make funny jokes.
- Hello.
It's hot in here.
You look great.
I thought you wouldn't come.
Your mom told me a parent's job
was to let his child live their own life.
She said you should get to live
the life you want for yourself.
It's overdue, but congrats.
I hope you live a very happy life.
I will.
It's time.
Let's go.
Our son has grown old enough
to get married.
It sure hits you differently.
Stop acting friendly
as if nothing has happened.
Do you want to get a cup of tea
after the wedding?
And now,
the dashing groom will enter.
Please welcome the groom!
You look wonderful!
Next,
the woman of the hour,
the bride, will enter.
Please welcome the bride.
You're so pretty!
You're beautiful!
Shall we go?
Anywhere with you.
KING THE LAND
EPILOGUE
- No?
- No.
Right? White's a bit much.
I thought so too.
- Should I go change?
- You should go change.
I can't breathe.
You look great. Let's go with this one.
Do you like this one?
I liked everything,
but this one's the best.
Shall we go now?
Shall we?
Yes.
Let's go home.
People are watching.
What people?
Over there.
Who cares?
THANKS FOR WATCHING
KING THE LAND
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs