KING THE LAND
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Hello. Thank you for your hard work.
Sir,
is there something wrong?
It's been a while,
hasn't it?
How have you been?
I don't think that's
an appropriate question
coming from someone
who knows full well how I was banished.
Don't tell me
you expected me to be happy
after losing my son
and vanishing without a trace?
I'm sorry.
I had no power back then.
No.
Even if it were now,
you would've chosen the company.
That…
is who you are.
It must be a family tradition.
You got rid of her
while Won was on a business trip.
Like me.
If only you hadn't formed a union,
that wouldn't have happened.
The president's wife
incited the employees
to rebel against the company.
How was my father supposed to accept you?
It was you who broke our promise.
You cowardly turned your back
on everything we dreamed of together.
It was to protect everyone.
You chose the easiest thing to abandon,
and that was me.
There was only one reason why
I left quietly.
It was for Won.
Your father took that young child hostage
to threaten me.
He said he'd protect Won
if I disappeared.
That is why I lived as if I didn't exist.
Like I was never even born
in the first place.
I've…
always felt sorry about that.
I'm not here to receive an apology.
I'm here to warn you.
Don't drive Won into a corner anymore.
If you continue to do so,
I'll no longer sit back and watch.
I…
never got to live my own life.
Did you…
get to live your own life?
Please let Won live his life
the way he wants to.
Let him live for himself
rather than for the company or the family.
That's what you should do as his parent.
Leading him in the right direction
is also what I should do.
Although he'll make his own decisions.
It's a relief
to hear that you'll let him decide.
I'll be leaving.
You're not going to show up
in front of Won, are you?
That's up to me.
He's doing fine right now.
Don't confuse him.
Those threats don't work on me now.
HEAD MANAGER GU WON
Won.
I'll do it for you.
This…
is a pocket watch.
Don't lose it no matter what.
Okay.
Won.
It's me, Mom.
Do you…
remember me?
What brings you here?
I came to apologize.
For what?
I was always afraid…
that I wouldn't be able to protect you.
This may sound like an excuse,
but I thought leaving
was the only way to protect you.
I heard about why you left.
Or sent away, to be exact.
The people of King Group
were too powerful for me to fight against.
I thought living
like I didn't exist in this world
would be what's best for you.
But…
I was wrong.
You grew up to be a wonderful person
even without
anyone's protection.
Back then,
you were but the same age as me.
It's an age in which
you're not quite an adult yet.
That's why I thought
you could've been scared.
I understand you a bit now.
So
don't feel guilty and be at ease.
You're even considerate enough
to say things that will ease my guilt.
You're all grown up.
I'm not making things up
to put you at ease.
And I'm not trying hard to understand you.
It's just…
I now know how it feels
to want to protect…
something precious to you.
So from now on,
you should live for yourself.
Don't try to protect anyone
or hide because of me.
Live for yourself.
Don't…
forgive me.
Whatever the reason,
I left you alone
and…
made you suffer.
I never once resented you.
Although I don't have
many memories of you…
I could still feel
how much you loved me.
"She's not someone who would abandon me."
"She just had no other choice,
so she left momentarily."
That's the thought I held onto
to make it through those long years.
Thank you for not letting me down.
That's all I needed.
I'm sorry that all I have to say
is that…
I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
Be well.
Mom, I love you.
Me too.
EPISODE 15
You've still got it.
Cotton pads and swabs
should always be filled to only 90%.
I still remember your instructions.
You're so smart.
I need to sit for a bit.
I didn't know
I would be working in a sauna.
This place is so tough.
It's a place of exile.
They sent us
because it's so understaffed here.
Ever since I first got here,
they didn't hire anyone
saying it'd close down soon,
but that was already five years ago.
Is this place closing down?
We keep losing guests,
and sales figures aren't that great.
The hotel is holding out
thanks to weddings,
1st-birthday parties,
and 70th-birthday parties,
but that's not enough.
If this place closes down,
us exiles won't have anywhere to go.
Everyone treats each other
like family here.
It would be a shame
if this place were to disappear.
That's why everyone is holding out.
They want to save the hotel.
Let's keep our heads up.
We got this!
By the way,
how is everything going with Mr. Gu?
What do you mean?
Are you two still going strong?
You've been here for a while,
but he's never visited you.
That's why everyone keeps saying
you already broke up with each other.
He's just so busy.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
Why were you waiting for me?
Go ahead and eat.
Enjoy your meal, sir.
I already ate. It's way past lunchtime.
The reason why I asked
all of you to gather is…
Why don't you guys use your vacation days?
I told you I can't make payouts
even if you don't use them.
Make sure to use them all
by the end of June, okay?
It's not like we don't want to.
How are we supposed to rest
when we're so short-staffed?
I told you not to work hard.
If you have that much energy,
just find another job
because this hotel will be sold soon.
Has it been confirmed?
I'll be hearing good news soon.
So stop wasting your time
and just work on filling up your résumés.
Mr. Wang,
I know I may be out of line here,
but why don't we work together
to look for ways to save this hotel?
Why are you all so passionate
about this hotel that's about to go bust?
Everyone's sacrificing themselves
and doing their best
to protect this hotel.
If we all just--
You were kicked out of King Hotel, right?
I was reappointed here.
Reappointed, my foot.
You must be acting up
counting on a certain someone.
Get your act together.
Can you still not understand
after being banished?
Don't you understand it's over?
You should be embarrassed
and keep your head down.
It's not because I'm counting on anyone.
As an employee of King Tourist Hotel--
That's exactly my point.
You're an employee, so act like one.
How dare you talk back
to the head of the hotel?
I run this place.
I make the decisions. Got it?
How pretty.
Sa-rang.
Can you check the outdoor speaker
to see if the music can be heard?
All right.
TRUE RELAXATION BEGINS
WITH YOUR STAY AT KING TOURIST HOTEL
Sa-rang, did you check?
I can't hear anything.
I'm here to pick you up.
Did you have a good trip?
Yes.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It was hard on your own, right?
What about work?
Did everything go well?
Yes, it did.
Let's go back now.
I work here now.
It doesn't matter.
You're mine.
Hang on.
Yes, this is Cheon Sa-rang.
Right now?
All right.
What now?
Go ahead.
I'll wait.
Do you want to go with me?
Anywhere with you.
Here.
- You know how to do it, right?
- Did you forget?
I never forget anything once I learn it.
Of course.
Then can you set all the tables
starting from there?
I need to go to the kitchen.
My rate is expensive.
Will you be able to handle it?
After work, I'll recharge you
for the amount of time we were apart.
What do you think?
I'll get it done quickly.
Thanks.
Here we go.
Hey, you.
Over there.
Hey, tablecloth guy.
Come over here and grab this.
Yes, I'm talking to you.
Let's move quickly.
We're so busy right now.
Grab that end and align it with this end.
- Make it parallel.
- Me?
Then should I?
Quickly.
Stretch it out more.
Yes. Good.
Okay.
I did a good job.
But are the employees
in charge of this kind of stuff too?
Don't we usually hire agencies?
Doing this stuff on our own
gives us a competitive edge.
By the way,
have we met before?
No, it's my first time meeting you.
Then why do you look so familiar?
By any chance,
you're not Sa-rang's boyfriend
from King Hotel, are you?
What makes you think I'm not?
I am Sa-rang's boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
I mistook you for a one-day part-timer.
I have committed a grave sin.
May I just ask you to do one thing?
Of course. It can be multiple things.
You spoke informally to me
from the get-go, right?
Even if someone works here for a day,
we're all colleagues.
Please respect everyone.
I couldn't agree with you more.
I will make sure
to keep that in mind, sir.
All right, then.
I'm sorry, Mr. Gu.
It's okay.
Sa-rang!
You're very experienced.
This is nothing.
Sit down. I'll do it.
No, I don't have time to rest.
After this, I have to put up signs
all over the hotel.
You just had to come on the busiest day.
It's a good thing
that I came on the busiest day
since I can be of help.
You're so reliable.
Okay. One, two, three.
Thank you.
It's so warm.
I met my mom.
Really?
When? How did you meet her?
She came to me.
She seemed like a good person.
She was warm-hearted.
That's good to hear.
I knew she would be a good person.
To be honest,
I thought I had forgotten about her.
I thought I didn't miss her
and that I didn't need her anymore.
But after meeting her, I realized…
that I had never once…
forgotten about her.
I'm really sorry
that you had to come here.
It's been a while
since I greeted guests in the lobby
and worked in the sauna,
banquet hall, and linen room.
I've been super busy,
but I like it here.
It reminded me of the start of my career.
I really do like it here.
I don't see anything good
about this place.
Well,
that's what everyone says.
But they're just not looking hard enough.
There's a small forest behind the hotel.
It's been left in its natural state,
so it's beautiful and mysterious.
Just looking at it
makes me feel healed.
Hello.
- Were you exercising?
- Yes.
- I see.
- Goodbye.
Be careful.
I thought I needed to know the area well
in order to guide the guests,
so I looked around on my day off.
Thank you.
And there were
a lot of hidden gem restaurants.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
I only ordered one thing,
but they gave me
a bunch of other stuff to try.
I thought I was at a buffet.
I FOUND A GREAT RESTAURANT!
LET'S COME HERE TOGETHER SOMETIME
Excuse me, Miss. Have a yogurt drink.
Thank you.
The people here are so generous too.
A lot of them are family members
of the hotel staff,
so they give me drinks and ice cream
whenever they see me.
- Don't flatter me.
- You should marry my grandson.
And especially
this spot.
Doesn't it look like
all the stars in the galaxy are here?
It's beautiful.
You're right.
So beautiful.
Right? They're different
from the stars in Seoul.
If you just pay a little attention,
you can see everything.
It's such a shame.
But still, you should be in King the Land.
Let's go back now.
I'm sorry,
but I can't follow
the orders of my ex-boss.
What do you mean by ex-boss? That's harsh.
I came here as soon as I arrived in Korea.
It's my affiliation.
This is an official reappointment.
Let's go.
There are three banquets next week.
Let me finish those before I go back.
Why do you want to do that?
Because it's my responsibility.
I want to see to it myself.
Also, all the employees here
are working hard to protect this hotel.
I don't want to turn a blind eye
and run away by myself.
The employees are protecting the hotel?
I think this hotel
is going to be sold soon.
That's why everyone is troubled.
I hear your divorce story is out.
Let's go for a consolation drink.
Go away or I'll beat you up.
Your old feistiness is showing.
You know, your brusqueness is your charm.
Just swallow your worthless pride
and follow me.
Hey.
Why do I have to suffer
when you registered our marriage?
Live the rest of your life
in atonement, got it?
Try hitting on me one more time.
I'll tell your wife
how the father of her children
keeps begging me to get a drink with him.
- Are you okay?
- Are you okay, Mr. No?
Why you…
Has she gone mad?
Why would I hit on
a divorced woman like her?
Right?
Don't you agree?
Captain No Byeong-gu.
I like Pyeong-hwa a lot.
So what?
So I'm telling you
to watch out.
If you ever mess with her again,
I will no longer sit back.
- Does it not hurt?
- Are you okay?
Pyeong-hwa.
Why do you keep avoiding me?
Can you just leave me alone?
I want to disappear
to a place no one else exists.
That's why I can't.
It feels like if I do,
you'll really fly somewhere far away.
Let's go.
Why aren't you asking me anything?
Do I have to?
Everyone's curious.
It's in the past.
I'm sorry, but I'm not interested
in the Pyeong-hwa of the past.
I like who you are right now.
I have no hope.
I deceived everyone.
You didn't deceive us.
You just didn't reveal a painful memory.
Everyone has a side of themselves
that they don't want others to see.
Rain falls on everyone.
It's just that some
get wetter than others.
But eventually, the rain stops.
I'll be your umbrella.
- It looks good.
- Right? It was really good.
When I came by myself,
there was a huge line out there.
Here's the potato pancake.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- I sent you a picture last time.
This place is good,
and there are
many other good restaurants here.
Let's go somewhere else next time.
- Hello.
- What a lovely couple.
She came here by herself last time.
But she's not alone today.
- I'm her boyfriend.
- I see.
I couldn't let her be by herself.
You two are a perfect match.
Don't we look good together?
Yes, you both have clear skin.
You…
This is how much I respect you.
Please enjoy.
I could've gotten my own food.
I wish you all the best
from the bottom of my heart.
I'll be fine thanks to your wishes.
Please sit.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Help yourselves. Thank you.
Thank you.
By the way,
may I ask if you're here because of that?
What do you mean?
Goodness, Mr. Gu!
Salute.
I heard you were here,
but I thought you would've already left.
You must like fishing.
Well of course.
Anglers like me
even only watch fishing shows.
You went fishing during working hours.
Because it's part of my job.
I went with the city's head
of urban planning development.
We discussed
whether we could use this land
for the city's cultural center
after demolishing the hotel.
So you went to a fishery
to sell the hotel?
You think that's all?
I also go to golf courses, saunas,
restaurants, and whatever else
you can think of.
Rather than trying to sell the hotel,
do you do anything to improve the hotel?
I don't think you understand
the situation here, sir.
This neighborhood is dead.
The tourist attractions closed ages ago.
There's no hope left for this place.
It's better to just sell the hotel
before its value drops even more.
But in the countryside,
only city hall can handle
land of this size.
That is why I'm working so hard.
I see.
Disposal is probably the easiest option.
But the head of the hotel
shouldn't do that.
You're not only responsible for the hotel
but also the future of your employees.
Jeez.
Okay.
Let's say I'm doing something wrong.
Even so, I don't think
you have any right to get involved.
This place is a subsidiary
of King Distribution, not King Hotel.
Ms. Gu ordered me to sell the hotel,
and I'm just working toward that goal.
You're right.
They're separate companies,
so I can't tell you what to do.
I mean,
since you're the chairman's son,
I guess you can boss me around…
but I'm just saying
I have no reason to follow your orders.
I'll buy this hotel.
- Sorry?
- You said you were selling it.
I will buy King Tourist Hotel
at your desired price.
Are…
Are you being serious?
I made this decision
after careful consideration.
Although I wasn't here for long,
I took a tour around this whole village.
Behind the hotel,
there is a dense forest
that has been left untouched.
The sun, the wind,
and the smell of the forest.
You can become one with nature.
Mountain fog fills the air at dawn,
and countless stars
light up the sky at night.
I can make this a hotel that people visit
to escape from their busy lives
and find perfect rest.
I mean…
This all may look special to you
because you're from Seoul.
But there's nothing special
about this area.
All you see are mountains and fields.
- This hotel has no competitive edge!
- Exactly.
We need to create it.
I'm thinking of starting
a forest therapy program
that includes yoga,
tea ceremonies, and meditation.
The rooms will be remodeled too.
We'll have rooms with floor heating,
red clay rooms, and cypress rooms.
The annex that's in disuse
will be turned into a lounge
filled with music and books.
I am also thinking of creating a program
in which the village elders
can teach the guests
how to make traditional liquor
and crackers of this town.
If that happens,
our hotel itself
will become the best tourist attraction.
Well…
It could yield
a low or negative return on investment.
Didn't I tell you?
Disposal is the easiest option.
But since I've made the decision
to protect the hotel,
I'm not going to hold back
for fear of suffering a loss.
Congratulations on the sale.
Since you've achieved your goal,
you may leave now.
Eat.
Let's eat.
How tasty.
Thank you.
Everyone's so happy
because there's hope now.
You all deserve to have hope.
So does this hotel.
I…
want to create my own story.
I want to tell people
that I protected everything I wanted to
until the end.
I want to be as cool as you.
You're already so cool.
I wanted to be like you.
You rubbed off on me.
I was tinged with the most
magnificent color called Cheon Sa-rang.
Please excuse me for a moment.
Thank you.
Mr. Gu, thank you so much.
All of us will work really hard.
I look forward to working with you.
Me too.
Speaking of which,
you're not going to
take Sa-rang back to Seoul, are you?
Of course I am.
No, you can't.
You can't take our best employee away
while promising to revive the hotel!
Respectfully,
Ms. Cheon Sa-rang is mine.
Sa-rang was mine from the very beginning.
I was the first person
to show her the ropes and…
Tell him.
I'm the first person you met at the hotel.
I can grant you everything else but this.
The reason I even came here
was to take Sa-rang back with me.
I'm not going back on my own.
Mr. Gu,
I think it's because
you're in your honeymoon phase,
but if you're always with each other,
you'll get sick of each other.
In the long run,
long-distance relationships are the best.
You'll value each other more.
We value each other greatly
even though we see each other every day.
Sa-rang, why don't you decide?
Are you going with him or staying here?
Why would you ask her that?
She obviously wants to go with me.
Nothing is certain.
The choice is hers.
Fine.
I'll tell you.
KING TOURIST HOTEL
Sang-sik,
shouldn't we let her know now?
A surprise visit is the best.
We need to appear
out of nowhere
for her to be emotionally moved.
You're so clueless, Ro-un.
That's why you're not in a relationship.
Sorry?
But I am in a relationship.
You are? All of a sudden?
What a funny joke.
I'm being serious.
Congratulate me.
Really? Who are you dating?
An amazing woman.
- What? Who won you over?
- Really?
I wanted you to be Pyeong-hwa's boyfriend.
I know, right?
What?
It just happened.
Oh my.
What in the world?
Congratulations! What a surprise.
Thank you.
Really? This isn't a prank?
You two are dating?
Is love that easy for you?
I thought you were popular.
I am popular.
But nobody's bold enough to ask me out.
Are you sure you're popular?
Forget it. Let's go look for Sa-rang.
Ms. Cheon Sa-rang works here, right?
Can you call her for us?
We're her friends.
- Well, the thing is--
- Wait!
Don't tell her we came. It's a surprise.
I'm sorry, but she's not here.
Where did she go?
She went to Seoul a few moments ago.
Why?
For love, I suppose.
But we came all the way here for her.
Is she really not here?
No, she's not.
She really left?
We need to talk.
Really?
Thank you.
- Follow me.
- Have a great day.
This is why I said
we should've called her.
- Exactly.
We all agreed to surprise her.
Isn't that right?
- No.
Who's the one who said
we were clueless about relationships
when we suggested we call her?
It was you.
Hey, Ro-un! How could you say that?
We talked on the phone about how--
Whatever.
From now on, you have no say.
I'm going to be the leader
of the six siblings.
- I approve.
- Me too. I approve no matter what.
I approve as well.
Since we came all the way here,
why don't we grab a bite to eat?
The meal will be on you, Mr. No.
Me? But we pooled our money.
I think I should pay. Yes, I want to.
Right! There's a cafeteria nearby.
They sell amazing stir-fried pork.
What do you think of stir-fried pork?
I'm the leader here.
All right, let's go.
We're going to get short ribs!
- Short ribs?
- Let's get short ribs!
- Short ribs.
We're getting short ribs.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello. Long time no see.
Congratulations on your inauguration, sir.
You don't need to do this from now on.
The chairman is waiting.
You want to take over King Tourist Hotel?
Yes.
Are you confident?
King Hotel is going to
rapidly rise as a global chain.
For that to happen,
we should have a strong domestic base.
I'm not doing this because I'm confident.
I'm doing it because I have to.
You're the president of King Hotel now.
Give it your best shot.
Yes, sir.
Where are your questions?
You probably have a lot to say.
Will anything change if I ask?
I don't care
what you think.
Because that's what you want.
And…
I'm going to do what I want.
Very well.
I did everything I could.
The rest is up to you.
But remember, whether you succeed or fail,
you have to deal with it.
Okay.
President Gu?
Don't think it's all over.
This is just the start.
I won't let you
take away a single thing.
I wasn't thinking of
taking anything from you.
Father wasn't either.
It's not that you didn't think of it.
It's that you never dared to.
Get your facts straight.
I'm just trying to say
that I don't want us to fight.
We're family.
"Family"?
You and I are family?
I've never thought that.
Not even once.
What did you do?
It was you, right?
No one else could've done it.
I gave her money
and she left on her own.
What you called love
was nothing much.
All it took
was some chump change.
What cheap love.
That's why I warned you.
I told you I'd divorce you
at the right time
and that you should stay put.
This is why you can't be loved.
You act like you're distinguished,
but you're just a poor soul
who's hungry for love.
So are you.
All the people you "loved" left you.
They're all fake.
If you still don't get it, keep trying.
Try finding out
if love even exists in this world.
I feel…
so bad for you.
Mom, don't cry.
I'll leave.
I'll go back to the US, so stop crying.
I'm sorry.
I'll be the one to do as you say.
Don't cry, Mom.
- Hello, Ms. Do.
- Hi.
Continue working.
After this month, fire the junior member.
Sorry?
You told us to reach the target
to maintain our staff,
so we did.
The higher-ups want me
to give someone the boot.
I have no choice.
- Does it only need to be one person?
- Yes.
It's good that it's not two people.
Then…
may I pick out someone
who is truly unnecessary?
Of course.
Now you're talking.
In my opinion,
I think Alanga will thrive
as long as we don't have you.
- What?
- I saw your social media posts.
You enjoyed beef omakase with your family,
but you reported it as a team dinner.
Wait.
Why do you have this?
You left it on top of the fax machine.
What's more,
you paid for a café date with your friends
with a corporate credit card.
The dates here match your posts.
That's wrong. Give it to me.
You even requested overtime pay.
I was the one who worked overtime
inspecting the goods in the warehouse.
Why do I see your name
when you didn't even show up?
That's just because
I got the dates mixed up.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Do you have to nitpick?
Don't try to just gloss over this.
You misappropriated company funds
for personal use,
regularly snuck out of work,
and even forged private documents.
These are serious offenses.
So please leave willingly.
How dare you threaten me
when you're just a contract worker?
I'm the one who reports
everything that happens here.
Who will you report this to?
Do you know someone at headquarters?
I wasn't going to say this,
but I'm friends with a director there.
We're super close.
People side with friends, not strangers.
Do whatever you want.
Ms. Gang. Look.
Hello, I'm Do Ra-hee of King Distribution.
- It is an honor to meet you.
- Yes. Thank you.
What brings you here?
I had a meeting here, so I stopped by.
I heard about your wasted trip
to King Tourist Hotel.
Yes.
- Because of someone.
- I know.
Why did you trust him?
I also heard you earned the highest sales
in the country this month.
You heard about that?
I told him.
Since you are the proud leader
of the six siblings.
"Six siblings"?
Yes, six siblings.
Mr. Gu, Ms. Gang,
me, and three other people
are the six siblings
that are closer than family.
"Family"?
Could you please take these?
Mr. Gu bought these
for you to enjoy together.
Please take good care of Ms. Gang.
Let me know if you need anything,
and call me right away
if there are any problems.
- Yes, I will.
- Keep up the good work.
See you next time.
Goodbye.
You got this.
"Do you know someone?"
He left.
Did he?
Ms. Gang.
I'm sorry for everything.
If you had sincerely apologized even once,
I would've given you a chance.
I'm going to make an official report.
Just follow HQ's decision.
Welcome to Alanga!
KETTLE-COOKED COW'S HEAD GUKBAP
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I told you I'm just here
because I missed you.
Did you two argue?
There's no reason for us to.
Then what's the matter?
Tell me.
Say something.
- Why you…
- Gosh! I'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Goodness.
That's why I told you to stay still!
Are you not going to tell me?
Do you want to see me die of frustration?
Can I see something more special?
All the items I've shown you
are limited editions
crafted specially
by the brand's head designers.
My girlfriend has a pretty smile.
I want her to smile brightly
when I present her with the ring.
Is there something that special?
Just one moment, please.
What do you think?
It is a design
that symbolizes unchanging love.
It is a symbol of eternal love
and also signifies
a celebration of a special moment.
"Eternal love"?
Yes, sir.
I'll go with this one.
Okay.
Isn't this the restaurant from back then?
That's right.
We had our first meal together here.
Do you remember?
Of course. It was my birthday.
People will think we're a couple.
No one will think that.
I could do so much better.
Back then,
I never imagined
that we would end up like this.
Did you?
No.
No comment.
But we're the only ones here again.
Yes, you're right.
Anyway,
I'm glad we're here again.
Right?
Yes.
- Your food is ready.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Why do you keep checking your phone?
Is there a problem?
What?
No, there isn't.
Then what's wrong?
You look so anxious.
What are you talking about?
I don't know
the first thing about feeling anxious.
It'll start in three minutes.
Please get ready.
DRONE OPERATOR
Actually,
I have
something important to say.
I also have something I want to say today.
What is it?
- You can go first.
- No, go ahead.
What I want to say
is really important.
I want to call it quits.
What do you mean?
No matter how hard I think about it,
I just think this isn't it.
I feel out of place.
THE SHOW WILL BEGIN. YOU MAY NOW PROPOSE.
I'm done.
I want to leave.
KING THE LAND
Subtitle translation by: Stephanie Jung
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs