KING THE LAND
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Yu-ri.
Don't date me.
Date someone who likes you.
Sure.
I'll tell you when I start dating.
So you need to tell me first
when you begin to fool around.
Don't let me hear it from someone else.
I've already met
someone I like.
Yo, chicken!
Look at me, look closely
Don't betray my love
Come on, come to me
This will be the last time
Why would you leave?
Why would you abandon me?
Stop nagging and come to me, chicken
Come
Can we talk for a minute?
Mr. Gu.
I thought you wanted chicken.
Can you eat this all by yourself?
Wait. Why are you here?
Let's talk over chicken.
Sorry?
Where are you going?
You can't go inside!
- Pizza
EPISODE 7
You should've told us
you were Sa-rang's coworker.
I'm sorry for showing up unexpectedly,
but if you think about it,
you didn't give me a chance to--
We're basically family. Go easy on us.
We work for King Group too.
- I work at Alanga, King Fashion.
- I work at King Air.
- We are all one big family.
- One big family.
- Hermès.
Do you work
in the same department as Sa-rang?
No.
He's--
Yes, we do.
It must be tough.
I heard there was
a stuck-up jerk working there.
Hey.
No, there isn't.
What are you saying?
Right. It was the head manager.
Yes, it was the head manager.
What was his name again?
His name… Gu Won.
The chairman's son. The nepotism guy.
Right?
- No.
- Oh, my.
He tortured you that much?
You're tearing up just hearing his name.
It's okay.
I heard he goes to work for fun.
He should have fun
without bothering others.
There's always one in every bunch.
Hey…
Well…
at first.
At first, he was like that.
Just slightly.
But he's not like that anymore.
What do you mean?
You said he has a rotten personality.
Did I?
Yes. You said he was a douchebag.
I see. When?
- Yesterday.
- And two days ago.
- Last week too.
- And last month.
So I did.
Come to think of it,
we never even introduced ourselves.
What's your name?
Guys,
- this is--
- You can call me Manager No.
My goodness. You're a manager?
I manage my team as well.
I'm Gang Da-eul. I work at Alanga.
Stop by if you ever go overseas.
- I'll give you a big discount.
- Okay.
My name is Oh Pyeong-hwa.
She's almost a purser at King Air.
Give me a call whenever you fly.
Thank you.
Steer clear of them.
By the way, Mr. No.
Why did you come here?
Why do you think?
It's because he couldn't stop
thinking about her.
Have you two already gone that far?
Hey.
Eat this and leave.
Why? We're having so much fun.
What are you going to do once we leave?
Hey, Gang Da-eul.
Do you want to get kicked out?
Hey, half of this house belongs to me.
We split the deposit and the rent.
Don't be rude to my guest.
You can stay as long as you want.
Thank you, Pyeong-hwa.
But what is that?
- Is it a gift?
- Oh, this.
Here. It's medicine.
I didn't know your symptoms,
so I got everything.
This is for me?
Why do I need medicine?
You didn't look so well earlier.
I thought you were sick.
Mr. No, you pass.
I give you my approval as well.
Don't be absurd. That's enough.
What did we do?
She must be feeling embarrassed.
Let's pretend
we don't know what's going on.
I told you it's nothing like that.
If I may,
I'd like to talk to her in private.
- Right? Okay.
- Go ahead.
You must have a lot to talk about.
- We'll give you some privacy.
- Of course.
- Take your time.
- Enjoy your time.
You can take as long as you need.
Let's go.
Drink this.
All right. Thanks.
I'm sorry.
It was pretty hectic, wasn't it?
Well,
I'd say it was a valuable time
for me to learn what you thought of me.
A jerk
and a douchebag
with a rotten personality.
Don't take those jokes too seriously.
They're such jokesters.
You must be super close.
We're practically family.
You have a great family.
But why did you actually come here?
Well, you didn't look too well earlier,
so I was worried that something was wrong
or that you might be sick.
Even so, you shouldn't have
left your girlfriend to come see me.
On her birthday, no less.
She's not my girlfriend.
- She isn't?
- No, she isn't.
Then why did you hug her?
- What?
- Why did you hug her
when she's not even your girlfriend?
Is your chest just open to anyone?
What are you, a public rest area?
Don't tell me
you're feeling jealous right now.
Me?
Why would I be jealous? No way.
What do you mean?
Your eyes are blazing with jealousy.
Nothing's blazing here.
Look.
No matter who you date,
I don't care in the slightest.
Fine.
Since you're so insistent,
I'll make sure
no one ever comes into my arms.
I never asked you to do that.
Fine.
From now on,
I'll make sure
there are no more uncertainties.
So don't worry.
I'm telling you, it's not like that.
Are you sure?
All right.
I'll play along.
What was that?
Are they dating now?
Must be nice.
- Have a great time.
- Take your time.
Shall we go on a date?
Right now?
It's too late.
What about tomorrow morning?
We have to go to work.
Then what time works for you?
The best time to eat,
the best time to drink tea,
or the best time to have a drink.
Let me know
what times are convenient for you.
I'll think about it.
Why do you need to think about it?
Can't it just be whenever you want?
I need to check my schedule.
You should get going.
Already?
Let's take a few more laps around.
I'll give up my precious time.
I humbly decline your precious time.
Hurry up and go now.
Don't tell me to leave.
I'll leave when the time is right.
I think now is the right time.
All right then.
After one last lap.
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
I'm just trying to protect you.
Don't get your hopes up
about anything else.
I wasn't expecting anything else.
Anyway, people drive
so aggressively around here.
It's too dangerous for you
to walk around alone.
I can watch out for any cars if I need to.
So let go of my hand and leave.
I think people are sleeping.
Let's be quiet.
Keep it down a bit.
HAWAIIAN SUN, HAWAIIAN HOST
DIOR PERFUME 30 ML
Hello.
Do you need something?
You've been coming to work
with a young dude these days.
Are you two dating?
I'm asking you.
Let go while I ask nicely.
Does he know about us?
Is it fun messing around
with a younger man?
What's it to you?
It's none of your business.
Do you want me to reveal
the skeleton in your closet?
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
That's why you should quit acting up.
You acting like this
makes me want to run my mouth.
Don't you dare say anything.
If you do,
I won't let you get away with it.
I love that fiery glare of yours.
This is why I can't get over you.
Does your wife know you act like this?
Hello, sir.
Hey.
Ro-un,
what do you think
of a woman with a dirty past?
A sly woman
who hides her true identity.
Why…
are you asking me that all of a sudden?
Then again,
why do I bother asking?
No man would like that.
Well then. I'll leave you guys to it.
If you ever run into problems
or need any help,
you can tell me everything.
All right?
Hello, how are you?
Not good. Why are you asking?
I'm already so pissed.
Are you making fun of me?
Just get changed.
What is this?
I was told to doll you up and escort you.
I heard they even sent a helicopter
just to save you.
You're really something.
I'm sorry.
Is that how you should say sorry?
Do you think I'm a joke
because I delivered clothes to you?
Do you think you're all that now?
No, ma'am.
What are you doing?
Hello, Ms. Jeon.
I was teaching her basic manners.
She lacks basic propriety
but lucked out and rose to the top.
It seems to have gone to her head.
Ms. Kim, did you climb up the ladder
because you lucked out?
Sorry?
I obviously climbed up the ladder
due to my competence alone.
Of course.
No one at King Hotel
can climb their way up on luck alone.
On top of that, King the Land is only open
to the most competent employees.
Am I right?
You are. But--
Sa-rang was chosen as the best talent
for two consecutive years.
As a result, she got to promote the hotel.
Her success is a result
of her own efforts.
It's not because she was lucky.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
If you ever mistreat my concierges again,
I'll have to give you a lesson in manners.
Why are you here?
Ms. Gu told me
to get her ready for a press conference.
She ordered that Ms. Cheon
look elegant from head to toe.
I can help her. You may leave.
Yes, ma'am.
Just read off the script.
All the questions will be directed at me,
so don't worry.
Yes, ma'am.
PRESS CONFERENCE ANSWER SHEET
This part is slightly unsettling.
What?
It says I was
in a life-and-death situation,
but it wasn't that serious.
That doesn't matter.
People don't care about the facts.
They want drama.
That is why we need to tell a story.
That would be deceiving them.
Do you know how much it cost
just to rescue you?
The company paid for it.
Don't you even feel sorry?
I'm sorry.
I arranged this event
to help you ease your guilt.
The PR team even created a story for you.
How convenient, right?
We're all doing you a favor.
So you should do your best too.
Yes, ma'am.
Read the last part.
Right now?
Yes, right now.
"I was stranded
in a life-and-death situation
due to extreme weather."
"I am thankful that King Hotel…"
…AND MANAGING DIRECTOR GU HWA-RAN
What is it? Is there a problem?
The person who rescued me
was Head Manager Gu.
I authorized the helicopter.
He doesn't have that authority.
So I'm the only one you need to thank.
Read it again.
Best date spots in Seoul.
"Sweet and romantic.
Don't worry, we have you covered."
- Are you going on a date?
- Nice.
What are you doing?
HEAD MANAGER GU WON
Who's your date?
No one.
There's no date.
Yes, it is. Look.
Come on.
I was just trying to check and see
if our hotel was
on the list of date spots.
What was that snicker?
Do you even know what it's like
to be on a date?
- Of course I do.
- Of course you don't.
I have the ultimate skill that can steal
a woman's heart in one minute.
Do you want me to teach you?
In one minute?
One minute.
You think I would learn
from you?
A date
is like a war in which you must
win a woman's heart.
And do you know
the key thing to help you do so?
What is it?
Right. You said you didn't need my help.
Jeez.
I'll do you a favor and listen.
Okay.
You probably didn't know this,
but you have to get her to notice you.
Stay within her line of sight
and brush past her sometimes
as if it were a chance encounter.
Get it?
That would be stalking her.
You can't make it obvious.
You have to appear,
then disappear.
Get close but not too close.
You get it?
Then she'll think,
"Why do I keep running into him?"
"Can it mean something?"
Just when you're on her mind,
you have to disappear.
Then she'll start missing you
and thinking about you.
Then it's game over.
That'll work?
Of course. It definitely will.
Goodness.
Where are you going?
I have something to report.
Does it have to do with me?
Not really, but you still need to
have an idea of the company's--
From now on, if it's unrelated to me,
don't report it.
How entertaining.
Do you need anything else, sir?
No. I just stopped by as I was passing by.
Don't mind me.
Yes, sir.
Are you looking for someone?
Did all the employees clock in?
Yes, sir.
Why don't I see Ms. Cheon Sa-rang?
She went to a press conference.
A press conference?
PRESS CONFERENCE ON KING HOTEL
SUPER FARMER WEEK EMERGENCY RESPONSE
You could've just waited
after reporting it to emergency services.
Instead, you called all the board members
for an emergency meeting at night.
Is it true?
Yes. An employee was in danger.
Was there a reason
for your personal involvement?
I received news that the search
was being delayed due to the weather.
She was alone in the mountains.
Of course I had to.
Dispatching a helicopter
just to save one employee
was probably not an easy decision
for the company.
No. It was easy.
Once again,
an employee was in danger.
I'm sure it was difficult not to consider
the expense of dispatching the helicopter.
Don't companies these days,
especially conglomerates,
usually act in their own interests?
That is true.
Profit comes first for any company.
But the employees
are the ones who generate that profit.
That's why we say
that the employees are its true owners.
It sounds like your employees
can really trust the company.
It is my responsibility
to make that possible.
I have a question for the employee.
Do you have
any last words for the company?
I was stranded
in a life-and-death situation
due to extreme weather.
I am thankful that King Hotel
and Managing Director Gu Hwa-ran
came to my rescue.
Managing Director Gu,
do you have a message for your employees?
Excuse me.
Can I say one last thing?
There was someone who flew
through the storm in the helicopter.
Thank you, Head Manager Gu Won,
from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you very much.
Ms. Gu, please look over here.
"Third-generation business leaders
are on the rise."
They talk as if
that's just gotten started.
"When Managing Director Gu Hwa-ran
learned of the plight of her employee,
she held an emergency board meeting
and dispatched a helicopter herself to…"
She stole your spotlight.
You're the one who dispatched it.
This is absurd.
Mr. Gu, you have to learn this from her.
Her self-promotion
has the press printing out rumors
that the successor has been chosen.
Are you listening to me? Are you?
The owner of the company is speaking.
I mean…
It says here that the employees
are the owners of the company.
Why didn't you tell me
about the press conference?
You told me not to report
anything unrelated to you.
How was this unrelated to me?
A King the Land employee
being dragged away
and manipulated like a puppet
deserves a report.
Then make it clear.
How much do you want to know?
I'll report everything.
Only things that have to do with me.
Exactly.
How involved do you want to get?
For example,
schemes Ms. Gu employs
to secure her spot as the successor?
I don't need to know that,
nor do I want to.
Then what about this?
In a few days, a prince named Samir
from the Middle East will visit Korea.
He's the 13th richest man in the world,
and his one-night stay
is worth a month's sales.
Every hotel in Korea is at war
to get him to stay at their hotel.
Even Ms. Gu tried, but she failed.
You can use this point
to your advantage, sir.
That has nothing to do with me.
Report about my employees only.
Who?
- Should I do a background check?
- No.
I want to know who's having a tough time
or being treated unfairly.
That's all I need.
All employees have it rough
and are treated unfairly.
That comes with the job description.
Mr. Gu,
if you really want to get involved,
you have to let me brief you.
I know you're displeased
with how Ms. Gu is acting.
You need to gain power
in order to protect your employees.
Don't stare me down like that.
Gain the power
that's suitable for your position.
You did exceptionally well
at today's press conference.
The successor of a company
isn't just decided internally.
Public opinion matters too.
It reflects who comes to mind
when they think of our group.
Are you trying to lecture me?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Are we out of options with Prince Samir?
First Royal Hotel is already
in negotiations regarding his stay.
We tried everything, but he was obstinate.
Is this what I have to hear
after six months of groundwork?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
But there's nothing we can do.
Let's give up then.
From now on,
it's none of our business.
Was it you?
You had her mention your name?
Or was it Sa-rang's own decision?
I made her do it.
I did save her after all.
So you piggybacked off of my plan.
Don't you think it's pathetic?
It's better than deceiving others.
I enjoyed the show though.
"The employees
are the true owners of the company."
Is that what you really think?
Of course.
The owners of the company
are the employees.
And I happen to own the employees.
How shameless of you.
I pay them.
In any world, the person
who provides the money is the owner.
If you really think that way,
you don't deserve to become
the owner of the group.
Then do you?
Do you realize
how much damage you've caused?
I'm the one who restored what you damaged.
Though I'm sure the economic impact
generated by today's articles
will go over your head.
Don't calculate someone's worth
with money.
This is why you're not good enough.
The head of a company
must maximize its profits,
even if it means putting on an act.
The company can't exist without me,
and the employees
can't exist without the company.
Well done, Ms. Gu.
You demonstrated
how to improve the company's image.
Today's articles on the economy
are all about you, Ms. Gu.
Your story is continuing to
circulate on social media,
and journalists are writing about it.
Is that so?
I didn't think that far ahead,
but I'm glad we attracted publicity.
What about the Arab prince?
I think he will stay at First Royal Hotel.
If it isn't official yet,
do whatever it takes
to bring him to our hotel.
We should,
but King the Land is in charge
of inviting and managing our VIP guests.
So it's Head Manager Gu's responsibility.
Then you should do whatever it takes
to bring him to our hotel.
If they take him,
it won't just be a matter of sales.
This could determine
the industry's leading position.
It could change the game.
Do you understand?
Why aren't you answering?
Didn't you make any preparations?
If you're not up for it, tell me.
That way, your sister can take action.
I'll do it.
Are you confident?
I'll bring the Arab prince to our hotel,
even if I have to put on an act.
Good.
You know there was a banquet today, right?
Do you know how busy we were?
You're lucky you got to slack off.
The world is so unfair.
I wasn't slacking off.
I was following Ms. Gu's orders
for a scheduled event.
That's not my problem.
We served the guests when it was busiest,
so you can clean up on your own, right?
By myself?
No one was able to rest
because we were so busy.
We'll be in the staff lounge.
Call us when you're done.
Let's go, guys.
Good luck.
So you wanted to thank me?
Sorry?
I mean…
Since you're thankful,
let's have some coffee.
I'm extremely busy right now.
I have to rearrange everything
before break time ends.
Then I'll help you.
Wait. That's not how you do it.
Don't I just have to cover it?
There are no "justs" in the hotel.
The edges of the tablecloth need to
hang evenly at the perfect angle.
Is all of that necessary
when they'll only be used once?
A lot of people
devote their time and energy
to satisfy the guests
that'll be sitting here.
And I'm spreading out their devotion.
Isn't it fine as long as it's neat?
Do you have to give meaning to it?
If I don't,
the things that I do become chores
that can be done by anyone.
However,
if I give meaning to it, it becomes
something special that only I can do.
That also gives meaning
to my career as a hotel concierge.
I'll spread out that devotion with you.
Teach me.
I'll learn how to do it properly.
All right.
Then try grabbing the edge like this.
- The edge?
- Yes.
- And…
- Like this?
No, you can't stretch it out like that.
Let's see. This much?
- Is this good?
- No.
There still needs to be some tightness,
so around this much.
So…
if it can't be too tight…
Yes.
…or too loose,
I can just hold it however I want.
Just leave. I can do it by myself.
Fine. I'll put in more care and effort.
How do I do it? Like this?
Yes.
All right.
On the count of three,
you're going to gently let go.
- Gently?
- One, two, three.
Good.
Are we done now?
Yes, you did a good job.
Well, of course.
I'm good at everything.
Lucky you.
I just dropped in while I was passing by.
I know.
Just in case
you were thinking that I came on purpose.
I wasn't.
Why don't you ever think about me?
All I said was I didn't think
you came on purpose.
I never said I don't think about you.
That's true.
There's no way
you wouldn't think about me.
Follow me.
There's still so much left to do.
Hurry up.
Grab the end and lay it down gently again.
One, two, three.
HEAD MANAGER GU WON
What do you want for dinner?
- Anything but short ribs.
- No short ribs.
I hope you guys weren't slacking off
while I was away.
If you're that worried,
you can work with us.
Why would I do that?
Mark my words.
I'm watching all of you like a hawk.
Yes, ma'am.
I was thinking of having
a team dinner this week.
Let me know when you all are free.
For the record, I'm busy every day
except for Thursday.
Then we can do Thursday.
Really?
If that's what you want.
What should we eat?
Whatever the girls want to eat.
What do you want to eat?
- Sashimi. It's been a while.
- You're right.
I went to a sushi buffet
and had my fill yesterday.
I'm sick of eating raw fish.
What about grilled beef intestines?
How do you eat that stuff?
Then Ms. Do,
what do you think of a family restaurant?
Are you a kid?
Should we throw a birthday party?
What about pork trotters?
The place next door is good.
How dare you put trotters
on the dining table?
They stink.
We can go wherever you want.
Just decide among yourselves.
Must I decide everything for you?
Then we'll let you know
after discussing it.
The place we went to last time…
What was it called again?
Gosh.
They had good short ribs.
You know, I'm just saying.
- Well, then.
- Goodbye.
Have a good evening.
Why did she have to say
she wanted short ribs
in such a roundabout way?
She was just trying to sugarcoat it.
I'll call them to make a reservation.
Yes, ma'am.
Five servings of fresh short ribs.
Wait. Marinated ribs are best here.
- Can you make those marinated?
- Sure.
They like fresh ribs.
How much did the revenue increase by?
Around 15%.
At this rate,
we'll be able to achieve our goal of 20%.
Why don't we increase it by another 10%?
That's ridiculous.
We're already overworked as it is.
You'll get an incentive trip.
We were already promised one
if we reached 20%.
Instead of three days in Jeju,
let's go to Southeast Asia for six days.
How's that?
Bali, Phuket, Cebu, Kota Kinabalu…
Choose wherever you want to go.
- Really?
- Of course.
If we increase our sales,
we can go anywhere.
You can do it, right?
But still, 30% is a bit far-fetched.
If you think it's impossible, it is.
If you think it's possible,
you can do anything.
It all depends on you, Ms. Gang.
Da-eul, let's make it happen.
If we add another 10%,
we won't be able to take any breaks.
Are you okay with that?
Yes, we don't need any breaks.
Of course.
What could go wrong
when we have you, Ms. Gang?
Okay. To our vacation.
- Cheers!
Did you hear the news?
The Arab prince is staying at our hotel.
He has refined taste
befitting a member of the royal family.
He knows for a fact
which hotel is the best in Korea.
We're named First Royal Hotel
for a reason.
I heard it was a provisional contract.
Goodness. You should know better.
He already reserved
a week's worth of meals,
and we changed
the curtain colors and toilet.
How is that provisional?
You never know
until everything's set in stone.
Jeez. You two fight like cats and dogs.
When will you grow up?
Just admit that you're jealous.
Anyway, the tables have turned.
First Royal is number one.
King Hotel is number two.
That means King the Land is second too.
Our best talent.
How is she your best talent?
She's my hotel's best talent.
The Arab prince
will be staying at our hotel.
Come and greet him
as my hotel's employee representative.
- Pardon?
- Goodness.
Stop bothering my hardworking employee
with your nonsense.
I might be able to give you this hotel,
but I'll never let you have her.
Do you want to bet?
Yes.
Just make a bet.
Man up and bet your hotels.
- Jeez.
- Goodness.
Is that so?
- What?
- I have bad news for you.
The Arab prince is coming to my hotel.
- What?
- My son, Won, got it done.
A hotel's history and reputation
are what make it number one.
Hold on.
When the Arab prince comes,
you can greet him
as our employee representative.
Okay?
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Hey, it's me.
What happened?
What happened with the Arab prince?
We even changed the toilet!
Good work.
As expected of my son.
You have tricks up your sleeve.
I heard he already made the down payment.
Is he really coming to our hotel?
Yes, I called him.
The prince changed his mind
after a single call from you?
How is that possible?
I know, right?
But it was possible.
Hello?
Samir?
You know it's me.
Of course, it's me. What's up?
I heard you're coming to Korea.
Why are you digging around me?
Come to my hotel.
Oh, I heard your father
runs a hotel business.
Is the business not going well?
You want me to spend some money there?
You don't need to spend your money.
So, just come.
But you hated me
ever since we were in the same school.
Because you believe
that I only care about the money
Yes, I still hate you
I love your honesty.
But I already decided to stay at
the First Royal Hotel.
Why would I switch to your hotel?
I will treat you well.
Treat me well?
Explain "well" in detail, please?
Tell me everything you want.
I will make it happen.
Anything?
Anything.
Okay.
I'll send you the contract.
So, sign it.
Is he really your friend?
Even the legal team
has never seen such a contract.
He's not my friend.
We're just acquaintances.
It'd be better were he a stranger.
Look at the contract.
"You will always answer me with 'yes.'"
"You will always serve me with a smile."
How is that a contract?
He's just looking for a slave.
You can't sign it.
Why not?
You just can't.
He's going to shove you around.
What does he take you for?
You're a selfish jerk
who doesn't listen to others.
You've never smiled at anyone.
You'll definitely break the contract.
Who's going to deal with it? Me?
- I can't.
- Why not?
Do you think I'm a douchebag
with a rotten personality?
Did someone say that to you?
I don't think you're that bad.
I told you not to sign it.
You've never kowtowed to
or served anyone before.
I can just half-ass it.
No, you can't.
You won't be able to stand him.
Do you want to see?
- What?
- Here.
Imagine I'm Prince Samir.
Hey, Gu Won.
Come take my shoes off
and bring me some slippers.
You have to say "yes" sincerely
with a smile on your face.
Or else I won't pay a single penny
for breach of contract.
Yes.
Great.
Good job.
Come over here.
I should lift up my right leg.
I want you to get down on your knees.
Easy.
Good job.
Make sure you polish my shoes.
They're very expensive.
What did I tell you? Goodness.
Get
over here!
Prince Samir,
the 13th richest person in the world,
has arrived in Korea.
His trip was announced as leisure travel,
but it seems his purpose is to negotiate
the import of next-generation warplanes.
During his stay, he'll likely meet with
the head of the Defense Acquisition
Program Administration…
Get off.
Open the door.
Your driving sucks, just like you.
So, make your guard
drive for you, not me.
No, that's no fun.
Hold this.
Smile.
Prince Samir,
welcome to King Hotel.
I'm Gu Hwa-ran,
and I'm in charge of this hotel.
We did our best to welcome you,
and we will provide you
with the best service.
I only learned how to greet you in Arabic.
Welcome to King Hotel.
Are these flowers for me?
You're good at Korean.
Welcome.
How beautiful.
Thank you.
On behalf of the hotel,
I prepared a small gift from the heart.
Can I take a look at it now?
Yes, Your Highness.
You may be disappointed
because it's such a small gift.
It's a gift from your heart.
How could I be disappointed?
What is this?
It is a traditional Korean knot bracelet.
I had one prepared in green
as I heard green is associated
with abundance, sanctity, and paradise
in the Arab world.
I have a keen eye.
I'm incredible.
- Sorry?
- The moment I saw you,
I knew your heart
would be as beautiful as your face.
"Sa-rang."
Will you put it on for me?
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll put it on for you.
There.
You're all checked in,
so you can head straight to your room.
Follow me.
I received such a precious gift.
I must do something in return.
Have you eaten yet?
Sa-rang?
Sorry?
You have to hold it in, sir.
Why aren't you eating?
Do you want something else?
It's okay.
I don't even think
I can finish all of this.
You don't have to.
Just eat what's good.
Yes, Your Highness.
By the way,
I was surprised by your Korean skills.
My first love was Korean.
Really?
I studied hard to tell her how I felt,
but I got rejected.
What a horrible woman.
Maybe it was to meet you.
Like destiny.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
You look displeased.
Well…
This is where I work, actually.
So it's slightly uncomfortable to sit here
while everyone else is working.
- Should I tell them to leave?
- No, it's okay.
Please don't.
No…
Have you never eaten in places like this?
No, this is my first time.
It feels weird to be
sitting at the table that I set.
It seems people always put duty first
and enjoying their rights second.
I rented out this whole place for you.
You are the star of the day.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
Thank you.
How dare you sit down?
I want to enjoy my rights too.
I drove you,
opened the door for you,
and held your luggage.
I think I deserve to eat as well.
I'll give you food.
Eat over there by yourself.
Don't mind me.
You're an eyesore.
I'd like to say the same thing.
Hey,
don't you think
you've messed with me enough?
You had enough fun.
- You should stop now.
- I was already planning on it.
I don't need you anymore. Get going.
Okay. Good thinking.
I'll have our hotel's best employee
attend to you.
- Let's get up.
- No, you don't need to.
I already chose my attendant.
It's Sa-rang.
- Pardon?
- What, punk?
Not her.
Why not?
Because I said so.
Ms. Cheon Sa-rang is my…
personal assistant.
I am? Since when?
Starting today.
Remember the contract?
You have to say yes to everything I say.
Then I'll stay.
No, I don't need you. Get out.
Remember the contract?
I have to
stay next to you at all times.
The meeting is taking a while.
You don't have to go too far.
What do you mean?
I'm saying you don't have to
prepare a heartfelt gift
and serve him with your utmost sincerity.
He is an important guest of our hotel.
I should serve him
to the best of my ability.
You're being excessive.
King Hotel provides the best service
to all of our guests.
It is what we take pride in.
Just a moderate amount of kindness
is unacceptable
as an employee of King Hotel.
Still, don't give him such a pretty smile.
Do I look pretty when I smile?
I thought you hated my smile.
Well, it's not that pretty.
Then how do I have to smile
to not look pretty?
Like this?
Stop it.
Just do what you've been doing.
You're not even going to listen to me.
No, I really don't know what you mean.
Ever since my first day here,
I kept smiling from ear to ear every day.
I even practiced smiling in my sleep.
I'm sure all of the King Hotel employees
have the best smiles in the nation.
Why would you practice even in your sleep?
Because I wanted to do well.
You're sincere about every little thing.
So,
you should also try your best
while you're at it.
Me?
Why?
Today, we're representing the hotel
as a team.
Let's work hard to make Prince Samir
think that he made the right call
by choosing King Hotel.
Bump.
Fine.
Teach me what to do
to be a good representative of the hotel.
All right.
First,
you have to greet the guest
with a bright smile.
Smile broadly.
Are you okay?
Whatever. Forget it.
I mean, the heart is first.
The expression is second.
You're not smiling
because someone asked you to.
It needs to be sincere.
The guests all know
how you're feeling inside
through your smile.
So try thinking in your mind,
"Welcome to our hotel!"
and then lightly smile.
Yes.
That's good.
Yes. It's a lot better than before.
See? You need to smile from the heart.
Sincerity is something you can feel.
So?
What do you think?
Sorry?
Can you feel my sincerity?
Can you feel my heart?
Sa-rang!
I'm done for the day. Let's go.
- No more meetings?
- No.
I agreed to buy your country's
fighter jets and ended it quickly.
Have you been on a jet before?
Why would I?
It's the best hobby.
They've gotten a lot cheaper,
so they only cost a hundred billion won.
You should buy one for yourself.
Sa-rang, I'll take you for a ride one day.
Thank you.
Sa-rang,
what's that?
It's the palace where
the kings of the Joseon Dynasty lived in.
"Palace."
I want to go there.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
I'm excited!
You can leave.
No.
I'm going too.
We're going together?
Joseon kings walked along this path,
and it's called eodo.
Only the king was allowed
to walk down this path.
Isn't it fascinating?
How beautiful.
You've seen everything.
Let's go now.
You go.
I'll go if you go.
Why you…
Just go and buy some coffee.
Coffee?
I'm not someone who runs errands.
Yes, you are. Remember the contract?
I'll buy the coffee.
What would you like?
No.
You are my special guest.
Hurry up.
You dare make me fetch you your coffee?
How impertinent.
This place seems oddly familiar.
Korea is such a beautiful country.
Among everything here,
you're still the most beautiful.
Thank you.
Sa-rang,
do you have a boyfriend?
Well, not yet.
Really? What a blessing.
I'd like to thank the heavens
for bringing me to you.
I'm the one you should be thanking.
Here.
I bought this coffee myself,
so you should enjoy it
with a thankful heart.
Thank you.
Hey.
We were in the middle
of something important.
Get lost.
I can't even if I want to
because of the contract.
- Isn't the coffee good?
- Yes.
- Right?
- It's good.
Sa-rang, what is that?
It's a traditional nuptial experience.
- "Nuptial"?
- A wedding.
I want to try that
with you.
With me?
Yes. Is there a problem?
Well, I know it's just a fake experience,
but it's usually done between couples.
Don't take it seriously.
It's just a cultural experience.
Cut the crap.
If you ever come with your girlfriend,
I'll escort you back here.
I just simply want to experience
traditional Korean culture.
Traditional culture, my foot.
What a player.
Am I asking for too much?
It's a no-brainer.
Don't do it.
Remember the contract?
"Obey no matter what."
No, I didn't forget.
I'm not saying
I won't stick to the contract.
I'm going to break it.
- What?
- I'll find you another hotel.
Get out of my hotel.
I paid good money.
Can a bum like you make up for it?
I gladly will.
This contract
is void.
You can't.
- I'll do it.
- Do what?
That traditional wedding ceremony.
You don't have to. Don't.
It's just work.
It's not an actual wedding.
I'll think of it as a meaningless event.
So please don't ruin everything
over something like this.
I'll go get prepared.
Wait. But to me, it's--
Your employee is better than you.
Wait for me, Sa-rang!
Sa-rang!
A wedding.
It's a wedding.
Sa-rang, wait for me.
The bride's palanquin will enter.
Now, the beautiful bride
will step forward.
Groom, take a bow and step forward.
KING THE LAND
Subtitle translation by: Stephanie Jung
Hey!
How dare you deceive me?
You're our VVIP employee.
You deserve to stay here tonight.
I knew you'd look great
in an elegant garment like this.
My love.
Cheon Sa-rang.
No. Let go of him.
Wait, are you jealous?
Since when did you care so much
about the company?
I'm going to try and protect the people
that you deem as nobodies.
If you keep beating around the bush,
you'll end up losing her.
Just ask her out.
I want to talk about us.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs