KING THE LAND
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
- Goodness.
- Dad.
Oh.
Let us serve the meal.
Yes, sure.
It's Ms. Best Talent.
It's been a while.
Hello, have you been well, sir?
If she's titled the Best Talent,
she must be very talented.
Not at all.
He's just being generous.
Then let us serve the soup first.
It's already been decided,
so there's no need to drag this out.
Won, now that your position is settled,
marry Yu-ri within the year
before it's too late.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm asking if you're okay.
What?
Yes, I'm fine.
It's dangerous, so step away.
I'll clean it.
No, I'll do it, sir.
I'll do it.
My apologies, sir.
Allow me to do it.
- Sa-rang, you may leave.
- No, ma'am.
- I'll--
- Sa-rang?
I'm sorry.
- Mr. Gu.
- Yes.
Goodness.
- It's delicious.
- Is that so?
EPISODE 13
Seeing Won manage
the 100th-anniversary event made me think,
"This kid sure can put up an act."
But it wasn't an act
by the looks of things today.
He actually cares about his employees.
That's why I like him.
He even takes care of people like her.
He's different from
all the pretentious men out there.
You're amazing for liking that about him.
Chairman Han and I
will arrange all the wedding preparations.
Understood?
Yes, Father.
Won.
What about you?
I…
am in love with someone else.
What were you thinking?
I'm sorry.
How did you join King the Land
with those skills?
I'm sorry.
I'll be the main server
and have Sa-rang assist me.
How can I let her go back in
when she dropped a plate?
I'll do the serving.
Stay on the second floor.
Wouldn't the second floor
be too difficult for a new member?
That's why you take charge there.
- Ha-na.
- Yes, ma'am.
Since when did King the Land
become so lax?
It wasn't like that when I was there.
It's the room at the very end.
Let's not make any more mistakes.
Yes, ma'am.
Gosh, I thought Won was just a kid.
He's all grown up now.
He even has someone he loves.
- Do you love her a lot?
- Yes.
Of course.
A man should know how to love a woman.
We're not here today
to find out who you're in love with.
We're talking about marriage.
We only need to talk about you and Yu-ri.
I told you from the very beginning.
I'm sorry,
but I've never had feelings for Yu-ri.
- And my feelings won't change.
- Won.
It's okay.
Everyone falls in and out of love.
It's completely normal.
Don't be too concerned.
Won.
Love her all you want,
then break up with her.
We have to get married anyway.
She's my daughter,
but she has such a big heart.
That is exactly why I had my eye on her.
She has a big heart.
I said…
I'm in love with someone else,
but no one is interested.
I was upset for a second.
But I don't think I need to be.
Because
I also have no interest
in any of this marriage talk.
I'll be leaving first.
I hope you have a good time, sir.
You too, Yu-ri.
Let's meet by ourselves next time.
I thought that punk was a softie.
But he has a firm character.
Right, Dad?
He grows on you, doesn't he?
Yes, I like him.
I'll apologize on his behalf.
It's okay.
He's mine anyway.
I'm not going to let anyone else have him,
so don't worry.
The person you have called is unavailable…
We need to talk.
Why didn't you answer my call?
My phone is in my locker.
I'm working right now.
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
Let's talk later.
Are you mad?
No.
I was just a little shocked.
It's not going to happen.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's talk later.
I need to serve this quickly.
But why are you working here?
This isn't the hotel.
I wonder that myself.
I'm pretty sure I'm someone
who works at a hotel.
Can you please step aside, sir?
Fine.
Call me as soon as you get off work.
I'll be waiting.
Go ahead.
Your food is ready.
I will go ahead and serve your food.
Your food will be served.
Oh my god!
Are you an idiot?
You're so funny.
Look at your face. It's hilarious.
Who are you?
How dare you talk to me like that?
Call me "sir."
Sir, my foot. Apologize.
If you apologize now, I'll forgive you.
That's what people like you do.
I'm not someone who apologizes.
What's wrong with you?
This is your last chance.
Apologize while I count to three.
What? Why should I?
One,
- two…
- Three.
What are you going to do?
Apologize.
Why should I? Do you know who I am?
I don't need to know who you are.
Spoiled kids like you
need to be taught a lesson.
I told you to apologize!
Stop!
If you don't stop, I won't forgive you!
I get to forgive you.
You just have to apologize.
I'm sorry. Happy now?
In Korean!
I'm sorry. I said I'm sorry.
My gosh.
Just watch. I'll make you pay.
You're going to regret this.
Well, too bad.
I don't regret anything.
Ms. Cheon Sa-rang?
Yes, this is Cheon Sa-rang.
Escort Mr. Ji-hu downstairs.
The chairman is asking for him.
- Sorry? Who?
- Mr. Ji-hu.
Ms. Gu's son.
So you're Ji-hu?
The chairman is asking for you.
Shall we go down together, sir?
How delicious.
Our Ji-hu is here.
It has been a while.
How have you been, sir?
I see. You must be Ji-hu.
He's so mature now.
I know, right?
You're starting to look like your uncle.
You're flattering me.
He has not once ever acted like a baby.
I have a wonderful grandson.
It is an honor
to have been born as your grandson.
Did you hear him?
How could I not adore him?
Good work today.
Accept this with gratitude.
Thank you, ma'am.
You're aware that you don't deserve
to receive this, right?
I'm sorry.
Please be lenient.
It didn't end up being a big problem.
She also went through a lot
working upstairs.
If you're ever chosen
to be a part of the Dream Team again,
relearn the basics before coming back.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
My pay for the day
is as much as my monthly paycheck.
So you're in love?
Yes.
I'll keep this short.
End it.
I don't intend to.
I'm
the father
of both you and King Group.
You too are the son
of both me and King Group.
To us,
marriage carries greater value than love.
No matter who you love,
you won't be able to protect her.
And she will end up leaving you too.
No.
That will never happen.
Also,
I'm going to protect her
at all costs.
Because I love her
from the bottom of my heart.
That's what everyone says at first.
You may not understand
what I mean just yet,
but you'll find out soon enough.
That's all I have to say.
The person you have called…
I've called so many times.
Should I just hop over?
The lights are on.
Sir. Excuse me.
Do you live here?
- No.
- You don't live here, right?
We received a report
about a suspicious person loitering.
A suspicious person?
No, I'm the only one here.
Yes, that's why we're here.
Can I see your ID, please?
Someone must've gotten the wrong idea.
I'm not a suspicious person.
Then why are you here?
My girlfriend lives here.
I called her numerous times,
but she wouldn't pick up.
So I was worried.
Yeah, he's definitely a stalker.
Let's take him to the station
before sending him home.
We shouldn't conclude that he's a stalker
- without checking.
- Checking what?
- Right.
- His girlfriend won't even pick up.
She's deliberately avoiding him,
but he followed her to her house.
He's definitely a stalker.
What do you mean I'm a stalker?
What about me suggests that I'm a stalker?
Everything about you. Without a doubt.
This is your problem.
How do you know if it's romance
or stalking without hearing him out?
Isn't that right, sir?
Yes, I'm not a stalker.
Your eyes speak the truth.
I knew it. It's romance.
He came all the way here
to check on his girlfriend.
He was too sorry
to even ring the doorbell.
Right?
Yes.
Please. Cut the crap, will you?
You have the experience to know better.
Look. The lights are on,
very brightly at that.
So why won't she pick up?
She just hates your guts.
Yet you keep calling her nonstop.
And you even came to her house.
Gosh. Who would like that?
The thing is, stalkers don't
even realize that they're stalking.
Then is that why
you never called me when I got upset?
Why are you bringing that up again?
Did you ever come to my house
when I cried after our fight?
I said that I was going to,
but you specifically told me not to.
If I tell you not to,
do you take that at face value?
This is why you're a lost cause!
You keep bringing up the past.
Come to think of it,
you sure can hold a grudge.
Who made me like this?
Me. It's all my fault.
It's me. Everything is my fault.
- At least you know.
- It's all because of me.
So after listening to you two talk,
- How ridiculous.
- I think the two of you
should hold hands
and make peace.
I hope you have a deep conversation
and reach an amicable agreement.
Well, then. I'll be leaving.
Have a dazzling conversation.
Goodbye.
Give him his ID.
I'll take care of the rest.
You can take a break.
You didn't even eat yet, right?
It's okay. I can eat after this.
I'm not okay with that.
Get some rest.
We're selling duty-free items.
Please let me know if you need anything.
Duty-free sales.
We're selling duty-free items.
Do you need anything, ma'am?
I would like to buy this.
What? Why are you back already?
We have to dim the lights soon.
How will you increase sales
with that mindset?
Continue until I say you can stop.
I don't think we should disturb
the passengers' time of rest
to increase sales.
This is exactly why
you'll never be promoted.
Pyeong-hwa,
shouldn't you insist on continuing
even if I tell you to stop?
Go out and sell at least one more item.
I'm sorry,
but I can't do that.
Pyeong-hwa.
Who is in charge here?
- You, ma'am.
- And?
You're going against my orders?
For the passengers' rest
and the safety of the employees,
I'm asking you to follow the rules.
I didn't know you cared so much
about the passengers and employees.
Did you come alone, sir?
- Yes.
- I'll escort you to your table.
Your coffee is ready.
I called you.
I fell asleep early last night,
so I couldn't answer.
When I woke up,
it was too late to call you back.
Can we talk after work?
Won!
You were here.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I don't want you to visit me at work.
I'm here as a guest.
- I want coffee.
- Do you want it to be warm?
- Yes.
- All right. I'll get that ready for you.
What do you want?
I'll just cut to the chase.
There are a lot of men
who want to marry me.
I know.
That's why I won't apologize.
You're so offhand. That's why I like you.
Yu-ri.
Yes?
I want you
to experience what love is like.
I've been in a ton of relationships.
True love.
Then you'll be able to understand
what it means
when I say
I'm in love with someone.
That's why I'm going to give it a try
with you.
Find someone else.
Someone who can truly cherish you
and love you.
Meet someone like that.
Think carefully.
If you turn away now,
you won't get another chance.
If I help you,
you know you can have
King Group for yourself.
I'll pay for your coffee.
Enjoy your time here.
- One for each of you?
- Yes.
All right. Thank you.
I'll get that ready for you.
I didn't order this.
It's on the house. Enjoy.
Why?
You obviously had a fight
with your girlfriend. Just drink it.
We didn't fight.
You may take this back.
Then were you dumped?
No, we didn't fight, nor did she dump me.
I already told you.
Why is everyone doing this to me?
I'm being serious. We didn't have a fight.
I didn't get dumped either, so take this.
Just accept it.
It's from my heart.
You got this.
Thank you!
Are you okay?
My head says one thing,
and my heart says another.
That means you're not okay.
You don't have to pretend you're okay.
I'm going to give it some thought.
All right.
You probably need some time
to think it through.
But you don't have to be too worried.
How am I supposed to do that?
I know you must be worried,
but I hope you can trust me.
I'll take care of it.
It's my problem.
It's up to me to decide my future.
Still, I hope you're not thinking
of breaking up with me.
Why would I think of breaking up with you?
Were you thinking of that?
No, why would I?
I would never think that.
I could never let you go.
Then why did you say that?
It's making me upset.
I mean…
You said you were feeling down
and needed time to think,
so I thought it was
because of the other day.
The marriage talks?
It did take me by surprise.
But it's not like I expected your father
to welcome me with open arms.
You didn't get
my grandma's approval yet either.
What are you talking about?
I'm always number one inside her heart.
You mean candidate number one.
Anyway,
the irreplaceable number one in her heart
is yours truly.
Why are you so proud?
It's not even something that great.
What do you mean it's not something great?
It's the best among the titles I hold.
You're finally smiling.
I really wanted to see
that smile on your face.
You used to hate my smile.
So don't worry.
You know how I feel.
That's why I was more worried.
Anyway, don't take
what my father said to heart.
I made it clear
that I'm in love with someone.
I mean,
I was a bit startled, but it's okay.
I knew you wouldn't change over that.
So I tried not to think
negatively about it.
Then
what did you mean when you said
you needed time to think?
Have you heard of the Dream Team?
The Dream Team? What's that?
Apparently, it's every concierge's dream.
I didn't know it at first,
but after experiencing it,
a thought came to mind.
If I work really hard and reach the top,
I just become a maid for a wealthy family.
This isn't the hotel work
that I dreamed of.
I didn't know our employees
got drafted for personal events.
I didn't even know
why you were there that day.
I'll try to make a change,
so just wait a little.
Even if it takes some time,
I'll make sure it happens.
I'll also get rid of the Dream Team.
I'm not sure what's right.
Everyone else seemed to love it
because of the money.
It's just my personal opinion.
My personal disapproval
shouldn't prevent others
from earning more money.
Okay. You've been waiting for a long time.
Man, you look more energetic now.
Earlier, he was on the verge of tears.
What are you talking about?
What a shame.
I would've loved to see you cry.
- No, he's making things up.
- Then were you on the verge of death?
Jeez.
Just cook for us, please.
All right. Just for you two,
I'll start off with the last course.
- It's my heart.
- I was going to say that.
Put it all in your bag.
Dad, what are we eating today?
I'm busy today.
Just order some chicken
to eat with your mom.
What? We were supposed to eat out today.
I can't. I have a meeting.
Today's your wedding anniversary.
Don't tell me you forgot again.
You forgot, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
My boss just had to
make all of us gather today.
Today of all days?
Did you tell him what today is?
Of course I did.
But it's not like the company cares
about personal circumstances.
How are you always the same?
People were right
when they said people don't change.
The old sayings are always true.
Well, we can celebrate over the weekend.
By the way,
you should go grocery shopping later.
My dad complained about the side dishes.
Why don't you cook for him?
You're his son, you know?
Oh no!
Nice!
Good shot!
- Help me.
- Look.
You're too tense right now.
It will ruin your swing.
Here. Open up wide to the right,
then swing gently.
Good. Nice shot!
- Was it okay?
- It was great.
Ready.
Hey!
Nice shot!
What? "Nice shot"?
"It was great"?
Let me explain. Honey, wait.
How great, you jerk!
- Honey.
- You're dead.
When will you get a grip?
Honey!
Ow, my legs. My back hurts.
Who said you could get up?
A part of the scallion flew here.
But how did you know I was here?
Hang on.
I'll do it.
Here. Give it to me.
What are you doing?
You should help with this stuff.
You said you had a meeting.
Should I call your manager?
Well, there was a meeting…
Fine. I'll call him.
I quit my job.
I mean,
they gave me the works
because I messed up a contract.
Seriously. Everyone makes mistakes!
Have you lost your mind?
When did you quit?
Not too long ago.
Exactly when?
In the spring?
Last year.
Almost a year ago?
My goodness.
Then you've been
pretending to go to work every day?
Where did you get the money to golf?
Come on. My severance pay.
They give you quite a lot.
I don't know
what I would've done without it.
Seo Chung-jae, you scumbag.
I'm going to kill you tonight.
HEAD MANAGER GU WON
Ta-da.
You're here.
This is how I've been working
with my employees.
- Here.
- There's more?
Strength, weakness, opportunity, threat.
What do consumers
perceive to be our strength?
Our strength?
I'm calling in regard to Dubai Hotel.
Yes.
Mr. Gu.
I heard Ms. Gu had all of the executives
stay up all night for a week
writing the proposal.
Will we be able to beat them?
It's going to be a head-to-head battle.
We're not here to fight.
We're here to work.
I know that,
but they keep picking a fight.
You trust me, right?
Of course I do.
You got this!
Okay. Go ahead.
Present it to him.
Yes, ma'am.
Goodness.
SURVIVAL MANAGEMENT IMPLEMENTATION PLAN
You've come quite prepared.
The key point is simple.
It's about the overall reduction
of our fixed and variable expenses.
The first expense to consider is payroll.
We should hire fewer full-time employees
and create more contract positions.
Will we have enough employees
for peak seasons and banquets?
We can employ trainees
or part-time employees.
Wouldn't that affect our service quality?
No. They will be trained before banquets,
and they'll only have to serve meals.
It won't be a problem.
Additionally, if we implement
a smart check-in and check-out system,
we will be able
to gradually reduce manpower.
"Discontinuing the shuttle bus,
slimming down the employee cafeteria menu,
and eliminating water and snacks
in the staff lounge."
You really tackled everything.
It's survival management.
What's the expected effect?
It's expected to save
about a billion won a month
and over ten billion won a year.
Ten billion won?
Head Manager Gu,
do you know how many standard rooms
need to be sold to make ten billion won?
In terms of standard rooms, about 34,000.
How precise.
Do you still think
cutting costs is ineffective?
Yes.
Our Mr. Gu here sounds so confident.
Whatever you say from this point on
needs to be worth
more than ten billion won.
A hotel
should not just focus on selling rooms.
It should provide a memorable experience.
In order for the employees
to serve from the heart,
- the company must support--
- Enough with the theories.
Talk about the money, okay? The money.
Then,
should I start with
a hundred billion won?
What?
I offered management consulting
to 170 local hotels around the world,
and 30 hotels
signed management agreements with us.
As you may know, a management agreement
grants us a portion of the hotels' profits
in return for our name and services.
The expected annual return
is more than 35 billion won.
When did you get all of this done?
A six-star hotel
under construction in Dubai has offered
to make King Hotel a hotel chain.
We've already signed a chain contract
with Comfortabele Resort of Belgium,
a newcomer to the industry.
King Hotel will no longer remain
a domestic brand.
You will be able to see
King Hotel all over the world.
This was only possible
because King Hotel
won the World of Best Talent Award.
I didn't accomplish anything on my own.
It's thanks to the people
who built this hotel over 100 years,
which includes everyone here.
The company makes the employees.
And the employees make the company.
You mentioned casual employment.
That would make it easy to
hire people briefly and get rid of them.
But it would also make it easy for them
to abandon the company.
So those ready to abandon each other
will be working together.
Let's not do that anymore.
In my opinion, this project
will bring in
more than a hundred billion won.
What do you think, Ms. Gu?
Cost reduction
is something that any company
must achieve,
no matter how great
the increase in sales is.
Yes, I agree with you on that.
But the thing is…
whenever I traveled overseas,
I always thought the same thing.
"Why does this country
not have a King Hotel?"
"Why can't we become
a worldwide hotel chain?"
It's not like we don't have
enough resources.
Right?
Mr. Gu,
what is the reason?
I think it's because King Hotel
doesn't have an established brand image.
It's just one of the numerous
luxurious hotels out there.
However, an image is not made easily.
It needs to be built up over time.
Fortunately,
our hotel has a 100-year history.
With the 100th-anniversary event,
it can be said that King Hotel
has gained its own image.
Mr. Gu.
Starting next month,
you're the president of the hotel.
Be at the forefront and make
King Hotel the best hotel in the world.
- Father…
- You should do whatever you can to help.
You can do that, right?
Yes, I will.
You accomplished
what I desperately wanted to do.
Why don't you give up on the hotel, ma'am?
I think it'd be best for you
to focus on Air and Distribution.
That might be more effective.
The hotel is smaller in scale
compared to Air and Distribution.
But the thing is,
I don't want to give him anything.
Is there a reason
why you can't give up on the hotel?
Because Won likes the hotel.
All the more reason not to give it up.
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
Are those divorce papers?
Since when did you ask me such questions?
Even if you get a divorce,
it can't be now.
It's not the right time.
You should wait it out.
Mr. Choi.
You've known me for a while, right?
I've worked for you since you were young.
Have you ever seen me give up on anything?
No.
So why would you say that
when you know that very well?
"Give up on the hotel"?
There's only one way
for Won to possess the hotel.
It's when I abandon it.
Only then will it be possible.
I understand.
You may leave.
Thank you.
This is unbelievable.
Did you hear the news
that's hot off the press?
What is it?
Mr. Gu outrivaled Ms. Gu
and is finally going to be the president.
Really?
If I knew this would happen,
I would've gotten on his good side.
Sa-rang, can we have a word?
Yes, ma'am.
You will be on special duty.
You won't be working
in King the Land for the time being.
- Just me?
- Yes.
Special orders from the chairman.
The chairman?
I'm sorry.
Ji-hu said it had to be you.
Please look after him while he's in Korea.
That kid's a shrewd judge of character.
He knew you were our hotel's
best employee right away.
I'm sorry,
but may I ask if I'm doing this
as a King Hotel employee?
Let's call it a personal request.
It's the first time
that he's ever asked me for anything.
I just wanted to grant my grandson's wish.
Did I go too far?
No, sir. I understand.
- But…
- What is it?
Can I treat him
like he's my younger brother?
I couldn't ask for more.
Ji-hu is an only child,
so he grew up lonely.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Ji-hu?
Where could he be?
Ji-hu!
Where in the world are you?
Are you over here?
What? You scared me!
How does that make you feel?
How dare you?
Do you think you'll get away with this?
Watch out.
You'll get a taste of hell.
What?
Then did you call me
to get revenge and torment me?
Why? Are you scared?
No, not at all.
If you're a man, you should play fair.
But you were hiding in a mask.
Maybe it's because you're a kid.
Your behavior is ungentlemanly.
Don't call me a kid.
I'm not a kid.
Is that so?
You're right.
Seeing how childish you are,
you're not a kid.
A baby. You're a baby.
You're a baby, right?
Don't call me a baby!
- Bring it on.
- "Bring it on."
It's my turn.
I won, so now you have to speak politely.
Let's play one more time.
It's ten to zero.
You said it was the last round.
Just one more round.
- Do you want to play that much?
- Yes.
Then how should you ask me?
Sa-rang,
can we play one more round,
please?
Good.
All right.
- This is really the last time.
- Awesome!
Not up…
Try again. Ready?
One,
two,
three.
Good job.
It's tasty, isn't it?
Yeah.
By the way, I have a question.
Why do you do that?
Why do you act nice
in front of the adults,
then bully the weak?
Is that fun?
I do what I want.
You don't have any friends, do you?
Only nobodies make friends.
I don't need them.
I knew it.
Who would want to hang out
with a grump like you?
That's not true.
I'm just not making any
because I don't need them.
That's what you want to think.
No, it's not.
You need to be nice
if you want to make friends.
If you pick on people and bully them,
you won't make any friends.
So don't be like that from now on. Got it?
Let's go inside now.
Can we play a little more?
Are you asking me a favor?
All right. Just because it's a favor.
Yes!
Okay. Let's play.
Grandpa!
Why hello.
You must've had a lot of fun.
Yes. We're going to play again
tomorrow too.
Go upstairs and wash your hands.
I'll bring some snacks.
Okay, Sa-rang.
I've never seen him look so happy.
It's like you're his actual sister.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. I had a lot of fun too.
You were home.
Why are you here?
I'll be working here for the time being.
The chairman asked me to look after Ji-hu.
He asked you to look after Ji-hu?
You don't have to. I'll talk to him.
He asked me respectfully.
He didn't order me to do it
as the chairman.
He asked me out of love for his grandson,
so I said yes.
But still,
how could he ask you to do that?
I already agreed to it.
I'm having fun in my own way,
so don't worry.
All right, fine.
But you have to tell me
if anyone gives you a hard time.
Okay. I will.
So this is Head Manager Gu Won's room.
- Can I look around?
- Of course.
But how long are you going to
call me by my title?
We're not even at work.
Fine, Mr. Won.
What's "Mr. Won"?
I don't know.
It's the king carp.
This…
It was so hard
trying to put these pieces back together.
Why did you go
to the trouble of doing that?
It's a memory
from our first date.
What's this?
Wait.
Is this when you started liking me?
Well, not exactly.
- Give it back. I'm embarrassed.
- Gosh.
- No.
- Come on.
- Come on. I'm embarrassed.
- No.
- Give it to me.
- I'm embarrassed.
- No.
- Give it back already.
What are you doing in my house?
So this is
the bed that you sleep in, Mr. Won.
Sa-rang.
Are you in here?
Sa-rang, are you in here?
Ta-da!
What are you doing here?
Hide-and-seek!
You have to hide this time, okay?
-Ten,
-Hold on.
-nine,
-Count slowly.
eight, seven,
six,
five,
four, three…
two, one!
Here I come!
Ji-hu, that punk. He didn't even knock.
It was exhausting, right?
I heard parenting
is the world's hardest job.
I think that's true.
By any chance,
have you ever spent time with Ji-hu?
When Ji-hu was younger,
I was studying abroad.
And when I was in Korea, he was abroad,
so our paths rarely crossed.
Why do you ask?
Just because he's young,
but he already looks so lonely.
- Ji-hu does?
- Yes.
It feels like he has no one around him.
He's so well-behaved and mature,
so I had no idea.
Kids being mature is not a good sign.
Adults should be the mature ones.
Even being mature as an adult is hard.
Ji-hu,
you should sleep in your bed.
Ji-hu.
You're home, Uncle Won.
Yes. Let's go sleep upstairs.
Mom isn't home yet.
I think your mom will be late.
Why don't you go to bed early
and see her tomorrow?
I missed her yesterday
and the day before that.
I really want to see her today.
Can I just wait for her?
Sure, go ahead.
Okay. Thank you.
Mom!
Why are you still here?
Did you not go to the US?
Can't I stay here for a little longer?
I told you that now's not a good time.
Why won't you listen?
I'm sorry.
Go to your room.
Okay.
You sure prepared a lot behind the scenes.
I told you.
You don't deserve
to be the owner of the group.
You talk like you've already won.
Do you really think it's over?
You're so naive.
Is the company all that matters?
Does Ji-hu not exist to you?
Do you know how long he waited for you?
What?
Does he remind you of yourself?
You always cried, looking for your mom.
But you know what?
Ji-hu isn't you.
And I'm not like your mom.
Don't give me advice
from your lowly perspective.
How arrogant of you.
It's my first time in your room.
It's your first time back in a while.
Is there anything you want to do?
I'm okay.
Well,
if you happen to think of something,
please let me know.
We can do it together.
- Ta-da!
- It's gimbap!
You made all of this yourself?
Of course I did.
Here.
- Ji-hu. One, two, three.
- Hold this.
- Here.
- You're good at this.
I'm pretty good.
We did it.
I'm going to grow up to be like you.
Why?
You're cool.
You're the coolest person in the world.
Thanks for saying that.
However,
there's one thing I did
that you shouldn't do.
What is it?
You have to cry when you want to
and laugh when you want to.
If you're mad, get mad and make a fuss.
But most importantly,
if you miss someone,
tell them that you miss them.
Whether it's your mom or your dad.
Can I do that?
Of course.
Being honest isn't a bad thing.
It means you're brave.
I…
want you to become a brave person.
A brave person is the coolest person.
Even cooler than me.
Then…
can I stay in Korea for a little longer?
- Is that what you want to do?
- Yes.
I never got to play with my mom yet.
Okay.
I'll help you do that.
Really?
Thank you.
- Ji-hu.
- Sa-rang!
What is that?
Tornado potatoes.
Have you tried it before?
- No.
- You haven't?
- Give it.
- You want it?
You can't have it.
Here you go.
You're not here
to talk about work, are you?
No, I'm not.
Then
may I speak casually?
Yes, you may.
I've been waiting.
Waiting for you to come find me.
You're…
the one who sent me
my mother's personnel record, right?
There's something I'd like to ask.
Do you think
you can understand your mom now?
No.
There's no need for that anymore.
It happened so long ago.
Do you want to know where she is?
It's okay.
I just wanted to know the truth.
I never wanted to see her.
Thank you for being honest with me.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
- Soybean paste stew?
- Doesn't it smell good?
Yes, it looks so good. Can I have a bite?
A bite?
Nice.
I'll cut this too.
This is mind-blowing.
Just one bite.
- Enjoy your meal.
Soybean paste stew.
Rice.
And rolled omelet.
This is nice.
Are you not going to meet your mom?
I wanted to know why she left me.
Now I know. That's enough.
It could've been
because she loved you so much.
If she loved me,
she should've stayed by my side
no matter what.
Whatever the reason may be, she left me.
That means I didn't mean much in her life.
There could be another reason
that you're not aware of.
That's why I wanted you to meet her.
That way,
you'd be able to know how she felt.
I don't want to
think about my mom anymore.
It finally feels
as if I'm free from her.
As long as you feel at ease now.
Yes.
Thank you
for bringing me all the way here.
KING THE LAND
"Third-generation chaebol's
secret love affair."
How did you pick him up?
Share your secrets.
You have caused greater damage
just for your personal gain!
We, the board of directors,
oppose Mr. Gu's promotion to president.
I understand why Won likes you.
And it's scarier because of that.
Only the worst transgressors end up here.
Where is Ms. Cheon Sa-rang?
Subtitle translation by: Stephanie Jung
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs