Previously on "Batwoman"...
I lost my sister Beth. Remember her?
Beth has gone down, down,
down the rabbit hole,
and she's never coming back.
Alice is looking for a Mouse.
She has big plans for him.
- What is...
- Chipped him.
He leads me to Alice,
I figure out who Mouse is.
I never understood why you stopped
looking for me.
I always thought a father would do
anything to find his daughter.
I won't let you forget
me, Commander, not again.
You'd think having spent 9 months
in our mother's womb together
and every other day for 13 years,
we wouldn't be such great mysteries
to one another, but we are.
I don't know what
the rest of her story is,
but that's the puzzle
I'm determined to solve...
Before it's too late.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
They're calling him the Skin Pirate
because apparently he likes
to take skin from the booty.
- Never say that again.
- I didn't write the article.
Point being whatever
they're calling him,
he has quite the work ethic.
He hit 3 morgues in one night,
and all 3 break-ins
were 9 minutes apart.
That's a pretty tight window.
Yeah. Calculating the
quickest route between them.
Can you get eyes on that?
Yeah.
It looks like our he is a she.
Does she look familiar to you?
- Is that Alice?
- No.
You sure about that? Hang on.
She's not the Skin Pirate, okay?
It's too sick even for her.
Let's not forget we
have access to something
the GCPD doesn't...
Wayne's closed circuit cameras.
There aren't many, but let's
see if they caught anything.
Yeah. Yeah. That's her.
I'll look into whatever the hell
she could be using the skin for
if you remind me to clear
my image search history.
- What are you doing?
- Stopping her.
Whatever she's got planned
for Gotham ends today.
You don't even know where she is.
Nope, but I put a tracker in Dodgson.
I know where he is, and she
likes to keep her toys close.
Bruce doesn't have night vision goggles.
Batman doesn't do goggles.
Forgetting pain is convenient.
Remembering it, agonizing,
but recovering the truth
is worth the suffering.
Now tell me the truth.
What did you reveal to her?
Nothing. I wouldn't betray you.
Good. Because if you ruin
all I have been working for,
off... with... your... head.
Hmm. It looks like my dear sister
wasn't very kind to you, was she?
It's only a matter of
time before she gets hers.
Aah!
I'm not afraid of the dark,
and I'm not afraid of you!
Show yourself!
Heh.
Kinky... even for you.
Stealing skin off corpses...
Sadistic, even for you.
Key word... corpses.
I didn't hurt anyone.
What's the skin for?
You hit 3 morgues in one night.
You're working on something.
Dodgson said, uh, you
had plans with a Mouse.
Heh heh. Oh, I'm sure he
said lots of silly things
when your attention-starved
stepsister illegally drugged him.
Is Mouse a real person or a figment
of your imagination?
And what are you two planning?
If you keep going down this
road, it's gonna end badly,
but it doesn't have to.
I can get you into a
rehabilitation hospital,
a real one, Beth.
Nice try, but Alice will do.
You're gonna have to give me something.
Mouse was the one who
found me after the crash.
You do remember the crash?
What happened to you?
Aren't you the great detective?
Figure it out!
Heh.
- What are you doing?
- Calling Dad,
just letting him know I'm with you.
But he'll track your phone,
and if he finds us,
he'll ruin all our fun.
And he'll send you straight to Arkham.
- Kate?
- Hi, Dad.
I'm with Alice.
What do you mean you're with Alice?
I have her.
Well, where are you? I'll send a team.
I'm fine. She's... contained.
- Kate?
- Just thought you should know.
Clock's ticking. Start talking.
Fine, but I'll have to show you.
Show me? Heh. I don't think so.
The clock's tick, tick, ticking.
Let me down, and I'll tell you
all about my...
Long, sad tale.
Hmm. So where to begin.
I suppose it started... Tsh, tsh, tsh...
14 months before Catherine
Hamilton faked my death.
What are you talking about?
Oh. No one told you.
Hmm. That is so them.
Those bones, they belonged to a deer.
Our stepmother faked my DNA results,
and Daddy just found out
he had a funeral for Bambi.
I wonder if they have a prenup.
The bones at Miller Farm.
You don't seem that surprised.
Is that because deep
down you always knew
those bones weren't mine?
And now you know why.
Am I supposed to turn somewhere?
You're not asking the
right questions, Kate.
What is my evil plan?
Who am I targeting next?
How am I gonna do it?
When you really need to be asking why?
- Why am I like this?
- Okay. Why?
Oh, you don't want to know that.
I have waited 15 years to hear it.
Well, it all began with
an unfortunate event
which I remember vividly,
and if given the chance again,
I would take it back in a heartbeat.
It was a simple, effortless thing
that I had done so many times before.
I woke up.
Dad, she woke up.
Oh, hi. You must be terrified.
What's your name?
Beth. Where am I?
Hello, Beth. You're okay.
My son Johnny and I were
fishing in the river,
and we saw you along the rocks.
Any idea how you got there?
Where's my mom?
Well, the police will be here soon.
I'm sure they can call her for you.
No. She was in the car
with me. She needs help.
It's gonna be okay, all right?
- Are you hungry?
- I want my dad.
I'm gonna make you a sandwich.
The little boy just sat there
with his hair in his eyes,
playing with his trucks.
For him, it was an ordinary day...
But for me, it was the
first worst day of my life.
What was the man's name?
Oh, I have no idea.
What do you mean you have no idea?
He rescued you.
It'll all make more
sense when we arrive.
Go down the road a mile, take a right,
go two miles, and
there's a roadside diner.
Consider it your first
stop down the rabbit hole.
It doesn't make sense.
Why would she call you and
not tell you where she was?
No idea. She knows I'll trace the call.
Maybe that was her intention.
We should get a team together.
No. No. For now, it's just you and me.
Sir, it's Alice. I don't
need to read you her résumé.
And I don't need another standoff
like we had in Burnside Park.
Found her.
She's headed west on the interstate.
Let's go.
I don't get it. How could they mix up
animal bones with human ones?
I mean, the bone density alone
should have tipped them off.
Not to mention the fact that the
genomes are completely different.
Because it wasn't a mix-up.
It was a lie.
What? Are you covering
up for the lab's mistake?
Mom, you don't have to do that, okay?
You can just tell me
the truth, and we can...
I am.
I was trying to give
Jacob and Kate closure.
No. You wouldn't do that
because that would be...
That would be horrible.
I am so sorry, Mary,
but I wanted you to hear it from me,
not from Jacob or Kate, from me.
I know you, okay?
I know you,
so please tell me you didn't do this.
Oh. Uh, two beers, please.
None for me.
You do not want to be sober
for the remainder of this story.
Trust me.
Ahem. Just the one beer.
Right back with that.
We're here. Talk,
and what does this place
have to do with anything?
Well, when your life
unfolds into a nightmare,
you pray your dreams
will take you elsewhere.
I used to dream of running away
with you to a place like this,
and then my hunger would wake me.
Alas, it wasn't meant to be.
This would be entirely
easier with two free hands.
You're my sister, Alice.
We spent half our lives together.
Where did that person go?
Down, down, down the rabbit hole.
Look. I'm done messing around.
If you're gonna talk, talk.
If not, we'll just sit here
and wait for Dad to find us.
As I was saying,
I remember it like it was yesterday...
The toys, the books, the treats.
Upstairs, there was a room
like a child's wonderland.
It was Mouse's room.
Goonies never say die!
He went by Johnny then.
It's leviosa,
not leviosar.
I can do any voice I hear.
You kids want lemonade?
Who else has come
to ease our woes?
Cinderella!
Why do you cover your face like that?
To hide what happened in the accident.
You shouldn't have to hide who you are.
I'll scare people.
You don't scare me.
We interrupt this program
with breaking news.
Police announced earlier that
they've expanded their search
for the missing Kane girl
to the county of Blüdhaven.
Police and volunteers have been...
Wait. Your dad said
he called the police.
Why don't they know I'm here?
The family says a
reward is being offered
for any tips...
Johnny, no more TV today.
They're looking for me.
We have to call the police.
I told you, Beth. They'll be here soon.
We don't want you to leave us.
Please. Let me go! You're hurting me!
- Dad!
- Johnny, stay here!
Please! Aah! Let me go!
- Dad!
- Let me go!
Aah! Stop it, please!
Ow! Stop, please. Let me go now, please!
Aah! I'm sorry!
No!
No, no. Let me out.
No. Let me out!
Aah!
And that was just the first day.
Hmm. I think she'll take that drink now.
Kate! Kate, I need to talk to you, okay?
I hate her, too! Kate!
Here she is. Wouldn't
stop trying to buzz in,
insisting she's related to Ms. Kane.
- But I am.
- And...
I'll take it from here. Thanks, Carl.
Uh, can I help you,
possibly to an AA meeting?
That depends. Is your name Kate?
Most definitely not.
Then can you tell her that I'm here?
I'm sorry. Who's here?
Mary, Kate's soon-to-be ex-stepsister,
and you are?
Luke, Kate's, uh, associate, assistant,
real estate person.
Look. Kate's not here.
You know what? You could
leave her a message.
Okay.
Tell her... that I'm so sorry
I was ever born from the
wicked witch of Gotham,
and I get why she's avoiding me,
but I'm totally on her side.
I can't believe that my mom
would ever do something so awful.
Oh, my God. Do you think that
she killed that deer, too?
Are you getting any of this?
All I heard is that your mom may
or may not have killed a deer.
Ugh. It's probably best I
start from the beginning.
Sir, I know this is
completely inappropriate
for a subordinate to ask her commander,
but are you okay?
Catherine and I are going
trough a rough patch.
Copy that, sir. My apologies.
I was under the impression it
had something to do with Alice.
It turns out it does.
Catherine paid the DNA analysts
to say the skull
fragments found were Beth's.
And they weren't?
And I just confirmed she was responsible
for the bomb on Loeb
Bridge targeting Alice.
Damn. So Kate was right this whole time.
We don't know what's right.
The only way to settle this
for good is to catch Alice,
run her DNA, and... and let
science tell us the truth.
Kate's signal stopped moving.
Looks like they're at
some place called Dusty's.
Mmm. So good. Sure you don't want to?
Why?
I think the beef is grass-fed.
Why was there a face in a sink?
- Oh, that.
- I'm serious, Alice.
You survive a crash, wash up on shore,
some Hannibal Lecter finds you,
keeps you as his prisoner.
Did he want to kill you,
skin you, what?
Well, I wasn't a prisoner.
Then what were you?
I was a friend.
Friend, I've learned, takes
on a different meaning,
depending on who you ask.
Socialization is essential
to one's development.
It's as important as
food, water, and shelter.
It allows one to
develop a sense of self,
a sense of purpose.
W-what is that?
Oh, a little experiment.
You see...
My dear son didn't get the opportunity
to develop a sense of purpose
because the world made him an outcast.
They called him a monster.
He waited a very long time
for someone...
Like you.
I just want to go home.
This is your home now.
I want my dad.
Don't cry.
You'll get used to it here.
Dad! Dad! Daddy!
Little Johnny didn't have any friends,
and then I came along.
What was he using the skin for?
Experiments.
Trying to hide Mouse's
hideous face. Heh.
He thought if he could find
a way to make him look normal
the ridicule would end and
he'd live happily ever after.
So... ahem... the skin
at the... at the morgue,
what... what were you...
What am I what, Kate?
Go on. Speak up.
Uh...
Oh. Oh, no. Don't tell
me you're a lightweight.
What's wrong, dear sister?
What did you do to me?
Take cover now!
Come out, come out, Commander.
Dodgson.
There's a propane tank on the east.
I'll distract them.
Keep your asses on the ground.
Where's my daughter? Where is she?
Which one?
What the hell happened to you?
You happened, Commander.
I joined the Crows
to make Gotham better,
but you divided it.
The city's not safe.
The wealthy are safe,
and you're too blind to see it
just like you were too blind
to see your own daughter.
Sir! Sir!
Sir, stop, sir!
Commander, come on.
Didn't have to be this way, Commander.
You could have saved her.
Ooh!
Ooh.
I mean, God, Kate knew this whole time
that Beth was alive.
You know, that celestial sisterly bond
is real, man.
Actually, that's really heavy.
It just made me dizzy.
Let me call you a car.
To take me where?
The penthouse built on lies
of falsely dead children?
Hard pass.
Look. I get that you're
going through a lot right now,
but Kate is obviously not here,
and I'm really trying to work.
Seriously, Luke, I am going
through a major family
crisis here, okay?
I don't even know who
my own mom is anymore.
I just found out I have
a second stepsister.
Kate found her actual full sister?
Oh, my God. Wait.
Is Kate with Alice right now?
If I say yes, will you leave?
Wow.
Here I am at the literal lowest point
that I've ever been, and
Kate decides to choose today
of all days to go out
for some sisterly bonding
with a coldblooded killer?
Meanwhile, how many people
have I murdered, hmm?
- What?
- Guess!
How many people have I killed?
It's between zero and why are you even
hesitating right now?
Zero. I've killed zero people.
I'm the good sister.
You found the tracker, didn't you?
You knew I'd come for you.
Yes, I found the tracker. Heh.
I knew a few morgue thefts
would stir you into action,
arranged for a friend
to drug your drink,
and now I've taken you
out of the equation.
You see, my dearest Mouse and I
were cooking up a little
something special for Gotham,
and it'll undoubtedly
go down more smoothly
without a Bat in the broth.
Let me go, Alice.
But we haven't even gotten to
the best part of the story yet.
Alas after weeks and weeks in captivity,
like a little rabbit
down a hole so small,
I... finally managed...
To claw... my way out.
It's curious, for there are
so many out-of-the-way things
that when one becomes desperate
present themselves.
I found one such opportunity
in a rusty, little friend.
Oh, dear, oh, dear, my
poor, delicate fingers,
but success I eventually did make mine.
- Hello.
- Daddy, it's me Beth.
- You have to help.
- Beth?
Oh, my God. Beth, where are you?
If anyone comes looking
for you, I will kill them...
And it will be all your fault.
Do you understand me?
I remember that call.
My first and last chance at freedom.
Dad had it traced.
After all that time and there
were so many false leads,
the GCPD didn't believe us,
said they'd already searched
this area several times...
But we were here within an hour.
You stay here.
- Where is she?
- Mr. Kane, there's been
- a terrible misunderstand...
- Where's my daughter?
Sir, please allow me to explain.
My daughter Beth called me not
one hour ago from this house.
She said, "Help," clear as can be.
It was all an insensitive prank.
I'm... I'm... I'm so embarrassed. I...
Mr. Kane, your daughter is not in there.
Beth! Beth! Beth!
Beth, you in here?
Mr. Kane, like I said, it was my son.
He has... an ability, I guess you'd say,
for mimicry.
Johnny, please show him what you did.
I don't want to.
Show him what you did.
I said I don't want to.
Show him!
Hi, Daddy. It's me Beth.
I learned a new song on my cello
that I can play on the
first night of Chanukah.
Here. Let me show you.
That's impossible.
How do you know what
her voice sounds like?
He saw a home video
clip on the nightly news.
He's been obsessed
with her disappearance
since it happened.
If anyone comes looking
for you, I will kill them.
Beth?
I was there.
He told me if I made a peep
that he'd kill you both,
so I just waited.
I waited for you to feel it,
to know,
to sense,
but alas, nothing.
I guess what they say about twins
being connected,
that profound, soulful, magical tie
is just fantasy...
The thing you dream about
before your hunger
wakes you up.
I've lost Kate's location, sir.
She must have turned off her phone.
- Sir?
- I've been out here before.
15 years ago.
Sir, what's happening?
I know where they are.
Hi, Kate. Me again.
Fifth time now actually.
Still got that big... showing
with that big buyer.
Urgent, real urgent, need
you to call me back ASAP.
Hey, hey!
Wow.
What the hell is this?
Okay.
Alice hit up 3 morgues last night,
stole flesh from a
bunch of dead bodies...
Oh, my God. Alice is the Skin Pirate?
- Of course she is.
- I know, I know.
You've skinned zero corpses.
Well, I haven't.
Is it disgusting that this is making me
really hungry for pizza?
Yes, that is absolutely disgusting.
Here. Check this out. Found something.
Two weeks ago, a guy
named Jonathan Cartwright,
who admitted to having a similar hobby
of stealing skin from dead people,
escaped in the Arkham breakout.
What Arkham breakout?
There was a breakout... At Arkham.
Uh, pretty sure I would have heard
about something like that.
Uh... but you didn't, so...
So... Arkham officials covered it up.
Comforting.
You think this creep has
something to do with Alice?
I think the timing feels
incredibly suspicious.
I got the front. You take the back.
Sir, a couple of shacks in the back.
- Checking them out.
- Copy that.
Hi, Daddy.
Where's Kate?
"Where's Kate?"
"Is Kate okay? Is Kate happy?
Is she sleeping enough?
"Has she done her homework,
seen a doctor, had enough to eat?"
Kate, Kate, Kate, Kate, Kate, Kate!
I'm so sick of Kate!
What are you doing?
Where's Beth?
When was the last time you uttered
those words, Commander Crow?
Was it here?
Was it in this house?
Come on. Don't do this.
Was it when I called you
and you didn't even believe it was me?
Let's go outside. We'll talk.
You told your men to kill me.
Put down the knife.
Because you don't care.
You've never cared!
Put down the knife.
You gave up on me!
Beth, drop the damn knife!
"Beth."
You... you said it.
Agh!
Unh.
- Sophie.
- Kate.
Sophie, I'm in here.
Hurry.
Agh!
Hey. I need some... unh!
What the hell?
Aah!
There's a guy in the
shed. His face, I...
Shh. I know who he is.
Ugh!
Ohh!
Drop it!
You need to decide right now
what you care more about...
Revenge or Mouse.
I said drop it, or the
next one goes in his head.
Two can play this game... Sister.
We both know you don't have it in you.
But I do.
I suppose killing Daddy
would be all too easy
and no fun at all.
Let us all walk out of here,
and no one has to die today.
Dad.
Kate... it's her.
It's Beth.
So it has been an experience,
but your chariot has arrived.
2015 hybrid hatchback,
power everything, 4.3 stars.
- I can take a hint.
- Wasn't really hinting.
Oh!
If Kate calls, can you just...
Tell her that I'm sorry for everything?
- Sure.
- Maybe if I go kill someone
she'll actually call me back.
Only one way to find out.
I thought if I let Alice tell her story
the puzzle would fit
together, but the pieces are
grim, grotesque, inhuman,
and it's my fault.
I was there and didn't feel her.
I'm her twin, Bruce.
How am I supposed to
connect with her now
when I couldn't connect with her then?
Shouldn't you be in the hospital?
You know I hate hospitals.
What if I don't know my sister
well enough to save her?
What if nobody does?
Well, Alice may have
been forced to flee.
In the end, she got the cheese.
You didn't visit me.
My dearest Mouse, we both know
if I'd shown up to Arkham
with a freshly baked pie I would have
no sooner been locked in a cell myself.
- Heh.
But you felt me in your dreams?
Every night.
"Twined in memory's mystic band."
Beth?
Go away.
I shouldn't have tricked
your dad and sister.
I'm sorry.
I want to go home.
You know he won't let you.
But you can.
You can let me out.
Maybe, but...
I also don't want you to go.
I want to be your friend.
To keep you company.
"Oh, Mouse,
do you know the way out of this pool?
I am very tired of
swimming in my own tears."
"I do know a way.
I will help you escape
your pool of tears."
And you did.
You saved me.
I have a gift for you, too.
I love you, Alice.
I love you, too, Dear Brother,
and now that we are together again
I can help you become
anyone you want to be,
and once we are done with Daddy,
he will never forget about me.
Never, ever again.
Are we mad?
I'm afraid so.
Ha ha ha!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --