Trust me, this isn't the story
I expected to be telling.
But you know as well as I do
that stories,
like the people who tell them,
aren't always what they seem.
Let's take a picture, Beth.
Mom! Wake up! No! Mom!
Batman's here. He's gonna save us!
Batman, where are you going? Wait!
You're leaving us to die!
Beth, grab my hand!
Grab my hand!
- Kate!
- Mom, Beth, no!
- Too slow.
- You covered the damn hole!
And you found way, own way.
Tomorrow,...find faster.
I suppose I should start here
in Gotham.
Three years ago, when Batman
mysteriously disappeared
it divided the city.
Some hoped he'd be back,
others figured he was dead.
I thought he abandoned Gotham
for the same reason
he abandoned my family.
Because he didn't care.
Keep it on! Keep it on!
Keep it on!
- Don't turn off the bat signal!
- Keep it on!
Keep it on! Keep it on!
Keep it on! Keep it on! Keep it on!
How cute is this little kid?
Mary, you're embarrassing me.
Keep it on! Keep it on! Keep it on!
Excuse me, ma'am.
This isn't beneath you, Commander?
Well, it's the only excuse
I have to see my radiant wife.
Concerned the police
couldn't keep order
in a Gotham without Batman,
my dad started Crows Security.
A private firm
that protects the people
that the Dark Knight left behind.
Moore to Crows' nest.
North side's clear.
How are we out front?
Perimeter looks good.
What's the word, Vasquez?
- West Side's clear.
- Copy.
Let's lock it up.
All right, Dodgson, how much?
Ten thousand bucks a plate
just to watch a light flip off.
Must be nice.
Operational leadership
at its best, Agent Moore.
Well, done tonight.
My pleasure, sir.
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight is about reality.
Batman gave up on us.
It's been three years, Gotham.
The Bat's not coming back.
Mayor Akins, help us say goodbye
to Gotham's outdated tradition.
It's time to turn off the signal!
My kid used to stare at this thing
through his bedroom window.
Now, I got to be the one
to flip it off?
Together, I invite you to gaze out
at the Bat-Signal one last time.
Commander Kane, I just lost
our city surveillance.
What about the rooftop feed?
- Sir, we're totally blind.
- Something's up.
Eyes everywhere.
We're gonna start
the countdown, Officer.
Copy. Standing by.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Turn the light off, boys.
What's happening?
"Hello," said Alice.
Shall we believe
the Crows will protect us?
Oh, I believed six impossible
things before breakfast.
Do you feel safe
behind these security gates?
Because one of you
won't be going home tonight.
The Crows are not the hero
of this story, Gotham.
Batman couldn't save you
and neither will they.
Get these people out of here now.
Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Mom?
- Jacob, what's happening?
- Get out now.
Agent Moore, do you copy?
Sophie, do you copy?
We got her.
Call for you.
Girl who talk too much.
- Hello?
- Kate? It's Mary.
- Your step-sister?
- Mary,
our parents have been married
for over a decade,
I know who you are.
Oh, okay.
You have to swear you won't tell
anyone I'm telling you this...
Mary, what happened?
Sophie's missing.
They think someone took her.
I just... I thought you should know.
I had spent years
traveling the world,
training with combat
and survivalist specialists,
so I could join the Crows.
Sophie's disappearance
brought me home early.
I had to find her.
But first, I had to convince
my dad I was ready.
Crows represent order,
security, safety.
These monsters
long for the good old days
when gangs ran around unchecked.
They spread fear by saying,
"Look at us.
If we can get a Crow, we can get
your wife, your kid."
- Where are we on surveillance?
- Afraid it doesn't exist, sir.
If it were any one of you,
Agent Moore would not sleep
until you were found.
Let's do the same for her.
Let's bring her home.
Kate.
Hey, Dad.
Come here, kiddo.
I didn't add cream,
but please tell me!
You kicked that vegan thing, huh?
I wish you called.
- We're gonna find her.
- Then let me help.
Neck tattoo, that's new.
Dad, I'm ready to come home
and work for you.
Sir, Mayor's on two.
He's talking about canceling
the Movie in the Park.
Tell him I'll be right there.
Do you know who took her?
Ruthless, spineless maniacs,
who frankly don't stand a chance
against a team of ex-Navy SEALs
and Green Berets.
- And what about me?
- You take after your cousin.
You're a female Bruce Wayne.
But unlike him,
you actually have a shot
at making something of your life.
Bruce was the one person
who was actually there for me
after Mom and Beth died.
Let me help The Crows find Sophie.
It's great to see you,
but I gotta take this call.
Oh, we don't get we exposed a
week before graduation.
About that?
How about that after we graduate,
I take you to the house
for a week alone on a yacht.
But like...
- with the chef?
- Obviously.
Oh, shed, things you have seen.
Defacing school property.
Why not?
Got me to break every other rule.
"Loves."
Bold.
Cadet Captain Kane,
is there something you'd like
to report to your squad?
Not that I'm aware of, sir.
Perhaps you're not aware
of the academy's code of conduct.
I had to find her.
So, I needed to go to the one place
that always seemed to have
the answers,
to the heart of Gotham,
which just happened to have eyes
all over the city.
Bruce isn't in his office. Come on.
Kate, we're not supposed to be
in here.
What's that?
Why does Bruce
have a girl's necklace?
Come on.
No, I don't think we're supposed
to touch that. Come on.
Step away from the desk! Move!
Wayne Security.
Not to tell you how to do
your job, Mister...
Luke.
Luke, but your boss is my cousin.
Think you're the first squatter
I've met related to Bruce Wayne?
How the hell
did you even get in here?
I'm Kate Kane,
I practically grew up here,
and Bruce was like my fun,
irresponsible big brother.
Okay.
- When's his birthday?
- February 19th.
Middle name?
Trick question. He doesn't have one.
Favorite soup?
Is it weird that you know that?
If you are Bruce's cousin
you know that no one's heard
from him in almost three years.
Hey, yeah.
Luke Fox over at Wayne here.
Got another B and E for you.
Bruce gave me a great piece
of advice once.
Grow into the person
you needed as a kid.
That's great.
Police are on their way.
It turns out that the person
that I needed as a kid can do this.
Hey!
Get these handcuffs off me right now.
Password still "Alfred?"
- Hey!
- You might want to change that.
Wait. You can't...
Can you just step away
from the computer, please?
Hey. What are you doing?
What the Crows aren't able to.
Get this thing off me.
Hey, hey.
You can't just...
I see the relation now.
Dad, I think I found something.
Surprise!
Keep us waiting, why don't you?
- Hi, hey.
- Hi!
- Hi.
- Where's, where's my dad?
No idea because you, me,
cotton candy shots now.
Come on.
So, I'm on the roof
Alice is threatening to kill
literally everybody,
and the first thought that pops
into my brain is,
"Oh, my God, what a bummer.
Now, I'll never be able to read
my future children
Alice In Wonderland.
But then I was like
"Mary, rearranging
your entire life out of fear
is exactly how the terrorists win."
Why did you call me?
I may have found a box
of pictures in your closet
when I was borrowing
your Balenciaga T...
- You know what? Never mind.
- Look. I don't know your drama,
but we all got a box
of picture somewhere.
I just thought you'd want to be here.
Welcome home, Katie.
I hope you don't mind my making you
the center of attention tonight.
No place I'd rather be.
Then let's make sure
we're posting happy photos
to our social media accounts.
Because why wouldn't this party
have an agenda?
If we feel safe,
then our clients feel safe.
Movie in the Park is Friday,
and it's Gotham's first
public event in three years.
Anyway, the councilwoman
would like a photo, Mary.
Excuse us.
"I hereby deny the below allegation
of homosexual conduct."
Blah...blah...blah.
Kiss my ass.
Guess that's that then.
What do you say we burn these
and scatter the ashes
across the Mediterranean?
I can't.
I'm staying.
You signed it.
I told them what they wanted to hear.
You lied.
I need this school, okay?
I want to be here.
But they don't want you.
Unfortunately,
I don't have the luxury
of being offended by that.
And maybe it's best if you just
kept your distance from now on.
Hey.
I know you love me.
Tell me that I'm wrong,
and I'll walk away
and let you make the biggest
mistake of your life.
You're wrong, Kate.
I have to go.
Dad, I have something.
Where'd you get this?
Wayne's camera feed
isn't on the Crows' network.
Wayne's defunct.
Not sure how facial rec's
supposed to work here.
They're in masks.
Wait. What does that paddle say?
"Milk, well-behaved, C-H."
"Not for the mild,
well-behaved child."
It was their creepy
disciplinary motto.
- It was whose motto?
- The Burnside Orphanage.
Beth and I used to sneak in there
with our Ouija board
and freak each other out.
That's where they are.
Taylor, get a satellite feed.
I want eyes all over this.
Dodgson, cover
the north entrance with me.
Banks takes his team on the south.
Kate?
Curiouser and curiouser.
Up, up.
I thought you'd been sent away,
but now, you seem to be here.
How do you know me?
Better now.
Where's Sophie?
Gone. And just in time,
because I am not used to being found.
Clever girl.
If you didn't want an audience,
I'd be dead.
So, what do you want?
I need you to send
your father a message.
He thinks he's Gotham's white knight,
but he's a bully whose army
bullies this city into obedience,
and I want the world to know
that he doesn't scare me.
I want to take away his power.
Then take me and let Sophie go.
Oh, dear. This is quite sad actually.
You poor thing.
You haven't figured it out yet.
I took Sophie
because she'll actually get
his attention.
Your father doesn't want you, Kate.
He shipped you away,
and you show up
without the proper postage.
I assumed you knew.
But then again,
you have been so busy
trying to convince him to love you,
you sweet,... pathetic girl.
Sophie is the daughter
your father always wanted,
not you, dear.
Who the hell are you?
Right. I'm Alice.
How do you do?
Dodgson, what do you got?
- Just missed them, sir.
- Where's Kate?
Found her bike stashed
in some bushes,
but no sign of her.
What do you mean no sign of her?
Where am I?
Hi...
And don't kill me.
What is this place?
This is my humble,
little illegal clinic
Gotham University has generously
and unknowingly lent me.
Hey, hey, Mr. Whittaker.
We're gonna have to keep that on,
okay?
We talked about this, remember?
Got to keep that on.
Can we be done with this? I got to...
Hang on. I was mid-stitch.
How did you find me?
Someone dumped you at the door.
One of my guys brought you in.
You have guys?
So I swear this began with me
offering water and Band-Aids,
and the next thing you know,
I'm the Meredith Grey
of Sherwood Forest.
I'm sorry if stealing from my med
school makes me a bad person.
It doesn't.
It actually makes you deeper
than I thought.
Thanks.
Done.
Keep your ear to the street,
and if you hear anything
about Sophie, call.
Yeah.
I was right.
Alice was there,
and wherever they went,
it's probably not far.
Where the hell have you been?
We thought she took you too.
I got half my guys out there
looking for you!
And here I am telling you
her vendetta isn't against Gotham,
isn't against the Crows,
but against you.
- Why?
- You are not listening.
You ran into an unknown
terrorist cell
without proper backup.
If you treated me
like everybody else,
- I would have had backup.
- Except you're not everyone else.
No, I'm not.
I never will be...
Because no matter what I do
trying to prove myself to you,
you don't want me.
What did I tell you
after you got expelled
from the Academy?
Kate, I love you.
I wouldn't want you any other way.
I remember what you said
because it was right
before you sent me away
to train for a job
that you were never gonna give me.
I was giving you a second chance.
You were getting rid of me.
Because when you look at me,
you see Beth,
and when you see Beth, you see mom.
And instead of dealing with it,
you spent the last 15 years
pushing me away.
You win, Dad.
I'm gone.
Kate.
Hey, hey, hey.
How did you even get in...
I know you know where Bruce is.
Call him and tell him
that I am looking for someone.
- I have no idea where he is.
- That was me asking nicely.
Okay,
if Bruce wanted to come home...
He would, he would for me.
Okay.
Someone moved that.
How the hell would you know?
It was my Aunt Martha's.
She was wearing it the night
that she and my Uncle Thomas
were killed,
but he always kept it here.
Look.
You... You don't want to do that.
I mean, it looks really old.
Probably not even up to code,
if it even works.
You are seriously not supposed
to know what's down there.
So I have this thing with rules...
Bruce Wayne is Batman.
Yeah, I'm dead.
The Bruce I knew
had a million secrets
and now I know why
they were kept from me.
Let's take a picture, Beth. Make
sure our necklaces are in it.
There. Ready? Cheese!
What is this guy doing?
Beth, are you okay?
We're gonna go over!
Batman's here. He's gonna save us!
He spent years trying to figure out
what went wrong that day.
He knew the car was gonna go over,
so he shot two hooks,
each with a safe load of one ton.
The weight, the angle,
he was so sure he secured the car.
Go, Kate! Hurry! Get out!
Where are you going, Batman? Wait!
Wake up now! Mom, please!
Beth, you need to grab my hand now!
Kate!
Grab my hand!
No!
Beth! No!
Mom! Beth!
The steel in the trunk
still ripped away.
It was crappy engineering.
It was the one calculation
he didn't make.
I grew up thinking
that Batman cared more
about getting the bad guy than...
The lives of innocent people.
No, he cared.
He saved 34 kids that day.
He thought he saved your mom
and sister too.
I mean, his only living family,
and he got it wrong.
Haunted the hell out of him.
Yeah, don't push that.
No. Okay.
Not about to get myself fired
twice by Batman, so...
Find your own way.
- What?
- That's why Bruce became Batman,
to play by his own rules.
It made him terrifying
to his enemies.
Yeah, and his friends
and his co-workers.
- We really need to go.
- People aren't afraid anymore.
An army may not scare them...
but that will.
I need you to fix his suit.
The suit is literal perfection.
It will be...
When it fits a woman.
- Mary.
- We found one of Alice's guys.
I think I know
where they took Sophie.
Come on this way.
I don't like that building.
- Who's covering it?
- That'd be Dodgson, sir.
Dodgson.
I love it.
Have fun.
You, too.
Traitor! Don't!
Don't!
Commander.
Dare I say Gotham is looking
a little like the good, old days.
Sorry, I had my doubts.
City trusts us for a reason, Mayor.
Enjoy the movie, excuse me. Kane.
I haven't missed the show, have I?
Now, you tell me where you are,
and then I'll dump you
at Arkham myself.
We're all mad here, Commander.
I'm mad, you're mad.
Sanity is so pedestrian.
I want to be memorable,
the kind of girl who never
leaves your thoughts,
so I took it upon myself
to fill a Crows' truck
with forget-me-nots.
How do you like the Queen,
said the cat?
These are families. Kids.
Then keep your mouth shut
and everyone will stay alive
to see how this boring movie ends.
Try anything, and boom.
Look up.
You'd never forget about Sophie,
would you, Commander?
Your favorite little birdie
up in the sky,
but, oh dear, oh my,
can your little birdie fly?
For if she moves an inch, she'll die.
Pick one, Commander.
Sophie or Gotham.
Why are you doing this?
Why is a raven like a writing desk?
Who's there?
I thought you were dead.
Simple math, barrel weighs 500lb.
Birdie weighs a quarter of that.
Once barrel weighs
less than birdie...
No.
You're...
Not him.
Mommy, look.
It's Batman!
Good morning, Gotham.
Your girl Vesper Fairchild here.
So was I dreaming,
or is Batman really back?
If so, things are looking up
for this city.
If not, I just revealed
way too much about my dreams.
Talk to me, Gotham.
Are you as excited
about Mr. Tall, Dark
and Unavailable as I am?
It was so cool, and then Batman
flew into the sky
and was swinging from buildings.
See? I told you he'd be back.
Dodgson and Alice
are Crows' priority number one.
- What about the Bat, sir?
- Oh, come on.
Seen these wannabes before.
He gets the city all hot
and bothered,
and then thanks
to a total lack of skill,
he usually dies
in some spectacular fashion.
He?
Welcome back, Agent Moore.
You say something?
- Not important, sir.
- All right.
Let's find these two.
Wouldn't drink that if I were you.
It's toxic.
Christmas gift from Gotham police.
Good to know.
Hi, by the way.
Hi.
I heard you came back for me.
Thanks.
There she is,
I thought we talked about
never letting you out
of my sight again.
I'm fine. Seriously, I'm good.
Tyler, this is Kate.
Kate, Tyler works
for Crows International.
Sorry to barge in,
but got in late last night,
and now I am that annoyingly
overprotective husband.
You're married.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
Nice to meet you, Tyler.
I should probably go.
See you, Sophie.
Figured you'd left town.
I want you to tell me
that I was right.
You were never going
to make me a Crow.
You're right.
I never wanted you to be a Crow.
The Military was my dream for you.
I'd call in a favor,
get you a desk job, a staff,
and the occasional papercut
would be the only bloodshed
you'd ever see.
- That wasn't my dream.
- No.
No, you wanted to be in the action.
That's why I didn't want you
to be a Crow
because I'm selfish
and overly protective...
And I'm terrified,
and because
you're all I have left, Kate.
And I don't want to lose you, too.
Look, this is all my way
of saying that if...
If you want to be part of the team...
You're in.
My dad was running from his pain,
but I was running, too,
toward everything
that didn't want me,
a military academy,
a private army, my own father.
I spent 15 years searching
for a place I fit,
and I think I've finally found it.
Some see fear, others hope.
I see the freedom to be myself,
to play by my own rules.
I believe you're going
to come home one day, Bruce,
and before you kill me
for borrowing a few of your things,
I want you to read my story
because it's only just begun.
Miss you. Your cousin, Kate.
You know, for a minute there,
really felt like he was home.
Hey, look, for what it's worth,
Bruce never stopped looking
for your sister's body.
It is worth more than you think.
Guy had the best tech on the planet.
Why didn't he find her?
Make sure our necklaces are in it.
Beth.
I'll win you over, my dear sister.
The two of us will rule Gotham...
Together.