Previously on "Batwoman"...
How about we don't get expelled
a week before graduation?
I need this school,
OK? I want to be here.
But they don't want you.
Maybe it's best if you just
kept your distance from now on.
I know you love me. Tell me that
I'm wrong, and I'll walk away
and let you make the
biggest mistake of your life.
You're wrong, Kate.
- Is this you?
- Wasn't me.
So what is she doing with herself?
So are you on this assignment
to keep tabs on me or on Kate?
- Dad?
- Catherine Hamilton's investigators found bones,
skull fragments of a little girl.
It's Beth.
Hi, Daddy.
Put down the knife.
You gave up on me!
Beth, drop the damn knife!
Agh!
- Dad.
- Kate, it's her. It's Beth.
I have a gift for you, too.
Now that we are together again,
I can help you become
anyone you want to be.
Are we mad?
I'm afraid so.
Ha ha ha!
Absolutely not.
Listen. The victim had
the courage to come forward
and face her attackers.
Well, I'm confident a jury
will make the right decision.
The question is are you?
Oh, my God.
No, no, no!
Oh, God!
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Beth was being held by a
madman with a medical license.
We don't have much to go on.
The deed to the house belonged
to Dr. August Cartwright.
I have teams trying to pick up a trace,
but it's like he just disappeared.
Apparently he's a better
magician than he was a doctor.
Beth was held in a cell by
a guy making human skin masks
while I was at home playing club soccer.
We need to find him.
- We will.
- We didn't find her.
How many times can I say I'm
sorry for not listening to you?
I don't know.
How many times will it
take to get Beth back?
Sir, you're gonna want to see this.
Gotham is reeling over the death
of prosecutor Angus Stanton,
who was murdered horrifically tonight.
Stanton was seen by
many as a hero to Gotham,
one who brought justice to the victims
of some of the city's
most notorious criminals
such as Jack Napier,
otherwise known as The Joker.
Channel 9 has the
security camera footage.
Conviction rate, Stanton was known...
What's he wearing?
It's an old-fashioned
executioner's hood.
- Ax is a nice touch.
- This is Dana DeWitt reporting live from Old Gotham.
Anybody want to tell
me why every news outlet
in Gotham had this
and we didn't even get
so much as a heads-up from the GCPD?
Technically, it's
outside district lines.
And I believe it's because
they called someone else.
I am not about to stand
around and let Gotham cry out
to be saved by someone
who hides behind a mask.
The Bat is nothing more
than a symbol of false hope.
I want this so-called
Executioner cuffed
and stuffed in a cell in Blackgate.
If this city starts to think it can rely
on a vigilante for justice,
we might as well hand
it over to the crazies.
Sir... I know it's all hands
on deck with the Stanton case,
but I was hoping to get your permission
for another special assignment.
Who is it this time?
Batwoman.
Don't you want to know
who's behind the mask?
Heh heh heh!
Hmm.
Head back, sweetie.
Mm-hmm.
One... final... touch.
There.
Ahh. Dazzle me.
Oh. A perfect match for Dean Deveraux.
Wouldn't you agree, Mr. Deveraux?
Please don't hurt me.
I don't understand why
we don't just kill him.
Because my sister is
watching me like a hawk.
Still trying to bring the old Beth back.
You're not thinking of giving her
the old Beth back, are you?
Of course not.
Really? Because the old Alice I remember
wouldn't give a second thought
about opening his throat
with a butterfly knife.
She's changed you.
Not at all.
You're the one who's changed.
You used to trust me.
What about you, Dean?
Do you trust me?
I think you'd make an excellent partner.
I seem to be in need of a replacement.
Stop. Stop.
I'll do whatever you want.
Good.
Because I need you to steal
Catherine's shiny, new toy,
the one that she's too stingy to share.
- You see the Bat-signal?
- That is why I'm here.
You know what this means, right?
First time the city's called Batwoman
for backup means I can't screw it up.
It means you're in.
GCPD's got you on their speed dial now.
Commissioner Forbes trusts you.
Commissioner? My dad
still sees me as his enemy.
Stopping this guy has to
convince him otherwise.
That's not the only
reason worth stopping him.
Stanton was the prosecutor
who put away the guy
that killed my dad.
It was an armed robbery, right?
Night of my high school graduation.
We were celebrating me getting into MIT,
ran out of ice.
My dad went out to go get some.
Next thing I know, there
are two cops at the door.
Wanted me to come
down and I.D. the body.
We were waiting on him to cut the cake.
Lucius Fox did a lot
of good for this city.
Yeah. So did Stanton.
Never stopped until he put the guy
who shot my dad behind bars.
Any suspects?
Well, if you exclude the
law-abiding citizens of Gotham,
that leaves the other half.
There has to be some
way to narrow that down.
Start with the violent offenders.
Cross reference with recent parolees,
work release, and escapees
with whatever biometrics we can get
from the security footage.
All right. Huh. This is interesting.
Chris Medlock, otherwise
known as Chris The Fist,
ex-boxer, ex-con.
What was The Fist in for?
Uh, shot and killed a bartender.
He confessed, later
claimed it was coerced.
But they found the gun in his car.
Pleaded down to second-degree murder,
got 30 in Blackgate.
He was lucky to avoid the death penalty.
Yeah. The Fist did not see it that way.
Check out his sentencing.
I'll get you, you son of a bitch!
This ain't over!
I got a whole bunch
of time to figure out
how I'm gonna kill your ass!
Thanks to overcrowding, he was paroled
just a few months ago.
Can't wait to meet him.
Guy have an address?
We may not need one.
Uh, check out what just
came in over GCPD dispatch.
Someone claiming to be The Executioner
barricaded himself inside a building
at the 200 block of Rucka Avenue.
Claims to have several hostages.
That's in West Harlow.
- Put it on the screen.
- OK.
All right. Let's get on this.
I don't care if it's
outside our district.
Let's show Gotham we can keep them safe.
Move!
- Talking.
- Says he'll only speak to one guy,
a Detective Donnelly.
- Who?
- Detective Donnelly,
time is running out on
your hostages. Get in here,
- or I start shooting these people.
- Listen. You don't have to go in there.
- Let me get a negotiator down here.
- Nah. Me and The Fist go way back.
Detective.
Like the new look.
Red suits you.
Goes with everything.
Time's up, Donnelly.
No. Donnelly, stay back!
No. Wait! Stop!
I'm hit.
You're bleeding.
- I'll get you help.
- Thanks... Kate.
Oh, my God! Sophie!
I need to know if you can fix her.
What was she shot with?
- A bullet.
- I know it's a bullet.
I mean, hollow point,
blackout, wadcutter?
Does it matter?
Why did you bring her here?
She can afford a real hospital.
You were closer, and, uh,
I need you to keep her until I get back.
Crows don't know she's missing.
- No, you can't...
- Do not let her leave.
Man of the hour.
Congratulations.
You have succeeded where
so many have failed.
The coil accelerator, it works at last.
I just have to know
how were you able to overcome
the ferromagnetic projectile saturation?
Ha ha! You almost had
me there, Ms. Hamilton.
Trick question. That's
proprietary information.
Hard to imagine...
Something so delicate
harnessing enough power
to penetrate the Batsuit.
Well done, Dean.
- She called you Kate?
- She knows who I am.
I mean it. That's just great, fantastic.
So naturally, you
decided to drop her off
at your sister's unlicensed clinic.
Mary will take care of her.
She'll also keep her from leaving,
and as long as she can't
leave, she can't talk.
But she's a Crow, your
father's second in command.
You really think you can
convince her not to tell him?
I'll deal with that after we've
dealt with The Executioner.
We need to figure out his next target.
Guy's not making it easy.
He keeps changing his M.O.
50,000 volts of electricity,
then a bunch of rifles.
Doesn't make any sense.
Unless it's a pattern.
The Fist dresses up as an executioner,
kills Stanton with electricity
like an electric chair.
Then he gets Donnelly to walk
in on that shooting gallery.
Like a firing squad.
He's using methods of capital
punishment to kill his victims.
On it.
Gotham's used 3 ways to
kill people on death row...
electric chair, firing squad...
which made a brief comeback
under Mayor Cobblepot...
and the gas chamber.
So his next victim will be with gas.
Guy's got a flair for detail,
so I bet you a batarang he'll
use hydrogen cyanide pellets
just like they did in
the gas chamber, and...
And there's only one warehouse
in Gotham that stores them.
Who's there?
Someone who needs information.
Holy crap! You're her!
Yo. I got to get this.
- Damn, girl!
- Not happening.
Anything out of the
ordinary around here lately?
- What, besides this?
- Answer the question.
Naw. That means someone
had to bet by me,
and that ain't gonna happen.
It's been quiet,
but, uh, you know,
it doesn't have to be.
Yo. Let me buy you a drink,
and you can tell me all
about the superhero thing.
I've been thinking about
getting into the game myself.
What do you say?
I get off at 11:00, and, uh,
if you play your cards right,
you won't be too far behind.
OK. So this place hasn't seen any action
and apparently neither has its guard.
Yeah. I think I might know why.
Got a visual on Chris The Fist,
alleyway on Sprang.
Unh! Ooh!
Get off me! I didn't do nothing.
Oh, got it. So you're just
out for a late-night jog, huh?
Crows got The Fist.
Well, I guess a lot of people
will be sleeping easier tonight.
I know you wanted to catch him,
but you can convince the Crows
you're not the enemy tomorrow.
Tomorrow may be too late.
I need to check on Sophie.
Unh!
Kate, you copy?
_
Hey, K... Kate!
Kate, do you copy? What just happened?
The Crows got the wrong guy,
and The Executioner
got what he came for.
All this Bat tech, and you
came up with frozen water?
Hmm. I checked every camera angle
in the warehouse security system, but,
the license plate's got
mud or something on it.
Can't really get a good view of it.
Don't suppose you were
able to make it out.
Didn't quite catch it
when it plowed into me.
Oh. Yeah. Oh, yeah. That's great!
My ribs would argue otherwise.
No. I'm serious, OK?
The suit's carbon fiber ribbing
is designed to absorb any impact,
so any deformation in the fibers is
recorded in the suit's data.
So it was originally
designed to track damage
caused by bullets, you
know, blunt-force trauma,
that kind of thing.
There's no reason it wouldn't pick up
- an impression from a car bumper.
- Or a license plate.
Hmm. OK. Uh, it's a
partial, but it'll work.
OK. The truck is registered
to a... Bertrand Eldon,
and... he was at Blackgate for 20 years.
What was he in for?
He worked there. He
was their executioner.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Uh-uh!
I just did some of the
best work of my life
crocheting you back together.
What?! Where am I?
Mary, what the hell is going on?
Batwoman brought you in.
- You were shot.
- Unh. Batwoman?
I feel like we glossed over the part
where I saved your life.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
You work here?
It's mine.
My followers think I'm
turning up at the club,
ordering bottle service.
Truth is I'm usually here,
trying to help serve the people
that Gotham hospitals turn away.
- Mary.
- Hmm.
- If your dad ever found out about this place...
- He won't. He can't.
Yeah. I didn't do that.
Well, you better undo it.
Batwoman would kill me.
Frankly, she's scarier than you.
Mary, why am I cuffed to this bed?
Uh, she said not to let you leave.
Do you know who she is?
No. Honestly, I don't want to know.
I don't need that
kind of responsibility.
Well, I do know who she is,
and that's why she won't let me leave.
I'm in.
No one's home.
Why would a guy working
at Blackgate target
a cop and a prosecutor?
They're on the same side.
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm looking for that answer right now.
Looks like he was a model employee.
Stay frosty. This guy is methodical,
technically proficient,
always a few steps ahead.
He could have anything
waiting for you in there.
Already has just sitting
on the coffee table.
- What?
- The hydrogen cyanide pellets.
I found them.
- On the coffee table?
- Yes.
It... it's probably a trap.
I'm aware, but I don't see
any trip sensors or wires
or pressure plates.
What's the Bat protocol with this?
- Uh...
- Well, I can't just stand here
staring at this thing, waiting
for The Executioner to come back.
- Come on.
- Yeah. OK. Hang on.
Can you play some hold
music while I wait?
No. OK. I'm just gonna grab it.
No, no, no, no. Don't do that.
- Kate, don't!
- Too late.
- And?
- And I'm still talking to you.
It's light.
Is it empty?
Hmm.
Not quite.
So if you found this, then...
you found me, and, um...
And I did it.
I am guilty as sin,
but I'm not the only one.
For 20 years, I threw the switch
on the worst people
Gotham ever spat out.
I was glad to do it, too.
Doing the public a service,
and it never bothered me
when they said they were innocent.
Great. Sadistic and long-winded.
I mean, what else were
they gonna say, right?
See, then all their stories,
they started to sound the same.
The same names kept coming up,
same evidence,
and everybody who sat in my chair
started to look the same...
black, brown, poor.
In 20 years, I never
juiced a rich white guy,
so I started digging in their files.
You know what I found?
The same 3 corrupt law
enforcement officials
pulling the strings in every case.
Coerced confessions
and murder weapons suddenly
showing up out of nowhere.
I mean, obviously planted.
Didn't Chris The Fist say
that his confession was coerced
and the murder weapon just
suddenly turned up in his car?
The people that I
executed were innocent,
which meant that...
that I was the guilty one,
that... that cabal, they
turned me into a murderer,
which... they made me
punish the innocent.
So who's the third member of this cabal?
Wait. You're not actually buying this?
OK. Believe me. I know racial
profiling is a thing in Gotham,
but this guy is obviously crazy,
almost killed Sophie,
nearly made you roadkill.
- Doesn't make him wrong.
- He's an admitted killer, Kate.
I knew Stanton, OK?
He spent hours with my
family day after day,
and he never, ever stopped working
until he found justice.
If Stanton is accused of being dirty,
my dad's killer could use
that go get a new trial.
But if Chris The Fist or anyone else
can do go down for something
that they didn't do,
how is that justice?
A little present from the Crows.
Next time, call us first.
We may not have a Klieg light,
but we do have a phone number.
Aah!
Unh! Ohh!
Everybody fan out!
Move, move!
Your turn.
Uh, it... it's OK.
You can just win.
I said... your turn.
King me.
What?!
It's me.
How did you get this number?
Let's call it twintuition.
Why did you send Mouse
into Hamilton Dynamics
to get a weapon that can kill Batwoman?
- Where is he?
- He's fine,
or he will be as long
as you tell me the truth.
Heh. Dear sister, if
I wanted to kill you,
I wouldn't have to wait for
you to be wearing the suit.
That's so sweet of you.
Your concern for me is
so touching, dear sister.
So Kate is Batwoman.
I do not like being toyed with!
And I don't like traitors.
What's wrong with you?
First, she abandons you, then
she tries to lock you away,
and still, you try to protect her.
Because she's still my sister.
Real family doesn't abandon their own.
Who snuck food to you in
the middle of the night?
Who taught you rummy
and let you sleep with Mr. Pandy
and promised to protect
you no matter what?
Me! I did, Alice, because I was there,
and she wasn't!
After everything we've been through,
you keep secrets from me?
Try keeping that a secret.
OK. So who had Batwoman
rescues a psychopath
on their bingo card?
Because I've got some
big, fat, empty spaces
for Batwoman takes down Alice
and Batwoman gets a cat out of a tree.
Talk to me, Gotham. Anyone else feeling
a little "Bat-trayed"?
The people that I
executed were innocent,
which meant that...
that I was the guilty one.
That cabal by Judge Calverick
condemned innocent people to die.
I heard you got a visit from Batwoman.
More like an ambush.
Now one nut job wants me to listen
to another nut job.
Claims Judge Calverick, one of Gotham's
most upstanding justices, is a fraud.
So you're not even gonna
look into this judge.
Why? Because some social justice warrior
thinks he knows more
about the rule of law
than the cops and the
lawyers who protect this city?
Nah. We got the right guy.
Batwoman interfered.
Batwoman wouldn't have stepped
in if she didn't have a reason.
Before you give a shred of credibility
to some criminal in a Bat costume,
let me remind you that Batman
destroyed our family's lives.
He is not the one that drove
Mom's car off that bridge.
Well, he may as well have been.
Batman brought out all
the crazies in Gotham.
If it weren't for him, there
wouldn't have been a Joker!
Your mom would be alive,
and Beth wouldn't be Alice.
Beth is Alice because we
stopped looking for her.
I'm not arguing about this right now.
That would be a lot easier, wouldn't it,
just act like we did nothing wrong.
We looked... Everywhere for Beth.
I looked everywhere. I held
onto hope for the both of us
despite the lack of evidence,
despite the police giving up,
despite the fact that
everyone thought she was dead.
I hoped when it was hard,
and you... Just gave up
and put your energy into blaming Batman
because it was easy.
That's why Beth is Alice.
You wouldn't listen then,
and you won't listen now,
and an innocent man is
gonna pay the price for it.
Look who lucked out by getting
the last grape Popsicle!
Hmm. Looks like you're healing nicely,
but I guess healing can't get in the way
of you spilling the tea on Batwoman.
Believe it or not, I'm
trying to protect her.
By having my dad shut
down her entire operation?
She's gonna get herself killed.
Batwoman can take care of herself
just like she took care
of you twice by my count,
and now you're just gonna betray her?
Uh... I mean, what?
Is that, like, your thing?
What's that supposed to mean?
I mean, that's what you did to Kate,
and then she had to put an entire ocean
between you and her,
and... now you walk around,
pretend like she meant nothing to you.
You don't even know what happened.
No, but I saw what it did to her.
Look. You're right. It's not my drama,
so do what you want.
In the meantime,
ibuprofen every 4-6 hours
and change the bandage once a day.
Don't tell my dad about this clinic...
And maybe think about whether or not
you want to add Batwoman to
the list of people you hurt.
Working late, Your Honor?
H... how did you?
Looks like you're burning
more than the midnight oil.
Is that the evidence?
Donnelly got the confessions,
Stanton convinced the jury,
you just banged your gavel?
I can pay you.
You have to protect me from him.
You'll get round-the-clock
protection at Blackgate
free of charge.
Go!
Unh!
You protect him, a man who sent
so many innocents to their deaths?
The law will take care of it.
Yeah? I used to believe that, too,
until the law turned me into a murderer.
The law's not perfect,
I'll give you that.
Doesn't mean you get
to rewrite it in blood.
You trust the law so much,
why are you wearing that suit?
I'm gonna need backup.
What do you want me to say?
He makes a good point.
No. For the judge.
Get the judge into
protective custody now.
Right. On it.
Sweep the rest of the building.
Glad you decided to
go after the right guy.
I don't see how you and
him are that different.
Taking the law into your own hands,
appointing yourself judge and jury.
Pretty sure you just
did the exact same thing.
I saved your life.
You telling me I made a mistake?
I don't know. Ask The Fist.
I admit I got it wrong,
but you know the difference
between me and you?
When I make a mistake,
everybody knows my name.
I am accountable to
the people of Gotham.
You... you hide behind your anonymity.
Who are you accountable to?
Guess we'll find out.
Heart rate monitor linked
to a dead man's switch.
Looks like we're about to join him.
This is Kane. Anybody read me?
Whoa! Suit showing
oxygen levels dropping.
No kidding. Executioner turned this room
into a gas chamber.
Can your men get us out of here?
He triggered the lock-down procedure.
Every way in and out
of here is sealed off.
Steel-reinforced doors.
By the time my guys get through them...
Air's getting thin in here. I
need a solution. You went to MIT.
I got in. I didn't actually go.
OK. Uh... OK, OK.
OK. Hydrogen cyanide,
emphasis on hydrogen.
It's flammable. Think the Hindenburg.
- Not a comforting thought.
- The point is you can ignite it.
The flames will burn off the cyanide.
- OK. Copy.
- Only problem is
hydrogen will only
burn at 6% saturation.
For those of us who didn't get into MIT.
You got let the gas fill the room first.
We're not gonna last that long.
Well, you got to try, Kate.
You're only at 3%.
You got hang in there.
You need to stay low to the ground.
- Get away from me.
- Come on.
That symbol took everything from me.
It's not gonna be the last thing I see.
Stay with me. Stay awake.
Come on, Commander. Talk to me.
Tell me all the reasons you hate Batman.
That symbol let my family die.
4%.
Hey. If you're gonna hate
the symbol, hate the symbol.
Let it fuel you into staying alive.
5%.
I have to blame that symbol.
If I don't...
If you don't, what? Tell me.
I have to blame myself.
6%. Do it!
Kate, come on. Talk to me.
Commander, Commander, come on!
We're OK.
Never let it be said
that Gotham's gadfly
does not give credit
where credit is due.
Batwoman got this one right,
and the rest of us whiffed.
Guess Jacob Kane won't be the only one
eating a little Crow.
Boxer Chris "The Fist"
Medlock was not only cleared
in The Executioner
murders but also exonerated
of his past murder conviction.
Talk about a one-two punch.
Not so good news for
the man who convicted him
Judge Raymond Calverick.
The D.A. has vowed to
reopen all cases tainted
by this extralegal cabal,
including deceased
Detective Stu Donnelly
and prosecutor Angus Stanton.
You're right behind me, aren't you?
Where is she?
I... you know, she just left.
- Uh, how can I put this?
- You let her escape?
I know you said to hold onto her,
but my stepdad is her boss,
and I'm running a little
short on family right now,
not that you asked
about my personal life,
but it's a mess.
The last thing I need
is him shutting down
the one good thing I have going on.
Thank you for saving her life.
Oh. Yeah. It's, like, my thing.
Hey. FYI, she knows who you are.
Hey. Chill. She didn't tell me,
but I got the distinct impression
that she's gonna tell my stepdad,
so good luck with that.
Well, Bruce, now I know how much
it must have hurt hearing
your uncle blame you
for what happened on the bridge,
but he had to blame someone.
Seeing him fight so
hard to avoid the truth
that was right in front of him
made me realize I was
doing the same thing.
I've been blaming my dad
for not saving Beth that day,
but it wasn't his hand on that
door only inches away from her.
He wasn't the one who crossed that house
off the list of places
where Beth could be.
I don't know how,
but we are gonna get Beth back,
and this time, I swear to you
I won't ever give up.
I don't know if forgiving my father
will help me forgive
myself, but I have to try.
I thought I might find you here.
How could you ever think I was
trying to replace you, little Mouse.
Why are you so
determined to protect her?
Because I'm saving her
a seat at our tea party!
It was supposed to be a table for two.
Yes, the two of us,
two halves of one whole
just as Kate and I are two halves,
and I need your help to make us whole.
I can't do this without you.
I don't want to share you with her.
Mouse.
You won't have to share me
because we'll be sharing her.
And what if she doesn't want to play?
Well...
Then it's good we have that then, hmm?
Trade you Mr. Pandy for it.
You kept it?
To remind me of you.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Greg, move your head!