[LIQUID POURING]
_
SARA: Never thought we'd be
pouring one out for Oliver.
We're not gonna wait for Barry?
I don't think he's
ready to say good-bye.
So anybody want to...
Say some words for Oliver?
He sacrificed himself for me and Barry.
Shouldn't have done that.
His sacrifice saved
a billion more people.
Let's not call that a mistake.
Look. Oliver died the
way he lived, a hero.
[BANG]
Not to rush a tender moment,
but I think the multiverse
is ending soonish, so...
No. I can't, I can't. Barry's right.
It feels like giving up.
We managed to get billions
of people to safety.
There has to be a way we can undo this.
Oliver, my mom, Argo, Earth...
ugh... all those Earths,
all those people who vanished.
There has to be a way
we can get them back.
Or we focus on stopping
it from happening
to every other universe.
[WHOOSH]
Oh, hey. Welcome to the joy zone.
- Where's Dig?
- At home with JJ.
He still doesn't know about Oliver.
- Lyla, you...
- I know. I just...
I need to figure out
- how to tell him.
- Yeah.
RAY: You can't just
hijack the Waverider.
Our crew is still on there.
MONITOR: If there is any
chance at surviving the Crisis,
we need its technology.
Hoo. Yeah. I kind of promised our crew
they'd never have to
do another crossover.
We don't need your crew,
just Ray's lab,
and we have an entire multiverse
of Waveriders at our disposal.
Oh.
_
[CLATTER]
- LYLA: Is anyone here?
- COMPUTER: Welcome aboard.
My name is Leonard, an interactive,
artificial consciousness
programmed to operate this
vessel's critical systems.
I know who you are.
Always pleased to meet a fan,
but you're trespassing.
Any preference on how you'd like to die?
What he's saying is
flame or frost?
I thought the Legends
of Earth-74 all retired.
We did. Well, some. One died.
No one was using the ship, so I took it.
It's my ship.
- Why are you here?
- I like the quiet.
LEONARD: He's trying to be a writer.
- Shut up.
- Of romance novels.
Well, you can see how that's going.
It's going fine, you piece of...
You're basically living out of your car.
Listen, snowflake. I'm just...
Boys. Come with me, Mick Rory,
and I promise you'll have
plenty of beer to drink
and stories to tell.
The multiverse needs saving,
and its heroes need a ship.
Hmm.
You had me at beer.
MONITOR: You have all lost a great hero.
The wrong hero.
I do not disagree.
You have suffered a horrible loss,
but you have every
reason not to lose hope,
7, in fact.
Across space and time...
[BABY JONATHAN CRYING]
Across space and time exist 7 heroes,
beings of the purest
will who can ultimately...
[CRYING CONTINUES]
- Sorry. You want to try?
- What?
MONITOR: Beings of the purest will
who can ultimately...
It's not working.
Nope.
[CRYING CONTINUES]
MONITOR: Beings of the purest will,
who can ultimately
defeat the Anti-Monitor...
LOIS: Go, go, go.
And help save the multiverse.
They are known as Paragons.
Paragons? And you're just
dropping this on us now?
I only recently learned
of their existence
by consulting "The Book of Destiny".
How? We destroyed it last year.
[VOICES WHISPERING]
After Oliver's early demise, I went back
into the time stream
and retrieved it intact.
It is now safely stored
in this ship's library.
BARRY: So it's what, plan "B"?
That's comforting.
Phhh. Anyone else wishing
they'd done that shot?
Uh, but wait. If the
book can rewrite destiny,
can it bring back Earth-38
or any of the other Earths?
MONITOR: Trying to
re-create an entire world
would surely drive one to madness.
What about my dad?
Could it bring him back?
I wish it could.
While Oliver Queen was
to die in this Crisis,
this is not how I saw events unfold,
but as the Anti-Monitor gets stronger,
I grow weaker.
We must find all 7 Paragons.
How about, like, a hint?
I have 4.
Kara Zor-El,
despite all you have endured,
you are the Paragon of Hope.
Well, you might want to
double-check your omnipotence
because I'm not feeling
that hopeful right now.
Sara Lance is the Paragon of Destiny.
Oh. Well, that makes sense.
Captain of time travel and all that.
I have only descriptions
for the other two paragons.
One is of a second Kryptonian,
who is said to have
suffered a greater loss
than most mortal men could endure.
Today, he stands as
the Paragon of Truth.
I'll find him.
I'll go with you.
And the fourth?
The Paragon of Courage
is known only as the Bat of the future.
Seriously, where do you get these names
and pseudonames anyway?
I enlisted the assistance
of Felicity Smoak,
who earned the wisdom of a second book.
That's a lot of books.
The Tome of the Guardians.
It revealed the names of
Ms. Zor-El and Ms. Lance,
as well as the other two.
Bummed out Kryptonian and future Bat,
which technically means...
Earth-99 exists in a future time
where Bruce Wayne has dedicated himself,
body and soul, to fighting crime.
I'm sorry. Go back.
Bruce Wayne is the Dark Knight?
If we could all keep that to
ourselves, that'd be great.
MONITOR: The path to find him
will lead you to the Paragon of Courage.
Okay. Who wants to meet Batman?
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
_
LEX: An entire universe
wiped from existence
distilled down to a computer graphic.
Got to say... missing that wow factor.
Lena killed you.
Yeah. Only for a little while. Tck.
MONITOR: Everyone has a part to play,
even Lex Luthor.
You did this?
You brought that...
poisonous snake back?
His destiny was unfulfilled.
Lex Luthor still has an
important role to play.
So you can revive him, but
you can't bring back Oliver?
I restored Luthor long
before the crisis caused
my power to wane.
KARA: And what about those
innocent lives on Earth-38?
Did they not have destinies to fulfill?
I'm sorry, but I can't trust a man
who thinks Lex Luthor is an ally.
All I got from that is
that if you die again
that dude can't bring you back.
And you are?
New... and unfriendly.
Lex Luthor... kind of a dick, huh?
[SIGHS]
When I think of all
those people on my Earth
that we wanted to save but couldn't,
it just feels unfair.
Look. A day ago, I didn't think
my life could get any worse.
My sister murdered my stepmom
and framed my dad for it.
That's dark, even for Gotham.
I'm fighting for a
chance to make it right,
and this fourth Paragon, my
cousin Bruce on another Earth,
finding him might help
me get that chance.
Only if you believe the Monitor.
What kind of talk is that
from the Paragon of Hope?
[UNZIPS POCKET]
Come with me.
Let's go save the universe.
[VOICES WHISPERING]
MAN: Stop him!
[GASPS]
- WOMAN: Stop him.
- MAN: Before he finds the book.
BOTH: Stop him before he finds the book.
Find the book.
Stop Lex Luthor.
You're not supposed to have that.
And man was never meant
to fly, but here we are.
Good-bye, Superman, all of you.
VOICES: Stop him!
MONITOR: Lex Luthor
has the Book of Destiny.
He's going to use it to kill Supermen.
If he kills the Paragon,
we're all doomed.
What have you done?
As I said,
everyone has a part to play.
I'm glad you're here.
Me, too.
From what you told me, the
Monitor was wrong about Oliver,
so I don't know, Barry.
Maybe he's wrong about you, too.
Maybe... you're not supposed to die.
Listen. Oliver told me
about how he brought
Sara and his sister back to life
using something called a Lazarus pit.
I don't know. That sounds
too good to be true.
Well, it... I mean, it is.
It turns out Thea destroyed
all the pits on this Earth,
but there are more
Earths to choose from.
I know that you want Oliver back
more than anything, but this is...
He can't be dead.
Not him.
Okay.
Funny enough, the Monitor
gave me a mission of my own.
To find our hopeless
Kryptonian Paragon. Heh.
Did you ever think
this would be our life?
I will take whatever
life with you I can get.
SARA: So I miss one group chat,
and now there's Paragons,
and I'm supposed to be one of them.
Yep, and Barry and I are
gonna use a Lazarus pit
to bring my dad back.
Mia, it's not that simple.
The Lazarus pit isn't
some magical mud bath
where you get your soul and a
cup of cucumber water at the end.
You lose your humanity.
Nyssa told me everything I need to know
about Lazarus pits,
and she told me everything
I need to know about you.
Why don't you share your opinion
when it's about your life?
Why don't you share your
opinion when it's about your dad?
_
[PORTAL OPENING]
So the Paragon of Courage is apparently
afraid of yardwork.
Better let me do the talking.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Wow. That's a really
impressive six-pack.
Sorry. Do I know you?
- Oh.
- No.
No, but I know you.
Well, a different... like,
a less this version of you.
I... I'm Kate Kane. I'm Bruce's cousin.
Yeah, no.
Earth-one villain?
Only friend actually.
Oh. Well, at least, he's cute.
Nope. Uh-uh. Let's not make
that weird. That's weird.
Hsss.
Ttt, ttt, ttt. Can I just...
- Please.
- Okay.
Ahem.
[GUN COCKS]
You need to leave...
Now.
MAN: Don't be so rude, Luke.
[SERVOS WHIRRING]
You'll have to forgive him.
[SLOW FOOTSTEPS]
We're not used to having guests.
Kate.
Bruce?
KATE: Where is Luke taking Kara?
BRUCE: Library.
Just while we get to
know each other again.
Well, the Bruce I knew wore
a different kind of suit.
Lifetime of injuries,
but you've aged well
for a dead girl.
- I died?
- 5 years ago.
Huh.
Never been a ghost before.
Hmm. Plenty of ghosts in this place,
but you're not one of them.
Clayface is a puddle of mud,
and last I checked, Jane
Doe was locked in Arkham,
so who the hell are you?
Can you, uh... can
you sit in that thing?
Because you're gonna need to for this.
_
LOIS: Hang on.
- What is it?
- Iris.
We have a new problem.
It turns out Lex Luthor is alive.
- What?!
- According to Iris,
Lex is jumping from
universe to universe,
killing off Supermen.
If one of them's the
Kryptonian Paragon...
It's game over.
We need to find this Earth's Superman
before Lex jumps here and offs him.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I think it's a little late for that.
Disappeared into thin air.
Lex killed him and breached out.
He won't stop until we're all dead.
You sure you want to do this?
A Lazarus pit's nasty business.
- MIA: We're sure.
- BARRY: We don't have a lot of time,
so could you please take
your smoke break later,
maybe just do the spell?
Simmer down, speedy. This is the spell.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
It's all in the wrist.
What is it, some kind of star map?
Parallel Earths spread out
by vibrational frequency.
We are well and truly bolloxed.
So many Earths already gone,
and more vanishing as we speak.
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
I give you the needle
in the celestial haystack,
an Earth with a functioning Lazarus pit.
Okay. Well, now what?
Ah. Perhaps a thank you
and a little well-earned awe
for a magical job well done, eh?
How about I thank you
when you bring my dad back?
All right. Come on. Let's go.
We can't screw this up, okay?
When we bring Oliver back,
I need you to promise me
you can bring back his soul.
Yeah. One thing at a time, right, love?
I need to hear you say it.
- I'll do it.
- Thank you.
To the best of my abilities.
[SIGHS]
_
[THUD]
IRIS: Is that him?
It's either him or the buff guy
on the paper towel rolls.
I can do that with one bare hand.
Hello.
LOIS AND IRIS: Hi.
You are Clark Kent, right?
Can I help you?
IRIS: Uh, yeah, hopefully. Heh heh.
Um, so, uh, this universe
and an infinite number of others
is in the process of
blinking out of existence,
and there are 7 people
in all of space and time
who can supposedly...
Lex Luthor is gonna try to kill you.
- Lois.
- He is.
- Lex?
- Yeah.
I didn't know the President was in town.
Look. I've faced a lot
of these type of things...
LEX: Hello, old friend.
Who are you?
Don't you know me, Clark?
I'm Lex Luthor.
Hmm.
You're not Lex.
Maybe not the Lex you know.
The multiverse has a
way of aligning fates.
What'd you do with those people?
Sent them back to their
flying tin can in the sky.
Let's hope they learn
from this teachable moment.
Now I'm here for you, not them.
Whoever you are, I'm just a guy
working on his farm.
You will always be my greatest enemy
on any Earth.
It's written in the stars
and in this book,
or I wouldn't know that on this Earth
Clark Kent... heh heh... is Superman.
Where I come from, that
would be ridiculous.
He can't see past his glasses.
Hmm.
So what do you want?
Why, to kill you of course
and every version of
you across the multiverse
so that if the, uh, super friends
somehow find a way to save existence
there won't be a single Superman
to stand in my way.
That's Kryptonite.
Which has no effect on me
ever since I gave up my powers.
You gave up your powers?
Can't say I've missed these chats.
You were basically a God.
You could fly.
You could see through walls.
You had superstrength.
[CRUNCH]
You're kidding me.
That is worth more than any superpower.
LOIS LANE: Hey, Clark.
The girls want to show
you what they've made.
I think it's time for you to...
Ah. Still stronger.
You took all the fun out of it.
Enjoy your little slice of mediocrity
while you can, Clark.
You're all doomed anyway.
Hey.
Was somebody here, or were
you talking to the cows again?
That was Lex Luthor from another Earth.
Apparently, the multiverse is ending.
Ha ha! Smallville, you made a funny.
It's taken you about a decade,
but you're getting the hang of it.
- Hmm. What'd the girls make?
- A mess.
They can't wait for you to see it.
Oh. That sounds like a job for...
Us.
I thought you told them not to.
Ha ha ha!
Paragon of Courage?
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
You're a few years too late.
"Reign of terror"?
It's like a wise man once said,
"Battle not with monsters
lest you become a monster".
I've lost track of how
many people I've killed.
The Bruce I knew had a code.
You start with a code,
you hang onto it with every
self-righteous breath,
but then you take one life,
then another,
then another, then another.
You'll see.
My Kate...
My Kate put on the cape,
thought she'd succeed where I failed.
All she did was get herself killed.
Well, I'm not her.
And I'm not an old man
held together with wire and metal.
Fine. You're a broken,
pissed off, old hermit
waiting to die in this
11-bedroom, 7-bath coffin,
but apparently, you're needed.
I am giving you the
chance to be a hero again
and not just to Gotham.
The whole damn universe.
[JONATHAN CRYING]
Uh, Mick, if you could...
I just... i really need to concentrate
if I'm ever gonna finish
this Paragon detector
the Monitor asked for.
Sure.
"Once he awoke her desire,
he was hers to explore willingly".
- Is that your...
- "Caged Passion",
my romance novel.
LEONARD: Your only
novel, self-published.
Still counts.
Uh, Mick, your book doesn't sound
too kid-friendly.
It's very friendly. Kid loves it.
Look at him.
Anyway, "Chapter 19.
As he caressed the nape of her back,
he struck like a cobra".
Heh heh. You like that. So do I.
It's my best writing. Anyway...
_
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Now this is a newspaper.
Ray tracked Lex's last
breach to this Earth,
so he can't be far.
Well, let's find him... me...
Clark before Lex does.
- Ohh!
- Oh, excuse me. So sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- It was my fault.
- It was mine.
No. Heh heh.
I'm sorry. You seem so familiar.
Have we met before?
Ahem.
Uh, he looks just like Ray Palmer.
Who?
Hey. Nice glasses.
Oh. Thanks.
Um, do you have a second?
Sure. For a citizen
of Metropolis, always.
If you wouldn't mind
contacting my assistant.
It's about Lex Luthor.
How did you say you knew Kate?
I didn't.
We're still sort of...
Getting to know each other.
Hmm.
What are those?
Mementos...
From Batman's greatest victories.
You mean trophies.
Um...
Yeah. Those belonged to Superman,
his alter ego at least.
Bruce killed this Earth's Superman?
Who do you think put
him in that exoskeleton?
Yeah. Big mistake.
I appreciate your concern,
but this isn't my first
go-around with Luthor.
I can handle him.
CLARK: That's what you're not hearing.
He's changed the game.
IRIS: Yeah. The... the book
allows him to do anything.
He made us vanish right
in front of the last Clark.
What is this?
Perry White, Jimmy Olsen,
Lois Lane?
Why are all these names on your wall?
A reject from Gotham felt
that we didn't cover him enough,
so he played what he
called a practical joke
and gassed the building.
All these people died?
My friends,
my wife.
I lost everyone in one fell swoop.
Almost as if you've
been through more loss
than any mortal man could endure.
I think we just found our Paragon.
We need you to come back with us.
I know this sounds insane,
but... you might be the key
to saving the multiverse.
That's actually one of the least
insane things I've ever heard.
First, we stay and face Luthor.
And you won't do it alone.
LOIS: We won't let him kill you.
LEX: Oh, I've moved on from that.
Never thought I'd say this,
but I'm tired of killing Supermen.
So much more fun making Superman
kill Superman.
You don't belong here.
We're here because we need your help.
Help? I couldn't even
save my wife, my friends.
I don't care about your universe.
Yes, you do.
You're the Paragon of Truth.
There's only one truth.
I serve Lex Luthor.
Kal, stop.
Unh!
Oh. What did Lex do?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You have to get Luthor
out of your head, Kal.
The multiverse needs you!
And what about what I need?
[BOOM]
Come on, honey. You got this.
Kal... no.
Gah!
Let me show you how it feels
to lose the ones you love.
Oh, my God.
Get away from the window!
This should be fun.
Agh!
Huh!
You can read about it later.
Help me with the book.
[GRUNTING]
Picture the Clark that we met.
Focus on what the universe
knows he's meant to be.
There's only room in
this world for one of us.
IRIS: I'm pretty sure it's not working.
It's like... it's like Lex turned
all of his love into hate.
Love.
Clark, this isn't you,
not the real Clark, the one that
Perry White respected and
Jimmy Olsen looked up to
and Lois loved.
You know nothing about me or them!
We know more than you think.
They would want your memories of them
to lift you up, not
drive you to darkness.
That's the truth, Clark,
and the truth means everything to you.
Remember who you are.
[GROANS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You okay?
Actually, this is the second time
I've gone nuts and fought myself.
I can see why you married her.
_
CONSTANTINE: Yep. This is the place.
Yep. That's clean enough.
Eww.
We'll clear this out.
All right. We'll go get Oliver.
Are you sure that you want to do this?
More than anything.
Yeah. Your father wouldn't
take no for an answer either.
When I think of all the
stupid stuff we got into
when we were your age,
it's amazing we didn't
get arrested more.
Arrested more?
But you're way smarter than him.
You get that from my your mom.
JONAH HEX: Seems you little
ladies have tied your horse
to the wrong saloon.
This mine is off limits.
MIA: I don't care who owns it.
We need to use this pit.
Well, I'm a-sure we can
come to an arrangement.
The mine is ours.
The hell it is.
Guess you were gonna get
this scar eventually, hex.
Ease up, cowgirl.
The mine's yours. The mine's yours.
Oh. Thanks.
So did you change your mind
about us using the pit then?
I miss Ollie, too.
[PORTAL OPENS]
Did we miss something?
Just put him in the water.
[WATER BUBBLING]
See for yourself.
I can barely walk, let
alone wear that again.
KATE: Do you understand how
many people, how many worlds
are going to die?
Well, if they're
anything like this world,
maybe that's for the best.
How can you even say that?
There was no hope for this world.
KARA: That's because
you killed Superman.
This guy's not a Paragon of anything.
I was right. We can't trust the Monitor.
What did you do?
Clearly what you couldn't.
How was he a treat?
Strange visitor from another planet
comes to Earth with powers and abilities
far beyond those of mortal men?
Clark.
Clark always said yes to anyone
with a badge or a flag.
He gave them too much power.
My parents taught me a
very different lesson...
life only makes sense
if you force it to.
[KARA GROANING]
A little souvenir from the old hometown.
It's not working.
Just give it some time.
Guys, Mia's right. This isn't...
[GROWLING]
- You good?
- Thanks, mate.
Dad.
[GROWLS]
What? You tranqed him?
I tranqed his body.
We have to get his soul back.
That isn't Oliver yet.
The Kate I knew didn't trust anyone,
let alone a Kryptonian.
KATE: I don't know what
happened to you, Bruce,
but it ends now.
Yes. Let it end.
Let it all end.
This world's not worth
saving in any universe.
If you really think that,
you're gonna have to
kill one more person.
Me.
Don't be a fool.
Don't! It'll kill you.
Kate... listen to me.
There is no hope.
Oh. So, uh, do you have
a gluten sensitivity too?
No. Not that I know of.
LEX: Congratulations. You're a ringer
for a filthy Kryptonian.
Your mom must be so proud.
[BABY COOING]
MICK: Kid was a piece of cake.
Here.
There's someone I want you to meet.
Hi there, handsome guy.
Wow. He looks just like my son Jason.
MONITOR: Well done. You have succeeded
in finding the Paragon of Truth.
Lex Luthor played his role.
He led you to him.
KARA: Yeah? How many
more people did he hurt
to do that?
You think you're a good
guy, but you're not.
I think he's kind of neat.
Ok. Well, we still only have 3.
Bruce Wayne wasn't the
Paragon of anything, so...
Whoa, Ray. You are looking jacked.
CLARK: No, no, no, no. This
is your cousin sort of...
Huh.
Ok. Uh, so Batman tried to kill Kara,
and now he's dead, so we're doomed.
We shall see.
I believe Dr. Palmer's
work is now finished.
At least I think it
is. I've never actually
built a Paragon detector before.
Uh, okay. This will be the trial run
to find the final 3.
Everyone might want to take a step back.
[DETECTOR POWERING UP]
And which Earth is that?
None of them. That's us, this ship.
Apparently, there are still a few bugs.
MONITOR: Your machine works just fine.
That light is the Paragon of Courage.
Yeah. Well, Bruce's body
isn't on the ship, so...
MONITOR: No, but you are.
I said the path to Earth-99
would lead you to the Paragon,
and that has come to pass.
You are the Bat of
the future, Kate Kane.
You are the Paragon of Courage.
[CONSTANTINE SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
- Huh.
- What?!
It's, uh... something's wrong.
This has, uh... this has
never happened before.
With all the anti-matter in the system,
I've lost my magical mojo.
BARRY: If we can't get Oliver's
soul back, he's gonna be
a... monster forever.
Yeah.
Do these things even work on you?
Not really,
but you looked like you
could use a drinking buddy.
Yeah.
Time travelers, Aliens.
I've barely even started
this whole vigilante thing.
How am I a Paragon?
I've seen you in action.
You saved me,
and last year, you saved
Oliver and Barry's asses,
thank you very much.
- Accurate.
- Heh.
How much you care, how hard you try,
those are the things that make you hero,
not powers or time travel,
and you may not feel like
you have the experience now,
but you have the heart.
You're one of the bravest people I know.
That Bruce was brave once, too,
and he had heart.
What if I end up like him?
You won't.
You'll make your own destiny.
I found this in his library.
That's Beth and me.
From Earth-99.
I wish I knew her like this.
Maybe you still can.
Sounds like the Paragon of
Hope just got her hope back.
Ohh.
Hope, help, and compassion for all.
That's what I'm gonna do for Earth-38.
But Earth-38 is gone.
I know,
but maybe I can use the Book
of Destiny to bring it back.
The Monitor said that would
be really dangerous, Kara.
I know what he said...
But what good is being
the Paragon of Hope
if I don't have any?
[VOICES WHISPERING]
Stop. Please stop.
VOICES: Come to me, Harbinger.
It is time.
MAN: Lyla Michaels,
Harbinger,
I need you.
Who are you?
Universe after universe
has fallen before my power.
World after world consumed.
With every death, I steal
my mirror's strength,
and mine grows every stronger.
Who am I?
I am the Anti-Monitor.
Come, Harbinger. There
is work to be done.