Previously on Batwoman...
Tommy said that this book
holds the key to killing Batwoman.
And I want her very, very dead.
Lucius Fox wrote
the entire journal in code.
You did it. You know what it says.
Why aren't you happier about this?
The book contains the secret
to killing you.
These are Lucius Fox's glasses.
They unlock the code.
Let Luke and Julia go
and they're yours.
Go bring me Tommy so he can tell me
where to find
a little green rock
called kryptonite.
I have to do this.
- I have to stop you.
- You won't be able to.
- You'd be surprised.
- Kryptonite? Why do you have that?
It was Bruce Wayne's.
He lost hope. I never will.
Keep it. I have the courage
that you'll never have to use it.
Batwoman's in cell block D.
No. Please, don't.
Psychotic escapees are all over
this city right now thanks to you.
Let this serve as your warning.
If I see you again, it's war.
This is the Burnley Line,
bound for Central Gotham.
Knife! Hey! Hey!
Go.
Move! Move! Move! Out of the way!
Knife! Knife! Knife!
Get away from the trains!
Drop the knives.
Why? So you can send me back there?
These are innocent people!
I don't care!
I told you to stay in the car.
Who the hell was that?
I have no idea.
Rumor has it the machete-wielding
maniac was Arkham escapee
and college football phenom,
Tim "The Titan" Teslow.
Since apparently, the Crows'
commander couldn't take down
this hulking Gotham Goliaths'
tight end with a 12-gauge,
let's hope Batwoman
has a slingshot in her Batbelt.
Have you seen this?
The Crows have an app now.
Darling, my light.
It's hard enough to see
out of Lucius Fox's glasses.
You just push the button
and the ants come marching in.
Anyone with a phone can use it,
client or not.
Which means anyone with a phone
can turn us over
with the click of a screen.
We gotta get out of Gotham, Alice.
What is that?
The bats! What is happening?
Why are they here?
Because bats eat rats, Alice.
And that's what we are down here.
We're rats living among rats.
You promised me that we would start
a new life together
outside of all this.
But we can't do that
if the Crows find us and kill us.
How is one supposed to start anew
when all that is old
still haunts her?
Is that the Alice you want
to frolic beside in our Wonderland?
Or do you wish your Alice to be full,
and complete and happy?
You know that's what I want.
Then patience,
until I can figure out
where to find this rock
that penetrates the Batsuit.
A hiding spot Lucius Fox
forgot to mention in his journal.
Alice!
What the hell is this?
You call this... This a face?
- Really? This?
- I mean...
I don't see the problem.
I got you the journal.
I helped you decode it.
Because of me, you know how
to kill your sister, Batwoman!
It's true.
But I am not about to spend
the rest of my life
looking like the bastard
that couldn't get the rods
in the nuclear reactor in time!
Give me a face I can wear.
That's good.
Shoot her dead. That'll get you
your face, you stupid idiot.
It's quite all right, Mouse.
I can take a note.
Wait, what?
No. You can't actually
be listening to him.
I owe him a face.
Which means I'll need to go
to the university morgue
for better materials.
Skin, thread, scalpels,
you know the drill.
- Back soon.
- Alice...
You are holding the only shard
of kryptonite on the planet.
Why was this in a puddle
in the Batcave?
Safekeeping.
Bruce was holding on to it
for a friend.
Let me guess, tights, cape,
big S on his chest.
Yo... how do you know that?
Lucky guess.
So, why fish it out
of a perfectly good hiding space?
Alice knows this can penetrate
the Batsuit
along with whatever else my dad
wrote about it in his journal.
Hamilton's coil accelerator
is defunct,
you melted down Bruce's rail gun
and once I figure out
how to destroy this
Batwoman is as good as invincible.
Unless you know something I don't.
Nope. Go to town.
Okay.
Hey. I thought we were bat-huddling
over this Titan Teslow psycho.
"Bat-huddling" isn't a thing.
And I'm off to destroy
an alien mineral.
Just another day on the Bat team?
Pretty much.
So, Tim "The Titan" Teslow,
obviously you know the basics, right?
Just remind me again?
He was pretty much the Goliaths'
best tight end of all time.
A TD every game,
over a hundred catches
and a thousand yards every season.
Let's not assume I know
what any of those words mean
because I'm a lesbian.
He was really, really good.
And brutal.
As in gladiator-esque.
Turns out, there's a not-so-secret
secret to all of his success.
- Say it with me, steroids.
- Sexy cheerleaders.
Point being, it all came to a head
during a playoff game
against the Cougars.
Titan didn't like a call
and went straight up Mortal Kombat
finishing move
against the official.
He snapped his neck on the field
in front of a stadium full of people.
Since when did
you become a Goliaths fan?
Since Titan's brother, Apollo,
started dating Selu Corova.
Apollo's the Goliaths' running back.
You seriously need to get out
of that Batcave.
I seriously need to suit up
and talk to this brother.
- Might know Titan's whereabouts.
- Are we sure that's the best idea?
I do,
Ms. Batwoman-Doesn't-Get-a-Sick-Day.
I said that
before Commander Kane promised
if he ever saw Batwoman again,
it'd be war.
I feel like Gotham's
got enough Greek tragedy
happening at the moment.
You don't know my dad like I do.
I do, though,...
because he's my dad too.
Not what I meant. Just...
I know how he gets and I know ways
of getting around him.
Like when teenage Kate
wanted a Crows SUV,
he said no, you took one anyway
and he had you arrested?
Or when he said no parties
in the penthouse
and you had one anyway,
and he called the police commissioner
to land a helicopter on the roof
to have you arrested?
I can keep going.
If I can stop Titan
before he kills anyone else,
then my dad
and the rest of the Crows,
they might start seeing Batwoman
as one of the good guys.
Jacob Kane will never see
a vigilante as one of the good guys.
Jacob Kane has never met a vigilante
who is also his daughter.
If I can start changing the way
that he sees Batwoman
then maybe one day I can come clean
about who Batwoman really is.
I'm a winner, I'm a, I'm a winner
Independent, make my own moola
I'm a winner, my own breadwinner
Girl in the mirror, a go, go-getter
Go, go-getter
Professor Darby, I presume?
A go, go-getter
You...
For a man
who plays with rocks all day,
this must be very exciting.
But it doesn't have to be.
I am looking for a little
green nugget called kryptonite.
Kryptonite.
You mean kaolinite.
Do I, or do I mean kryptonite?
Maybe kimberlite?
Or kyanite?
Or, um, charoite?
The head of the Geology Department
and dumb as...
Professor Darby, your name
was written beside it in a journal.
Glows green, cuts through anything.
A mineral with a natural
green luminescence
and strong covalent bonds
with that kind of cutting power.
Actually, I did analyze something
with those properties once.
It wasn't called kryptonite.
It was some kind of rare meteor rock.
There you go.
Hand it over.
I can't, it was sent back
to its owner, Lucius Fox.
Lucius Fox is dead.
It just says Lucius Fox,
Wayne Enterprises, Gotham City.
And what do you suppose I do?
Just waltz into Wayne
and ask for it nicely?
I don't know, okay?
It's not here.
You need to go talk to them.
Well, then I suppose
that's what I'll do.
Until then, it's probably best
nobody knows I was here.
And with that...
I believe the Geology Department
needs a new head.
Still hasn't checked in
since you looked ten seconds ago.
Sorry if the idea
of my dad killing my sister
is somewhat of a concern to me.
Her suit is bulletproof.
Besides, Kate knows what she's doing.
No, Kate thinks she knows
what she's doing,
which can be worse than most people
not knowing what they're doing.
Yeah, me included, apparently.
Look, I've tried acetic,
sulfuric and hydrochloric.
All non-reactive.
I can see why this thing
can penetrate the Batsuit.
Have you tried crushing it?
With what, a hammer?
- I said I was nervous.
- All right.
I like the pressure
Not afraid of the storm
'Cause it's all mine
I'm exhausted just watching you.
Who's there?
Someone who thinks you're pretty bold
to be running bleachers
with Titan on the prowl.
If this is about season tickets,
I can't help you.
If this is about my brother,
I guess my question is
are you helping him?
You're the only family he has left.
I don't think he sees it that way.
Not after I testified against him
- and got him sent away to Arkham.
- You did the right thing.
Got a dangerous psychopath
off the streets.
He's not a psychopath.
Tell that to the ref
he murdered on the field.
He wanted to win,
so much that he was willing
to have his soul beaten out of him.
Every practice, every game,
every hit to the head.
You know he used to walk
the neighborhood kids
to the bus to make sure
they were safe?
Ten years later, he ripped
a ref's spine out of his neck.
This game turned him into a monster.
Then help me make sure
he doesn't die one.
Make sure he gets the help he needs.
Tell me where to find him.
Apollo! You betrayed me!
This is the part where you run.
You abandoned me to the prison.
Now this one will be yours.
I'm reporting live here at the scene
of yet another grisly attack
by the fugitive,
Tim "The Titan" Teslow.
And this time,
the victim was his own brother,
star running back
for the Gotham Goliaths,
Apollo Teslow.
Commander Kane.
Commander Kane,
any comments on this latest attack?
And what about reports that not even
Batwoman was able to stop Titan?
Batwoman is the reason lunatics
like Titan are on the street
in the first place.
We got one man dead
and one of Gotham's
most promising athletes
- cut down in his prime.
- So you don't see Batwoman's efforts
to stop Titan as helpful?
I see Batwoman
like I see every vigilante,
a threat to the good people
of this city.
The Crows and the GCPD
will bring her to justice.
And we will not discriminate
between the Bat
and those who aid her, abet her,
or so much as turn on
a damn Batlight!
That was Crows Commander Kane
with some pointed words
for Batwoman and her followers.
I don't remember tensions like these
since Commissioner Loeb and Batman.
Which begs the question who,
if anyone,
can keep Gotham City safe...
I'm gonna have to reset
your shoulder.
Fair warning,
this is gonna hurt a lot.
No comment.
That was Julia.
She saw your dad on the news
and thinks
you should sit this one out.
You might not have a choice.
I'll need an x-ray to make sure,
but I'm guessing you have
a couple of cracked ribs.
I'll be lucky if it's just a couple.
I've never been up against someone
this strong before, Mary.
It was like I was nothing to him.
All the more reason
to avoid a rematch.
At least for a few weeks
till you've had time to heal.
I don't have a few weeks.
Titan's on some killing spree
and we have no way of knowing
who he's gonna strike at next.
Actually, maybe we do.
You're not gonna believe this.
That commuter he beheaded
on the subway
wasn't just some random guy.
He had a connection to Titan.
He used to be an administrator
at his university's neuro clinic
until he was fired for falsifying
student athletes' brain scans.
Apollo said the game
turned his brother into a monster.
Or the people behind the game.
Where's the rock?
Hidden among 45 stories of anywhere
and a million square feet
of possibility.
Our beloved little rock
may as well be
a grain of sand along the beach.
So...
That's it, then. It's not happening.
It's over. We can leave now.
Or we can walk right through the door
and ask for it.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Everyone knows eyebrows
don't grow themselves.
You're making him a face.
You promised me
we were gonna kill him.
We will! But today,
he's an integral part of my plan.
And tomorrow, what then?
And the next day, what then?
When does this end?
Why are you pressuring me?
Because we're being hunted, Alice.
Is this rabid obsession
with your family
really worth it
if we both end up dead?
I suppose it is.
Well, not for me, it's not.
It's over, Alice. I'm leaving.
And where do you imagine going?
Where we've always planned to go.
To the beautiful garden
among the bright flowerbeds
and the cool fountains.
You,...
out in the world?
Alone?
How would you even survive?
The same way I survived
in Arkham for five years
without you visiting me once.
Not on my birthday, or a holiday,
or even just because.
You really think
I can't survive without you?
Alice, between the two of us,
I'm not the one I'm worried about.
You can't leave me all alone.
Then don't make me.
Forget all this.
Come with me.
I would never let you leave me,
my little Mouse.
But we must leave Gotham
the right way.
With a party.
Every season Titan underwent
a mandatory brain scan
to assess his eligibility to play.
And Gotham U claimed this...
was his most recent brain scan.
Totally healthy.
But after digging deep
into the neuro clinic records,
thanks to Mary's
med school connections.
Technically,
it's not a HIPAA violation
if you're not a real doctor.
Turns out this...
was his actual brain scan.
Oh, God. All those years
of head trauma.
Dorsal posterior insula's
basically shriveled to nothing.
That sounds really bad.
It's the part of the brain
that governs pain.
No wonder he didn't feel
that Batarang.
They cover it all up
and they give you
a big, fat, championship ring
for your troubles.
Wow. Interesting.
GU's coach, Donahue,
took an early retirement
right before the scandal broke.
All right.
He might be Titan's next victim.
Where are you going?
You can barely stand,
much less take on a literal goliath
who's hella impervious to pain.
Yeah. Not to mention,
the Crows would love
to put your pointy-eared head
on a pike.
And what do you expect me to do, hm?
Stand down?
Just let Titan
rampage through Gotham?
Well...
there is another idea.
But I don't think
you're gonna like it.
Go, go, go!
If you see the Bat, shoot.
Got something behind the light.
Don't shoot!
I'm here on behalf of Batwoman.
Where is she?
Dad, I'm fine!
Everything's okay.
What's going on?
How the hell did she get to you?
Can you just please talk to her?
You just made this way too personal.
- We need to talk about Titan.
- Which part?
About how he doesn't play
by the rules
or care about collateral damage?
I want to team up.
We can take him on together.
What's the matter?
Titan too much for your army of one?
Honestly, yeah.
I could use the muscle
and you can use me
because I know how to draw him out.
Oh, like you drew me out
by using my own daughter?
What sort of wannabe hero
puts an innocent girl
in front of a firing squad?
Could have blown her damn head off!
Everyone off the roof now!
You heard him. Go. Go.
How the hell did she find you?
- She didn't! I found her.
- What are you talking about?
I'm saying this was my idea!
You told me that the Crows
wanted to make over their image.
Why not start by allying yourself
with someone
this city actually roots for?
You did this?
I knew I'm one of the only people
who can get through to you!
I believe in her, Dad.
Mary, I said anyone affiliated
with her will be brought to justice.
Okay, then arrest me.
Arrest me for believing in someone
who saves lives
and who stops criminals
and who inspires hope
without charging a penny for it!
I'm your daughter and if I don't
believe in what you're doing,
how can you expect
a city of strangers to?
Except the person you believe in
doesn't even have the guts
to show her face.
I can't show you my face,
but I can offer you this.
A truce.
We partner up,
protect the city together.
Please.
So, how do we get him?
I'm at Gotham City Arena
with Gotham University's
former head coach Kurt Donahue.
Kurt, what are your thoughts?
If you're listening, Titan,
I'm sorry for thinking the sport
was bigger than the human life.
And I hope you'll come
join me on the 50-yard line
where I can apologize
to you in person.
It's called a trauma bond exercise.
I just write the thing
that anchors us
to our pain
so that we can move on.
Look who paid attention
in group therapy.
Maybe a little.
This book is our chain.
It locks us to the Caterpillar,...
the Queen...
that basement cell.
It binds us to every terrible...
twisted thing
we were forced to endure.
Burning it breaks our attachment
and frees us to move on...
which we always intended to do.
Move on.
What happened to us...
should never happen to anyone.
But there's no one in the world
I would have rather
gone through it with than you.
Nor I without you.
And I mean this with all of my heart.
I still wanna join you
in the beautiful garden...
and smell the seasons
in bright flowerbeds
and make a wish in cool fountains.
I wanna meet a man with many hats.
And smile back at the Cheshire cat.
And run with you forever...
through our Wonderland.
Alice...
No!
What did you do?
You made me choose.
You poisoned me?
Why did you do that?
Because I couldn't let you leave me.
Not you too.
This...
This wasn't even real?
If only pain could turn to ash
with the strike of a match.
But my pain is a part of me,
the way my family is a part of me.
You could never understand
why I need to enact my revenge,
because you've never experienced
true betrayal.
At least not until now.
Goodbye, my sweet Mouse.
My brother...
my everything.
I'll see you again in Wonderland.
Are we missing the company party
or something?
Where's the commander?
It's all hands on deck
at the arena with Batwoman.
- What did you mean "With Batwoman"?
- They teamed up to bring down Titan.
Two hours ago he said he would arrest
anyone affiliated with her.
Now he's tagging her into the ring?
Something's up.
We need to get there.
Call her and give her the heads-up.
Saying what, exactly?
To watch her six.
It's the smoke laying low
Before the flame shows
It's the far away light
In the quiet in the night
I don't think this guy is gonna show.
Could that have anything to do
with the Crows lying in wait?
I'm not standing down the welcoming
committee, leave tactical to me.
So choose your weapons wise
Uh, Batcave to Batwoman,
Julia just texted...
- Yeah, I got it too. I'll be fine.
- Julia seems to think otherwise.
Julia didn't look into my dad's eyes
when she shook his hand, okay?
I'll be fine...
ish.
What just happened?
Someone cut the power.
Why are we in the dark?
Not sure, commander.
Working on it now.
Under attack
All positions report in.
Section 30, clear.
Box level, clear.
- End zone one...
- It's him.
Go!
Stop!
Tim, this isn't you!
Apollo told me who you are.
Big brother,
used to walk the neighborhood kids
to the bus stop.
Make sure they were safe.
I know that person
is still inside you.
I didn't wanna be this.
I know.
You didn't have to kill him!
What are you doing?
I promised you war.
This is what it looks like.
We're on the same team.
You can't do this.
We're on the same team...
Stop! What are you doing?
Is that why you sidelined me today?
If you want to take me off the field
to launch this app, fine.
But if you're using it to distract me
while you and everyone else
are trying to take out Batwoman...
And why would I need to do that,
Agent Moore?
Because you would've gone
behind your own team's back
to protect a criminal?
I'm protecting you from being
on the wrong side of this.
What is it about her?
You, now Mary,
tell me what I'm missing.
With all due respect, sir, hope.
If it weren't for her, my wife's
killer would still be in Arkham.
Hope is a luxury I don't have.
Thought you two used to be tight.
We are.
At least...
we were.
I thought you called Batwoman
to warn her.
I did. She didn't listen.
You don't believe me.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just looking for flaws
because I'm terrified of being
in a relationship with a woman.
No. I'm pretty much being shady
by design, love.
Okay.
So, in one of my many thrilling
and sexy adventures,
I met the wrong person
and proceeded to betray her.
So, you're hiding? From who?
Her name is Safiyah
and I'll say no more
because I'll only pull you into it.
A sexy and thrilling adventure?
Maybe I want to be pulled in.
I wish it were that simple, love.
I knew I had a target on my back,
I just didn't know its circumference.
These were left
at my hotel this morning.
Do you need this?
My thoughts exactly.
I actually pictured myself coming out
to him as Batwoman one day.
I looked him in the eyes
and I believed him.
I'm really, really sorry, Kate.
If it means anything to you,
I believed him too.
I always thought
when I put that suit on
that nothing could hurt me.
But I was wrong.
His betrayal hurt a million times
more than any of those bullets.
- My dad hates me.
- No. Batwoman.
He hates Batwoman. You, he loves.
He once loved Beth too.
In his mind,
Batwoman is just as crazy as Alice.
He's wrong.
Thank you for having my back today.
To sisters.
Am I interrupting?
Come in.
May I present to you...
I'll stick with booze. Thanks.
What... No, that's not...
That's kryptonite.
I figured out how to destroy it.
Oh, my God.
You used a hammer.
Okay, more like 40,000 tons
of compressive force.
Wayne has access
to a hydraulic press.
So just a really expensive hammer.
Yeah, Mary. This is all thanks
to your brilliant hammer idea.
Point being, this is what's left
of the only thing on Earth
that can penetrate the Batsuit.
Okay.
And that is me taking the only weapon
that can kill you off the table.
Before we get too cocky...
No more secrets.
Not between us.
And not after today.
- Where did you get that?
- The same way Bruce did.
A friend gave it to me
for safekeeping
in case she ever lost her way.
And you're just telling us
about it now because...
I honestly didn't think
you'd figure out a way to destroy it.
Well, we did. So hand it over.
And because I can't.
It's not mine to destroy.
Kate, if that gets into
the wrong hands, it'll kill you.
I promised my friend I would keep it.
And she trusts me.
And until I can talk to her about it,
I need you guys to trust me too.
Come.
Sir, thought
these might interest you.
Collected them from the arena.
That in particular
is a slug from a Desert Eagle.
Desert Eagle
can shoot through anything.
Well, almost anything, sir.
Then we're going to need
to find something stronger.
I must admit, Tommy,
I find you to be one of the most
loathsome men in Gotham.
Vain and uncouth.
Humorless and dull.
I pity any woman who confuses
the buzz of her martini
with your charms.
And yet, here you are.
My masterpiece.
What did you do?
I made all your dreams come true.
I look like Bruce Wayne.
You made me Bruce Wayne.
So, my rich, handsome,
beloved Bruce,
I need you to strut through the doors
of Wayne Tower
and get me that shard of kryptonite
from your dear cousin Kate.