Happy birthday!
- How did you get in here?
- Easy.
Hey, did you guys fire
that hot front-desk guy?
Because he was the best part
of this place.
Hi.
I'm back.
Happy birthday.
- Did Sophie let you go?
- Who?
Kate, I'm home from a semester abroad
and this is how you react?
It's bad enough that they converted
my apartment into a boy's dorm room,
and no one chose to talk to me...
- Who are you?
- What's wrong with you?
- It's me. It's Beth.
- Beth?
- Who the hell else would I be?
- Kate, you're hurting me.
- Not yet, but I will.
"Are there any lions
or tigers about here?"
"It's only the Red King snoring."
- Happy birthday, Beth.
- You remembered.
I hope you like blueberry.
And I got you a present.
I found this out by the shed.
It's a kitty.
My dad can't know.
- It has to be a secret.
- Hi, little guy.
What are you gonna call him?
Chessie.
You'll be our Cheshire Cat.
Johnny tells me it's your birthday.
Beth, you're very lucky to have
such a kind and thoughtful friend.
I suppose...
it wouldn't be official
without making a wish.
What'd you wish for?
To see my sister and father.
Beth.
If you say your wish out loud,
it means it will never come true.
Time for your classes, Johnny.
Beth's dead.
Whatever happened
to her in that house erased
all traces of my daughter.
She's gone.
Don't make the mistake I made.
It'd be a mistake
to not even try to interrogate Alice.
So, she can prattle off a bunch
of nonsensical nursery rhymes?
Or incriminate herself.
I appreciate the attempt, but you're
not getting a confession out of her.
- It's too big a risk.
- Risk of what?
Letting Alice into your head.
Let's just keep her on ice until
she can be transferred to Arkham.
After that, she's their problem.
Were you planning on telling me
that Alice escaped?
What are you talking about?
She showed up at my office just now.
That's impossible.
She's been in a holding cell
for the last eight hours.
- Is that a live feed?
- Yes. With two guards at the door.
She's downstairs.
You're welcome to see for yourself.
I swear I just saw her.
Then you're not the only one.
Mary saw her too.
I took prints off the messenger bag
the Alice look-alike left behind.
They're an exact match
for Alice's prints
in the Crows's database.
Look, there's more.
I found this in her wallet.
It's not in the system,
but that is hands-down
the best fake ID I've ever seen.
- Somebody went to a lot of trouble.
- You're telling me.
Apparently, she wrote
a 300-page dissertation
on Theoretical Extragalactic
Astrophysics and Cosmology.
Maybe there's some answers in here.
It's locked with a security code,
but I might be able
to crack it in a couple hours.
Or...
- "Waffles."
- How did you know that?
Beth always used it. Only password
she could ever remember.
Okay.
Oh, my god.
How are you and her...
I don't know.
You two seem really close.
We should tell your dad about this.
No. Not until we figure out
what's going on.
Wait, where are you going?
To see if anyone in Gotham
University's astrophysics department
has ever heard of... Beth?
Are we calling her Beth? Alice 2.0?
Well, when you figure it out,
let me know.
Okay, I've seen pictures
like this before.
Beth and me, together.
Only it was on a different Earth.
So, when that dude
put all the Earths in a blender...
Somehow she landed on this one.
But how is she Beth and not Alice?
Like, what happened after the crash?
Maybe there was no crash.
Infinite Earths, infinite variables,
I'd bet. A butterfly flaps its wings.
No Cartwright, no Mouse, no Alice.
She was spared all that.
Still, this world has gotta be
a very scary place for her.
One second, she's on her Earth.
The next, she's slingshot
to this one, where nobody knows her.
Yeah, and the only person
who does attacks her.
Her own twin sister. Happy birthday.
- I gotta find her.
- Yeah, where do you think she is?
Where we'd always go on our birthday.
Beth! Beth, I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
You gonna attack me again, psycho?
No. No, I...
It's a long story,
but I didn't recognize you then.
But I do now.
Well, you are the only one.
Nobody else even knows who I am.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
What's happening?
My wish came true.
I understand you have a request.
Oh, I have a lot of requests.
But since I highly doubt
that you'll grant me my freedom,
or my butterfly knife,
I'll settle for my book.
Your book?
Yes. My copy of Alice in Wonderland.
I imagine it's around here somewhere.
Plundered by your Crows
when they raided my little hideaway.
It did bring me so much comfort the
last time, I was locked in a cell.
Unless you're willing
to admit to framing my boss
for the murder of his wife,
I'm not interested in your comfort.
Well, that is no way to treat someone
on their birthday.
I wouldn't hold out hope
for me throwing you a party.
That's okay.
One's already being planned.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, I wouldn't wanna ruin
the surprise.
You see, Kate always hated surprises.
But me?
I love them.
Hi.
You have something I want.
And I have something
that you'll want back.
Two things, in fact.
- Say hello to Steven.
- Help!
Commissioner of Forbes and Son.
And Bryan, Mayor Akins's
heir apparent.
I'll give you until 9.00pm.
to release Alice.
If you don't,
I'll snuff out Gotham's best
and brightest.
So, literally no one knows me
on this Earth?
On the upside, I guess none
of my exes know me here either.
You're taking
this death-of-the-multiverse
thing better than thought.
I do have a master's degree
in astrophysics,
so the concept of multiple universes
isn't that bizarre.
Here's to making up lost time.
I have to ask, what the hell
do all your tattoos mean?
So, you're telling me
that the parallel Kate,
- did not have tattoos?
- Are you kidding?
Commander Kane would've disowned
you.
So, my dad was still the head
of the Crows on your Earth?
Yeah, and technically,
he was our dad.
- God, it's so weird.
- I know.
But you know what's really weird,
despite your tats
and the fact that this used
to be my bank...
is that it feels
like I'm back on my Earth.
And it's just a normal day
just chatting to my sister.
And not to be a total creep, but...
you still just feel like
the best friend
I've had my whole life.
We were best friends.
Yeah, ever since you pulled me
from the car, I've always...
Wait. What car?
Right...
When we were 13, driving back
from our bat mitzvah,
- our car went off a bridge.
- So, there was a crash?
Yeah.
That's how Mom died.
Mom, you can't go. Mom!
But you...
You climbed back into the car.
Kate, where are you going?
Wait.
And you pulled me out.
- Beth, please, grab my hand.
- Get me out.
You saved me.
Beth!
No!
And ever since then,
you've been my hero.
- What is it?
- You near a TV?
Gotham is on high alert
in the wake of the Wonderland Gang
committing what could be
their most brazen crime to date
with the kidnapping of the sons
of two of Gotham's highest officials.
Despite the unfolding
hostage situation
involving Commissioner
Forbes's own son,
the GCPD has not turned
on the Bat-Signal.
- Commissioner Forbes...
- Commissioner...
Does your refusal to turn on
the Bat-Signal have anything to do
with the Batwoman
coming out as a lesbian?
My wife and I
are incredibly concerned
for the safety of our son
and that of Bryan Akins.
Let's not get distracted
by politics. Thank you.
Okay. If they're not
gonna take Batwoman's help,
they're sure as hell gonna need ours.
Oh, so now you come bearing gifts.
It is your birthday.
I know what you're doing.
But the question is, do you?
I'm granting your request.
I ran it through x-ray,
thermal imaging,
even an ion mobility spectrometer.
- Turns out it's just a book.
- Oh, no.
- It's so much more than that.
- Yeah?
So, what makes it so special?
It set me free from
that house of horrors.
Hold still.
Johnny, if you don't keep still,
the adhesive won't set.
It's all wrong.
The seams, it's hideous.
You look like a quilt.
It turns out we were both
trapped in that awful place.
I was in that house.
I can't imagine what years in
that place must've been like.
But you do know
what it's like to feel trapped.
Don't you, Sophie?
I imagine you've felt
that way your entire life.
It's unbearable.
When the only thing
you dream about is being...
Out.
Prep the suit. I'm coming in.
How are we doing on the location?
I'm working on it
but GCPD's got nothing.
Not a surprise.
They don't have enough sense
to turn on the Bat-Signal.
Haven't you heard? I'm too political.
So they'd rather avoid
a political hot potato
than have Batwoman save the kid?
That's crazy.
Welcome to the world we live in.
I'm gonna save them anyway.
That sounds like something Bruce
would say.
Yeah. Well, he'd probably
actually do it too.
Okay. What is it?
I could've saved her, Luke.
Everybody told me that if I went
back in that car to get Beth,
that I would've been killed.
Well, it's not true.
You wanna hear the truth?
You got Beth back.
She doesn't need saving.
But right now, there's some
pretty high- profile hostages who do.
On my way.
It's in the air
It's everywhere you go
According to Mouse's deadline,
you've got two hours
to find these hostages.
Copy.
Time's up
West Hollow's clear.
Cut down Sanders Avenue.
Thanks.
Rise! Rise! Rise!
Rise! Rise!
Kate? Batcave to Kate,
can you hear me?
Kate, say something.
Kate? Kate? Kate!
You guys okay?
Did you enjoy your nap?
I thought it best to intercept you
before you made your wardrobe change.
You know, you are much more docile
without your evening wear.
How are they treating you?
Well, I'm chained
to a table on my birthday, so...
I don't think they value the lives
of the hostages you've taken.
Well, I may have someone that
they might care a bit more about.
Sophie.
- Kate?
- Hi, sis.
- Are you hurt? Are you okay?
- No worse than Survival Training.
You remember that, how we never
would've made it without each other?
- Yeah.
- Then I need you to listen to me.
Let Alice go.
Let Alice go. Do you understand?
I understand.
Good. Because time's running out.
And my next call will be to tell you
where to find Kate's body.
Hey, Luke.
Right. You don't know me.
But you know me?
Yeah. You work for my cousin, Bruce.
- You're Lucius Fox's son.
- Yeah.
- I'm just looking for Kate...
- She's been kidnapped.
Sorry. There's no easy way
for me to get that out, but yeah.
Kidnapped? As in taken?
By whom?
There's no easy way for me
to get this out either, but by you.
- Yeah, that's not happening.
- What?
Did you hear Kate
practically begging for her life?
In Survival Training, Kate
and I learned to fool our captors
by sending coded messages
in the open.
Repeat a message twice,
it meant, "Do the opposite."
She was saying, "Don't let Alice go."
Clever and sweet.
You two have your
own little language.
Let me tell you a secret. Mouse
and I had one too.
See, we needed a way
to make sure
the Caterpillar didn't figure out
what we were up to.
"Are there any lions
or tigers about here?"
"It's only the Red
King snoring."
That was the little code
that the coast was clear
and we were safe.
You made Chessie a sweater.
I cut up one of my blankets.
He looks so, so fancy.
Johnny, get upstairs.
Time for chores.
What was that?
No, no.
You know these creatures
carry all manner of diseases.
Please, Daddy, no. It's my fault.
I brought him here.
Don't hurt him. Johnny can put
him back where he found him.
Please...
I guess you could say
he made the Cheshire Cat...
Disappear.
That's awful.
Tell me...
How awful it will be...
when you lose the thing you love
so dearly?
If Kate's been kidnapped,
shouldn't we call my dad?
He'll know what to do.
He's Special Forces.
He's in jail.
- What?
- For killing your stepmother,
but he didn't do it. Alice did.
Okay...
Dumb question,
do police exist on this Earth?
Yes. But honestly, the Wonderland
Gang is always a few steps ahead.
But fortunately, I got
a little something the cops don't.
And that is a GPS on Kate's bike.
The signal's weak. The transmitter
must've gotten damaged.
I just gotta find a way
to boost it enough
to get a lock on her location.
Then we send in the cavalry?
No. No. They'll be ready for that.
And that'll just get Kate
and the others killed.
This Mouse guy is demanding Alice,
yeah?
Well, what if we give her to him?
No. No. Sorry.
That's not gonna happen.
That's insane and Kate
would never let you.
Kate saved my life in my world.
I'm gonna save her life in this one.
- Batwoman's gonna save us, right?
- Not sure I'd count on that.
Yeah. Because my idiot dad
isn't gonna turn on the Bat-Signal.
Dude, it's 2020. Nobody cares
about gay-straight anymore.
"Oh, my ears and whiskers,
how late it's getting."
Look, Alice.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
My heart breaks for that little girl
who was trapped in that cell.
For everything that man did to her.
And I know somewhere deep down...
That little girl is still fighting
to get out.
Kate used to think that too.
But just like that little kitten...
Beth never made it out
of the basement.
Did you make this?
Answer me!
My dad will kill you.
Oh, my dear.
Your father has already forgotten
about you.
You've been replaced.
Now...
I want you to tell me,
did you make this?
Yes. I did.
Sorry.
Don't be sorry, my dear.
This is exactly...
The kind of delicate craftsmanship
that Johnny needs.
Now...
I want you to use these nimble little
fingers...
to do exactly...
What you did with this sweater...
With these.
That was the day I learned
to make faces out of human skin.
First were the eyebrows.
Or was it the lips?
I don't remember.
Perhaps my thoughts
were so preoccupied
with the horrid realization
that no one was coming...
To rescue me.
So she's basically got two
go-to moves in
her repertoire of crazy.
Either say something terrible
in a really sweet voice,
or you say something sweet
but make it sound like
it's the scariest thing in the world.
She sounds lovely.
Yeah, and if you really get
into some trouble...
just throw out a random quote
from Alice in Wonderland.
"Curiouser and curiouser." Or...
"Off with her..."
- What? Do I look that bad?
- No, no.
You...
You look perfect.
- Then what is it?
- Just...
The last time
I looked into those eyes,
my mom was dying in my arms.
Poisoned... By Alice.
- So. it's just hard not to...
- Hate me?
I don't blame you.
Alice is...
Me. And I'm her.
At least, in some ways, I guess.
Which is why I can't help
but feel responsible
for what happened to your mom.
And I am so, so sorry.
You don't have to be.
You are nothing like that bitch.
I got a lock. I know where Kate is.
A scrapyard outside of town.
- Time's almost up!
- No.
- No, no, no, this is not...
- No. Please.
I can't die. I can't die.
"The Dormouse shook
its head impatiently
and said, without opening its eyes,
'Of course, of course, just what
I was going to remark myself.'"
They let you go?
You played your part well,
my little Mouse.
You made them fear you
and they set me free.
And alas, a deal's a deal.
And now we must do the same for them.
Why does she get to live?
She was perfectly happy
living her life without you.
Now, it's time for you
to live yours without her.
Were you followed?
No. Of course not.
"Are there any lions
or tigers about here?"
What are you talking about?
"Are there any lions
or tigers about here?"
Who are you?
No!
Let me out! Help!
This is your last chance.
You can still be
the person you once were.
If you say your wish out loud,
it will never come true.
Your father has already forgotten
about you.
I want you
to use these nimble little fingers.
Thank you...
For helping me look normal.
I'm sorry about the book,
but I got some
of my dad's fishing line.
It's really strong.
We can fix it, Beth.
I'm gonna call you my little Mouse.
And you can call me Alice.
Shall we have a tea party?
The book was my escape.
That's how you dealt
with all that trauma?
By creating an entirely different
reality and becoming someone else?
Isn't that what you did, Agent Moore?
Escaping your prison
by becoming someone else?
Lying to yourself and everybody else
about who you really are.
Retreating into the arms
of that yummy Boy Scout.
Get her out of here.
Maybe Arkham will
have better luck bringing out
- who you really are, Beth.
- This is who I really am.
Drop it.
My dear sweet little birdie.
I may be free of my cage,
but you're still trapped in yours.
And you always will be.
Because it's one of your own making.
And that...
Is a hell more unbearable than...
- Hey!
- Hey, get me out of here!
- Let me out!
Let me out! Please!
- Please help!
- Let me out!
Please, help. Please!
Get me out of here!
Help! Please. Let me out.
Let me out, please.
Let me out, let me out!
- Goddamn.
- Please get me out. Please.
Get us out. Please, please.
Get me out. Please. Please, please.
Someone help. Please help me!
Kate!
Come on. Come on, hurry!
Come on!
Get back, get back, get back.
Evening, Gotham. Notice
how I didn't say "good evening"?
That's because
Alice is back on the streets.
And while Gotham's golden boys
may be safe
and snug in their beddy-byes,
I'll be sleeping
with a Louisville Slugger tonight,
because with Batwoman
on the GCPD's do-not-call list,
it's the only bat
that's going to protect me.
Shut down Brown
and Loeb Bridge. Leave Trigate open.
Give her one way out.
Search every vehicle top to bottom.
If she tries it,
we'll stop her there.
What's the status on Mouse?
Just got out of surgery, in ICU.
I want a six-person team
on him around the clock.
Kate.
- How are you?
- I came to ask you the same thing.
Rattled, embarrassed, pissed.
Mostly pissed.
Well, I'm just glad you remembered
our code.
Of course I did.
I remember everything.
For example, happy birthday.
Did you get anything good,
besides kidnapped?
I did, I did, actually.
And now with
the city gripped by fear
with reports of Alice's
bloody escape...
What's going on at the GCPD?
Protestors have taken
to the steps of the GCPD,
demanding that they turn
on the Bat-Signal.
Turn on the light! Turn on the light!
Turn on the light!
Sometimes this city surprises you.
Turn on the light! Turn on the light!
Oh, now we know you're listening
Turn on the light!
Turn on the light! Turn on the light!
Now, we know you're listening
We're the new tradition
Any idea where she could be?
I don't know.
And I'm sorry, commander.
I should've listened to you.
- And now...
- You didn't kill those agents.
Alice did.
Yeah.
But because of me,
now she's escaped.
That's how we're gonna stop her.
If anything happened to Alice
when she was in Crows's custody,
we'd have to answer for it.
But she's a fugitive now.
We could put a bullet in her
and no one would bat an eye.
It's time we do exactly that.
- Surprise!
- I had nothing to do with this.
Yeah, yeah. She told me
that you would hate this.
She would be right, ahem.
Twin intuition. Happy birthday, Beth.
Happy birthday.
Your bar needs bigger glasses.
You know, I'll be honest,
I never really understood
why you were so hell-bent
on redeeming that psychopath Alice.
But now that I've met Beth,
I totally get it.
I see what you lost.
Yeah.
To miracles.
Actually, I don't think that,
that's what it is.
And this could just be
my little friend talking here,
but I read your sister's thesis
on extra-astral
galactic stuffy stuff.
I think Beth's being here
is some kind of cosmic anomaly.
Hear me out.
What if there are multiple universes?
Kind of like a bunch
of different planet Earths.
And then they all kind of...
Collapsed into one.
Only there were some parts left over.
Kind of like after you built
an Ikea bookshelf
and Beth is just one of the parts
that made it into the box somehow.
You know, you're right, it's crazy.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday
Okay. Make a wish.
Well, all I ever really wanted
was a second chance.
And here you are, so...
Here you go.
Hey, hey.
Hey, what's happening?
Beth, what's happening? What is it?