Previously on Batwoman...
Bruce never stopped looking
for your sister's body.
Catherine Hamilton's investigators
found skull fragments
of a little girl.
It's Beth.
You never would have moved on
if you didn't think
that Beth were dead.
I paid the DNA analyst
to write the report.
As hard as I have tried
to get over you,
I can't, it's definitely
not fair to Tyler.
Maybe it's best if I keep
my distance from now on.
Daddy.
Catherine seems to think so.
We are to host the most
memorable mad tea party
Gotham has ever seen.
They say the choices
we make define us.
But despite all the darkness,
despite all those who doubt,
and despite my own fear
that I've lost my sister forever,
I choose to hope.
That Beth is still there.
Don't tell anyone, Bruce,
but I think this makes me
an optimist.
- Give me your jacket.
- Wait. What?
- This is vintage, bitch.
Okay. Take it, take it, take it.
Vintage.
Thanks, not exactly my style.
Or size.
And... Is that blood?
You really shouldn't have.
Front right pocket.
Rabbit dropped it in there
before I made run for it.
Think we can use the phone's
GPS to track Alice?
I can try.
I see you broke the staff in two.
Like I won't notice?
Sorry, for the record,
it'd be a whole lot cooler
if it actually came apart.
It doesn't though, so...
Okay, here's every location
the phone's gone to
- the past seven days.
- Where's this?
Slice of Gotham.
Worst breadsticks in the city.
But location two
is a little more promising.
It's a warehouse in The Bowery.
Then that's where she is.
Don't wait up.
Too sad. Too loud.
Too mundane. Why?
Why do I have nothing to wear?
If you're going to kidnap me again
do wait until I can dolly up
into something with...
a little more flair.
Did you hire The Rifle to kill me?
Says the walking, talking,
living girl.
He shot someone he believed
to be Batwoman
with the coil accelerator.
A weapon designed
for only one reason, to kill me.
The guy who designed it was found
with a butterfly knife in his heart.
Yeah, let me rephrase that.
So an evil man was trying
to kill my twin sister
and I ensured that...
that didn't happen.
What is this?
That is a multi-million dollar
piece of technology
that allows the coil accelerator
to penetrate your suit.
That's the only one
that exists on the planet.
Anyone who knew how to make it
is well exactly that
past tense so...
You're welcome.
Turn yourself in, Alice.
Let me help you.
I know my sister is in there.
This again.
You kept this.
From the day of our b'not mitzvah.
Take it, and be gone.
I am quite busy
and I have nothing to wear.
It's Kane.
I'll be back in Gotham
later tonight.
We'll go over the floor plan
for the gala
first thing tomorrow.
Talk then.
So the way I see it,
you can either spend
your Friday night
in here inhaling asbestos
or you can join me in wearing
this season's sexiest
haute couture.
Seriously.
Gigi and Bella could not even
get their hands on this yet.
You want me to go
to that thing tonight.
Okay, that thing is
The Gotham Humanitarian Gala,
i.e. the most important event
of the season.
Honoring your mom, who told
my dad that Beth was dead.
Asbestos it is.
I get that we're bordering on
too soon.
Pretty sure we're right
in the middle of it.
I know that this isn't
important to you.
But it's important to me, okay?
So, why can't it be important to you
that it's important to me?
Because you think that
if Gotham sees us as a family
that we'll start to believe it.
And that's just not how it works.
- Not after what Catherine did...
- You gave Alice a second chance.
And a third. And a fourth.
How can you write off
my mom as Satan
but you don't seem
to have any problem
holding out hope for the actual
most evil person in Gotham.
Because she's my family.
And I'm not. Got it.
I guess I am the crazy one,
you know?
For thinking you and I
could still be sisters.
Of course, you're my family
it's just...
Different. Yeah, do yourself
a favor, stop digging.
Listen, even if I wanted to go,
I could never do that to my dad.
You don't know?
He decided to come tonight.
For me.
Sorry for thinking
that you would do the same.
You're going to the
Humanitarian Gala?
Yeah, I meant to talk to you
about that.
Unless Catherine somehow
didn't fake Beth's death,
then I don't know what there is
to talk about.
- Are you getting back with her?
- No.
When you've been with someone
for a decade and a half,
you don't just walk away.
You're letting her weasel her way
back into your life...
There's no weaseling, Kate.
We've been spending
some time together.
When? You've been out of town.
Well, you know, we had breakfast
when I got back.
You're seriously forgiving her.
I'm not defending what Catherine did.
She's not either but...
I am beginning to understand
why she did it.
As a mother, as a wife.
She thought she was helping us
move on.
Wake up, father dear.
Why, what a long sleep you've had.
I thought it was high time
you and I finally had
a daddy-daughter chat.
That is all I want.
But come on.
Not like this.
Let me out of these chains...
You're not the Commander here,
Commander.
Kate will know I'm gone.
Will she?
Because I saw her last night
and there was nary
a mention of you.
Guess she's oh-for-two
in missing family members.
What do you want me to say?
I'm sorry?
There's no word to describe
what it feels like
to know that I left you behind.
Then find the words to explain
why you never tested the skull
fragments Catherine found.
I had no reason
to think that she was lying.
But your daughter was missing.
And this was just
a handful of bones
found by some woman
you'd known for less than a year.
Maybe believing
that you were dead was easier
than waking up every morning
with hope,
or going to sleep every night
with a broken heart.
Of course,
I should've looked longer,
I should've hoped harder,
I should've, I should've had
the DNA tested myself.
I wish...
I wish I could've been your father
for the past 15 years. But...
I failed.
I failed you.
Thank you for saying that.
And thank you for making me
who I am today.
What are you planning?
Tell me what to do to stop it.
Today is the day of my mad tea party,
to which you've been invited.
I'm fairly certain you'll attend,
and Catherine will be delighted.
But how can that be,
if you're stuck here,
and still the guest of honor?
I guess you'll see,
as we drink tea...
And someone ends up a goner.
Catherine manipulated my dad
15 years ago,
and here she is, just doing it again.
My dad is the head of the Crows,
I mean, how is he even falling
for this...
Alice has been on a killing spree
since you got back,
and this is what's got you
drinking Bruce's good stuff?
Alice was brainwashed
against her will.
Well, this is different,
my dad, he's choosing...
He is choosing to forgive
a woman who
lied about the death of his daughter.
Catherine paid a team of scientists
to change DNA results.
My dad once found a joint
in my backpack
and grounded me for a whole summer.
It doesn't make sense,
this is not him.
This isn't him.
What am I missing?
If you're calling with a lecture,
I don't have time.
The opposite, actually.
I know complicated
better than anyone else.
And if you want to work things out
with she-who-must-not-be-named...
It's not my business.
Well, I appreciate that, kiddo.
And in thinking about it,
I realize that
I... I never really gave her
a chance.
Remember the wedding,
the big snowstorm,
and I just kept wishing
that maybe if we got snowed in,
you wouldn't have to get married.
If only a snowstorm
were our biggest hurdle.
Anyway, I just wanted to say
I'm sorry,
- and have fun tonight.
- Thanks, Kate.
My dad married Catherine
on the hottest day of the year.
- So if that's not your dad, then...
- It's Mouse.
So, you know those vacation days
we banked?
What if we took one of our
old school road trips?
I was thinking down south,
maybe Dollywood.
Sounds cool.
What is up with you?
I just suggested a road trip
to Dollywood.
Nothing is up with me.
Nothing, or you're pretending
to be cool about Kate and me
and you're obviously still freaked?
Ty, if this is going to be a thing,
we should talk about it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I wanted to go over tonight's agenda.
As you know, this is one
of the city's biggest nights,
so I need you two to run point.
Sophie, you take the Alpha team,
cover the interior.
Tyler, you're with Bravo
locking up the perimeter.
Teams are already down in the theater
beginning their sweep.
I want this evening go off
without a hitch.
Good evening, Gotham.
Tonight is the city's
Humanitarian Gala,
which is "rich person"
for "let's dress up
and congratulate each other
on being rich and dressed-up."
And it's all to honor
Hamilton Dynamics'
Matriarch of Munitions,
Catherine Hamilton-Kane.
Not sure how they're gonna fit
a Tomahawk missile
into a swag bag.
So I'm here en route
to the Humanitarian Gala
with the 'rents, what up?
Where mom is being honored
as the Gotham Giver of the Year,
hashtag "proud daughter."
I just want to take a moment and say
how thankful I am for family,
and for sticking by each other
through thick and thin.
That's what's all about.
To Catherine.
A most extraordinary woman.
Cheers.
Must be time to move.
You are becoming incessant.
And you are becoming predictable.
Whatever you have planned
for the Gala,
The Crows are already on it.
Tell me where Dad is.
Or what?
You'll have me arrested?
Institutionalized? Killed?
You hate him. I get it. I would too.
But he did not mean to hurt you.
You keep holding on so tight, like,
to the childish notion that Beth
is still in here.
If Beth is gone,
then why did she keep this?
You saved this for the same reason
you saved me from The Rifle.
Because despite the hate,
the resentment, the rage,
there's still good.
There's still Beth.
So tell me where Dad is.
I left him in the same place
he left me.
Thank you.
Kate?
He's not doing so well,
you might wanna be quick about it.
Hi.
I assume we have everything in order.
Ten-four, Commander. All good here.
Gotta hand it to you, Mouse.
That's impressive.
But if you're not Jacob,
then you're...
Not a Crow, oh, crap.
To date, the Hamilton Foundation
has donated countless millions
to fund work in the health,
emergency relief, poverty,
and education sectors,
both globally and in Gotham.
All of these philanthropic efforts
are spearheaded by Catherine herself.
I can think of no one more deserving
of the Gotham
Humanitarian of the Year Award
than Catherine Hamilton-Kane.
Thank you, Dr. Campbell,
for that wonderful intro,
and to Mayor Akins
and the City of Gotham
for this great honor.
When I took over this company
from my father,...
Tyler.
Wake up!
What happened?
Commander tranq'd us.
What?
Help! We're here!
One-way windows, sound-proof walls.
No one can hear us or see us.
Kate was right.
Alice's new minion
is impersonating Jacob Kane.
I'm still way too drugged up
to process that.
Alice must be planning something
at the gala.
Which is why she took us out.
I thought Alice was more of a...
slit-open-our-necks
and pose-us-for-a-tea party
type of murderer.
Ketamine's a little dull, no?
She didn't want to hurt us.
We're talking
about the same Alice, right?
She's trying to preserve
some sick relationship with Kate,
and killing me would...
Killing you would mean Kate
would never forgive her.
Because Kate's
still in love with you.
I have no idea.
And what about you?
Any idea how you feel?
We should probably figure out
how to get out of here.
Today, Hamilton is a household name
in technology innovation...
Tonight...
You honor me as one
of Gotham's heroes...
An honor that I...
Bought and paid for...
Quite literally, with...
blood money.
My company makes millions
by putting weapons of war
in the hands of Gotham's criminals.
My husband...
rakes in even more
by protecting you from them.
Dad.
Quite the scam we've been running,
wouldn't you say?
What my husband doesn't
want you to know
is that the true villains of Gotham
don't go by the name Joker...
Or Riddler...
Or Alice...
Gotham's true enemies
are right in front of you.
I...
I... I...
Mom! Oh, my god.
Orpheum Theater, we need medics.
You hang in there, sweetheart.
You're okay.
Hello?
Something's happened to my mom.
She's breathing, but we need
medical help immediately.
You keep an eye over them
until I get back.
Oh, my god.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna meet the medical help
- and bring them here.
- Okay, all right.
- Hang in there, sweetheart.
- Okay.
Oh, my god.
- I don't have a choice.
- It's okay.
Just stay with me.
Stay with me. Help is on the way.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as we get medics
for Mrs. Hamilton-Kane,
please stay in your seats.
There's no cause for alarm, please.
Everything's under control
stay in your seats.
There's no need to panic.
The Crows are holding us.
Get us out of here.
Okay, I'm in position.
Batwoman is here! Let's pounce.
- A little left.
- Trying.
No. Other one.
- Got it.
- Nice.
I'm really regretting not getting
you a bigger one of these
in this moment.
- I wouldn't have wanted it.
- Sure you still want this one?
- Tyler.
- It's a little hard to ignore
the irony of using
the engagement ring I got you
to escape your ex-girlfriend's
lunatic sister who didn't kill us
because she knows more
about your past relationships
- than I do.
- What do you wanna know?
What was it between you two?
Don't say it was just
some drunk college hook up
unless you were actually drunk
for three years.
Look...
All my life I've followed the rules.
My family's rules, the Army's rules.
This was the first time I broke one
and it almost cost me everything.
That's why I lied.
You didn't answer my question.
Let's go get some help.
Commissioner, with all due respect,
I need your men to stand down.
She's infiltrated the Crows.
If you breach, we're all dead.
- Why isn't Jacob back?
- He'll be back soon.
Your husband won't be joining you.
Get me the tray.
Catherine, you don't look so well.
You stay the hell away from us.
I'm not the one
you should worried about.
For it was all very well
to say "drink me,"
but you should have first look
to see whether
it's marked "poison" or not.
You poisoned her?
Group effort.
I use the Catherine Hamilton
recipe.
- Project 4782 ring any bells.
- Four-seven-eight-two?
Catherine, do you want to tell her?
I think her internal organs
are liquefying.
I'll just tell you.
It's a deadly neurotoxin designed
to kill without mercy.
First, there are the dizzy spells
and then nosebleeds,
and then comes muscle paralysis,
and, oh, respiratory failure.
But, lucky for us,
Hamilton developed an antidote.
Okay, mother,
you just got to hold on
until we can get that antidote.
Oh, no, my dear,
I'm confusing my stories.
Hamilton never even bothered
to develop an antidote.
If she dies, I'll kill you myself.
She made a choice.
Maybe if she made better choices
in the past,
we wouldn't be here right now.
You're just gonna let her die.
Mary, my darling,
impetuous step sister.
I'm... I'm not a total monster.
No.
- No.
- I found the solution.
A universal cure-all,
all the way from Coryana.
Where's Coryana?
On a map or two.
It's made from the desert rose
that blooms only on the island.
One prick of its thorns
can kill you on the spot.
But harness the flower
and nurture its serum
and it gives your life.
What do you want?
A simple apology.
For all the pain you've cause me.
I'm sorry... Alice.
I could just don't believe you.
Get me eyes on Alice and Jacob.
She said she was sorry.
Do you think I enjoy watching
a daughter lose her mother?
No.
I was just inches
from my own mother's.
Severed head floating
down the Gotham river.
After our car plummeted
off the bridge.
Oh, please...
Please just try.
I can't loose you. Please just try.
I'm a mother.
Alice.
When I saw Kate grieving,...
I saw my own daughter.
I just wanted to take away
your pain.
But in trying to take away
Kate's pain,
I gave you a lifetime of it.
It's all my fault, Alice.
All the lost years,
all agony you endured,
It's all my fault. It's all...
I'm truly sorry.
Thank you, Catherine.
I do believe you've earned
a draught of this tea.
- Oh, dear, not you too?
- What?
Oh, what did you do? How did you...
Tell me you didn't both drink
the champagne.
Oh, that's such a shame
it means there's only enough
antidote for one.
Dad drank the champagne, too.
We need to find him.
He'll be fine. He knows better
than to poison himself.
- What?
- He poisoned you, Mary.
Jacob would never hurt us.
Getting closer.
You had someone impersonate him.
What?
The skin pirate.
There was an escapee from Arkham.
That wasn't Jacob in the limo.
There you go.
Now, what were we talking about.
Yes?
They're choices we make.
Do choose wisely.
Okay.
If we split it,
maybe there will be enough time
to get to the emergency room.
No, no, Alice,
would have accounted for that.
No, Mom. We have to try.
- Okay, we have to try.
- Mary, listen to me.
- Drink it.
- No, there has to be another one.
Mary, I'm your mom.
- No.
- Drink this. It's okay.
Did you do it?
Jacob's drugged
and I put him in the SUV.
- Good.
- He doesn't know what happened.
I have to go.
You're too late.
Where's my dad?
Our dad.
You'll find out soon enough.
Whatever you did, you can undo it.
But I don't wanna undo it.
I was locked in a cell for 11 years.
What do you think put me
to sleep at night?
Rainbows? Unicorns?
I dreamt of revenge.
What did you do?
It was all very well
to say "Drink me,"
but the wise little Alice
was not going to do that in a hurry.
Oh, come on.
It's sounds like Catherine
didn't have it coming.
You poisoned Catherine?
Catherine poisoned Catherine
when she slithered into our family
and brainwashed our father.
And replaced us with that vapid
human-run-on-sentence of a daughter.
Catherine brought this on herself,
and I was more than happy
to watch Daddy go down with her.
That's what I thought.
We need to go.
One way or another dear sister,
you'll come to see my way.
Hang on, Mom.
They'll be here, pump your stomach,
and we'll find an antidote.
You just need to hang on, okay.
I always wanted...
To see you work at your clinic
How did you know about the clinic?
I've always known.
How come you never said anything?
The fastest way for you
to stop doing something...
was for me to approve of it.
Oh, my god.
Do you know how many wardrobe
changes
I did in that elevator
thinking that I was fooling you?
Cameras in the elevator.
Mom?
Mom.
Yeah.
- Mary...
- Yeah.
You're the one thing I did right.
Nothing makes me prouder
the way we raised you.
Mom.
No, no, no. Mom, mom, mom.
Stay with me.
Wake up!
Mom, please.
Mom!
What is this?
- Kate?
- Who is this?
What? It's, it's me, Kate.
What did you get me
for my sixth birthday?
- What?
- What was it?
It was a bike.
It was too big for you.
You wrecked it the same day.
What is going on?
Alice and Mouse were at the gala.
Get out of the car commander.
- Dad?
- I'll call you right back.
What's going on, Commissioner?
Hands in the air, Kane.
Commissioner.
Jacob Kane, you're under arrest.
I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
I've never seen that before
in my life.
What the hell is happening?
Get your hands off of me.
Gotham is in shock tonight
over the death
of Hamilton Dynamics
CEO Catherine Hamilton-Kane,
allegedly at the hands of her husband
and head of Crows Security,
Jacob Kane.
Her death occurred
just after some stunning
and very public admissions
by Hamilton-Kane
while accepting an award
Gotham's Humanitarian Gala.
Mary.
Do you know how many horrible
people that are saved?
Drug user.
Thugs with face tattoos.
Pulled a windshield out of a guy
who stole the car that he totaled,
and he walked out of my clinic
the next day
like nothing had happened.
But I...
I couldn't save her.
- I'm so sorry, Mary.
- You know, how she died?
Exactly the way
that Alice planned it.
Slowly...
and in pain.
And the only way for her
to save herself
was for me to die,
and she sure as hell
wasn't about to let that happen
because she is not
the horrible person
that you and Alice claim that she is.
You...
You are literally the last person
who can bring me comfort right now.
I'm gonna ask you again, Kate.
Is Alice worth it?
- No.
- Finally.
Too bad it's too late.
Agent Sophie Moore.
Yeah, it's been a late night
for us, too.
Just put me on with the Commissioner.
He's got the wrong guy.
Because I've got a dart hole
in my neck to prove it.
Please have him call me.
This is insane.
How can they think
he actually did this?
People believe what they're told.
It's human nature.
Then people are idiots.
- I should call Mary.
- I want kids.
What?
And dog, and family traditions
that we bitch about
but do anyways.
Okay.
I don't want to move past this today
and then have it come up
again in two years
and realize I'm wasting my life
fighting for something
I can't actually have.
I don't want that either.
Do you love me?
Yes.
Are you in love with me?
Because if you love me
you'll be real with me right now.
I don't know.
Then let's not make this
any harder than it is.
I think you need to figure
yourself out.
And when you do and if you see
the same future, I do.
I'll still be here,
and maybe I won't.
We all make choices, Bruce.
I choose hope.
And I chose to believe Beth
was still alive.
I chose to save my sister
from the monster she's become.
But by making that choice,
I lost my entire family
for the second time.
And now the only thing
I'm left with this awful truth
that Alice was right.
Beth is gone.
My lawyer could only get us
five minutes.
I hate her so much, Dad.
When I get out of here,
I'm gonna put her down
once and for all.
And I won't stop you.
For so many years
I've traveled across worlds...
Across a multiverse to do one thing
to kill you.
And now over here...
You saved my life.
Submit and begin your life anew.
Show me.
The knowledge is with in you.