So, the monster who ripped this
family apart all those years ago
has brought us all back together.
Irony, you are one sick bitch.
And you, my darling sister,
are my hero.
We're finally putting Cartwright
to rest.
Knock it off
or your hands go back in the cuffs.
Take a load off, Daddy.
Farewell, Mr. Caterpillar.
Give my regards
to the Queen of Hearts.
How you holding up?
I'm not sure I am.
Kate, do not waste
your guilt on that man.
He does not deserve it.
So, we just pretend
it never happened?
Tried it, doesn't work.
Let's be honest.
Your brief sojourn into my hellscape
is but a flicker of my
every waking day for so many years.
Now, my Mouse is out in the world
alone, battling his greatest fears.
I need to find him.
We find him together.
I think we have very different ideas
about what happens to Mouse
after we find him, so...
Alice, stop. I cannot let you...
But you can.
It is amazing how distracted you get
when you find out
that both your daughters are killers.
Oh, a friendly reminder.
Your DNA and your DNA
is all over that body in the ground.
So, it's probably best that you
let me slink back into the shadows
where nobody has to hear about this.
Family reunion's over.
I never see you again. Understood?
Admit it, Batty.
Guys like me give you purpose.
Never again.
Do you understand?
Go!
Go.
My dad wants me to put
Cartwright behind me.
But it's not that easy.
I went to a dark place, Bruce.
To avenge Beth, Alice, my mom.
But in saving my sister,
I became more like her.
And in taking out a killer
I became one myself.
What does that make me now?
Any luck last night?
- With?
- Finding Cartwright?
Because I've got nothing on him
or any of his aliases,
and the thought of Beth's killers
still being out there...
Just tell me you found something.
Nothing on this end either.
Okay.
Bad news?
It's my mom.
Reggie Harris' post-conviction relief
hearing was moved up.
Reggie Harris.
The guy that killed your dad?
When did it get moved up to?
Today.
- Well, I'll come with you.
- No. There's no need for that.
Harris was found at Sip and Dash
with the murder weapon
and my dad's blood all over him.
So, what's there to review?
- Luke...
- Kate, seriously, I'm fine.
If you wanna be helpful,
find Cartwright, okay?
Mouse? Have you returned home?
Hello?
Evil henchmen? Is anybody there?
What a curious plan.
Who did this?
I got four cameras' worth of footage
missing from the Sip and Dash
on the night Lucius Fox was murdered
and a 50,000 dollar cleanup fee
sent from the Crows to Alia Nazari,
the Sip and Dash owner.
You think the Crows paid Nazari
to lose the tapes?
Who?
That's what I need you to figure out.
I don't trust anyone else to look
into it.
You must be scraping
the bottom of the barrel, sir.
You suspended me for lying.
I still haven't changed my opinion
on Batwoman.
I think we can both agree that this
is bigger
than two different opinions.
There should have been footage
of Fox's murder.
There wasn't.
Let me see if I can meet with Nazari
and get her side of the story.
This has to stay between us.
Consider me back on payroll.
Hey.
I got your text last night.
Late.
Like up-when-you-shouldn't-be late.
Just checking in to make sure
you're good.
Your mother was a beautiful woman.
It would've been a pity for her
to go to waste.
You stole everything from me!
Kate.
You missed a spot.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I've come to ask for your
assistance in locating someone.
Let me guess.
You needed help finding the guy
who put Dad in jail
and killed Catherine.
Both done at my request.
Didn't he also try to kill you?
And yet I still forgive him.
Choosing to see the best in him.
Ever tried that?
All the time. Never works out.
When I was dosed with fear toxin,
I relived all my worst fears.
If Daddy hadn't saved me,
there's no telling
what I would've done to myself
or anyone else
to make the horror end.
- The Crows will find him.
- The Crows won't hesitate
to put a bullet in his head.
You don't want another death
on your hands.
I want you to leave, Alice.
That is precisely the plan.
Once I find Mouse, I will flee
this wretched city for good.
Why should I believe you?
My cats and rabbits are dead.
What are you talking about?
Let's just say subtlety
is not a defining characteristic
of someone I wronged in the past.
Who?
Careful, Kate,
you're starting to sound interested.
Just help me and you will never
have to deal with me again.
Fine.
But on one condition.
We do it my way.
Considering your way
involved strangling a man
until he choked
to death on his own blood,
I would love absolutely nothing more.
Kate, everything okay?
I thought I'd offer a hand
in the search for Mouse.
Oh, we got our bases covered.
Take a load off, kiddo.
- Get some sleep.
- I'd sleep better if I knew
there were one less lunatic
on the streets of Gotham.
Yeah. You and me, both.
Mouse attacked a nurse
outside of Arkham last night.
- Nearly killed her.
- Arkham?
Why would he go back there?
Well, we'll figure it out.
Get some rest.
- I'll call you when we get him.
- Thanks.
Why is Mouse attacking nurses
outside Arkham?
He lived there for years.
A real fan favorite.
The warden, Dr. Butler,
an all-around vile waste
of a soothing voice,
used him as a guinea pig.
Subject Mouse to fear toxin,
gauge its effects
and have the nurses pull him
out of it.
And then start all over again
the next day.
Do you think that Mouse
is still feeling the toxin?
Cartwright dosed him for days.
I'm still...
shaking off the effects
after only one afternoon.
I can only imagine the hell he's in.
Maybe he's looking for someone
to pull him back out of it.
Someone like one of his former
nurses.
What are you doing?
Just checking to see
if we're the same size.
Why?
I do the talking.
Go ahead.
- Hello?
- Hi.
I'm Agent Kane and we're with the
undercover unit of Crows Security.
- Oh. I'm not in trouble, am I?
- No. But you could be in danger.
We're looking for one of your former
patients. Jonathan Cartwright.
Goes by Mouse.
Mouse?
Yes. He's a sweet boy,
but beyond help, sadly.
Oh, that's so sad.
We got word that he might
be coming here.
Here? He's locked away at Arkham.
He escaped last year.
And we think that he's been targeting
his former nurses.
Do you mind if we wait inside,
so we can grab him if he comes?
Please. Come in.
Can I offer you anything?
Just finished making some brownies.
- We're good.
- A brownie would be nice.
Seriously?
We buried a body this morning,
when did you have time to eat?
All rise.
The court is now in session.
The honorable Judge Wellington
presiding.
You may be seated.
This is the case
of the People vs. Reggie Harris.
What are you doing here?
I heard about what was happening
today.
And I appreciate
the whole I-need-to-be-alone thing,
but as someone
whose parent was just murdered
and the killer was never brought
to justice,
alone is not where you need
to be right now.
Thanks.
Where's your mom?
She barely made it to the funeral.
Imagine her being in the same room
as my dad's killer.
Mrs. Nazari?
Mrs. Nazari, it's Sophie Moore.
Couldn't have rigged that
to be any closer, could we, love?
What the hell just happened?
I work
with Special Reconnaissance Regiment.
We intercepted a communique someone
was offering a handsome bounty for
your head.
When I saw your name, I came calling.
We need to get out of here.
Sorry, how do you know my name?
You're Kate Kane's ex, right?
Well, so am I.
Julia Pennyworth. How do you do?
And I'm happy to tell you everything
I know, but,
can we deal with this first?
- You sure you don't want any?
- Positive.
More for me.
Are you trying to draw attention?
Who? Me?
- Wanna try?
- Nope.
It's really fun?
Because you can't,
and you don't want to admit that
I'm better at something than
you.
Exactly, Alice.
Nurse Tammy!
He's here.
- My poor Mouse.
- Get the adrenaline.
Nurse Tammy!
Please.
What are they doing here?
- Did you call them?
- No.
- Do not lie to me.
- When would I have called them?
- I've literally not left your sight.
- Get out of my way.
Alice, stop. You go out there,
they will shoot you too.
Don't you move.
Hands in the air.
Take him to Arkham.
How did they know he was
here?
I called the Crows.
All that time spent working in the
asylum, you think I can't
- Kate are you in there?
- spot someone who's
- Crows. Open up!
- selling me a story?
There he was, in our grasp,
yanked away by might.
But what's lost is not gone.
Whatever this is,
I want nothing to do with it.
When I was under
the influence of fear toxin,
of all the horrible
things I experienced,
the worst was being left behind.
By you.
I cannot sleep at night
knowing I left Mouse behind
locked in a cell.
You wanna break him out.
Yes. And you are going to help me.
We just took out an old lady,
I'm pretty sure that sister bonding
time is over.
It'll be a breeze.
When Mouse escaped last year,
he showed me all the ways
in and out of this place.
Sounds like you already have a plan,
so why do you need me?
As a recent escapee,
Mouse will be deemed high-risk.
Protocol will demand
that he be confined
to the most secure area,
the basement.
Far away from the other inmates.
Where your screams
echo against the walls,
until one day,
they become a friend screaming back.
Please. No, no, no. Come on.
Welcome back, Johnny.
We missed you.
I look forward to resuming your
therapy.
Please.
- Not that again.
- Oh, no, no.
There will be no escape for Mouse.
Access to his cell requires two keys.
The first is in the possession of
Dr. Butler.
The other stays
with the head of security.
Which is why you need me.
Two keys, two different places.
Two people.
You and me, sis.
Helping you find Mouse so
that you could leave Gotham
is one thing.
You're talking about breaking into
a high-security psychiatric facility,
distracting the guards,
and skirting the medical staff.
Oh and freeing a wanted killer
from captivity.
Does that sound insane?
I'm pretty sure it's a definition.
How fond she is
of finding morals in things.
I have to draw the line somewhere.
Yeah, but who arbitrarily decides
when and where those lines are drawn?
You?
Mouse is in custody. If I were
to help you break him out of there,
then how am I any better?
Don't you get it by now?
You're not.
I'm not a criminal.
And they say I'm the delusional one.
Here we are, two killers ourselves,
out and about
by the mercy of sweet old Daddy.
We aren't that different.
I never planned on hurting
Cartwright.
But I did.
See, I could have easily killed
him myself
and let you go on
being the city's symbol of hope.
But it was time for you to see
that you and I are one and the same.
You wanted this.
You left Cartwright for me to find.
You wanted me to hear your story.
You wanted to push me over the edge.
You set me up to kill him
so that I would be like you.
Kate, you can't give me all the
credits.
After all, it wasn't that hard.
You gonna kill me now too?
The court has reviewed
the defendant's case.
It's gonna be okay.
Judge Calverick has already signed
a statement indicating he cut corners
in order to close the
high-profile murder of Lucius Fox.
That, along with the defendant's
claims of a coerced confession
at the hands of a corrupt cop,
leads the court to believe that the
defendant has a basis for a retrial.
No way.
The state has the right to retry the
case at the DA's discretion.
Until then, the defendant
is free of his own volition.
This court is adjourned.
We're gonna fight this.
This is not over, okay?
I know.
Battle not with monsters,
lest you become a monster.
I'm afraid that passage wasn't
in the one book
I was allowed to read.
Someone once said it to me.
How did that work out?
I became a monster.
I know I've made light of things...
but I owe you a thank you.
Thank you for killing the man
who destroyed my life...
destroyed our family.
Do not feel guilty for what you did.
I... I don't.
The only thing I feel guilty about...
is that I don't feel guilty.
So now, you're scared
you're becoming me.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Would that really be so awful?
I'll do it.
I'll reunite you with Mouse.
But I need to be able to trust you.
Okay.
Say it.
You can trust me, Kate.
No one dies in the process.
Kate, have I ever lied to you?
Literally dozens of times.
Yeah, okay.
I promise...
no... one...
will die.
You can trust me.
What's this?
Well, we're breaking a killer
out of Arkham,
so you can't exactly go in
disguised as a flying rodent.
ID, please.
Code black.
Repeat! Code black!
Hands where I can see them.
What's going on?
Possible incendiary device
at the main gate.
Slowly exit the vehicle. Now!
That should be the guards
responding to our little decoy.
- Alice, if they shoot that driver...
- Oh, relax, he drives a linen truck.
Guards finding a fake bomb
on the axle
could be the most exciting thing
that's ever happened to him.
Well, that should take us up
to the maximum security wing.
Don't forget this.
Once we pop the cork on this bunny,
things are going to get crazy.
We're clear.
I'll get the keys from Dr. Butler.
And I'll get the keys
from the head guard.
Wait.
Remember your promise.
No killing.
You can trust me.
The doctor's not in, so...
you get me.
Careful.
I can take a hit, love,
but it's the clean-up after
that I've never been good with.
This is probably a good time for me
to say thank you.
It comes with the paycheck.
- Hi.
- Mary. Hey.
- We could use your help.
- Oh, my god.
I've met you before.
- You're Kate's...
- Ex.
I know. We covered that.
I was gonna say assistant,
but that's much more fun.
Julia will suffice.
British Intelligence, SRR.
Julia took a bullet that was meant
for me.
Which leaves the question,
who wants me dead?
Who's the other vic?
Witness in the case. Alia Nazari.
Someone's cleaning up their tracks.
I could not see outside, you know?
All this time, Mom,
- I'm telling you.
- Right.
- No, you didn't. No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did. Yes.
- You didn't.
- Yeah, I did.
You know I'm gonna eat them all.
I will. I will do whatever...
Go on inside.
I'll be right in.
You murdered my father.
I didn't.
I am sorry somebody did.
- Your pops seemed like a good guy.
- Don't do that.
Don't act like you knew the first
thing about my dad.
I know he was proud of you.
Getting into MIT.
How the hell did you know that?
You kidding?
Your pops wouldn't shut up about it.
Told everybody
in the store that night.
"My son, Lucas, is gonna
change the world.
You heard it here first."
Then why did you kill him, man?
The truth is,
I went into a Sip and
Dash for a bag of chips.
I woke up with a gun in my hand,
your dad's...
Your dad's blood all over me.
Look at me.
Tats, dreads, record?
Of course, I'm gonna convince a jury
I killed Lucius Fox.
I was the winning lottery ticket
for a bunch of punks who needed
to keep their own ass out of jail.
Hey, Reggie.
Help! Help!
Dr. Butler, I presume.
You're supposed to be dead.
You know, it's funny
how this place can make people feel
like they're losing their minds.
Even you, doctor.
What... what do you want?
I have long dreamed of meeting you.
Repaying you for all the pain...
you inflicted on a...
dear friend.
One quick swipe,...
another name off my list.
But a promise is a promise.
Now, where are your keys?
Thank you.
You'll live.
Legs crossed
You're messing with the best now
You're messing with the
Legs crossed
Messing with the best now
You're messing with the best now
You're messing with the best
You like a fight
when your friend's near
Now, you're alone,
You lay low because you smell fear
I left my conscience burning
in the tarmac
Load my ammo, click it back
Bang, bang! And attack, yeah!
You're messing with the best now
Alice! Knife!
Guess you do know how to use it.
You're messing with the best now
Hush, hush, legs crossed
Mouse.
It's me.
Alice?
What are you doing here?
You know I'd never leave you behind.
They don't take any chances.
Why are there so many straps?
Kate, help me.
What are you doing?
Open the door.
I can't do that, Alice.
You...
You promised.
I promised to reunite you with Mouse.
You wanted to be with your brother.
Now you are.
Why did you trust her?
It's over, Alice.
You can't hurt anyone anymore.
Me?
You are no better than me.
And you?
You and I are the same person.
We are no different.
Let's get out of here.
No.
No, no, no.
Kate, don't leave me.
Don't leave me. No, no, no.
No, Kate, no.
No. No.
No, no, no!
No, Kate, don't leave me.
Don't leave me.
No! Kate! Kate!
Don't leave me! No!
Arkham officials have her in
isolation on 24-hour watch.
Getting her to trust you,
alerting me, helping your city,
it wasn't easy.
Took a hell of a lot of courage.
It had to be done
and I had to be the one to do it.
I...
I moved the body.
She can't threaten us anymore.
It's time
to put Alice behind us.
Kiddo.
We will fight turn the tide
In this world of darkness
Oh, my god.
Luke, are you hurt?
Let me take a look at you.
It's Reggie's.
What do you mean it's Reggie's?
I went to go confront him,
but someone shot him.
- Who?
-I don't... I didn't... I didn't see.
GCPD thinks it was a hit.
Professional.
Reggie gets shot
the day he gets released from prison?
Earlier today, Alia Nazari was shot.
Who?
The woman who owned the Sip and Dash
where your father was killed.
It was a professional hit too.
Why would anybody wanna kill her?
Nazari obviously knew something
that someone didn't want her
to spill.
Luke.
I think there's a chance
that Reggie didn't kill your father.
Yeah. After everything
that's happened today, I...
I don't really know what to believe.
If Reggie was set up...
Then my dad's killer's still out
there.
We will rise like raging fire
Reggie Harris' freedom
was short-lived today
when he was gunned down
outside of his home
just a handful of hours
after he was released from prison.
Harris, who had previously been
convicted of manslaughter,
has long proclaimed his innocence.
His case was currently awaiting...
- No frills,
- one of many cases that...
but no questions either.
We'll be safe here.
Guy claims he was set up for murder
then gets killed the day
of his release.
Well, that's no coincidence.
This cover-up I've been looking into?
It's centered around Lucius Fox's
murder.
Lucius Fox?
Know him?
He was my godfather.
We'll figure out who's behind this.
Where you are going?
I need to check on Luke.
Calling from a burner phone.
That's never a good sign.
You were right about the Crows,
but it goes beyond tampering
with evidence.
Someone took out two people today
and they put a hit out on me too.
Who hired you?
This is what you wanted
Right?
At least that's what I thought
Someone's aiming to see double
tonight.
Didn't realize you were in town.
Came by to check on Luke,
saw you out here.
But it looks like I've walked in
on a party of one.
I'd like to keep it that way, if you
don't mind.
Sorry, love...
I do.
You don't have to say anything,
but a friend wouldn't leave
you drinking on a ledge.
Hardest time
When all you see is the tide
Going in and out
I'm not the hero this city thinks
I am.
I betrayed my sister today.
Put her in Arkham.
What compelled that?
I felt myself becoming her.
I killed someone.
Buried him.
I didn't feel an ounce of remorse.
Don't get me wrong
I don't know who I am right now...
I'm strong enough to hold my own
But I do know
that I do not wanna be my sister.
Keeping my head above water
You are nothing like your sister.
"It was a glorious victory,
wasn't it?"
said the White Knight.
"I don't know,"
Alice said doubtfully.
"I don't want to be anybody's
prisoner.
I want to be a queen."