Never thought we'd be
pouring one out for Oliver.
We're not gonna wait for Barry?
I don't think he's ready
to say goodbye.
So, anybody wanna say
some words for Oliver?
He sacrificed himself
for me and Barry.
- He shouldn't have done that.
- His sacrifice
saved a billion more people.
Let's not call that a mistake.
Look, Oliver died
the way he lived. A hero.
Not to rush a tender moment,
but I think the multiverse
is ending soon-ish, so...
No, I can't. I can't. Barry's right.
It feels like giving up.
We managed to get
billions of people to safety.
There has to be a way
we can undo this.
Oliver, my mom, Argo, Earth.
All those Earths.
All those people who vanished.
There has to be a way
we can get them back.
Or we focus on stopping it
from happening
to every other universe.
Oh, hey, welcome to the joy zone.
- Where's Dig?
- At home with JJ.
He still doesn't know about Oliver.
- Lyla, you...
- I know. I just...
I need to figure out how to tell him.
- Yeah.
- You can't just hijack
the Waverider.
Our crew is still on there.
If there is any chance
at surviving the Crisis,
- we need its technology.
- Who?
Yeah, I kind of promised our crew
they'd never have to do
another crossover.
We don't need your crew.
Just Ray's lab.
And we have an entire multiverse
of Waveriders at our disposal.
- Is anyone here?
- Welcome aboard.
My name is Leonard, an interactive
artificial consciousness
programmed to operate
this vessel's critical systems.
I know who you are.
Always pleased to meet a fan.
But you're trespassing.
Any preference
on how you'd like to die?
What he's saying is "Flame or frost?"
I thought the Legends
of Earth-74 are all retired.
We did. Well, some. One died.
No, one was using the ship,
so I took it.
It's my ship.
- Why are you here?
- I like the quiet.
He's trying to be a writer.
- Shut up.
- Of romance novels.
Well, you can see how that's going.
It's going fine, you piece of...
You're basically living out
of your car.
- Listen, snowflake, I'm just...
- Boys.
Come with me, Mick Rory.
And I promise
you'll have plenty of beer
to drink and stories to tell.
The multiverse needs saving.
And its heroes need a ship.
You had me at "beer."
You have all lost a great hero.
The wrong hero.
I do not disagree.
You have suffered a horrible loss.
But you have every reason
not to lose hope.
Seven, in fact.
Across space and time...
Across space and time
exist seven heroes,
beings of the purest will,
who can ultimately...
- Sorry. Could you...
- What?
Beings of the purest will,
who can ultimately...
It's not working.
No.
Beings of the purest will,
who can ultimately defeat
the Anti-Monitor...
and help save the multiverse.
- They are known as Paragons.
- Paragons?
And you're just dropping this
on us now?
I only recently learned
of their existence
by consulting the Book of Destiny.
How? We destroyed it last year.
After Oliver's early demise,
I went back into the time stream
and retrieved it intact.
It is now safely stored
in this ship's library.
So, it's, what, plan B?
It's comforting.
Anyone else wishing
they'd done that shot?
But wait.
If the book can rewrite destiny,
can it bring back Earth-38?
Or any of the other Earths?
Trying to recreate an entire world
would surely drive one to madness.
What about my dad?
Could it bring him back?
I wish it could.
While Oliver Queen was to die
in this Crisis,
this is not how I saw events unfold.
But as the Anti-Monitor
gets stronger, I grow weaker.
We must find all seven Paragons.
- How about, like, a hint?
- I have four.
Kara Zor-El,
despite all you have endured,
you are the Paragon of Hope.
Well, you might wanna
double-check your omnipotence.
Because I'm not feeling
that hopeful right now.
Sara Lance is the Paragon of Destiny.
Oh, well, that makes sense.
Captain of time travel and all that.
I have only descriptions
for the other two Paragons.
One is of a second Kryptonian
who is said to have suffered
a greater loss
than most mortal men could endure.
Today, he stands
as the Paragon of Truth.
- I'll find him.
- I'll go with you.
- And the fourth?
- The Paragon of Courage.
He's known only
as "the bat of the future."
Seriously,
where do you get these names
and pseudo-names anyway?
I enlisted the assistance
of Felicity Smoak,
who earned the wisdom
of a second book.
- A lot of books.
- The Tome of the Guardians.
It revealed the names of Ms. Zor-El
and Ms. Lance
as well as the other two.
Bummed-Out Kryptonian
and Future Bat,
which technically means...
Earth-99 exists in a future time.
Where Bruce Wayne
has dedicated himself,
body and soul, to fighting crime.
I'm sorry. Go back.
Bruce Wayne is the Dark Knight?
If we could all keep that
to ourselves, that'd be great.
The path to find him
will lead you
to the Paragon of Courage.
Okay. Who wants to meet Batman?
An entire universe
wiped from existence
distilled down
to a computer graphic.
Gotta say, missing that wow factor.
- Lena killed you.
- Yeah. Only for a little while.
Everyone has a part to play,
even Lex Luthor.
You did this?
You brought
that poisonous snake back?
His destiny was unfulfilled.
Lex Luthor still has
an important role to play.
So, you could revive him,
but you can't bring back Oliver?
I restored Luthor
long before the Crisis
caused my power to wane.
And what about
those innocent lives on Earth-38?
Did they not have destinies
to fulfill?
I'm sorry, but I can't trust
a man who thinks
Lex Luthor is an ally.
All I got from that
is that if you die again
that dude can't bring you back.
- And you are?
- New.
And unfriendly.
Lex Luthor. Kind of a dick?
When I think of all those people
on my Earth
that we wanted to save
but couldn't...
It just feels unfair.
Look, a day ago, I didn't think
my life could get any worse.
My sister murdered my stepmom
and... and framed my dad for it.
That's dark, even for Gotham.
I'm fighting for a chance
to make it right.
And this fourth Paragon,
my cousin Bruce on another Earth?
Finding him might help me
get that chance.
Only if you believe the Monitor.
What kind of talk is that
from the Paragon of Hope?
Come with me.
Let's go save the universe.
Stop...
Stop him. Before he finds the book...
Stop him before he finds the book.
Find the book. Stop Lex Luthor.
You're not supposed to have that.
And man was never meant to fly,
but here we are.
Goodbye, Superman. All of you.
Stop him!
Lex Luthor has the Book of Destiny.
He's going to use it
to kill Supermen.
If he kills the Paragon,
we're all doomed.
- What have you done?
- As I said,
everyone has a part to play.
I'm glad you're here.
Me too.
And from what you told me,
the Monitor was wrong about Oliver.
So I don't know, Barry.
Maybe he's wrong about you too.
Maybe you're not supposed to die.
Listen, Oliver told me
about how he brought Sara
and his sister back to life
using something called a Lazarus Pit.
I don't know.
That sounds too good to be true.
Well, maybe it is.
It turns out Thea destroyed
all the Pits on this Earth
but there are more Earths
to choose from.
I know that you want Oliver back
more than anything, but this is...
He can't be dead.
Not him.
Okay.
Funny enough, the Monitor gave me
a mission of my own.
To find our hopeless
Kryptonian Paragon.
Do you ever think
this would be our life?
I will take whatever life
with you I can get.
So I missed one group chat,
and now there's Paragons,
and I'm supposed to be one of them?
Yep.
And Barry and I
are gonna use a Lazarus Pit
to bring my dad back.
Mia,
it's not that simple.
The Lazarus Pit
isn't some magical mud bath
where you get your soul
in a cup of cucumber water
at the end.
You lose your humanity.
Nyssa told me everything I need
to know about Lazarus Pits.
And she told me everything
I need to know about you.
Why don't you share your opinion
when it's about your life?
when it's about your dad?
So the Paragon of Courage
is apparently afraid of yard work.
Better let me do the talking.
Wow, that's
a really impressive six-pack.
Sorry, do I know you?
- No.
- No, but I know you.
Well, a different, like,
a less this version of you.
I... I'm... I'm Kate Kane.
I'm Bruce's cousin.
Yeah, no.
- Earth-One villain?
- Only friend, actually.
Oh, well, at least he's cute.
No. Let's not make that weird.
That's weird.
- Can I just... Okay.
- Please.
You need to leave. Now.
Don't be so rude, Luke.
You'll have to forgive him.
We're not used to having guests.
Kate?
Bruce?
- Where is Luke taking Kara?
- Library.
Just while we get to know
each other again.
Another Bruce I knew wore
a different kind of suit.
Lifetime of injuries.
But you've aged well for a dead girl.
I died?
Five years ago.
Never been a ghost before.
Plenty of ghosts in this place.
But you're not one of them.
Clayface is a puddle of mud.
And last I checked,
Jane Doe was locked in Arkham.
So, who the hell are you?
Can you...
Can you sit in that thing?
Because you're gonna need
to for this.
- Hang on.
- What is it?
Iris.
We have a new problem.
It turns out Lex Luthor is alive.
- What?
- According to Iris,
Lex is jumping
from universe to universe,
killing off Supermen.
If one of them's
the Kryptonian Paragon...
It's game over.
We need to find this Earth's Superman
before Lex jumps here and offs him.
I think it's a little late for that.
"Disappeared into thin air."
Lex killed him and breached out.
He won't stop until we're all dead.
You're sure you wanna do this?
- Lazarus Pits. Nasty business.
- We're sure.
Hey, we don't have a lot of time,
so could you please take
your smoke break later.
- Maybe just do the spell?
- Simmer down, Speedy.
This is the spell.
It's all in the wrist.
What is it? Some kind of star map?
Parallel Earths. Spread out
by vibrational frequency.
We are well and truly bollocksed.
So many Earths already gone
and more vanishing as we speak.
I give you the needle
in the celestial haystack,
an Earth
with a functioning Lazarus Pit.
Okay, well, now what?
Perhaps a thank you?
And a little well-earned awe
for a magical job well done?
How about I thank you
when you bring my dad back?
- Hey, come on. Let's go.
- Yeah.
We can't screw this up, okay?
When we bring back Oliver back,
I need you to promise me
you can bring back his soul.
See, yeah, one thing at a time,
right, love?
- I need to hear you say it.
- I'll do it.
- Thank you.
- To the best of my abilities.
Is that him?
It's either him or the buff guy
on the paper towel rolls.
I can do that with one bare hand.
Hello.
- Hi.
You are Clark Kent, right?
Can I help you?
Yeah. Hopefully.
So this universe
and an infinite number of others
is in the process of blinking
out of existence,
and there are seven people
in all of space and time
who can supposedly...
Lex Luthor is gonna try to kill you.
- Lois.
- He is.
- Lex?
- Yeah.
I didn't know the president
was in town.
Look, I've faced
a lot of things, things...
Hello, old friend.
Who are you?
Don't you know me, Clark?
I'm Lex Luthor.
You're not Lex.
Maybe not the Lex you know.
The multiverse
has a way of aligning fates.
What'd you do with those people?
Sent them back to
their flying tin can in the sky.
Let's hope they learn
from this teachable moment.
- I'm here for you, not them.
- Whoever you are,
I'm just a guy working on his farm.
You will always be
my greatest enemy. On any Earth.
It's written in the stars
and in this book.
Or I wouldn't know
that on this Earth,
Clark Kent is Superman.
Where I come from,
that would be ridiculous.
He can't see past his glasses.
- So, what do you want?
- Why, to kill you, of course,
and every version of you
across the multiverse.
So that if the Superfriends
somehow find a way
to save existence,
there won't be a single Superman
to stand in my way.
That's kryptonite.
Which has no effect on me
ever since I gave up my powers.
You "gave up" your powers?
Can't say I've missed these chats.
You were basically a god.
You could fly.
You could see through walls.
You had super strength.
You're kidding me.
That is worth more than
any superpower.
Hey, Clark. The girls want
to show you what they made.
I think it's time for you to...
I'm still stronger.
You took all the fun out of it.
Enjoy your little slice of
mediocrity while you can, Clark.
You're all doomed anyway.
Hey.
Was somebody here, or were you
talking to the cows again?
It was Lex Luthor from another Earth.
Apparently, the multiverse is ending.
Smallville, you made a funny.
It's taken you about a decade,
but you're getting the hang of it.
- What'd the girls make?
- A mess.
They can't wait for you to see it.
Sounds like a job for us.
Paragon of Courage?
Yeah.
You're a few years too late.
"Reign of terror"?
It's like a wise man once said.
"Battle not with monsters,
lest you become a monster."
I've lost track
of how many people I've killed.
The Bruce I knew had a code.
You start with a code.
You hang on to it
with every self-righteous breath,
but then you take one life...
Then another and another
and another...
You'll see.
My Kate...
My Kate put on the cape,
thought she'd succeed where I failed.
All she did was get herself killed.
Well, I'm not her.
And I'm not an old man
held together with wire and metal.
Fine.
You're a broken,
pissed-off old hermit.
Waiting to die in this
11-bedroom, seven-bath coffin.
But, apparently, you're needed.
I'm giving you the chance
to be a hero again.
And not just to Gotham.
To the whole damn universe.
Mick, if you could...
I just... I really need
to concentrate
if I'm ever gonna finish
this Paragon detector
- the Monitor asked for.
- Sure.
"Once he awoke her desire,
he was hers to explore willingly."
- Is that your...
- Caged Passion.My romance novel.
- Your only novel. Self-published.
- Still counts.
Mick, your book doesn't sound
too kid-friendly.
It's very friendly. Kid loves it.
Look at him.
Anyway, chapter 19.
"As he caressed
the nape of her back,
he struck like a cobra."
You like that? So do I.
It's my best writing. Anyway...
Now, this is a newspaper.
Ray tracked Lex's last breach
to this Earth,
so he can't be far.
Well, let's find him, me,
Clark, before Lex does.
Oh, excuse me. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- It's my fault.
- It's mine.
Mine.
I'm sorry. You seem so familiar.
Have we met before?
- He looks just like Ray Palmer.
- Who?
Hey, nice glasses.
Thanks. Do you have a second?
Sure. For a citizen
of Metropolis, always.
If you wouldn't mind contacting
my assistant...
It's about Lex Luthor.
How did you say you knew Kate?
Oh, I didn't.
We're still sort of getting
to know each other.
What are those?
Mementos.
From Batman's greatest victories.
You mean trophies.
Yeah, those belonged to Superman.
His alter ego at least.
Bruce killed this Earth's Superman?
Who do you think put him
in that exoskeleton?
Yeah, big mistake.
I appreciate your concern,
but this isn't my first go-around
with Luthor.
I can handle him.
That's what you're not hearing.
He's changed the game.
Yeah, the book allows him
to do anything.
He made us vanish
right in front of the last Clark.
What is this?
Perry White. Jimmy Olsen. Lois Lane.
Why are all these names
on your wall?
The reject from Gotham felt
that we didn't cover him enough.
So he played what he called
a practical joke...
- And gassed the building.
- All these people died?
My friends,
my wife...
I lost everyone in one fell swoop.
Almost as if you've been
through more loss
than any mortal man could endure.
I think we just found our Paragon.
We need you to come back with us.
I know this sounds insane, but...
You might be the key
to saving the multiverse.
That's actually one of the least
insane things I've ever heard.
First, stay and face Luthor.
And you won't do it alone.
- We won't let him kill you.
- Oh, I've moved on from that.
I never thought I'd say this,
but I'm tired of killing Supermen.
So much more fun making Superman
kill Superman.
You don't belong here.
We're here because we need your help.
Help? I couldn't even save
my wife, my friends.
I don't care about your universe.
Yes, you do.
You're the Paragon of Truth.
There's only one truth.
I serve Lex Luthor.
Kal, stop.
Oh, what did Lex do?
You have to get Luthor
out of your head, Kal.
The multiverse needs you.
And what about what I need?
Come on, honey. You got this.
Kal, no.
Let me show you how it feels
to lose the ones you love.
- Oh, my god.
- Get away from the window.
This should be fun.
You can read about it later.
Help me with the book.
Okay, picture the Clark that we met.
Focus on what the universe knows
he's meant to be.
There's only room in this world
for one of us.
I'm pretty sure it's not working.
It's like, it's like Lex turned
all of his love into hate.
Love.
Clark, this isn't you.
Not the real Clark,
the one that Perry White respected
and Jimmy Olsen looked up to
and Lois loved.
You know nothing about me or them.
They know more than you think.
They would want your memories
of them to lift you up,
not drive you to darkness.
That's the truth, Clark.
And the truth
means everything to you.
Remember who you are.
You okay?
Actually, this is the second time
I've gone nuts and fought myself.
I can see why you married her.
Yeah, this is the place.
Yep, that's clean enough.
I'll clear this out.
All right. We'll go get Oliver.
Are you sure
that you wanna do this?
More than anything.
Yeah.
Your father wouldn't take no
for an answer either.
When I think of
all the stupid stuff we got into
when we were your age,
it's amazing
we didn't get arrested more.
Arrested more?
But you're way smarter than him.
You get that from your mom.
Seems you little ladies had tied
your horse to the wrong saloon.
This mine is off-limits.
I don't care who owns it.
We need to use this pit.
Well...
I'm sure we can come
to an arrangement.
- The mine is ours.
- The hell it is.
I guess you were gonna get
this scar eventually, Hex.
Ease up, cowgirl.
The mine's yours. The mine's yours.
Nice.
So, did you change your mind
about us using the pit, then?
I miss Ollie too.
Did we miss something?
Just put him in the water.
See for yourself.
I can barely walk,
let alone wear that again.
Do you understand
how many people, how many worlds,
are going to die?
If they're anything like this world,
maybe that's for the best.
How can you even say that?
There was no hope for this world.
That's because you killed Superman.
This guy is not a Paragon
of anything.
I was right.
We can't trust the Monitor.
What did you do?
- Clearly, what you couldn't.
- How was he a threat?
Strange visitor from
another planet comes to Earth
with powers and abilities
far beyond those of mortal men?
Clark.
Clark always said yes to anyone
with a badge or a flag.
He gave them too much power.
My parents taught me
a very different lesson.
Life only makes sense
if you force it to.
A little souvenir
from the old hometown.
- It's not working.
- Just give it some time.
Guys, Mia's right. This isn't...
- You good?
- Nice one.
Dad.
- You tranq'd him?
- I tranq'd his body.
We still have to get his soul back.
That isn't Oliver yet.
The Kate I knew didn't trust
anyone, let alone a Kryptonian.
I don't know what happened
to you, Bruce, but it ends now.
Yes. Let it end.
Let it all end.
This world's not worth saving
in any universe.
If you really think that,
you're gonna have to kill
one more person. Me.
Don't be a fool.
Don't! It'll kill you.
Kate,
listen to me.
There is no hope.
So, do you have
a gluten sensitivity too?
No, not that I know of.
Congratulations.
You're a ringer
for a filthy Kryptonian.
Mom must be so proud.
Kid was a piece of cake.
There you go.
There's someone I want you to meet.
Hi, there, handsome guy.
He looks just like my son, Jason.
Well done.
You have succeeded in finding
the Paragon of Truth.
Lex Luthor played his role.
- He led you to him.
- Yeah?
How many more people
did he hurt to do that?
You think you're a good guy,
but you're not.
I think he's kind of neat.
Okay. Well, we still only have three.
Bruce Wayne wasn't the Paragon
of anything, so...
Ray, you are looking jacked.
No, no, no.
This is your cousin. Sort of.
Okay. So Batman tried to kill Kara.
And now he's dead, so we're doomed.
We shall see.
I believe Dr. Palmer's work
is now finished.
At least I think it is.
I've never actually built
a Paragon detector before.
Okay. This'll be the trial run
to find the final three.
Everyone might wanna
take a step back.
- And which Earth is that?
- None of them. It's us.
This ship.
Apparently,
there are still a few bugs.
Your machine works just fine.
That light is the Paragon of Courage.
Yeah, well, Bruce's body
isn't on the ship, so...
No, but you are.
I said the path to Earth-99
would lead you to the Paragon.
That has come to pass.
You are the bat of the future,
Kate Kane.
You are the Paragon of Courage.
- What?
- Yes. Something's wrong.
This is...
It's never happened before.
With all the antimatter
in the system...
I've lost my magical mojo.
If we can't get Oliver's soul back,
- he's gonna be a monster forever.
- Yeah.
Do these things even work on you?
Not really.
But you looked like you could use
a drinking buddy.
Yeah.
Time travelers. Aliens.
I have barely even started
this whole vigilante thing.
How am I a Paragon?
I've seen you in action.
You saved me.
And last year, you saved
Oliver and Barry's asses.
Thank you very much.
That's accurate.
How much you care,
how hard you try,...
those are the things
that make you a hero.
Not powers or time travel.
And you may not feel like
you have the experience now,
but you have the heart.
You're one of
the bravest people I know.
That Bruce was brave once too.
And he had heart.
What if I end up like him?
You won't.
You'll make your own destiny.
I found this in his library.
That's Beth and me.
From Earth-99.
I wish I knew her like this.
Maybe you still can.
Sounds like the Paragon of Hope
just got her hope back.
No.
Hope, help, and compassion for all.
That's what I'm gonna do
for Earth-38.
- But Earth-38 is gone.
- I know.
But maybe I can use the Book
of Destiny to bring it back.
The Monitor said that would be
really dangerous, Kara.
I know what he said.
But what good is being
the Paragon of Hope
if I don't have any?
Stop. Please, stop.
Come to me, Harbinger.
It is time.
Lyla Michaels.
Harbinger.
I need you.
Who are you?
Universe after universe
has fallen before my power.
World after world consumed.
With every death,
I steal my mirror's strength,
and mine grows ever stronger.
Who am I?
I am the Anti-Monitor.
Come, Harbinger.
There is work to be done.