Damn.
Watch where you go,
I'm an animal
You don't wanna dance,
don't wanna dance
Sure, babe. Whatever you say.
Oh, oh, with the devil-oh
Watch where you go,
I'm an animal
If you dance with the devil oh, oh
I'm going for the jugular
What... what the hell?
Are you insane?
I can't feel... Anything.
I think you'll find that's
to your great advantage...
Babe.
I'm an animal
An animal
Watch where you go,
I'm an animal...
It wasn't supposed to be Beth.
We did everything right.
We found a loophole.
We kept her alive.
We got her through the checkpoints.
I thought we were in the clear
and then, it just...
It just came out of nowhere.
It wasn't your fault, Luke.
Look, we need to figure out
who shot her.
I agree.
First, we need to prepare ourselves
for the real Alice.
The Crows think
that she's dead and she's not
which means no one's
out looking for her.
And if my twin picked
my alien doppelganger's
life over mine,
I'd be on the verge of going nuclear.
No offense.
You're right.
I looked her in the eye and told her
I chose to save someone else.
Kate.
You did the right thing.
You have to know that.
It doesn't matter
because the wrong Beth lived.
Now, Alice is back on
the loose because of me.
We need to brace ourselves
for the consequences.
Mr. Kane, Mr. Kane,
how does it feel to be exonerated?
Any day that justice prevails
is a good day in my book.
You've proven you were framed
by Alice and her gang.
What are your next steps?
Return to the Crows
and restore peace to this city.
Look, Alice is dead.
Gotham is safer because of it.
At the end of the day,
it's all that really matters.
What do you plan on doing?
Gotham knows her as Alice.
But here at county morgue,
she's simply Jane Doe 7-1-1-3.
No name, no medical history.
No next of kin.
Could we have a moment, please?
My own daughter, one of Gotham's
most diabolical killers
dead on a metal slab.
After everything, it seems there
should be so many emotions but...
all I feel is hollow.
It was destined to end this way, sir.
The bullet wasn't one of ours.
You radioed in and said you
had her in your sights.
What... what happened?
Call off the shoot-to-kill
order on Alice.
- You're kidding?
- Let me find her.
Tell the Crows to stand down.
I didn't have a lock.
The target kept moving.
Well, someone got her anyway.
Side effect of making an entire city
your enemy.
Tick tock.
Oh, silly Mouse.
What is the purpose of a rendezvous
spot if only one party obliges?
Yes?
This is all that was left
in his hospital room.
What do you mean "left"?
Where'd you get this?
I took it off Beth.
After...
Thank you.
So, I ran the mystery shooter's
partial plate.
And?
The three numbers I remembered
don't match
a single registered Sedan.
I think the plate was stolen.
Not only did we let
an innocent girl die
but I can't even bring her
killer to justice.
Mary's making reward flyers
for any info on that vehicle.
We'll find something.
In the meantime, though,
we still live in Gotham
where there's plenty
of justice to dole out.
Maybe this will take
your mind off things.
- A vampire?
- A wannabe vampire.
- You're not serious?
- That's kind of my point.
Lately, things have been
a little... too serious.
You could use a distraction.
Then bring me
an old-fashioned bomber
or an arsonist, or someone
that exists in the real world.
- Apparently she does. Nocturna is...
- "Nocturna"?
Is Night-Bite taken?
She seduces her victims, drains their
blood and leaves them for dead.
It's all very early 2000s.
Both victims were lured out of clubs
on the strip in Old Gotham.
Crows are replacing every doorman
so I thought, we should patrol
the only other bar
in the neighborhood on that street.
It's a place called The Catch.
That's a janky old fisherman's bar.
It's not really her demo,
but what about Curse?
EDM? It's invite only?
Oh! Oh, Curse.
The... Yeah, yeah, right.
Okay, yeah, I thought...
I thought you said, "Purse".
Which is why I was like,
"A club called 'Purse'?
- That'd be weird."
- You have no idea what I'm talking
- Not a one, no.
- Cool.
So, does this mean you're suiting up?
I've always wanted to slay a vampire.
Got something.
One Vic, female, bound, unconscious.
No sign of Nocturna.
Scratch that. Found her.
And I found you.
Vampire, bat.
It screams duo to me.
- I work alone.
- I heard that.
Flattered, but you're not my type.
But you're mine.
I'm a universal recipient.
Seeing double? Losing sensation
in your limbs? Don't fight it.
What did you do?
I've always wondered
what bat blood tasted like.
Too bad, Batsy.
I do hope we get to do
this another night.
Okay, I'm reading your stats.
She injected you with a paralytic.
- I got that.
- And you have six Crows incoming.
I got that, too.
I'm gonna hit you
with an adrenaline shot.
It takes about 30 seconds
to kick in.
I don't got that.
Modulator, now.
Copy.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Save her. She's unconscious
but she's still alive.
We've got medics coming.
We need to hurry.
Thank you.
I thought you said
we needed to hurry?
You're gonna get my ass fired, so...
So?
So... next time,
I'll have to bring you in.
Which means there can't
be a next time.
Understood.
- Could've been anywhere.
- Got it with you?
No, I don't.
It's clear. I've got the victim.
Check the roof.
You heard her. Move out.
I'm more than happy to run your blood
but you don't seem
like you have the flu.
I've been, pulling all-nighters
doing real estate courses.
And that's like germs galore.
- You know you can tell me anything.
- Right. Yeah.
So, maybe these
perceived flu-like symptoms
are a manifestation
of the guilt you feel?
For choosing Beth over Alice?
And even though Alice
miraculously survived,
you drew a line in the sand
you can't erase,
forever altering the dynamic
between you and your twin.
- You got all that from a blood draw?
- Kate, I'm serious.
Look...
Beth deserved to live.
Do not think that there
is not one single minute
that goes by that
I'm not remembering her.
Her warmth, her spirit.
Her laugh.
Okay, that's weird.
- You have Special K in your blood.
- Ketamine?
You want to tell me how
that happened?
I was partying pretty
- hard last night.
- Partying?
Someone must have slipped me
something.
I thought you said you were taking
real estate classes?
I was. No one wants to learn
about zoning laws sober.
- Thank you.
- Kate.
Temporary paralysis was a result
of Nocturna injecting you
with an animal tranquilizer.
That's gotta be her M.O.
It wasn't really an injection.
It was more like a bite,
nibble, lip thing.
- TMI.
- I'm just saying
she had actual fangs
that delivered the ketamine.
Like when she bit down on my lip.
Understood and moving on.
Since the encounter was so intimate,
we may be able to get something off
the suit's UV detection system.
Behold, 600 watts of 95 percent UVA
and five percent UVB.
It works great for fingerprints...
counterfeit money,
checking out motel bed spreads.
Yet somehow, Nocturna didn't leave
a single trace.
Well, if we can't track her down,
maybe we can draw her out.
Please don't say blood drive.
We know she's targeting club-goers.
Maybe your little black light
will come in handy after all.
- We're having a party?
- We're having a party.
Alice may be gone...
So is the city's trust.
We are hemorrhaging clients not
because we're weak
or ineffectual, or indecisive.
It's because, for the first time
in four years, we have competition.
The city likes Batwoman
because she doesn't subscribe
to the rules.
It makes her entertaining.
She gets to dress up,
cause whatever mayhem she chooses
and zip-line away
to cheers and adoration.
That is not how protecting
a city works.
And now, there is a new predator
on the streets.
Nocturna.
Let's find this blood-guzzling serial
killer before Batwoman does.
Let's remind everyone
what real authority
actually looks like.
Like you never left.
Know anything about this?
Mary's Instagram page?
As little as necessary. Why?
She's posting about a grand opening
tonight at Kate's bar.
I thought it was still
several weeks off.
Probably not the best night
for an opening...
considering Nocturna's
targeting club-goers.
You want me to go
and keep an eye on things.
You better get it
Better get it girl
You better get it girl
You better get it
Mary's here.
Did we just lure a vampire
to us using a bar full
of walking blood bags?
Theoretically, yes.
Technically, no.
Think of our high-res facial
recognition cameras
as a sort of digital garlic.
If Nocturna shows, we'll get her.
Though so far,
the most suspicious woman here
has three outstanding
parking tickets.
What?
Is that Sophie?
Better get it girl
You better get it girl
Someone write my obituary
because I am dead.
Thanks, but I'm just blending in.
I'm here for work.
Well, you are definitely working
something.
Come with me.
So, that's the Sophie?
Yes.
She broke up with you, right?
Because...
I'll be in the field.
Sparkling water.
With a little vodka.
Mary, I'm working.
Oh, I know. So does everyone
else in here. You need to chill.
I need to find Nocturna.
She drugged Batwoman last night,
nearly killed her.
I didn't hear that.
- No one did.
- Except you.
I'm getting a strong whiff
of Earl Grey. Spill.
I may have freed her
before my guys could bring her in.
- Really?
- Tell your dad and I'll kill you.
This is way too enjoyable
for me to squander.
Tequila, please.
- Sophie, come on.
- What?
What?
No.
Sorry, did I just totally cut in
between you guys
like the rudest person ever?
No, you're fine. We were just...
Hi, Elle.
Sophie.
Guess who almost wore
that exact dress tonight?
I'm glad I didn't.
I would've felt incredibly less than.
Oh, I'm sure you would've looked...
Great.
Oh, my God. Fantasia, hi!
- Mary.
- BRB.
So, Sophie, what do you do?
Base to Kate, we've got a
legit lead here.
Elle Scatlin, 28, dark hair,
arrest record
and works in veterinary medicine.
Which means she has access
to ketamine. Which one is she?
Well, she's... The one
all over Sophie right now.
Sir. I was just coming to find you.
We were able to grab
the surveillance footage from
inside the warehouse.
- Do you know who Nocturna is?
- Unfortunately, no.
I have a dozen other things
I need to be dealing with.
Sir, I'm the only one who knows
about what's on here.
If you choose to do nothing,
it can completely vanish.
But I do think you need to see it.
If you don't wanna see me
Did a full 180, crazy
Thinking about the way I was
Sophie's just working her.
Just trying to figure out
if it's Nocturna.
Convincingly so.
No one is that funny.
She seems to be a little funny.
So, we can either sit here
and make a reaction video,
or you could go out and figure out
who Elle Scatlin is yourself.
I'll look like a jealous ex.
Or a hero who catches
a serial killer.
You go if you're so eager.
You're Batwoman.
I'm wearing the glow-in-the-dark tie.
Is Sophie doing
the nervous napkin fold?
Oh, smiling, blushing, folding.
You are never leaving
the Batcave again. Okay?
Okay.
Crow Security.
And here you seem so promising.
I take it you're not one of our
clients.
My family used the Crows
when I was a kid.
I used to love having Eddie
walk me to school
and having the guys
protect the house.
So, what changed?
I grew up.
I realized they were more
of a status symbol
than actual protection.
And if I'm going to root for someone
who skirts the law
and lacks accountability,
it's gonna be Batwoman.
And the head-to-toe black leather
certainly doesn't hurt.
It's not leather, actually.
It's bullet-proof nanotech.
Supposedly, nothing
like it on the planet.
Intimate details.
You two ever thrown down?
On the house.
Kate, hey.
Thanks for the drink. I'm Elle.
Kate. Hi.
Oh, dear.
Mary Hamilton, right?
Andi Ostergaard.
- I follow you online.
- Oh, okay, right.
So, how do you two know each other?
We don't. We just met.
And we're already
having our first fight.
- Batwoman. Pro or con?
- Batwoman?
Oh, that is definitely
gonna leave a mark.
Oh, my God.
Sorry. Blood makes me...
Can I get some water?
I'm sorry.
I'm a light-headed blood wimp.
- Everything okay, Kate?
- I think so.
Duty calls.
Be careful with that knife.
I will.
I drive an i8, the new one.
Never really saw myself as a Beemer
chick, but it's pretty sweet.
So, you here with anyone or?
- What?
- Mary.
Hey, I was waiting for you outside.
My bad. I thought
that you said by the bar.
Sorry, are you guys?
- Oh, my boyfriend's brother.
- Together.
Okay.
I'll let you two sort that out.
See you on socials, Mary.
- Don't drink and drive.
- Yeah. Okay.
Kind of went a long way
to make clear I'm not your boyfriend.
- Does your tie glow in the dark?
- Yes, it does.
I actually love that.
It's not her.
You positive
or you just got uncomfortable?
- Who are you talking to?
- Kate.
- What?
- No. Not you, Kate.
- I'm talking to Mary.
- Why are you talking to Kate?
I thought you were her real estate
assistant.
Associate.
With a hidden ear piece
to direct-line into his boss
at a club on a Saturday night?
Kate's needy.
I need you now.
I have to go.
He's so strange.
I'll call the GCPD.
I got it.
Kate, we have a club full
of innocent people.
I said I got it.
Where is he?
- Where is who?
- Mouse. Where are you keeping him?
No idea.
Then this was a waste of my time.
We should talk about what happened.
Talk?
Why?
Do you think letting me die
on a linoleum floor
got lost in subtext?
I get it, Kate.
I mean nothing to you.
The Crows think you're dead.
You got a second chance, Alice.
You had a second chance
to save me and you didn't take it.
Instead, you chose
a complete stranger.
Beth wasn't a stranger.
Don't you get it? She was you.
The kind, compassionate,
good version of you.
The version of you
I thought you could be.
The version who couldn't survive...
despite everything you did
to keep her alive.
That's rich.
I guess this is the new normal now.
I hope she was worth it.
What did you tell me
from the beginning?
"Don't let her in your head, Alice.
She is changing you, Alice."
And what did I do?
Answer me, Mouse!
What did I do...
exactly...
my sweet, innocent, Mouse?
I ignored you.
I said I was in control.
I was stronger.
I would win her back.
But I was wrong.
And my sister let me die.
You're right.
I mustn't let her get in my head.
I can't.
Why should I care
what she thinks of me?
Why should I care if
she doesn't love me?
What about Willow Martin?
She fits the physical description
and she has a record.
No. She was livestreaming
a concert last night.
Rhonda Schifino is a possibility.
Goth, arrived solo.
Found her puking tequila shots
in the bathroom.
She's going through a breakup.
I'll add her to the "no" pile.
We gonna talk about this?
I know you called the police.
That's what people tend to do
when a serial murderer shows up.
We're currently in the process of
inviting a serial murderer in here.
- Now,...
- Nocturna's different, okay? She...
What? You can say it.
She can't get to you
the way Alice does.
Look, whatever hope I had
for Alice is gone.
No guilt- trip that she can put on me
will change that.
Wait, who is that?
Natalia Night, 27.
Adopted by a Charles Night...
who's a janitor at
the Gotham Cathedral Church.
He died of a heart
attack two weeks ago.
Right before the killing started.
Natalia was born
with a unique type of porphyria.
Okay, she can't be exposed
to sunlight
and her kidneys have trouble
cleaning her blood.
That's why she needs fresh blood.
And if Dad was a caretaker
and he died...
Then Natalia was left
to her own devices.
Got an address?
No, but I have Wayne's cameras.
Try to find out where they're going.
Look, you wanna top yourself off,
be my guest.
But pretty soon my...
"Check engine" light's gonna go off.
That's how this works.
You've seen my face.
And you've seen mine.
I don't want anyone
to know I'm alive.
And you don't want anyone
to know what you look like.
So get your fill, let me go and...
No one has to be the wiser.
My fill, Alice, is every last drop.
So try to relax.
Adrenaline adds a nasty aftertaste.
- You're making a big mistake.
- Heard all the lines, sweetie.
No. Seriously.
See, you are running around Gotham,
drinking gas station whiskey...
when there is a beautiful...
500-dollar bottle...
of Beaujolais...
Just sitting on the shelf.
Okay, Alice.
You can color me intrigued.
We have Crows all over the Strip
but no leads on Nocturna yet, sir.
I wonder if Batwoman has one.
You working with her?
With Batwoman?
I've had a few run-ins with her...
Have you ever helped her
and has she helped you?
Sir, I assure you,
I'm a Crow through and through.
You are the last person
I expected to see.
- Where's Nocturna?
- Wish I knew.
Unfortunately,
I've been a little tied up.
Have a good night.
Hello?
Oh, girl, you are a little too drunk
for those shoes. You all right?
- I'm fine. I just... I need...
- Yeah.
Let me get your hair, at least. Yeah.
Thank you. You're sweet.
What did she inject me with?
Ketamine. It'll wear off soon.
Lovely.
Rope she used on me was red.
I've seen colored ropes like this.
- They're bell ropes.
- Bell ropes?
From a church. Every bell has
a different color, like notes.
Luke, does Gotham Cathedral
have bells?
Let me check.
Why did she start to fill these up
and then stop?
I don't know.
- She's fickle.
- She's meticulous.
She doesn't leave a victim
until they're bone-dry.
I'm sorry that my being alive
continues to disappoint you.
You're hiding something.
Why didn't she kill you?
I told you.
I have no idea.
You should be dead.
I know, Kate.
You did everything in your power
to make sure of that.
Gotham Cathedral does have
bells.
However, it's abandoned.
Hasn't held mass in over a year.
Headed there now.
Mary! Mary!
Touch me rough
and I'll make you mine
You won't break me
Oh, hit me with your thunder
She's lost too much blood.
What's her type?
B negative.
Well, looks like I drew
the short straw.
You're A Positive.
I'm O Negative. Universal donor.
I don't have a lot left.
It's been a bit of a day.
This should be enough
to get her heart started.
No, I won't seek cover
You can pull up a chair and watch
or go catch Nocturna.
If you so much as...
Kill her? Look at her.
It's me or nothing.
Go.
No, I won't seek cover
Come in with your best shot
Oh, you know I won't stop
Till I'm 6ft under
Your little fantasy is over.
I think it's just starting.
For the record, killing people,
not sexy.
You see victims. I see kids
with perfect skin,
perfect kidneys, perfect lives...
who pollute their blood with every
toxin they can get their hands on.
So, they deserve to die?
And I do? I never even had a chance.
No!
Yes, I let her go.
Nocturna was on the premises
and I thought Batwoman could help...
Help us?
Do you have any idea
what kind of position
you put me in here?
Answer it.
- Sir, it's not important...
- I gave you an order.
Agent Moore.
Nocturna is on the roof
of Gotham Cathedral.
- Cuffed.
- I have to go.
Sir, we could use the help.
Look. While you were in the jail,
we practically turned Gotham
into a police state
in order to find Alice.
We have no accountability.
- We're losing the public...
- Enough!
I woke up today thinking
my biggest problem
was the masked vigilante
running around the city.
It turns out my
biggest problem, Moore,
is that I no longer trust
my second-in-command.
You need to decide
who's team you're on.
Batwoman's or mine.
Now, you take some time
to think it over.
You're suspended.
Get out.
Hey, how are you doing?
I think I'm on sugar high.
Do you remember anything
about last night?
I remember Nocturna drugging me
and then performing some
ritualistic blood sacrifice
and then I passed out.
The next thing you know, Batwoman
brought me here and gave me these.
- I'm really sorry, Mary.
- It's not your fault.
Not to mention, the idea of Batwoman
going into a c-store
to buy me cookies is semi priceless.
Do you know
why Nocturna targeted you?
She said the blood
from the Desert Rose
- could cure her condition.
- Desert Rose?
Yeah, that super rare cure-all
that's supposedly in my blood.
Though I ran several tests
on my own sample last week
and it didn't yield anything
extraordinary.
How'd she know about your blood?
Honestly, she can have it.
It's caused us all way
too many problems.
I will be back later. I have to go.
Wait, you just got here.
How did Nocturna
know about the Desert Rose?
You mean, how did you know
that Nocturna knew
about the Desert Rose?
Yes, Mary is alive
because I saved her.
You sent her after Mary.
Of course I did.
It was Mary's life or mine.
And someone had
to choose me for once.
If you want me to feel guilty,
I don't.
I never will, not after everything
you've done.
See, I don't believe you.
I think somewhere deep down,
there's a teeny-tiny part
of you that's relieved I lived.
That you hadn't quite failed at
saving me.
And they call Nocturna a vampire...
When all you do is feed off my guilt
like the parasite you are.
So, you're saying
that you feel guilty?
What's the endgame, Alice?
Why'd you save Mary?
To prove to you how stupid
you were for letting me die.
"Stupid"?
Stupid was thinking
that my sister was redeemable.
Stupid was convincing
the Crows not to kill you.
Stupid was rescuing you
from the Gotham River.
Convincing Dad
that I could get Beth back.
Stupid was thinking
that you could ever,
ever possibly be worth it.
But maybe I don't want you
to give up on me.
Mouse only had two visitors,
you and a Dr. Campbell.
What do we know
about this Dr. Campbell?
Figured you'd ask.
Gotham's most elite plastic surgeon,
20 years of Lippo, rhino...
Now, this is interesting.
Six years ago, he took a sabbatical.
When he returned, divorced his wife.
Started specializing
in facial reconstruction
of child burn victims.
Six years ago?
What a long and sad tale you have,
Dr. Campbell.
Or should I perhaps
call you August Cartwright?
What do you think?
Is the caterpillar trying to convince
the world that he's a butterfly?
If so, I will follow him to you...
My little Mouse.
And together,
we will pull off his wings.
Put a stake in her,
she is done, Gotham.
Our local two-fanged menace
is en route to Arkham
thanks to Crow Security.
Turns out, they didn't need
a special undead division
for this bust.
Because Nocturna, aka Natalia Night,
is just your run-of-the-mill mortal
with a skin condition
and dental implants
that injected ketamine
into her victims.
- That said, she did do her...
- Ketamine.
- You have Special K in your blood.
- Ketamine?
Wait.
I need to find Nocturna.
She drugged Batwoman last night.
With a hidden ear piece,
to direct line into his boss?
I have to go.
Kate.
You are totally Batwoman.
I hate when you go
But I hate when you're here
I was fine all alone
I thought they banned this thing.
They did, but I couldn't exactly
slide into your DMs.
So my boss found out
we've been working together.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
Damn.
I have no idea
who I am without my job.
I know the feeling.
I mean...
I'm not even 30...
and I'm second-in-command of one
of the biggest security firms
in the country.
This is my dream job.
It's all I know.
It's all I've trained for. I...
It would be insane
to throw everything away...
I get it.
I'll keep my distance.
Wait.
Throwing everything off track
All your trouble
I'm in too deep
Now, I know what they mean
When they say it's serious
How could this be?
When we touch, it's a dream
Oh, you're making me delirious
This is love