Previously on "Batwoman"...
LUKE: Seriously, Kate.
You can't be going out
in Gotham every night
pretending to be Batman.
Catherine Hamilton's investigators found
bones, skull fragments of a little girl.
It's Beth.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Alice.
How do you do?
I think Alice is Beth.
I know that you want to
believe that Beth is alive.
I do, too, but facts are facts.
My father gave up on me,
and I want to make him suffer
the way that I did!
_
YOUNG BETH: "Will you
walk a little faster?"
Said a whiting to a snail.
"There's a porpoise close behind us,
and he's treading on my tail.
See how eagerly the lobsters
and the turtles all advance.
They are waiting on the shingle...
Will you come and join the dance?"
"Will you, won't you,
will you, won't you?
Will you come and join the dance?"
[CREAKING]
[RATTLING]
Aah!
[GASPS]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.MY-SUBS.com ...
Alice figured me out, Bruce.
I put on your suit to terrify her,
but it can't protect me
if she knows who I am.
I lost my advantage,
and in the process, I gave
Gotham their hero back.
I didn't sign up for this part.
I never meant to give
the city so much hope.
I can't do this.
I'm not you.
Subtle.
Hmm. I guess it's broken.
It's supposed to call Batman.
- What do you want?
- What happened to your Batsuit knockoff, Kate?
Too tight, no give,
or did you just realize that
you accidentally blew a dog whistle
that you can't unblow?
I wore it to protect myself
from you and your goons.
And in the process, you made
everyone horny for Batman.
All these poor souls
gazing up at the Bat-light,
thinking, "My life is about to change."
No. Still sucks.
Are you suggesting
that I put it back on?
No. Being a hero is
not your strong suit.
I would know, seeing as
you let Dad declare me dead.
Where's my boyfriend?
Hanging in there.
You like damaged men.
He's badly damaged.
You may want to get him back soon.
Okay. I'll play. How?
Show me you can stop killing people.
Last 24 hours,
and I'll reassess.
Rats!
I lost my pocket watch.
And I lost my sister: Beth. Remember her?
Yeah. I would like her back.
Ohh! You are going to be
very annoying, aren't you?
Very.
[SIGHS]
Fine. No killing,
but only for my darling Dodgson's sake,
not for Beth.
Beth has gone down, down,
down the rabbit hole,
and she's never coming back.
Much like Gotham's beloved... Bat.
You've worked hard to
get to where you are.
You deserve to feel safe.
Don't you want your kids
to be able to play outside again?
Elliot Estates are Gotham's
walls within the walls
with on-site 24-hour Crows security
and a safe room in every unit.
Have you been mugged?
Has your property been vandalized?
At Elliot Estates,
you don't ever have to
worry about that again.
How do I know?
I'm Tommy Elliot,
and I'm here to make Gotham safe again.
[GRUNTS]
Nice. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Now I am that annoyingly
overprotective husband.
You're married.
Yeah, yeah. Nice. Nice.
Are you happy?
Here. Lean in.
You're a little more
aggressive than usual.
What's the problem? You can't take it?
All right.
You need to move on.
Ha ha ha!
You know, most couples just
have breakfast together.
I've got an energy bar in my bag.
Oh. Can we split it?
[WATCH BEEPS]
Hmm. Well, front desk
says the commander's here.
I got to go.
[SIRENS ON COMPUTER]
You can watch it a million times.
Alice still gets away at the end.
No one's taken
responsibility for the attack.
Trail's gone cold.
Who'd want her dead when
she's already in custody?
Besides most of Gotham?
What can I do for you, Agent Moore?
I think I can be helpful, sir.
Considering Alice could
attack again at any time,
I was hoping to get your approval
for a special assignment.
VESPER: Okay, people.
Vesper Fairchild here.
So I'm staring at my wall chart.
Has it really been 10 days
without a Batman sighting?
Anyone else feeling ghosted?
Talk to me, Gotham. Where's Batman?
Just gonna pinch a little bit.
3... 2...
And... you're done.
Wow. You are so brave. High-five.
Ha ha!
WOMAN: ♪ Out of commission ♪
♪ Out of control now ♪
♪ It can feel like a shell
with no answer inside ♪
♪ And the paint, though, it's justified ♪
♪ Oh, but I cannot deal... ♪
Late night?
Sophie, hey.
If you're looking for
Kate, she's not here.
In fact, she rarely comes home.
You know, I wouldn't be surprised
if she was, uh, dating again,
seeing as she's single
and gorgeous
and emotionally available.
Do you normally stay out all night
when a psychopath is
targeting your family?
What was I supposed to do,
not go to Kylie Q's Glam Jam
and miss next summer's colors?
You're in danger, Mary.
Okay. Well, I also have a life, so...
So your father just
made me your bodyguard.
I'm sorry. What?
That is not your desk.
TOMMY: Shh.
Do you hear that?
That is the sound of me
officially having more money
than Bruce Wayne.
Tommy Elliot.
How the hell did you even get in here?
Oh. What's up, Candy Kane?
What? Bruce never showed
you the hide-a-key?
Wait. I thought you were... you were
buffing up on some
lesbian ninja retreat.
Why are you here, Tommy?
Come here. Check it out.
Now you see this building?
I just bought it.
5 stories taller than Wayne Tower.
Bruce and Tommy, childhood friends
who still act like children.
What is a friend?
A single sole dwelling
in two bodies, right?
Is that some secret society thing?
Heh. It's an Aristotle thing.
Gotham has gotten all intense
now that Batman's back.
I mean, have you heard?
Gotham's Dark Knight has
the city swooning again.
I saw the picture. Yeah. It was, uh...
Pixelated.
Wow. I... that's your reaction?
The guy had... your mom
and your sister in his win column.
He blinked...
And they died.
Oh, Kate. I thought you'd be more upset.
I've had time to process.
Batman saved your mom's
life a few years later.
Guess he's not a total
deadbeat, you know?
So, um, where's, uh, Brucey boy?
I wanted to, uh, invite him to celebrate
my new pile of bricks.
Bruce hasn't been in Gotham for 3 years.
- You know that.
- Yeah, but he's back now.
- No, he's not.
- Pretty sure he is.
Trust me. I'd know.
Well, maybe just leave it on his desk.
Will do.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Where are you?
LUKE: Where are you?
Needless to say, this is not what
Wayne's advanced weaponry
vault should look like.
The tech in here is top secret.
If something was taken, it's bad.
Had to be Alice's gang, right?
Did you pull the security footage?
They jammed the cameras.
It'll take a minute to
figure out what they took,
but in the meantime, I'll call Bruce,
tell him what happened.
You really expect him to answer?
One of his properties containing
millions of dollars worth
of weaponry was compromised.
If something was gonna
get Bruce's attention,
it'd be this.
What is this?
Not yours.
Two-way grappling hook, okay?
Twice the hook, twice
the chance for disaster.
POLICE RADIO: Possible 1054
at "Gotham City Gazette."
OFFICER: 10-4 on the "Gazette."
Clear the area. We're en route now.
Code 10.
Okay. You stay back,
figure out what they took.
- I'm gonna check this out.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God. This is horrible.
- Oh, my God.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
MAN: Who would do this to Batman?
_
KATE, VOICE-OVER:
I tried to be Batman, Bruce,
and I drew out your
enemies in the process.
Today, it's an effigy.
What happens when your enemies
start to kill real people
in order to draw you out?
The Gotham you set out to protect
is now less safe because of me.
VESPER: So what's the deal, Batman?
Are we really gonna let some loser
with a party store gift card
and way too much time on
his hands win this one?
Step out of the shadows
and into the ring.
Gotham needs you.
- MAN: Hey.
- MARY: Hey.
So you're really doing
nothing for my game.
Is there any chance that you could...
kind of looking for my
future husband over here.
Unfortunately, the Commander
was pretty specific.
We keep a-list clients within 10-15 feet.
Joy.
Biochemistry?
Not exactly fodder for small talk
at Kylie Q's Jam Glam party.
Uh... med student.
Kind of thought you
went to med school to...
look for your future husband.
So is my dad forcing Kate to have
a pocket Crow, or is it just me?
He figures since she'd
been offered a job with us
that it wasn't necessary.
That is so not fair.
So why didn't she take the Crows job?
I have no idea.
I mean, she finally
gets offered a position
she spent 5 years training for
and doesn't take it?
Doesn't make sense.
You know Kate.
She's crazy.
So what is she doing with herself?
I hear she keeps late hours, too.
So are you on this assignment
to keep tabs on me or on Kate?
Because I'm getting a very
distinctive jealous ex vibe.
I told her to move on.
You want to know why Kate's not a Crow?
It's because you're a Crow.
It's because 5 years
of training was easier
to walk away from than going to work
with the girl who broke her heart.
[LOUDLY] The Batsuit is made
of a military-grade Kevlar
woven with enriched carbon
nanotubes of my dad's own design.
- You're screaming.
- What?!
You're screaming!
Oh. Sorry.
This is a Desert Eagle Mark IX .50 AE,
one of the most powerful
handguns in the world.
It can literally blast
a hole through anything.
[COCKS GUN]
[PING]
Doesn't make a dent.
Yeah. You know, it stings a
little just, uh, for reference.
This... is a rail gun.
Turns out this is what the
thieves took from Wayne R&D.
It has a parallel
conductor that generates
a pulsed force of electromagnetism,
accelerating the velocity
of the projectile.
It's the most lethal weapon
that Bruce ever had built.
This is a prototype,
but for demonstration purposes.
[POWERING UP]
You're gonna fix that, right?
Yeah.
It's the only gun that can shoot a shot
strong enough to penetrate the suit.
Bruce had it built in case the
suit fell into the wrong hands.
Whosever in possession of
the gun can kill Batman.
I put on the suit, and I
dragged out one of his enemies.
Or maybe Alice doesn't like you
having her boy toy strung to a pipe.
If she has the gun, she
levels the playing field.
Except Alice doesn't know
that Bruce Wayne is Batman.
Whoever stole the gun knew
that Bruce had to have
the suit to test it on.
Yeah.
If they know that Bruce is Batman...
Let me show you something.
He's an entitled 1% asshat.
Now he's inviting you to show
off his new douche château.
- Point?
- The invitation wasn't for me.
It was for Bruce.
Tommy's adamant that he's back in town.
Why would he think that?
Because if Batman's back, Bruce is, too.
Tommy's parents were
in that car accident.
Batman pulled his mom from the fire.
- Why would he want to kill him?
- No idea.
I'll go ask.
Or you could be Batman.
Sorry. That just sounded like
Mr. That's Not Meant For You
wants me to put the suit back on.
If Tommy did steal the gun,
he is trying to intimidate Batman.
Go show him the Bat's
not afraid of anyone.
- He has that.
- Yeah, and you have that
and an entire city behind you.
That includes me.
Knowing Bruce, if he built a rail gun,
he built something that can stop it,
and I will figure out how to use it.
You're stronger than this guy, Kate.
Go kick his ass.
And if I can't, I let
down an entire city.
I'm not Batman, Luke.
[HUMMING "LONDON BRIDGE IS FALLING DOWN"]
Ahh.
[GLASS CRUNCHING]
WOMAN ON RADIO: All Crows,
be on heightened alert.
Hey. What are you doing?
Alice, wait, wait!
Oh. Kate's gonna be so disappointed.
SHAED: ♪ I've been havin' dreams ♪
Elliot party.
♪ Jumpin' on a trampoline ♪
♪ Flippin' in the air ♪
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
♪ I never land, just float there ♪
Oh.
Hey.
What is happening here?
Your dad assigned me as
Mary's security detail.
- That sucks.
- No kidding,
but what was I supposed to do,
miss the party of the weekend
because I have a full-time babysitter?
Can't have the Queen
of Gotham's party scene
go radio silent on socials.
What about you, Kate?
What brings you to an adult frat house?
I was told to move on.
SHAED: ♪ I never feel so loved ♪
We get it, Tommy.
Could you live any higher?
[DIFFERENT SONG PLAYING]
What can I get you?
Just looking for the man of the hour.
He's around, but if you
want to save yourself
from a verbal carwash
of veiled misogyny,
you might want to plant yourself here.
He'll be by soon.
In that case, I will have a beer.
I'm Reagan, by the way.
Kate Kane. Thought that was you.
Tyler. We, uh... we met a few weeks ago.
Sophie's husband. I remember.
You know, I hate these things.
Guy has 10 contracts with the Crows,
so we all come here to kiss his ass.
Well, at least you get
to work with your wife.
Yeah. You know, speaking of,
I... I didn't catch how you
and Sophie know each other.
What do you mean?
Well, she... she never
told me she was friends
with the boss's daughter.
She didn't tell you who I am.
No.
I'm Kate... from Point Rock.
Oh. Oh, you went to
the Academy together.
Right. That explains it.
That explains it. Ahem.
Well, boss is here.
You have a nice night,
Kate from Point Rock.
He married your ex and has no idea.
Wow! You're good.
Professional level. Started bartending
before I could drink.
You learn to read people.
All right.
- Read him for me.
- Tommy Elliot?
- Mm-hmm.
- Danger. Hazardous waste.
King of real estate.
Thinks he's doing us
all a favor when he really just helps
fund the walls that
are separating our city.
Gotham. Am I right?
Yeah.
Thank goodness. Someone
who loathes Tommy Elliot
as much as me.
Isn't he one of your biggest clients?
Unfortunately.
Well, I'm glad you're here, Kate.
It means you're not out
gallivanting with Alice.
You would tell me if she'd
reached out to you again, right?
I don't think Alice is
gonna be a problem today.
What's that supposed to mean?
Twin instincts.
Mom.
Security detail? Seriously?
Unfortunately, this is the
world we're living in now.
Well, I need my world to have
a little bit more elbow room.
I can't even reapply lip gloss
without getting poked by an AK.
KATE: Nice view of Wayne Tower.
Well, took half my life,
but I'm finally looking
down on Bruce Wayne.
What makes you think he's back?
We're cosmic besties.
And here I thought I
was his favorite cousin.
Not even a phone call.
Well, he's a busy man.
You're right. He's probably preoccupied
with that break-in at Wayne R&D.
They stole a specialized, uh, firearm.
That sucks.
Good news is the morons
who took it probably don't
realize there's a hidden GPS
tracker inside the device,
and... pbbb... it's only a matter of time
before Wayne Security come
knocking on their door.
Hmm.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Kane.
[CELLO PLAYING BACH'S
"CELLO SUITE NO. 1, PRELUDE"]
Who is this?
Heh heh. You taught me, remember,
or did you give up on music
like you gave up on me?
What are you trying to do, Alice?
You're not getting in my head.
Heh. You'd be surprised where
I can get into, Commander.
Where are you?
Well, I could tell you,
but that would ruin the surprise.
Let's talk until you're
finished tracing my call.
I never understood why
you stopped looking for me.
I always thought a father would do
anything to find his daughter...
Swim oceans, move mountains,
but now I get it.
You're on top of the mountain.
Heh. If I had this view,
I'd stop looking for me, too.
More time to enjoy your new life.
How'd you get in my house?
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Oh. You should be ashamed, Commander.
King of the Crows, can't
even protect your own nest.
I'm coming for you.
Maybe if you'd uttered
those words 15 years ago,
we wouldn't be here now.
I won't let you forget me, Commander,
not again.
- We need to leave now.
- What is it?
I'll explain downstairs.
Kane to Moore. Get Kate and Mary
in an armored truck until
I deal with something.
Copy that.
Mary.
What's happening?
Oh... I'm... okay.
- Hey. Where's Kate?
- Probably left.
I'll text her.
That's some gun you got there.
Ahem. Party's not in here, Candy Kane.
It's over, Tommy. This isn't yours.
You don't want to get in my way.
- How do you know who he is?
- You mean Batman?
Oops. Did I say that out loud?
How do you know that?
Oh, because a few
months ago I paid a man
to riddle me the answer.
Gotta love the honorable
Bruce Wayne for designing
a failsafe so he could never become
too powerful in his supersuit.
He is such a great guy.
He's your best friend.
Yeah, he was. The bestest.
Nothing could be average with Bruce.
Even had to have more
dead parents than me.
Because he saved your mom's life.
Oh, yeah. No. I am aware.
Thanks to him, instead of
collecting my inheritance,
I was left wiping the spittle
of a jabbering madwoman's
lips for 13 years.
If you wanted him dead, why wait
until he's in a bulletproof suit?
Because Bruce didn't ruin my life.
Batman did. Do you know what it's like
to have the villain of your
story be the hero of your city?
He is a monster, who left me anchored
to a repulsive, gold-digging bitch,
and now he's gonna die.
Well, that answers that.
Bruce's is bigger.
[BEEP]
[THUD]
Aah!
- Aah!
- Hold it!
[CLATTER]
What did you do?
You have Batman meet me on the roof,
or the elevators I just hijacked,
they start to drop.
Batman isn't here.
Yeah, because he's hiding.
It's time for Gotham's hero to man up.
Next one's in an hour.
It'll look like this
but with people the
city will actually miss.
[BEEP]
[SCREAMING]
[SIRENS]
Oh, my God!
[MAN GRUNTING]
It's my leg.
I'm so sorry.
You're gonna be okay.
Help him.
Okay? And then check all the elevators.
I swear I heard something crash.
Yeah. Me, too. Does
anyone have reception?
Moore to base. Check, check. Hello?
How is our signal dead?
Hello? FYI, I'm a
social media influencer,
so if you people don't
want a scathing review
of your building's safety,
you should hop to it!
No service. I hope Mary's okay.
Why did you pull us out of there?
- Alice.
- Alice?
Is she the reason we're stuck right now?
Very well could be.
She just called me from our penthouse.
What?
I swear if this is Alice
I'm gonna be so pissed.
They'll find us, babe.
MARY: Oh, my God.
What?
Nothing. I just totally
forgot you two were married.
3 years but still full of surprises.
Saw Kate inside.
You two went to Point Rock together?
Yeah, we did. Why?
Was it a secret or something?
No. Why would it be a secret?
I don't know. Why would
you never mention her?
She's our boss's daughter.
Didn't I mention her?
No, Soph, you didn't.
I don't know. We weren't that close.
Never occurred to me.
MARY: Anyone want to try
prying open the doors?
How the hell did she get inside?
I have no idea.
How can this city trust us to protect it
when we can't even keep ourselves safe?
- We'll contain it.
- We should have contained Alice
when we had the chance.
Trust me. That was the plan.
Kate threatened to
cut me out of her life.
What was I supposed to do?
All right. I'll go and
help pull you out, okay?
SOPHIE: Okay.
Okay. Come on.
All right. We should split up and see
if anyone else is stuck.
Okay.
- I know what you're gonna s...
- I didn't say anything.
LUKE: Why are you here?
He's gonna drop another one.
I know that. All those
people are hurt because
I put the suit on.
- It's not your fault, Kate.
- It is, Luke.
It is my fault.
I brought this to Gotham.
Tommy today, someone else tomorrow.
This is on me.
You said if anything was gonna get
Bruce's attention, it would be this.
I need you to be real with me.
Do you think he's coming back?
- Luke.
- No.
Tommy wants Batman.
The city needs Batman,
and I am not Batman.
But maybe I'm better because I'm here.
How long's that gonna take to fix?
- There aren't enough.
- What?
EMTs.
Ma'am, how are you feeling?
Ma'am?
Any head pain, headache?
This woman needs help now.
We already checked her.
Well, check her again.
Mary, they're professionals.
You're a second-year med student.
She's got a headache and a blown pupil.
Could be a subdural or
an epidural hemorrhage.
I read ahead.
You're right. Thanks.
KATE, VOICE-OVER: Your friend
Tommy wants to kill you, Bruce,
and since you're not here,
it looks like I'm gonna
have to kick his ass
on your behalf...
And send a message to anyone else
who'd come after you,
but to do that, I need
to be honest with the city
that I'm not you.
I'm me.
[SIRENS]
[CAPE FLUTTERING]
[FLUTTER]
[GRINDING]
[PLINK]
You're not Batman.
That's the point.
Who the hell are you?
I want Batman, not his side piece.
I found Tommy.
Activate the disruptor in the gauntlet.
When the light flashes green,
his gun will neutralize.
Yeah. That's not happening.
- Did you charge the glove?
- Wait. What?
Where's Batman?
Okay. Activated the charge.
You need to stall for 30 seconds.
Unh!
Stalling.
[CLATTER]
[GAUNTLET BEEPING]
I'm done with you.
Ugh!
No!
[BEEP]
What the hell is that?
Don't move. It's not stable.
What the hell was that?
TOMMY: See you at the bottom.
[BONES CRACKING]
Let... go.
[GROANS]
Unh!
A red wig?
And I'm the crazy one.
You saved my life.
Guess we're even.
This place is crawling with Crows.
You shouldn't be here.
Well, I came to crash the party.
Turns out our host beat me to it.
I didn't know that it
was a costume party.
Let me guess...
Red.
The color of our birthstone.
To remind us where we came from.
About that.
They say if you want to quit
you have to really want to,
and, well, I didn't want to.
You see, 24 hours is a really long time.
Guess you're gonna have to
let my sweet Dodgson die.
Like I said...
Beth is gone.
Then why save me?
Because I have plans for you, Kate.
That, and it's no fun
torturing a corpse.
Believe me, I've tried.
Anyhoo, good luck on the upkeep.
You think Tommy's annoying.
Wait till your roots grow in.
If you kill again, it's over,
and I will stop thinking
of you as my sister.
You're finally... catching... on.
That is exactly what I want.
You say that, but it's not true,
and I know you know that, too.
Right money in the right hands.
I will be out in an hour.
They're taking you to Arkham, Tommy.
Good luck buying your way out of that.
You tell Bruce that I won't stop
until he shows his face.
Reagan.
- Hey.
There you are.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I guess Tommy's a bigger
dick than I thought.
So that whole I can read people thing,
yeah, so you're into me.
I mean, you would know.
You're the professional.
Cool. I'll call you then.
I'd like that.
JACOB: Catherine?
Catherine?
There you are. You okay?
Alice broke into our home
and murdered that guard.
You have to stop her, Jacob.
I know. We're gonna find her.
And put an end to this.
When Alice called, she was playing
a song on Beth's cello... Bach.
I used to tell Beth it was our song.
She could have found one
of Beth's recitals online.
You're smarter than that, Jacob.
Jacob, don't let her in.
KATE, VOICE-OVER: I wasn't
afraid of letting down the city.
I was afraid of letting down you, Bruce,
but whatever happens,
whatever I face,
it's worth it.
VESPER: Okay, Gotham. Someone just dropped
a bombshell on this city,
and I mean that literally.
The Bat is back...
Just curvier and sexier,
so the big question,
what are we calling her...
Batlady, Batchick?
Talk to me, Gotham. We need a name.
Batwoman.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.MY-SUBS.com ...