You got it?
Looks like there's no room
for you girls.
Well, I guess we'll just have
to give a few
of these presents away
to make room in the back.
- Very funny, Daddy.
- We can go with Mom.
Oh, I see.
Now, that you're officially
young women...
you're making your own decisions.
Understood.
Then, I will see you both
at home.
- Great party, honey.
- Love you.
- You too.
- See you at home.
Now, there was one gift
that couldn't fit in his car.
- Awesome.
- It's our birthstone.
Red is a very symbolic color.
It's the color of love.
But it's also the color
of passion, courage, war.
At one point or another,
you're going to have to wrestle
with all of these emotions.
And what defines your character
is how you balance them.
So keep me close to your heart...
because I'll be thinking of you
when I wear mine.
Mazel tov.
Come here.
I'm so proud of you.
Okay, I don't see your car.
Can you flash your lights
or something?
A creepy guy is following me.
Oh, what?
You won't even talk with me?
Just leave me alone.
No one with those legs wants
to be left alone.
Come on. I'm friendly.
- I'm not.
- This just became a party.
You okay?
- What a dick.
- Oh, my God.
I'd ask for a selfie, but I think
you're needed elsewhere.
Next time.
Cartwright.
What couldn't you tell me
over the phone?
I need you to promise
you won't kill him.
- Kill who?
- Yeah, didn't sound like a promise.
Kate, open the damn door.
- How did you find him?
- He was left.
By whom?
I will tell you everything,
but first,
I need you to drink this.
Kate.
Drink it. Trust me.
I think Alice found him
and left him for me.
- Alice is dead.
- That's the thing. She's not.
Mouse?
Mouse, where are you?
Oh, dear, I shall be too late.
Stay away from me.
Mouse. It's me, the Caterpillar
told me where to find you.
You're dead. You're dead.
You're dead!
- Help!
- Mouse!
Cartwright thought he killed me.
But he was wrong.
It was someone else.
Another woman who fooled you.
- I'm here now.
- What's the secret password?
"Are there any lions
and tigers about here?"
"It's only the Red Queen snoring."
See?
It's me.
Your beloved sister.
Now, what is this place?
This...
- This used to be her house.
- Whose house?
The Queen.
The Queen of Hearts.
You've moved your things
out of the attic?
How long is she gonna be
staying with us?
Johnny, that's no way to talk.
Your grandmother can't
live on her own anymore.
Put that bucket away, Alice.
Alice!
The bucket goes away.
Oh, sorry.
It's fine, stay inside.
I'll just pull this thing
through the cold myself.
Hello, Mother.
Welcome home.
Your dear mother is
carting an oxygen tank
and you greet her
with an open flame?
I can take a hint.
And who is this handsome
young boy?
Hi, Grandma.
Johnny, get your grandmother's
bags.
You fixed his scar beautifully.
When are you going to fix this?
Mother, you're still as
beautiful as can be.
And this must be the girl.
My name is Alice,
so please, your Majesty.
Well, aren't you a curious thing
with your milky, young complexion.
I like your purse.
And I like your necklace.
Where did you get that?
Oh, I don't actually remember.
I saw Beth's body. She was dead.
I know what you saw.
All that matters is
that it wasn't our Beth.
Well, what are you saying,
that the girl on that metal slab
- was an imposter?
- Or another Skin Pirate minion.
Gotham has seen crazier things.
In fact, there's one
right in front of us now.
Turns out the bastard
who makes faces in his basement
also masquerades around
Gotham's elite
as the city's beloved
plastic surgeon.
Right under our nose.
We need to call the GCPD
and get him arrested.
Based on what?
Some crazy horror story
you and I tell
the very same Police Commissioner
who wrongly accused me of murder
no less than four months ago?
It's the truth.
Which can only
be corroborated by a lunatic
who everyone in Gotham
thinks is dead.
We need to think this through.
What do you suggest?
We kill him, bury his body
and go on with our lives?
Rise and shine,
you son of a bitch.
I was expecting Alice.
Well, you got one meaner.
Do you want me to start
with your nose or your kneecaps?
Who is Mommy Dearest?
Alice is playing games
against the master of games.
I'm not going to let her win.
You don't know Alice like I do.
I know I've spent the last
six years fooling Gotham...
your late wife...
and the both of you.
What is the Caterpillar doing?
Why would your own father
lock you here
and poison you like this?
He wanted me to see the truth.
What are you talking about?
The toxin...
He wanted me to unlock
my greatest fear.
And as it turns out,
you psychotic bitch...
my greatest fear is you.
Mouse, stop.
What are you doing?
You destroyed our family.
And now, your greatest fear
- No.
- will destroy you.
No.
Kill...
Off with your head!
So pop by in a week and we'll see
how you're healing, okay?
- Thank you.
- Of course.
So, this is the clinic
I've heard so much about.
You're here. Good.
So I called
because I have Beth news.
- Where's Kate?
- Figured you'd also call her.
Aren't you, like, her keeper?
Aren't you, like, her sister?
I got us a lead on Beth's murderer.
- That guy killed Beth?
- No.
He came in for a flu shot
but he saw our flyer.
- Mr. Dog.
- Just Mad Dog.
Yeah, well,
just tell him what you told me.
I saw the car y'all looking for.
- Okay, this seems legitimate.
- Where was it?
Junkyard off the 30 at Green.
Same color, same partial plates.
You didn't think
to take a picture, Mad Dog?
- You got a problem with that?
- No. We believe you.
Thank you.
Pretty sure you just gave
a thousand bucks
to a guy with a face tattoo.
He is our first lead
towards finding Beth's killer.
You're really dragging me
to this junkyard.
Technically, you're driving.
After so many years apart...
the only way my son and I
could start our life anew...
was if he believed Alice
was his enemy
who destroyed our family.
He was quite suggestible to the idea
after I used a little concoction
from an old colleague.
You may have heard of him.
Dr. Jonathan Crane.
Fear toxin. Scarecrow's MO.
- Triggers your greatest fear.
- And now Alice is his.
Much like the rest of Gotham...
Mouse thinks that Alice is dead.
Seeing his greatest fear
manifested in front of him...
Mouse will undoubtedly snap.
My guess is, by now, he's dosing her
with insurmountable amounts
of the hallucinogen himself.
Unless adrenaline
is administered soon...
she'll be gone forever.
Where is she?
I'll tell you where she is.
In return for my freedom.
Not happening.
Alice, until now, has been focused.
Her plans are always calculated,
pointed.
Collateral damage is minimized.
But this type of chemical
exposure will undo all of that.
Any wisps of sanity
Alice is clinging to
will dissolve in the wind.
If she doesn't jump off
the nearest rooftop, well then...
I imagine
she'll unravel completely...
out herself to Gotham
in the process of going nuclear.
I would hate to be in the
blast radius when that happens.
Dad, stop!
Stop, Dad!
Dad!
If you kill him,
then we are no better than he is.
Not to mention you'll never find out
where Alice is being tortured.
I can only imagine the darkness
she has inside of her.
Though I have a feeling I know
exactly who's paying her a visit.
- Who?
- Mommy Dearest.
- I beg pardon, Your Majesty.
- Put it there, girl.
I was as beautiful as you once.
You're still beautiful, ma'am.
I'm a circus act
leashed to this can of air
like it's my damn dog.
You have no idea
how lucky you are.
I wasted my life with a man
who never loved me
and took too long to die.
Now, not only am I alone,
I'm alone and old.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
Have you ever made tea, Alice?
I have.
Then you ought to know how
to keep it from being so sweet.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
I thought that you wanted it sweet.
You were wrong.
Hold out your hands.
I thought you wanted it sweet.
I thought you wanted it sweet!
I said hold out your hands, girl.
No, no, no.
- No.
- Palms up!
No, I swear I didn't do...
How many times have I told you,
if it's too hot for the hands,
it's too hot for the lips.
You changed your hair.
Why would you change your hair?
No, I kept it short,
just as you like it.
You colored it, it was so pretty.
What did you do, Alice?
You were such a pretty girl.
No, no, please,
I love my hair, please.
- Your hair wants cutting.
- I'm sorry, please, stop it!
No, no.
No!
- We're out of cream.
- I assure you, I brought cream.
Why are we out of cream, Alice?
I'll find some. I'll go now.
I'll find some.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, we can't have run out.
There's no cream.
We haven't any cream.
What are you doing here?
- Why is this locked?
- Why are you here?
- I need cream for the Queen's tea.
- There's no cream out here.
I'm desperate, she hates me.
- Mother doesn't hate you.
- She does hate me.
Because I am young and beautiful
and she's old and haggard.
It was my mother...
who siphoned her happiness...
snuffed her spark,
beat her so hard and so often
that eventually, it was easier
for Alice to be numb
than human.
I imagine, now, in the throes
of Alice's madness...
my mother is once again
calling for her tea.
You threw Beth in a cellar
and taught her
how to carve up faces...
but mommy is the bad guy?
Nice try.
I am gonna find her and then
I'm gonna skin you alive.
This is his.
Trace it, see if we can find out
where he led Alice.
- How about a glass of water?
- How about not.
Is that why Alice told me to ask
about Mommy Dearest?
Because your mom
was the one who broke her?
She wanted you to hear her story
and get you to kill me.
She wanted to break you, too.
You're wrong.
She knows I would never kill anyone.
Because...
You're so different?
We are different.
Then be merciful.
Give me water.
I'll tell you where she is.
You never knew my real sister.
The girl I grew up with...
was kind and good...
had a soft spot for people
who didn't necessarily
deserve it.
Now, tell me where Alice is.
You'll never find her.
So you paid a guy a thousand bucks
to tell you there's a car
in a junkyard.
How much will you give me
if I tell you there's sand
at the beach?
Okay, why don't we chase down
one of the leads
that you've generated?
So, you don't happen to have
a cool gadgety thing with you
to help us narrow down
the search, do you?
You know, from work?
I'm sorry, how would
a "real estate gadget"
- help with this exactly?
- Forget it.
Okay, look. Obviously,
Mad Dog was high on something.
And if we put faith
in anything that he said...
we're just as high as he was.
Okay, so if you
were gonna get high...
where would you go?
No idea.
Because I wouldn't.
But if you were,
you would go somewhere
where it was warm.
It's gotta be around here
somewhere.
There.
That's the only car
that still has its tires on.
And the color matches.
And the plate's a match.
This is me apologizing
for ever doubting you.
Is that it?
It's the same caliber
that killed Beth.
Hold this.
Hi. I don't know what you're selling,
but, please put me
on your do-not-call list.
Mary, I need your help.
Batwoman?
I am sorry, Batwoman's calling you?
How do I close
a severe neck wound?
- Yours?
- Not mine.
He's a bad guy, I...
He has information that I need.
Can you get him to a hospital?
Would I be calling you if I could?
Right. Okay.
- Is it the carotid artery?
- Carotid artery? Is she okay?
Is the blood flow pulsing?
Rhythmic?
No.
Okay, then it's not
the carotid artery.
But you still need
to close the wound.
Do you have a needle and thread?
I have a staple gun?
Oh, wouldn't be my first choice.
Okay, here goes nothing.
How do I know if it worked?
Slowly release your fingers
from the pressure point.
Anything?
No, nothing's coming out.
Does he have a pulse?
- Yes.
- Okay, good.
I mean, I think that's a good thing.
You said he was a bad guy.
He still gonna need treatment.
Thanks, Mary. Thanks.
Of course, anytime.
Literally, any time.
I'm here just waiting to be beckoned.
What? What is happening?
Sorry. Doctor-vigilante
confidentiality.
Please. I'm so very tired
of being all alone here.
You're alone because no one cared
enough to find you.
No one came for you then,
and no one will come for you now.
That's not true. That's not true!
- Alice, I'm here.
- Yeah.
- You're here.
- I'm here.
- No one can hurt you...
- Get away from her.
We can help her.
She can be saved.
She's a lost cause.
And the world is better off
with her dead.
No, no, no.
You know that's not true, Kate.
All the pain, all the misery,
all the hurt, it's because of her.
You're right.
She's not worth it.
And she never will be.
No.
Oh, Kate...
No. No, don't leave me.
Don't leave me, Kate!
Daddy, wait. Kate, stop.
Don't... don't leave me.
Don't leave me again.
Don't leave...
Clearly, you'd rather die
than help me.
And the longer you sit there...
the less likely those staples
are gonna hold.
and you die anyway.
Looks like you're in a bit
of a conundrum.
You're right. I am.
So I'm gonna give something
to live for, your freedom.
Why do I have a hard time
believing you?
I'm offering you a free pass
out of here.
And the second I tell you
where she is...
what's to stop you
from killing me?
- Me. Because I am not a killer.
- Yet.
You don't know me,
so let me tell you who I am.
I am everything you stripped away
from my sister.
Hope, honor, integrity.
I am what she would've been
if not for you.
I am giving you an out.
Tell me where she is.
She's at 614 Williams Street.
Did he tell you that?
We cut a deal.
Let me know
if he's telling the truth.
I don't get it.
I'm not getting any hits
from this license plate.
Are you sure
you entered it right?
Yeah, pretty sure I typed in
all six digits correctly
the first five times I entered them.
What are you doing?
I was just curious about
"The International Periodical
of Technology & Innovation.
Volume Two."
You got a book report due?
Well, I could've finished reading it
in the time it's taken you
to find one license plate.
I thought you were like Kate's
tech guru.
I've been searching
active registrations.
I didn't search inactive.
Yes, okay, I got something.
Okay. So the plates expired
20 years ago.
- Whose car is it?
- Car was last registered to...
- What?
- Mabel Cartwright.
August Cartwright's mother.
We need to call Kate.
I can't... I can't do this again!
I can't be locked away again.
"And she began by taking...
the little golden key...
and unlocking the door...
that led...
into the garden."
No! Alice, please. No.
Get away from me!
- You're not real.
- I'm real... Alice.
It's me.
- What's that?
- Adrenaline.
It's adrenaline.
It nullifies the toxin.
You're okay now.
Daddy?
Where's Kate?
Waiting outside
with her hand on the door?
She's with Cartwright.
She's the one who got him
to tell us where you were.
And you came running.
Why?
Because I care.
And to keep you hanging on
to whatever sense
of sanity you have left.
Touching.
Well, I take it
if Cartwright's still alive...
he hasn't gotten
to the part in the story
about Mommy Dearest?
Oh, he told us everything.
His mother sounded like a treat.
His mother?
Is that who you think
this is about?
Where is Mabel right now?
Your sister didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
Mother died years ago.
So you were driving her car.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Did you shoot a woman
who you believed to be my sister?
Answer me.
We made a deal.
I talk, I walk out of here alive.
Did you shoot a woman
in a motel parking lot
who you believed to be Alice?
She looked exactly like her.
The face, the eyes...
Of course you did.
Of course it was you!
I swore it was her.
Even wore a necklace
that matched those damn earrings.
What did you just say?
What necklace matched
what earrings?
The ones my mother so coveted
and caused all the problems.
What earrings?
How do they look?
Where did you get those?
They were a gift from my son.
That was the moment I remembered
where I got my necklace.
It was meant to match
Mother's earrings...
So that Kate and I could always
keep her close to our heart.
How did Cartwright know
about Gabi's earrings?
Trust me, Daddy.
Some things...
Are better left.
Alice, tell me
where he got the damn earrings!
Exactly where you think.
My mother wanted a fresh start.
She begged for your mother's face
from the day
I fished it out of the river.
As she got older...
Her obsession only got worse.
I kept pushing it off...
knowing it would cause trouble
once she took on the face
of a dead woman but...
It gave her something
to live for.
Your mother
was a beautiful woman, Kate.
It would've been a pity
for her to go to waste.
The tea's gone cold.
I said I need you to warm this tea.
Consider it a pleasure.
What the hell are you doing?
Long live the queen.
You stole everything from me!
Red is a very symbolic color.
It's the color of love.
It's also the color
of passion, courage, war.
At one point or another...
you're going to have to wrestle
with all of these emotions.
And what defines your character
is how you balance them.
Come on.
Live.
Come on. Live!
Help me.
Oh, no. He can't be dead.
Kate, what did you do?
- Please. Dad, save him.
- Wake up, you son of a bitch!
Kate.
"Oh, I've had such
a curious dream," said Alice...
and she told her sister all these
strange adventures of hers.
and when she had finished,
her sister kissed her and said,
"It was a curious dream, dear.
Now run in to your tea,
it's getting late."
So Alice got up and ran off,
thinking while she ran...
what a wonderful dream
it had been."
Congratulations, Daddy.
Now, both of your daughters
are killers.
Died seven years ago.
Burned to death in a house fire.
Right around the time
Cartwright disappeared.
And the next time he crawls out
of the woodwork,
- he kills Beth.
- We should've seen this coming.
Hey, don't make this harder
by blaming yourself.
That's easier said than done
after watching Beth...
- die in my arms.
- If I know Kate...
she won't rest until she brings
that monster to justice.
I thought I found the balance,
Bruce.
But I was wrong.
I crossed the line.
And now I'm the very thing
I've been fighting against.
Can I get one on the house?
We're gonna need this
with the night we have ahead of us.
What do you mean?
Last time I checked...
Bodies don't bury themselves.