Previously on Batwoman...
Seriously, Kate, you can't be
going out in Gotham every night
pretending to be Batman.
Catherine Hamilton's
investigators found bones,
skull fragments of a little girl.
It's Beth.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Alice. How do you do?
I think Alice is Beth.
I know that you want to believe
that Beth is alive.
I do too, but facts are facts.
My father gave up on me,
and I want to make him suffer
the way that I did.
"Will you walk a little faster?"
Said a whiting to a snail.
"There's a porpoise close behind us
and he's treading on my tail.
See how eagerly the lobsters
and the turtles all advance.
They are waiting on the shingle,
will you come and join the dance?"
Will you, won't you,
will you, won't you,
will you come and join the dance?
Alice figured me out, Bruce.
I put on your suit to terrify her,
but it can't protect me
if she knows who I am.
I lost my advantage.
And in the process,
I gave Gotham their hero back.
I didn't sign up for this part.
I never meant to give the city
so much hope.
I can't do this. I'm not you.
Subtle.
I guess it's broken.
- It's supposed to call Batman.
- What do you want?
What happened
to your batsuit knockoff, Kate?
Too tight? No give?
Or did you just realize that you
accidentally blew a dog whistle
that you can't unblow.
I wore it to protect myself
from you and your goons.
And in the process
you made everyone horny
for Batman.
All these poor souls gazing up
at the bat light, thinking...
"My life is about to change."
Nope. Still sucks.
Are you suggesting
that I put it back on?
No.
Being a hero is not your strong suit.
I would know, seeing as
you let Dad declare me dead.
Where is my boyfriend?
Hanging in there.
You like damaged men.
He's badly damaged.
You may want to get him back soon.
Okay, I'll play.
How?
Show me you can stop killing people.
Last 24 hours and I'll reassess.
Rats.
I lost my pocket watch.
And I lost my sister.
Beth. Remember her?
Yeah. I would like her back.
You are going to be
very annoying, aren't you?
Very.
Fine. No killing.
But only for my darling
Dodgson's sake,
not for Beth.
Beth has gone down,
down, down the rabbit hole
and she's never coming back.
Much like Gotham's beloved Bat.
You've worked hard
to get where you are.
You deserve to feel safe.
Don't you want your kids
to be able to play outside again?
Elliot Estates are Gotham's
walls within the walls,
with on-site 24-hour Crows security,
and a safe room in every unit.
Have you been mugged?
Has your property been vandalized?
At Elliot Estates,
you don't ever have to worry
about that again.
How do I know?
I'm Tommy Elliot and I'm here
to make Gotham safe again.
Nice. Okay, yes.
Now I'm that annoyingly
over-protective husband.
- You're married.
- Yes, yes. Nice.
- Nice.
- Are you happy?
Yeah.
You're a little more aggressive
than usual.
What's the problem,
you can't take it?
All right.
You need to move on.
You know most couples
just have breakfast together.
I've got an energy bar in my bag.
Oh, can we split it?
Well, front desk says
the commander's here.
I gotta go.
You can watch it a million times.
Alice still gets away at the end.
No one's taken responsibility
for the attack.
Trail's gone cold.
Who'd want her dead
when she's already in custody?
Besides most of Gotham?
What can I do for you, Agent Moore?
I think I can be helpful, sir.
Considering Alice could attack
again at any time,
I was hoping to get your approval
for a special assignment.
Okay, people, Vesper Fairchild here.
So I'm staring at my wall chart,
has it really been ten days
without a Batman sighting?
Anyone else feeling ghosted?
Talk to me, Gotham, where's Batman?
Okay, I'll just get this.
It'll pinch a little bit.
Three, two and you're done.
Wow, you are so brave. High-five.
- Late night?
- Sophie, hey.
If you're looking for Kate,
she's not here.
In fact, she rarely comes home.
You know, I wouldn't be surprised
if she was dating again
seeing as she's single, and gorgeous,
and emotionally available.
Do you normally stay out all night
when a psychopath
is targeting your family?
What was I supposed to do,
not go to Kylie Q's Glam Jam
and miss next summer's colors?
You're in danger, Mary.
Okay, well, I also have a life, so.
So your father just made me
your bodyguard.
I'm sorry, what?
That is not your desk.
Do you hear that?
That is the sound of me
officially having more money
than Bruce Wayne.
Tommy Elliot.
How the hell did you even
get in here?
What's up, Candy Kane?
Well, Bruce never showed you
the hide-a-key?
But I thought you were buffing up
on some lesbian ninja retreat.
Why are you here, Tommy?
Come here. Check it out.
You see this building?
I just bought it.
Five stories taller than Wayne Tower.
Bruce and Tommy.
Childhood friends
who still act like children.
"What is a friend?
A single soul dwelling
in two bodies."
Is that some secret society thing?
It's an Aristotle thing.
Gotham has gotten all intense
now that Batman's back.
And if you heard,
Gotham's Dark Knight
has the city swooning again.
I saw the picture.
Yeah, it was...
Pixilated.
Wow, I...
I mean, that's your reaction?
The guy had...
Your mom and your sister
in his win column.
He blinked...
And they died.
Oh, Kate,
I thought you'd be more upset.
I've had time to process.
Batman saved your mom's life
a few years later.
Guess he's not a total deadbeat,
you know?
So where's Brucey Boy?
I wanted to invite him
to celebrate my new pile of bricks.
Bruce hasn't been in Gotham
for three years, you know that.
- Yeah, but he's back now.
- No, he's not.
- I'm pretty sure he is.
- Trust me, I'd know.
Maybe just leave it on his desk.
Will do.
- Where are you?
Needless to say,
this is not what
Wayne's advanced weaponry vault
should look like.
The tech in here is top secret.
If something was taken, it's bad.
Had to be Alice's gang, right?
Did you pull the security footage?
They jammed the cameras.
It'll take a minute to figure out
what they took,
but in the meantime, I'll call Bruce
and tell him what happened.
And you really expect him
to answer?
One of his properties containing
millions of dollars' worth
of weaponry was compromised.
But if something was gonna get
Bruce's attention, it'd be this.
- What is this?
- Not yours.
Two-way grappling hook.
Okay. Twice the hook,
twice the chance for disaster.
Possible 10-54 Gotham City Gazette.
10-4 on the Gazette. Clear the area.
- We're en route now.
- Code ten.
I need you to stay back
and figure out what they took.
- I'll check this out.
- Okay.
I can't believe
this is happening in the city.
Where are the Crows, we need them!
Who did this to Batman?
I tried to be Batman, Bruce,
and I drew out your enemies
in the process.
Today it's an effigy.
But what happens when your
enemies start to kill real people
in order to draw you out?
The Gotham you set out to protect
is now less safe because of me.
So, what's the deal, Batman?
Are we really gonna let some loser
with a party store gift card
and way too much time
on his hands win this one?
Step out of the shadows
and into the ring.
Gotham needs you.
- Hey.
So you're really doing nothing
for my game.
Is there any chance that you could...
I'm kind of looking
for my future husband over here.
Unfortunately, the Commander
was pretty specific.
We keep A-list clients
within ten to 15ft.
Joy.
Biochemistry?
Not exactly fodder for small talk
at Kylie Q's Jam Glam party.
Med student?
I kind of thought
you went to med school
to "look for your future husband."
So is my dad forcing Kate
to have a pocket Crow
or is it just me?
He figured since
she'd been offered a job with us
that it wasn't necessary.
That is so not fair.
So why didn't she take
the Crows job?
I have no idea.
I mean, she finally gets offered
a position
she spent five years training for
and doesn't take it?
Doesn't make sense.
You know Kate.
She is crazy.
So what is she doing with herself?
I hear she keeps late hours too.
So are you on this assignment
to keep tabs on me or on Kate?
Because I'm getting a very
distinctive "jealous ex" vibe.
I told her to move on.
You wanna know why Kate's not a Crow?
It's because you're a Crow.
It's because five years of training
was easier to walk away from
than going to work with the girl
who broke her heart.
The Batsuit is made
of a military-grade Kevlar
woven with enriched carbon nanotubes
- of my dad's own design!
- You're screaming.
- What?
- You're screaming!
Oh, sorry.
This is a Desert Eagle
Mark Nine 50 A-E.
One of the most powerful handguns
in the world.
It can literally blast a hole
through anything.
- Doesn't make a dent.
- Yeah.
You know, it stings a little.
- Just for reference.
- This...
is a rail gun.
It turns out this is what
the thieves took from Wayne R&D.
It has a parallel conductor
that generates a pulsed force
of electromagnetism,
accelerating the velocity
of the projectile.
It's the most lethal weapon
that Bruce ever had built.
This is a prototype,
but for demonstration purposes...
You're gonna fix that, right?
It's the only gun
that can shoot a shot
strong enough to penetrate the suit.
Bruce had it built
in case the suit fell
into the wrong hands.
Whoever's in possession
of the gun can kill Batman.
I put on this suit.
I dragged out one of his enemies.
Or maybe Alice doesn't like you
having her boy toy strung to a pipe.
If she has the gun,
she levels the playing field.
Except Alice doesn't know
that Bruce Wayne is Batman.
Whoever stole the gun
knew that Bruce had to have
- the suit to test it on.
- Yeah.
They know that Bruce is Batman.
Let me show you something.
He's an entitled one-percent jerk.
Now, he's inviting you to show off
his new douche chateau. Point?
The invitation wasn't for me.
It was for Bruce.
Tommy is adamant
that he's back in town.
- Why would he think that?
- Because if Batman's back,
Bruce is too.
Tommy's parents
were in that car accident.
Batman pulled his mom from the fire.
- Why would he want to kill him?
- No idea.
I'll go ask.
Or you could be Batman.
Sorry, that just sounded like
Mr. That's-Not-Meant-For-You
wants me to put the suit back on.
If Tommy did steal the gun,
he's trying to intimidate Batman.
Go show him the Bat's
not afraid of anyone.
- He has that.
- And you have that.
And an entire city behind you.
That includes me.
Knowing Bruce,
if he built a rail gun,
he built something that can stop it.
And I will figure out how to use it.
You're stronger than this guy,
Kate. Go kick his butt.
And if I can't,
I let down an entire city.
I'm not Batman, Luke.
All posts, we are on crisis alert.
Hey, what are you doing?
Alice, wait, wait!
Kate's gonna be so disappointed.
Elliot party.
Hey.
What is happening here?
Your dad assigned me
as Mary's security detail.
- That sucks.
- No kidding.
But what was I supposed to do?
Miss the party of the weekend
because I got a full-time babysitter?
Can't have the Queen of Gotham's
party scene
go radio silent on socials.
What about you, Kate?
What brings you
to an adult frat house?
I was told to move on.
We get it, Tommy,
could you live any higher?
What can I get you?
Just looking for the man of the hour.
He's around.
But if you wanna save yourself
from a verbal carwash
of veiled misogyny,
you might wanna plant yourself
here, he'll be by soon.
In that case, I will have a beer.
I'm Reagan, by the way.
Kate Kane. I thought that was you.
Tyler. We met a few weeks ago.
Sophie's husband. I remember.
You know, I hate these things.
Guy has ten contracts with The Crows
so we all come here to kiss his ass.
Well, at least you get to work
with your wife.
Yeah, you know, speaking of,
I didn't catch how you and Sophie
know each other.
- What do you mean?
- Well, she never told me
she was friends
with the boss's daughter.
- She didn't tell you who I am?
- No.
I'm the Kate. From Point Rock.
Oh, you went to the academy together.
Right. That explains it.
That explains it.
Oh, boss is here.
You have a nice night,
Kate from Point Rock.
He married your ex and has no idea.
Wow, you're good.
Professional level.
Started bartending
before I could drink.
- You learn to read people.
- All right.
- Read him for me.
- Tommy Elliott?
Danger, hazardous waste.
King of Real Estate,
thinks he's doing us all a favor
when he really just helps
fund the walls
that are separating our city.
- Gotham, am I right?
- Yeah.
Thank goodness.
Someone who loathes
Tommy Elliott as much as me.
Isn't he one of your biggest clients?
Unfortunately.
Well, I'm glad you're here, Kate.
It means you're not out
gallivanting with Alice.
You would tell me
if she'd reached out
to you again, right?
I don't think Alice
is gonna be a problem today.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Twin instincts.
Mum.
Security detail? Seriously?
Unfortunately, this is the world
we're living in now.
Well, I need my world to have
a little bit more elbow room.
I can't even reapply lip gloss
without poked by an AK.
Nice view of Wayne Tower.
Well, took half my life,
but I'm finally looking down
on Bruce Wayne.
What makes you think he's back?
We're cosmic besties.
And here I thought
I was his favorite cousin
and not even a phone call.
- Oh, he's a busy man.
- You're right.
He's probably preoccupied
with the break-in at Wayne R&D.
They stole a specialized firearm.
That sucks.
Good news is, the morons who
took it probably didn't realize
there's a hidden GPS tracker
inside the device.
And it's only a matter of time
before Wayne Security
come knocking at their door.
Kane.
Who is this?
You taught me. Remember?
Or did you give up music
like you gave up on me?
What are you trying to do, Alice?
You're not getting in my head.
You'd be surprised
where I can get into, Commander.
Where are you?
Well, I could tell you
but that would ruin the surprise.
Let's talk until you're finished
tracing my call.
I never understood
why you stopped looking for me.
I always thought a father
would do anything
to find his daughter.
Swim oceans, move mountains.
But now I get it.
You're on top of the mountain.
If I had this view,
I'd stop looking for me too.
More time to enjoy your new life.
How did you get in my house?
You should be ashamed, Commander.
King of the Crows
can't even protect your own nest.
I'm coming for you.
Maybe if you uttered those words
15-years-ago,
we wouldn't be here now.
I won't let you forget me,
Commander. Not again.
We need to leave now.
- What is it?
- I'll explain downstairs.
Kane to Moore.
Get Kate and Mary in an armored truck
- until I deal with something.
- Copy that.
- Mary.
- What's happening?
Okay. All right. Okay.
- Where's Kate?
- She probably left.
I'll text her.
That's some gun you got there.
Party's not in here, Candy Kane.
It's over, Tommy.
This isn't yours, just...
You don't wanna get in my way.
- How do you know who he is?
- You mean Batman?
Did I say that out loud?
How do you know that?
Oh, because a few months ago
I paid a man to riddle me the answer.
Gotta love the honorable Bruce Wayne
for designing a failsafe
so he can never become
too powerful in his super suit.
He is such a great guy.
- He's your best friend.
- Yeah, he was.
The bestest.
Nothing could be average with Bruce,
even had to have
more dead parents than me.
Because he saved your mom's life.
Oh, yeah, no, I am aware.
Thanks to him, instead
of collecting my inheritance,
I was left wiping the spittle
of a jabbering madwoman's lips
for 13 years.
If you wanted him dead, why wait
until he's in a bullet proof suit?
Because Bruce didn't ruin my life.
Batman did.
Do you know what it's like
to have the villain of your story
be the hero of your city?
He is a monster who left me anchored
to a repulsive gold-digging bitch.
And now he's gonna die.
Well, that answers that.
Bruce's is bigger.
What did you do?
You let Batman meet me on the roof,
or the elevators I just hijacked,
they start to drop.
- Batman isn't here.
- Yeah, because he's hiding.
It's time for Gotham's hero
to man up.
Next one's in an hour.
It will look like this,
but with people the city
will actually miss.
Oh, my God.
It's my leg...
I'm so sorry.
You're gonna be okay.
Help him.
I'm gonna check
all the elevators.
- I swear I heard something crash.
- Yeah, me too.
Does anyone have reception?
Moore to Base. Check, check. Hello?
How is our signal dead?
Hello? FYI,
I'm a social media influencer.
So if you people
don't want a scathing review
of your building safety,
you should hop to it!
No service. I hope Mary's okay.
Why did you pull us out of there?
- Alice.
- Alice?
Is she the reason
we're stuck right now?
Very well could be.
She just called me.
From our penthouse.
What?
I swear if this is Alice,
I'm gonna be so pissed.
They'll find us, babe.
Oh, my God.
What?
Nothing. I just totally forgot
you two were married.
Three years,
but still full of surprises.
Saw Kate inside.
You two went to Point Rock
together?
Yeah. We did. Why?
Was it a secret or something?
No. Why would it be a secret?
I don't know
why would you never mention her?
She's our boss's daughter.
Didn't I mention her?
- No, Soph, you didn't.
- I don't know.
We weren't that close.
Never occurred to me.
Anyone wanna try prying
open the doors?
- How the hell did she get inside?
- I have no idea.
How can the city trust us
to protect it
when we can't even
keep ourselves safe?
- We'll contain it.
- We should've "contained" Alice
- when we had the chance.
- Trust me, that was the plan!
But Kate threatened
to cut me out of her life.
What was I supposed to do?
All right, I'll go
and help pull you out, okay?
All right, we should split up
and see if anyone else is stuck.
Okay.
- I knew...
- I didn't say anything.
Why are you here?
He's gonna drop another one.
I know that,
all those people are hurt
because I put the suit on.
- It's not your fault, Kate.
- It is, Luke. It is my fault.
I brought this to Gotham.
Tommy today,
someone else tomorrow.
This is on me.
You said if something
was gonna get Bruce's attention,
it would be this.
I need you to be real with me.
Do you think he's coming back?
- Luke.
- No.
Tommy wants Batman.
The city needs Batman.
And I'm not Batman.
But maybe I'm better
because I'm here.
How long is that gonna take
to fix?
There aren't enough.
- What?
- EMTs.
Ma'am, how are you feeling?
Ma'am?
Any head pain? Headache?
This woman needs help now.
- We already checked her.
- Well, check her again!
Mary, they're professionals.
You're a second year med student.
She's got a headache
and a blown pupil.
Could be a subdural
or epidural hemorrhage.
- I read ahead.
- You're right. Thanks.
Your friend Tommy
wants to kill you Bruce.
And since you're not here...
it looks like I'm gonna have
to kick his butt on your behalf.
And send a message to anyone else
who'd come after you.
But to do that, I need to be
honest with the city...
that I'm not you.
I'm me.
You're not Batman.
That's the point.
Who the hell are you?
I want Batman, not his side piece.
I found Tommy.
Activate the disruptor
on your gauntlet.
When the light flashes green,
his gun will neutralize.
- Yeah, that's not happening.
- Did you charge the glove?
- Wait, what?
- Where's Batman?
Okay, I activated the charge.
You need to stall for 30 seconds.
Stalling.
I'm done with you.
No!
- What the hell was that?
- Don't move. It's not stable.
What the hell was that?
See you at the bottom.
Let go.
Red wig?
And I'm the crazy one.
You saved my life.
Guess we're even.
This place is crawling with Crows.
You shouldn't be here.
Well, I came to crash the party.
Turns out our host beat me to it.
I didn't know
that it was a costume party.
Let me guess.
Red.
The color of our birthstone.
To remind us where we came from.
About that...
They say if you wanna quit,
you have to really want to.
And, well, I didn't want to.
You see,
24 hours is a really long time.
Guess you're gonna have
to let my sweet Dodgson die.
Like I said...
Beth is gone.
Then why save me?
Because I have plans for you, Kate.
And that it's no fun
torturing a corpse.
Believe me, I've tried.
Any who, good luck on the upkeep.
If you think Tommy was annoying,
wait until your roots grow in.
If you kill again, it's over.
And I will stop thinking of you
as my sister.
You're finally catching on.
That is exactly what I want.
You say that, but it's not true.
And I know you know that too.
Right money in the right hands,
I will be out in an hour.
They're taking you to Arkham,
Tommy.
Good luck buying your way out
of that.
You tell Bruce that I won't stop
until he shows his face!
- Reagan.
- Hey.
- There you are.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I guess...
Tommy's a bigger jerk than I thought.
So that whole I can read
people thing?
Yeah, so you're into me.
I mean, you would know.
You're the professional.
- Cool. I'll call you, then.
- I'd like that.
Catherine? Catherine.
There you are.
You okay?
Alice broke into our home
and murdered that guard.
- You have to stop her, Jacob.
- I know.
- We're gonna find her.
- And put an end to this!
When Alice called, she was
playing a song on Beth's cello.
Bach.
I used to tell Beth it was our song.
She could've found
one of Beth's recitals online.
You're smarter than that, Jacob.
Jacob, don't let her in.
I wasn't afraid of letting down
the city.
I was afraid of letting down you,
Bruce.
But whatever happens,
whatever I face...
It's worth it.
Okay, Gotham.
Someone just dropped a bombshell
on this city,
and I mean that literally.
The Bat is back.
Just curvier and sexier!
So, the big question,
what are we calling her?
Batlady? Batchick?
Talk to me Gotham, we need a name.
Batwoman.