Previously on Batwoman...
What's so special
about Lucius Fox's journal?
It's a failsafe.
To kill the Bat.
No!
We can make you into anyone
you want to be.
You want to be.
When do I get my face?
As soon as I get that journal.
Kate?
Reagan?
What do you mean it's gone?
I woke up and
Reagan was gone and...
And so was the book.
The book filled with secrets
my dad died to protect.
- I never thought Reagan...
- Guys!
The million-dollar question is what
would a bartender want with it?
You got your book.
Trade it for your freedom.
But I'm done being advance scout
for Magpie.
How's my new favorite book?
Lucius Fox wrote the
entire journal in code!
Wait. Please. Don't...
- Oh, my God!
- What the hell?
Hush.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my god.
I double-locked that.
- Where's the journal?
- How did you even find me?
You don't get to ask questions,
Reagan.
No more BS.
Tell me where the journal is
and I will get out of your life.
It wasn't all BS, Kate.
Sorry I must have misinterpreted
the part where you slept with me
to steal my property.
Yes, I stole it.
And yes, I slept with you.
But it wasn't all...
I still...
I totally get why you hate me.
- Where's the journal?
- I don't know.
And that's the truth. I...
I gave it to someone.
Who?
It will sound worse than it is.
Who do you work for?
It's more like "with."
My sister, Margot.
You know her...
as Magpie.
Magpie is your sister?
Surprise.
Why did she want it?
It bought her, her freedom out of
Arkham.
- Who did she give it to?
- I don't know.
I don't ask for details
for exactly this reason.
Besides, by now it's lost up the food
chain, she's in the wind.
- I told all this to your friend.
- What?
What friend?
Blond chick. With the British accent.
She cornered me in a parking lot,
put a knife to my throat,
didn't stop to give a name.
Good evening, Janet.
I heard you had quite the
encounter with Abraham earlier.
Well, they don't call it the mess
hall for nothing, Dr. Butler.
Indeed.
That was the wrong answer,
Professor Carr.
Try again.
Is he done yet?
Does he look done yet?
I think this numeral is Aramaic.
This is Mayan.
These two letters could be
Babylonian.
I mean, if you want Kate dead so
badly,
why don't you just shoot her?
I'm sure Tommy will give you
the friends-and-family rate.
So, the last thing she sees
is his gauze pad and his gun,
and has no idea what's happening.
No.
Her betrayal deserves a reckoning!
You see this, douchewad?
Not exactly the lady-killer
I used to be
before that looney toon decided
to hold my new face hostage
until you figure out
what the hell this books says
so glue a few brain cells together,
and decode it!
This is extraordinarily complex.
My expertise is actually
numerical analysis, iterative...
Please, please, just let me go!
I won't tell anyone I was here!
Please...
Oopsie.
Looks like Professor Carr
ran out of gas.
You didn't even give him a chance.
- Can we move on to my plan now?
- No.
We can't bring Luke Fox into this.
His father designed the code.
It doesn't take a cryptologist to
puzzle together he's our best choice.
If we kidnap the kid,
we draw out the Bat.
It's already dangerous enough
bringing these other people.
We found our Wonderland.
Hot showers. Comfortable beds.
Three meals a day.
And we get to be together.
If we draw her out,
we could lose everything.
Tommy said that this book holds
the key to killing Batwoman.
And I want her very, very dead.
Having said that...
I hate to see you fret.
He's number one.
You have two strikes left.
Now, put on your Dr. Butler face
and escort Tommy out the door.
Good morning, Gotham.
Or should I say
"Good morning, Gotham"?
After a showdown in GU's library
last night,
the GCPD have coined
the bandage-wrapped gunslinger
after the only word
witnesses heard him utter,
"Hush."
Welcome to Gotham City, Hush.
Sounds like you're gonna fit
right in.
What, you,
didn't think I'd find her?
Sorry, love, you caught me before my
latte.
Reagan said you came looking
for the journal.
Right. I did.
Considering her little dine and dash
I figured I'd spare
you the humiliation.
- Did I do something wrong?
- Why did you want it?
- For you.
- You held a knife to her throat.
Tell me you're not
defending the woman
who lured you into bed
to pluck a book out
from underneath your pillow.
Why didn't you just use your name?
Tell her you're with the Crows?
I see.
Reagan can't be trusted
and now no one can be trusted.
Not no one.
Just people who've lied
to me in the past
and last time I checked,
that includes you.
Thanks.
Kate, hey.
Didn't expect to see you here.
She was just leaving.
Commander called a briefing.
We should go.
Approximately 20 minutes ago,
one of our clients was kidnapped.
Tony Kim, 45, undercover NSA agent.
He was taken while reporting for work
at the field office
at Tricorner Yards.
In searching the area, their security
also discovered last
night's kidnapping victim,
Professor John Carr, dead,
in a dumpster.
Based on CCTV footage at Tricorner,
we can confirm Kim was abducted
by the same faceless perp
that took Carr from the university.
And apparently, the press has already
given him a nickname,
Hush.
Let's find Agent Kim
and snuff this homicidal bastard out.
That doesn't make any sense.
Why would Julie want the book for
herself?
I don't know.
Why is Julia suddenly back in town,
working for my dad, dating my ex?
- She's not scheming against us.
- And you'd know that how?
Because she pretended
to fall in love with you?
When she was just a babysitter
sent by Bruce Wayne?
Okay, it's time to day drink.
Because I've known her
since we were kids.
She's legit.
So, you believe her over me?
Am I not allowed to disagree with
you now?
- Not when we're both being lied to.
- I trust her, Kate.
Then I can't trust your judgment.
Says the girl who went home
with a bartender
and left the key to
destroying Gotham out.
Damn!
If you don't like how I do things,
no one's making you stay.
You know what?
You are absolutely right.
I have to find this damn book.
Which would be easier with Luke.
Because computers and stuff.
Okay, I gotta...
Gotham safety alert.
There's been another kidnapping.
They think it's the same guy
who hit up GU's library last night.
"NSA Data Analyst."
NSA?
Wait. Hang on.
In college, one of my friends
had Professor Carr.
At least until he had to have
an emergency heart surgery.
And apparently they got, like,
the hottest sub to replace him.
- The class became standing-room...
- Mary?
Sorry. Right.
I think...
Yup. Doctor Carr taught
Cryptography 1 and 2. Codes.
Just like the NSA.
Okay, Reagan said the journal looked
like it was written in
hundreds of languages,
like a cipher.
So, you think this Hush guy
is kidnapping codebreakers
because he has the journal?
Yeah.
If he gets one to break the code
before I find him...
Then the same monster
who shot up a library full of people
will know all about
the deadliest weapons in Gotham.
Agent Kim, hi.
I was hoping to employ your services.
Hmm?
And to think...
He was hired to protect our country.
They need more than 90 minutes
to figure it out.
Alice, you keep killing them.
Well, they keep disappointing me.
You realize the more people we
abduct, the more we risk exposure.
And you realize none of this is real,
right?
You can play house and dress up
and pretend this funny farm
is your own private castle.
But at the end of the day,
you're just a freak
who made out with a radiator.
Enough! Boys.
You'll just have to find me someone
else.
Every codebreaker in the city
is on lockdown because of him!
Well, there is one codebreaker
no one knows about.
You are such a dork.
You know, my mom is now obsessed
with that show, thanks to you.
As she should be.
She understands cultural relevancy.
My mom thinks culture is spaghetti
with...
Oh, my God!
Hush.
Parker? What's up?
According to The Gazette, Carr's body
was found covered in burn marks.
What does that mean?
It means poor Professor Carr.
Like he hadn't been through enough.
Right. You said he had heart surgery.
Any chance that surgery involved
getting a pacemaker?
Hm.
Because a pacemaker
is totally traceable.
Exactly.
So, we trace it back to where
it transmitted its last signal.
And then we'll know where he died,
and then we'll find Hush.
That's genius.
- Right.
- So...
- Okay. Yeah.
- Yeah. Right.
So, trace it.
- How?
- You don't know?
Kind of a Luke thing.
- Maybe it's time to apologize?
- Wait, me?
You have a landline?
Gotham Pride Real Estate.
Is Kate Kane there?
- Who is this?
- My name's Gina,
I'm Parker Torres' girlfriend,
and she said she knew you.
Okay, yup, hi.
So, I don't know what happened,
we were FaceTiming
and then the phone started shaking
and then she screamed to call you,
but then it went dead
and the last place she showed up
on Find My Friends was in Somerset,
and now I'm freaking out.
Who is Parker Torres?
So if you're scared to show your face
in Gotham, that's bad.
- Like what's under there?
- Shut up!
- Aren't you supposed to say, "Hush"?
No offense,
but I've been kidnapped by worse.
I know if you haven't killed me yet,
it means you can't kill me.
Kate, this is Mary. Oh, wait,
are we allowed to use our real names?
It doesn't matter.
I'm in Somerset.
Okay.
There's a van going south
on the Williams Viaduct.
Just triggered
three speed-trap cams.
Probably him.
I'm heading north.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
Uh, let me zoom in real quick.
Come on, how do you...?
Is there a manual?
Oh...
Oh, okay. Hello? Can you still hear
me?
I think you're driving the wrong way
on a one-way.
Kate! You're going the wrong way!
Batwoman.
Oh, Batty wants to be a hood
ornament.
Come on.
Hey!
Oh...
Hello, Parker. Welcome.
Thank you for joining us.
I'm a teen. I have angst.
We get it, Alice.
Do you?
Because you couldn't handle
a teenage schoolgirl.
Well, Batwoman showed.
I had to bail.
What do you mean, "Batwoman
showed"?
We're you followed?
I sort of stopped thinking clearly
when she threw a batarang in my leg!
Boys, boys.
All the more reason to want her dead.
Now, I have met disappointment...
thrice.
Are we finally ready...
to do things my way? Hm?
Gotta jet. We've got a possible Hush
sighting on the Williams Viaduct.
Got it.
- Uh, you go ahead, I'll meet up.
- Copy.
Hey, you.
I love visits and all, but I'm sure
you're not supposed to be here.
That's funny.
Because I did a little digging,
Julia,
and I'm pretty sure I can say
the same thing about you.
OMG!
Yeah, full disclosure?
I thought "Batcave" was metaphor.
Are there like...?
Yep. Not a metaphor.
Uh... Hi.
I think you got off at the wrong
floor.
It's fine. This is Parker Torres.
KK and I go way back. And you're...?
Mary. Otherwise known as the last
person to find out
that Kate is Batwoman.
Hush got away.
What do you mean, "Hush got away"?
He was our only lead since you've
refused to ask Luke how
to track a pacemaker.
I'm well aware, thank you.
Maybe you should kiss and make up
and get his butt back here.
Who are you?
And then SRR found out I was doing a
spot of freelancing
for another party and...
Well, they let me go.
A spot of freelancing
doesn't get you blacklisted
from the biggest intelligence agency
in the EU.
Who are you working for?
- Who wants my dad's journal?
- Luke, if I told you that,
we wouldn't be sitting here right
now.
- Hello?
- Hey! Where are you?
Wilson Plaza by Crow Headquarters.
What phone are you using?
Stay there, I'll find you.
Okay.
Kate's on her way down.
So, are you gonna tell her or am I?
Ballistics matched these rounds
to the library crime scene.
Same .45 caliber pistol. It was Hush.
And he wasn't alone.
We're lucky there wasn't much traffic
on that bridge
or we'd be bagging a lot more
than batarangs.
Sir.
I don't want to fight with you
about Batwoman's intentions.
My fight's not with you.
But I also don't want to wait and
find out which masked freak is gonna
get more people killed.
I'm bloody serious, Luke,
Kate can't know any of this.
I blew up on Kate in your defense
and she was right about everything.
Not everything, okay? There's stuff
about Kate you don't know.
Are you here already?
- What are you talking about?
- What do you mean, what am I ta...?
Hush.
Welcome to Arkham.
You're going to decipher Daddy's
code,
or we will fry this little cutie...
like bacon.
There's no way.
My dad was a genius. Legitimately.
MENSA, 163 IQ, it would take a team
of codebreakers weeks,
months to crack this.
Well, sadly...
I don't think he's gonna give you
that long.
- It's Luke...
- Now he's not answering.
- Can you text him?
- I am, it's green.
I think his phone is off.
Something's up.
He might be mad at me,
but he wouldn't turn off his phone.
Wait, is that him?
No, it's Sophie in the elevator.
Should I invite her down here?
Since apparently everyone else is
allowed?
Good talk.
Hmm.
Sophie, hey.
You okay?
Honestly, trying to rein in a little
panic.
Not to make this awkward, or...
whatever...
But have you seen Julia? She's MIA.
Who's the babe?
Way off limits. It's Kate's ex.
Of course, she is. And who's Julia?
Her other ex.
Okay. Move.
I heard you two are hanging out.
Julia and me?
I... I guess you could say that.
Is that...
okay?
- No, it's not okay.
- Oh, this is torture.
Because if it's not, I'll keep it
platonic.
Whatever makes you happy.
- No! Tell her you love her.
- Oh, shush, I can't hear.
If I hear from Julia, I'll tell her
to check in.
Would you ask Luke too?
He was with her
before she went radio silent.
Luke...
Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop, you're killing her!
Nope. Not yet. Still alive. For now.
You are a tough one, lass.
Arkham's power bills
are gonna be through the roof.
But, just between me, you,
and, well, science...
I'm not sure how much more you can
take.
I've had worse.
Not yet.
But you will. If the human abacus
over here
doesn't show me how the
cipher works.
How do you expect me to concentrate?
You want me to figure this out,
give me some space.
Indeed.
Oh.
And show me your work, Mr. Fox.
Because if you're lying,
I'm going to turn blondie...
into a glowstick.
You can do this, right?
I don't know. I...
I need more brain power, I need...
I need more time. I need...
- I need my dad.
- Luke.
You are every bit as smart as your
father.
No, I'm not!
Okay? I, more than anybody, wish that
were true,
but I am not my father, okay?
I'm not even close.
And we're both going to die because
of it.
I don't understand
why we're keeping Tommy alive.
Because he spent the last decade
looking for ways to kill Batman.
He managed to steal the rail gun
from Wayne R&D before
my sister pilfered it.
Maybe he'll know where we can find
whatever weapon we glean from this
journal.
And then we'll kill him.
Off to group therapy.
Mr. Calderone is right on the
verge of a real breakthrough.
Go get them, doc.
Heh, heh.
Of course, Hush took Luke,
his dad wrote the journals.
Anything?
I can't get a ping on either of
their phones.
What about running a trace on
Professor Carr's pacemaker.
- Yeah, maybe but not from this.
- How about that?
That looks older than my mom.
Sure you don't have anything
more modern, like a sundial?
Sorry, why does this rando teen get
to know that you're, Batwoman.
Let me see what I can do.
Julia.
It's a polyalphabetic cipher.
Okay.
That's a start.
- How many letters are in it?
- Hundreds.
Hundreds in multiple languages
and alphabets.
Well, can you work out the sequence?
So far, I got A corresponds
with Heth,
the first letter
of the Aramaic alphabet,
which is alphabetically the first
other alphabet my Daddy used.
B takes us to the Babylonian
alphabet, the next, alphabetically.
That's bloody brilliant.
Can't you slide one letter at a time?
No, I... I tried that.
That would be way too easy for my
Dad.
There's an interval variance
each time
he switches to a new alphabet.
Now, if l could figure out
the number sequence for the integrals
then I'd have the key to decrypt
this.
That leaves us ten minutes to work
out a few billion
random number sequences.
Except my Dad was meticulous.
It would never be random.
It'd be personal to him.
Or personal to me.
Okay. The first slide's five,
the second slide's three.
The third, five...
He used my social security number.
- Okay, no pressure...
- That's what people say
to pressure someone.
It's just that we're running
out of time.
I'm in.
Manufacturer's database says
there are three John Carrs
with pacemakers.
- Do you have their locations?
- Not yet,
but if I'm not careful, I could kill
the two John Carrs that aren't dead.
So, yeah, no pressure.
Anything I can do to help?
Can you bypass the data throttling,
get me more speed out of this heap?
Nope.
Then I'll settle for you not
distracting me.
Oh, how cute was baby Luke?
Hey, Mr. Fox.
Your frames are on point.
Glasses.
It's the glasses.
They can translate the journals, try.
The journals need these
to decode them.
You did it.
Didn't you?
You know what it says?
Yeah.
Why aren't you happier about this?
You did it!
What does it say?
Something that I can't tell anyone.
Most of all, Gotham's
least mentally stable villain.
I'm sorry.
Time's up. Pencils down. Now...
Read to me
from my new favorite bedtime story.
We're not telling you.
Does she speak for both of you or...?
My father was willing to die for this
secret.
And we're willing to do the same.
Okay, two of the John Carr pacemakers
are still active
and the third stopped working...
Here. Professor Carr's heart beat
for the last time at...
- No.
- Is that Arkham?
Alice is behind this somehow.
Reagan stole the journal
to get Magpie out of Arkham.
That's who she bought
her freedom from.
Not to state the obvious,
but Alice is an inmate.
She's also Alice. Being
captive is a way of life for her.
You know how Carr
had burn marks on his body?
Yeah.
I think I know
how she's torturing her victims.
How?
Oh, she usually doesn't tell
us what she's thinking.
So cool.
Hey, stop right there!
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
Sorry, guys, I didn't wanna do that.
By not having the right
tool. Can I get an "Amen"?
That's right, and when it comes to
drill bits, I'm the...
Delta 1566, give me a call on...
Batwoman just took out
a pair of guards at Arkham.
We're still rounding up perps
from the last breakout.
I want all available teams
getting a handle on this now!
- I can do this all day.
- Oh...
She's so strong.
Toasty.
Now, tell me what daddy had to say.
Do you not get it, Alice?
You are the reason
there's a code in the first place.
And you're the reason
Alfie Pennyworth has to go...
casket shopping.
Let them go.
I'm sorry, who are you?
All the torture therapy I've endured
has messed with the old noggin.
I said let them go.
Oh...
Batty...
You're outnumbered and sadly,
we don't do demands.
I'm not demanding, I'm trading.
These are Lucius Fox's glasses.
They unlock the code.
No.
Let Luke and Julia go
and they're yours.
- You cannot do this.
- If l don't, she'll kill you.
And she'll kill you!
The book doesn't contain
Bat-weapon designs.
It contains the secret to killing
you.
My offer stands.
Let them go.
Take these stairs to the bottom.
You'll find a hatch in the floor
to the tunnels.
- Get her out of here.
- Where you going?
To stop Alice and get the book back.
Hey!
Batwoman's in Cell Block D.
What did they do now?
Oh, we gotta get out of this place.
Our cover's blown.
Get the van, pull to the side lot,
by the air vents. We'll find you.
Alice, you gotta get back to your
cell now. Hey...
What are you doing?
No. No, no...
It was all very well and good while
it lasted, my dear Mouse.
Please, don't.
Yeah. Yeah.
Nice.
- Free.
- Come on,
we're headed to the main roof.
No!
Alice!
Help me!
This doesn't matter.
It does matter. We built a life for
us here.
It's over, Mouse.
We've been exposed.
- No!
- Let's go, tunnels now.
Get out, now.
Sir, we were too late.
It's World War III in there.
Lock it all down.
And find me the Bat.
Hey.
I thought you went home.
Let me just say something real quick.
You messed up today, okay?
I'm not worth the death of Batwoman.
I'm not worth seeing hundreds
upon thousands of citizens lose hope
as a result of whatever insane plan
Alice is formulating.
I am not worth all the lives that
could've...
We both know there's no Batwoman
without Luke Fox.
I was lost without you today.
- Good.
- Sorry. Hi.
I'm... Where... What...?
I am gonna go.
Thank you for your help today.
Not that you're gonna take advice
from a rando teen, but...
Sophie?
Maybe fight a little harder.
We'll see.
I was gone for five hours.
Yeah.
What's the damage?
Well, my left hand's numb.
Some nerve damage in my arm.
Medic thinks I'll heal eventually.
Or sooner.
- I'm glad you're okay.
- Me too.
Kate.
Looks like a bad time.
Hey.
I'm gonna go.
Luke told me everything.
He couldn't have told you everything
because he doesn't know everything.
I know you're lying about why you're
after a book that describes how to
kill me.
The Rifle showed up in Gotham
to assassinate you several months
ago.
I helped thwart him and he
disappeared.
Ever wonder why he never came back?
Because I followed him to his boss
and made a deal with her to stop
pursuing you.
In exchange for your life,
I'd fetch her the journal
and we'd both be on our merry way.
If she had the journal, she could
kill me.
She played me.
I didn't know what the journal
entailed till today.
Now that I do,
the deal's off.
Who is she?
Safiyah Sohail.
- I've never heard of her.
- Well, she's heard of you, love.
And now that I've double-crossed her,
we've both got targets on our backs.
How's Arkham?
It's a mess.
Psychotic escapees are all over this
city right now, thanks to you.
Thanks to Alice.
She had the entire asylum in...
Alice isn't the one claiming
to be the city's hero.
She needs you as much as
you need her.
The Joker had Batman like she has
you,
and guess who always ends up
as collateral damage?
I will protect my city.
No, you won't.
Because you're done. Get out.
You know I won't leave.
Let this serve as your warning.
If I see you again...
it's war.
This isn't a shelter,
Alice, this is...
back to where we started.
No one's forcing you to stay.
I told you that inviting Luke
into your obsession
would draw out
the Bat.
And now, here we are,
freezing, wet,...
drenched in sewer water!
And I told you that Luke would bring
us the answers that we need,
so I suppose we're both right.
I was happy, Alice.
I was happy.
What happened to you?
Do you ever care
that you burned the whole thing down?
I care...
about killing the Bat.
So, go bring me
that walking facial gone wrong
so he can tell me
where to find a little green rock...
Called kryptonite.