Previously on "Batwoman"...
Bruce never stopped looking
for your sister's body.
Catherine Hamilton's investigators found
skull fragments of a little girl.
It's Beth.
You never would have moved on
if you didn't think that Beth were dead.
I paid the DNA analyst
to write the report.
As hard as I have tried
to get over you, I can't.
It's definitely not fair to Tyler.
Maybe it's best if I keep
my distance from now on.
Daddy!
Catherine seems to think so.
We are to host
the most memorable mad tea-party
Gotham has ever seen.
Ha ha ha!
They say the choices we make define us,
but despite all the darkness,
despite all those who doubt,
and despite my own fear that
I've lost my sister forever,
I choose to hope that
Beth is still there.
Don't tell anyone, Bruce, but I
think this makes me an optimist.
- Give me your jacket!
- Wait. What?
Unh! Give me your jacket.
This is vintage, bitch.
Hyah!
Okay. Take it, take
it, take it, take it.
- Synced and Corrected By NaShWaN AL-YeMeN 2019 -
- www.subscene.com -
♪ Batwoman S01 - Ep08 ♪
Eps Title :- A Mad Tea Party
- Vintage.
- Thanks.
Not exactly my style or size.
Ooh. Is that blood? You
really shouldn't have.
Front right pocket.
Rabbit dropped it in there
before he made a run for it.
Think we can use the
phone's GPS to track Alice?
- I can try.
- Cool.
I see you broke the staff in two.
Like I wouldn't notice?
Sorry. For the record,
it'd be a whole lot cooler
if it actually came apart.
It doesn't, though, so...
Okay. Here is every location the
phone's gone to the past 7 days.
Where's this?
Ah. Slice of Gotham. Worst
breadsticks in the city,
but location two is a
little more promising.
It's a warehouse in The Bowery.
Then that's where she is.
Don't wait up.
Ohh! Too sad, too loud, too mundane!
Whaa! Why do I have nothing to wear?
Ugh. If you're going to kidnap me again,
do wait until I can dolly
up into something with, um,
a little more flair.
Did you hire The Rifle to kill me?
Says the walking, talking, living girl.
He shot someone that he
believed to be Batwoman
with the coil accelerator,
a weapon designed for only one reason...
To kill me.
The guy who designed it was found
with a butterfly knife in his heart.
Yeah. Mm-hmm. Let me rephrase that.
So an evil man was trying
to kill my twin sister,
and I ensured that that didn't happen.
What is this?
Uh, that is a multimillion-dollar
piece of technology
that allows the coil accelerator
to penetrate your suit.
That's the only one that
exists on the planet.
Anyone who knew how to make it is,
well, um, exactly that, past tense,
so... you're welcome.
Turn yourself in, Alice.
Let me help you.
I know my sister is in there.
Oh, this again.
You kept this...
From the day of our bat mitzvahs.
Take it and be gone.
I am quite busy, and
I have nothing to wear.
It's Kane. I'll be back
in Gotham later tonight.
We'll go over the floor plan for
the gala first thing tomorrow.
Talk then.
So the way I see it you can either spend
your Friday night in
here inhaling asbestos,
or you could join me
in wearing this season's
sexiest haute couture, hmm?
Seriously, Gigi and Bella could not
even get their hands on this yet.
You want me to go to that thing tonight.
That thing is the
Gotham Humanitarian Gala,
i.e. the most important
event of the season.
Honoring your mom, who told
my dad that Beth was dead.
Asbestos it is.
I get that we are bordering on too soon.
Hmm. Pretty sure we're
right in the middle of it.
I know that this isn't important to you,
but it's important to me, okay,
so why can't it be important to
you that it's important to me?
Because you think that if
Gotham sees us as a family
that we'll start to believe it,
and that's just not how it works,
not after what Catherine did.
But you gave Alice a second chance
and a third and a fourth.
How can you just write
off my mom as Satan
but you don't seem to have any problem
holding out hope for the actual
most evil person in Gotham?
Because she's my family.
And I'm not? Got it.
I guess I am the crazy one, you know,
for thinking that you and
I could still be sisters.
Of course you're my family.
It's just...
Different? Yeah. Do yourself
a favor. Stop digging.
Listen. Even if I wanted to go,
I could never do that to my dad.
You don't know? He
decided to come tonight...
For me.
Sorry for thinking that
you would do the same.
You're going to the Humanitarian Gala?
Yeah. I meant to talk to you about that.
Unless Catherine somehow
didn't fake Beth's death,
then I don't know what
there is to talk about.
Hmm.
- Are you getting back with her?
- Hmm.
When you've been with someone
for a decade and a half,
you don't just walk away.
You're letting her weasel
her way back into your life.
There's no weaseling, Kate.
We've been spending some time together.
When? You've been out of town.
Oh. You know, we had
breakfast when I got back.
You're seriously forgiving her?
I'm not defending what
Catherine did. She's not either,
but I'm beginning to
understand why she did it
as a mother,
as a wife.
She thought she was helping us move on.
Wake up, father dear.
Hmm. Why, what a long sleep you've had.
I thought it was high time you and I
finally had a daddy-daughter chat.
- That's all I want.
- Hmm.
Oh, come on. Not like this.
- Let me out of these chains.
- Shh.
You're not the commander here...
Commander.
Kate will know I'm gone.
Will she? Hmm.
Because I saw her last night,
and there was nary a mention of you.
Guess she's 0 for 2 in
missing family members.
What do you want me to say? I'm sorry?
There is no word to
describe what it feels like
to know that I left you behind.
Then find the words to explain
why you never tested the skull
fragments Catherine found.
I had no reason to
think that she was lying.
But your daughter was missing,
and this was just a handful of bones
found by some woman you'd
known for less than a year.
Maybe believing that you were dead
was easier than waking
up every morning with hope
or going to sleep every
night with a broken heart.
Of course, I should have looked longer.
I should have hoped harder,
I should have... I should have
had the DNA tested myself.
I wish... I wish I could
have been your father
for the past 15 years, but...
I failed.
I failed you.
Thank you for saying that.
And thank you
for making me who I am today.
What are you planning?
Tell me what to do to stop it.
Today is the day of my mad tea-party
to which you've been invited.
Hmm. I'm fairly certain you'll attend.
Catherine will be delighted,
but how can that be if you're stuck here
and still the guest of honor?
I guess you'll see as we drink tea
and someone ends up
a goner.
Catherine manipulated
my dad 15 years ago,
and here she is just doing it again.
My dad is the head of The Crows.
I mean, how is he even falling for this?
Alice has been on a killing
spree since you got back,
and this is what's got you
drinking Bruce's good stuff?
Alice was brainwashed
against her own will.
This is different. My dad is choosing.
He is choosing to
forgive a woman who lied
about the death of his daughter.
Catherine paid a team of scientists
to change DNA results.
My dad once found a joint in my backpack
and grounded me for a whole summer.
It doesn't make sense. This is not him.
- This isn't him.
- What am I missing?
If you're calling with a
lecture, I don't have time.
The opposite actually.
I know complicated
better than anyone else,
and if you want to work things
out with she who must not be named,
it's not my business.
Well, I appreciate that, kiddo.
And in thinking about it, I realized
that I never really
gave her a chance. Heh.
Remember the wedding
and the big snowstorm
and I just kept wishing that
maybe if we got snowed in
you wouldn't have to get married?
If only a snowstorm
were our biggest hurdle.
Anyway, I just wanted to say
I'm sorry and have fun tonight.
Thanks, Kate.
My dad married Catherine on
the hottest day of the year.
- So if that's not your dad, then...
- It's Mouse.
So you know those
vacation days we banked?
What if we took one of
our old-school road trips?
I was thinking down
south, maybe Dollywood.
Sounds cool.
What is up with you?
I just suggested a
road trip to Dollywood.
Nothing's up with me.
Nothing, or you're pretending to be cool
about Kate and me and you're
obviously still freaked?
Ty, if this is going to be a thing,
we should talk about it.
_
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I wanted to go over tonight's agenda.
As you know, this is one of
the city's biggest nights,
so I need you two to run point.
Sophie, you take the Alpha team
and cover the interior.
Tyler, you're with Bravo
locking up the perimeter.
Teams are already down in the theater
- beginning their sweep.
- _
I want this evening to
go off without a hitch.
Good evening, Gotham.
Tonight is the city's
Humanitarian Gala, which is rich person
for "let's dress up and
congratulate each other
on being rich and dressed up",
and it's all to honor Hamilton Dynamics'
matriarch of munitions
Catherine Hamilton-Kane.
Not sure how they're gonna fit a
Tomahawk missile into a swag bag.
So I'm en route to the
Humanitarian Gala with the rents.
What uuup?!
Where Mom is being honored
as the Gotham giver of
the year... #prouddaughter.
I just wanted to take a moment and say
how thankful I am for family
and for sticking by each
other through thick and thin.
That's what it's all about.
To Catherine, a most
extraordinary woman.
Cheers.
Ugh.
Must be time to move. Ha ha!
You are becoming incessant.
And you are becoming predictable.
Whatever you have planned for the gala,
The Crows are already on to it.
Tell me where Dad is.
Or what? You'll have me arrested,
institutionalized, killed?
You hate him. I get it. I would, too,
but he did not mean to hurt you.
You keep holding on so tightly
to the childish notion
that Beth is still in here.
If Beth is gone, then
why did you keep this?
You saved this for the
same reason you saved me
from The Rifle.
Because despite the hate,
the resentment, the rage,
there's still good, there's still Beth.
So tell me where Dad is.
I left him in the same place he left me.
Thank you.
Kate.
He's not doing so well.
You might want to be quick about it.
Dad?
Hi.
Good evening.
I assume you have everything in order.
10-4, Commander. All good here.
Got to hand it to you, Mouse.
That's impressive.
If you're not Jacob,
then you're...
Not a Crow. Oh, crap.
To date, the Hamilton Foundation
has donated countless millions
to fund work in the health,
emergency relief, poverty,
and education sectors
both globally and in Gotham.
All of these philanthropic efforts
are spearheaded by Catherine herself.
I can think of on one more deserving
of the Gotham humanitarian
of the year award
than Catherine Hamilton-Kane.
Whoo! Ha ha!
Whoo!
Thank you, Dr. Campbell,
for that wonderful intro
and to Mayor Akins
and the city of Gotham
for this great honor.
When I took over this
company from my father...
Tyler. Tyler!
Wake up!
What happened?
The commander tranqed us.
What?
Help! We're in here!
One-way windows, soundproof walls.
No one can hear us or see us.
Kate was right. Alice's new minion
is impersonating Jacob Kane.
I'm still way too drugged
up to process that.
Alice must be planning
something at the gala,
which is why she took us out.
I thought Alice was more of a...
Slit open our necks and pose
for a tea-party type murderer.
Ketamine's a little dull, no?
She didn't want to hurt us.
We're talking about
the same Alice, right?
She's trying to preserve
some sick relationship
with Kate, and killing me would...
Killing you would mean
Kate would never forgive her
because Kate's still in love with you.
I have no idea.
And what about you?
Any idea how you feel?
We should probably figure
out how to get out of here.
Today, Hamilton is a household name
in technology innovation.
_
She's fine.
"Tonight...
You honor me as one of Gotham's heroes,
an honor that I...
bought and paid for"...
"Quite literally with... blood money.
My company makes millions
by putting weapons of war
in the hands of Gotham's criminals"...
"And my husband...
rakes in even more by
protecting you from them".
Dad.
"Quite the scam we've been running,
wouldn't you say?"
"What my husband
doesn't want you to know
is that the true villains
of Gotham don't go
by the name Joker,
Riddler, or Alice".
"Gotham's true enemies
are right in front of you".
I... I... I...
Mom!
Mom, Mom, Mom!
Orpheum Theater. We need medics.
You hang in there,
sweetheart. You're okay.
Hello? Something's happened to my mom.
She's breathing, but we need
medical help immediately.
You keep an eye over
them until I get back.
Oh, my God. Where are you going?
I'm gonna meet the medical
help and bring them here.
- Okay. All right. Okay.
- Hang in there, sweetheart.
Oh, my God.
I didn't have a choice.
It's okay.
She made me.
Stay with me. Help is on the way.
Ladies and gentlemen, as we get medics
for Mrs. Hamilton-Kane,
please stay in your seats.
There's no cause for alarm. Please.
Everything's under control.
Stay in your seats.
There's no need to panic.
The Crows are holding us!
Let us out!
Okay. I'm in position.
Batwoman's here. Let's bounce!
Rrrraaahh!
Aah!
A little left.
Trying. Nope.
Other one.
- Got it.
- Nice.
Yeah. I'm really
regretting not getting you
a bigger one of these in this moment.
I wouldn't have wanted it.
You sure you still want this one?
Tyler.
It's a little hard to ignore the irony
of using the engagement
ring I got you to escape
your ex-girlfriend's lunatic sister,
who didn't kill us
because she knows more
about your past relationships than I do.
What do you want to know?
What was it between you two?
And don't say it was just
some drunk college hookup
unless you were actually
drunk for 3 years.
Look.
All my life I followed the rules,
my family's rules, the army's rules.
This was the first time I broke one,
and it almost cost me everything.
That's why I lied.
Didn't answer my question.
Let's go get some help.
Commissioner, with all due respect,
I need your men to stand down.
She's infiltrated The Crows.
If you breach, we're all dead.
Why isn't Jacob back?
He'll be back soon.
Your husband won't be joining you.
Get me the tray.
Catherine, you do not look so well.
You stay the hell away from us!
I'm not the one you should worry about,
for "It was all very
well to say, 'Drink me',"
but you should have first looked
to see whether it's
marked poison or not.
Oh! You poisoned her?
Group effort. I used a
Catherine Hamilton recipe,
project 4782.
Ring any bells?
4782?
Catherine, do you want to tell her?
I think her internal
organs are liquefying.
I'll just tell you.
It's a deadly neurotoxin
designed to kill without mercy.
First, there is the dizzy spells
and then nosebleeds and
then comes muscle paralysis
and, uh, oh, respiratory failure,
but lucky for us, Hamilton
developed an antidote.
Okay. You just got to hold on
until we can get that antidote.
Oh, no, my dear, I'm
confusing my stories.
Hamilton never even bothered
to develop an antidote.
If she dies, I'll kill you!
She made a choice.
Maybe if she'd made
better choices in the past,
we wouldn't be here right now.
You're just gonna let her die.
Aw, Mary, my darling,
impetuous stepsister,
I'm not a total monster.
No. I found a solution,
a universal cure-all
all the way from Coriana.
Where's Coriana?
Hmm. On a map or two.
It's made from a desert rose that blooms
only on the island.
One prick of its thorn
can kill you on the spot,
but harness the flower
and nurture its serum,
and it gives you life.
What do you want?
Hmm. A simple apology...
for all the pain you've caused me.
I'm sorry... Alice.
I just don't believe you.
Get me eyes on Alice and Jacob.
She said she was sorry!
You think I enjoy watching
a daughter lose her mother?
Gah!
I was just inches from my own mother's
severed head floating
down the Gotham river
after our car plummeted off the bridge.
Oh, please.
Please just try.
I can't lose you. Please just try.
I'm a mother.
Alice...
When I saw Kate grieving,
I saw my own daughter.
I just wanted to take away her pain,
but in trying to take away Kate's pain,
I gave you a lifetime of it.
It's all my fault, Alice.
All the lost years, all
the agony you endured,
it's all my fault. It's all...
I'm truly sorry.
Thank you, Catherine.
I do believe you've earned
a draught of this tea.
Oh!
Oh, dear. Not you, too.
What?!
Uhh. No. What did you do? How did you...
Tell me you didn't both
drink the champagne.
Oh, that's such a shame,
seeing as there's only
enough antidote for one.
Dad drank the champagne, too.
We need to go find him.
He'll be fine. He knows better than
- to poison himself.
- What?
He poisoned you, Mary.
Jacob would never hurt us.
Hmm. Getting closer.
You had someone impersonate him.
What?
The Skin Pirate.
There is an escapee from Arkham.
That wasn't Jacob in the limo.
There you go.
Now what were we talking about?
Yes. The choices we make.
Do choose wisely.
Okay. Maybe if we split it,
maybe we'll buy enough time
to get to the emergency room.
No, no. Alice would
have accounted for that.
No. Mom, we have to try, okay?
We have to try.
Mary, listen to me. Drink it.
No. There has to be another way.
Mary, I am your mother.
Ugh! Drink it.
It's okay.
Drink it.
Did you do it?
Jacob's drugged, and
I put him in the SUV.
- Good.
- He doesn't know what happened.
I have to go.
You're too late.
Where is my dad?
Our... dad.
You'll find out soon enough.
Whatever you did, you can undo it.
But I don't want to undo it.
I was locked in a cell
for 11 years.
What do you think put
me to sleep at night,
rainbows, unicorns?
I dreamt of revenge.
What did you do?
What did you do?!
"It was all very well
to say, 'Drink me',
but the wise little Alice
was not going to do that in a hurry".
Oh, come on. It's not like
Catherine didn't have it coming.
You poisoned Catherine?
Catherine poisoned Catherine
when she slithered into our family
and brainwashed our father
and replaced us with that vapid
human run-on sentence of a daughter.
Catherine brought this on herself,
and I was more than happy to watch
Daddy go down with her. Ha ha ha!
Unh!
Ha ha ha!
That's what I thought.
We need to go.
One way or another, dear sister,
you'll come to see my way.
Hang on, Mom.
They'll be here, they'll
pump your stomach,
they'll find an antidote.
You just got to hang on, okay?
I always wanted to see you work
in your clinic.
How did you know about the clinic?
I've always known.
How come you never said anything?
The fastest way for you
to stop doing something
was for me to approve of it.
Oh, my God.
Do you know how many wardrobe
changes I did in that elevator
thinking that I was fooling you?
Cameras in that elevator.
Ha ha ha!
Mom?
Mom. Shh. Yeah.
- Mary...
- Yeah?
You're the one thing I did right.
Nothing makes me prouder
than having raised you.
I love...
I...
love...
Mom? No, no, no, no, no, no.
Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom, stay with me.
Wake up.
Mom! Please!
Mom!
What is this?
Ohh.
- Kate.
- Who is this?
What? It's... it's me, Kate.
What did you get me
for my sixth birthday?
- What?
- What was it?
Ohh. It was, um...
It was a bike that was too big for you.
You wrecked it the same
day. What is going on?
Alice and Mouse were at the gala.
Get out of the car, Commander.
- Dad?
- I'll call you right back.
What's going on, Commissioner?
Hands in the air, Kane.
Commissioner.
Jacob Kane, you're under arrest.
I don't understand. What
are you talking about?
I've never seen that before in my life.
What the hell is happening?
Get your hands off of me!
Gotham is in shock tonight
over the death of Hamilton Dynamics CEO
Catherine Hamilton-Kane,
allegedly at the hands of her husband
and head of Crows security Jacob Kane.
Her death occurred
just after some stunning
and very public
admissions by Hamilton-Kane
while accepting an award at
Gotham's Humanitarian Gala.
Mary?
Mary.
Do you know how many horrible
people that I've saved?
Druggies... thugs with face tattoos.
Pulled a windshield out of a guy
who stole the car that he totaled.
Walked out of my clinic the next day
like nothing had happened,
but I...
I couldn't save her.
I am so sorry, Mary.
You know how she died?
Exactly the way that Alice planned it.
Slowly...
And in pain...
And the only way for her to save herself
was for me to die, and she sure as hell
wasn't about to let that happen
because she is not the horrible person
that you and Alice claim that she is.
You...
You are literally the last person
who can bring me comfort right now.
I'm gonna ask you again, Kate.
Is Alice worth it?
No.
Finally.
Too bad it's too late.
Agent Sophie Moore.
Yeah. It's been a
late night for us, too.
Just put me on with the Commissioner.
He's got the wrong guy.
Because I've got a dart
hole in my neck to prove it.
Please have him call me.
This is insane.
How can they think he actually did this?
People believe what they're told.
It's human nature.
Then people are idiots.
- I should call Mary.
- I want kids.
What?!
And a dog and... family traditions
that we bitch about but do anyways.
Okay.
I don't want to move past this today
and then have it come
up again in two years
and realize that I'm wasting my life
fighting for something
I can't actually have.
I don't want that either.
Do you love me?
Yes.
Are you in love with me?
Because if you love me, you'll
be real with me right now.
I don't know.
Let's not make this
any harder than it is.
I think you need to figure yourself out,
and when you do and if you see
the same future I do,
maybe I'll still be here.
Maybe I won't.
We all make choices, Bruce.
I chose hope.
And I chose to believe Beth
was still alive.
I chose to save my sister
from the monster she's become,
but by making that choice...
I lost my entire family
for the second time,
and now the only thing I'm left with
is the awful truth that Alice was right.
Beth is gone.
My lawyer could only get us 5 minutes.
I hate her so much, Dad.
When I get out of here, I'm gonna
put her down once and for all.
This time, I won't stop you.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly & chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
For so many years,
- I've traveled across worlds,
- _
across the multiverse to do one thing...
Kill you,
and now here, you save my life.
Submit and begin your life anew.
Show me.
The knowledge is within you.