This is constructed
of actual human skin?
Yeah. We've linked DNA on the mask
to dozens of individuals, all dead.
- I'm not following.
- Alice robbed a series
of morgues a months ago.
We think she was stealing skin off
corpses to help Mouse make that mask
so he could impersonate
Commander Kane
and kill Catherine in the
process.
Look, Dr. Campbell, your name carries
a lot of weight in this city.
We could really use your testimony.
I agree there's a definite
likeness to you.
But, the notion of a man crafting
a mask out of different skins
to perfectly resemble
the face of another man
and pulling it off convincingly,
this...
Is science fiction.
Right now,
we have an innocent man in prison
and a murderer in custody
who's refusing to talk.
Doctor, if there's any
way you can help with this...
I'm sorry.
You say you have, this Mouse
character under lock and key?
Yeah. We got him on 24-hour watch
in Gotham General.
I'll need to meet him.
I'll run a few tests and if they
convince me this is possible...
Then I'll sign
the affidavit testifying
that an innocent man
could have been framed.
Thank you, Dr. Campbell.
I hope I can get you
out of here. I really do.
We need you back at headquarters.
Don't doubt yourself.
- You'll find Alice.
- If I don't...
Her next victim is on me.
You wanna prove to this city
from Alice to every two-bit
criminal wannabe
that you're a force
to be reckoned with?
Well, then, you... you eliminate
the threat, at any cost.
Go, go, go.
Move, move, move.
Honestly, I don't know
who's a bigger threat to Gotham...
Alice...
Or us...
For letting her get away.
Hands up!
Don't move.
Show us your hands.
I want her dealt with, for good.
Which is why I'm ordering a B-42.
- Sure you can do that, Moore?
- It's acting commander.
And yes. If you see Alice,
do not hesitate.
Shoot to kill.
Weird observation, but, Gotham
seemed a lot less bumpy on my Earth.
Sorry, Beth.
I'm avoiding checkpoints.
We need to get you out of town.
Once we get you out
of The Crows's crosshairs,
we can figure out what's wrong
with you... Oh, my god.
Your ear.
You're bleeding.
It's getting worse. Speed up.
I would love to, Mary,
but slight problem.
Since when is there
a checkpoint here?
Guys, I can't exactly turn around.
Tell them I'm going into labor
and we need to get to a hospital.
Have you seen you?
- I can't breathe.
- Now, what the hell is the problem?
I'm obviously having an asthma attack
and in need of medical attention...
Okay. I'm sorry. Your asthma
attack's not very believable.
- You're yelling... Stop!
- Why can't you just lie?
- Guys!
- Yeah, we're screwed.
- Under the blanket. Go, go, go.
- Okay.
- It's tight.
- Guys, guys, guys, I gotta stop.
Look, not to pull the whole,
"Do you know who my father is?"
but maybe the reason Alice
escaped your custody
in the first place
is because the Crows have a tendency
of overlooking minor details
like, "Hi, my dad is your boss."
- Miss Hamilton.
- Exactly.
So if you could tell your boys
to stand down.
- Just trying to do our job, ma'am.
- And we so do appreciate it.
Go Gotham.
Okay, I need you
to step out of the car.
That was my Yorkie.
Automatic weapons are
giving him anxiety.
Get out of the damn car!
Hey, we're cool. Just gonna reach
for my seatbelt, okay?
Any ideas?
Panic?
Step out of the vehicle, ma'am.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay.
Really, we're doing this?
Got someone in the back.
What's going on?
Halt. Stop!
Go!
Apologies for a late broadcast,
Gotham.
Like many of you,
I was stopped on my way to work
by Crows agents looking for Alice.
On the upside, I'm pretty sure
that involuntary pat-down
counts as my annual mammogram.
Holy police state, Batwoman.
Can we find her already?
What are we looking for?
Now, see, I wouldn't
be caught dead in that uniform.
But I'm glad you were.
Hey, you figured it out yet?
No swelling, no pressure build-up.
Her hearing is fine.
Hemophilia causes nosebleeds,
but she has no signs of any bruising
and it doesn't explain the migraines.
All of that is to say that no,
I haven't figured it out yet.
But I won't stop until I do.
You missed all the fun.
Batwoman showed up and saved us.
Really? That's fortunate.
She likes me.
Plus, she kind of owed me one.
Really?
- Okay, problem.
- What?
Her cells are disintegrating
on a molecular level.
May I? I'm no expert at multiverses.
But you are two credits
shy of astrophysicist.
So whatever you're thinking, spill.
I've read some theories
on multiple universe hypothesis.
Inflation model,
MWI of Quantum Mechanics.
MWI?
- Many-Worlds Interpretation.
Does anyone here
speak real people?
Right.
In my research, I theorized that all
of these universes
are separated for a reason.
If I'm right, it means Alice has one
mother of a headache now too.
Collateral damage
from the multiverse collapsing.
In other words, this universe is
literally not big enough
for the both of us.
And the longer
we coexist in this world...
the more we're living
on borrowed time.
Except, we're borrowing it
from each other.
As cells decay, the body goes
haywire. Synaptic misfire.
Pain receptors go into overdrive.
Until eventually...
If we can't find a way to save you,
you're both gonna die.
So not to pile on, but according
to this neurodegeneration program
at this rapid rate
of cell deterioration
"eventually" is about
seven hours from now.
Does alcohol slow down
degeneration or something?
Here.
No, but it gives me a buzz
while I face my mortality.
You are not going to die, right?
Okay. So, when in your mind
did I become proficient
in extraterrestrial cell decay?
We need to get her to a hospital.
Where the Crows will kill her
before anyone can say "multiverse".
See? Whiskey.
We have three of the smartest people
in Gotham in this room right now.
Put your heads together
and think of something.
Where are you going?
If Beth is enemy
number one in Gotham,
then we have to get her
to a hospital outside the city.
Maybe a face-to-face
with this new commander
can help us get past
the check points.
I'm sorry.
By telling her what, exactly?
- I haven't figured that out yet.
- I have.
It's easy. All you have say
that an event called Crisis
merged an infinite number
of universes resulting
in Alice's not so-evil twin
from another earth
ending up on this earth.
Just ask Supergirl or the Flash.
And oh, by the way,
I swear, I'm not Batwoman.
Orders to transport the inmate.
- Get away from me.
- Mouse.
It's me, my darling.
I've come to get you out of here.
How are you doing that?
How are you her?
How am I who?
You're speaking nonsense.
"The Queen of Hearts,
she made some tarts,
all on a summer day.
The Knave of Hearts,
he stole those tarts," and?
- Yeah.
- And?
"And took them quite away."
What's wrong with you?
- Alice?
- Yes.
- Who the hell else would I be?
- She tricked me.
- Who?
- A girl...
With your face,
and your eyes and your smile.
Alice, she was...
She was you, I swear.
That, that girl and your sister,
they convinced me she was you.
That's how Kate got away,
how I ended up here.
It was a perfect match
and I believed her.
Alice, your ear.
I do believe you to be right
and something else to be wrong
from beginning to end.
Why are your ears bleeding?
You have enough on your plate
without having to worry about me.
Where... where are you going?
Change of plans, little Mouse.
I have some digging to do.
And when I find my answers,
I'll be back for you.
I know you will.
Eyes on all the floors.
Dumpsters, rafters, drain pipes.
Remember, she's a sewer rat.
You ambushed five of my guys
at a checkpoint last night.
Care to explain?
Detaining the former
commander's daughter?
That's a statement. Besides,
what happened to probable cause?
Alice got away on my watch.
It's on me to find her.
- And it's on me to protect my city.
- Copy that.
So, if the law-breaking vigilante is
done telling me how to do my job...
I should get back to it.
Call off the shoot-to-kill
order on Alice.
Why are you protecting a terrorist,
all of a sudden?
I'm protecting you.
Is this really how you wanna
start your command?
Brushing up innocents?
Unlawful searches?
Your boss is in jail.
You're losing your clients.
And half the city thinks the Crows
are on some kind of power trip.
A manhunt like this
puts innocent lives in jeopardy.
Alice puts innocent lives
in jeopardy.
Then let me find her.
My way.
- Tell the Crows to stand down.
- Are you crazy?
You once told me you trusted me.
- I'm sorry.
- Commander Moore.
I can't.
Coming back out.
Remember me, commander?
Dodgson.
I take that as a yes.
What about Cryo technology?
Bruce knew a guy
with a Cryogenetic tank.
We freeze your body in cryostasis
and slow the cell deterioration.
So a -196 degree bath
in liquid nitrogen?
- Yeah. That sounds survivable.
- Fair.
Hyperbaric chamber?
We could simulate high altitude
and increase my red blood cell.
You'll never adapt
to hypoxia in the...
Three hours
and 37 minutes you have left.
It'll probably just kill you faster.
Okay. I'll just keep drinking.
We have to be able to think of
something.
We already have, Luke.
We're both just too polite to say it
because it's the one option
that Kate refuses to consider.
The Earth's balance can't handle
the existence of two Beth Kanes.
In order for one of us to live...
The other has to die.
You are...
Not me.
A cataclysmic collapse
of another universe?
An infinite number, actually,
probably having existed
in parallel past, present
and future timelines.
"Alice thought
the whole thing very absurd,
but they all looked so grave
that she did not dare to laugh."
How did you get in here, Alice?
The front desk guy, Kyle...
Kent?
- Karl?
- Karl, yes.
You'll find him in
the janitor's closet.
Well, we need a new plan,
Sophie is not messing around...
You weren't going to tell me, Kate?
We have a sister.
You haven't exactly
made yourself available.
Here I am.
And...
Here you are.
Smart.
Friendly.
Adorable.
Leave her alone.
No. It's... it's okay.
I understand why she resents me.
Oh, goody. Let's add
"blindly empathetic" to the list.
I'm just saying...
I wasn't held captive
for half my life.
I'm confused.
Surely, someone found you
washed up on the riverbank
after mommy's car crashed
into the river.
No one found me.
Because I never washed up
onto the riverbank.
Then how did you survive
the infamous crash?
Do tell.
I doubt you simply swam
to shore like a nimble little frog,
paddling past mother's head
as it bobbed in the rapids.
Beth didn't go over.
But there was a crash.
Was there not?
Oh, I see.
So on your Earth...
Rather than simply standing by
and sobbing...
your Kate pulled you
from the car before it fell.
I've always wondered
what my life would have been like
if you had saved me.
I just never imagined
that I'd be so...
Basic.
Eyes that never had
to witness the horrors that I saw.
Ears that never had
to hear the evils I heard.
Lips that never had
to beg for her life.
Two Beth Kanes
can't exist at the same time.
Technically speaking,
we are an anomaly
of intergalactic proportions.
Got it.
So in order for one of us to live...
The other has to die.
Now, I am no astrophysicist.
But I'm pretty sure
that two minus the one
who doesn't belong
means I get to live.
And my knife is pretty good at
subtraction.
How did you do that?
- Alice, stop!
- Kate, Beth needs you.
We're running out of time.
You got a trial date yet?
They're a little slow around here.
I thought you and I could use
a little alone time to talk.
I didn't think you did anything
without Alice's permission.
The only thing more dangerous
than a corrupt man...
Is one who thinks he's noble.
Not sure I need a morality lesson
from the guy
who sided with one of Gotham's
most prolific killers.
Alice had a psychotic break
to survive.
She never claimed to be good.
You did.
But your men tampered
with evidence.
Bribed and beat the people
who were too poor
to afford the Crows' services.
Your men killed good people.
So now I'm gonna kill you.
Thank you.
You're better to me alive, puppy dog.
According to my sources,
you're on your way out of here.
And now that I got a target on my
back for saving a glorified cop,
it's only a matter of time
before I need you
to return the favor.
Cell abnormalities...
Common birth defects...
Where are you, cosmic catastrophes?
Oh, look, another sister.
Do no harm, remember?
Help me.
- No?
- You...
are not allowed to discriminate.
Do something.
Freak show cosmic anomalies
are way above my pay grade.
Lest we forget...
I saved your life.
Oh, lest we forget, you had your
creepy, little door mouse
dress up as my dad
- and poison me and my mom.
- But you lived.
Healed from the...
Poison instantly.
Because I gave you
the only antidote on the planet.
The serum from
the Coryana Desert Rose.
People underestimate you, Mary.
Turns out...
you are very, very useful.
No!
Paging Dr. Stateman
to the mental ward, please.
Dr. Stateman, please.
Jonathan Cartwright.
My name is Dr. Ethan Campbell
and I am a plastic surgeon
here in Gotham.
I understand that you've pulled off
quite the scientific feat.
Consider me... intrigued.
I'm not speaking to anyone.
Look at you, all grown up.
Out in the world,
with friends who love you.
From my research, it seems
that you even got yourself a job
at Dusty's Roadside Tavern.
You see, purpose in life
is a hard thing to come by.
I would know.
I spent a decade reestablishing mine.
- Am I supposed to know you?
- That's precisely the point, Johnny.
You aren't.
No.
My purpose?
Shielding my son from ridicule.
Carving out a pocket
in a world of anguish
so that he could feel love
and joy.
That purpose...
was undone when...
my own boy...
betrayed me.
Dad?
Hello, son.
It is a father's greatest joy to see
his son follow in his footsteps.
You could have made me so proud.
- I thought you were dead.
- As I intended.
Meanwhile, I took on
the life I deserved.
Recognition, praise, prestige.
But...
At the cost of losing you.
Because of her.
- Tell me where Alice is.
- Why?
So, you can kill her? That...
Tell me where she is, Johnny,
so I can forgive you.
Forgive me?
For what?
For standing up to my abuser?
For being a weak little boy.
Too powerless to realize
a broken girl
with a distorted imagination
was taking advantage of you.
- You... you gave her to me.
- As a playmate.
And you...
Let her convince you
that she was family.
She was my family.
She accepted me.
All of me.
The scars, the burns, the face...
you raised me to believe was
too repulsive for the world to see.
You looked at me
and you saw a monster.
She saw the window to the world.
I will never...
ever betray her.
- Tell me where she is, son.
- What are you doing?
Making it so you no longer have a
choice.
No, no, no.
Let me have it!
Mary!
My brilliant, beautiful stepsister.
I beg you.
As a family.
That blood is the only thing
that will keep me alive.
I know.
And I can't think
of anyone who deserves it less.
Crows Security.
I understand you're looking
for the leader of
the Wonderland Gang.
I believe I know
where that little wench is hiding.
Good news, Mary called.
Said she found something out.
- She's on her way.
- I like her.
Promise me you'll protect her, okay?
We are not having
those conversations, okay?
You're gonna make it through this.
You just have hold on.
Distract me, then.
What's a Good Luke's deal?
Why?
Okay, the hallucinations
have definitely started.
What about you?
Why are you still single?
You sure this is how you wanna spend
your last 45 minutes?
You and I...
We never did
the "twin jealously" thing.
We're always looking out
for each other.
Checking in.
Getting advice.
But there was one thing that you had
that I always wanted.
- A soulmate.
- Really?
Anyone I know?
Alice, we know you're inside.
Surrender immediately.
We have the building surrounded.
I'm at the west entrance
of Wayne Tower. Position for entry.
What the hell is going on?
Alice called the Crows
hoping they would kill you.
Even on her deathbed,
she's ruthlessly brilliant.
We have a major breach.
They're in the lobby,
ascending the east and west stairs.
- Lock the elevators.
- They're gonna be here any second.
Kate?
Kate!
- Batcave, now.
- Okay.
Wait. What?
If the Crows find you,
they will kill you.
Yeah, I know...I got that.
Where are we going?
Catherine?
I see.
I'm being haunted on my deathbed
by my past sins.
I'm so scared.
The universe must
think fondly of Kate
to give her everything she wants...
the version of you that she lost.
You don't know my sister.
No. I beg to differ.
I've known her almost
as long as you've known her.
Because you're a snake...
Who slithered her way into my family.
I was accepted...
By your father, by your sister.
And despite all of the mistakes
that I made, I showed remorse.
You don't have any remorse, Alice.
You're evil through and through.
And that's why Kate
will never choose you.
Here's what's gonna happen.
Mary is gonna take
that syringe to Kate...
And tell her that it
will only save one of us.
And Kate...
Kate's gonna pick me.
For your sake, I hope that's true.
But just in case
she chooses otherwise...
I'll save you a seat in hell.
Well, I finally found something
on this Earth to be jealous of.
Why risk your life every night
for a city of strangers?
Well, I think not saving Beth
that day on the bridge
ignited something in me.
You couldn't save your
own mom and sister, so...
Now, you save every mom and sister.
Guilt can make sane people
do crazy things.
This isn't guilt.
This is courage.
Okay. You need to sit.
So the Crows are searching this
place, top to bottom.
I counted 50 or so on foot.
They have ten trucks outside,
a chopper in the air.
We really gonna have
to wait them out.
We don't exactly have time
to wait.
Mary, where have you been?
Okay. I'll be right out.
What the hell happened?
Alice called the Crows
and send them into the building.
Oh, my God. Did they find Beth?
She's fine.
I have a panic room. remember?
Okay. That's right. It's genius.
- Okay. So how do we save them.
- What?
You said you found a way
to save them, what is it?
No, no, no. I said I found a solution
to save one. Beth.
My blood.
When Alice poisoned me,
she gave me an antidote.
The serum from
the Coryana Desert Rose.
She claimed it was
a universal cure-all
and it worked like a charm.
So we give it to them both.
Then it will cancel out
and we'll end up right
where we started.
One has to have
the edge over the other,
even if it's just a few seconds.
My blood will regenerate enough
of Beth's red blood cells
for her to live a little bit longer.
And Alice dies?
And I walk away
from her all over again?
You are not actually
considering saving Alice...
are you?
Kate. This is a no-brainer.
And not to rush you, but you've
got less than 20 minutes
before they're both dead.
So go in there and save one of
the most compassionate,
smartest humans that I've ever met.
Or go back into that clinic
and save Alice, who killed my mom.
The choice is yours.
Kate.
- That's not really you.
- It's me.
Tell me you found Mary.
- Yeah.
- And did she...
The syringe?
I know her blood is the key
to saving you.
I knew you'd come back.
I knew you'd choose me.
- Hey.
Can we have a minute?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
You're not gonna tell me
who my soulmate was, are you?
And ruin all the fun?
Luke told me about the blood.
I'm sorry you're in this position.
More sorry you are.
Look, before you make your
decision...
Can I just say, after spending time
with... with Alice...
face-to-face, her rage, her pain.
Somehow, I understand her.
If the circumstances
had turned out differently...
They didn't. I didn't act.
I didn't save her.
I did nothing.
And I'm not about
to do nothing again.
You have to hurry.
- Alice.
- Oh, Kate.
There's... There's no time.
Do it.
I came to say goodbye.
What?
Goodbye, Alice.
No.
Are you sure this is
what you wanna do?
Just you asking that is proof
that I made the right choice.
You've always been my hero.
You have to get her out of here.
They're tearing through
this place book by book
and it's only a matter of time
before they find the elevator.
Yeah. But there's still the small
problem of the checkpoints.
Right. Take my bike.
The tunnels will get you
past the parameter of the building.
And... and the bike will get you
through the checkpoint.
- I'll be there as soon as I can.
- Just back up.
Take your...
- Your who now?
- Bat bike.
Okay. Yeah. I'll just make sure
I heard what you said.
Kate.
I don't know how can
I ever thank you.
You're alive and that's all that
matters.
Hey.
Why?
Because she's pure...
And good?
You don't even know me.
Not the real me.
I know what you showed me.
I couldn't save you.
And all I can hope is
that you find peace.
Kate, stay with me?
I'm here.
Halt. Stop!
William Checkpoint to Moore.
- Go for Moore.
- Possible Bat sighting
blazed through William Checkpoint,
headed north.
Unknown passenger, looked female.
It could be Alice. Possible target.
- Want us to pursue?
- Negative. Stay put. I'm on it.
Oh, I hope that guard
won't miss his face.
What the hell are you doing
to me?
Hush now, son.
I'll be back for you soon.
Man, the acceleration index...
Moore to base.
I need backup for an arrest
at the Twin Pines Inn.
No. Hey. No, no, no.
Hey. Oh, come on.
Hey. No. Come on. Wake up,
Beth. No. Beth, come on.
No, no, no.
You...
Let me die.
But I didn't.