All there.
Used, unmarked bills, as promised.
Congratulations.
You're now, the new proud owner
of seven hearts,
14 kidneys,
seven livers, 14 lungs...
and 14 corneas.
Some disassembly required.
Get her, get her!
Where'd she go?
She's over there,
she went that way. Go, go!
Get her!
I'm just saying,
like a braid could help.
I am not wearing a braid.
Congratulations!
On behalf of the medical profession,
both licensed and unlicensed,
I'd like to offer my sincerest
"what up" on shutting down
that chop shop.
I wasn't sure how you
guys celebrated.
Usually by icing my knuckles.
So, this is what a victory
lap looks like.
Trafficker got away.
Some asshat yanked my wig,
almost pulled off my cowl.
Who could've predicted that
30,000 strands of grab-me red hair
would be like waving
a flag in front of a bull?
What if you ran an electrical charge
through the cowl
so the next person
who tried to get grabby
would have 10,000 volts
of "hands off"?
As much as I love the thought
of wrapping my head in lightning...
Right. Dumb.
I've had a few of these. Withdrawn.
We will celebrate.
As soon as we get this
organ-selling creep behind bars.
Okay.
Well, go Bat-team.
Which I am not on.
Taking the champagne.
Backing away.
The cowl shock thing,
not the worst idea.
She wants to be part of this
and the answer is no.
She doesn't wanna be part of this
as much as she wants
to be part of your life.
Then I will take her out for dinner.
We need to focus on
your dad's journal.
If that thing really is the cookbook
of Wayne Enterprise's
best-kept secrets
we need to find
where Tommy Elliot hid it.
So, where do we start?
Whichever aisle has the property
seized from Tommy Elliot.
Of course, Tommy collected like
every Kitty Delgado comic.
Oh, my God.
Well, there's no way a cat burglar's
squeezing into all
those tight spaces
with those jubblies.
So, if I were the smoking gun
that links Tommy Elliot
to the murder of Lucius Fox
- where would I be?
- I don't know, love.
But I hope the Crows pay overtime.
I'll settle for hazard pay.
Tell me you found that journal.
We've gone through the entire place,
which is basically a shrine
to his twig and berries.
But, alas, no Lucius Fox journal.
The guy owned at least 40 buildings
in Gotham alone.
Who knows where he
could've stashed it?
Well, there is one person who knows.
Candy Kane.
Why, your real estate business
must really be tanking
if you were willing to let them frisk
you for quite a few how-to's.
Believe it or not, Tommy boy,
I'm not here for a measuring contest.
That's too bad.
Speaking of being the bigger man...
have you heard from Bruce?
Visiting hours are four days a week,
he's total no-show.
Is that any way
to treat your best friend?
It is.
If you killed his actual best friend,
Lucius Fox.
That's an outrageous lie.
Lucius was never Bruce's best friend.
Of course, that would be
your take away.
What did Lucius Fox ever do
for Bruce?
You mean besides
turning Wayne R&D
into the world leader
in defense technology?
Oh, but you already knew that.
That's why you had him killed.
For his journal.
You wanted the keys
to the candy store.
Where's the journal now, Tommy?
I miss...
I miss my mommy!
Can I talk to her?
That's okay, Tommy.
The guy you hired to pull the
trigger, he's had a lot to say.
Thanks for stopping by, double K.
And tell your cousin,
the bells are on!
It's fine, thank you.
Get out of my cell.
But yours is so much
roomier than mine.
And there's going to be a vacancy
when they strap you
to the electric chair
for murdering Lucius Fox.
Oh, but Alice, haven't you heard?
I'm crazy, a hundred percent
unfit to stand trial.
Not anymore, I'm afraid.
I got a call this morning
from a judge asking my opinion
in regards to your fitness
to stand trial.
As Arkham's chief medical officer,
I could hardly lie.
So, the Crows will be
here soon to collect you.
But we can help you.
Why...
would you help me?
Because you're gonna help us.
I couldn't help but listen in
to your little visit with Kate Kane.
Because when my sister
wants something,
I want it more.
What's so special about the dearly
departed Lucius Fox's journal?
- Just between us bad guys.
- I'm sorry.
Are you two working together?
What's going on here?
You can answer
the question voluntarily...
or we will extract it.
Supposedly, it's a fail-safe...
to kill the Bat if the suit
ever got into the wrong hands.
Why is Bruce Wayne's R&D guy
telling dear diary about that?
Because Bruce Wayne is Batman.
"Curiouser and curiouser."
And now, I want to know all the more.
Where is the book?
I'm just debating...
It should I hand it over to...
Gotham's most prolific killer
for nothing in return?
Give us the journal
and we will let you walk out of here.
Really?
Well, just out on to the street where
every wanted poster will have my...
face on it?
Not if we get you a new one.
This is what it's like bartering
with a psychopath.
We can make you into anyone
you want to be.
Real, imagined.
Whoever your little heart desires.
So, do we have a deal?
You called it. Whatever you said
must have rattled Tommy's cage.
Twenty-two minutes
since you left Arkham
and there's already an
outgoing call to...
- Address says The Lookout.
- Isn't that Johnny Sabatino's club?
Technically, but Tommy
owns the building.
Sabatino's been laundering
Tommy's money through
their club for years.
That is one posh laundromat.
Tommy, how's the padded palace,
buddy?
Hoping to make it a distant memory.
Listen, remember that item
I had you hold onto?
What, the one you had me break into
your office to get the
night you were arrested?
No idea what you're talking about.
Oh, yeah, it's still here.
Living rent-free.
Well, it's time for it to come home.
Understood, I'll be in touch
to work out the details.
Well, at least we know
where the journal is.
Yeah, at the very high floor
of a mob-infested nightclub.
How would you like
to infiltrate that?
By walking through
the front door.
Wait. You feel that?
Nope. Feeling nothing.
What is happening?
I think you feel it.
- Okay.
- We're...
- going clubbing?
- We're going clubbing.
Okay, so these are all the finalists,
because they deliver on the
and Bat-gadget concealment.
Because we wanna hide the goods,
but not hide the goods.
You feel me?
Okay, the goal is to blend in.
Yeah, but at this place,
standing out is blending in.
I mean, The Lookout
is the hottest club in Gotham.
No offense to your bar, it's...
It's more of a lounge.
And fortunately, your Bat-boots
are both functional and on trend.
What's in that one?
Oh, that is mine.
Check it.
How insane is this?
Oh, but if you wanna
wear it instead, you can.
You're not going, Mary.
- What?
- I'm sorry, it's too dangerous.
Dangerous? I've been poisoned,
stabbed and nearly exsanguinated.
And the fact that I lived to use
that word as a verb is proof
that I can look out for myself.
That place will be filled
with mobsters.
Which is why you need backup.
I already have it.
I thought there weren't any more
spots on the Bat-team.
Oh, I'm just an honorary member,
love.
The Crows plucked her from the SRR.
She's literally trained for this.
Seriously, it's nothing personal.
And thank you so much
for all of this.
Sounds like Soph's on her way
to arrest Tommy Elliot.
Good for Soph.
Yeah. With Robles's confession,
they're charging Tommy
with Lucius Fox's murder.
Luke will be glad to hear that.
Is all official Crow's business
conducted using hamburger emojis?
It's a cheeseburger.
She wanted to see
if I was out celebrating.
You never mentioned
she was a burger connoisseur.
Don't bother trying to convince her
that kimchi is the best topping.
I've already taken that hill.
It's her new favorite.
When?
What do you mean?
When did you find time
to take on that hill?
Don't you two have, like,
work or something?
All we do is work, love.
Between the late hours
and all the stress with her mum,
let's just say greasy food's
her best mate right now.
Her mom?
Yeah, she came out to her mum.
Seriously?
Gravely serious, I'm afraid.
Mum's not talking to her.
Soph's a right mess.
Good evening, party crashers.
Tuxedo One, you have a date
with the utility hub one level down.
Red One, there's an employee
bathroom on the north end.
Could be a good place
for a wardrobe change.
- Copy that.
- 10-4.
The classic way that you move
Ok, ok now you've got my attention
Can't take my eye off of you
Kate?
Reagan?
- Hi.
- What're you doing here?
Don't you have a club
of your own now?
I'm checking out the
competition.
Promise not to tell your boss?
Only if you let me make you a drink
on the house.
If you promise not to tell my boss.
- Deal.
- I actually stopped by
The Hold Up a couple of times.
I was hoping...
I don't know. Maybe
I would run into you.
I don't really oversee the
day-to-day.
Too busy?
Yeah. I remember.
At the risk of sounding
even more stalkery,
I've been following
your real estate endeavors.
Buying up property around Bennet Park
and actually lowering the rents?
This city could use a
lot more Kate Kane.
Cheers.
- This is really good.
- It's called an...
"I sort of thought
you'd fight harder to win me back
and I've regretted
walking away ever since."
That is very specific.
Any chance you know how to make
a "Kate Kane is a total idiot"?
You ask her to make a
"What the hell are you doing"?
You have a mission to complete.
Is your ear okay?
It's fine.
Can you hear that
annoying whining sound?
Hilarious.
No, I don't.
I'm gonna get an Advil.
Okay.
Smooth.
I'm not talking to you.
Tuxedo One, you still talking to me?
I'm here. Found the controls.
Intense. Johnny really likes
keeping tabs on his clientele.
But his office is completely empty.
I'm thinking it's time
for lights out.
Is it a power outage?
Hey!
Bloody hell.
I'm made.
We got a problem. Julia's been
grabbed. I think this is a trap.
The building's schematics
shows a wall safe.
I'm betting it's in there.
Or it's just sitting on his desk.
Awfully important book
to just leave lying around.
Kate? Kate, come in! Kate?
Mr. Elliot's cell is 243.
Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall,
Humpty Dumpty had a great fall
All the kings horses
and all the king's men
Couldn't put Humpty
together again
But he was an egg.
And never should've been sitting
on that wall in the first place
and honestly, what were a bunch
of horses gonna do?
When do I get my face?
As soon as I get that journal.
And it's not just a face,
Tommy, it's a whole new you.
What's the deal with the other one?
Mary Poppins says she works for SRR.
A little out of her zip code.
Talk to our guys across the pond,
see if she's worth anything.
Take her in the back.
And let's put the word out
to the families.
We're auctioning off Batwoman
to the highest bidder.
Winner gets to cure Gotham
of its bat problem.
Yeah. You got it, boss.
What do you mean they caught her?
What happened to your member of
the Special Reconnaissance Regiment?
Turns out that I'm not good...
I didn't call you for a Yelp review,
Mary. I need you on the comms.
- Monitoring the cameras for me.
- What?
I'm going in to save Kate and Julia.
Going in as what?
Sabatino's accountant?
No offense, this is not gonna
get you past the bouncer.
It has to be me.
Okay, no offense, but you're insane.
I know Sabatino's cousin.
I pumped her stomach when she OD'd.
She owes me one. She can get
me face time with her cousin.
And then what? Ask him nicely?
Offer to tag his club in your Insta?
You sound like Kate.
Because she's right, Mary.
It's too dangerous.
Case in point, she was
just apprehended.
- What's the Bat-protocol here, Luke?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
All I do know is that I really
wish my dad were here
because he would
know what to do.
But he's not.
Because he died protecting
that journal,
now, Kate and Julia
might do the same
and I cannot add you
to that list.
Look, I know no one trusts me
to pull this off,
but I trust you to keep me safe.
Okay.
Fine. Then you're gonna need
some Bat-accessories.
Don't worry. They go with everything.
Tomcat.
Hey, man, thanks,
for giving me the need-to-know
on our uninvited guests,
but I gotta ask,
how'd you know, Batwoman would
be coming for the journal?
Well, I have friends in low places.
- Yeah, that I know.
- The Bat's been
a thorn in my bottom line
for too long.
- Can't wait to clip her wings.
- Oh, well, you enjoy that, buddy.
- Where's the journal?
- Yeah, see, here's the thing.
If that book was so important
that the Bat-baby wanted it,
thinking that you
undersold me on its value.
- So, I'm gonna hang on to it.
- Johnny, Johnny, Johnny.
Don't be a dick.
Tommy, your accounts
are frozen, you're on ice.
Can you blame me
for giving you the cold shoulder?
Take care of yourself, buddy.
That son of a bitch was
like a brother to me!
Clearly, you are an only child.
Otherwise, you'd know that
our dearest siblings
are the ones most
predisposed to betray us.
Why aren't you more upset?
Considering you won't be getting the
journal you so desperately want.
You should be more careful
who you trust.
If you can't trust a money launderer,
who can you trust?
No one.
I only trust in the fact
that people can't be trusted.
So, you knew that Johnny
was gonna betray me?
No.
I just didn't trust him not to.
Well, congratulations,
Alice, you were right.
But you still don't have the book.
I have a contingency. You see...
I released a rare bird
from her cage here at Arkham.
Gotham's most notorious
feather-clad klepto.
The chick who thinks
she's a myna bird?
She prefers to be called Magpie.
Dance for me, dance for me
Dance for me oh, oh, oh
Vodka. Venti.
Woman after my own heart.
Sure that's the best idea?
Aria!
Hi.
I'm... not placing you.
Oh, picture me upside down,
holding a bedpan of your puke.
- Oh, my god. Mary, hi!
- Hi!
Okay, I'm impressed.
What are you doing here?
I was actually looking for
your cousin.
Oh, cousin Johnny? He's just
in a super intense meeting right now.
Oh, I know, with a bunch of his...
Do not say crime families.
- Mafia bros.
- Mafia?
- Yeah. You're dead.
- Or his frat bros or something?
I don't know,
but he texted me 911 with typos.
Issues with embarrassing
nosebleeds from the...
Oh! Say no more.
Let me see what I can do.
Sweating through this
dress right now.
You're doing awesome.
Sold to Vasily Kosov.
You are the proud owner
of Batwoman's very own grappling gun.
All right, now,
onto the final item of the night
and let's face it,
the reason you're all here.
Give you the Scarlet Knight herself.
We will start the bidding
at two million dollars.
Two million, do I have two
and a half?
How about three million?
- Come on, do I have four?
- Ten million dollars.
So, who are you supposed to be?
The Bat's sidekick?
I'm gonna tell you
what I told you nine punches ago.
I'm not with Batwoman.
I'm with the Special
Reconnaissance Regiment.
That's interesting.
Because I just got off the phone
with our contact at the SRR.
He says you haven't been under
their employ for the past six months.
Something about going rogue
and betraying the
organization's trust.
Now...
let's start fresh.
Shall we?
Who are you really working for?
This is a surprise.
Usually when they say I have a
visitor, it's followed by the words,
"Just kidding."
And a lot of laughter at my expense.
You're the one who put yourself
in here, Alice, not me.
Technically, if we're
splitting hairs,
Kate shoved me into the cell
and you helped lock the door,
but whatever lets you sleep at night.
Tommy Elliot just hanged himself.
Or that's what it was
made to look like.
Do you know anything about that?
Now, what do I know?
I know, I don't give two hoots
about Tommy Elliot!
I know I don't have any
motivation to help you.
And I know, it is impossible
for one to heal from the trauma
of being locked in a cage
when one is still locked in a cage!
How many times did you tell me
that Beth was never coming back?
This is me admitting
that you were right.
Do you know what they do
to patients in here?
They put electrodes on our heads
and blast us with so much electricity
that we seize.
And I don't know the exact
science, but...
after about 10 jolts...
let me tell you...
you start convincing
everyone around you that it worked.
I'm sorry... that it ended up
this way.
If you mean that...
Then get me out of here.
I can't.
I have to protect the daughters
that I have left.
The thing they don't tell you
about ECT is that...
once it's over...
all that's left is clarity.
I see everything now.
How this came to be...
how it will end.
And I promise you, Daddy,
what I have in store for you
is so much worse
than a cage, or electrodes,
or insanity.
I guess you could say it's...
worse than being me.
But you'll see.
- Who are you?
- The heir to Hamilton Dynamics.
And I got money to spend.
Look, I don't care about any personal
vendetta against Batwoman.
Whether she blew up a shipment
of H or bataranged your dog,
I don't give a feel.
Hamilton Dynamics
wants the technology in that suit
and we're willing to pay for it.
Okay. Well, I don't know how you
heard about our little bake sale,
but I do know what
10 million dollars looks like.
- And it won't fit in that briefcase.
- It's 2.5.
The balance will be wired
to whatever account you...
This is an all-cash business,
Miss Hamilton.
But you want the suit?
It's yours, as soon as we peel it off
of her dead body.
So, I got good news and bad news.
Nope. It's all bad,
and it somehow just got worse.
Shiny, shiny.
2.5 million
for the suit off her dead body.
And with the highest bid
for the privilege of killing her...
sold!
To the gentleman
with a score to settle with the Bat.
The money I lost is nothing
compared to what I'll get for you.
People will pay a premium
for a piece of the Bat.
Luke, now!
Hold still.
Go check it out.
Please. Please. I won't tell anyone
about you and SRR!
I know.
Okay, so that was awesome.
- Also, Magpie's here.
- Magpie.
Yeah, I don't know,
but she has the journal
and Luke said she's
heading to the roof.
I'll get her. You get
her out of here.
Seriously?
Early bird gets the worm.
You're a long way from Arkham.
I told you I wasn't a jailbird.
You know what they say
about a bird in the hand?
Yeah. I do.
No!
Okay, so which one
do you wanna hear first?
Thanks for saving my ass
or sorry for always shutting you out?
You pick.
I'm sorry for always keeping you
at arm's length.
But it's not because
I don't trust you or
think that you can't
handle yourself,
which obviously you can.
It's because I've
already lost one sister.
And the thought of
losing you too, I...
I can't, Mary.
Thank you for not listening to me
and risking your life to save mine.
I guess I just have to get used
to the fact that you are
a total badass.
Badass enough...
to be one of your real
estate assistants?
I believe they prefer
to be called associates.
Okay. All right. I'll see you
in the Batcave.
That is literally the coolest thing
anyone has ever said to me.
- Okay.
- Okay. All right, bye.
We'll always we'll always be home
Crazy night?
- You could definitely say that.
- And apparently, Batwoman was here.
Which is super weird because
the last time I saw Batwoman,
I was with you.
- Kind of a crazy coincidence.
- Actually, it's not.
I wasn't really at the club
sussing out the competition.
Johnny Sabatino stole something
from Wayne Enterprises
and I needed it back,
and Batwoman helped me.
Think you could,
get me her autograph?
Probably not.
But I could give you a ride home.
After tonight I was heading
to get a drink.
Your place still open?
Nope.
I want I wanna show you
Forget forget the old news
You got the world
Right in front of you
They say patience is a virtue
I been looking for the right
I been looking for the
right time to show you
Get up get up and resist
Put up put up your two fists
We need we need a new fix
Can't keep going on like this
I been looking for the right
I been looking for the right time
To show you
Oh, my god.
Holy crap.
What?
Oh, god.
No, no, no!
- Okay.
- What?
This, absolutely no one can know
about this place, understand?
- Yes.
- Kate's life depends on this,
Mary. I'm serious.
You can trust me, really.
This is the biggest secret
you will ever keep in
your whole life, okay?
Okay, look,
when Bruce first showed
me this place...
Bruce Wayne is Batman?
Oh. That's...
Okay.
What do you mean it's gone?
I woke up and Reagan was gone and...
And so was the book.
The book filled with secrets
my dad died to protect.
I never thought that Reagan would...
- I'm sorry, Luke.
- Yeah, sorry doesn't undo the fact
that your life is very much
in danger, again,
as in right where
we started but worse.
Guys, with everyone in Gotham trying
to get their hands on that journal,
I think the million
dollar question is
what would a bloody
bartender want with it.
Hope you know you cost me
a really hot girlfriend, Magpie...
again.
That's what you get
for falling for a mark, again.
You know how this works.
We steal from the rich
because they'll never miss it.
You aren't supposed to miss them.
You got your book.
You can trade it for your
freedom but I'm out.
I'm done being advance
scout for Magpie.
I thought you'd do
anything for your sister.
I'm pretty sure I just did.
- Hey.
Since we missed dinner,
how about we grab a
celebratory brekky?
With Tommy Elliot not
getting his day in court,
I'm not sure what there
is to celebrate.
I think we can think of something.
Oh, I gotta get this.
I'll catch you up?
Yeah.
I was gonna call you.
I understand.
There's been an unforeseen setback.
I don't have my hands on the
journal yet, but I assure you I will.
And then it'll be yours.
Hold still.
One wrong move and my little
tracker friend will zap you
and you'll be a dead dodo.
There.
Now, you're free to fly the coop.
Good.
I was never meant
to be a homing pigeon.
How's my new favorite book?
Have you gotten to the chapter yet
that tells us how to kill the Bat?
No, because it appears Tommy Elliot
neglected to share one
very crucial detail.
Lucius Fox wrote the
entire journal in code!