Duela, hurry up. It's time to go.
First, apply your base
and rub it all around.
Then follow your hollow
to shave off the pounds.
Fine-line your lips,
to hide that off-putting frown.
Duela, get out here.
We have to go.
Come on. We're gonna be late.
Duela, I am so not kidding...
Oh, my God! Your... your face!
Have a good one.
- Mary. Hey.
- Hi.
- Super cute boots.
- Thanks.
You're in a good mood.
You say that like it's a bad thing.
Where's my cowl?
In the shop.
- Giving it a little upgrade.
- Upgrade?
Like...
- X-ray vision?
- No.
Echolocation?
That would've been a really good
idea, but no.
- Somebody's in a good mood.
- Am I?
You so are. Like giddy happy.
I'm not allowed to be happy?
You just got suspended
from the Crows, so no.
Oh, my God, you're sleeping
with someone.
I'm not sleeping with anyone.
But, can we please pause for
a moment to appreciate
the fact that those words
- actually came out of your mouth?
- Okay, fine, hooking up with.
- We shared a moment.
- With?
With?
If you tell anyone,
it'll take me an hour
to hide your body.
Spill.
- Batwoman.
- No, you didn't.
It was a peck.
That lasted several minutes.
Batwoman can't have a girlfriend.
- It was a kiss, Luke.
- Yeah. Last night. Then what?
You really wanna know
the answer to that?
Does she know who you are?
I have no idea.
Which, I admit,
is a little strange, but...
- You said, you knew who she was.
- I thought I did.
I was wrong.
Like, really, really wrong.
- So, you seriously have no idea?
- No.
Wait, do you?
No.
You finally get Sophie off your tail.
Now, you swapping spit with her.
I don't think you know
what kissing is.
what Bruce went through...
why Batman pushed people away.
You realize the moment anyone knows
Batwoman cares about Sophie...
it puts a target on her back?
She becomes a liability.
- Nobody needs to find out.
- Doesn't mean they won't, Kate.
She totally just texted you,
didn't she?
She wants to meet at my place later.
I'm leaving now.
Have fun. And, Sophie.
I'm happy for you.
"Alice, aka Jane Doe 7113,
the deranged leader
of the Wonderland Gang,
was fatally gunned down last week
in a motel parking lot
by an unidentified shooter.
"No services are planned
at this time"?
I'm sorry, this is my obituary?
"Mentally-deranged leader"?
That's my synopsis?
A tiny little blurb below the fold?
I survived captivity
for 11 years, escaped
and enacted the perfect revenge.
- What took you so long?
- Wanted to get a clear shot of him.
That's not the face
I see in my nightmares...
but I'd recognize
that pipe anywhere.
Even in the dark.
It's him.
As you know, some wacko
dubbed The Executioner
blew a hole in the city's corrupt
court system a few months back.
And I blew a hole in him.
What's your point?
It forced the DA's office to reopen
a bunch of his old cases,
and then, funnel them through
a new judge.
But you know this new judge.
Davis Wellington?
Crows contracts dating back to 2004.
My client hopes
that you call the judge
and get him to move his case up.
Why would I do that?
Because my client's Reggie Harris.
And you owe him your life.
Thank you.
You're better to me alive, puppy dog.
Reggie is an opportunist
using this cabal nonsense
as a get-out-of-jail-free card.
He confessed to gunning down
Lucius Fox in a C-store robbery.
That confession was coerced
by a corrupt GCPD cop.
- Not a Crows problem.
- Yet.
Based on some whispers
my client heard in the slammer
about this place,
the Crows have some secrets
of their own.
That almost sounded like a threat.
It is.
Let's not turn it into more.
Call the judge, get him
to move Reggie's court date up.
Or this place gets blown open
the same way the DA's office did.
I leave gold on
the floor wherever I go
Yeah, I'm killing it, I'm killing
it I'm stealing the show
Words fall out my mouth
And they break the door
Like, oh, na-na-na...
So we're at the beat
And everybody boom, boom
Your eyes on me
Make your body vroom-vroom
I break the rules,
but I make the rules
Like, ooh, na-na-na...
Lekka to be me, strong and free
Doing what I do
Do what I do, what I do now
Hey, hey, hey...
This is definitely a first.
Me too, actually.
So...
Do you wanna come inside?
I can't.
I came here to tell you,
this has to end...
- before you get hurt.
- I can take care of myself.
This is different.
I have enemies.
If they connected us,
they could use you against me.
Well, I won't tell them if you don't.
You know it's not that simple.
So, what do you suggest?
That we walk away.
Okay.
So walk.
I can't help that
I wanna do bad things
Bad things, bad things...
- Someone's here.
- I'm on it.
No. I got it.
Give your own mother a heart attack.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Surprising you.
Next time, I'll call first.
- We're locking up.
- I'm on the phone.
My company's valuation
is twice that much.
I don't care about fixed capital.
Look at our intangible assets,
i.e. me.
My brand. My image.
You can't put a price on that.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
They had no budget
for this photo shoot
and it's starting to show.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Not even like a janitor or someone?
Who's there?
Talk about the unkindest cut.
Social media influencer Kimberly
Wright was the victim
of a brutal face-slashing last night.
GCPD suspect this is now
the second social media influencer
attacked by the serial slash-onista.
Talk to me, Gotham. Where's
the dislike button when you need it?
How'd it go with Sophie?
Sophie...
Well, she...
It was really cold
and it was a bit hard to hear
and then, her mom just showed up
out of nowhere.
So, dog ate my breakup?
There is a lunatic with a box cutter
targeting kids. We need to focus.
Already on it.
Kimberly Wright described her
attacker as a woman in her 20s
who wore a hoodie
and a surgical mask.
That's why the GCPD can't ID her.
Interestingly, neither of the victims
had any stab wounds on their bodies.
She went after their face.
Their face is their brand.
Their business. This is personal.
Where you off to?
To see the only Instaface
I care about.
Yeah, and it's
all my feed is talking about.
Even Kylie Q is threatening
to go web-silent out of respect.
Thank you, doctor.
Are you okay?
I mean, I barely knew Kimberly.
But still, it's pretty freaky.
And don't worry, my fan base left
when my stepdad supposedly
killed my mom.
- So I am hardly worth the data.
- Good.
Not about the fanbase.
I mean, that sucks.
Do you anyone in that circle
that could be a target?
Well, it depends on who you ask.
I mean, everybody knows that Kimberly
Wright has Miley McGinn's nose.
Except me, apparently.
Same corrective surgery. Shape,
slope, length. I mean, it's a thing.
People were even whispering maybe
Miley had something to do
with the attack.
Pissed that Kimberly stole her nose.
But if you think about it,
Miley copied Mia's cheekbones.
And Mia and Xena have the same chin,
which I believe belonged
to Ariana at one point.
Anyway, I am sure there's a
"who's who of potential victims"
in Dr. Campbell's waiting room
as we speak.
- Dr. Ethan Campbell?
- Yeah.
The only plastic surgeon in
this city worth going to.
Not that I would know.
Actually, if you're looking into this
because you own a real estate firm
and these women are most
likely future property buyers...
Exactly. Yeah.
I'm around if you need
a side person.
I mean, I'm a DM away
from half these girls.
I'd be happy to poke around
for some clues or whatever.
It's probably safest if
you stayed out of it.
I might ask someone to drop by
Campbell, just give him a heads up.
I can do it.
I mean, I'm a med student
where he lectures.
So, now that I think about it,
my vast array of medical knowledge
could come in handy
in endless scenarios.
I'm good, Mary. Thank you.
Okay... Well, I'm happy to help.
Bye, Mary.
Rewind.
You and your husband separate
and you didn't think to call me?
I thought it was best
to let the dust settle.
Where is my phone?
I will tell Tyler all
the ways he's making
- the biggest mistake of his life.
- Mom, stop.
It's not like that.
- It was me.
- You?
I...
I fell out of love with him.
You fell out of love with a handsome,
decorated, capable man
who always sent me flowers
on my birthday.
Why don't you give me the real story?
Mom, that is the real story.
Well, Jacob Kane called.
He told me about your suspension.
So that's why you're in town.
This isn't some motherly
I-missed-you visit.
More of a
please-don't-end-up-under-a-bridge
visit. How are you going to
pay the rent?
By working at a place
that aligns with my values.
I don't see eye-to-eye
with the Crow's way
of doing things anymore.
Oh, please don't tell me you wish
they were more like the GCPD.
No.
More like Batwoman.
She is someone
who represents all of Gotham.
The poor, the rich and in-between.
She's saved my life
on several occasions...
She is a damn criminal
who gets away with it.
You never had a problem with Batman.
- You thought he was cute.
- Batman was different.
How, Mom? How was Batman different?
He represented values
I actually believed in.
You mean he's not gay.
Hey. I don't have a lot of time
so we should probably
make this quick.
You okay?
My mom. She...
I'm 28-years-old, I have two degrees
and own a condo on a river.
And I spend every waking moment
wondering if she's proud of me.
And if she were
to find out about this?
Upside of having to hide it?
She won't.
So, what's up?
I did some digging.
And I think that Gotham's serial
slasher is targeting patients
from a plastic surgeon
by the name of Ethan Campbell.
I know him. His affidavit cleared my
boss of murder charges.
That's why I'm here.
I need you to find out what he knows.
I have no authority.
The Crows suspended me.
Does Campbell know that?
The last victim of the slasher
was also a patient of yours.
Mia Cortez.
We're worried the next
victim could be
a name on one of those files.
Kimberly Wright told every one
of her ten million followers
about her nose job.
So if it's a case of jealousy...
you have a lot
of names to sift through.
One theory
is she's targeting copycat surgeries.
- Have you ever...
- Cut a smile into a patient's face?
No, Agent Moore.
I certainly have not.
Then maybe
she's not targeting copycats.
Maybe she's making copycats.
By inflicting her victims
with the same scars she has?
Have you ever treated a woman
with this type of scarring?
Actually, yes. Eight years ago.
A teenage girl was brought to me
with a psychiatric rap sheet as
long as my arm.
And the worst self-inflicted scars
I've ever seen.
She cut her own face?
Yes, she did.
Duela Dent, what can you
find on her?
Daughter of Evelyn.
Father unknown.
Her Uncle Harvey is a beloved ADA.
Wait, here's something.
She was just released
from a mental health facility.
How did you get her name?
Bat sources, okay?
Would these Bat sources
be of the tall,
dark and girlfriend-material variety?
I'm choosing to ignore that.
I found something.
It's her hit list.
Run the name Myrtis Dinker.
Myrtis Dinker.
Nope. Nothing. No Myrtis Dinker.
I have an idea.
Press the red button
on your right gauntlet.
Sorry. Your left gauntlet.
- That was your upgrade?
- Cowl-cam.
- What do you think?
- Use this without my permission
and I'll find a new place
to put my Batarang.
Yeah, copy that.
Running the image now.
And?
I'm still working out the bugs.
You're okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I'm gonna go get you help.
Just...
Come any closer and I turn
my mom into a Pez dispenser.
Duela, you don't need to do this.
And she didn't have to force me
to be someone I'm not.
Someone I hate.
Someone I can't even look at.
So I'm gonna go,
and you're gonna need a mop.
No! No.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
It's gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
I have spent hours upon hours
cooking up all the ways
that I could torture that vile man.
Now, that he's right here,
right under my nose, I...
You're blocked.
Exactly, Dr. Malone.
I am blocked.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It's a normal reaction.
Victims held in physical
and emotional captivity
oftentimes revert back to the age
they were held
when facing their captor.
So, what are you saying?
I don't find closure?
No, of course not.
But you clearly have unresolved fear.
My fear is
that I will kill him instantly.
Forgetting to relish
in his slow and painful demise.
Those are just
your defenses talking.
I don't have defenses.
If you don't mind,
in my professional opinion...
I see you're putting up a hard,
blustery exterior.
But the truth is,
you are still terrified of this man.
You are still just a little girl.
And you know, when you
confront him face-to-face
that he will find a way to regain
that power over you once again.
So, then... shrink me.
- What do I do?
- I suggest an emotional shield.
A third person that acts as a buffer
between you and the abuser.
You have been incredibly helpful,
Dr. Malone.
I do wish we could've made
this a weekly affair.
No, please.
No, I won't tell anyone you're alive.
Please. I won't tell anyone. Please!
Please, don't!
I won't tell anyone!
Well, well,
Dr. Fix-Me threatened with a lawsuit
by a 16-year-old who did not consent
to the restorative plastic surgery
he performed on her.
What an interesting little
psychopath.
How long are you gonna keep me here?
As long as it takes
for you to come to your senses?
Alice will find me.
Alice is dead.
No.
I shot her.
No. No.
- Son...
- No, no.
You're better off without her.
All she ever did was put
your life in danger
to advance her own agenda.
All I've done
is protect you
from the cruelty of the world.
The only thing cruel
in my world is you.
You think that way now.
But in time...
- you'll come to see the truth.
- Get away.
What are you doing?
What are you doing to me?
You wanted to see me, sir?
Our favorite ambulance chaser
Bobby Reeves stopped by.
He's poking around a murder case
your team ran point on.
Yeah. Hard to forget.
Harris gunned down Lucius Fox
and a cashier at a Sip & Dash.
What's the problem?
We turned him over to the GCPD.
Yeah, to Stu Donnelly.
The officer accused of coercing
confessions in at least 21 cases.
We handed a lot of perps over
to Donnelly, commander.
- Are we saying they're all innocent?
- You don't find it unusual
that the Sip & Dash's four security
cameras weren't working
in the five-hour window
when the robbery took place?
Only thing I find unusual
is Lucius Fox was a hero
to this city...
and people are trying
to set this killer free.
I was wondering
when you were gonna hit me up
- about the slasher case.
- How did you know?
Because I am smart and perceptive.
Two traits people often overlook.
Anyway, I was hoping
that you could help me ID someone.
Someone that doesn't pop up
in my facial recognition system.
Oh! That's Veronica May.
- You're sure?
- Yeah.
Apparently, she changed her name
after high school.
And if my name was Myrtis Dinker,
I would, too.
And I'm guessing the reason
why her face stumped your Bat-tech
is because that's not her nose
anymore.
- Or her chin.
- Any idea how I can find her?
Well, she pretty much lives
onboard the May-Mobile.
- The what?
- It's part-makeover truck...
part-rolling billboard
for her makeup line.
Just look for the gaudiest thing on
the road.
We need to find that cosmetics truck.
I appreciate that,
but a truck in Gotham
kind of a needle in a haystack.
- The needle is hot pink.
- That narrows it down.
Let me run a color filter
on the satellite.
Okay. We've got an ice cream truck
an unfortunate paint job
on a Lambo...
That's not good.
Duela's been here.
No sign of Veronica.
Hold up. I think I got company.
- You shouldn't be here.
- Neither should you.
I've been listening into
the Crow's radio.
They'll be here any minute.
I'm not leaving until
I find every single person
that was in that truck.
Looks like Duela forced them
into another vehicle. Why here?
Veronica's skincare line is made
at the plant down the road.
You by the truck
- get's your hands in the air now!
- We have to get out of here.
Let's get out of here now! Come on!
- Get on.
- Wait, what?
Get on.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you have a problem
with people stealing
medical supplies?
Because...
- Hi.
- I thought I made it clear
how I felt about you when
I left you to die.
You did, but then I saved your life
and now you owe me, so...
- Did Batwoman not tell you?
- Not tell me what?
After Nocturna drained your blood,
you were on death's door.
I found you and revived you
with my own.
Meaning, I literally pumped life
back into your veins.
I need a bleach transfusion.
- I'll take that as a thank-you.
- Why would you do that?
Let's just say it was more about
Batwoman and less about you.
Thanks for the goods.
Do you know who she is?
Batwoman?
Of course I do.
Do you not?
Sad.
Guess you two aren't really pals
after all.
Duela, stop. Please. Let me down.
I'm helping you, Veronica.
I mean, Myrtis.
Oh, my God.
Look, you made your point, okay?
I wasn't a great friend
after the incident.
But honestly? I was afraid of you.
Because I was finally happy?
Happy people don't
slice their faces open.
What do they do?
Shave a bone off their nose?
Slit their eyelids open,
stab needles into their lips?
You know, the only difference
between you and me
is that I got institutionalized
and you got famous.
- My mother wanted me to be you.
- Put me down, you psycho!
It's time to show the world what
I see when I look at Veronica May.
No, Duela, stop! Please! Don't! No!
Going somewhere?
Tell me someone got that on camera.
So, should I take Veronica up
on her offer to share an Uber?
Call me crazy, but I felt
like we made a good team in there.
- We did.
- But?
How do you see this playing out?
Dinner, movie,
I take you back to my cave?
You live in a cave?
Cold concrete beneath my back...
I don't know. I guess
I haven't really thought about it.
If I were to tell you
who I am right now...
- would you wanna know?
- What?
Because once that happens,
I'm no longer a secret.
I'm a face.
A person.
A woman.
And I bring all the complications
that come with that.
So do you wanna be in a real
relationship,
or do you wanna be with someone
you can keep secret?
Because we can never
be more than this.
And that shouldn't be enough.
You're right.
As long as I'm with a woman
who wears a mask,
I'll always be wearing one myself.
I think I have some things
I need to figure out.
When you're down...
I'll let the GCPD know about Duela.
When you're down, down, down...
Goodbye, Sophie.
Nowhere to go No further to fall
When you're on the floor
And you're already down
Down, down, down...
Down, down, down
Who's there?
Please! Help untie me, please.
- Who's there?
- An ally.
You and I were both wronged
by the same man.
He took my adolescence,
just like he took your smile.
I will get revenge for both of us.
But first, I'm gonna need
a little something from you.
You wanna explain this?
- It's a bank statement.
- I know it's a bank statement.
I don't know why the Crows
sent the Sip & Dash $50,000
after the Lucius Fox murder.
It says right here, Code 501.
A restoration courtesy payment
for us trashing the place
when we arrested Harris.
So this money has nothing to do
with the lost security footage?
You don't really think
a Crow would destroy evidence?
Like the hunter on his prey
Once you think you got me trapped
I make my escape...
I thought Dispatch said she was
locked up.
I'm coming out of my cage...
Duela.
How did you get in here?
Just flashed that pretty
smile you gave me.
- What's you got?
- Hold tight.
Over here.
- Is that the slasher?
- I'm coming out of my cage...
I'm coming out of my
Lord have mercy.
I'm finally perfect.
You shouldn't be here, Duela.
Sorry.
You got the wrong girl.
No.
No, you're dead. I...
I shot you.
Again, you got the wrong girl.
You like taking things
from children, don't you?
Well...
we're all grown up now...
And here for a little payback.
I'm coming out of my cage...
Moore. It's me.
Look. I may question
your decision-making
when it comes to Batwoman.
But, I've never questioned
your integrity.
And at the moment,
I need it more than ever.
I think the Crows have a major
problem.
I'll explain when you call me back.
Not sure how charging
five dollars for a coffee
is not a criminal offense.
I think you're gonna need
something stronger.
I lied to you the other day.
That's what I do now. I lie.
I lie so much I don't even realize
I'm doing it anymore.
Oh, Sophie.
What lie?
I didn't break up with Tyler...
because I fell out of love with him.
I broke up with Tyler
because I was never in love with him.
Sweetheart,
I need you to start making sense.
When I was at Point Rock...
I met someone.
And for the first time...
I was happy.
Really, really, happy.
And I wanna find that again.
Okay. Okay. Then go find him, honey.
- Go find him.
- It wasn't a him, Mom.
It was a her.
For years, I kept it a secret.
I thought I could have both.
The version of me that my school
and my family could be proud of...
and the version of me
who knew who she was.
I try not to hold my breath
So, the good Lord didn't make it
hard enough on you?
I'm scared of the past
Not enough to be a woman of color,
not enough to come from nothing,
not enough to have to prove your damn
worth to the world
every time you wanna be part of it?
You gotta add this on top of it?
I didn't ask for this.
Just like I didn't ask
for any of those things.
But each of them make
me who I am.
Why am I only hearing about it now?
Because I didn't want you
to look at me the way
- you're looking at me now.
- Oh, Sophie.
I am so sorry about that, sweetheart.
I can feel the changes coming
What did you expect disappointment
to look like?
What I've been,
what I'm becoming...
You look like you had a long night.
More like a really long day.
If you wanna talk about it,
if you wanna talk about anything...
you know I'm here, right?
I lost a piece of real estate
I had my heart set on.
But it wasn't the right move.
Timing was off.
All the others here and now...
Do you remember the day
that you came back to Gotham?
I threw you that welcome home party
and then six hours later,
I was stitching up your shoulder,
telling you
that I owned an illegal clinic?
Of course, I remember.
It never once occurred to me
that you'd tell my mom or your dad
that I was living a double-life.
Or that you'd try to shut me down,
or tell me I could get sued
or kicked out of school, or arrested.
I knew I didn't have
to worry about you judging me.
Because I trusted you.
So I hope one day
that you feel the same way about me.
What do you want?
For you to drop the act.
And the face.
I thought I would never have
to see you again.
But I was wrong.
I see this face every night
as I go to sleep
and every morning as I wake.
And sometimes, when I close my eyes
and shake too long.
If you're gonna kill me, do it.
Kill me.
Get it over with.
We mustn't speak of such nonsense.
I would never kill you.
At least not with these nimble little
fingers.
What do you want?
My brother Mouse.
Surely, you have him and I want him.
So, where is he?
Why is that so funny?
What?
Yeah.
I will tell you where you can find
your...
Precious Mouse.