Previously on Batwoman...
To Catherine
the most extraordinary woman.
You should have first looked
to see whether
it's marked "poison" or not.
Jacob would never hurt us.
You know how she died? Exactly
the way that Alice planned it.
Hands in the air, Kane.
You're under arrest.
What the hell is happening?
Get your hands off of me!
You had someone impersonate him.
The Skin Pirate.
I'm gonna ask you again, Kate.
Is Alice worth it?
Wasn't that our train?
What the hell?
That's my stop.
He missed my stop completely.
Hey, Keanu!
Some of us have tickets
to Jagged Little Phil...
That's not right.
Attention, ladies and gentlemen,
it appears our computer system
has stopped responding.
We've lost our brakes.
This is not a drill.
Brace for impact.
Conductor sent GCPD an SOS
five minutes ago
that his brakes went out.
At his rate of speed and taking
into consideration rush
hour passenger weight
on a 650 volt three-rail system,
they've got about half a mile
of track before they get
to the end of the line.
Didn't hear what I
just said, did you?
I love this bike.
Figured you couldn't exactly
have the same ride as Kate Kane.
Agree. But it's not
my birthday for two days.
Birthday?
You had no idea?
- Yes, so the next stop should be...
- Got it.
Look out!
I got you, ma'am.
Ma'am?
Oh, boy.
Good morning, Gotham.
After the death of Oliver Queen
I think we all needed
a reason to smile.
And we've been getting it
all week.
A bombshell caped crusader
and a cop with Chris Evan vibes?
Talk to me Gotham, are we
shipping these two or what?
Congrats, your street cred's
off the chart right now.
Officer Slam Bradley
is as hometown hero as it gets.
Why is this guy suddenly
everywhere that I am?
Well, GCPD is probably
stepping up their game
now, that the head
of The Crows is in jail.
Slam is Mr. March in the annual
hunks of the GCPD calendar.
Handcuffs are a nice touch.
Well, I got to say,
I can't really blame people
for shipping you and Captain America.
Have we not had this conversation?
- I'm very, very gay.
- Have you not seen Batwoman?
Major straight vibes.
Kate, it's not a total negative.
Oh, that I'm apparently dating
Mr. Underwear
that leaves nothing
to the imagination?
That Gotham's confused.
It's misinformation.
The less they know about you
the easier it is
to keep you a secret.
A train lost its breaks.
And I saved 450 people from
smashing into a concrete wall.
And all Gotham cares about
is Batwoman's sex life.
- They just want to see you're happy.
- Well, too bad because she is not.
Fill up your glasses
as quick as you can
and sprinkle the table
with buttons and bran.
Put cats in the coffee
and the mice in the tea.
And welcome Queen Alice
with 30 times three.
Oh, Catherine,
do tell me if it's too weak.
What's that, dear?
Too bitter.
Then it's perfect.
Now, back to sleep.
Nighty night.
It's such a shame our dear sister
couldn't join us today.
I guess that would require her
taking one of your calls...
Or answering a text,
or a letter,
or a cryptic gift.
- Your tea's getting cold.
- I am getting cold.
Perhaps we should resume this
when the condition are
more favorable to celebration.
Catherine Hamilton is dead.
The sunshine is implied.
Look,
Alice...
I know you have this fantasy
that the three of us
are going to be a family one day,
but Kate doesn't.
I killed our mutual enemy for her.
She'll come around.
That's not a gesture of love to her.
It's a weakness.
It's another strand
in your unraveling psychosis.
She doesn't see her sister.
She sees a soul in need of saving.
She's the city's hero.
The city's hero can't be seen
sipping tea with fugitive dreck.
As long as she wears that mask
you're never going to bring her
into this family.
Hey, guys.
So this may come as news
to some of you
but my Insta account's
not actually a place for you
to list all the ways
that I'm human garbage.
My stepdad's a murderer
my mom's company is corrupt,
we're all evil, got it.
Loud and clear.
And since there is not enough
bandwith on the internet for me
to explain all of the ways
that you're wrong...
I'm gonna sign off for a bit.
Be better to each other. Seriously.
Peace.
- Oh, my God.
- Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
I know and you didn't mean for your
twin sister to poison my mother,
but we all know how that turned out.
I just... I wanted to let you know
that I put in a call to Hewitt
and Associates.
I figured that an extra
legal team wouldn't hurt.
Yeah, I know. Which is why
they've all been hired.
Thanks, but we got this.
- We?
- Your dad, Sophie and me.
Your dad has every lawyer
in Gotham on retainer,
Sophie built a strike team
to try to find Mouse
and I am looking
for a plastic surgeon
willing to testify that face
replacement is a great way
- to frame someone for murder.
- Okay. How can I help?
You can tell your sister to stop
defiling my mom's grave.
Wow, I...
She's been looking for a way
to get my attention.
She thinks that I want to be sisters.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Look, if you want to help,
tell your sister
to leave my dead mother alone.
She'll listen to you, right?
Wait.
- Mary, I am so sorry.
- I know. I know you are.
I know you never wanted to believe
that your sister could be capable
of doing something so horrible,
but I did.
And you decided to ignore me.
So I'm really busy...
Bye.
Yeah.
Here. Put this on.
We're officials
for the Transit Authority.
Ever since the Scarecrow incident,
Gotham City trains run
on an independent analog system.
In theory, that should
make them unhackable.
- Suicidal conductor?
- GCPD already released him.
Black box data showed
no indication of engineer error.
It was like the train's brake system
got possessed or something.
Please don't touch that.
Great.
That made this harder
by about a 100 percent.
This help?
That could, theoretically, have
something to do with it.
Yeah, it's a packet analyzer.
It intercepts and jumbles traffic as
it passes over a digital network.
the hacker probably used it to hijack
the train's brakes remotely.
I love to dig.
Because when I dig, I found
all the secrets you buried.
- Did you just get...
- The same thing.
If I can hack your subway,
I can hack your phone
computer, home security cameras.
Did I get your attention? Good.
Now, crowdfund my escape from
Gotham.
Click the link and help me raise
five million dollars
by midnight on Friday,
or your secrets come out.
It doesn't matter
if you are a porn addict,
masked vigilante, or everyday
Joe Schmo. Pay up, Gotham.
Mayor, are you calling this
a terrorist attack?
Sir, how wide-spread
is this cyber breach?
Folks, please, just let me speak.
First and foremost, Gotham City
has no reason to be alarmed.
We have layers of cyber security
in place
and we will certainly not be coerced
into the demand
of some silly prankster.
I encourage everyone to go
about their daily activities.
Authorities will work it
around the clock
to ensure that this
never happens again.
- You're kidding me.
- This guy is good.
If you're so safe,
whyarethe Mayor's
personal credit card numbers
flashing across the screen?
Go shopping, Gotham
- What are you doing?
- Shutting us down.
Guy just doxed the Mayor. We're one
hack away from total exposure.
With this on the firewall?
The guy just hijacked the subway,
the city's cell network
- and overtook a feed on live TV.
- So?
So you're the most famous person
in Gotham right now.
You don't think
you're the obvious target here?
Come from the genius
who puts a bat emoji
on every single text messages.
That was just cold.
Look, can you just use this
to trace the IP address
- and find the user's location?
- I could, if we had internet.
- Don't do it.
- We can't stop him
if we can't find him.
We can't stop anyone
if everyone knows who you are.
- Please.
- Seriously, don't.
- Five minutes, then we go dark.
- Fine.
Fine.
Food is getting cold, Commander Kane.
Where is your bite, puppy dog?
Some classic ass poetry about the man
who locked up half the fools in here
is now, eating
out of the same doggie bowl.
Welcome home.
Help yourself.
So after all that, we're able
to pull up your hearing week.
Because the last thing we need
is to start your trial
on Valentine's day
with the bunch of jurors thinking
about the significant others
while hearing the DA's theory
on how you killed yours.
But less great news, I'm still
working on finding a medical expert
willing to testify that
face-swapping is totally a thing.
- Mary...
- Dr. Keller is supposedly
on sabbatical aka he's just too
scared to be associate with you
and apparently, Professor Vivek
is too good for us now, that
he's been on Dr. Phil...
Mary, stop.
You mother has been killed
and Gotham thinks I killed her,
it's incomprehensible.
How are you dealing with everything?
I'm engaging in escapist
strategies as a defense tactic
so that all the walls holding up
everything I know to be true
don't come crumbling down around me.
Mary, Kate and I think
you need to talk to someone.
Like who? You?
You wanted to divorce my mom.
Your mother and I had a fundamental
difference of opinion.
I've never stopped
wanting to be your dad.
I don't have time to sit around
feeling sorry for myself.
So we need to find Alice,
force a confession
and get you out of there.
Sit tight. I will find somebody
to help us.
Okay, the trace on the device worked.
This place is definitely
giving me Mr. Robot vibes.
- Batwoman to Batcave.
- Luke.
You turned the comms off.
One of you needs to start talking.
We've been surveilling
this operation for months.
Up until last night
you were just rejects
working for a Russian hacking ring
who got off on stealing social
security checks from old ladies.
- So, why hijack a subway?
- We didn't do that.
We're not terrorists.
Oh, now, you wanna talk.
So, which one of you
cut the brakes on the train?
I swear, none of us.
My wife takes the train to work every
morning. I'd never do that to...
Which one of you cut the brakes?
I promise you on
my mother's grave, it wasn't us.
- Please don't kill me.
- Then answer the damn question!
I know you're there.
Want to talk about it?
Not really.
I get it.
Maybe some other time.
You ever feel like you're
hiding from the world?
I'm literally standing in the shadow.
Not sure why I'm asking someone
who crushes on Slam Bradley
for life advice.
Try me.
My husband left me.
I'm sorry.
He thinks I'm lying to myself.
Are you?
Maybe.
Maybe I'm too terrified
to deal with it.
We all wear masks.
Maybe it's time you take yours off.
You're one to talk.
- Dr. Campbell.
- Mary.
Are you okay?
I am so sorry to hear about your mom.
That night at the Gala
was absolutely horrific.
Thank you. I know that you're busy
and I don't mean to ambush you
after a three-hour college lecture
but I read your dissertation
on skin grafts and facial restoration
and wondered if you'd be willing
to be an expert witness
in my step dad's trial.
I'm sorry, I'm not following.
He was set up by a guy
who made a face out of real skin
that looks exactly like Jacob Kane.
Look, I know what it sounds like.
And you think that I'm in denial
and grasping at straws
and, yes, I've seen
every episode of Dateline
and know the husband always
does it, but not this time.
Look, your mother was really
generous to Gotham University
and I wish I could help. But
for a man to perfectly
resemble another man, it's...
It's science fiction, Mary.
I know what I saw.
Sometimes when...
People under extreme duress, they
see what they wanna see.
I'm sorry I can't be more helpful.
I really am.
Good night.
You turned off the comms?
We went dark,
that includes satellite feed.
And when you find the Terrier
Terrorist, I'll reconnect.
Until then, you're running solo.
The packet analyzer
was a diversion tactic.
Whoever planted it rerouted the
IP to some of Snowden wannabe.
So much for honor
among cyber thieves.
Am I a fraud?
You're still hung up
on this Slam Bradley love affair?
Yeah, whenever I put on this suit,
I feel like I'm lying
to our entire city.
Well, that's the job.
According to the multiverse,
my job is to be
the Paragon of Courage.
Right, because a Paragon
Finder said so
before the infinite earths collapsed
into a single space-time continuum.
I'm sure it was all very exciting.
I live in shadows, I wear a disguise
and I let people believe
that I'm dating Captain America.
What part of that is courageous?
Kicking bad guy's asses
to protect your city
is pretty damn courageous.
You said it yourself, I'm the
most famous face in Gotham.
But their image of me
is not me.
They think you're a hero, Kate.
You are.
This is gonna help you.
It's an electric charge disrupter.
It will kill every electric current
within 100m radius for ten seconds.
- How does that help us?
- Because whoever hacked Gotham,
probably has a firewall on her phone
strong enough to resist this.
So we narrow down her location,
kill the power
her phone stays on, boom...
You keep saying "her".
Right, I was just about
to get to that
consider us both guilty
of making assumptions.
So I did an offline reverse
audio modulation
on the talking terrier emoji to
access the hacker's actual voice.
If I can hack your subway,
I can hack your phone, computer,
home security cameras.
It's a girl. Like, a young girl.
Play it again.
If I can hack your subway,
- I can hack your phone,...
- You hear that?
Lower the voice,
amplify the background.
Okay.
If I can hack your subway,
I can hack your phone...
Right there, isolate that.
You heard that.
- That melodic tone?
- It's a bell.
I recognize it.
I know where she recorded this.
It's the most vile,
lawless place in the world.
Gotham Prep.
My old high school.
What'd Campbell say?
Apparently, the psychological
ramifications of
witnessing my mother's death
have caused me
to see and believe things
that are not there.
He thinks you're crazy.
Totally off my rocker.
Just like everyone else.
Look, Mary,
it's not my business, but...
Have you tried talking to Kate?
She lost her mom too.
She's been through this.
I know, which makes not trusting
her that much more tragic.
We'll find someone
who can help your dad.
My cousin went to med school
in Metropolis,
maybe she knows a plastic surgeon...
- Okay, that's creepy.
- What?
Alice is at Gotham University.
Are you sure?
The woman poisoned my mom,
then danced on her grave,
yes, I know what Alice looks like.
Mary, get out of there now.
I'm sending a team.
- Who's the Terrier?
- What just happened?
Is that Batwoman?
I asked who is the Terrier?
So not me, but do you mind?
Batwoman crashed our party.
This is sick!
Is Slam Bradley here too?
- Bat-selfie. What's up?
- No.
You broke my phone?
Why did it just go dark?
Wait, what did you do
with our phones?
What happened.
My phone not working man?
What do you want?
I'm just a kid at a dance.
If I can hack your subway,
I can hack your phone, computer,
home security cameras.
A kid who hacked a subway
full of innocent people.
- You got a name?
- You don't know my name?
I thought you were
some bad-ass crime fighter.
Parker Torres.
And I wasn't gonna crash the train.
My grappling hook begs to differ.
I was on it,
controlling it from my phone.
I was gonna stop it,
but you stopped it first.
Whatever, it's a dumb prank.
What the hell were you thinking?
I'm sorry, okay?
- Chill.
- I don't chill.
Look...
I really am sorry.
I just thought if I could...
Scare my parents
into thinking I almost died,
they'd just be happy I was alive,
and forget their daughter
was a freak.
- You're not a freak.
- I am to them.
I'm a...
Gay.
Kayla Mason revenge outed me
to my mom and dad.
- Kayla Mason?
- My ex.
She said, being in the closet
was pre-historic.
I either told them the truth
or she'd leave me.
She didn't get it,
I couldn't tell the truth.
So when I told her to just go,
she went nuclear
and told my parents for me.
My mom and dad thought
they'd been raising
some BTS-loving heteronorm.
Now they sleep clutching rosaries
and want to disown me.
That's why I need the money
to get out of Gotham.
That's sucks and it's not fair.
But it is not an excuse to put
hundreds of lives in jeopardy...
My parents want me
to be someone I'm not.
Do you know how that feels?
I hate myself, okay?
And let's raincheck
your "It gets better" PSA.
We both know I'm gonna grow up
hiding my girlfriends
and aspiring to be represented
by an ancillary character
on my favorite TV show.
Just like you were probably
the cool girl in high school
and now you're famous
and everyone's shipping you
and the hottest guy in Gotham.
We have nothing in common.
In fact, you pretending
to feel bad for me
is kinda making it worse,
so, could you just leave me alone
before I find more reasons
to wish I were dead?
Moore to base,
just showed up to Gotham U.
She saw her gone to room 119.
You're that psycho.
Charmed, I'm sure.
And I understand you're the terrier.
Run, Parker.
Don't worry about the bat,
she'll come play later.
For now, believe it or not,
I actually need you.
I love living in the world
where we trust teenagers
with these things.
Why are you doing this?
Because my inner mean girl
never got to live out
her high school experience.
I'm looking for Batwoman,
and you moronic classmates
tagged her in a photo here.
Knock it off.
Good. The hall monitor's back.
Let the girl go.
I will.
But first, I need you to figure out
that you are not a hero.
What does she have to do with this?
She's a very important tool
in my very important plan.
Which I'll tell you.
After you drop
the whole hero complex.
Take off the mask, Batwoman.
What's going on? Where is everyone?
What's the point of running a clinic
when you can't even save
your own mom.
I'm not a doctor.
If you're here, I'm hoping that
means that Alice is at Arkham.
She wasn't at Gotham University.
What are you talking about?
I saw her run into that building.
We searched every dorm room, Mary.
She wasn't there.
Maybe Dr. Campbell was right.
You should go somewhere.
Relax, grieve your mom.
You think I'm seeing things too.
I think your world just fell apart...
And you're looking for something
to distract you
from how painful it is.
Look...
No judgment.
My marriage just blew up...
And I nearly took the wrong guy's
head off earlier.
We're human.
We'd rather be doing anything...
Other than feeling our feelings.
I'm not crazy.
I swear I'm not imagining things,
Sophie.
Finding Alice isn't going
to bring your mom back.
What's wrong, Batwoman?
Shy?
Come on, show us
your pretty little face.
Why are you doing this?
Because you're obsessed
with saving people
who don't want to be saved.
Give it up, give up, give up!
I know what you're doing.
I put away the bat,
so I can join you
in some twisted fairytale.
Take off the mask, Batty!
You're sick, Alice.
Alice, stop.
Stop it!
Do it!
Fine!
Holy crap.
You're Kate Kane.
That would be me.
I, like, drive by
your real estate firm every day.
- Hi.
I just read the Advocate.
Lesbian CEOs under 30.
Oh, my god. I was such a bitch
to you earlier.
Why didn't you say
you were super gay?
Kind of still figuring out
how much to tell people.
Okay, hello. Boring!
- Can we move this along, please?
- Happily, just...
Let her go.
No. I meant, to the next
phase of my plan.
You see, I've been following you
and now I need cyber sunshine
to do that thing that she did
where she accessed
everyone's phones
on Gotham's cellular network.
And then I need her to out my sister
as Gotham's red-headed knight.
Don't do this, Alice.
No hero, no bat,
no one trying to change who I am.
Everyone lives happily ever after.
And if I don't?
What are you going to do? Kill me?
You need me, if you kill me,
you lose.
As do you.
Because you're dead.
I'm sorry, did they not
teach math in school?
Alice!
It's fine!
I'm obviously not going to kill her.
I will kill everyone else
in this school, though.
I didn't know who to bring
to the dance,
so I brought C-4.
They do still teach science
in this school, right?
- You're lying.
- No, she's not.
I'm not outing Batwoman.
Send the message or
she will kill everyone in here.
If I out you,
everyone you care about
will be in danger.
You'll probably will be arrested.
You won't be Batwoman anymore.
- I can take care of myself.
- But Gotham can't.
We need you.
If Batwoman goes away,
the city's hope goes with it.
I think I just puked in my mouth.
I'll do it.
Tell everyone.
Fine.
Well, I guess we figured out
why they call you generation Z.
Because...
You try hacking ten cellular networks
with one hand.
It's done. I did it.
All of Gotham now knows
Kate's secret.
Is everyone seeing this?
Alpha team, run the move
to Gotham Prep, let's go.
- Go.
- Maybe I don't want to.
Maybe I don't care, go!
Now, where were we?
- Hey!
- Right about there.
How do I disarm this bomb?
Enough with the games.
You're not a hero!
It doesn't take a hero to know
what pure evil looks like.
You ruined my life.
I fixed your life, Kate.
Our father didn't believe us.
Now he's being punished.
Catherine tried to keep us apart
for 15 years,
and now she's dead.
What more do I have to do
to prove my loyalty to you?
You can tell me that you didn't
put a bomb in a gym full of kids.
Here we go again.
- Judgy, judge, judge.
- If everything you have done
has been some kind of gift to me,
then take it all back.
Why can't you accept me
for who I am?
We're sisters, Kate.
Be my sister!
We were sisters.
And then Beth died.
And the world would be
a whole lot better
if she had stayed dead.
I don't believe you.
What did she do?
She saved their lives.
We establish the perimeter,
then make contact.
I'll lead a team to the west,
there's a faculty entrance
on the South side.
Let's get there, now!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Get off the driveway.
There's a bomb in the high school.
Get back, take cover.
Come on! Let's go!
Come on! Everyone out!
Go! Let's go, now! Move!
Well, she saved most of their lives.
What are you talking about?
No one said that...
that was the detonator.
Where is it?
Go! Let's go, let's go!
Oh, my god!
Kiss, kiss, kiss!
Not happening!
Why not?
It's an office.
What were you expecting?
Like, I don't know,
a bunker or something?
Where's your bat bike?
What bat bike?
What bat bike.
Ow, child, remember?
Community service.
For that stun that you pulled
on the subway
and then doxing the mayor.
A 150 hours scrubbing gravity?
Yeah, and if I found out
you're still hacking,
you'll be scrubbing toilets
at Gotham Juvie.
Oh, and you're going to pay back
every single person
who send you blackmail money.
Fine.
Alice could've killed you.
I was outed before I wanted
my parents to know.
I wasn't about to do
the same thing to you.
And if you're wondering
if I'm going to tell anyone
about you, I...
I'm not.
Dismissed.
Okay, then.
See you around.
Parker...
You're right.
Sometimes it feels like
it's not going to get better.
You will.
If you stop hating yourself.
If you ever want to talk
about your parents, or
Kayla Mason, anyone.
I'm here.
Thanks.
You know...
When you took off your mask...
I never in a million years
expected it to be you.
Someone like me.
I'm glad it was.
No one offered you anything to drink?
Good.
Careful, Sophie.
We know how this job
worked out for your old boss.
The Mayor was more than willing
to hand you over to me.
So you're going
to sit here indefinitely
until you tell me
where to find Mouse.
Well, look who reached
cover girl status.
Look, I... I know what are you
going to say,
it was reckless,
it links me to Batwoman,
it puts our operation in jeopardy.
I was going to say that
whole lot of people
are about to feel a lot less alone,
and if this fallout,
we'll figure it out.
Happy birthday!
Baked it myself by the way.
Turns out when
I'm not on the comms,
I have way too much free time
on my hands.
Yeah, can you not leave me
alone like that again?
It's weird, kind of sounds
like you missed me.
- I managed.
- So that's a yes.
Hope it comes true.
Okay, people, time to recalibrate
our gaydar.
Batwoman is a lesbian,
not that there's anything
wrong with that.
But talk to me, Gotham,
whatever happened to politics
staying out of our superheroes?
We all wear a mask of some kind
a cowl, a husband,
wife, denial, anger.
We all need our shield
to protect us from the world.
But for people like us,
it's not always about stopping
a runaway train
or disarming a bomb.
Okay, as a doctor, you should
really remove the word crazy
from you every day vernacular.
Yes.
Thanks, have fun
on the wrong side of history.
Bye.
Hi.
Sometimes the best way
to save someone,
is to be yourself.
You were right.
Mary just needed a hug.
I'm sure she wasn't the only one.
You two are gonna need each other
now more than ever.
You're on my phone, puppy dog.
We're going to get you
out of there, dad.
I wish I could be with you today.
Happy birthday, kiddo.
Happy birthday!
How did you get in here?
Easy.
Hey, did you guys fire
that hot front desk guy?
Because he's the best part
of this place.
Hi.
I'm back.
Happy birthday!
- Did Sophie let you go?
- Who?
Kate, I'm finally come home
after a semester abroad
and this is how you react?
It was bad enough that they
converted my apartment
into a boy's dorm room
and no one chose to tell me...
Kate!
Who are you?
What's wrong with you?
- Who are you?
- It's me, it's Beth!
Beth?
Who the hell else would I be?