Previously on Batwoman...
- So, you're into me?
- You would know.
- I'll call you then.
- I'd like that.
Bruce never stopped looking
for your sister's body.
The guy had the best tech
on the planet.
Why didn't he find her?
- I think Alice is Beth.
- I thought they found her body.
They found bone fragments.
Skull fragments matching Beth's DNA.
She is your daughter.
King of the Crows,
can't even protect your own nest.
How'd you get in my house?
You're making this personal, Alice.
It is personal!
What the hell do you want?
You're gonna tell me
everything you know about Alice.
You're not Batman.
That's the point.
Shiny, shiny.
Keep your Tiffany's close
and your Mikimoto closer, Gotham.
Last night marks
the third bling theft in a week,
this time nearly killing a guard
in the process,
while today everyone is asking,
where was Batwoman?
Hot off the heels
of her city-wide debut
and she's a no-show.
Seriously, was she curling her hair?
Overcome by the myriad
of red lipstick shades?
Going through a breakup...
Thank you.
Going through a breakup?
Batwoman literally risked
her life protecting the city.
Well, I heard she's doing Batman.
Oh, you heard?
From who? Killer Croc?
I kind of like her, actually.
- Gotham could use a woman as such.
- Oh, so you are into red heads now.
No, not at this exact moment.
I hate whoever that is.
Sorry, it's my...
My friend type thing.
Girlfriend, because that's
just what sounded like.
It's a guy friend from work. We share
a office space, the water main broke.
That sounds really serious.
I know, yeah, I should probably go.
You come over super late,
you leave before breakfast.
I feel like I can date you
and start a new hobby.
I'll make it up to you.
- Okay, I have to go.
- What if you don't? Stay back.
A wise woman once said,
"Hurt me with the truth.
Don't comfort me with a lie."
Yes, Bruce, I'm quoting Rihanna.
Because I'm not a liar.
I have never hidden who I am.
I came out when Brad Morrison
told all the kids at school
that I was gay.
I said, "Yeah, and?"
And punched him.
Ever since then
I've been out and proud
as long as I can remember.
So how the hell am I supposed
to wake up every morning
and hide who I am?
That is brilliant.
But do watch the glare, Margot.
Can I get a bounce card?
Hey, wanna tell me
what the hell is going on?
You must be Roxanna.
Such a pleasure, Ms. Kane.
The Museum of Antiquities
is so grateful
you're lending us
Martha Wayne's necklace.
We cannot think
of a better showpiece
to represent strong women
and pillars of their community.
She always loved your museum.
Margot, is that the last lens change?
- Yes.
- Shall we get a few more shots?
Then we can get out
of Ms. Kane's hair.
- Where have you been?
- Now, here.
I'm seeing someone.
Okay, so, while you've been...
That Magpie struck again.
She nuked a place last night.
Nearly killed a security guard.
The vinework is so earth chic.
It's a work in progress.
Well, with that giant
"Wayne" sign on the building,
I'm sure whatever it is
will make Gotham proud.
- No pressure, right?
- I'll have our security team
bring the necklace
to the event tomorrow.
Smart.
With everything that's been
happening around the city,
you can never be too careful.
So, that is not why I called.
So your pet, Dodgson,
not looking too good
and probably not smelling great.
What are we doing here?
He hangs out until he tells us
Alice's grand plan.
- Or he dies.
- He's just dehydrated.
- He's septic.
- Were you this annoying
when Batman took people prisoner?
I didn't think so.
Yeah, he needs an ER.
Does your husband know
what's in plot 283, Catherine?
Your driver's gone nighty-night.
He's on a Benzo break.
What are you doing here?
The great existential question.
What are we all doing here?
You know, the thing I love
about bad guys
is that despite ourselves,
we are all so tragically predictable.
Of course you'd follow
the cards I left right back here
to cover your tracks.
What do you want?
To keep this to myself.
And in return,
you are gonna give something.
A very powerful toy.
I understand that Hamilton Dynamics
is developing a very
"top secret weapon".
I own one of the largest
defense companies in the country.
I'm hardly privy
to its day-to-day project
- management side.
- But you are.
You are the priviest.
Because this particular project
was your idea.
How do you know that?
Well, I spent an hour
in your house, Catherine.
What did you think,
I was just only poking around
your shoe closet?
Which should be its own monument,
by the way.
Yeah, you are gonna give it to me
by 10.00pm tomorrow,
or Commander Kane will know that
you are the one who convinced him
his dear darling daughter was dead.
Oh, my God.
Hi! You're Batwoman.
Mary Hamilton. Huge fan.
But not in, like, an annoying way.
Can I just say welcome to Gotham?
And you know what, screw the haters.
I once wore a jumpsuit and it was
bordering on last season...
I need your help.
I heard you're discreet.
Okay. Yeah. Anything.
Okay, so, he actually
just tried to kill me, so...
That's not me saying no.
It's just slightly more complicated.
Why do you have him?
I need to know
what Alice is planning.
This is grossly infected.
You don't have any Neosporin
in your bat belt?
- Can you save him?
- I can try.
Because I actually subscribe
to a code.
It's called "do no harm."
- I'll be back for him.
- We'll be here.
Hopefully, alive.
If I wanted to be
a beacon of hope to Gotham,
I needed to show them
that I was there.
I had to restore their confidence
in the Bat.
And to do that,
I needed to catch
Gotham's most dangerous thief.
Batcave to Batwoman.
How long have you waited
to say that?
Honestly, it just came to me
two seconds ago, so...
What do you want?
I've been thinking, why is this
Magpie woman so hard to track?
The police can't find her,
she's one step ahead of The Crows,
no trace of her
on any city surveillance,
and then it occurred to me,
everyone's looking for a woman,
when we should be looking for a bird.
Eagle cams.
Do we have to be
on opposite sides?
Birds of a feather
should flock together.
I'm allergic to feathers.
An egg? Really committing to this
whole bird thing, aren't you?
- You really think it's worth it?
- Maybe not to you.
But to me it's food,
a roof over my head,
and a modicum of dignity.
Batarang? More like Bat-a-wiff!
According to the gallery's
security footage,
last night, our lady crusader
missed the return
on her not-so-trusty batarang
and caused some major damage
to a gilded vase
that once belonged
to Marie Antoinette.
And we thought
Magpie was a threat to this city.
Talk to me, Gotham.
Do we need to take out
an insurance policy
on our new hero?
You probably miscalculated
the precession torque.
- I didn't.
- Maybe you angled it wrong.
- Maybe it's broken.
- It's not broken.
If it worked, I would've caught it.
Did you try flicking your wrist
backward then snapping it for...
You're batsplaining. I already
have the whole city on my butt.
I do not need you
joining in the chorus.
Well, good news, bad news.
I figured out what you ripped off
Magpie's belt last night.
Grenades.
Yeah, cute but no less deadly.
Concussion or fragmentation?
Probably an M67
filled with TNT or gunpowder.
I'll know more
after I run a chemical analysis.
It could help us track down Magpie.
- How long would that take?
- Depending on the complexity
of the deformulation,
hour and a half?
- Great. I'll see you then.
- Wait, where are you going?
I owe someone a lunch.
Someone? A date?
Cool. Yeah, no, I'll be here.
Not dating anyone
because I love to work.
Love to work.
This is great. Have fun.
Pretty song.
Alice was playing it
when she broke into the penthouse
the other night.
Alice plays the cello?
That's so...
On brand.
Beth played the cello.
This was her favorite piece.
Do you think...
What did you bring me?
The report detailing
the bomb that blew up
Alice's transport van.
I thought you'd want to see it
before anyone else.
It's an IED
using high-standard components.
The convoy had seven vehicles.
It hit Alice's van
with a 99.9 percent accuracy.
Bomb probably used
an advanced sensor initiation
to detect its target.
A sensor with that level of detection
is unreleased technology
unique to Hamilton Dynamics.
What are you saying?
The bomb's one of ours?
Why would someone at Hamilton
want to ambush the convoy?
You were living with polar bears,
under the Borealis,
no rent, no traffic,
no getting mugged in line
grabbing a coffee.
Why the hell did you move back here?
- Long story.
- So an ex-girlfriend.
Told you I can read people.
Her name is Sophie
and she's in the past,
and according to her
we never even had a past,
so there's that.
You came home for your ex
who doesn't see you as an ex.
Sounds like
I have nothing to worry about.
Why are we talking about her?
I used to live there.
Before it was that,
it was a small, charming,
ten-unit place full of sweet,
neighborly, hardworking people
who all got exiled
to parts of the city
that no one cared about.
Meanwhile, all the predatory
real estate moguls,
who don't give a crap about
the lives they're uprooting,
get rich.
You were literally evicted
from your childhood.
That's awful.
Not that I'd want to live
in a Crows District anyway.
- No offense.
- You Googled me.
Of course I did.
No one's allowed to have secrets
anymore.
So does that mean
that you will tell me
- where we're going for lunch?
- It does.
My mom taught English
to the woman who owns the place.
She's super cute
and has the best tofu paneer.
I think you're gonna like it.
Another plumbing emergency?
Electrical fire
in the ventilation system.
That sounds like a real mess.
What is it that you do again?
Nothing, really. Just keeping
tabs on my cousin's building.
Not so good at it, huh?
There's a fundraiser later
at the Antiquities Museum.
- You wanna be my date?
- Maybe.
Come on. 9.30. No emergencies.
Please, please, please.
Okay. Holding you to it.
9.30?
You gotta be kidding me.
Oh, come on.
She stole the necklace.
She took it by feathers and force.
I'll let the museum know
they're losing their showpiece.
Bruce's mom was killed
for that necklace.
Yeah.
He spent years
looking for it on the streets.
Finally found it at an auction
and spent a million dollars
buying it back.
I should have been here.
I have to get it back.
Any leads on the bomb?
Actually, yeah.
Magpie 3D printed them.
- That's new.
- Yeah, I know.
Nano thermites via ink jet.
- Explosive ink.
- It's regulated.
Only a few companies sell it.
Then we find everyone
that it's sold to.
Well, you know, The Crows
do track munition shipments
in and out of the city.
You could ask your girl Sophie
if she can get a list
of who's buying exploding ink.
It's bad timing.
Bad timing.
A bomber loose in Gotham.
I...
Exploding ink? That's specific.
Magpie used one
to break into Wayne Tower.
She take anything?
My Aunt Martha's pearl necklace.
Damn. Does your dad know?
Copy.
Heard the Bat had a run-in
with her the other night.
The Bat?
I thought they were calling her
Batwoman now.
Is that official?
I think so. It's catchy, mature...
So, if she's on the case,
why are you?
You know why.
I don't trust vigilantes.
How's the search going?
Just texted it to you.
Everyone within a hundred mile radius
who recently purchased
explosive ink.
I really appreciate it.
I'm glad you came to me.
I know things between us
have been a little tense,
but we always make a good team.
I have to go.
So clever of Catherine
to send you boys
to find my cozy burrow.
But you're not the only ones
with ears all around this city.
When you start asking
about our location,
it gets back to me.
Desperate, desperate
Catherine Hamilton-Kane
sending her goons
to clean up her mess.
Perhaps she needs a little reminder
that I'm not playing games.
Who wants to help me
send her a message?
Eeny, meeny,
miney,
moe.
You.
It was him. You pointed at him.
Like I said, I'm not playing a game.
There are no rules.
Another construction firm,
fireworks manufacturer,
gold mining company.
Wait, this shipment
doesn't have a destination.
- Can you key the address?
- Yeah, let me check.
Sophie thinks I'm the Bat.
- How?
- Because I suck at hiding it.
How did Bruce make living
a double life look so easy?
- Oh, he didn't. He was miserable.
- Bruce Wayne?
Guy had three Ferraris
and slept with half of Gotham.
The playboy thing gave him a cover.
Different women meant he could
tell the same lies easily,
but it sucked for him, too.
Honestly, in those last few months,
I think being Batman
was easier for him
than being Bruce.
So the address is a P.O. box.
You can send explosives
to a P.O. box?
If you don't wanna get caught.
I just got to the old Gotham Hotel.
The address linked
to the P.O. box account.
Guy at the facility
gave it to me.
Do I want to know how you
got him to tell you that?
Let him take a selfie.
Definitely not the answer
I was expecting.
Let me guess,
Batman never posed for selfies.
Wasn't gonna say it.
I think I found Magpie's nest.
I see jewelry, a computer,
a 3D printer...
And my breath, room's freezing.
Well, that's smart.
It's climate rigged.
If anyone enters, their body will
raise the room's temperature
and set off an explosion.
You might wanna lead with that.
I'm sorry, but, yo, check this out.
The suit can lower your body
temperature to match the room
and bypass the sensors.
That is uncomfortably cold.
Rather cold than dead.
Oh, one more thing.
- What?
- You know you can't breathe,
- right?
- You're kidding me.
I didn't invent kinetic energy.
How long can you
hold your breath for?
Gets dicey after two minutes.
All right, that's how long you got.
Actually, now might be
a good time to let you know
that I fixed the batarang.
And by fixed, I mean realized
it was calibrated for Bruce,
who has longer arms than you.
I guess
it wasn't entirely your fault.
You're probably thinking some
pretty choice words right now,
but since you'll blow up
if you say them out loud,
probably best to keep them
to yourself.
Anyway, all fixed,
recalibrated, for you,
a woman with slightly shorter arms.
Oh, while you're in there,
if you can try to clone a copy
of her hard drive, it'd be great.
It might give us a clue into what
Magpie gets her talon into next.
Definitely been a minute.
Still alive? Don't answer that.
Did you just...
Why?
Stop, Alice.
No.
Don't want to.
Alice! Help me.
Alice...
Oh, I'm not actually Al...
Curiouser and curiouser.
Alice?
Yes, darling.
It's me.
It's Alice.
Where am I?
You're in the rabbit hole, darling.
With the Caterpillar
and the Mad Hatter
and the Queen of Hearts.
I'm actually quite happy you're here.
You see, I've foolishly forgotten
the details of my evil plan.
Perhaps you could...
Stir up a memory or two.
Where is she?
She thinks...
it's me you care about.
Who, dear? The Batwoman?
Darling?
Finish your thought.
The Batwoman thinks
I care about whom?
She...
Has no idea...
About...
About who?
Who? Who?
Mouse...
She has...
Big plans for him.
- In position.
- Let me know when you see her.
Way too much tempting bling
for her not to show.
What is that noise?
Magpie had some
complicated schematics
for something on her hard drive.
They're encrypted,
but I'll try printing them.
Whatever it is
could be her next target
and help us track her down.
- I gotta go.
- Go where?
Reagan's here.
Wait. You invited her to a takedown?
I invited her on a date.
That just happens to be
at the takedown location.
I don't need to tell you that...
Batman would've never done that,
I know.
- Is it done?
- Does this look done to you?
Oh, my God.
That bitch is a rare breed
of psychopath, okay?
Take your money, take your power,
I don't care.
This is your mess, Catherine.
You want her gone, do it yourself.
This is Catherine.
"Oh, dear, oh, dear.
I shall be too late,"
said the rabbit,
tapping at his watch.
Kate.
Sophie.
I didn't know
you were working the event.
I wasn't.
But I figured with
a jewelry thief on the prowl,
we could use the extra manpower.
- Of course you did.
- Kate.
Reagan. Hi. I'm sorry I'm late.
- Hey. Reagan.
- Sophie.
Figured.
Sorry, I didn't realize
you were here with anyone.
I got us drinks.
You two have fun.
So I don't know about you,
but I'm gonna drink this
and pretend
it's not totally uncomfortable
that your ex is here.
Sorry...
I'm being a really crappy date.
Can we start over
and I mention how beautiful you look?
Thank you.
And I hate that that worked.
Ms. Kane. Welcome.
I'm so glad you made it.
- I'm sorry the pearls didn't.
- What do you mean?
Didn't Luke Fox
get in touch with you?
Yes, but I was just so relieved
when the security guards
showed up with them
in the nick of time.
Perfect timing. Excuse me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight, we are here
to celebrate powerful women
throughout history.
And who better embodies that
than Martha Wayne?
It is with utmost gratitude
to the Wayne Estate
that I present to you
tonight's showpiece,
her beloved pearl necklace.
Would you excuse me for a minute?
I was just about to call you.
Martha's necklace is at
the exhibit, which is impossible,
because we never gave it
to the museum.
That is not her necklace.
It's replica. It's the last thing
that Magpie printed.
She snuck a bomb in here.
Why would Magpie bomb the museum?
She's not. It's a Trojan Horse.
Use the explosion in the showroom
as a distraction
and she'll have free reign
over the exhibit room.
The Wayne family has been
a hallmark to Gotham,
and their legacy lives on even today.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen,
it looks like we have
a little situation on our hands.
Everyone,
please move towards the exit!
Everyone, calmly towards the exit.
I'm not meant to be a jailbird.
Looks like you have a choice to make.
The shiny jewels are all insured,
but those sitting ducks
only have one life.
Which are you gonna save?
Mommy, I found a marble.
It's really you.
It's over.
I've seen you before,
you're the photographer.
You weren't just taking photos
at Wayne Tower,
you were casing it.
People like you
never notice people like me.
You put a lot of lives
in danger tonight.
Well, some of us don't have
the privilege of sitting in our tower
having angst about what to do
with our lives, Ms. Kane.
We just do it. To survive.
Time to go to Blackgate, Margot.
- Hey, did you see that?
- I didn't. I was on a call.
Batwoman showed up. It was surreal.
I tried calling you.
I must've been in a dead zone.
You just said you were on a call.
I did. I...
So here's why this sucks.
I like you.
You're funny. You're cool.
But that's not really enough.
I'm not a needy person, Kate,
but if I'm gonna make an effort,
miss a spin class,
or rearrange a work shift...
All I ask for is a little honesty.
Here's why this sucks.
I think you're fun and cool
and seem to care about
all the right things.
And I'm not in a place right now
where I can share all of myself
with someone else.
I am sorry.
I get it.
You obviously have a lot going on.
I just hope whatever it is,
it makes you happy.
Well,
this is a nice surprise.
Sweetheart, you okay?
Alice came to me today.
She came to you. Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. She didn't hurt me.
She wants something.
Hamilton is developing a new project,
and Alice has taken interest.
- What?
- It doesn't matter.
I refuse to put any weapon
into the hands of a terrorist.
Don't answer that. It could be her.
Well, if it's her, I should get it...
Jacob, please...
You should hear this from me.
Sweetheart, what's going on?
It was years ago.
I thought
it was the right thing to do.
You thought what was
the right thing to do?
You and Kate wouldn't stop looking.
Kate was up all night.
She wasn't going to school.
She was refusing to eat.
She wouldn't give up,
and she wasn't living her life.
The more despair that she felt,
the more broken you became.
What did you do, Catherine?
You were both
in a downward spiral, Jacob.
You never would've moved on
if you didn't...
Think that Beth were dead.
They found bones.
Skull fragments.
Hamilton employees found bones...
From a deer.
I paid the DNA analyst
to write the report.
The police, the...
My investigators, the entire city,
had been looking and looking for Beth
without finding so much
as a sock, Jacob.
- She was gone.
- Stop.
Get away from me.
Just...
Just get away from me.
You have to stop doing that.
Sudden adrenaline release
can lead to cardiac arrest
and I'm way too busy to have
a heart condition right now.
- You fixed him.
- He's stable.
An hour later
and I may not have been able to.
You were right.
I shouldn't have let him
get this bad.
Yeah, so, on that topic,
I may have prodded him a little
while he was under
a morphine haze.
I know, but he ruined
my favorite plaid shirt
when he stabbed me.
So my point is
Alice is looking for a Mouse
or someone named Mouse.
He said "Mouse,"
and she has big plans for him.
So I thought you should know.
Hang on! You can't just...
What is that?
Subdermal transponder.
- A what?
- Chipped him.
He'll lead me to Alice,
I'll figure out who Mouse is.
Oh, okay.
- Good work, Mary.
- Okay.
Thank you.
The bomb-loving bird is finally
in a cage where she belongs.
Batwoman clipped her wings.
And she wasn't very sweet
about it either.
Hey, Batwoman,
you have a such a pretty face.
Ever think about smiling more?
Another win in the bat column.
Almost got a compliment
out of Vesper Fairchild, too.
I reunited a bunch of billionaires
with things
they probably didn't miss.
You also saved
a lot of innocent lives.
The city trusts you now.
They trust Batwoman.
Kate Kane is a different story.
What do you know
about real estate?
Everyone hates popcorn ceilings?
So more than me.
I'm starting a real estate firm.
Okay, so,
the last thing the city needs
is another predatory developer
cluttering the skyline.
I agree.
That's why I want to buy
run-down buildings
from outside the Crows districts,
keep the rents low,
and give them back
to the community.
So Bruce was a billionaire playboy,
and you're gonna be who,
Joanna Gaines?
- You can be Chip.
- I just told you.
I don't know anything
about real estate.
Well, you better learn quick
because you're gonna be
my assistant.
- Associate.
- Up for debate.
Dear, Bruce, Queen Rihanna was right.
Lies don't make anyone comfortable,
especially the one telling them.
But no one said anything
about this job being comfortable.
If I'm going to embrace the Bat,
then I'm going to have to embrace
hiding a part of myself
from the outside world.
Living this double life
is a sacrifice.
But our city is worth it.