Previously on Batwoman...
How about we don't get expelled
a week before graduation?
I need this school, okay?
I wanna be here.
But they don't want you.
It is best if you just
kept your distance from now on.
I know you love me.
Tell me that I'm wrong
and I'll walk away
and let you make
the biggest mistake of your life.
You're wrong, Kate.
- Is this you?
- It wasn't me.
So, what is she doing with herself?
So, are you on this assignment
to keep tabs on me or on Kate?
- Dad?
- Catherine Hamilton's
investigators found bones.
Skull fragments of a little girl.
It's Beth.
Hi, Daddy.
- Put down the knife.
- You gave up on me!
Beth, drop the damn knife!
- Dad.
- Kate, it's her. It's Beth.
I have gift for you too.
Now that we are together again,
I can help you become anyone
you want to be.
Have we met? I'm afraid so.
Absolutely not.
Listen, the victim
had the courage
to come forward
and face her attackers.
Well, I'm confident a jury
will make the right decision.
Question is, are you?
Oh, my god.
No, no, no!
Oh, god.
Beth was being held by a madman
with a medical license.
We don't have much to go on.
Deed to the house belonged
to Dr. August Cartwright.
I have teams
trying to pick up a trace
but it's like he just disappeared.
Apparently, he's a better
magician than he was a doctor.
Beth was held in a cell by a guy
making human skin masks
while I was at home
playing club soccer.
We need to find him.
- We will.
- We didn't find her.
How many times can I say I'm sorry
for not listening to you?
I don't know.
How many times will it take
to get Beth back?
Sir.
You're gonna want
to see this.
Gotham is reeling over the death
of Prosecutor Angus Stanton,
who was murdered
horrifically tonight.
Stanton was seen by many
as a hero to Gotham
one who brought justice
to the victims
of some of the city's
most notorious criminals
such as Jack Napier,
otherwise known as the Joker.
Channel Nine has the security
camera footage.
Conviction rate,
Stanton was known...
- What's he wearing?
- From being a formidable
opponent in the courtroom,
in addition to being...
It an old-fashioned
executioner's hood.
- This is Dana Dewitt...
- Ax is a nice touch.
from old Gotham.
Anybody want to tell me
why every news outlet in Gotham
had this and we didn't
even get so much
as a heads-up from the GCPD?
Technically,
it's outside district lines.
And I believe it's because
they called someone else.
I am not about to stand around
and let Gotham cry out
to be saved by someone
who hides behind a mask.
The Bat is nothing more
than a symbol of false hope.
I want this so-called
Executioner cuffed
and stuffed in a cell in Blackgate.
If this city starts to think
it can rely on a vigilante
for justice
we might as well hand it over
to the crazies.
Sir, I know it's all hands
on deck for this Stanton Case,
but I was hoping
to get your permission
for another special assignment.
- Who is it this time?
- Batwoman.
Don't you want to know
who's behind the mask?
Head back, sweetie.
One final touch.
There.
Dazzle me.
A perfect match for Dean Deveraux.
Wouldn't you agree, Mr. Deveraux?
Please, don't hurt me.
I don't understand
why we don't just kill him.
Because my sister is watching me
like a hawk.
Still trying to bring
the old Beth back.
You're not thinking of giving her
the old Beth back, are you?
- Of course not.
- Really?
Because the old Alice I remember
wouldn't think second thought
about opening his throat
with a butterfly knife.
- She's changed you.
- Not at all.
You're the one who's changed.
You used to trust me.
What about you, Dean?
Do you trust me?
I think you'd make
an excellent partner.
I seem to be in need
of a replacement.
Stop.
I'll do whatever you want.
Good.
Because I need you to steal
Catherine's shiny new toy.
The one that she's too stingy
to share.
- You see the Bat-Signal?
- That is why I'm here.
You know, what this means, right?
First time the city's called
Batwoman for back-up means
- I can't screw it up.
- It means you're in.
GCPD's got you
on their speed dial now.
- Commissioner Forbes trusts you.
- Commissioner might.
My dad still sees me as his enemy.
Stopping this guy has
to convince him otherwise.
That's not the only reason
worth stopping him.
Stanton was the prosecutor
who put away the guy
that killed my dad.
It's armed robbery, right?
Night of my high school graduation.
We were celebrating,
me getting into MIT.
We ran out of ice.
My dad went out to go get some.
Next thing I know,
there are two cops at the door,
wanting me to come down
and ID the body.
We were waiting on him
to cut the cake.
Lucius Fox did a lot of good
for this city.
Yeah, so did Stanton.
He never stopped until he put the guy
who shot my dad behind bars.
- Any suspects?
- Well, if you exclude
the law-abiding citizens of Gotham,
that leaves the other half.
There has to be some way
to narrow that down.
Start with the violent offenders.
Cross-reference with recent parolees,
work release, and escapees
with whatever biometrics we can get
- from the security footage.
- All right.
This is interesting.
Chris Medlock, otherwise known
as Chris the Fist.
- Ex-boxer. Ex-con.
- What was The Fist in for?
Shot and killed a bartender.
He confessed,
later claimed it was coerced...
But they found the gun in his car.
Pleaded down to second-degree murder.
Got 30 in Blackgate.
He was lucky to avoid
the death penalty.
Yeah, The Fist did not see it
that way.
Check out his sentencing...
I'll get you, you son of a bitch!
This ain't over!
I got a whole bunch of time
to figure out
how I'm gonna kill your ass!
Thanks to overcrowding,
he was paroled
just a few months ago.
Can't wait to meet him.
Guy have an address?
We may not need one.
Check out what just came
in over GCPD dispatch.
Someone claiming to be
the Executioner
barricaded himself
inside a building
at the 200 block of Rucka Avenue.
Claims to have several hostages.
That's in West Harlow.
- Put it on the screen.
- Okay.
All right, let's get on this.
I don't care
if it's outside our District.
Let's show Gotham
we can keep them safe.
Move!
He talking?
Says he'll only speak to one guy.
- A Detective Donnelly.
- Who?
Detective Donnelly,
time is running out on your hostages.
Get in here or I start
- shooting these people!
- Listen,
you don't have to go in there.
Let me get a negotiator
down here.
No, me and The Fist go way back.
Detective!
Like the new look.
- Red suits you.
- Goes with everything.
Time's up, Donnelly!
No, Donnelly! Stay back!
No, wait! Stop!
I'm hit.
You're bleeding. I'll get you help.
Thanks, Kate.
Oh, my god! Sophie.
I need to know if you can fix her.
What was she shot with?
- A bullet.
- I know it's a bullet!
Hollow-point,
blackout or wadcutter?
- Does it matter?
- Why did you bring her here?
She can afford a real hospital.
You were closer and I am not.
And I need you to keep her here
until I get back.
The Crows don't know
she's missing.
- No, you can't...
- Do not let her leave.
Man of the hour.
Congratulations.
You have succeeded
where so many have failed.
The coil accelerator,
it works at last.
And I just have to know,
how were you able to overcome
the ferromagnetic projectile
saturation?
You almost had me there,
Miss Hamilton.
Trick question,
that's proprietary information.
Hard to imagine...
Something so delicate
harnessing enough power
to penetrate the bat suit.
Well done, Dean.
- She called you Kate?
- She knows who I am.
Amazing. That's... look great.
Fantastic.
So naturally,
you decided to dropped her off
at your sister's unlicensed clinic.
Mary will take care of her.
She'll also keep her from leaving.
And as long as she can't leave,
she can't talk.
But she's a Crow.
Your father's second in command.
You really think you can
convince her not to tell him?
I'll deal with that after we've
dealt with the Executioner.
We need to figure out
his next target.
The guy not making it easy.
He keeps changing his MO.
50,000 volts of electricity,
then a bunch of rifles.
- Doesn't make any sense.
- Unless it's a pattern.
The Fist dresses up
as an executioner.
Kills Stanton with electricity,
like an electric chair.
Then, he gets Donnelly to walk in
on that shooting gallery.
Like a firing squad.
He's using methods
of capital punishment
- to kill his victims.
- On it.
Gotham's used three ways
to kill people on death row,
electric chair, firing squad,
which made a brief comeback
under Mayor Cobblepot,
and the gas chamber.
So his next victim will be with gas.
Guy's got a flair for detail,
so I'll bet you a batarang,
he'll use hydrogen cyanide pellets
just like they did
in the gas chamber.
And...
And there's only one warehouse
in Gotham that stores them.
- Who's there?
- Someone who needs information.
Holy crap. You're her.
I got to get this.
- Damn, girl.
- Not happening.
Anything out of the ordinary
around here lately?
- Well, besides this?
- Answer the question.
That'd mean someone
had to get by me
and that ain't gonna happen.
It's been quiet.
But, you know, it doesn't have to be.
Let me buy you a drink
and you can tell me
all about the superhero thing.
I've been thinking about
getting into the game myself.
What do you say?
I get off at 11.00,
and if you play your cards right,
you won't be too far behind.
Okay, so this place
hasn't seen any action.
And apparently,
neither has its guard.
Yeah. I think I might know why.
Got a visual on Chris The Fist,
alleyway at Sprang River.
Get off of me, man.
I didn't do nothing.
Oh, got it.
So you're just out
for a late night jog.
Crows got The Fist.
Well, I guess a lot of people
will be sleeping easier tonight.
I know you wanted to catch him,
but you can convince the Crows
you're not their enemy tomorrow.
Tomorrow may be too late.
I need to check on Sophie.
Kate, you copy?
Kate? Kate?
Kate, do you copy?
What just happened?
The Crows got the wrong guy.
And the Executioner
got what he came for.
All of this Bat-Tech and you
came up with frozen water?
I checked every camera angle
on the warehouse security system,
but license plate's got mud
or something on it.
We can't get a good view of it.
Don't suppose you were able
to make it out?
Didn't quite catch it
when it plowed into me.
Oh, that's... oh, that's great!
- My ribs would argue otherwise.
- No. I'm serious, okay?
The suit's carbon-fiber ribbing
is designed to absorb any impact.
So any deformation in the fibers
is recorded in the suites data.
Okay. So it was
originally designed
to track damage caused by bullets.
You know, blunt force trauma,
that kind of thing.
There's no reason it wouldn't pick up
an impression from a car bumper.
Or a license plate.
Okay. It's a partial,
but it will work.
Okay, the truck is registered
to a Bertrand Eldon.
And he was at Blackgate
for 20 years.
What was he in for?
He worked there.
He was their executioner.
No!
I just did some of the best work
of my life
crocheting you back together.
What?
Where am I?
Mary, what the hell is going on?
Batwoman brought you in.
You were shot.
- Batwoman?
- Okay.
I feel like we glossed over
the part where I saved your life.
Thank you.
You work here?
It's mine.
My followers think
I'm turning up at the club
ordering bottle service.
The truth is, I'm usually here,
trying to help serve the people
the Gotham hospitals turn away.
Mary, if your dad ever found out
- about this place...
- He won't.
He can't.
Yeah, I didn't do that.
Well, you better undo it.
Batwoman will kill me.
And frankly, she's scarier than you.
Mary, why am I cuffed to this bed?
She, she said not to let you leave.
Do you know who she is?
No. Honestly, I don't want to know.
I don't need
that kind of responsibility.
Well, I do know who she is.
And that's why
she won't let me leave.
I'm in.
No, one's home.
Why would a guy working
at Blackgate
target a cop and a prosecutor?
They're on the same side.
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm looking for that answer
right now.
Looks like he was a model employee.
Stay frosty.
This guy is methodical,
technically proficient.
Always a few steps ahead.
He could have anything
waiting for you in there.
Already has,
just sitting on the coffee table.
What?
The hydrogen cyanide pellets.
I found them.
- On the coffee table?
- Yes.
- Well, it's probably a trap.
- I'm aware of that.
I don't see any trip-sensors
or wires or pressure plates.
What's the Bat-Protocol
with this?
Like, I just stand here
staring at this thing
waiting for the Executioner
to come back, come on.
Yeah, okay. Hang on. Just...
Can you place some hold music
while I wait?
No, okay. I'm just gonna grab it.
No, no, no! Don't do that.
- Kate, don't.
- Too late.
- And?
- And I'm still talking to you.
- It's light.
- Is it empty?
Not quite.
So if you found this,
then you found me and...
And I did it. I am guilty as sin.
But I'm not the only one.
For 20 years,
I threw the switch on the worst
people Gotham ever spat out.
I was glad to do it too.
Doing the public a service.
And it never bothered me when
they said they were innocent.
Great. Sadistic and long-winded.
I mean, what else
were they gonna say, right?
See, then all their stories,
they started to sound the same.
The same names kept coming up.
Same evidence.
And everybody who sat in my chair
started to look the same.
Black, brown, poor.
In 20 years,
I never juiced a rich, white guy.
So I started digging
into their files.
You know, what I found?
The same three corrupt
law enforcement officials
pulling the strings in every case.
Coerced confessions.
And murder weapons suddenly
showing up out of nowhere.
I mean, obviously planted.
Didn't Chris the Fist say that
his confession was coerced?
So it turns out...
And the murder weapon just
suddenly turned up in his car?
The people that I executed
were innocent.
Which meant that...
That I was the guilty one.
That, that cabal, it, it turned me
into a murderer.
Which they, they made me punish
the innocent.
So, who's the third member
of this cabal?
Wait.
You're not actually buying this.
Okay, believe me, I... I know racial
profiling is a thing in Gotham,
but this guy is obviously crazy.
Almost killed Sophie.
Nearly made you roadkill.
- Doesn't make him wrong.
- He's an admitted killer, Kate!
I knew Stanton, okay?
He spent hours with my family,
day after day.
And he never, ever stopped working
until he found justice.
If Stanton's accused of being dirty,
my dad's killer could use that
to get a new trial.
But if Chris the Fist
or anyone else goes down
for something they didn't do,
how is that justice?
Little present from the Crows.
Next time, call us first.
We may not have a klieg light,
but we do have a phone number.
Everybody, fan out!
Move, move.
Your turn.
It, it's okay. You can just win.
I said, your turn.
King me?
- What?
- It's me.
How did you get this number?
Let's call it "twintuition".
Why did you send Mouse
into Hamilton Dynamics
to get a weapon
that can kill Batwoman?
- Where is he?
- He's fine. Or he will be.
As long as you tell me the truth.
Dear sister, if I wanted to kill you,
I wouldn't have to wait for you
to be wearing the suit.
That's so sweet of you.
Your concern for me
is so touching, dear sister.
So Kate is Batwoman.
- I do not like being toyed with!
- And I don't like traitors.
What's wrong with you?
First, she abandons you.
Then, she tries to lock you away.
And still, you try to protect her.
Because she's still my sister!
Real family doesn't abandon
their own.
Who snuck food to you
in the middle of the night?
Who taught you Rummy,
and let you sleep with Mr. Pandy,
and promised to protect you
no matter what?
Me! I did, Alice!
Because I was there and she wasn't!
After everything we've been through,
you keep secrets from me?
Try keeping that a secret.
Okay, so who had
"Batwoman rescues a psychopath"
on their bingo card?
Because I've got some big,
fat empty spaces
for "Batwoman takes down Alice"
and "Batwoman gets a cat
out of a tree."
Talk to me, Gotham. Anyone
else feeling a little bat-trayed?
The people that I executed
were innocent.
Which meant that...
That I was the guilty one.
But that cabal
led by Judge Calverick
condemned innocent people to die.
I heard you got a visit
from Batwoman.
More like an ambush.
Now, one nutjob wants me
to listen to another nutjob.
Claims Judge Calverick,
one of Gotham's most
upstanding justices, is a fraud.
So, you're not even gonna look
into this Judge?
Why? Because some
social justice warrior
thinks he knows more
about the rule of law
than the cops and the lawyers
who protect this city? Nah.
We got the right guy.
Batwoman interfered.
Batwoman wouldn't have stepped in
if she didn't have a reason.
Before you give a shred
of credibility
to some criminal in a bat costume,
let me remind you that Batman
destroyed our family's lives.
He is not the one that drove
Mom's car off that bridge.
Well, he may as well have been.
Batman brought out
all the crazies in Gotham.
If it weren't for him,
there wouldn't have been a Joker.
Your Mom would be alive.
And Beth wouldn't be Alice.
Beth is Alice because
we stopped looking for her.
Not arguing about this right now.
That'd be a lot easier, wouldn't it?
Just... act like
we did nothing wrong?
We looked everywhere for Beth.
I looked everywhere.
I hold onto hope for the both of us.
Despite the lack of evidence,
despite the police giving up.
Despite the fact that everyone
thought she was dead.
I hoped when it was hard.
And you just gave up
and put your energy
into blaming Batman
because it was easy.
That's why Beth is Alice.
You wouldn't listen then,
and you won't listen now.
And an innocent man
is gonna pay the price for it.
Look who lucked out
by getting the last grape
popsicle.
Looks like you're healing nicely.
But I guess,
healing can't get in the way
of you spilling the tea on Batwoman?
Believe it or not,
I'm trying to protect her.
By having my dad shut down
her entire operation?
She's gonna get herself killed.
Batwoman can take care of herself.
Just like she took care of you.
Twice by my count.
And now,
you're just gonna betray her?
I...
I mean, what?
Is that like, your thing?
What's that supposed to mean?
I mean,
that's what you did to Kate.
And then,
she had to put an entire ocean
between you and her.
And now you walk around,
pretend like
she meant nothing to you.
You don't even know what happened.
No. But I saw what it did to her.
Look, you're right.
That's not my drama.
So do what you want.
In the meantime,
ibuprofen every four to six hours.
And change the bandage once a day.
Don't tell my dad about this clinic.
And maybe think about
whether or not
you want to add Batwoman
to the list of people you hurt.
Working late, Your Honor?
- How... how did you...
- Looks like you're burning
more than the midnight oil.
Is that the evidence?
Donnelly got the confessions,
Stanton convinced the jury,
and you just banged your gavel.
I can pay you.
You have to protect me from him.
You'll get around the clock
protection at Blackgate.
Free of charge.
Go!
You protect him?
A man who sent so many innocents
to their deaths?
The law will take care of it.
Yeah, I used to believe that too.
Until the law turned me
into a murderer.
The law's not perfect.
I'll give you that.
Doesn't mean
you get to rewrite it in blood.
If you trust law so much,
why are you wearing that suit?
I'm gonna need backup.
What do you want me to say?
He makes a good point.
No. For the Judge.
Get the Judge
into protective custody now.
Right. On it.
Sweep the rest of the building.
You decided to go
after the right guy.
I don't see how you and him
are that different.
Taking the law into your own hands.
Appointing yourself judge and jury.
Pretty sure you just did
the exact same thing.
I saved your life.
You telling me I made a mistake?
I don't know. Ask The Fist.
I admit I got it wrong.
But you know the difference
between me and you?
When I make a mistake,
everybody knows my name.
I am accountable
to the people of Gotham.
You...
You hide behind your anonymity.
Who are you accountable to?
Guess we'll find out.
Heart rate monitor linked
to a dead man's switch.
Looks like we're about to join him.
This is Kane. Anybody read me?
Suit's showing
oxygen levels dropping.
No, kidding. Executioner turned
this room to a gas chamber.
Can your men get us out of here?
He triggered the lockdown procedure.
Every way in and out of here
are sealed off.
Steel-reinforced doors.
By the time my guys
get through them...
Air's getting thin in here.
I need a solution.
You went to MIT.
I got in. I didn't actually go.
Okay.
Okay, hydrogen cyanide.
Emphasis on hydrogen.
It's, it's flammable.
Think the Hindenburg.
Not a comforting thought.
The point is, you can ignite it.
The flames will burn off
the cyanide.
- Okay, copy.
- Only problem is,
hydrogen will only burn
at six percent saturation.
For those of us
who didn't get into MIT.
You got to let the gas
fill the room first.
We're not gonna last that long.
We got to try, Kate.
You're only at three percent.
Okay, you got to hang in there.
We need to stay low
to the ground.
- Get away from me.
- Come on.
That symbol
took everything from me.
It's not gonna be
the last thing I see.
Stay with me. Stay awake.
Come on, Commander. Talk to me.
Tell me all the reasons
you hate Batman.
That symbol let my family die.
Four percent.
Hey, if you're gonna
hate the symbol,
hate the symbol. Okay?
Let it fuel you
into staying alive.
Five percent.
I have to blame that symbol.
If I don't...
If you don't, what? Tell me.
I have to blame myself.
Six percent. Do it.
Kate, come on. Talk to me.
Commander. Commander.
We're okay.
Never let it be said
that Gotham's Gadfly
does not give credit
where credit is due.
Batwoman got this one right
and the rest of us whiffed.
Guess Jacob Kane
won't be the only one
eating a little crow.
Boxer Chris "The Fist" Medlock
was not only cleared
in the Executioner murders,
but also exonerated
of his past murder conviction.
Talk about a one-two punch.
Not so good news for the man
who convicted him,
Judge Raymond Calverick.
The DA has vowed to reopen
all cases tainted
by this extra-legal cabal,
including deceased
Detective Stu Donnelly
and Prosecutor Angus Stanton.
You're right behind me,
aren't you?
Where is she?
I... You... you know, she just left.
- How can I put this?
- You let her escape.
I know you said to hold on to her.
But my stepdad is her boss,
and I'm running a little short
on family right now.
Not that you asked
about my personal life,
but it's a mess.
The last thing I need
is him shutting down
the one good thing I have
going on...
Thank you for saving her life.
Yeah. It's not a big thing.
Hey, FYI, she knows who you are.
Hey, chill, she didn't tell me.
But I got the distinct impression
that she's gonna tell my stepdad,
so good luck with that.
Well, Bruce, now I know
how much it must have sucked
hearing your Uncle blame you
for what happened on the bridge.
But he had to blame someone.
Seeing him fight so hard
to avoid the truth
that was right in front of him,
made me realize
I was doing the same thing.
I've been blaming my dad
for not saving Beth that day.
But it wasn't his hand on that door.
Only inches away from her.
He wasn't the one who crossed
that house off the list of places
where Beth could be.
I don't know how,
but we are gonna get Beth back.
And this time, I swear to you,
I won't ever give up.
I don't know if forgiving my father
will help me forgive myself,
but I have to try.
I thought I might find you here.
How could you ever think
I was trying to replace you,
little Mouse?
Why are you so determined
to protect her?
Because I'm saving her a seat
at our tea party!
It was supposed to be
a table for two.
Yes.
The two of us.
Two halves of one whole.
Just as Kate and I are two halves.
And I need your help
to make us whole.
I can't do this without you.
I don't want to share you with her.
Mouse.
You won't have to share me.
Because we'll be sharing her.
And what if she doesn't want
to play?
Well...
Then it's good we have that then.
Trade you Mr. Pandy for it.
You kept it?
To remind me of you.