Previously on Batwoman...
Kate, it's Mary. Sophie's missing.
- Kate.
- Hey, Dad.
- We're gonna find her.
- Then let me help.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm Alice.
Bruce never stopped looking
for your sister's body.
Guy had the best tech on the planet.
Why didn't he find her?
Pick one, Commander.
Sophie or Gotham.
Why are you doing this?
- I am not used to being found.
- Clever girl.
Let's take a picture, Beth.
Make sure our necklaces are in it.
Beth.
Mom! Mom, wake up!
- Tell me something, Bruce.
- Mom!
- What's the difference between...
- Beth, please! Grab my hand!
- being hopeful and being crazy?
- Kate!
Because whatever it is
got me through that day
and the years that followed.
Mom! Beth!
Beth wasn't found in the car
with my mom,
and as long as there wasn't a body,
there was hope.
The entire city went out
looking that first night.
But days went by, and then
weeks, and then months,
and eventually,
it was just my dad and me.
- Beth!
A decade and a half later
and my dad and I are still looking,
but while I'm looking for my sister,
my dad is looking
for someone else entirely.
Alice is a lunatic,
Dodgson a traitor.
Former Crow turned Wonderland Gang
second in command.
Together, they want to terrorize
the citizens of Gotham
by undermining the people
actually protecting them, us.
I want them stopped, dead or alive.
Wait.
- Let's go.
- Yeah, let's bounce.
Cool.
Where's Alice?
What the hell is that?
My dad would never believe
my theory that Alice was Beth,
but I didn't have a choice.
I had to make him understand
before the Crows killed her first.
Three hours later?
Where the hell were you?
Around.
Did anyone see you?
Bystanders, police,
cameras, cell phones?
Seriously, Kate,
you can't be going out
in Gotham every night
pretending to be Batman.
I need to find her.
If Alice is my sister,
I need to know.
Good morning, Gotham.
Your bestie, Vesper Fairchild, here.
On a normal Tuesday,
I'd want to know who wore who
to last night's Gotham Gala,
who got drunk, who got clawed,
but Batman fever is upon us, people.
It has been four days
since we saw him
soaring through the sky.
And it's still all anyone
can tweet about.
Is Batman finally back
after a three-year hiatus?
- Talk to me, Gotham.
- I think it's him.
If you look at that picture
they have in the paper,
it's his cape. It's iconic.
Heard Alice's gang firebombed
a Crows truck last night.
Batman picked a good time
to come home.
In my search for Alice,
something else happened.
A city divided by walls,
money, and bad luck
rallied around a single hope,
Bruce, you.
Except I was too busy to notice.
I don't like their market
response to the AR.
Let's pull out and see if we can
spark interest in Dubai.
Do you see this baby turtle
eating this strawberry?
It's so cute, I want one.
- Morning, everyone.
- Morning.
Herd the Crows killed a lead
on Alice last night.
Maybe if you reconsidered
my offer to join my team,
you could help us with that.
The Crows aren't really
a good fit for me right now.
- Because of Sophie?
- Oh, my gosh.
Can we talk about the fact
that she's married to a man?
Let's not.
I'm not trying to label her
or anything,
but what's her deal exactly?
- She's married, honey. Drop it.
- Yeah.
I get that, but she could
still be bi, bi-curious,
- pan, poly, omni...
- I think Alice is Beth.
Well...
Kate, what are you talking about?
That's ridiculous.
I thought they found her body.
They found bone fragments.
Skull fragments matching Beth's DNA.
I was able to get one
of Alice's knives.
It has a garnet stone,
our birth stone.
If we can test the knife
for DNA...
Kate, listen to yourself.
She has a vendetta against you.
Why?
Why not kill me
when she had the chance,
and why does she seem to know
everything about me?
I know that you want to believe
that Beth is alive.
I do too, but facts are facts.
Beth's dead.
Katie, Alice kidnapped Sophie.
She drove a bomb
into a park full of families.
She killed two police officers
in cold blood.
How on earth could she be Beth?
Alice is Beth,
and I'll prove it to you.
Such a lovely home.
So nice of you to let us stay.
Is the pleasure
of making a daisy chain
worth the trouble of getting up
and picking the daisies?
We're all thinking it.
You should give up, Alice.
Simon's dead, Gus is in the wind,
and we're all scampering
about from hole to hole,
trying to avoid getting
snatched up by our tails.
But we're still poor, are we not?
We're still vulnerable, are we not?
And they are still rich and powerful
and protected by the Crows.
Bullies paid for by richer bullies
all with the goal of sweeping us
into the shadows to be forgotten.
Jacob Kane is not man enough
to protect this city
because he's a quitter,
and when things get difficult,
he gives up.
I think it's time for Gotham to watch
Commander Crow squirm.
Yeah!
Tell me you found my favorite knife.
- No luck.
- What the hell did I do with it?
It is so much more fun
unveiling my evil plan
when I can flip it about for cadence.
And how does Kate Kane
fit into that evil plan?
Now, you are so cute
when you're jealous.
I want to make sure we stay on point.
Uproot the city's confidence
in the Crows,
let chaos reign.
It's so boring when he says it.
You're making this personal, Alice.
It is personal.
My father gave up on me,
and I want to make him suffer
the way that I did
by stripping away everything
that he cares about
until he's all alone.
Where is my damn knife?
Mom! Beth!
Beth!
Hey, kiddo, you're okay.
I'm right here.
Same one?
You...
You know, you have a bed.
I need to stay out here
in case she calls.
Dad?
Do you promise
we'll never stop looking for her?
I promise.
Got your text.
Yes, technically,
Wayne is in possession
of a thermal cycler and PCR mixers.
- PCR?
- Polymerase chain reaction.
It's used to separate
and amplify DNA,
which then needs to be analyzed
against another sample for a match.
So, if I could provide you
with another sample...
Sorry, I just keep the doors
locked and the lights on.
For Bruce Wayne, who isn't here.
Currently, but not ultimately,
which is why we need to talk
about his suit.
Are you watching the news?
The city is clamoring
for a hero that isn't here,
and I know you don't want
to be the city's next great hope,
but it's too late
because they think you're him.
I need that suit to stop Alice.
My cousin figured it out years ago.
Be more terrifying than your enemy.
Do you know what this is?
A Bat-weapon.
Laser saw.
This thing will cut through anything.
Cool.
- What about this?
- Gas mask?
Rebreather.
To breathe underwater without a tank.
See, these aren't toys.
These are one-of-a-kind
dangerous tools
which even I don't know how to use.
I don't how to use half
the stuff in here
because it's not meant for me.
It's meant for Batman.
You know who you sound like?
- I'm sure you'll tell me.
- Lucius Fox.
Trust me, I am a far cry
from my father.
Oh, I know.
He was actually useful.
That's funny.
"Define the goal,
define the objective,
define the terms of victory."
Your dad made those
for the office.
Now, imagine him teaching you
how to play T-ball.
Is this you?
What? This? This dude in the picture?
The person in this picture
dressed as Batman
who saved my life the other night.
- Was that you?
- Anyone who knows me
knows I hate Batman.
So does your dad,
which would make putting on this suit
an incredibly reckless move.
Wasn't me.
Besides, if I were gonna save you
in a dramatic fashion,
I would totally dress
as Wonder Woman.
Can we go somewhere private?
I need you to run that for DNA.
Alice tried to kill me.
She put me on a plank
20 stories in the air
and watched it drop.
She's sick.
She's a monster, Kate.
She's not your twin.
If I can get her DNA off the knife,
I can compare it with my own.
Look.
I know why you want Beth to be alive,
but aren't you getting
your hopes up over nothing?
Maybe.
But you know me and hope.
Your dad would kill me.
I can't.
You know, if...
If I'd known
you were getting married,
I would have come back sooner.
I didn't think
weddings were your thing.
Not to go. To stop it.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Got it. Got it. Go, go, go!
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
Are you though?
Not really.
This is exactly
what I was worried about.
You put yourself directly
in Alice's crosshairs,
and you brought her
right to our doorstep.
How the hell did she even know
I had her knife?
Are you hearing yourself?
Talk some sense into her, please.
All due respect, sir,
I don't see any harm
in running a DNA test on Alice
if we can catch her.
My daughter died.
I have the lab results that prove it.
Alice, that thing, is a cop killer
who drove enough C-4
into Robinson Park
to level a square block.
I am not saying
Alice is a good person.
All I'm saying is
it has been 15 years.
We don't know what happened to her.
What if somewhere deep down
inside of her
she is actually Beth?
The GCPD just gave us
the green light to put her down.
- I'm not wasting the shot.
- Excuse me, sir.
Update on the missing rabbit
from last night.
Traced him into Tricorner,
found a blood trail,
then it disappeared
somewhere around Bennett Ave.
What are you doing here?
Is there a password or something?
Get in.
It goes without saying,
but this clinic breaks
no less than ten laws an hour,
and considering that
your dad runs the Crows...
- Not planning to tell him.
- Good,
because it's hard enough
balancing this with med school,
and I can't exactly protest
Gotham's failing healthcare system
from the inside of a prison cell.
What's your stance on
doctor-patient confidentiality?
Came in this morning,
bleeding pretty bad.
Won't say anything, not unusual,
but then, look at what I pulled
out of his scapula.
He's a Batman victim.
I'm so keeping this, FYI.
He's one of Alice's guys.
- I saw it on the news.
- Good to know.
Actually, I'm really glad
that you're here.
I was thinking that we haven't
really had any sister time
since you've been back,
and I was just reading about
this brand-new plant-based cafe
that is so organic,
your fork literally dissolves
in your hand
if you don't eat fast enough.
- Sounds good.
- Oh, cool. Okay.
So, see you back here at seven?
Not sure that's a good idea
considering
he's a domestic terrorist.
I need you to send a message
to Alice from Kate Kane.
Waffles. Now, get out of here.
Waffles?
If Alice is Beth,
she'll know what it means.
What does it mean?
It's better if you don't know.
See you at 7.00.
Surveillance narrows them
to the Kubert District.
Caught Dodgson in alley
about three hours ago.
The rabbit we shot last night
was seen at a C Store earlier
just a few blocks away.
Must be hovering around there.
In a suburban, white
picket-fence neighborhood?
Not really the MO of a gang
who hides in the shadows.
I know where they are.
Get every available man
to 1472 Norman Drive, now.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir?
We're wasting time.
- Hey, I can't really talk.
- Then just say yes.
I need you to buy me some time
while I find Alice.
Kate, it's too late.
I just need you to stall
the Crows for a couple of hours.
Kate, I'm not helping you
if I don't know what you did.
I got her a message.
I asked her to meet
at our favorite place,
and if she's really Beth,
she'll know what it means.
The waffle stand.
- You remembered.
- You know how dangerous she is.
Don't do this.
My dad is going to kill
my sister, Sophie.
Please just...
Buy me some time
so I can prove him wrong.
Oh, come on. Hey, hey.
Why are you doing that?
What are you doing, Luke?
It's not a toy.
Stop.
Please just...
I did not mean to...
Okay.
What, you don't like chocolate
all of a sudden?
I'm not hungry.
Come on.
You're the world record holder
for fastest waffle consumption.
Title's in jeopardy.
We shouldn't be eating.
We should be looking for Beth.
Been looking for months.
We deserve a sugar break.
It was my fault.
Hey.
Hey, why would you say that?
You weren't there, Dad.
After we crashed,
Beth went to check on Mom
in the front seat.
Instead of helping, I climbed out.
I left her.
You were being safe.
But I could have grabbed her,
but I was too scared
if my feet left the ground,
I'd go over, too.
I should have just climbed
on the car and grabbed her.
She was my sister.
Why didn't I try a little harder?
Come here. Come here.
You're okay.
Go, go, go!
Oh, my God!
They're gone, sir.
TV dinner's still in the microwave.
Damn it.
How did you know she was here?
Beth grew up here.
This was our old house.
- Sir, you don't think...
- Of course not.
She's trying to get in my head.
It's not gonna work.
Well, look who finally
figured it out.
Are you my sister?
Who in the world am I?
Now, that is the great puzzle,
isn't it?
Did you know I was gonna have
your knife tested for DNA?
You had my knife?
And here I've been going around
using this charmless contraption.
You didn't have your guys jump me.
Jump you?
Kate, we're sisters.
Prove it.
Let me test your DNA
before the Crows kill you.
I already proved it.
I'm here.
I knew the password.
"Waffles."
Our favorite spot.
We used to come here
after school on Fridays
and gorge our faces
in chocolate-covered garbage.
How else would I know that?
Unless...
Oh, dear.
Did the press mention that
you and Beth used to come here
as part of your
silly little tradition,
and did I read
an old article online?
- Sir.
- We're going to Tricorner.
They just left can't be too far.
Sir, she's not in Tricorner.
I want checkpoints
on all the bridges.
Sir?
I know where she is.
They found skull fragments.
They declared you dead.
Then why are you still here?
If I were really your twin,
wouldn't you feel something?
How did you survive the crash?
Crash. The crash.
Oh, yes, the crash.
Let's see. We hit the water
with a dramatic splash.
When I opened my eyes,
my mother's head was on
the other side of the windshield.
A surreal sight, a motherless head.
Poor Gabi, or was it Abby?
Nevertheless, it was cold.
Have you ever had a tea party
on the inside of a block of ice?
It's much akin to that.
Water rushed through
every seam of the car
up to my knees
and then to my neck.
I didn't know whether to hold
my breath or to scream,
but as I tilted my head
like a little mouse,
sucking in the increasingly
shrinking bubble of air,
one thought kept me calm.
"Surely, someone will come
and save me."
Feel free to get that.
What's wrong?
No interest in painting your nails,
gossiping about boys?
We have a lot to catch up on.
I'd rather not.
I came here tonight
to ask you one simple question.
After I disappeared,
when did you sleep through the night
for the very first time?
I haven't yet.
Sure you have.
I never moved on.
Why is that?
Because I never gave up hope
that I would find you.
And why is that?
Because I should have been with you.
Here's my DNA, dear.
Go prove it to Daddy.
Target green. I have a clear shot.
- Tattletale.
- Wait...
Get out of the way, Kate.
Tell your men to stand down.
Kate, she's in your head.
Then arrest her and get her help.
She's got a knife.
Drop it, or they will shoot you
and call it self-defense.
- Not if you stay put.
- Get out of the way.
Get out of the way.
She's your daughter,
and if you kill her,
you won't just lose Beth,
you'll lose me, too.
Take her to Arkham.
Kate.
Kate, hang on.
And here I thought
you could keep a secret.
I didn't tell them you'd be here.
"Tell us a story,"
said the march hare.
"Yes, please do," pled Alice,
and so the dormouse began,
"Once upon a time,
there were three little sisters."
What did you do?
You don't remember why we'd
each have to get our own waffle
when we came here?
- Because you don't like to share.
- Exactly.
And you are my sister, Kate.
No.
Hey, so not to rush you,
but I made 7.00pm rezzies,
and it's 7.45pm,
and I had to call in
a favor for these.
So, yeah, okay.
Call me...bye.
Wonderful.
Oh, my God. What are you doing?
Alice doesn't like competition.
Psycho!
All right.
I got you.
Will impact his future.
We have an update on the ongoing
Wonderland Gang story.
Let's go to our eye-in-the-sky
reporter for more.
This is News Eight Gotham
in the sky with breaking news.
Is the city's nightmare finally over?
Alice, the leader
of the Wonderland Gang,
has been captured.
The Crows apprehended
the notorious killer
minutes ago in Burnside Park.
Now, as you can see, we're live.
We're following
the prison transport to Arkham,
where... Wait...wait. What was that?
What just happened?
The van has exploded...
Kate, can you hear me?
Batcave to Kate.
You're still five minutes out.
I can make it.
Tell me you realize
that place is crawling with cops.
- Go, go, go!
- If you see her, shoot!
Maybe it was fate,
watching her drown in a river
the way everyone assumed
she had years ago.
And maybe I was meant to stand by
and watch it all happen
all over again.
After all, my dad was right.
Alice was a monster.
She was a liar, a manipulator,
a killer, but despite all that...
She was still my sister.
Grab my hand! Grab my hand!
Hey. Batcave to Kate.
Batcave to Kate.
Kate, are you okay?
Wake up, Kate.
River's down here.
Hey. Batcave to Kate.
You got a lot of cops
coming towards you right now.
You need to get up now.
Kate!
I know there's a defibrillator
on the suit.
Nothing here, nothing.
Okay, people. Time to get real.
Massive explosion
on the Loeb Bridge last night.
The leader
of the Alice in Wonderland Gang
is in the wind,
and Batman was not there.
Was there a cowl convention
we didn't know about?
Was it Robin's
high school graduation?
Talk to me, Gotham.
Did we put our hope in a ghost?
I just came to apologize
for missing dinner,
but apparently,
I missed something else.
Sorry.
So, okay.
Look. I get the whole
needing to know with Alice
because she's your sister,
and duh, sisters.
But her boyfriend
tried to kill me last night
because apparently,
she sees me as her replacement.
Which, under normal circumstances,
could, you know,
maybe be borderline flattering.
Except here, it's just ironic,
considering the most sisterly thing
that you've ever done for me
is pretty much
act like I don't exist.
Mary, it's not like that.
Look, don't worry.
You know, he took off and got scared
before doing any permanent damage,
and, no, I didn't tell your dad.
The last thing I need is my own
personal security detail.
Mary, I am so sorry.
Is Alice worth it?
Because if she is,
could you just tell her
that I'm not a threat, please?
How the hell did someone
get a bomb on that bridge?
There is something else
going on here,
and between the Crows
and the GCPD,
it needs to start making sense.
Get out!
I take it I'm next.
That stunt you pulled,
it's called aiding and abetting.
You crossed the line.
And you're about to kill
your own daughter.
Now, you tell me again
how my daughter did this.
She went into the house
where you grew up.
She murdered the current owners
by slitting open their throats.
She's not Beth, Kate.
Drop it, now.
Or I'll have you arrested myself.
Dad?
Hey, kiddo.
Come here.
Catherine Hamilton's
investigators found
bones on Miller Farm.
- No.
- Skull fragments
of a little girl.
They...
They had them tested,
and it's her, Kate.
It's Beth.
No, Dad. I checked Miller Farm
a million times.
Kate, they found her.
See? There's nothing there, Dad.
I would have seen it. I looked!
It's time to say goodbye, Kate.
You said you'd never give up!
- Kate.
- You're a traitor!
Kate.
She could have killed you.
You totally sold me out.
- It's called caring about you.
- If you cared,
you wouldn't have lied to an
entire military academy about me.
That's not fair, Kate.
So, you didn't lie?
I would never lie to you.
I won't ever lie to you.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Yes or ish?
I'm happy, Kate, and...
There is no us, okay?
You need to move on.
Did you get the suit wet?
Okay, so I couldn't find
the auto-dry function.
Yeah, because that's not a thing.
10.8 million dollar suit.
Kind of feels like an oversight.
Just saying.
Hey.
Thank you for bailing me out.
Yeah, I mean, I found the comms,
and I saw you hadn't moved in
a while, and I figured maybe...
- Let's not get misty-eyed.
- Yep, no problem.
No problem.
Alice said her thugs didn't jump me,
which means there is someone else
who doesn't want me knowing the truth
about the DNA on the knife.
Yeah.
Well, just so you know,
while you're figuring that out,
you're getting a whole lot
of people excited over nothing.
Get rid of it.
It'll be melted it
into a paperweight.
Destroy the masks while you're at it.
I'll take care of whatever
surveillance was in the garage.
Like it never happened.
Luke was right, Bruce.
Gotham needed
something to believe in.
They wanted hope
just as I started to lose mine.
I spent half my life
looking for my sister,
and today, I found someone else,
someone I didn't know or recognize.
For the first time in 15 years,
I felt something other than hope.
I felt doubt.
You're gonna tell me
everything you know about Alice.
Thought you were Batman.
You wish.
It may have taken you years,
sweet, darling Kate,
but you found me eventually...
Even if I'm not the girl
you expected me to be.
I had my secrets
just as you have yours,
but do be careful, my dear sister.
Putting on that suit
and all the darkness
that comes with it...
Makes you just as crazy as me.