Previously on Batwoman...
I lost my sister, Beth.
Remember her?
Beth has gone down, down,
down the rabbit hole,
and she's never coming back.
Alice is looking for a "Mouse"?
She has big plans for him.
- What in?
- Chipped him.
He leads me to Alice,
I figure it out who Mouse is.
I never understood
why you stopped looking for me.
I always thought a father would
do anything to find his daughter.
I won't let you forget me,
Commander, not again.
You'd think having spent
nine months
in our mother's womb together
and every other day for 13 years,
we wouldn't be such
great mysteries to one another.
But we are.
I don't know
what the rest of her story is...
But that's the puzzle
I'm determined to solve.
Before it's too late.
They're calling him
the "Skin Pirate"
because apparently
he likes to take skin
- from the booty.
- Never say that again.
I didn't write the article. Point
being, whatever they're calling him,
he has quite the work ethic.
He hit three morgues in one night.
All three break-ins
were nine minutes apart.
That's a pretty tight window.
Yeah. Calculating the quickest
route between them.
Can you get eyes on that?
Looks like our he is a she.
Does she look familiar to you?
- Is that Alice?
- No.
- You sure about that?
- Hang on.
She's not the Skin Pirate, okay?
It's too sick. Even for her
Let's not forget we have access
to something that GCPD doesn't.
Wayne's closed circuit cameras.
There aren't many, but let's see
if they caught anything.
Yeah. Yeah, that's her.
I'll look into whatever the hell
she could be using the skin for
if you remind me to clear
my image search history.
- What are you doing?
- Stopping her.
Whatever she's got plan
for Gotham ends today.
You don't even know where she is.
No. But I put a tracker in Dodgson.
I know where he is and she likes
to keep her toys close.
Bruce doesn't have
night vision goggles?
Batman doesn't do goggles.
Forgetting pain is convenient.
Remembering it, agonizing.
But recovering the truth
is worth the suffering.
Now, tell me the truth.
What did you reveal to her?
Nothing. I wouldn't betray you.
Good.
Because if you ruin
all I have been working for
Off. With. Your. Head.
It looks like my dear sister
wasn't very kind to you, was she?
It's only a matter of time
before she gets hers.
I'm not afraid of the dark.
I'm not afraid of you.
Show yourself.
Kinky, even for you.
Stealing skin off corpses?
Sadistic even for you.
Key word, corpses.
I didn't hurt anyone.
What's the skin for?
You hit three morgues
in one night.
You're working on something.
Dodgson said you had plans
with a "Mouse".
Oh, I'm sure he said
lots of silly things
when your attention-starved
step-sister illegally drugged him
Is Mouse a real person
or a figment of your imagination?
And what are you two planning?
If you keep going down this road,
it's going to end badly.
But it doesn't have to.
I can get you into
a rehabilitation hospital.
A real one, Beth.
Nice try, but Alice will do.
You're gonna have to give me
something.
Mouse is the one who found me
after the crash.
You do remember the crash?
- What happened to you?
- Aren't you the great detective?
Figure it out.
- What are you doing?
- Calling Dad.
Just telling him know I'm with you.
But he'll track your phone.
And if he finds us
he'll ruin all our fun.
And he'll send you
straight to Arkham.
- Kate?
- Hi, Dad. I'm with Alice.
What do you mean you're with Alice?
I have her.
Where are you? I'll send a team.
I'm fine. She's contained.
- I just thought you should know.
- Kate.
Clock's ticking. Start talking.
Fine. But I'll have to show you.
Show me? I don't think so.
The clock's tick, tick, ticking.
Let me down and I'll tell you
all about my long, sad tale.
So where to begin?
I suppose it started...
14 months before Catherine
Hamilton faked my death.
What are you talking about?
No one told you. That is so them.
Those bones, they belonged to a deer.
Our stepmother
faked my DNA results
and Daddy just found out
he had a funeral for Bambi.
I wonder if they have a prenup.
The bones at Miller Farm.
You don't seem that surprised.
Is that because deep down
you always knew
those bones weren't mine?
And now you know why.
Am I supposed to turn
at somewhere?
You're not asking
the right questions, Kate.
What is my evil plan?
Who am I targeting next?
How am I going to do it?
When you really need to be
asking, why?
Why am I like this?
Okay, why?
Oh, you don't wanna know that.
I have waited 15 years to hear it.
Well, it all began
with an unfortunate event
of which I remember vividly.
And if given the chance again,
I will take it back in a heartbeat.
It was a simple, effortless thing
that I had done so many times before.
I woke up.
Dad? She woke up.
Oh, hi.
You must be terrified.
What's your name?
Beth. Where am I?
Hello, Beth. You're okay.
My son Johnny and I
were fishing in the river
and we saw you along the rocks.
- Any idea how you got there?
- Where's my mom?
Well, the police will be here soon.
I'm sure they can call her.
No, she was in the car with me.
She needs help.
It's going to be okay.
- All right? Are you hungry?
- I want my dad.
I'll make you a sandwich.
The little boy just sat there
with his hair in his eyes,
playing with his trucks.
For him, it was an ordinary day.
But for me, it was
the first worst day of my life.
- What's the man's name?
- Oh, I have no idea.
What do you mean you have no idea?
He rescued you.
It'll make more sense when we arrive.
Go down the road a mile,
take a right.
Go two miles
and there's a roadside dinner.
Consider it your first stop
down the rabbit hole.
It doesn't make sense.
Why would she call you
and not tell you where she was?
No idea.
She knows I'll trace the call.
Maybe that was her intention.
We should get a team together.
No. No.
For now, it's just you and me.
Sir, it's Alice.
I don't need to read you her resume.
And I don't need another stand-off
like we had in Burnside Park.
Found her, she's heading west
on the interstate.
Let's go.
I don't get it.
How could they mix up
animal bones and human ones?
I mean the bone density alone
should've tipped them off.
Not to mention the fact
the genome are...
Because it wasn't a mix up.
It was a lie.
Are you covering up
for the lab's mistake?
Mom, you don't have to do that.
Okay, you can just
tell me the truth. We can...
I am. I was trying to give Jacob
and Kate closure.
No, you wouldn't do that
because that would be,
that would be horrible.
I am so sorry, Mary.
But I wanted you to hear it
from me.
Not from Jacob or Kate. From me.
I know you, okay? I know you.
So please tell me you didn't do this.
- Two beers, please.
- None for me.
You do not want to be sober
for the remainder of the story.
Trust me.
Just the one beer.
Right back with that.
We're here. Talk.
And what does this place
have to do with anything?
Well, when your life unfolds
into a nightmare,
you pray your dreams
will take you elsewhere.
I used to dream of running away
with you to a place like this.
And then my hunger would wake me.
Alas, it wasn't to meant be.
This would be entirely easier
with two free hands.
You're my sister, Alice.
We spent half our lives together.
Where did that person go?
Down, down, down the rabbit hole.
Look, I'm done messing around.
If you're gonna talk, talk.
If not, we will just sit here
and wait for Dad to find us.
As I was saying, I remember it
like it was yesterday.
The toys. The books. The treats.
Upstairs, there was a room
like a child's wonderland.
It was Mouse's room.
Goonies never say die!
He went by Johnny then.
It's leviosa, not leviosar.
I can do any voice I hear.
You kids want lemonade?
Why do you cover your face
like that?
To hide what happened
in the accident.
You shouldn't have to hide
who you are.
- I'll scare people.
- You don't scare me.
We interrupt this program
with breaking news.
Police announced earlier that
they've expanded their search
for the missing Kane girl
to the county of Bludhaven.
Wait, your dad said
he called the police,
why don't they know I'm here?
The family says a reward
is being offered for any tips...
Johnny, no more TV today.
They're looking for me.
We have to call the police.
I told you, Beth,
they'll be here soon.
We don't want you to leave us.
- Please let me go!
- Dad!
- You're hurting me! Let me go!
- Stay here!
- Please! Let me go!
- Dad!
Let me go!
Stop it, please. Aw! Stop, please.
Let me go for now, please.
No, no! Let me out!
No. Let me out!
And that was just the first day.
I think she'll take that drink now.
Kate? Kate, I need to talk to you!
- Okay? I hate her too! Kate?
- Here she is.
Wouldn't stop trying to buzz in,
insisting she's related to Miss Kane.
- I am.
- And...
I'll take it from here. Thanks, Carl.
Can I help you?
Possibly to an AA meeting?
That depends. Is your name Kate?
Most definitely not.
Then can you tell her that I'm here?
I'm sorry, who's here?
Mary. Kate's soon-to-be
ex-stepsister.
- And you are?
- Luke.
Kate's associate
assistant, real estate person.
Look, Kate's not here.
You know what,
you could leave her a message.
Okay.
Tell her...
that I'm so sorry I was ever born
from the wicked witch of Gotham.
And I get why she's avoiding me,
but I'm totally on her side.
I can't believe that my mom
would ever do something so awful.
Oh, my god.
Do you think that she killed
that deer too?
Are you getting any of this?
All I heard was that your mom may
or may not have killed a deer.
It's probably best that I start
from the beginning.
Sir, I know this is completely
inappropriate for a subordinate
to ask her commander.
But are you okay?
Catherine and I are going through
a rough patch.
Copy that, sir. My apologies.
I was under the impression
that it had something
- to do with Alice.
- As it turns out, it does.
Catherine paid the DNA analyst
to say the skull fragments found
were Beth's.
And they weren't?
And I just confirmed
she was responsible
for the bomb in the lower bridge,
targeting Alice.
Damn.
So Kate was right this whole time.
We don't know what's right.
The only way to settle this
for good is to catch Alice,
run her DNA and...
And let science tell us the truth.
Kate's signal stopped moving.
Looks like they're at some place
called Dusty's.
- So good. Sure you don't wanna...
- Why?
I think the beef is grass-fed.
Why was there a face in the sink?
- Oh, that.
- I'm serious, Alice.
You survive a crash,
wash up on shore,
some Hannibal Lector finds you,
keeps you as his prisoner.
Did he wanna kill you?
Skin you? What?
I wasn't a prisoner.
Then what were you?
I was a friend.
Friend, I've learned,
takes on a different meaning,
depending on who you ask.
Socialization is essential
to one's development.
It's as important as food,
water, and shelter.
It allows one to develop
a sense of self.
A sense of purpose.
What is that?
A little experiment.
You see...
My dear son
didn't get the opportunity
to develop a sense of purpose
because the world
made him an outcast.
They called him a monster.
He waited a very long time
for someone like you.
I just wanna go home.
This is your home now.
I want my dad.
Don't cry.
You'll get used to it here.
Dad! Dad! Daddy!
Little Johnny
didn't have any friends...
And then I came along.
- What was he using the skin for?
- Experiments.
Trying to hide Mouse's hideous face.
He thought he could find a way
to make him look normal.
The ridicule would end,
and he'd live happily ever after.
So the skin at the morgue...
What were you...
What am I what, Kate?
Go on. Speak up.
Oh, no, don't tell me
you're a lightweight.
What's wrong, dear sister?
What did you do to me?
Come out, come out, Commander.
Dodgson.
There's a propane tank on the east.
I'll distract them.
Keep your asses on the ground.
Where's my daughter? Where is she?
Which one?
What the hell happened to you?
You happened, Commander.
I joined the Crows
to make Gotham better.
But you divided it.
The city's not safe,
the wealthy are safe.
And you're too blind to see it.
Just like you're too blind
to see your own daughter.
Sir.
Sir! Sir! Stop, Sir.
Commander, come on.
Didn't have to be this way,
Commander.
You could've saved her.
I mean, god.
Kate knew this whole time
that Beth was alive.
You know, that celestial
sisterly bond is real, man.
Actually, that's really heavy.
Wow, that just made me dizzy.
- Let me call you a car.
- To take me where?
The penthouse built on lies
of falsely dead children?
Hard pass.
Look, I get that you're going
through a lot right now,
but Kate is obviously not here,
and I'm really trying to work.
Seriously, Luke,
I am going through a major family
crisis here, okay?
I don't even know
who my own mom is anymore.
I just found out
I have a second step-sister.
Kate found her actual full sister.
Oh, my god. Wait.
- Is Kate with Alice right now?
- If I say "yes", will you leave?
Here I am at the literal lowest
point that I have ever been
Kate decides to choose today,
of all days,
to go out for some sisterly bonding
with a cold blooded killer?
Meanwhile, how many
people have I murdered?
- What?
- Guess.
How many people have I killed?
It's between zero and why are you
even hesitating right now?
Zero. I killed zero people.
I'm the good sister.
You found the tracker, didn't you?
- You knew I'd come for you.
- Yes, I found the tracker.
I knew a few morgue thefts
would stir you into action,
arranged for a friend
to drug your drink,
and now I've taken you
out of the equation.
You see, my dearest Mouse and I
were cooking up a little
something special for Gotham,
and it will undoubtedly
go down more smoothly
without a bat in the broth.
Let me go, Alice.
But we haven't gotten to
the best part of the story yet.
Alas, after weeks
and weeks in captivity,...
Like a little rabbit
down a hole so small...
I finally managed
to claw my way out.
It's curious,
but there are so many
out of the way things
that when one becomes desperate,
present themselves.
I found one such opportunity
in a rusty little friend.
Oh, dear, oh, dear,
my poor delicate fingers.
But success,
I eventually did make mine.
- Hello?
- Daddy, it's me, Beth.
You have to help.
Beth? Oh, my god, Beth.
Where are you?
If anyone comes looking for you,
I will kill them.
And it will be all your fault.
Do you understand me?
I remember that call.
My first and last chance at freedom.
Dad had it traced.
After all that time,
there were so many false leads.
The GCPD didn't believe us,
said they'd already searched
these areas several times.
But we were here within an hour.
You stay here.
Where is she?
Mr. Kane, there's been
a terrible misunderstanding...
- Where is my daughter?
- Sir, please allow me to explain.
My daughter Beth called me
not one hour ago from this house.
She said "help", clear as can be.
It was all an insensitive prank.
I'm... I'm... I'm so embarrassed.
I do...
Mr. Kane, your daughter
is not in there.
Beth? Beth?
Beth?
Beth, are you in here?
Mr. Kane, like I said, it was my son.
He has an ability.
I guess you'd say for mimicry.
Johnny, please show him
what you did.
I don't want to.
- Show him what you did.
- I said I don't want to.
Show him!
Hi, Daddy. It's me, Beth.
I learned a new song on my cello
that I can play
on the first night of Hanukkah.
Here, let me show you.
That's impossible.
How do you know
what her voice sounds like?
He saw a home video clip
on the nightly news.
He's been obsessed
with her disappearance
since it happened.
If anyone comes looking for you,
I will kill them.
Beth?
I was there.
He told me if I made a peep...
That he'd kill you both.
So I just waited.
I waited for you to feel it,
to know, to sense.
But alas, nothing.
I guess what they say
about twins being connected
that profound, soulful,
magical tie, is just fantasy!
The thing you dream about
before your hunger wakes you up.
I've lost Kate's location, Sir.
She must have turned off her phone.
- Sir?
- I've been out there before.
Fifteen years ago.
Sir, what's happening?
I know where they are.
Hi, Kate. Me again.
Fifth time now, actually.
Still got that big showing
with that big buyer.
Urgent, real urgent.
I need you to call me back asap.
Hey, hey!
Wow, what the hell is this?
Alice hit up three morgues
last night.
Stole flesh from a bunch
of dead bodies.
Oh, my god. Alice is the skin pirate?
- Of course she is.
- I know, I know.
You've skinned zero corpses.
Well, I haven't.
Is it disgusting
that this is making me
really hungry for pizza?
Yes, that is absolutely disgusting.
Here check this out,
I found something.
Two weeks ago, a guy
named Jonathan Cartwright,
who admitted to having
a similar hobby
of stealing skin from dead people,
- escaped in the Arkham breakout.
- What Arkham breakout?
There was a breakout at Arkham.
I'm pretty sure, I would have
heard about something like that.
But you didn't, so...
So Arkham officials
covered it up. Comforting.
Do you think this creep
has something to do with Alice?
I think the timing
feels incredibly suspicious.
I got the front, you take the back.
Sir, a couple of shacks in the back.
- Checking them out.
- Copy that.
Hi, Daddy.
Where's Kate?
"Where's Kate?"
"Is Kate okay?" "Is Kate happy?"
"Is she sleeping enough?"
"Did she done her homework?"
"Seen a doctor?"
"Had enough to eat."
Kate. Kate. Kate. Kate. Kate.
I'm so sick of Kate.
What are you doing?
Where's Beth?
When was the last time
you uttered those words,
Commander Crow?
Was it here?
- Was it in this house?
- Come on. Don't do this.
Is it when I called you
and you didn't even believe
it was me.
Let's go outside. We'll talk.
You told your men to kill me.
Put down the knife.
Because you don't care.
You've never cared.
Put down the knife.
- You give up on me.
- Beth, drop the damn knife.
Beth.
You, you said it.
- Sophie.
- Kate!
Sophie, I'm in here. Hurry.
Hey, I need some...
What the hell?
There's a guy in the shed.
His face, I...
I know who he is.
Drop it.
You need to decide right now
what you care more about.
Revenge or Mouse?
I said drop it
or the next one goes in his head.
Two can play this game.
Sister, we both know
you don't have it in you.
But I do.
I suppose killing Daddy
would be all too easy
and no fun at all.
Let us all walk out of here.
And no one has to die today.
Dad?
Kate, it's her.
It's Beth.
So, it has been an experience,
but your Chariot has arrived.
2015 hybrid hatch-back.
Power everything.
Four point three stars.
- I can take a hint.
- Wasn't really hinting.
If Kate calls, can you just tell her
that I'm sorry for everything.
Sure.
Maybe if I go kill someone,
she'll actually call me back.
Only one way to find out.
I thought if I let Alice
tell her story,
the puzzle would fit together.
But the pieces are grim,
grotesque, inhuman,
and it's my fault.
I was there and didn't feel her.
I'm her sister, Bruce.
How am I supposed
to connect with her now
when I couldn't connect
with her then?
Shouldn't you be in the hospital?
You know I hate hospitals.
What if I don't know my sister
well enough to save her?
What if nobody does?
While Alice may have been
forced to flee,
in the end, she got the cheese.
You didn't visit me.
My dearest Mouse.
We both know
if I had shown up to Arkham
with a freshly baked pie,
I would've no sooner been
locked in a cell myself.
But you felt me in your dreams?
Every night.
Twined in memory's mystic band.
- Beth.
- Go away.
I shouldn't have tricked your dad
and sister. I'm sorry.
- I wanna go home.
- You know he won't let you.
But you can. You can let me out.
Maybe, but...
I also don't want you to go.
I wanna be your friend.
To keep you company.
Mouse, do you know
the way out of this pool?
I'm very tired of swimming
in my own tears.
I do know a way.
I will help you
escape your pool of tears.
And you did.
You saved me.
I have a gift for you too.
- I love you, Alice.
- I love you too, dear brother.
And now that we are together again,
I can help you become
anyone you want to be.
And once we are done with Daddy...
He will never forget about me.
Ever, ever again.
Are we mad?
I'm afraid so.