Previously on Batwoman...
Dazzle me.
A perfect match
for Dean Deveraux.
Wouldn't you agree, Mr. Deveraux?
Catherine Hamilton
and some investigators found
skull fragments of a little girl.
It's Beth.
You never would have moved on
if you didn't think
that Beth were dead.
I paid the DNA analyst
to write the report.
Get away from me.
Just get away from me.
If I wanted to kill you
I wouldn't have to wait for you
to be wearing the suit.
Your concern for me
is so touching, dear sister.
So Kate is Batwoman.
- Is this you?
- It wasn't me.
- Tyler, this is Kate.
- You're married.
I don't know how you did it,
Bruce.
You spent night after night
in these same shadows
prowling, hunting, hiding...
And you did it in secret,
all alone.
Everyone all right?
Bravo team,
check on Alessandro's.
- I'll circle around back.
- You heard her. Move out.
Did it ever get to you, Bruce?
The loneliness?
Did you ever let yourself
trust anyone?
- Kate.
- How'd that work out for you?
Sorry to disappoint.
Your dad ordered the Crows
to stop you at any cost.
He needs to know
you're his daughter.
You have the wrong girl.
Kate, I'm serious.
You're in danger.
And if you won't tell him, I will.
- Do you trust me?
- What?
I'll find you.
Shooter escaped.
Was that Batwoman?
She say anything to you?
No. She just took off.
Tuxedo One here.
I was right.
The Rifle's made his way
to Gotham.
The third time is not the charm
for Gotham's
prolific shadow shooter.
After killing two people this week
sources say Batwoman thwarted
his attack at Alessandro's
last night
which means I'm not the only one
who thinks they have
the best osso buco in the city.
Without this city's hero,
our doors would be shuttered.
Batwoman, if you see this
you're welcome for a free meal
at Alessandro's anytime.
Anytime!
Hey.
Just read this news blurb
your dad filed for divorce.
Yep.
Are you okay?
He married a woman who preyed on
his grief and convinced him that
I was crazy for thinking
Beth was still alive.
Can't say I'm losing any sleep over it.
If it means anything,
I didn't sleep last night either.
Why, Luke? What was on your mind?
Oh, thanks for asking.
I was up analyzing
the list of everyone
who was at Alessandro's
for dinner.
Hey, cool. Way to take
the initiative on that.
Find anything? I did, in fact.
Last two victims of the sniper
both worked for your future
ex-stepmother's companies.
Now, one of Alessandro's
dinner guests
Derek Holcomb,
works for Pyra Electric.
They make all of
Hamilton Dynamics' conductors,
which, following the pattern...
Makes him the target.
I need to find him.
I agree, but I haven't quite
found a home address.
Then find it.
Urgency's good.
You're being very urgent, though.
- Sophie knows who I am.
- Right.
- Thought Sophie was cool.
- You're not getting it.
She's threatening to tell my dad.
He's gonna freak out
and shut us down.
Means no more protecting people.
No, more helping the city.
No, more Batwoman.
Can you trust her?
I used to trust her.
With everything.
Then just be real with her.
And for the sake of the city
convince the hell out of her
not to tell your dad who you are.
- Hey.
Have you seen him?
Kane? Heard he went upstate. Why?
I need to talk to him
about something.
Oh, I'm sure he brought his phone.
Kind of an in-person thing.
Is it kind of a husband thing?
Because now I'm super curious.
I promise you'll be
the second person to know.
I thought you said,
Batwoman took off
before you could talk to her.
She did. Why?
Are you working with her?
Am I working with her?
Look how close you two are.
I commanded she surrender.
You're acting like
we exchanged brownie recipes.
Sophie,
do you know who she is?
No.
Tyler, I don't.
Okay.
So, now, Dad's not even showing up
to the divorce proceedings?
The lawyers said he's upstate.
He bailed. Kate bailed.
If I knew it was
attendance optional
I would've literally been
anywhere else.
Are we gonna talk about this
or just act like everything
isn't about to change?
Not everything has to change.
We still have the penthouse.
You can still go to school...
I'm losing my sister.
Kate and I have finally started
to have a connection
after five years,
and now she hates me.
Because of you.
When you are a mother,
you'll understand
why I did what I did.
What am I supposed to do
until then?
You're the only family
I have left,
and I don't even want to be
in this car with you right now.
Mary, I have enough
going on right now
without another guilt trip.
Your text doesn't make sense.
A coil accelerator
doesn't just go missing.
It's under
level five security protocol.
Then get me Dean Deveraux.
He created the gun. He'll know
exactly what's going on.
Oh, my god.
Killed by whom?
Derek Holcomb
just swiped his badge
at the Hamilton Dynamics exit
two minutes ago.
We need to get him
before the shooter does.
I see Derek.
Heads up. Second heat signature
30 feet to the west.
I see him too.
- Batcave to Batwoman, there's...
- Let me guess.
A third heat signature?
- Not another step, Batwoman.
- I'll be bringing him in.
Good news,
Derek Holcomb got away.
Bad news, so did the shooter.
Kate Kane.
What? I'd recognize
that Hammer Strike anywhere.
After all, I taught it to you.
Julia Pennyworth.
Figured Alfred would've
taught you better manners.
Let's leave my father
out of this.
Who is that assassin?
What the hell are you doing
in my city?
Good job, sweet Mouse.
And that is how you kill someone
the first time.
I killed two men for you.
Of the...
Three I requested.
If I walked around failing
at a third of everything I did,
I'd still be locked in a cell
on a diet of my own fingernails.
Mouse!
Can you tell our friend here
why we hired him
to kill those scientists?
Because they were
the only people on the planet
who knew how to make that gun.
Which makes this one of a kind.
See, I did your boss a favor.
Now, no one can recreate it.
Time to hand over
what she promised me in return.
Easy, blondie.
Where is it?
She's not giving you anything
until she finds out that works.
Send her a selfie.
And give me a call
when you have what I'm owed.
So, who does he work for?
The Rifle? Anyone and everyone.
That's what makes him slippery.
My agency assigned me to him
eight months ago?
You kept Dino.
Bruce would be so happy.
So, how'd the Rifle end up here?
I lost sight of him in Jakarta,
picked up a scent in Metropolis,
and then I followed a tip
that he got a job in Gotham.
Whenever the Rifle shows up,
he leaves death and destruction
in his wake.
I know the type.
Good for you.
Following in
your cousin's footsteps.
Bruce is apparently better
at keeping his secret than I am.
To be fair,
I did teach you that move.
And a few others, if I recall.
Holy crap!
- Don't worry. She's...
- Julia?
Luke Fox.
- What are you doing here?
- Business.
Glimpses of pleasure.
How you doing, love?
You know,
holding down the fort.
Of course you are.
A chip off the old block.
I was just gonna suggest
to Kate that we all team up
and nab this sniping bastard.
- What do you say?
- Not happening.
Unless you forgot
the last time we "teamed up."
I'm missing something.
Kate's still sore at me
for a little white lie
I told in the British Isles.
When I first met Julia,
she was pretending to be
a Krav Maga teacher.
She'd just been naughtily
expelled from military school,
sent off to train with strangers
around the world,
and Bruce asked me to check up
on his favorite cousin
without making it seem
like I was babysitting.
So you lied and pretended
that you had a thing for me.
Love, the only thing I lied about
was why I was there.
Oh, so you two "know each other"
know each other.
Well, I was only trying
to help you move on from...
What was her name?
- Sophie something.
- Yeah, that didn't work.
I'm sorry. Who asked you?
- Oh, we still not over her, then?
- She's married.
- To a man.
- We're done talking about this.
She is hell-bent on telling
my dad that I'm Batwoman,
and I need to convince her
not to.
How can I help?
Find the Rifle guy.
And stay the hell out
of my business.
"I hereby deny the allegation
of homosexual conduct.
Signing the above denial
will drop all disciplinary action
and permit the cadet
in question to reengage
with all academic activity."
- Damn it.
- It's gonna be okay.
For you.
Your dad doesn't dry-heave
when he sees a rainbow flag.
My mom calls gays
degenerate sinners.
We should tell the truth.
They'll kick us out.
We'll never make it
into the army.
If we lie, why are we even here?
Besides, they're not gonna kick
out the academy's top two cadets
a week before graduation.
- What if you're wrong?
- Sophie...
Look at everything we've done
over the past four years.
First off, we're women
at Point Rock.
Sophie freaking Moore broke
Shawn Izadi's obstacle record
by one second.
You did make the sharpshooter
competition your bitch.
And we did it all together.
And we'll get through this
together...
as long as we stay united.
You're right.
They're not gonna expel
Sophie freaking Moore.
Let's do it.
Let's tell them the truth.
We're telling them the truth.
I need to run a quick errand.
- Is it her?
- Who?
- Batwoman.
- No.
- And keep your voice down.
- So, it is her?
Look, I'll tell you everything
when I get back.
- I promise.
- Soph.
Hey. Thanks for meeting with me.
Interesting choice.
Wine. Candlelight.
Your favorite kicks.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think
you're about to propose.
Very funny.
So, why am I here, Kate?
Before I say anything,
I need to know I can trust you.
I can't promise you something
when I don't know what it is.
Yeah. I...
I need you to.
Okay. You can trust me.
So I should start by saying
I'm the last person
I ever imagined
would be in this position.
Pardon the interruption, ladies.
Unfortunately,
sneakers are not allowed
in the dining area.
I'm surprised
that you could see them
considering they're hiding
underneath our table.
- Dress codes are dress codes.
- Right.
That guy right there
is wearing sneakers.
Maybe you would enjoy instead
our lounge outside?
Thank you,
but we're really good here.
Sophie, my love,
what would you like to eat?
Kate.
Signora...
Let's avoid a scene.
Then admit that the only thing
offensive about my shoes is me.
Kate, chill.
Please tell me you get
what's happening right now.
Miss, I need to ask you to leave.
Then I need to call
my stepsister. Mary Hamilton?
Do you know her?
Because she knows you
and 3.5 million other people.
Oh, yeah, one snap from her
and she will shut this place down
faster than you can say,
"Gay people
make me feel uncomfortable."
- Enjoy your meal.
- Yeah.
Thanks, but we're not hungry
anymore.
- Was that necessary?
- Standing up for myself? Yeah.
That's what it looks like
when it comes out naturally.
Don't even go there, Kate.
I have no intention
of going there.
"There" is some sad
and lonely closet
that I want nothing to do with.
What went down at Point Rock
was the worst day of my life.
Worse than having
the love of your life
- lie straight to your face?
- I wasn't planning to lie to you.
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
I was going to do everything
we talked about.
Tell the truth, throw the letter
in their face, stand my ground.
- So, what happened?
- I got a second opinion.
So...
This day sucks.
Mr. Kane. Hi.
Your mom coming for the hearing?
I asked them not to call her.
She has no idea.
I love your daughter, sir.
Kate and I are going
to stick together on this.
They can't kick out
their top two cadets.
Well, Moore, you should do
whatever you think
you need to do.
But?
But if you think you're going
to walk out of there
without signing
that letter of denial
and still graduate,
you are in
for a major disappointment.
Did you say that to Kate?
Kate is fearless,
passionate, and reckless.
She is going to walk
into that hearing
and burn the house down.
Nothing I say
can convince her otherwise.
That's what I love about her.
But this will be her last day
at Point Rock.
What about the bad press?
The school is built on history,
tradition, and code.
They'll point to the rules,
say you broke them,
and forget you ever existed.
If I don't tell the truth,
it will destroy our relationship.
I can't make this decision
for you.
And I'm sorry
that you have to make it at all.
You looked me straight in the eye
and told me you didn't love me.
I thought it would be
cleaner than...
Than telling me
that my dad convinced you to lie?
He didn't tell me to lie.
He opened my eyes to reality.
I was going to get expelled.
And thanks to him,
I ended up serving. I graduated.
I... I made money for my family.
I got handpicked by your dad
to help lead the Crows.
You credit your entire career
to my dad.
I credit him for stopping me
from losing everything
I worked for.
And instead, you just lost me.
How long?
The details don't matter.
I'm here thinking you have
a bead on Batwoman's identity,
and you sit me down
and tell me that dating a chick
almost got you expelled
from military academy.
I'm owed some details, Soph.
We met sophomore year.
Our dorm rooms
were in the same building.
So, three years?
- Give or take.
Just to be clear,
three years is longer
than any relationship
I've had outside of you.
I'm not saying
it's insignificant.
Then why didn't you tell me?
You've met my mom.
Yeah. Does she know?
Of course not.
But that's what I'm saying.
I didn't tell anyone.
I just wanted it to go away.
Has it?
Tyler, you are my husband.
I love you.
Has your thing with Kate
gone away?
Got it, Soph.
So the guy just bursts through
the door of the noodle house,
yelling,
"Pennyworth, you're mine!"
So that's how Kate found out
who you really were.
Well, yeah. Once I knocked
the guy on his ass,
I couldn't really go back
to my egg drop soup
without explaining.
Kate's bags were packed, and she
was gone by the end of the day.
Story time.
You must have a 20 on the Rifle.
Sad news, actually.
We found Derek Holcomb.
Despite dodging death twice,
the poor bloke was found
knifed to death in an alley.
Not exactly the Rifle's MO.
So, the trail's gone cold?
For now.
- So, how'd Sophie take it?
- She didn't.
I didn't tell her.
You're a few sandwiches
short of a picnic, love.
She's going to tell your dad.
She would anyway.
There's no way Sophie will ever
be anything but loyal to him.
So, how do we keep him
from shutting us down?
- We move to plan C.
- Which is?
A little bit crazy.
Oh, my god,
you have a safe room?
- Mary.
- How did you get past security?
Karl at the front desk loves
double-whipped Frappuccinos.
- Good. He'll be making them soon.
- Anyway...
I thought we could confab about
the implosion of our family.
- You're new.
- This is Julia.
Julia's my assistant.
You have two assistants
who work past midnight
for a real estate company
without any real estate.
Now, is not really a good time.
Yeah, I got that.
Look, I know everything at home
sucks right now.
I will call you tomorrow.
Is our parents' divorce
even a blip on your radar?
Because it sort of feels like
I'm the only one trying
to hold our family together,
and I'm starting to wonder
if there's really any point.
Welcome back.
I know I'm the last person
you want to see right now.
Whatever it is, we should
work it out with lawyers present.
No, lawyers, Jacob.
This is bigger than that.
I think I know who the sniper
is targeting.
Hamilton Dynamics had been
working on a coil accelerator
that could penetrate
the Kevlar on Batman's suit.
When he disappeared,
we put the project on hold.
Then Batwoman showed up.
We had it reinstated.
And the only three engineers
intimately connected
to the project
have already been killed.
Including the designer,
whose last check-in
was at one of
Hamilton's top secret labs.
When we find the gun,
I'll call you.
A micro spectrometer can track
the gun's
electromagnetic radiation.
We don't have the technology
to do that here.
Actually,
we can do that now, sir.
Didn't mean to eavesdrop,
but ARGUS lent us
micro spectrometers
for testing last month.
You know, I don't recall
this being an open forum.
Permission for a moment alone,
sir?
It's urgent.
Thank you, Jacob.
If there's a coil accelerator
out there on the streets
of Gotham, you need to find it.
We will. But I have
other pressing matters
apart from cleaning up
another mess created by my wife.
- The gun could kill Batwoman.
- That's not really my problem.
Actually, it is, sir.
I said I'll deal with it
another time.
Sir, she's your daughter.
Kate is Batwoman.
And if there's someone out there
who wants to kill her
with this gun,
we need to stop him.
As you requested.
Then I have what she wanted.
Send Batwoman my love.
Alpha team, report.
- First floor's clear.
- Roof's clear.
Are we sure about this place?
The radioactive signature
on the gun is off the charts.
Whoever has it is close by.
You signed it.
I told them
what they wanted to hear.
You lied.
I need this school, okay.
I want to be here.
But they don't want you.
Unfortunately,
I don't have the luxury
of being offended by that.
And maybe it's best
if you just kept your distance
from now on.
Hey.
I know you love me.
Tell me that I'm wrong,
and I'll walk away
and let you make
the biggest mistake of your life.
You're wrong, Kate.
I have to go.
That's Kate's
sharpshooter competition medal.
Cadet Kane
doesn't go here anymore.
Do you even know
how she won that?
Guess it doesn't really matter,
does it?
She didn't even try.
In fact...
She was so hungover
from tequila shots
the night before it was insane
anyone even handed her a gun.
And she still managed
to be the best.
Out of 200 other cadets, she hit
the target dead-on every time.
Because Kate Kane doesn't waver.
She did more for this school
than anyone who's ever gone here.
So you can scrub her name
from every plaque
and banner and roster,
but you will never erase her
or the effect she's had
on the people here.
Base to Moore. What's your 20?
No, sign of him, sir.
- I'll check back in five.
- Ten-four.
Anything?
Not yet.
What did Sophie want?
It's complicated.
Is it me, or does everything
lately seem complicated?
But the thing about complicated
is we handle it better
than anyone I know.
We met under the most complicated
circumstances imaginable.
You were so lost, Jacob.
So full of guilt and anger
and hopelessness.
All I wanted to do was give you
a place to put it all.
So we channeled it here.
If we can turn the pain
into power,
we can do anything, Jacob.
As long as we do it together.
What are you doing here?
You need to get out
of this building.
- Seriously, you need to leave now.
- Sophie.
Before you say anything,
I want you to know
if I could do it all over again,
I would've jumped
on the back of your bike
and left Point Rock in my dust.
Did you tell Jacob Kane?
Yes.
But I didn't tell him
because I'm loyal to the Crows.
I told him because you're going
to get yourself killed,
if not by us,
then by one of your enemies,
and if that ever happened...
- Kate, I can't lose you.
- Sophie?
What the hell is going on?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
Touching story.
Couldn't help myself.
How are you here, Kate?
There was
an electromagnetic surge
- on the second floor.
- All units, converge.
- What the hell was that?
- A coil accelerator.
No, sign of the assassin, sir.
But we got one better. Batwoman.
Bring her to me.
I thought her suit
was bulletproof.
That's what I was trying
to tell you. Or her. Whatever.
Whoever shot her
used a gun that could kill her.
- The hell are you doing?
- Getting her back.
- Luke, come in. Luke.
- I've been trying to reach you.
I heard the explosion over comms
and got worried
- when you didn't report in.
- The Crows have Julia.
Activate the suit's GPS.
Please tell me
this has nothing to do
with the massive amounts
of electromagnetic radiation
- spewing from that area.
- Just activate the GPS.
Okay, they're on Fifth and Grant
in the Bowery.
They're headed toward
the 22nd Street tunnel.
Once they're through,
they're at Crows headquarters,
and Julia's screwed.
You gotta do something right now.
Get your ass on the ground!
Get on the ground!
Hey! Oh, thank god.
What the hell was that?
You were hit by a gun
that should've killed you.
I don't know why it didn't.
The gun didn't work.
You said the projectile
would penetrate the suit.
Oh, dear, how puzzling it all is.
And to think
you've personally killed everyone
capable of fixing it.
Oh, wait,
I had my little Mouse kill one.
Guess I'm one-third responsible.
Listen, you crazy bitch.
You didn't just play me.
You played her.
Safiyah's gonna be pissed from...
Don't you ever say her name
in front of me!
She's a smart woman.
She'll figure it out.
She's as smart
as she is unforgiving.
Whatever reason you betrayed her
better be worth it.
As you requested.
See, dear sister?
There isn't anything
I wouldn't do to protect you.
Careful.
I'm livid the Rifle got away.
The broken ribs from our little
ruse aren't helping either.
Consider us even.
So I thought about it,
and it makes sense.
The not-trusting-people thing.
Clear as day, in fact.
Don't tell me
you've figured me out.
I was gonna say I'm sorry.
I should've been straight
about who I was when we met,
especially once feelings
got involved.
Instead, I burned you.
And now your girl Sophie's
doing the same.
Trust be damned.
She's not my girl.
Whoever she is, it's a shame.
Because she loves you.
Not to crash the party,
but the knife police recovered
from Derek Holcomb's chest,
it was a butterfly knife.
You think it's Alice's?
Why would she want him dead?
She hired the Rifle
to kill anyone
who was connected to the gun
and then tried to kill me with it.
It sounds like
delicious family drama.
And unfortunately, I won't get
to see how the play ends.
You're leaving?
There's a sniper on the loose
who is trying to kill me.
Relax, love.
My agency's just got word
he's headed back to an island
off the Mediterranean
with that gun in tow.
Which means I'm on
a one-way flight to Santorini.
Just don't get yourself killed.
I'm touched you care.
See you again soon, Kate.
Luke, always a pleasure.
You know, apart from my father
and Lucius, of course,
Bruce Wayne never trusted a soul.
Now, I'm not judging his choices,
I wasn't in his shoes, but...
When you don't trust anyone,
it means that you can disappear
for four years
without a single person
on the planet
having any idea where you are.
Now, call me sentimental,
but I don't think
that's a good thing.
Nice digs.
Gotham Pride Real Estate's
first acquisition.
Catchy name.
So I heard someone took out
a Crows van
with a 50-meter precision shot.
I got the impression
that Batwoman means a lot to you.
And I didn't want her to end up
in the wrong hands.
Brought you something
to celebrate.
And I cleared things up
with your dad,
told him I was wrong
about the Batwoman thing...
and how I assumed
you weren't real with me
because of what went down
at Point Rock.
Me in a red wig?
Not happening.
Then why did you invite me
to dinner?
I...
I needed to clear things up
with you.
As hard as I've tried
to get over you,
I can't.
And it's, it's not fair to you...
And based on
what I heard you tell Batwoman,
it's definitely not fair
to Tyler.
- Kate.
- Actually, I...
I think you were right
six years ago.
And maybe it's best
if I keep my distance
from now on.
If that's
what you think will work.
I think it has to.
Good luck with the place.
See you, Sophie.
Batman was praised and revered.
But Bruce Wayne?
Not so much.
No, one knew the man
beneath the cowl.
You didn't let them in, Bruce,
for good reason.
Because even the people we love
are still people
at the end of the day.
You want the truth?
The truth is anything I felt
for Kate Kane went away
the day I chose
my future over her.
You're the only one I love,
Tyler.
They act out of fear,
pride, hope, pain.
And sometimes they let us down.
But you know better than I do
that no one can be
a lone wolf forever.
Need a hand with that?
That is exactly why I called.
So, of all the dumps for sale
in Gotham, why this place?
The guy across the street
asked me to leave his restaurant.
I wonder how he'll like it
when I turn this joint
into a gay bar.
So, obviously,
I'm running point on design.
I have to let people in,
even if it's just one person
and one small piece
of myself at a time.
Hey, kid, just checking in.
My lead on Cartwright upstate
was a dead end.
Guy I found came up clean.
Waste of a couple days,
but worth a shot.
Anyway, I'll probably stay
up here another night,
then head back to Gotham
to figure out our next move.
Hope you're good.
Daddy, you are so handsome.
Catherine seems to think so.
I assumed you'd let
the snake slither back
into her husband's good graces.
Burrowed in so deep
I can still hear her rattle.
They'll never see it coming.
A red, hot poker will burn you
if you hold it too long,
and if you cut your finger
deeply with a knife,
it usually bleeds.
And if you drink much
from a bottle marked "poison,"
it is almost certain to disagree
with you, sooner or later.
Get some sleep, my dear Mouse.
We need to be in our prime
if we are to host
the most memorable, mad
tea party Gotham has ever seen.