Oh, you think you're good?
Who's your daddy?
That's right. Me.
Come on.
Come to Daddy.
Yes!
Finally.
Hey, is there any more wine?
How did you beat him already?
I learned the secret
sucker punch combo.
The secret sucker punch combo
is the thing?
You know, which you would know about
if you, like, ever beat me, like,
one time.
Okay. I'm sorry that I spent the best
video gaming years of my life
locked in a basement cell.
That's one way to take
someone's head off.
She's giving me pointers
on how to be evil.
Nice building.
- I thought you renovated the place.
- I did.
Just badly, apparently.
Is this really happening?
- What?
- Us.
Bickering, drinking...
Playing video games.
Like actual sisters?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it's happening.
Hey, give me that. You suck.
I've had wine, so this will probably
be overly sentimental, but...
Thank you for never giving up on me.
Hey.
It's like I've always said,
you're worth it.
- It's not a bad connection, is it?
- No, it's not.
But it was nice while it lasted.
No.
Stop.
Let me stay here.
Let's try this again.
You live in a fantasy.
Fantasy is not reality.
This is your reality, Alice.
All right. Okay, you caught me.
Take the jewels.
- What do I care?
- Consider this your warning.
Whatever. Fine. I'm warned.
You're free. Go.
Don't be dead. Please.
Come on. Live!
Wake up. Come on. Please.
Wake up!
Up here.
Batwoman, you got company.
Talk to me, Batwoman.
Your heart rate's off the charts.
Kate, answer me. Are you okay?
- Kate?
- I'm fine.
The hell?
Oh, no. No, no, no.
Officer Wilcox, you have
a bomb strapped to your chest.
Don't worry. It's easy to disarm.
Simply push the yellow button
which will trigger a second bomb
I've planted somewhere else in
Gotham.
- What?
- That's right.
You disarm your bomb
to save yourself,
allowing countless others to die.
Or, you die and save all those people
you've never met
who will never know
of your sacrifice.
So, my friend, are you a hero?
The choice should be easy, right?
A hero would do anything
for his city. Would you...?
Now here's a blast from the past.
The Detonator is back
after a seven-year hiatus
and he's out to prove
there are no heroes left in Gotham.
Gotta admit, he made his point in
dynamite when a GCPD officer
blew up a bank last night
to save his own tail,
without even letting the timer
drop into the single digits.
Talk to me, Gotham, are you a hero?
Again?
You're the second one this week.
What happened?
I was helping a guy out of the bomb
wreckage and the ceiling collapsed.
I'm gonna take a look at your ribs.
No, don't cut it. No!
This thing took forever to make.
So, insider tip?
My scissors should not be able
to cut through your super suit.
Why are you pretending
to be Batwoman?
Because the real one is MIA
and the city still has PTSD
from when Batman left.
I thought, maybe, if people saw me
and believed that she
was still around, then...
I know. I'm an idiot.
Your heart is in the right place,
your ribs, however, are not.
Hey, you know people
in the underground.
Do you know where she is?
Trust me, I'm the last person
Batwoman would ever confide in.
I left you like this a week ago
and now it smells like this.
So, you just let yourself
into my home now?
Yeah. And I could have been anyone.
I remember this vile concoction.
They don't call it Chimney Sweep
for nothing.
Cheers.
You haven't returned my texts.
And while I'm decidedly not
that girl...
Do we need to talk about
what happened the other night?
Let's not turn this into a thing.
But...
Thank you for...
Being there for you?
No complaints from me, love.
Gotham, on the other hand,
feels right ghosted
by their caped crusader.
What's going on?
Whenever I put that suit on, I...
I crossed a line
when I killed Cartwright.
What if l screw up
and kill someone else?
I see.
You want to punish yourself.
Fine. You screwed up
and took a man's life.
Bruce would be blustery
with disappointment.
And now you need to get over it.
- That's your pep talk?
- Yeah. I'm needed elsewhere.
And so are you. Someone bombed
Gotham International Bank last night.
Killed a dozen people.
Vacation's over, Batwoman.
In my whole life,
my father urged me to hide my face.
To live in the shadows.
He claimed it was for my own good
to avoid ridicule.
But it turns out,
it was for his own good.
I hid for his comfort.
But the moment I realized I didn't
care if he was comfortable or not...
I became myself.
I became free.
What are you doing?
I'm unburdening myself.
Unburdening yourself?
We are trapped in yet another cage
thanks to my traitorous sister.
It's not a cage, it's a sanctuary.
One where your family can't hurt you.
Where Safiyah can't find you.
Where we have each other.
What else do you need?
Alice, would you like to share?
We haven't heard from you yet.
I'm gonna pass. Yeah.
I've got something to share.
Oh, goodie. It's Tommy Elliot.
Excuse me. Ahem.
All right, Bruce Wayne
could speak over 40 languages.
That's four. Four, zero.
Mr. Elliot, this group
started 15 minutes ago.
Okay. Well, so sue me.
Oh, that's right, you can't,
because my...
My estate's been frozen.
Mr. Elliot, I am thrilled that our
therapy has converted your disdain
for Mr. Wayne
into a deeper appreciation,
but we do need to move
on to other topics.
What's wrong, doc?
It's, like, too crazy?
Because that one thinks she's a cat.
- That one thinks she's a myna bird.
- Magpie.
The name is Magpie.
Steals people's faces.
I mean, this one drools
so much the orderlies have
to follow him around
with a mop.
And, you know, what about me?
What about me?
I'm the guy that taught Bruce Wayne
everything he knows.
So, where's my recognition, doc?
- Get him out of here, please.
- No, no, no!
No, no, no!
No! Bruce is my best friend.
And when he hears about this,
he will end your career, doctor.
One of us!
I can't live like this.
My client Reggie Harris
was wrongly incarcerated for years,
then gunned down
the same day he was freed.
Why?
What did he know?
I will not rest until his family sees
justice. Excuse me.
Bobby, Bobby, one more
question.
Michael Fisher?
Never heard of him.
Probably an alias.
But he killed Alia Nazari
and Reggie Harris and he tried
to kill me and my boss,
all to keep some cover-up
inside the Crows from getting out.
Which means we've got a juicy scandal
on our hands.
Assuming we can figure out
who he's working for.
This one's yours, extra pickles.
I'll look into his finances,
see if anyone's paying him
kill-four-people-in-one-day money.
I already did.
A wire was sent to his account
for 180 grand.
The day Reggie Harris was exonerated
for Lucius Fox's
murder.
Nicely done. I'll go pester
the bank manager, then.
Figure out who sent it.
- Which bank?
- Gotham International.
You're kidding.
- What?
- Gotham International Bank
is a pile of rubble, along with its
vault, its servers, backup servers.
Yeah, some bloke cleverly named
the Detonator bombed it last night.
Do you think
he could be involved in this?
No.
I remember the Detonator.
He was active
long before Reggie was convicted.
All right, move over.
If we can't trace
our sniper's paychecks,
maybe we can figure out
his real name.
That's new.
Wanna talk about it?
Not especially.
Luke,
the man you think killed
your father,
he was cleared and then shot
in front of you.
- Kind of think talking will be good.
- Then let's talk.
Why haven't you found anything
on Cartwright yet?
I don't know.
Maybe he's gone underground.
Well, while you've been away,
ignoring all my texts,
the bat light's gone unanswered.
Why do you think I'm here?
What do we know about the Detonator?
Seven years ago,
the Detonator crippled Gotham
with fear and uncertainty.
He's a terrorist
that targets the city's good guys
and compels them
to kill innocents at random.
The question is, why is he back now?
You want an honest answer to that?
You, Batwoman.
When the bat's away,
the crazies will play.
I've only been out a week.
The bad guys
are getting comfortable.
The Detonator targets people
the public views as heroes.
Doctors, police officers, firemen.
He wants to prove that they're not as
heroic as the world thinks they were.
Where'd you get these?
Bruce's research.
He was obsessed
with catching this guy.
Kept a long list of suspects,
but the trail
went cold before he could narrow it.
Two-one-four. The bomb that took out
Gotham International Bank
had these three numbers stamped
into the ground plate.
This signature matches all 15 bombs
detonated seven years ago.
To be clear, this information
was never released to the public.
Which eliminates the possibility
of a copycat. This is an original.
That is our assertion, although
we still don't know what 214...
actually means.
Anyone on that suspect list
with military experience?
Yeah.
Yeah, a couple.
Who's George Adler?
Private black-ops contractor.
He was fired for...
Yeah, that'll do it.
"He was caught taking selfies
with enemy corpses.
Adler was dishonorably discharged
from military school back
in the day."
No surprise there.
But clearly that wasn't enough
to implicate him in Bruce's mind.
Bruce didn't go to military school.
He wouldn't know the specific form
number on discharge papers.
DD-214.
I only know because Point Rock
put the same code on my papers.
So, the military deemed you
not good enough,
and now that very thing
is gonna save your city's ass.
I'm just gonna leave that
little piece of irony right there.
I'll go talk to Adler.
Welcome back, Batwoman.
You should know,
your suit's nanotech
is designed to withstand detonation
over pressures
of ten pounds per square inch.
Gotham can be glad
their hero is bomb-proof.
That blast will knock off limbs
and topple buildings.
But if you see any evidence
of nuclear materials, uranium,
grapple the hell out of there.
I'm not suiting up.
I'm going as me.
Like a fledgling
real estate developer?
- I'm just gonna talk to him.
- You haven't been out
looking for Cartwright, have you?
Okay. Look, the Bat team
doesn't have an HR department,
so as your co-worker and partner
and pretty much only person you see
on a regular basis,
shouldn't I know
what the hell is going on with you?
If I told you the truth...
You would not want me
to suit up either.
- Bruce Wayne wannabe.
- I'm sorry, what did you just say?
Oh, your boyfriend Bruce?
- He'd think you were a loser.
- Hey, knock it off.
Don't you ever say his name.
You will never be Bruce Wayne.
I need a doctor!
George Adler?
- And you are?
- Kate Kane,
Gotham Pride Real Estate.
I'm in the process
of buying this building
and I have to photograph the units.
Yeah, you got paperwork or something?
My assistant will e-mail you.
Really think he's back?
How the hell would I know?
- I thought you were in real estate.
- Where's the next bomb?
Who the hell are you?
Someone with an interest
in Gotham's property values.
Your obsession with explosives
isn't doing business any favors.
Hey, look, the bombs? That wasn't me.
I swear! It...
It was my old man. George Adler, Sr.
Talk.
The first time he killed a guy,
I don't know,
it triggered something
dark.
Look, I don't expect
a billionaire to understand
how taking a man's life
screws with your head.
Try me.
He snapped... okay?
He wanted to show people
that it's a lot harder
to act like a hero
when you're in the heat of it,
staring down your own death.
- Where is he now?
- Gotham Cemetery.
What?
He's dead. Died seven years ago.
No! No, no, no. Don't do this to me!
The charismatic defense
attorney
who claims to stand up
for the little guys, the everyman.
What a hero.
Now you have a choice.
Looking for me?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
No thanks to security. That's you.
They put Tommy in solitary.
Good.
Little does he know,
the Bruce-obsessed Neanderthal
played his part to a T.
I asked the nurse to be thorough.
What are you...? You're bleeding.
It's only temporary, Mouse.
Plus, what's a little blood
if it ensures our freedom?
I can't do this. I have a family.
You called us for a reason.
You know that.
Lives depend on you staying calm
and doing the right thing.
Jacob, look, I'm no hero, okay?
You have to be one today.
It's down to 22 minutes.
That's 22 minutes to get everyone
out, so you can push that button.
You just hang tight.
The Detonator wants his victims
to hear the explosion they've caused.
That means the secondary explosive
is likely within a one-mile radius
of Bobby Reeves.
Bomb squad's on its way to Bobby.
This guy uses half a dozen trip
wires.
If we wanna save lives,
we need to clear that mile
in less than a half hour.
- Bobby, you still with me?
- Yeah. Yeah.
The Detonator's dead.
It's gotta be a copycat.
You sure junior didn't pick up
where his old man left off?
He was at work. Alibi checks out.
Crap.
We're out of time, Kate.
The Detonator has another victim.
Crows and GCPD
are clearing buildings now.
- Where is it?
- Doesn't say.
But they're clearing Wiget
and Brighton.
- Isn't that right by...?
- Mary.
Residents are to take only pets
and leave everything else behind.
Follow authorities
to the nearest checkpoint
and not to return under
any circumstances
until the threat
has been neutralized.
We will continue to bring you live
updates
on this evacuation and bomb scare...
Go straight on Brighton.
You'll hit a police barricade.
You'll be safe from there, okay? Go.
- Mr. Whittaker, we need to move you.
- Okay.
- Get him to a checkpoint.
- You need to come with.
Nobody knows this clinic exists.
They're gonna detonate that bomb
whether this place is clear or not.
Come on.
I'm not leaving them.
Go.
Hey, Bobby, you're doing great.
- You gotta get this thing off of me.
- Oh, we will. We will.
But we need to give our guys
more time to clear the area.
I... I can't do it.
I can't!
You're gonna do the right thing.
Under order of Mayor Akins,
all civilians are ordered
to evacuate immediately.
Do not hesitate.
Do not pack your belongings.
Humans and pets only. If you
can hear this message, evacuate now.
Come on.
This is the last building
on this block.
I promise you
this is just a precaution,
like the fire drills you
had as a kid.
What can I do?
Why did you come back?
You need to get out of here.
These people need help.
Get everyone on the ground.
If they can't move, try
and cover them with a mattress
and pray this building
passed its earthquake inspection.
Mary.
GCPD just gave the all clear.
Okay, Bobby.
Gotham is under a mandatory lockdown.
The streets are not safe.
Remain in your homes.
Gotham is under a mandatory lockdown.
The streets are not safe.
Remain in your homes.
Mary!
Help, please!
Who is this?
Isn't it obvious?
She's Batwoman.
I have to go.
You wanna know
why people like her exist?
Or why they keep on showing up
to spread hope?
It's because you inspired them
and now they feel abandoned.
- What? What are you talking about?
- Please, Kate.
I know you're Batwoman.
I mean...
I just can't believe
I didn't figure it out sooner.
But of course, Batwoman's the same
girl who hunted down Derrick Peters
and locked him in a urinal
after he ditched me at homecoming.
And, of course,
the maniac on the bat bike...
Is the same maniac
who taught me how to drive
without actually having her license.
And totally charmed her
way out of a ticket
after my ass got us pulled over.
It couldn't be more obvious.
Batwoman is the same person
I've looked up to my entire life.
And now the city needs you
as much as I do.
It's not that simple.
It never is.
But Batwoman doesn't get a sick day.
- I'm not a hero, Mary.
- I'm not asking you to be a hero.
I'm just asking you to keep going.
And how are we feeling today, Johnny?
I think I had another moment
of clarity, Dr. Butler.
Really?
And what was that?
Well, you know, I have almost
everything that I want here.
Shelter, protection, my sister.
And what is it you're still missing?
Power.
Feel that, Dr. Butler?
This is your reality now.
Took a minute, but we figured
out the real identity
of the sniper who
killed Reggie Harris.
He lived at 2420 Maple Street.
The same 2420 Maple Street
that blew up?
Eviscerating all evidence linking
him back to whoever hired him.
- Great.
- In the last week alone,
everyone with any knowledge
of your father's real murderer
has been killed.
We think the Detonator hired the
sniper to kill Reggie Harris
and used these bombs
to cover his scent.
Except the Detonator's dead.
We're dealing with a copycat.
Real Detonator died seven years ago.
Which means
that we're looking for someone
who's intimately familiar
with the Detonator's case.
But who'd have had access
to the report?
It depends. Who was the
investigating officer at the time?
Miguel Robles. He was a rookie cop
on the Detonator investigation team.
Robles is head
of the Crows Homicide Division.
That's pretty high up
in your bird's nest.
After Lucius was killed,
the Crows paid Alia Nazari
a 50 grand clean-up fee
for the destruction
of her Sip and Dash.
The commander was worried it was a
payoff to delete the surveillance,
but Robles was convinced
the payment
wasn't out of the
ordinary.
He was also the first to arrive
at the Sip and Dash that night.
This guy's hands are in everything.
I want every piece of shrapnel
collected and tested for prints.
We'll find him
before he strikes again.
- You're wrong. I am not a killer.
- Yet.
You're scared you're becoming
like me.
You wanted this.
You left Cartwright for me to find.
You wanted to push me over the edge.
You set me up to kill him,
so that I would be like you.
Kate, you can't give me
all the credit.
After all, it wasn't that hard to...
I'm not asking you to be a hero.
I'm just asking you to keep going.
Jacob Kane, city savior.
You had to see this coming, right?
Hang on, you think our bomber
is a Crow?
Robles was at the scene
of my dad's murder.
- The facts line up.
- Where is he?
I just got a ping on his phone.
He's crossing
the 1200 block of Rucka Ave.
He's headed for the bridge
out of Gotham.
Got him.
What's going on? I heard gunshots.
Our boy Robles seems pretty eager
to get out of town.
You see the badge, bitch?
I'm a Crow.
And I'm gonna destroy you.
Like you did Reggie Harris?
Or Alia Nazari or the dozen people
at Gotham International?
- What do you want?
- The truth.
Did you kill Lucius Fox?
Who wants to know?
His kid?
He's never gonna be able to prove it.
Why?
I tie up loose ends.
- Luke, evacuate the building.
- What the hell is going on?
Disarm the damn bomb
or we both blow up in here.
I can't. Only way to disarm it
is for the other bomb to go off.
And where is that?
Ask Commander Kane.
Robles? No.
No, he wouldn't do this.
I didn't wanna believe it either,
but the evidence is there.
Even though he killed a lot of people
trying to cover it up.
- Tuxedo One here.
- It's me.
The second bomb is at Wayne.
Do not let anyone touch that button
until I give the all clear.
Copy that. Good luck.
Second bomb's at Wayne Tower.
- Says who?
- An associate.
Got you.
- Didn't realized you had associates.
- Just the one.
Call Kate.
Tell her to stay away
from that building.
- On it.
- Sir, I can deactivate two
of the trip wires, but there's
a pressure plate on your chest.
- If I move it, I can...
- Don't.
We'll let it tick down until
we can clear the area around Wayne.
You move the truck or tamper
with the timer, it blows.
If you don't disarm it, it blows.
- I need him alive.
- Luke.
- What are you doing?
- Introducing myself...
to the guy who killed my father.
Get up!
I said get up!
Look at me!
Luke, this bomb goes off in five
minutes.
Well, it's a good thing
my dad planned for that.
The city's safe.
Now the bomb blows up this room
and only this room.
You really wanna die a coward,
Robles? Don't.
You're fast,...
but you're not that fast.
I'll talk, just...
- put the gun down.
- Why did you kill...
My dad?
- Money.
- Money?
- Whose money?
- That rich asshat Tommy Elliot.
Why would Tommy Elliot
want Lucius Fox dead?
He had a book.
- Some journal Lucius was writing.
- What journal?
No idea.
All I know is that Tommy
was obsessed with it
and after I was recruited to
the Crows,
I was put on Tommy's personal detail.
He paid me 10 grand
to rough Lucius up.
You shot him in the chest!
By mistake.
I told your old man if he
didn't give Tommy what he wanted,
I would turn my attention...
To his kid.
You.
That set him off, he charged,
I pulled the trigger
and then it just snowballed.
After that I framed Reggie
and I spent the last four years
just covering up...
It's my fault. I started
the Crows to protect Gotham.
Now the whole city's on lockdown
because of me.
Robles going rogue is not your fault.
It's a high density blast radius.
They're still evacuating.
You should get out of here.
I'm on comms with Batwoman waiting
for the go-ahead.
So, if anything,
you should go.
I'm not leaving my boss.
Looks like we're stuck with each
other, then.
Luke, you need to get out of here.
There is a bomb strapped
to my dad and I...
I need to give him the green light
to disarm it.
Luke.
He took everything from me.
Killing him...
It won't change what happened
to your dad.
So, we just hand him over to the same
court that convicted Reggie Harris?
No, I'm dealing with this my way.
I killed Cartwright.
What?
- What?
- I didn't wanna suit up
because I feel like a fraud
in this thing.
I had every chance
to stop myself and I didn't.
Luke,
the world is short on heroes.
Do not let your anger turn you
into someone that you're not.
Grab his arms.
Julia, hit it.
Do it.
Couldn't have done
this without you, Moore.
Glad to officially be back, sir.
Formalities aside, this is the start
of a major overhaul.
Robles gave up everyone
who took part in Harris' frame job
to avoid the death penalty.
We are draining the swamp.
I'm putting a new strike team in
place and you are co-heading it.
I'm not capable of running it solo?
So, I just got off the phone
with my agency.
Apparently, I've been recruited
to run a Crows strike team.
Co-run, technically.
So, where do you wanna start?
Personal detail, homicide squad?
With burgers.
Good ones, not the garbage
you've been bringing
to the motel all week.
Go on, then, twist my arm.
You're buying.
Company card.
You'll get yours at orientation.
Bomb squad just left.
They're gonna
have some follow-up questions,
but since you weren't here...
Thanks.
I should be thanking you
for talking me
off the ledge last night.
That's what partners are for.
Hey.
Do you know anything about this
journal that Tommy Elliot wanted?
Yeah, let's just say
my dad's journals
weren't poems about his feelings.
This was an instruction manual
to building every piece
of Wayne technology.
Well...
It's a good thing
that Batwoman's back.
Why didn't you tell me
about Cartwright?
Honestly...
Sometimes, I feel like you think
I'm some infallible hero
that makes the right choice
every single time.
I just...
I didn't wanna see the look on your
face when you were wrong.
I'm not wrong.
- I broke Batman's code.
- You think you're the only one?
Ever wonder why the Joker
hasn't reared his head in five years?
He's not in Arkham, Kate.
Both you and Bruce stared
into the abyss.
The question is,
how long are you gonna
let it stare back at you?
Okay, so I assume that you've seen
this, because you look good.
Hi, Mary. Kate's not Batwoman.
That would be a major time suck
from real estate development,
her actual job.
It's fine, she knows.
She knows...?
She knows what, exactly?
Yeah, we don't have to play
this little game, anymore.
What game? So you know what?
Kate,
you have a showing in 15 minutes.
You should really get going.
I'll let you two work this one out.
Yeah, great. So, you know what,
I'm gonna...
You e-mail me
that investment strategy
and I'll forward you back
some comps about the building's
blueprints
and we'll make sure to get
on the numbers.
Now, you're just saying words.
Time for your therapy, young lady.
It is amazing what I can do
with a sharp edge
and a little threads...
Chief Physician Butler.
What do you say
we hit up the ice cream cart
before we skip
our way right out the front door?
I was thinking about what you said
about the allure of this place.
The protection, the anonymity.
The way the walls help the
outside world forget all about us.
Why be rats on the streets of Gotham
when we can be royalty in here?
You will be queen
and I will be king.
And when everyone has forgotten us,
we'll remind them who we are.
And they will never,
ever forget us again.
Now the lines are blurred
And faded
No one ever starts that way
This is how villains are made