1
00:03:16,497 --> 00:03:19,330
"A fine reward is
offered for the return

2
00:03:19,366 --> 00:03:22,858
of a slave woman stolen...

3
00:03:22,903 --> 00:03:27,067
or absconded from
the house of Claudius Appius.

4
00:03:27,107 --> 00:03:29,905
The following noblemen
returning from Greece

5
00:03:29,943 --> 00:03:34,607
have received pardon of Caesar
and must not be harmed:

6
00:03:34,648 --> 00:03:37,981
Publius Servilius Casca,

7
00:03:38,018 --> 00:03:41,044
Marcus Tullius Cicero,

8
00:03:41,088 --> 00:03:43,955
Gaius Cassius Longinus

9
00:03:43,991 --> 00:03:48,553
and Marcus Junius Brutus.

10
00:03:48,595 --> 00:03:51,928
The traitor Pompey
has fled to Egypt.

11
00:03:51,965 --> 00:03:54,092
Glorious Caesar follows."

12
00:04:23,997 --> 00:04:26,022
Shoulder arms!

13
00:04:27,568 --> 00:04:29,468
Forward!

14
00:04:30,671 --> 00:04:32,935
Forward face!

15
00:04:35,242 --> 00:04:37,506
Forward march!

16
00:05:24,291 --> 00:05:26,953
Behold, Ptolemy,

17
00:05:26,994 --> 00:05:30,191
he of the two ladies,

18
00:05:30,230 --> 00:05:32,960
he of sedge and bee.

19
00:05:34,401 --> 00:05:36,961
Behold Ptolemy,

20
00:05:37,004 --> 00:05:38,972
Son of Ra,

21
00:05:39,006 --> 00:05:42,339
Ptolemy the Divine.

22
00:05:48,916 --> 00:05:51,214
Greetings...

23
00:06:21,081 --> 00:06:24,573
How long may we hope
for the blessing of your presence?

24
00:06:24,618 --> 00:06:26,085
Not long.

25
00:06:26,119 --> 00:06:28,019
Oh, we are desolated.

26
00:06:28,055 --> 00:06:31,889
If His Glorious Honor cares
to divulge his purpose here,

27
00:06:31,925 --> 00:06:34,450
the servants
of the Mighty Lion

28
00:06:34,495 --> 00:06:36,963
would be ecstatic
to help you

29
00:06:36,997 --> 00:06:39,056
in any way
whatsoever.

30
00:06:39,099 --> 00:06:41,226
That is most kind of you.

31
00:06:44,471 --> 00:06:48,134
How goes your
preparation for war?

32
00:06:48,175 --> 00:06:50,507
War?

33
00:06:50,544 --> 00:06:52,512
We have no war prepared.

34
00:06:52,546 --> 00:06:54,514
I'm misinformed then.

35
00:06:54,548 --> 00:06:56,516
I was told the sister
of the Mighty Lion

36
00:06:56,550 --> 00:06:59,383
disputes his right
to the throne.

37
00:06:59,419 --> 00:07:01,944
Do not speak of her.

38
00:07:01,989 --> 00:07:05,720
I piss on her!
I shit on her!

39
00:07:05,759 --> 00:07:07,727
It is true
our beloved princess

40
00:07:07,761 --> 00:07:11,822
has listened to ill counsel
and raised some absurd claim.

41
00:07:11,865 --> 00:07:15,426
But... she has no support,

42
00:07:15,469 --> 00:07:18,905
none but traitors
and barbarians.

43
00:07:20,741 --> 00:07:22,709
What was that name?

44
00:07:22,743 --> 00:07:24,301
Deilogos of Pergamum.

45
00:07:24,344 --> 00:07:26,938
He can raise 10 legions.

46
00:07:26,980 --> 00:07:28,948
Deilogos of Pergamum

47
00:07:28,982 --> 00:07:32,145
can raise
10 legions for her.

48
00:07:32,185 --> 00:07:36,554
A petty bandit. I assure you,
you have no problem,

49
00:07:36,590 --> 00:07:39,787
no fears at all
about Cleopatra.

50
00:07:39,826 --> 00:07:41,350
Where is she?

51
00:07:41,395 --> 00:07:43,363
Well, nobody knows.

52
00:07:43,397 --> 00:07:46,662
Somewhere in the south,
we believe.

53
00:07:46,700 --> 00:07:49,430
He lies.
They have her.

54
00:07:49,469 --> 00:07:53,496
This dispute between
you both must end.

55
00:07:53,540 --> 00:07:56,668
Rome desires Egypt
to be at peace.

56
00:07:56,710 --> 00:07:59,736
Your grain ships
must keep sailing.

57
00:07:59,780 --> 00:08:01,748
We are in absolute
control of the country,

58
00:08:01,782 --> 00:08:03,909
from the lighthouse
to the Cataracts.

59
00:08:03,951 --> 00:08:06,511
Good, in that case
you should have no trouble

60
00:08:06,553 --> 00:08:08,646
in handing over
Pompey Magnus.

61
00:08:08,689 --> 00:08:10,623
I do not like his tone.

62
00:08:10,657 --> 00:08:12,215
He can go.

63
00:08:12,259 --> 00:08:14,420
Eh...

64
00:08:14,461 --> 00:08:18,727
Master, do you remember
what we spoke of before?

65
00:08:18,765 --> 00:08:20,858
Of crocodile and fox?

66
00:08:22,436 --> 00:08:24,768
Let us show him
our surprise!

67
00:08:24,805 --> 00:08:27,603
All right, go on.
Show him.

68
00:08:29,376 --> 00:08:31,276
Ahem...

69
00:08:31,311 --> 00:08:34,974
We have a gift for you,
Glorious Excellency,

70
00:08:35,015 --> 00:08:38,917
that we think you will
be very pleased with.

71
00:09:15,989 --> 00:09:17,820
We were going to
make him a body,

72
00:09:17,858 --> 00:09:21,419
moving arms and legs, and do a mime
show with real animals and everything...

73
00:09:21,461 --> 00:09:23,122
Silence!

74
00:09:33,340 --> 00:09:35,900
Shame on the house
of Ptolemies

75
00:09:35,942 --> 00:09:38,274
for such barbarity.
Shame.

76
00:09:38,311 --> 00:09:40,973
But... you are enemies.

77
00:09:41,014 --> 00:09:43,744
He was a consul of Rome!

78
00:09:50,924 --> 00:09:53,552
A consul of Rome.

79
00:09:54,761 --> 00:09:57,321
To die
in this sordid way...

80
00:09:57,364 --> 00:10:01,232
quartered like
some low thief...

81
00:10:01,268 --> 00:10:03,429
shame!

82
00:10:06,506 --> 00:10:09,134
Where is
the rest of him?

83
00:10:09,176 --> 00:10:11,337
Eh, um, he has been
cremated...

84
00:10:11,378 --> 00:10:14,609
with all proper
funeral rites of course.

85
00:10:14,648 --> 00:10:17,515
With all decorum.

86
00:10:17,551 --> 00:10:19,542
I shall return
tomorrow,

87
00:10:19,586 --> 00:10:22,851
at which time
you will give me

88
00:10:22,889 --> 00:10:25,187
the man that took
Pompey's life.

89
00:11:26,453 --> 00:11:29,320
Captain says
the wind is fair.

90
00:11:29,356 --> 00:11:33,588
- Good.
- We can leave whenever you like.

91
00:11:33,627 --> 00:11:37,961
You will take half the men,
return to Rome immediately.

92
00:11:37,998 --> 00:11:42,332
You shall have the honor
of announcing Pompey's death.

93
00:11:42,369 --> 00:11:45,566
I shall follow you...

94
00:11:45,605 --> 00:11:47,368
when I've settled
things here.

95
00:11:53,046 --> 00:11:56,777
Settled things?
Settled what things?

96
00:11:56,817 --> 00:11:59,445
Civil war is
in the air.

97
00:11:59,486 --> 00:12:01,750
It must be
prevented.

98
00:12:01,788 --> 00:12:03,756
Why?

99
00:12:03,790 --> 00:12:07,886
Let the wretches
fight it out.

100
00:12:07,928 --> 00:12:10,556
War will disrupt
the grain supply.

101
00:12:10,597 --> 00:12:14,761
Without Egyptian grain,
Rome goes hungry.

102
00:12:14,801 --> 00:12:19,033
It would be... unwise
not to intervene.

103
00:12:19,072 --> 00:12:22,974
And how will you intervene
with only half a legion?

104
00:12:23,009 --> 00:12:25,910
I do not intend to fight.

105
00:12:25,946 --> 00:12:30,042
I shall merely arbitrate
the various factions.

106
00:12:30,083 --> 00:12:32,574
You make it
sound so easy.

107
00:12:32,619 --> 00:12:37,318
Those various factions are united
only by their hatred of Rome.

108
00:12:39,426 --> 00:12:41,087
He's right.

109
00:12:41,127 --> 00:12:45,655
Ptolemy might use you to rouse
the people against a common enemy.

110
00:12:45,699 --> 00:12:48,668
I have conquered Gaul.

111
00:12:48,702 --> 00:12:50,897
I have defeated
Pompey Magnus.

112
00:12:50,937 --> 00:12:53,963
I think I can handle
a small boy and a eunuch.

113
00:12:54,007 --> 00:12:56,908
A small boy
with 100,000 men.

114
00:12:56,943 --> 00:12:58,843
I am aware of that!

115
00:12:58,879 --> 00:13:00,972
He's still
a boy nonetheless.

116
00:13:01,014 --> 00:13:05,713
You seem to forget that
our war is not over yet.

117
00:13:05,752 --> 00:13:08,653
Cato and Scipio
are still at large.

118
00:13:08,688 --> 00:13:11,748
Given time, they will
raise another army.

119
00:13:11,791 --> 00:13:13,759
And when they do
I shall crush them.

120
00:13:13,793 --> 00:13:16,023
I'm glad
you're so confident.

121
00:13:16,062 --> 00:13:19,759
Some would
call it hubris.

122
00:13:19,799 --> 00:13:22,427
It's only hubris
if I fail.

123
00:13:29,309 --> 00:13:33,370
Remember, she is
a princess of ancient blood.

124
00:13:33,413 --> 00:13:36,974
When you find her you will treat
her with the utmost respect.

125
00:13:37,017 --> 00:13:40,509
You must obey her in all
things, within reason.

126
00:13:40,553 --> 00:13:42,020
Understood, sir.

127
00:13:42,055 --> 00:13:44,455
I'm counting
on you, Vorenus.

128
00:13:48,161 --> 00:13:49,890
You have something
to say?

129
00:13:49,930 --> 00:13:53,161
Regarding Pompey Magnus,
sir, I wish to apologize.

130
00:13:54,734 --> 00:13:58,067
It was my actions that
brought him here to this end.

131
00:13:59,339 --> 00:14:02,172
- If I had done my duty...
- Indeed.

132
00:14:03,176 --> 00:14:04,666
Dismissed.

133
00:14:30,870 --> 00:14:32,929
Pompey's murderer.

134
00:14:34,507 --> 00:14:36,566
Alas, he has run away.

135
00:14:36,609 --> 00:14:39,043
Find him.

136
00:14:40,413 --> 00:14:42,381
In the meantime...

137
00:14:42,415 --> 00:14:46,317
these instruments tabulate
the money that was borrowed

138
00:14:46,353 --> 00:14:50,153
by His Majesty's
illustrious father, Ptolemy Xll.

139
00:14:50,190 --> 00:14:53,887
In the name of the Republic,
I have come to collect.

140
00:14:53,927 --> 00:14:56,794
17 thousand thousand drachma.

141
00:15:01,735 --> 00:15:04,033
17?

142
00:15:04,070 --> 00:15:07,096
Absurd!

143
00:15:07,140 --> 00:15:08,767
Four, perhaps.

144
00:15:08,808 --> 00:15:13,404
The tabulation includes
all monies borrowed from Pompey

145
00:15:13,446 --> 00:15:17,177
and other agents of the
Republic now unable to collect.

146
00:15:17,217 --> 00:15:19,617
That is not just!

147
00:15:19,652 --> 00:15:21,347
Post-mortem interests
of this type

148
00:15:21,388 --> 00:15:23,583
are legally entailed
to the presiding consul,

149
00:15:23,623 --> 00:15:26,421
i.e. Gaius Julius Caesar.

150
00:15:26,459 --> 00:15:29,451
- It's law.
- Roman law.

151
00:15:29,496 --> 00:15:32,761
Is there some
other form of law...

152
00:15:32,799 --> 00:15:34,926
you wretched woman?

153
00:15:37,037 --> 00:15:40,029
1,000 apologies.
Forgive us.

154
00:15:46,379 --> 00:15:48,643
There!

155
00:15:48,681 --> 00:15:52,378
- There's for your payment.
- So sorry...

156
00:15:52,419 --> 00:15:56,515
His Majesty forgets
he is a vassal to Rome.

157
00:15:56,556 --> 00:15:58,114
Vassal?

158
00:15:58,158 --> 00:16:00,388
Vassal?
I am no vassal!

159
00:16:00,427 --> 00:16:02,895
- I am king! I am...
- Sit down!

160
00:16:12,005 --> 00:16:13,802
Thank you.

161
00:16:13,840 --> 00:16:16,502
When can I expect payment?

162
00:16:16,543 --> 00:16:21,276
Your Honor, we have little enough
ready coin for our own needs.

163
00:16:21,314 --> 00:16:25,512
Our tax farmers have not been
working as they should because...

164
00:16:25,552 --> 00:16:27,247
Because?

165
00:16:28,788 --> 00:16:33,350
Cleopatra's foolishness has
stirred unrest in some parts.

166
00:16:33,393 --> 00:16:35,691
Nothing serious.

167
00:16:37,564 --> 00:16:42,001
Well, I do not wish
to appear unreasonable.

168
00:16:42,035 --> 00:16:46,267
I will accept 10 thousand
thousand drachma.

169
00:16:46,306 --> 00:16:49,366
Even that amount will
take many days to collect.

170
00:16:49,409 --> 00:16:52,901
In that case, I shall have
ample time to adjudicate

171
00:16:52,946 --> 00:16:56,211
your dispute with
Princess Cleopatra.

172
00:16:56,249 --> 00:16:58,217
Excellent notion.

173
00:16:58,251 --> 00:17:01,015
But alas, who knows where
Princess Cleopatra is?

174
00:17:01,054 --> 00:17:03,022
Oh, do not worry
about that.

175
00:17:03,056 --> 00:17:04,614
I shall find her.

176
00:17:16,002 --> 00:17:18,197
Blood and fire!

177
00:17:18,238 --> 00:17:20,638
It's as hot
as Vulcan's dick!

178
00:17:26,045 --> 00:17:28,013
What a dump.

179
00:17:28,047 --> 00:17:31,744
Gyppo gods must be right
wasters to make a place like this.

180
00:17:31,784 --> 00:17:35,220
Don't speak ill of the gods
in their own country.

181
00:17:35,255 --> 00:17:39,021
Gerrae.
I've seen their gods.

182
00:17:39,058 --> 00:17:42,824
Titus Pullo isn't scared of any
bastard with a dog's head on him.

183
00:17:42,862 --> 00:17:47,492
More fool you. These gods
are old and powerful.

184
00:17:47,534 --> 00:17:49,832
Egypt was a great nation
long before Rome.

185
00:17:50,937 --> 00:17:52,768
Was it?

186
00:17:52,805 --> 00:17:54,636
Mumped it up now,
then, haven't they?

187
00:18:00,446 --> 00:18:02,744
Why are we here, anyhow?

188
00:18:02,782 --> 00:18:04,477
Waiting.

189
00:18:04,517 --> 00:18:06,314
Yeah, I know we're waiting, but for who?

190
00:18:07,353 --> 00:18:09,184
I'll know
when I see them.

191
00:18:10,290 --> 00:18:13,350
Heh. Be like that.

192
00:18:15,395 --> 00:18:17,363
"Vassal," he says!

193
00:18:17,397 --> 00:18:19,524
Barbarian scum!

194
00:18:20,700 --> 00:18:22,759
It's simple extortion.

195
00:18:22,802 --> 00:18:26,329
If we do not pay him, he will
put Cleopatra on the throne.

196
00:18:26,372 --> 00:18:27,839
If...

197
00:18:27,874 --> 00:18:29,808
if he could find her.

198
00:18:29,842 --> 00:18:32,811
He is a resourceful man.

199
00:18:32,845 --> 00:18:35,313
He will find her.

200
00:18:35,348 --> 00:18:38,442
She should have died
when we first caught her.

201
00:18:39,519 --> 00:18:42,181
Now it must be done.
She must die.

202
00:18:42,222 --> 00:18:44,747
I agree.

203
00:18:46,426 --> 00:18:48,291
My men could be
with her by nightfall.

204
00:20:42,075 --> 00:20:44,168
Tell him "Wait."

205
00:20:48,614 --> 00:20:50,275
Cleopatra.

206
00:20:50,316 --> 00:20:51,783
Queen Majesty?

207
00:20:51,818 --> 00:20:55,379
Hutto asks to
speak with you.

208
00:21:05,898 --> 00:21:07,889
Slap me.

209
00:21:14,607 --> 00:21:17,167
- Night or day?
- Night.

210
00:21:19,145 --> 00:21:20,669
He may enter.

211
00:21:27,086 --> 00:21:29,145
Majesty...

212
00:21:29,188 --> 00:21:31,554
fresh word has come
from Alexandria.

213
00:21:33,393 --> 00:21:35,293
Speak, worm!

214
00:21:36,329 --> 00:21:38,889
I am most deeply
sorry to say

215
00:21:38,931 --> 00:21:43,459
Majesty must prepare herself
for her journey to the afterlife.

216
00:21:45,738 --> 00:21:47,706
When?

217
00:21:47,740 --> 00:21:50,004
Now.

218
00:22:19,739 --> 00:22:21,764
Say your words.

219
00:23:34,080 --> 00:23:36,275
Hello, ladies.

220
00:23:37,350 --> 00:23:39,648
Attack Caesar?

221
00:23:41,521 --> 00:23:43,751
Are you serious?

222
00:23:43,789 --> 00:23:45,757
Why not?

223
00:23:45,791 --> 00:23:48,089
He only has
a few hundred men with him.

224
00:23:49,195 --> 00:23:51,493
How many men
could you rally?

225
00:23:55,701 --> 00:23:58,568
You would be
the liberator of Egypt.

226
00:23:58,604 --> 00:24:00,936
Your name would
live forever.

227
00:24:00,973 --> 00:24:02,941
My mortal flesh should
be less fortunate.

228
00:24:02,975 --> 00:24:05,102
Rome does not
forget an injury.

229
00:24:05,144 --> 00:24:07,374
Oh, forget Rome!

230
00:24:07,413 --> 00:24:09,711
Rome is doomed.

231
00:24:09,749 --> 00:24:13,651
Her people tear at
their flesh like mad dogs.

232
00:24:13,686 --> 00:24:17,622
In 10 years the city
will be a forgotten ruin.

233
00:24:17,657 --> 00:24:20,524
Maybe so, but what
of next year?

234
00:24:20,560 --> 00:24:22,528
Perhaps you're right.

235
00:24:22,562 --> 00:24:26,896
Ergo,
caution is best, yes.

236
00:24:26,933 --> 00:24:31,836
Perhaps... you don't
have enough influence

237
00:24:31,871 --> 00:24:34,339
among the people.

238
00:24:36,042 --> 00:24:38,306
And Caesar has
so few men.

239
00:24:39,745 --> 00:24:42,737
I could raise the
whole city with a word.

240
00:24:44,850 --> 00:24:47,250
Think on it.

241
00:24:51,023 --> 00:24:55,960
Oh, do you think I could
borrow Septimius for a little while?

242
00:24:55,995 --> 00:24:58,293
I'd be most grateful.

243
00:25:00,366 --> 00:25:01,890
Of course.

244
00:25:11,777 --> 00:25:14,746
Messenger from
Ptolemy Xlll begs entry, sir.

245
00:25:35,668 --> 00:25:38,831
"Ptolemy the Water Bringer,
he of the two ladies,

246
00:25:38,871 --> 00:25:41,066
he of sedge and bee,
King of Kings, Son of Ra,

247
00:25:41,107 --> 00:25:44,133
informs His Most
Grand Honor, et cetera,

248
00:25:44,176 --> 00:25:47,942
that him who bears this message
is him that killed Pompey."

249
00:26:24,216 --> 00:26:27,083
He's handsome enough.

250
00:26:27,119 --> 00:26:30,486
Good, strong chin.

251
00:26:30,523 --> 00:26:33,048
Looks like a mean
old man to me.

252
00:26:35,861 --> 00:26:37,522
More.

253
00:26:37,563 --> 00:26:39,861
Divinity's mortal flesh
turns green.

254
00:26:39,899 --> 00:26:42,424
Give it here.

255
00:27:09,528 --> 00:27:13,020
She will look like a reptile
when she arrives at Alexandria.

256
00:27:23,976 --> 00:27:25,967
Weak, I call it.

257
00:27:34,587 --> 00:27:36,316
Weak, am I?

258
00:27:36,355 --> 00:27:38,823
She knows how to beat
her slaves well enough,

259
00:27:38,858 --> 00:27:41,691
but she cannot
throw away that pipe,

260
00:27:41,727 --> 00:27:45,629
- and she knows it.
- Insolent dwarf.

261
00:27:45,664 --> 00:27:47,393
You know nothing.

262
00:27:50,903 --> 00:27:52,530
Throw it out.

263
00:27:55,508 --> 00:27:58,102
Throw... it out.

264
00:28:40,586 --> 00:28:43,316
Weak, am I?

265
00:28:48,894 --> 00:28:52,728
That Gyppo princess,
now that's good cunny.

266
00:28:52,765 --> 00:28:54,790
Her father's people
rode with Alexander.

267
00:28:54,834 --> 00:28:57,667
- You can't speak of her like that.
- She is, though,

268
00:28:57,703 --> 00:28:59,728
and she wants me badly.

269
00:29:01,774 --> 00:29:06,177
Should've seen her when
I done that Nubian. Wet as October!

270
00:29:07,713 --> 00:29:09,681
Pullo, look at me.

271
00:29:09,715 --> 00:29:11,307
She is a princess
of royal blood.

272
00:29:11,350 --> 00:29:12,817
You touch her,
you die.

273
00:29:12,852 --> 00:29:14,820
I'm not stupid.

274
00:29:14,854 --> 00:29:16,583
I'm just saying
she wants me.

275
00:29:55,261 --> 00:29:57,923
Lovely. Lovely.

276
00:29:57,963 --> 00:30:00,989
Nothing like cold,
stinking sweat to seduce a man.

277
00:30:02,368 --> 00:30:04,893
Caesar will think himself
on Olympus with Aphrodite.

278
00:30:04,937 --> 00:30:07,428
Hush, piglet!

279
00:30:08,774 --> 00:30:12,471
What do you know
of seduction?

280
00:30:12,511 --> 00:30:15,207
As long as Caesar
is a man,

281
00:30:15,247 --> 00:30:17,215
I will have him.

282
00:30:17,249 --> 00:30:20,707
She seems very
sure of herself.

283
00:30:20,753 --> 00:30:24,416
I have him...
or I die.

284
00:30:26,058 --> 00:30:28,356
So I will have him.

285
00:30:28,394 --> 00:30:30,988
May it be so, Isis.

286
00:30:48,814 --> 00:30:51,749
I only wish
he were here today.

287
00:30:51,784 --> 00:30:55,584
My womb is
between the flood.

288
00:30:57,456 --> 00:31:01,586
A child would come
as sure as spring.

289
00:31:28,988 --> 00:31:30,751
Come.

290
00:31:32,791 --> 00:31:34,258
You, come.

291
00:31:48,307 --> 00:31:50,400
Ahh-ooh...

292
00:31:50,442 --> 00:31:52,706
So red!

293
00:31:52,745 --> 00:31:54,838
Your Highness, how can
I be of service?

294
00:31:59,385 --> 00:32:03,344
Leather. Olives.
Not so bad.

295
00:32:08,460 --> 00:32:13,227
- He will do.
- Majesty commands you will enter her.

296
00:32:13,265 --> 00:32:15,233
I do not understand.

297
00:32:15,267 --> 00:32:18,168
You have coitus with her.

298
00:32:18,203 --> 00:32:21,297
You have it wrong.
Coitus means to make babies.

299
00:32:21,340 --> 00:32:23,831
Exact!
So, make babies.

300
00:32:29,014 --> 00:32:31,312
Don't be scared.

301
00:32:31,350 --> 00:32:35,013
I'm not scared, I just
cannot do what you ask!

302
00:32:35,054 --> 00:32:38,023
It is not...
it is not in our custom.

303
00:32:38,057 --> 00:32:42,050
Roman men are not used
by women in this way.

304
00:32:42,094 --> 00:32:44,927
Come, you will enjoy it.

305
00:32:44,963 --> 00:32:47,523
My queen is
an excellent lover.

306
00:33:18,597 --> 00:33:20,656
What is he waiting for?

307
00:33:23,202 --> 00:33:25,033
He must do
as he is told!

308
00:33:26,105 --> 00:33:28,039
- Let me give you a hand.
- Get off!

309
00:33:28,073 --> 00:33:32,567
I must ask forgiveness of
Your Majesty, but I cannot comply!

310
00:33:32,611 --> 00:33:34,841
I am no slave
to be commanded so!

311
00:33:34,880 --> 00:33:38,543
- With all respect...
- He refuses?

312
00:33:40,018 --> 00:33:44,955
This... insect
refuses me?!

313
00:33:44,990 --> 00:33:48,619
You dare refuse
the daughter of a sun god?

314
00:33:51,330 --> 00:33:55,323
Pullo, report immediately to
Princess Cleopatra and do as she says!

315
00:33:55,367 --> 00:33:57,335
- Eh?
- You heard!

316
00:33:57,369 --> 00:34:00,532
- What's going on?
- Just go.

317
00:34:13,552 --> 00:34:16,544
Legionary Titus Pullo
reporting for duty, ma'am.

318
00:35:27,626 --> 00:35:29,856
Whooh.

319
00:35:33,131 --> 00:35:36,259
- Gods, that was something...
- I don't want to know.

320
00:35:36,301 --> 00:35:41,136
If you value your life,
you won't speak of it again.

321
00:35:41,173 --> 00:35:45,735
Why? I was only obeying orders.
Bloody good orders, too.

322
00:35:45,777 --> 00:35:48,211
What do you think Caesar
will do if he hears of it?

323
00:35:49,848 --> 00:35:52,817
I'm not stupid.

324
00:35:52,851 --> 00:35:55,649
I promised the princess.
I shall not speak of it.

325
00:35:55,687 --> 00:35:57,848
You can't keep a secret
to save your life.

326
00:35:57,889 --> 00:36:00,483
You've got a mouth
like a drain.

327
00:36:00,525 --> 00:36:02,459
Whooh.

328
00:36:48,307 --> 00:36:50,070
Princess Cleopatra, sir.

329
00:36:50,108 --> 00:36:52,474
Daughter of
the Two Rams,

330
00:36:52,511 --> 00:36:54,809
mistress of
sedge and bee!

331
00:37:37,556 --> 00:37:39,183
Oh!

332
00:37:39,224 --> 00:37:41,556
Well done, Majesty!

333
00:37:41,593 --> 00:37:43,083
Oh!
Thank you.

334
00:38:30,409 --> 00:38:34,470
Is something wrong,
little husband?

335
00:38:49,161 --> 00:38:53,461
How funny you look
in Father's chair.

336
00:38:53,498 --> 00:38:56,763
- I never wanted to harm you.
- Shh.

337
00:38:56,802 --> 00:38:59,999
Of course you did not.

338
00:39:00,038 --> 00:39:04,975
It was your gelding
led you astray, no doubt.

339
00:39:05,010 --> 00:39:08,104
- Mistress...
- It must not speak.

340
00:39:10,882 --> 00:39:12,509
It must die!

341
00:39:28,467 --> 00:39:30,025
It was him...

342
00:39:32,437 --> 00:39:34,302
not me.

343
00:39:35,440 --> 00:39:38,500
He led him astray,

344
00:39:38,543 --> 00:39:40,511
not me.

345
00:39:40,545 --> 00:39:43,571
It was him!

346
00:40:33,365 --> 00:40:35,526
Get in formation!

347
00:40:42,974 --> 00:40:45,204
And you, Pullo.

348
00:40:52,484 --> 00:40:54,850
Calpurnia...

349
00:40:58,757 --> 00:41:01,555
She's your third wife?

350
00:41:01,593 --> 00:41:03,925
She is.

351
00:41:08,366 --> 00:41:10,994
Has she given you a son?

352
00:41:11,036 --> 00:41:13,231
She has not.

353
00:41:14,940 --> 00:41:17,340
How sad.

354
00:41:17,375 --> 00:41:21,835
A man without sons is
a man without a future.

355
00:41:21,880 --> 00:41:24,348
I never thought
of it that way.

356
00:41:27,052 --> 00:41:29,782
Sad.

357
00:41:29,821 --> 00:41:31,880
Never mind.

358
00:41:33,558 --> 00:41:36,755
Have you secured
the upriver ports?

359
00:41:36,795 --> 00:41:39,491
You must do so
immediately.

360
00:41:39,531 --> 00:41:43,092
Whoever controls
the ports controls Egypt.

361
00:41:45,403 --> 00:41:48,031
Good advice, no doubt,

362
00:41:48,073 --> 00:41:51,099
- if I wanted to control Egypt.
- Of course you do.

363
00:41:52,110 --> 00:41:54,078
Why else are you here?

364
00:41:54,112 --> 00:41:58,549
And why save me so
heroically from death...

365
00:41:58,583 --> 00:42:02,280
if not to use me as your...

366
00:42:02,320 --> 00:42:04,880
puppet queen?

367
00:42:08,627 --> 00:42:10,595
Do you dislike
the notion?

368
00:42:10,629 --> 00:42:13,723
My wishes
are immaterial.

369
00:42:14,833 --> 00:42:18,234
You redeemed me
from captivity.

370
00:42:18,269 --> 00:42:21,568
I am your slave.

371
00:44:53,558 --> 00:44:55,753
Testudo!

372
00:45:38,536 --> 00:45:40,504
- Are you well?
- Well enough,

373
00:45:40,538 --> 00:45:42,733
though I do not sleep.

374
00:45:42,774 --> 00:45:45,334
I write very bad poetry
through the night

375
00:45:45,376 --> 00:45:48,539
and in the morning I give it
to the cook to stoke the kitchen fire.

376
00:45:48,580 --> 00:45:50,070
It's a form of magic.

377
00:45:50,114 --> 00:45:53,572
My ill conscience
is transformed into

378
00:45:53,618 --> 00:45:55,586
roast birds
and pastries.

379
00:45:55,620 --> 00:45:58,350
You should have
no ill conscience.

380
00:45:58,389 --> 00:46:01,051
We only did what
we had to do.

381
00:46:01,092 --> 00:46:04,892
No doubt Saturn said something
of the sort after eating his children.

382
00:46:06,564 --> 00:46:09,499
The question is...

383
00:46:09,534 --> 00:46:12,002
if Caesar does not
return from Egypt...

384
00:46:12,036 --> 00:46:14,266
Oh, Caesar has escaped
tighter traps than this.

385
00:46:14,305 --> 00:46:18,036
He has been besieged in
Alexandria the better part of a year.

386
00:46:18,076 --> 00:46:20,169
Perhaps his luck
has run out.

387
00:46:20,211 --> 00:46:22,736
Well, what fools
we shall look

388
00:46:22,780 --> 00:46:26,045
if we have kissed
the feet of a dead man.

389
00:46:26,084 --> 00:46:30,077
With Caesar dead,
that bastard Marc Antony

390
00:46:30,121 --> 00:46:32,089
will be unleashed
to do as he wants.

391
00:46:32,123 --> 00:46:35,957
Very likely, but it isn't
a concern of mine.

392
00:46:35,994 --> 00:46:37,859
I am done with politics.

393
00:46:37,896 --> 00:46:40,364
Self-pity is
all very well.

394
00:46:40,398 --> 00:46:44,129
I'm not unashamed myself.

395
00:46:44,168 --> 00:46:47,228
But we are still senators.

396
00:46:47,272 --> 00:46:49,706
We have responsibilities.

397
00:46:49,741 --> 00:46:52,369
I remind you we swore
an oath of loyalty.

398
00:46:52,410 --> 00:46:55,504
To Caesar,
not to Antony.

399
00:46:57,248 --> 00:47:01,014
Cato and Scipio have
raised an army in Numidia.

400
00:47:01,052 --> 00:47:03,020
If we were to
communicate with them,

401
00:47:03,054 --> 00:47:05,022
we might... we might...

402
00:47:05,056 --> 00:47:08,150
If it isn't Cicero.

403
00:47:08,192 --> 00:47:12,720
How strange. I was just
now thinking of you.

404
00:47:14,065 --> 00:47:16,033
I've received
some happy news,

405
00:47:16,067 --> 00:47:18,763
and my first thought was
to come and tell you two.

406
00:47:21,005 --> 00:47:22,768
And here you are.

407
00:47:24,742 --> 00:47:26,710
What a coincidence!

408
00:47:26,744 --> 00:47:30,339
It's amusing how often
that happens, eh?

409
00:47:30,381 --> 00:47:32,349
So I was walking
across the Forum

410
00:47:32,383 --> 00:47:34,317
and thinking of
this particular woman,

411
00:47:34,352 --> 00:47:36,081
who should arrive
right in front of me

412
00:47:36,120 --> 00:47:38,020
but the thing herself.

413
00:47:39,290 --> 00:47:41,815
Savage little
Spanish creature.

414
00:47:41,859 --> 00:47:44,191
Hair down
to her ass. Huh!

415
00:47:49,467 --> 00:47:51,492
Everyone misjudges me,
you know.

416
00:47:53,071 --> 00:47:55,198
I'm a merciful man.

417
00:47:55,239 --> 00:47:57,207
I know that's not
my reputation,

418
00:47:57,241 --> 00:47:59,038
but I am.

419
00:48:01,012 --> 00:48:03,947
Now, everyone's entitled
to a few mistakes.

420
00:48:03,982 --> 00:48:08,817
Gods know, I made
one or two myself.

421
00:48:08,853 --> 00:48:11,447
I've done things...

422
00:48:12,623 --> 00:48:16,684
things I'm ashamed
to think of.

423
00:48:19,764 --> 00:48:24,030
We are, all of us,
imperfect in our way.

424
00:48:24,068 --> 00:48:25,968
Exactly.

425
00:48:26,004 --> 00:48:29,872
We are, all of us,
imperfect.

426
00:48:35,079 --> 00:48:37,877
Give me your hands,
brother Cicero.

427
00:48:42,720 --> 00:48:45,917
With all my heart...

428
00:48:45,957 --> 00:48:47,447
I forgive you.

429
00:48:48,493 --> 00:48:50,358
I don't know
what you mean.

430
00:48:53,631 --> 00:48:55,758
Nothing escapes me.

431
00:48:57,502 --> 00:49:02,098
If a pigeon dies on
the Avantine, I hear of it.

432
00:49:04,976 --> 00:49:09,140
So be assured,
brother, if I ever again...

433
00:49:09,180 --> 00:49:12,980
hear your name connected

434
00:49:13,017 --> 00:49:15,815
with murmurs
of treachery...

435
00:49:21,526 --> 00:49:23,494
I will cut off

436
00:49:23,528 --> 00:49:27,726
these soft, pink hands,

437
00:49:27,765 --> 00:49:31,792
and nail them
to the Senate door.

438
00:49:49,854 --> 00:49:51,981
- Antony?
- Hmm?

439
00:49:52,023 --> 00:49:54,685
You said you had
happy news to tell us.

440
00:49:54,725 --> 00:49:57,523
Oh. Yes.
Of course.

441
00:49:57,562 --> 00:50:00,497
A courier came
from Alexandria.

442
00:50:01,532 --> 00:50:03,329
Caesar has
lifted the siege

443
00:50:03,367 --> 00:50:05,130
and massacred
the armies of Ptolemy.

444
00:50:05,169 --> 00:50:08,070
He is safe and sound,

445
00:50:08,106 --> 00:50:10,301
and master of all Egypt.

446
00:50:14,579 --> 00:50:16,945
The man is
a damn prodigy, eh?

447
00:50:35,266 --> 00:50:37,700
Atten-hut!

448
00:51:11,569 --> 00:51:14,766
Hail Caesar!

