1
00:02:02,038 --> 00:02:03,972
We should go.

2
00:02:04,007 --> 00:02:06,339
Night is coming.

3
00:02:06,376 --> 00:02:09,209
They sleep
standing up, you know.

4
00:02:10,781 --> 00:02:12,715
Elephants.

5
00:02:14,117 --> 00:02:18,577
On account once laid down,
they cannot rise again.

6
00:02:18,622 --> 00:02:20,419
Is that so?

7
00:02:21,758 --> 00:02:23,589
I was not aware.

8
00:02:34,337 --> 00:02:35,998
We should go.

9
00:02:36,039 --> 00:02:38,166
Where?

10
00:02:39,476 --> 00:02:41,637
Utica is not far.

11
00:02:41,678 --> 00:02:43,839
Utica.

12
00:02:45,015 --> 00:02:47,210
What's there for us?

13
00:02:47,250 --> 00:02:50,686
Shelter. Food.

14
00:02:50,720 --> 00:02:52,711
I need neither.

15
00:02:54,357 --> 00:02:56,086
Sleep, then.

16
00:02:56,126 --> 00:02:58,321
Sleep would be pleasant.

17
00:03:02,499 --> 00:03:04,490
So...

18
00:03:05,569 --> 00:03:07,867
Utica then.

19
00:03:55,719 --> 00:03:58,153
Dear me.

20
00:03:58,188 --> 00:04:00,986
Really, Aquinas, is this
the best we can do?

21
00:04:01,024 --> 00:04:04,187
No matter.
No matter.

22
00:04:04,227 --> 00:04:06,627
Bring water
for washing.

23
00:04:06,663 --> 00:04:09,188
And bread...
and wine.

24
00:04:14,137 --> 00:04:16,628
I think I shall make
myself drunk tonight.

25
00:04:16,673 --> 00:04:19,039
Perhaps just this once
you will join me.

26
00:04:19,075 --> 00:04:21,339
I think not.

27
00:04:22,646 --> 00:04:24,876
Cheer up.
We live.

28
00:04:24,915 --> 00:04:26,678
We do.
We live.

29
00:04:26,716 --> 00:04:28,707
And where there's life,
there's hope.

30
00:04:28,752 --> 00:04:31,050
I'm afraid if we have
done anything, old friend,

31
00:04:31,087 --> 00:04:33,521
we've disproved
that proverb.

32
00:04:33,556 --> 00:04:36,218
Aquinas, this bread
is stubborn.

33
00:04:36,259 --> 00:04:38,056
Give me your knife.

34
00:04:41,498 --> 00:04:43,261
Scipio...

35
00:04:44,401 --> 00:04:47,029
you have
a tolerant spirit.

36
00:04:47,070 --> 00:04:49,800
If you can,
you should...

37
00:04:49,839 --> 00:04:52,171
make your peace
with Caesar.

38
00:04:52,208 --> 00:04:54,642
Oh, I don't know about that.
I shall do whatever you do.

39
00:04:54,678 --> 00:04:56,236
I wouldn't do that.

40
00:04:57,847 --> 00:05:00,839
- Go your own way.
- In any case, let's not discuss it now.

41
00:05:00,884 --> 00:05:03,079
There'll be plenty of time
for such sad talk.

42
00:05:03,119 --> 00:05:06,054
If you'll excuse me.

43
00:05:06,089 --> 00:05:08,557
I need to urinate.

44
00:05:08,591 --> 00:05:10,684
There's a pisspot
through there, I believe.

45
00:06:04,881 --> 00:06:07,611
Help! Help!

46
00:06:39,315 --> 00:06:41,044
Send them away.

47
00:06:57,233 --> 00:06:58,894
Do it now.

48
00:07:03,206 --> 00:07:04,639
Cut deep, boy.

49
00:07:06,476 --> 00:07:08,467
Goodbye, sir.

50
00:08:17,180 --> 00:08:19,045
We thank you so much.

51
00:08:19,082 --> 00:08:22,643
We hope you have enjoyed
our humble efforts

52
00:08:22,685 --> 00:08:25,654
on this happy day!

53
00:08:27,390 --> 00:08:32,327
Happy day on which our
glorious father has returned!

54
00:08:32,362 --> 00:08:36,628
Happy day on which
the Julian sun has risen

55
00:08:36,666 --> 00:08:40,625
and banished
Pompeian night forever!

56
00:08:41,738 --> 00:08:46,072
Happy day on which
our brave soldiers

57
00:08:46,109 --> 00:08:49,101
have come home
to their families!

58
00:08:49,145 --> 00:08:52,706
Happy day!

59
00:09:03,359 --> 00:09:05,350
- Salve.
- Welcome back.

60
00:09:30,687 --> 00:09:33,815
- Are you home for good now?
- I am. I am.

61
00:09:33,856 --> 00:09:35,824
No more soldiering for me.

62
00:10:22,572 --> 00:10:24,233
Bona Dea.

63
00:10:24,274 --> 00:10:26,538
It's nice, isn't it?

64
00:10:27,543 --> 00:10:29,170
It is.

65
00:10:31,514 --> 00:10:35,006
- Who are these?
- I bought them last year.

66
00:10:36,185 --> 00:10:38,119
Four slaves we have now?

67
00:10:38,154 --> 00:10:40,179
They were a good price.

68
00:10:40,223 --> 00:10:42,191
On a soldier's wage?

69
00:10:43,626 --> 00:10:46,686
The butcher shop paid
for them with plenty to spare.

70
00:10:46,729 --> 00:10:48,321
The butcher shop?

71
00:10:48,364 --> 00:10:50,924
Me and Lyde have made
a nice business out of it.

72
00:10:50,967 --> 00:10:53,595
Five hundred head
a week sometimes.

73
00:10:53,636 --> 00:10:58,096
Pigs mostly, but some sheep
and cows for the religious trade.

74
00:11:12,322 --> 00:11:15,655
Eirene!

75
00:11:18,094 --> 00:11:21,120
- It's very good to see you.
- It's good to see you too, master.

76
00:11:21,164 --> 00:11:23,724
- You speak our words!
- If it pleases you.

77
00:11:23,766 --> 00:11:25,996
Oh, it does.
Of course it does.

78
00:11:29,138 --> 00:11:30,696
Can I get you anything?

79
00:11:30,740 --> 00:11:32,503
A bit of water
would be nice.

80
00:11:37,413 --> 00:11:38,903
Ah!

81
00:11:47,824 --> 00:11:49,815
I brought you something.

82
00:11:57,834 --> 00:12:00,598
Here, let me.

83
00:12:07,443 --> 00:12:09,001
Lovely.

84
00:12:12,949 --> 00:12:16,077
"Parentalia begins
on the Ides.

85
00:12:16,119 --> 00:12:18,087
Temples will be shut,

86
00:12:18,121 --> 00:12:20,214
and no wherein
celebrated.

87
00:12:20,256 --> 00:12:24,022
Public festivals shall be
at the fifth hour in the circus.

88
00:12:24,060 --> 00:12:26,961
Wine to be provided
by the Capitoline fraternity,

89
00:12:26,996 --> 00:12:30,432
and cakes by
the Guild of Millers.

90
00:12:30,466 --> 00:12:33,526
The Guild of Millers uses
only the finest grains...

91
00:12:33,569 --> 00:12:37,665
True Roman bread,
for true Romans."

92
00:12:44,147 --> 00:12:46,615
The fat old bitch
herself eh?

93
00:12:46,649 --> 00:12:49,140
Must be good
to be home.

94
00:12:50,920 --> 00:12:52,945
What is it, two years
you've been gone?

95
00:12:54,290 --> 00:12:56,520
Are you still
fucking my mother?

96
00:12:58,561 --> 00:12:59,687
When she'll have me.

97
00:12:59,729 --> 00:13:02,027
That would explain
your excessive familiarity.

98
00:13:03,699 --> 00:13:05,792
- Excuse me.
- That's all right.

99
00:13:05,835 --> 00:13:09,168
I was merely curious,
and you're correct.

100
00:13:09,205 --> 00:13:11,264
It does feel good
to be home.

101
00:13:27,924 --> 00:13:30,085
My darling boy.

102
00:13:30,126 --> 00:13:32,219
Oh!

103
00:13:34,197 --> 00:13:35,926
So handsome.

104
00:13:37,467 --> 00:13:39,867
- Sister, I hope you're well.
- Let me hug you.

105
00:13:43,039 --> 00:13:44,939
Come inside and wash.

106
00:13:44,974 --> 00:13:47,534
Let's get rid of the stink
of horse off you.

107
00:13:47,577 --> 00:13:51,707
Timon, I'll, uh...
see you later.

108
00:13:57,220 --> 00:14:00,189
Please, Mother,
we will be late.

109
00:14:00,223 --> 00:14:03,624
Oh, we must not be late.
That would never do.

110
00:14:03,659 --> 00:14:06,560
I do not want to go to dinner
any more than you do,

111
00:14:06,596 --> 00:14:08,860
but Caesar has treated me
extremely well,

112
00:14:08,898 --> 00:14:10,729
and we must go if asked.

113
00:14:10,766 --> 00:14:12,734
- Honor demands...
- Honor?

114
00:14:12,768 --> 00:14:15,532
- Honor.
- Not honor then,

115
00:14:15,571 --> 00:14:17,300
common sense.

116
00:14:17,340 --> 00:14:20,002
I cannot ask mercy
of Caesar,

117
00:14:20,042 --> 00:14:22,101
accept rank
and favor from him,

118
00:14:22,144 --> 00:14:23,839
and then refuse
his friendship.

119
00:14:23,880 --> 00:14:27,441
What sort of man asks
for mercy in the first place?

120
00:14:27,483 --> 00:14:30,145
I assure you, Mother,

121
00:14:30,186 --> 00:14:32,620
I am not proud
of myself.

122
00:14:32,655 --> 00:14:35,146
I am not proud at all.

123
00:14:35,191 --> 00:14:37,250
In lieu
of a noble suicide,

124
00:14:37,293 --> 00:14:39,659
you shall have to
be content with that.

125
00:14:43,633 --> 00:14:45,897
Bring me my shawl.

126
00:14:45,935 --> 00:14:47,664
Please, do not come.

127
00:14:47,703 --> 00:14:50,069
I shall make
your excuses to Atia.

128
00:14:50,106 --> 00:14:52,506
Certainly not.
I will go.

129
00:14:52,542 --> 00:14:55,636
Not to be there
would be seen as weakness.

130
00:15:05,821 --> 00:15:08,187
Perhaps it will
do you good to see him.

131
00:15:09,225 --> 00:15:11,591
See that he is
just a man.

132
00:15:12,828 --> 00:15:15,319
The loss of his affection
is not worth

133
00:15:15,364 --> 00:15:17,662
this endless
raging sorrow.

134
00:15:17,700 --> 00:15:20,032
I feel neither
rage nor sorrow.

135
00:15:20,069 --> 00:15:23,971
My objection to Caesar
is purely political,

136
00:15:24,006 --> 00:15:26,440
not personal.

137
00:15:28,344 --> 00:15:30,141
The Pontic troops
ran so fast

138
00:15:30,179 --> 00:15:32,147
I don't know
if they ever stopped.

139
00:15:32,181 --> 00:15:34,649
It is no wonder Pompey
took Pontius so readily.

140
00:15:34,684 --> 00:15:36,515
A child with a stick
might have done so.

141
00:15:36,552 --> 00:15:39,453
What next, sir?
Germany perhaps?

142
00:15:39,488 --> 00:15:42,753
I'm afraid I must put on
a triumph this next month,

143
00:15:42,792 --> 00:15:45,056
and they're damnable
beasts to organize.

144
00:15:45,094 --> 00:15:47,392
Still, the people
love a good parade

145
00:15:47,430 --> 00:15:49,057
and we must not
disappoint them.

146
00:15:49,098 --> 00:15:51,498
How lovely to see you both.

147
00:15:51,534 --> 00:15:54,799
- It's been far too long.
- We are joyful to be here.

148
00:15:54,837 --> 00:15:57,806
- Joyful, indeed.
- Is this a mourning shawl?

149
00:15:57,840 --> 00:16:00,673
It's very pretty.
Has someone died?

150
00:16:00,710 --> 00:16:02,974
A great many have died.

151
00:16:03,012 --> 00:16:05,572
How true.
But it's all over now,

152
00:16:05,615 --> 00:16:07,344
and we're
still alive, neh?

153
00:16:07,383 --> 00:16:09,943
It's not possible.
Octavian?

154
00:16:11,187 --> 00:16:14,987
Gods, you make me
feel old.

155
00:16:16,492 --> 00:16:18,255
Come.

156
00:16:29,538 --> 00:16:31,506
It is the height
of four men,

157
00:16:31,540 --> 00:16:33,371
with a long neck
like a goose,

158
00:16:33,409 --> 00:16:36,537
spots like a leopard,
and the speed of a horse.

159
00:16:36,579 --> 00:16:39,104
I don't believe it.
A new Chimera.

160
00:16:39,148 --> 00:16:40,979
I assure you,
it is quite real.

161
00:16:41,017 --> 00:16:42,712
With any luck, you may
see one at my triumph.

162
00:16:42,752 --> 00:16:44,720
I have been trying to bring
one over for months now,

163
00:16:44,754 --> 00:16:46,722
but the wretched creatures
keep dying on the way here.

164
00:16:46,756 --> 00:16:49,554
- They do not like the sea.
- It all sounds very tiring.

165
00:16:49,592 --> 00:16:51,856
After this
infernal triumph is done

166
00:16:51,894 --> 00:16:55,193
- you must go to the country and relax.
- I should like that,

167
00:16:55,231 --> 00:16:57,131
but then my work
begins in earnest.

168
00:16:57,166 --> 00:16:59,600
I must set about putting
the Republic to rights.

169
00:16:59,635 --> 00:17:03,366
Splendid notion. How shall
you proceed, do you suppose?

170
00:17:03,406 --> 00:17:07,035
I have a few ideas,
but I am open to suggestion.

171
00:17:07,076 --> 00:17:10,341
Yesterday, I saw Malchio
the baker in a litter.

172
00:17:10,379 --> 00:17:12,939
A baker! I'd put a stop
to that sort of thing immediately.

173
00:17:12,982 --> 00:17:14,711
I shall have it
looked into.

174
00:17:14,750 --> 00:17:16,547
- Octavian?
- Hmm?

175
00:17:16,585 --> 00:17:18,917
How would you proceed,
were you me?

176
00:17:18,954 --> 00:17:22,321
- Uh, proceed with?
- Putting the Republic to rights.

177
00:17:22,358 --> 00:17:25,225
Ah. Um...

178
00:17:25,261 --> 00:17:27,559
how to proceed.

179
00:17:27,596 --> 00:17:30,588
I would start a large program
of public works...

180
00:17:30,633 --> 00:17:33,067
employ citizens
and free men,

181
00:17:33,102 --> 00:17:35,502
repair the aqueducts,
levee the river... that sort of thing.

182
00:17:35,538 --> 00:17:37,972
I would create at least
100 or so new senators,

183
00:17:38,007 --> 00:17:40,703
that I could be sure were my creatures
rather than my secret enemies.

184
00:17:40,743 --> 00:17:42,506
What is your point,
Octavian?

185
00:17:42,545 --> 00:17:44,775
I did not mean you, Brutus,
you're a man of honor.

186
00:17:44,814 --> 00:17:46,805
I believe that your
capitulation is sincere.

187
00:17:46,849 --> 00:17:48,111
How nice of you
to say so.

188
00:17:48,150 --> 00:17:49,913
I just had a thought.

189
00:17:49,952 --> 00:17:53,410
Did not your man
Aelius Siculus die recently?

190
00:17:53,456 --> 00:17:56,323
I'm afraid he did.
In Thapsus, in fact.

191
00:17:56,358 --> 00:17:59,816
Just so. You shall take his seat
at the pontiff's table.

192
00:17:59,862 --> 00:18:01,830
Pontiff? So young?

193
00:18:01,864 --> 00:18:03,491
I was not so much older

194
00:18:03,532 --> 00:18:06,000
- when I entered the college.
- Very true, but...

195
00:18:06,035 --> 00:18:07,662
I believe I have
the authority

196
00:18:07,703 --> 00:18:09,432
- to appoint whom I like.
- Indeed, yes.

197
00:18:09,472 --> 00:18:11,838
This is a great honor.
Kiss your uncle's hand.

198
00:18:11,874 --> 00:18:14,775
I kiss your hand, Uncle,
but truly I would make an ill pontiff.

199
00:18:14,810 --> 00:18:17,040
Don't be ridiculous.
You'll make a lovely pontiff.

200
00:18:17,079 --> 00:18:18,979
You'll see to it, right?

201
00:18:19,014 --> 00:18:21,642
I had rather thought to concentrate
on my poetry for a while.

202
00:18:21,684 --> 00:18:24,517
- He'll make a lovely pontiff.
- Poetry can wait.

203
00:18:24,553 --> 00:18:26,714
It should not wait
too long.

204
00:18:26,756 --> 00:18:29,725
Poetry is
a young man's calling...

205
00:18:29,759 --> 00:18:31,522
don't you think?

206
00:18:42,671 --> 00:18:46,232
There's us with the walls
of Thapsus at our backs

207
00:18:46,275 --> 00:18:48,470
and your father
was just here.

208
00:18:48,511 --> 00:18:50,638
Now coming towards
us on the plain

209
00:18:50,679 --> 00:18:53,614
with all their
legions, cavalry

210
00:18:53,649 --> 00:18:57,050
and 900 war elephants,

211
00:18:57,086 --> 00:18:59,145
Scipio and Juno.

212
00:18:59,188 --> 00:19:03,022
"Hold fast," says General Caesar,
"let the bastards come!"

213
00:19:03,058 --> 00:19:04,992
- I'll do it.
- Please, don't, master.

214
00:19:05,027 --> 00:19:07,120
This is my work.
Lady will be angry.

215
00:19:07,163 --> 00:19:08,960
Who's master, eh?

216
00:19:08,998 --> 00:19:11,899
...ballistas on the city walls,
and the front line thinks

217
00:19:11,934 --> 00:19:14,903
they've heard the order to advance,
so before the officers can stop it,

218
00:19:14,937 --> 00:19:17,838
the whole fucking army charges
on Scipio's men double tempo.

219
00:19:17,873 --> 00:19:19,363
Now, the elephants...

220
00:19:19,408 --> 00:19:22,002
elephants see us
come running and screaming

221
00:19:22,044 --> 00:19:24,877
and they turn tail and charge
on their own lines...

222
00:19:24,914 --> 00:19:26,711
boom! Chaos!

223
00:19:28,484 --> 00:19:30,850
Oh, don't cry,
it was just a game.

224
00:19:32,988 --> 00:19:36,583
You must be bored,
sitting around here all day.

225
00:19:36,625 --> 00:19:38,559
I don't mind it.

226
00:19:38,594 --> 00:19:41,859
- You've been discharged a month.
- I know.

227
00:19:41,897 --> 00:19:45,458
I mean, there's no hurry. We're
all right for money and everything...

228
00:19:45,501 --> 00:19:47,492
But I can't be loafing
around here forever.

229
00:19:48,971 --> 00:19:51,303
So you don't want to take up
the butchering trade?

230
00:19:51,340 --> 00:19:52,705
Shopkeeping?!

231
00:19:52,741 --> 00:19:56,006
It will give you
something to do.

232
00:20:14,029 --> 00:20:16,497
This is fine work
for a prefect, eh?

233
00:20:16,532 --> 00:20:19,194
- Smells like old times.
- It does that.

234
00:20:19,235 --> 00:20:20,896
You remember that little
siege at Avaricum?

235
00:20:20,936 --> 00:20:22,927
You'll not learn a trade
sitting on your pugas.

236
00:20:22,972 --> 00:20:24,837
There's plenty more
carcasses to be hung.

237
00:20:39,021 --> 00:20:40,818
Tomorrow! You'll have
your money tomorrow!

238
00:20:40,856 --> 00:20:43,757
- Let's take his nose off.
- No, not me no...

239
00:20:43,792 --> 00:20:45,350
- Don't... don't fuss.
- Hey, stop that!

240
00:20:47,596 --> 00:20:49,325
Take your business
elsewhere.

241
00:20:49,365 --> 00:20:51,526
- What's it to you, you bastard?
- It's bad for trade.

242
00:20:51,567 --> 00:20:53,228
And who the fuck are you,
little man?

243
00:20:53,269 --> 00:20:55,100
- I am Lucius Vorenus,
- I know you.

244
00:20:55,137 --> 00:20:59,005
Soldier boy, isn't it?
Up by the dyeworks, tasty wife.

245
00:20:59,041 --> 00:21:00,633
Do not speak of my wife.

246
00:21:00,676 --> 00:21:02,644
Get gone.
That's an order.

247
00:21:02,678 --> 00:21:04,475
No no no. Orders?
Orders? No no no.

248
00:21:04,513 --> 00:21:07,778
You're not a soldier now.
You're a fucking shopkeeper's clerk.

249
00:21:11,820 --> 00:21:15,017
- You're dead, you are.
- Walk away now

250
00:21:15,057 --> 00:21:17,855
and do not let me see you
on this street again.

251
00:21:19,194 --> 00:21:22,357
Both of you...
dead.

252
00:21:33,108 --> 00:21:34,905
Get back
to your business.

253
00:21:37,179 --> 00:21:38,737
You shouldn't
have done that.

254
00:21:38,781 --> 00:21:41,409
Those were
Erastes Fulmen's people.

255
00:21:41,450 --> 00:21:43,315
He won't take disrespect
like that.

256
00:21:43,352 --> 00:21:46,753
- You hit him.
- It was nothing.

257
00:21:46,789 --> 00:21:49,724
Erastes Fulmen
will kill you.

258
00:21:49,758 --> 00:21:52,693
- He's just a crook.
- He used to be.

259
00:21:52,728 --> 00:21:55,162
Since Pompey's gangs left
he's had the run of the hill.

260
00:21:55,197 --> 00:21:57,222
He's a big man now.

261
00:21:57,266 --> 00:21:59,029
He kills whoever he wants!

262
00:21:59,068 --> 00:22:00,558
I'm no prole
to be abused!

263
00:22:00,602 --> 00:22:03,435
I was prefect
in the Evocati!

264
00:22:03,472 --> 00:22:05,770
Caesar himself
gave me a horse.

265
00:22:17,586 --> 00:22:18,917
Thank you, sir.

266
00:22:31,166 --> 00:22:34,465
I hope that dinner was
not too painful for you.

267
00:22:34,503 --> 00:22:38,963
Oh, I'm used to pain.
I don't mind it.

268
00:22:45,347 --> 00:22:47,815
I wish you didn't care
for him so much.

269
00:22:49,718 --> 00:22:52,744
I wish I didn't care
for you so much.

270
00:22:52,788 --> 00:22:54,847
Stop.

271
00:23:12,107 --> 00:23:15,941
That brother of yours
has become quite the pretty man.

272
00:23:15,978 --> 00:23:18,208
Caesar seems
very fond of him.

273
00:23:18,247 --> 00:23:19,874
Very much.

274
00:23:21,517 --> 00:23:23,712
Mother claims Caesar
took him for a lover.

275
00:23:23,752 --> 00:23:25,344
Really?

276
00:23:25,387 --> 00:23:28,788
The cook said she heard them
going at it in a closet.

277
00:23:28,824 --> 00:23:31,156
Octavian insisted
it was not so.

278
00:23:31,193 --> 00:23:33,161
He said the noises
she heard were

279
00:23:33,195 --> 00:23:35,186
some terrible affliction
of Caesar's.

280
00:23:35,230 --> 00:23:37,892
Mother wouldn't have it.
Once she gets an idea...

281
00:23:37,933 --> 00:23:39,662
Affliction?
What affliction?

282
00:23:41,136 --> 00:23:43,798
- I don't know.
- Did he not say?

283
00:23:43,839 --> 00:23:46,501
He was sworn to secrecy.

284
00:23:46,542 --> 00:23:49,136
But he said terrible?
He said terrible affliction?

285
00:23:50,746 --> 00:23:54,045
You must find out exactly
what this affliction is.

286
00:23:54,083 --> 00:23:55,812
You must find out
which god has cursed him.

287
00:23:55,851 --> 00:23:58,285
How can I do that?
It's a secret.

288
00:23:58,320 --> 00:24:01,016
You must find it out.
This is the weapon I seek.

289
00:24:01,056 --> 00:24:03,616
With the god's help,
I can destroy him.

290
00:24:03,659 --> 00:24:05,354
Please don't talk this way.

291
00:24:05,394 --> 00:24:06,725
Would you rather
I lied to you?

292
00:24:06,762 --> 00:24:08,889
I would rather that
you think of something

293
00:24:08,931 --> 00:24:11,092
other than the destruction
of my uncle.

294
00:24:14,002 --> 00:24:16,596
I have never lied to you.

295
00:24:16,638 --> 00:24:19,198
He still has
some terrible hold over me.

296
00:24:19,241 --> 00:24:23,405
I wish it were not so,
but he will not let go.

297
00:24:23,445 --> 00:24:26,414
Will you ask your brother?

298
00:24:30,452 --> 00:24:32,545
Would that make you happy?

299
00:24:32,588 --> 00:24:34,078
Yes, it would.

300
00:24:39,161 --> 00:24:41,254
What are you reading?

301
00:24:42,598 --> 00:24:45,499
A guide to the
interpretation of prodigies.

302
00:24:45,534 --> 00:24:48,094
Is it good?

303
00:24:48,137 --> 00:24:49,900
It's dull
beyond conception.

304
00:24:49,938 --> 00:24:53,567
If I am to be a pontiff, I must be familiar
with their ludicrous jargon.

305
00:24:53,609 --> 00:24:56,442
- Mustn't let down Uncle.
- Mustn't let down Uncle.

306
00:24:58,080 --> 00:25:00,071
I'm bored.

307
00:25:02,151 --> 00:25:05,450
- I could read to you.
- If you like.

308
00:25:06,622 --> 00:25:09,352
"Little sparrow,
my love is love,

309
00:25:09,391 --> 00:25:13,225
with whom she plays,
permits to lie within her lap,

310
00:25:13,262 --> 00:25:16,425
to nip her finger,
biting quickly with that bill,

311
00:25:16,465 --> 00:25:20,128
I should like to play with you as
she and soothe my troubled heart."

312
00:25:21,770 --> 00:25:24,762
- Very nice.
- You do not like it?

313
00:25:24,806 --> 00:25:27,104
No, you recite well,
but...

314
00:25:27,142 --> 00:25:29,474
I'm tired of poetry.

315
00:25:33,382 --> 00:25:36,249
- Tell me a secret.
- A secret?

316
00:25:36,285 --> 00:25:38,879
Something shocking
and dangerous that nobody knows.

317
00:25:38,921 --> 00:25:41,151
I don't know
any secrets like that.

318
00:25:46,728 --> 00:25:48,923
I know.

319
00:25:51,366 --> 00:25:55,234
What about Caesar
and his mysterious affliction?

320
00:25:57,906 --> 00:25:59,635
What affliction?

321
00:25:59,675 --> 00:26:02,007
Don't lie. The one
you told Mother about.

322
00:26:02,044 --> 00:26:05,673
Oh, it was nothing.
I was just making it up.

323
00:26:05,714 --> 00:26:08,478
- So you were lovers?
- Of course not.

324
00:26:08,517 --> 00:26:12,214
Either you were lovers, or some
god has cursed Caesar, which is it?

325
00:26:12,254 --> 00:26:14,848
- Sister, there are no gods.
- Don't be horrid.

326
00:26:14,890 --> 00:26:18,485
There is doubtless
a Prime Mover of some sort,

327
00:26:18,527 --> 00:26:21,860
but a community of beings that
look like us and meddle in our affairs?

328
00:26:21,897 --> 00:26:24,730
- Highly improbable.
- You don't trust me.

329
00:26:24,766 --> 00:26:26,791
I do trust you.
You are my dearest friend.

330
00:26:26,835 --> 00:26:28,962
- Then tell me!
- Why this in particular?

331
00:26:29,004 --> 00:26:30,869
Why do you care
if Caesar has an affliction?

332
00:26:30,906 --> 00:26:33,636
I don't care
the slightest bit.

333
00:26:33,675 --> 00:26:36,940
Only that it would be a terrible
secret and something worth hearing.

334
00:26:36,979 --> 00:26:40,142
And I doubt very much that
you have any terrible secrets

335
00:26:40,182 --> 00:26:41,809
of your own worth telling.

336
00:26:43,452 --> 00:26:45,852
- You'd be wrong.
- Oh please, like what?

337
00:26:50,559 --> 00:26:53,323
- I've tortured and killed a man.
- Liar.

338
00:26:53,362 --> 00:26:55,728
Do you remember
Lucius Vorenus?

339
00:26:55,764 --> 00:26:58,028
One of the soldiers
who rescued me in Gaul?

340
00:26:58,066 --> 00:26:59,829
- You killed him?
- Of course not.

341
00:26:59,868 --> 00:27:01,802
He has a wife
who deceived him.

342
00:27:01,837 --> 00:27:04,965
A child he thinks is
his daughter's son is in fact

343
00:27:05,007 --> 00:27:07,737
his wife's child
by a low half-Greek butcher.

344
00:27:07,776 --> 00:27:09,744
How sordid.

345
00:27:09,778 --> 00:27:14,147
It was the butcher I killed.
Helped kill, anyway.

346
00:27:15,150 --> 00:27:18,551
Oh. Bravo, I suppose.

347
00:27:18,587 --> 00:27:20,578
You asked
for a terrible secret.

348
00:27:34,369 --> 00:27:35,961
Try again.

349
00:27:43,478 --> 00:27:45,844
What?

350
00:27:45,881 --> 00:27:47,473
Get out of the way!

351
00:27:47,516 --> 00:27:51,577
Centurion!

352
00:27:52,587 --> 00:27:54,646
Lucius Vorenus!

353
00:27:57,392 --> 00:28:00,384
Lucius Vorenus!

354
00:28:03,498 --> 00:28:08,595
Niobe, looking
as lovely as ever.

355
00:28:08,637 --> 00:28:11,572
Phyllis sends
her best regards.

356
00:28:16,278 --> 00:28:17,939
Very pretty family
you have.

357
00:28:19,047 --> 00:28:21,743
It's good to see you
again after so long.

358
00:28:21,783 --> 00:28:25,446
So, back from the wars.

359
00:28:25,487 --> 00:28:27,921
Civilian life, eh?

360
00:28:27,956 --> 00:28:29,480
Must be hard to adjust.

361
00:28:29,524 --> 00:28:32,220
Different rules.

362
00:28:32,260 --> 00:28:34,854
Different fucking rules!

363
00:28:37,632 --> 00:28:40,726
My man Urbo here says
you slapped him in the face.

364
00:28:40,769 --> 00:28:43,067
- Did you do that?
- I did.

365
00:28:43,105 --> 00:28:46,563
Perfect example...
different rules.

366
00:28:46,608 --> 00:28:50,567
You see, I'm allowed
to chastise my people.

367
00:28:54,649 --> 00:28:57,812
Regular citizens like
you are not allowed to touch them.

368
00:28:57,853 --> 00:29:00,549
If someone does touch them,
they have to be punished.

369
00:29:00,589 --> 00:29:02,420
Rules.

370
00:29:02,457 --> 00:29:04,084
Get to your point.

371
00:29:04,126 --> 00:29:07,755
This is the second time
that Lucius Vorenus

372
00:29:07,796 --> 00:29:10,026
has shown me disrespect.

373
00:29:10,065 --> 00:29:12,124
Next market day
at noon,

374
00:29:12,167 --> 00:29:15,466
he will find me
in the Forum.

375
00:29:15,504 --> 00:29:17,972
He will kneel down
before me.

376
00:29:18,006 --> 00:29:21,908
He will kiss my feet
and he will apologize to me.

377
00:29:23,245 --> 00:29:26,009
If he does not do this,
I will come here and kill him.

378
00:29:27,416 --> 00:29:31,876
But before he dies, he will
see his wife and daughters raped.

379
00:29:31,920 --> 00:29:34,480
And then I will burn
down this building.

380
00:29:34,523 --> 00:29:36,388
Hold.

381
00:29:38,994 --> 00:29:40,962
- You've said your piece?
- I have.

382
00:29:40,996 --> 00:29:43,829
Then leave now.

383
00:29:43,865 --> 00:29:46,459
Good day to you.

384
00:29:58,914 --> 00:30:02,077
So the wife of this Lucius Vorenus
is a whore. What's that to me?

385
00:30:02,117 --> 00:30:04,950
I'm sorry,
that's all he told me.

386
00:30:04,986 --> 00:30:08,114
- He swears Caesar has no affliction.
- He's lying.

387
00:30:08,156 --> 00:30:09,214
Is it not enough then?

388
00:30:09,257 --> 00:30:11,589
If Caesar has
an affliction,

389
00:30:11,626 --> 00:30:14,254
he has it and suffers,
whether you know it or not.

390
00:30:14,296 --> 00:30:17,265
He suffers,
but he is not destroyed.

391
00:30:17,299 --> 00:30:19,790
You must go back to your
brother and get the truth from him.

392
00:30:19,835 --> 00:30:22,770
- How? I tried.
- Try again.

393
00:30:22,804 --> 00:30:25,170
Promise him something.

394
00:30:26,174 --> 00:30:28,802
You do have
something he wants.

395
00:30:31,880 --> 00:30:33,677
What do you mean?

396
00:30:33,715 --> 00:30:36,047
A young man will tell
his lover anything.

397
00:30:41,590 --> 00:30:43,455
You can't be serious.

398
00:30:43,492 --> 00:30:46,393
How can you...?

399
00:30:48,997 --> 00:30:50,521
You know he wants you.

400
00:30:50,565 --> 00:30:52,658
I would be betraying
my brother.

401
00:30:52,701 --> 00:30:54,965
I would be betraying
my family.

402
00:30:55,003 --> 00:30:57,528
Your family is a nest
of snakes.

403
00:30:57,572 --> 00:30:59,233
You have no
obligations to them.

404
00:30:59,274 --> 00:31:01,538
They are my family!
They love me, I...

405
00:31:01,576 --> 00:31:03,009
As I love you.

406
00:31:03,044 --> 00:31:06,343
You call this love?

407
00:31:08,149 --> 00:31:09,673
I can't.

408
00:31:09,718 --> 00:31:11,481
- Where are you going?
- Home.

409
00:31:11,520 --> 00:31:13,181
Don't go.

410
00:31:13,221 --> 00:31:15,382
Your mother
killed Glabius!

411
00:31:18,960 --> 00:31:21,155
My people caught
one of the men that did it.

412
00:31:21,196 --> 00:31:23,289
One of Timon's men.

413
00:31:36,645 --> 00:31:38,738
I'm sorry.

414
00:32:20,055 --> 00:32:23,081
- Do as Lyde says.
- Please, Mama, come with us.

415
00:32:23,124 --> 00:32:24,921
My place is here
with your father.

416
00:32:24,960 --> 00:32:26,689
But what
if you're killed?

417
00:32:26,728 --> 00:32:29,856
Then you must stay in the country,
don't come back to the city.

418
00:32:29,898 --> 00:32:31,957
You understand?

419
00:32:32,000 --> 00:32:35,561
Don't come back!
You'll be country girls. Mm-hmm?

420
00:32:35,604 --> 00:32:40,166
Your cousin will find you good
handsome farmers to marry.

421
00:32:44,412 --> 00:32:47,347
Go ask the gods
for blessing.

422
00:32:51,186 --> 00:32:53,677
Can't you get Vorenus
to do as Erastes asks?

423
00:32:53,722 --> 00:32:55,519
If you begged him...

424
00:32:55,557 --> 00:32:57,525
To kiss a man's feet?

425
00:32:57,559 --> 00:33:00,687
I'd never ask such a thing,
and he'd never agree to it.

426
00:33:00,729 --> 00:33:03,254
Always remember that you
are children of the Vorenii,

427
00:33:03,298 --> 00:33:05,027
an old and respected name.

428
00:33:05,066 --> 00:33:07,728
And always remember
that we love you.

429
00:33:07,769 --> 00:33:10,932
I love you very much.
Now go on.

430
00:33:22,784 --> 00:33:24,479
Go, go.

431
00:33:28,223 --> 00:33:29,247
Goodbye, sister.

432
00:33:44,239 --> 00:33:47,037
Eirene, are you going to
leave this mess on the table?

433
00:33:49,711 --> 00:33:51,679
Please, Niobe,
please, go with them.

434
00:33:51,713 --> 00:33:54,375
I will not
and stop asking.

435
00:35:00,648 --> 00:35:02,445
Good bread this.

436
00:35:02,484 --> 00:35:05,214
I bought the better kind.

437
00:35:05,253 --> 00:35:07,483
Hang the expense, eh?

438
00:35:18,500 --> 00:35:20,627
Get back.
Make way there.

439
00:35:20,668 --> 00:35:22,465
Run and hide.

440
00:35:28,343 --> 00:35:31,073
Here comes the Consul
Gaius Julius Caesar,

441
00:35:31,112 --> 00:35:33,672
Son of Venus, Imperator
of the Gaelic Legions.

442
00:35:36,084 --> 00:35:38,245
Salve, Lucius Vorenus.

443
00:36:11,519 --> 00:36:13,248
Your wife is
very beautiful.

444
00:36:13,288 --> 00:36:14,516
Her name?

445
00:36:14,556 --> 00:36:16,547
Niobe, sir.

446
00:36:20,261 --> 00:36:23,560
Rise, Niobe.

447
00:36:27,669 --> 00:36:29,899
Would you honor us
by drinking our water, sir?

448
00:36:29,938 --> 00:36:32,133
I'm happy to do so.

449
00:36:32,173 --> 00:36:34,164
Please, sit.

450
00:36:38,112 --> 00:36:41,343
I have always held you
in high regard, Vorenus,

451
00:36:41,382 --> 00:36:44,647
and I am told you are a man
of respect among your people here.

452
00:36:44,686 --> 00:36:48,019
- I hope so.
- That being so, I've come to ask you

453
00:36:48,056 --> 00:36:50,456
to stand for magistrate
of Lower Aventine...

454
00:36:50,491 --> 00:36:52,652
on my slate.

455
00:36:52,694 --> 00:36:54,252
Thank you.

456
00:36:57,165 --> 00:36:59,827
Well?

457
00:37:03,071 --> 00:37:07,235
I am deeply honored by your
presence here, sir, deeply honored.

458
00:37:07,275 --> 00:37:10,733
But... respectfully,
I must decline.

459
00:37:10,778 --> 00:37:14,145
So you still disapprove
of my actions?

460
00:37:14,182 --> 00:37:16,776
Sir, with respect,

461
00:37:16,818 --> 00:37:18,251
your politics
are not mine.

462
00:37:18,286 --> 00:37:19,753
I am aware of that.

463
00:37:19,787 --> 00:37:21,687
Were I a magistrate,
I would have to speak.

464
00:37:21,723 --> 00:37:23,691
And you will not speak

465
00:37:23,725 --> 00:37:26,592
in favor of a tyrant?

466
00:37:26,628 --> 00:37:29,153
I will not speak
against my beliefs.

467
00:37:29,197 --> 00:37:31,324
Delicious.

468
00:37:31,366 --> 00:37:33,664
You misjudge me.
I am no tyrant.

469
00:37:33,701 --> 00:37:36,465
I have taken dictator's
powers legally.

470
00:37:36,504 --> 00:37:39,530
And I will return those powers
to the people and the senate

471
00:37:39,574 --> 00:37:41,439
as soon as I am able.
I will not rest

472
00:37:41,476 --> 00:37:45,845
until Rome is as it was
in the golden age.

473
00:37:45,880 --> 00:37:49,145
I cannot succeed alone.
Will you join me?

474
00:38:06,234 --> 00:38:08,964
Hail Caesar! Hail!

475
00:38:09,003 --> 00:38:10,664
Hail Caesar!

476
00:38:15,043 --> 00:38:17,534
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!

477
00:38:39,400 --> 00:38:42,597
A little more, I think.

478
00:38:42,637 --> 00:38:45,003
No, the sleeves are fine,
leave those alone.

479
00:38:45,039 --> 00:38:48,531
You just be careful what
you're doing with that pin.

480
00:38:48,576 --> 00:38:50,976
Yes. Now, if you could
go around the side...

481
00:38:51,012 --> 00:38:52,604
at the hem,
at the bottom...

482
00:38:52,647 --> 00:38:54,740
that needs taking up
a little bit there.

483
00:38:54,782 --> 00:38:57,410
There.
No, that's fine.

484
00:38:57,452 --> 00:39:00,615
I don't know.
That just isn't working for me.

485
00:39:15,837 --> 00:39:18,397
Were you looking
for anything in particular?

486
00:39:18,439 --> 00:39:21,499
Oh... not really.

487
00:39:36,557 --> 00:39:38,252
Do you have
anything comical?

488
00:39:38,292 --> 00:39:40,590
Um, I don't think so.

489
00:39:47,402 --> 00:39:49,029
You.

490
00:39:52,040 --> 00:39:53,803
Why send him away?
It's hot.

491
00:39:53,841 --> 00:39:56,469
I don't like that one.
He looks at me.

492
00:39:56,511 --> 00:39:59,275
Does he?
Have Castor beat him.

493
00:39:59,313 --> 00:40:01,144
Maybe I will.

494
00:40:02,917 --> 00:40:05,852
- I'll call for another one.
- Don't.

495
00:40:06,854 --> 00:40:08,947
It's nice to be alone.

496
00:40:11,025 --> 00:40:13,118
Isn't it?

497
00:40:14,228 --> 00:40:17,493
- I suppose.
- Come lie down with me.

498
00:40:18,499 --> 00:40:21,297
Lie down with you?
Why?

499
00:40:22,336 --> 00:40:24,531
I would like it.

500
00:40:24,572 --> 00:40:27,166
- Why?
- Why not?

501
00:40:27,208 --> 00:40:29,301
I can think
of several reasons.

502
00:40:29,343 --> 00:40:32,506
When you were little, you would
come to my bed every night.

503
00:40:32,547 --> 00:40:35,778
Not every night.
Only when I was scared.

504
00:40:35,817 --> 00:40:37,478
You were scared
a great deal.

505
00:40:37,518 --> 00:40:39,486
I'm not scared now.

506
00:40:46,894 --> 00:40:49,920
- Pretend.
- I have no skill at pretending.

507
00:40:56,938 --> 00:40:59,133
I'm embarrassed now.

508
00:41:00,541 --> 00:41:02,702
I thought you wanted me.

509
00:41:08,282 --> 00:41:10,409
You're a man now,
aren't you?

510
00:41:13,354 --> 00:41:15,049
You can take
what you want.

511
00:42:12,313 --> 00:42:14,645
Brother,
tell me something...

512
00:42:15,650 --> 00:42:17,641
Ah.

513
00:42:17,685 --> 00:42:19,915
What do you mean, "Ah"?

514
00:42:21,589 --> 00:42:23,648
Now comes the price.

515
00:42:26,260 --> 00:42:28,820
- What do you mean?
- You're a virtuous woman,

516
00:42:28,863 --> 00:42:31,627
so you must know that seducing
your own brother is wrong.

517
00:42:31,666 --> 00:42:35,500
You and I are above such
petty social convention.

518
00:42:35,536 --> 00:42:37,902
But incest is not merely
wrong by convention.

519
00:42:37,939 --> 00:42:40,806
It's wrong in essence.
It must be,

520
00:42:40,841 --> 00:42:44,174
else why so many idiots and
monsters among the children of incest?

521
00:42:44,212 --> 00:42:47,477
- Don't.
- Don't worry.

522
00:42:47,515 --> 00:42:49,506
It's unlikely
I've seeded you.

523
00:42:49,550 --> 00:42:51,916
Not with the moon
in transit.

524
00:42:51,953 --> 00:42:55,354
The point is, you're not the woman
to do such wrong out of mere lust.

525
00:42:55,389 --> 00:42:57,516
Ergo, you must
have another purpose.

526
00:42:57,558 --> 00:43:00,823
I suspect you shall renew your
strange interest in Caesar's health.

527
00:43:04,865 --> 00:43:08,357
Wha... what have I done?
What have I done?

528
00:43:11,339 --> 00:43:14,206
What have I done?
What?

529
00:43:17,178 --> 00:43:20,705
What have you done?
Tell me.

530
00:43:23,317 --> 00:43:24,909
Promise.

531
00:43:24,952 --> 00:43:27,716
Promise you won't
tell Mother.

532
00:43:44,338 --> 00:43:46,135
Look at you.

533
00:43:46,173 --> 00:43:48,403
You look like laundry.

534
00:43:52,580 --> 00:43:54,172
There.

535
00:43:54,215 --> 00:43:57,548
- Does it look well?
- Very well.

536
00:43:57,585 --> 00:43:59,212
It feels strange.

537
00:44:00,254 --> 00:44:02,654
No, don't,
you'll dirty it.

538
00:44:02,690 --> 00:44:06,524
Does it hang properly
at the back?

539
00:44:06,560 --> 00:44:08,892
I think so.

540
00:44:33,554 --> 00:44:35,021
Calm down,
Mother, really.

541
00:44:35,056 --> 00:44:37,718
Calm down? I have not
even begun to get angry!

542
00:44:40,494 --> 00:44:42,724
Enough!

543
00:44:42,763 --> 00:44:44,663
I am your son
but not your child.

544
00:44:44,699 --> 00:44:47,668
- You will not strike me anymore.
- Will I not?

545
00:44:48,969 --> 00:44:51,369
You fucked your sister,
you little pervert!

546
00:44:51,405 --> 00:44:53,737
Don't tell me what
I will and will not do!

547
00:44:53,774 --> 00:44:56,004
- Be quiet!
- You wouldn't dare.

548
00:45:10,191 --> 00:45:12,785
How could you
do this to me?

549
00:45:12,827 --> 00:45:15,227
My own child.

550
00:45:15,262 --> 00:45:17,890
- You killed my husband.
- I told you, didn't I?

551
00:45:17,932 --> 00:45:20,594
- I told you I didn't kill him!
- You're a liar.

552
00:45:20,634 --> 00:45:23,296
Servilia caught one
of the men that did it.

553
00:45:23,337 --> 00:45:25,965
- One of Timon's men.
- And where is this man?

554
00:45:26,006 --> 00:45:28,440
Did you speak to him?

555
00:45:28,476 --> 00:45:30,706
Look at me.
Look at me!

556
00:45:32,113 --> 00:45:35,173
I swear on the spirits
of my ancestors,

557
00:45:35,216 --> 00:45:39,312
on the stone of Jupiter,
I did not kill your husband!

558
00:45:39,353 --> 00:45:41,651
You abased yourself
for a stupid lie!

559
00:45:44,125 --> 00:45:47,253
- I don't know.
- Servilia is the liar, you fool!

560
00:45:47,294 --> 00:45:49,626
She lied to turn you
against me.

561
00:46:00,708 --> 00:46:02,676
My poor lamb.

562
00:46:29,537 --> 00:46:30,936
Eirene?

563
00:46:32,673 --> 00:46:34,641
Eirene?

564
00:46:35,643 --> 00:46:37,338
Eirene?

565
00:46:38,345 --> 00:46:40,404
Eirene!

566
00:46:44,084 --> 00:46:45,711
Coming, master.

567
00:46:52,259 --> 00:46:54,784
Sit down.
Have a drink with me.

568
00:47:15,282 --> 00:47:17,307
My mother
had hair like yours.

569
00:47:20,120 --> 00:47:22,350
Grey eyes though.

570
00:47:22,389 --> 00:47:25,256
Big grey eyes.

571
00:47:28,195 --> 00:47:31,722
Slave... on one
of those farms up north.

572
00:47:33,567 --> 00:47:35,034
Smelled of pine trees.

573
00:47:35,069 --> 00:47:37,902
Worked in
the wood yards, probably.

574
00:47:37,938 --> 00:47:41,066
That's what I think.
Explains the pine smell.

575
00:47:45,412 --> 00:47:47,903
Don't know
who my father was.

576
00:47:47,948 --> 00:47:50,439
Just another slave probably.

577
00:47:52,019 --> 00:47:55,978
Some timid cunt shoveling shit
with a collar around his neck

578
00:47:56,023 --> 00:47:58,389
because he didn't have
the courage to die like a man.

579
00:47:58,425 --> 00:48:00,791
I'd cut my fucking heart
out of my chest

580
00:48:00,828 --> 00:48:03,729
and eat it before
I knelt down to anybody!

581
00:48:03,764 --> 00:48:05,459
- Cunt!
- Quiet!

582
00:48:05,499 --> 00:48:07,558
Keep it down!

583
00:48:07,601 --> 00:48:09,728
Suck my cock,
the lot of youse!

584
00:48:09,770 --> 00:48:12,330
I'm Titus Pullo, right?

585
00:48:17,845 --> 00:48:19,506
Right?

586
00:48:21,315 --> 00:48:23,283
Right, master.

587
00:48:24,652 --> 00:48:26,620
You're a good girl.

588
00:48:29,189 --> 00:48:30,986
You don't smile
much though.

589
00:48:33,160 --> 00:48:35,253
You want me to smile?

590
00:48:35,296 --> 00:48:37,196
I want you
to be happy.

591
00:48:42,269 --> 00:48:44,294
That's better.

592
00:48:46,240 --> 00:48:48,037
Have some wine.

593
00:48:59,420 --> 00:49:01,217
Come here.

594
00:49:16,837 --> 00:49:18,862
Closer.

595
00:49:27,281 --> 00:49:29,044
Take off your dress.

596
00:50:27,808 --> 00:50:29,673
What's the hat for?

597
00:50:29,710 --> 00:50:31,575
Yom Kippur.

598
00:50:31,612 --> 00:50:33,409
Oh, is that today?

599
00:50:33,447 --> 00:50:35,108
You call yourself a Jew?

600
00:50:35,149 --> 00:50:36,912
What, are you
my Rebbe now?

601
00:50:46,760 --> 00:50:49,991
- Move! Move!
- Vos!

602
00:50:53,767 --> 00:50:55,325
No!

603
00:50:56,370 --> 00:50:58,770
Quick, grab her!

604
00:50:58,806 --> 00:51:01,297
Strip her!

605
00:51:01,341 --> 00:51:04,572
No! No!

606
00:51:04,611 --> 00:51:06,602
Somebody help her!

607
00:51:14,221 --> 00:51:16,951
...keep and protect me.
Keep and protect me.

608
00:51:22,930 --> 00:51:26,627
Keep and protect me.
No!

609
00:51:26,667 --> 00:51:28,157
Let's go!

