1
00:02:29,750 --> 00:02:32,718
- I was thinking...
- Hmm?

2
00:02:32,752 --> 00:02:35,015
I was thinking...

3
00:02:36,087 --> 00:02:39,020
you and I might
go away to Baia.

4
00:02:39,055 --> 00:02:41,045
Hmm? After
next market day.

5
00:02:41,089 --> 00:02:43,648
It's supposed
to be nice there

6
00:02:43,691 --> 00:02:46,421
- and seeing how crowded it's been...
- That's a lovely idea, but...

7
00:02:46,460 --> 00:02:48,393
But what?

8
00:02:48,428 --> 00:02:50,793
I can't leave Lyde alone.

9
00:02:50,829 --> 00:02:52,818
- She needs me.
- She needs you.

10
00:02:53,964 --> 00:02:57,160
Evander's been missing for two months.
Something bad has happened.

11
00:02:57,199 --> 00:02:58,790
Very likely something
bad has happened.

12
00:02:58,833 --> 00:03:01,324
Very likely he is dead!

13
00:03:13,643 --> 00:03:15,769
Pullo, awake!

14
00:03:17,712 --> 00:03:19,646
Wake up!
Mark Antony's waiting.

15
00:03:19,681 --> 00:03:22,171
Mump off and die,
you pigfucker.

16
00:03:25,750 --> 00:03:27,740
Right.

17
00:03:31,454 --> 00:03:33,444
Aw, thank you,
my honey.

18
00:03:34,623 --> 00:03:36,385
You shouldn't
thank slaves.

19
00:03:36,424 --> 00:03:38,720
- No harm in it.
- It's bad for discipline.

20
00:03:38,757 --> 00:03:40,748
Happy again
this morning?

21
00:03:41,859 --> 00:03:43,793
Niobe, then?

22
00:03:43,828 --> 00:03:45,590
- How's she going?
- I don't understand her.

23
00:03:45,629 --> 00:03:47,994
All the hoo over her
sister's damn husband.

24
00:03:48,030 --> 00:03:50,521
Women, eh? Maybe
she's... she's...

25
00:03:50,566 --> 00:03:52,556
She's what?

26
00:03:53,568 --> 00:03:55,557
I don't know.
Women, eh?

27
00:04:18,749 --> 00:04:22,343
Mighty vice-conqueror
of Gaul,

28
00:04:22,385 --> 00:04:25,614
Mars and Bellona swell
with pride at your doings.

29
00:04:25,653 --> 00:04:29,520
- And I say...
- Oh, good Juno, what cac you speak.

30
00:04:29,556 --> 00:04:31,284
Would you just get on
with your point, man?

31
00:04:31,323 --> 00:04:33,483
Immediately,
Your Honor. I...

32
00:04:33,524 --> 00:04:35,924
Publius Servilius
is here.

33
00:04:35,960 --> 00:04:38,553
Ah, good. That'll do
for this crowd then. Off with you.

34
00:04:38,595 --> 00:04:41,619
- I...
- No, off with you!

35
00:04:41,663 --> 00:04:44,222
Master of Horse and People's
Tribune Mark Antony

36
00:04:44,264 --> 00:04:46,697
will receive
your petitions tomorrow.

37
00:04:48,800 --> 00:04:51,234
Vorenus!

38
00:04:52,737 --> 00:04:54,534
Out!

39
00:04:54,572 --> 00:04:56,367
Cynthia,

40
00:04:56,405 --> 00:04:59,271
a pear, my love, hmm?

41
00:05:09,547 --> 00:05:11,570
Servilius,

42
00:05:11,614 --> 00:05:13,513
my dear old friend.

43
00:05:15,484 --> 00:05:19,509
- How are you?
- Healthy healthy, I thank you.

44
00:05:19,552 --> 00:05:22,918
Forgive me,
have we met before?

45
00:05:22,955 --> 00:05:24,889
Have we not?

46
00:05:24,923 --> 00:05:26,684
No idea.

47
00:05:26,723 --> 00:05:29,555
I always pretend so
with civilians.

48
00:05:29,592 --> 00:05:31,752
It's more politic, nay?

49
00:05:34,095 --> 00:05:36,722
And this must be
your beautiful wife,

50
00:05:36,764 --> 00:05:38,924
whose name escapes me.

51
00:05:38,965 --> 00:05:41,158
Poppaea.

52
00:05:41,198 --> 00:05:43,063
A flower.

53
00:05:43,100 --> 00:05:44,896
You'll excuse
all the bustle.

54
00:05:44,934 --> 00:05:48,767
I found Pompey's taste
in decor rather dull.

55
00:05:48,804 --> 00:05:50,395
I like a little more color.

56
00:05:50,438 --> 00:05:53,873
- As you say.
- You shall make it lovely, we are sure.

57
00:05:53,907 --> 00:05:55,930
You'll forgive me if I talk
business with your husband?

58
00:05:55,974 --> 00:05:59,238
Of course.

59
00:05:59,276 --> 00:06:02,244
- Pretend I am not here.
- Impossible,

60
00:06:02,278 --> 00:06:05,610
but I shall try.
Now then...

61
00:06:05,647 --> 00:06:07,376
I'm sure you're
aware that Caesar

62
00:06:07,416 --> 00:06:09,440
has left me in charge
whilst he is in Greece.

63
00:06:09,483 --> 00:06:11,676
Yes.
Off having fun

64
00:06:11,717 --> 00:06:14,583
chastising Pompey et al.

65
00:06:14,619 --> 00:06:18,019
Left me here to scribble
and quibble like a damned civilian.

66
00:06:18,055 --> 00:06:21,285
However, I am determined
to make the most of it.

67
00:06:21,323 --> 00:06:24,120
I shall be
a good politician,

68
00:06:24,159 --> 00:06:26,591
even if it kills me.

69
00:06:26,626 --> 00:06:28,560
Or if it kills anyone
else for that matter.

70
00:06:29,561 --> 00:06:32,086
So you are, it seems,

71
00:06:32,130 --> 00:06:35,064
the most senior
senator left in Rome.

72
00:06:35,099 --> 00:06:36,827
I have that honor.

73
00:06:36,866 --> 00:06:40,130
- And a turnabout Pompeian to boot.
- I...

74
00:06:40,169 --> 00:06:43,534
Which is why I thought

75
00:06:43,570 --> 00:06:45,662
it could be amusing

76
00:06:45,705 --> 00:06:49,435
if we made you consul
for this year.

77
00:06:49,474 --> 00:06:51,600
Consul?

78
00:06:51,642 --> 00:06:53,633
That's most kind...

79
00:06:53,677 --> 00:06:55,644
Allow me to
finish speaking.

80
00:06:57,011 --> 00:06:59,104
When the Senate
next meets,

81
00:06:59,146 --> 00:07:01,375
there are a couple
of legislative items

82
00:07:01,414 --> 00:07:03,404
I wish to see
enacted immediately.

83
00:07:03,449 --> 00:07:06,679
I am sure you
will be happy to assist.

84
00:07:06,718 --> 00:07:08,743
- I... I...
- Item one:

85
00:07:08,786 --> 00:07:10,514
The Senate will ratify

86
00:07:10,554 --> 00:07:14,113
Caesar's election as your
co-consul for the coming year.

87
00:07:15,856 --> 00:07:17,721
But he is dictator
in any case.

88
00:07:18,991 --> 00:07:21,118
It sounds so much
better if he is consul.

89
00:07:21,160 --> 00:07:23,024
It's more amicable.

90
00:07:23,061 --> 00:07:25,426
- You got that?
- I... I do.

91
00:07:25,463 --> 00:07:28,259
- I... I have.
- Item two: You will propose

92
00:07:28,297 --> 00:07:30,355
the following law:

93
00:07:31,499 --> 00:07:34,524
Forthwith, in every
province of Italy,

94
00:07:34,568 --> 00:07:36,535
one third of all
those employed

95
00:07:36,569 --> 00:07:39,731
at laboring with
cattle or in agriculture

96
00:07:39,771 --> 00:07:41,762
must be freedmen
or citizens.

97
00:07:41,806 --> 00:07:43,738
I don't understand.

98
00:07:43,773 --> 00:07:47,037
Too many slaves, you see?
They've taken all the work,

99
00:07:47,075 --> 00:07:50,305
which causes unemployment
amongst the free populace.

100
00:07:50,344 --> 00:07:53,870
Now, we need to create
more jobs for our citizens.

101
00:07:53,913 --> 00:07:55,709
But it will be
hugely expensive!

102
00:07:55,748 --> 00:07:57,613
Mmm. It will.

103
00:07:57,649 --> 00:07:59,945
But only to
those few rich men

104
00:07:59,983 --> 00:08:02,007
who own all the land.

105
00:08:02,051 --> 00:08:03,609
And they shall
have the consolation

106
00:08:03,652 --> 00:08:06,279
of having done something
eminently patriotic.

107
00:08:06,321 --> 00:08:08,447
It seems rather...

108
00:08:08,489 --> 00:08:11,423
extreme to say the least.

109
00:08:11,457 --> 00:08:13,320
Ruinous even.

110
00:08:13,357 --> 00:08:15,086
You may well be right.

111
00:08:15,126 --> 00:08:17,491
But frankly, I do not care
whether it is the rich, poor,

112
00:08:17,527 --> 00:08:20,222
or, indeed
both that suffer.

113
00:08:20,262 --> 00:08:21,854
Caesar wishes
this law to be made.

114
00:08:21,897 --> 00:08:25,296
He is my friend,
I will have it made.

115
00:08:25,332 --> 00:08:27,425
If you prefer, I could
always bypass the Senate,

116
00:08:27,467 --> 00:08:29,524
call an Assembly
of the People

117
00:08:29,567 --> 00:08:31,557
and you can put your
arguments to them.

118
00:08:31,602 --> 00:08:34,332
A fine orator like yourself
might just persuade them

119
00:08:34,371 --> 00:08:36,634
that Caesar is wrong.

120
00:08:36,672 --> 00:08:39,834
- That won't be necessary.
- Good.

121
00:08:39,875 --> 00:08:42,399
Good.

122
00:08:42,443 --> 00:08:44,409
That's it then.

123
00:08:45,911 --> 00:08:48,105
- I don't know what to say.
- Say nothing then.

124
00:08:48,146 --> 00:08:50,079
It's often best.

125
00:08:52,082 --> 00:08:54,481
You know Posca of course,
Caesar's creature?

126
00:08:54,517 --> 00:08:56,347
He'll take
all the details.

127
00:08:59,051 --> 00:09:01,042
Poppaea...

128
00:09:02,254 --> 00:09:04,983
my dove, if your
husband should die...

129
00:09:06,791 --> 00:09:09,020
come to me,
we will marry, neh?

130
00:09:25,035 --> 00:09:27,594
So, keeping their
promises, isn't he?

131
00:09:27,637 --> 00:09:29,535
What?

132
00:09:29,570 --> 00:09:32,504
Caesar and Mark Antony,
doing right by the people.

133
00:09:32,539 --> 00:09:34,439
That was your
worry, wasn't it?

134
00:09:34,474 --> 00:09:36,839
That Caesar'd turn out to
be just another tyrant sort?

135
00:09:36,875 --> 00:09:38,842
But here's him
and Mark Antony

136
00:09:38,876 --> 00:09:40,844
getting jobs
for the unemployed.

137
00:09:40,878 --> 00:09:43,345
You can't complain
about that now, can you?

138
00:09:43,380 --> 00:09:45,846
He negotiates with a whore
and a dwarf at his side.

139
00:09:45,880 --> 00:09:48,313
Think you Cincinnatus
or Marius or even the Grachii

140
00:09:48,348 --> 00:09:50,815
- would demean themselves so?
- Who?

141
00:09:52,819 --> 00:09:55,514
Mark Antony has his odd ways,
there's no denying that.

142
00:10:03,858 --> 00:10:05,485
I'm not going home.
I need a drink.

143
00:10:05,526 --> 00:10:08,323
- Drink? You?
- I. Drink. What of it?

144
00:10:09,361 --> 00:10:11,352
I'll not argue.

145
00:10:14,199 --> 00:10:15,960
- Ouch!
- Sorry.

146
00:10:15,998 --> 00:10:18,989
- You need to calm down.
- How can I be calm? Two months of this.

147
00:10:19,034 --> 00:10:22,127
- Aren't you done yet?
- Will you sit still?

148
00:10:24,437 --> 00:10:27,235
Won't catch a pretty new husband
with a sour face like that.

149
00:10:27,273 --> 00:10:29,570
I don't want a new husband.
I want Crito.

150
00:10:29,608 --> 00:10:31,972
You can't stay
married to a drover,

151
00:10:32,008 --> 00:10:33,907
not now that your
father's a prefect.

152
00:10:33,943 --> 00:10:35,740
- It wouldn't be right.
- I told her.

153
00:10:35,778 --> 00:10:38,575
Far too low. Fortune blessed you,
you haven't paid out dowry.

154
00:10:38,613 --> 00:10:41,775
Don't worry, we'll find
you someone nice,

155
00:10:41,815 --> 00:10:44,612
- and proper status.
- I don't want anyone!

156
00:10:44,650 --> 00:10:47,583
You can't be unmarried.
It wouldn't be decent at your age.

157
00:10:47,618 --> 00:10:50,848
- Decent she says.
- What's that supposed to mean?

158
00:10:50,887 --> 00:10:53,286
You know what it means.

159
00:10:53,322 --> 00:10:56,722
- You hold your tongue.
- Or what?

160
00:10:56,757 --> 00:10:58,747
What will you do?

161
00:11:02,493 --> 00:11:05,052
It's all right, sweetie.
It's all right.

162
00:11:09,398 --> 00:11:12,457
I thought it was going
well for a while, but now...

163
00:11:17,970 --> 00:11:19,994
Maybe I should beat
her, do you think?

164
00:11:21,339 --> 00:11:24,239
I don't know.
That only works if you keep at it.

165
00:11:24,274 --> 00:11:26,537
A good thrashing
once or twice a day

166
00:11:26,575 --> 00:11:28,769
till they're docile.

167
00:11:28,810 --> 00:11:31,675
But then they
don't look so good.

168
00:11:31,711 --> 00:11:33,906
Be a shame to mark up
a beauty like her.

169
00:11:37,681 --> 00:11:39,672
She is, eh?

170
00:11:41,517 --> 00:11:43,280
She's a beauty.

171
00:11:43,319 --> 00:11:45,843
She is that.

172
00:11:45,888 --> 00:11:48,081
I give her slaves, money,
everything. What do I get?

173
00:11:48,121 --> 00:11:49,951
Nothing, that's what.

174
00:11:49,989 --> 00:11:52,617
I get a house
full of wailing.

175
00:11:52,658 --> 00:11:54,989
My wife won't
even couple with me.

176
00:11:56,526 --> 00:11:58,824
Why not?

177
00:11:58,862 --> 00:12:00,988
Says she can't while
her sister stays.

178
00:12:01,030 --> 00:12:02,859
What's her sister
to do with it?

179
00:12:02,897 --> 00:12:05,296
What difference
should that make?

180
00:12:14,638 --> 00:12:19,298
What is wrong with her?

181
00:12:19,340 --> 00:12:21,534
What is wrong with me

182
00:12:21,575 --> 00:12:23,735
that I'm served this way?

183
00:12:23,776 --> 00:12:25,539
You should
leave her, maybe,

184
00:12:25,578 --> 00:12:27,738
seeing as she
makes you so unhappy.

185
00:12:27,779 --> 00:12:30,144
No! I will
not leave her.

186
00:12:36,183 --> 00:12:38,673
I'd rather die
than leave her.

187
00:12:52,594 --> 00:12:54,584
It's all right, lamb.

188
00:12:54,628 --> 00:12:56,619
It'll be all right.

189
00:13:03,633 --> 00:13:05,828
Who, I say,

190
00:13:05,869 --> 00:13:09,166
faced with the
overwhelming force

191
00:13:09,203 --> 00:13:11,933
of the figures and the arguments
I have here marshalled

192
00:13:11,973 --> 00:13:15,202
could resist their
overwhelming conclusion?

193
00:13:16,342 --> 00:13:20,071
Therefore I ask you,

194
00:13:20,110 --> 00:13:22,805
honored conscript fathers,

195
00:13:22,845 --> 00:13:25,404
to support me in
this important and...

196
00:13:27,282 --> 00:13:30,011
patriotic legislation
which will...

197
00:13:36,187 --> 00:13:39,985
Does anyone wish to speak
against the motion?

198
00:13:45,427 --> 00:13:48,882
No opposition voiced.
No division required.

199
00:13:48,927 --> 00:13:50,792
Motion carried.

200
00:14:00,769 --> 00:14:02,793
Empty.

201
00:14:02,837 --> 00:14:04,803
Empty...

202
00:14:04,837 --> 00:14:06,828
If there's no wine,
water will do.

203
00:14:17,713 --> 00:14:19,702
Thank you, my dove.

204
00:14:22,148 --> 00:14:24,775
So, Lyde, I was asking
around, you know,

205
00:14:24,817 --> 00:14:26,875
about your man there,
Evander.

206
00:14:26,918 --> 00:14:28,714
Asking around?

207
00:14:28,752 --> 00:14:31,515
See if I could find
out anything for you.

208
00:14:31,554 --> 00:14:33,681
Only, I know a few
shady characters see?

209
00:14:33,723 --> 00:14:36,690
Types that might know what's
what when a man's gone missing.

210
00:14:38,791 --> 00:14:41,315
Anyroad,
they tell me

211
00:14:41,360 --> 00:14:43,884
that he got himself
into some trouble

212
00:14:43,928 --> 00:14:46,919
with some nasty Greek
boys across the river.

213
00:14:46,963 --> 00:14:49,727
- Gambling debts they say.
- Gambling?

214
00:14:49,766 --> 00:14:51,732
Evander never gambled.

215
00:14:51,766 --> 00:14:53,733
Well sure, it's
the sort of thing

216
00:14:53,767 --> 00:14:56,257
a man keeps quiet around
his wife, isn't it?

217
00:14:58,970 --> 00:15:00,870
What are you saying?

218
00:15:00,905 --> 00:15:04,067
I'm sorry to say it, but it looks like
he's not coming home.

219
00:15:05,540 --> 00:15:07,440
Dead, looks like.

220
00:15:07,476 --> 00:15:09,966
Are you sure?

221
00:15:10,011 --> 00:15:11,841
So they tell me.

222
00:15:11,878 --> 00:15:13,675
Dead. Killed.

223
00:15:13,713 --> 00:15:16,442
It isn't true.

224
00:15:19,017 --> 00:15:21,142
My advice,

225
00:15:21,183 --> 00:15:23,276
best forget about him.

226
00:15:23,319 --> 00:15:25,115
Best get on
with your life.

227
00:15:25,153 --> 00:15:26,915
It isn't true.

228
00:15:26,954 --> 00:15:29,354
It's not so bad.

229
00:15:29,390 --> 00:15:31,254
You've still got
people that love you.

230
00:15:31,290 --> 00:15:33,086
Look to them, eh?

231
00:15:33,125 --> 00:15:35,320
Isn't that right Niobe?

232
00:15:35,360 --> 00:15:37,223
Best she gets
on with her life.

233
00:15:37,260 --> 00:15:39,693
Best she looks to
the people that love her.

234
00:15:43,931 --> 00:15:45,898
Forget Evander.

235
00:15:45,932 --> 00:15:47,763
Forget the past.

236
00:15:53,037 --> 00:15:55,231
Well, I'm away.

237
00:15:55,271 --> 00:15:57,204
Need a drop of wine
to set me up for the day.

238
00:16:16,151 --> 00:16:18,448
Lyde, please don't.

239
00:16:18,485 --> 00:16:21,418
Shh.

240
00:16:22,421 --> 00:16:24,945
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.

241
00:16:26,657 --> 00:16:28,487
You're sorry?

242
00:16:28,525 --> 00:16:30,390
It's too late for sorry, isn't it?

243
00:16:30,427 --> 00:16:32,951
You weren't sorry when you
were fucking him, were you?

244
00:16:32,995 --> 00:16:35,360
You weren't sorry then.
I piss on your sorrow!

245
00:16:35,396 --> 00:16:37,191
- Shh!
- I will not shh. You shh!

246
00:16:37,229 --> 00:16:39,753
You're a thief and a whore
and you stole my husband!

247
00:16:39,798 --> 00:16:42,289
I stole nothing!
He came to me!

248
00:16:42,333 --> 00:16:44,766
He came to me!
I never loved him. I love my husband!

249
00:16:44,802 --> 00:16:47,429
And if you'd done...
if you'd been...

250
00:16:48,538 --> 00:16:50,505
If I had done what?

251
00:16:51,807 --> 00:16:54,967
If I had given him
a child. Is that it?

252
00:16:55,007 --> 00:16:57,134
I am sorry. Please forgive me.
Please forgive me!

253
00:16:57,176 --> 00:17:00,008
- Forgive me!
- I curse you, sister.

254
00:17:01,545 --> 00:17:04,672
By grace of the Furies,
I curse you.

255
00:17:08,348 --> 00:17:11,145
I'll keep your secret

256
00:17:11,184 --> 00:17:13,651
for the sake of the child,

257
00:17:13,685 --> 00:17:15,653
but don't you ever...

258
00:17:15,687 --> 00:17:18,484
ever speak to me again.

259
00:17:44,204 --> 00:17:46,195
Be careful!

260
00:17:56,177 --> 00:17:59,043
Ah!

261
00:18:00,280 --> 00:18:02,907
Bravo. Bravo.

262
00:18:02,949 --> 00:18:04,974
A little blood lust
suits you, Octavian.

263
00:18:05,017 --> 00:18:06,881
You look very handsome.
Does he not?

264
00:18:06,918 --> 00:18:09,680
- He does.
- Titus Pullo is a good teacher.

265
00:18:09,719 --> 00:18:12,209
Well it's a pity Caesar
isn't here.

266
00:18:12,254 --> 00:18:14,346
He'd put you on his
staff immediately.

267
00:18:14,388 --> 00:18:17,356
Perhaps you should go
and join him in Greece,

268
00:18:17,390 --> 00:18:20,188
get some real Pompeian
blood on your sword.

269
00:18:20,227 --> 00:18:21,989
- Don't be silly, Mother.
- Well why not?

270
00:18:22,027 --> 00:18:24,994
If we are not quick, Pompey
and Cato and all those fools

271
00:18:25,028 --> 00:18:27,996
will be dead before Octavian
gets his chance to shine.

272
00:18:28,030 --> 00:18:29,690
- He's still a child.
- I am not.

273
00:18:29,731 --> 00:18:31,926
He is not. He is quite
the little man now.

274
00:18:31,967 --> 00:18:34,264
I should think there's more
to manhood than swordplay.

275
00:18:35,668 --> 00:18:37,397
Octavian,

276
00:18:37,437 --> 00:18:40,097
- have you penetrated anyone yet?
- Mother, please.

277
00:18:40,138 --> 00:18:42,970
- Does that mean you have or haven't?
- Haven't, but...

278
00:18:43,006 --> 00:18:45,997
Titus Pullo, didn't I tell
you to sort that out?

279
00:18:46,041 --> 00:18:48,008
I'm sure I did.

280
00:18:48,042 --> 00:18:50,636
I... sorry, ma'am.
I'll see to it.

281
00:18:50,678 --> 00:18:52,645
Do that.

282
00:18:52,679 --> 00:18:55,077
Don't worry, darling.
There's really nothing to it.

283
00:18:55,113 --> 00:18:57,706
Once you're in
the saddle, as it were,

284
00:18:57,748 --> 00:19:00,341
it'll all come naturally.
Isn't that right, Pullo?

285
00:19:00,383 --> 00:19:02,078
That's right ma'am.

286
00:19:02,118 --> 00:19:05,086
And none of your sordid soldier's
she-wolves, mind you.

287
00:19:05,120 --> 00:19:07,087
Something clean and pretty.

288
00:19:07,121 --> 00:19:09,986
- Clean and pretty it is.
- Good.

289
00:19:10,022 --> 00:19:12,819
I'll get Merula make you a toga.
What else?

290
00:19:12,857 --> 00:19:14,586
Perhaps you can arrange
he kill someone.

291
00:19:14,626 --> 00:19:16,320
Oh...

292
00:19:16,360 --> 00:19:18,554
that will happen
in due course.

293
00:19:18,594 --> 00:19:20,858
We Julii always have
the needful enemies.

294
00:19:34,437 --> 00:19:36,462
Health to my child.

295
00:19:38,207 --> 00:19:40,002
My daughter.

296
00:19:41,041 --> 00:19:43,031
I wish for a son,
a healthy son.

297
00:20:11,626 --> 00:20:13,855
- I, uh...
- Good night, then.

298
00:20:17,397 --> 00:20:19,388
Good night.

299
00:20:46,315 --> 00:20:48,077
Husband.

300
00:20:48,115 --> 00:20:50,105
What's all this?

301
00:20:52,185 --> 00:20:55,415
I thought it might please you
if we had some time alone.

302
00:20:58,222 --> 00:21:00,553
I sent the girls
and Lucius to Clarissa.

303
00:21:03,992 --> 00:21:07,017
- And Lyde?
- She's gone to a friend's.

304
00:21:09,128 --> 00:21:11,356
- Please, sit down.
- I've already eaten.

305
00:21:13,197 --> 00:21:15,061
Oh...

306
00:21:15,098 --> 00:21:16,895
But...

307
00:21:16,933 --> 00:21:18,923
I can have some more.

308
00:21:24,004 --> 00:21:26,029
Excuse me.

309
00:21:53,923 --> 00:21:56,755
Sit down with me.

310
00:21:56,791 --> 00:21:58,757
- That's all right.
- Really, sit.

311
00:21:58,791 --> 00:22:01,156
I can't finish
all this on my own.

312
00:22:48,856 --> 00:22:50,880
The calendar is correct...

313
00:22:54,259 --> 00:22:56,624
if you would like
to have me tonight.

314
00:23:00,095 --> 00:23:02,085
I would.

315
00:23:03,564 --> 00:23:05,724
I'd like that.

316
00:24:58,167 --> 00:25:00,395
My dear Mark Antony,

317
00:25:00,434 --> 00:25:02,299
I hope this finds
you in better health

318
00:25:02,336 --> 00:25:04,394
than my hopes for victory.

319
00:25:04,437 --> 00:25:06,961
I chased Pompey from one
end of Greece to the other

320
00:25:07,005 --> 00:25:09,132
and he resolutely
refused to fight.

321
00:25:09,174 --> 00:25:11,903
I thought this was
his usual obtuseness,

322
00:25:11,943 --> 00:25:15,569
but the old man has
some sense left in him yet.

323
00:25:19,146 --> 00:25:21,011
While avoiding battle,

324
00:25:21,048 --> 00:25:23,675
he has gathered a good
10 legions from the east,

325
00:25:23,716 --> 00:25:25,842
and I find myself
badly outnumbered.

326
00:25:32,354 --> 00:25:34,287
Now the cat
barks at the dog,

327
00:25:34,322 --> 00:25:36,256
and Pompey is chasing me.

328
00:25:44,863 --> 00:25:47,261
I can outmaneuver
him for a while,

329
00:25:47,296 --> 00:25:49,126
but not forever.

330
00:25:52,433 --> 00:25:54,731
My men are tired
and ill-supplied,

331
00:25:54,769 --> 00:25:56,929
and we shall soon
have to stand and fight.

332
00:25:56,970 --> 00:25:59,494
I ask you to bring
the 13th here

333
00:25:59,538 --> 00:26:01,936
as speedily
as you are able.

334
00:26:16,382 --> 00:26:18,371
Damnation.

335
00:26:18,416 --> 00:26:20,542
Shall I summon
the legion legates?

336
00:26:20,583 --> 00:26:22,573
Hmmm.

337
00:26:23,585 --> 00:26:25,779
No. Wait.

338
00:26:25,820 --> 00:26:27,811
I must think on this.

339
00:26:30,724 --> 00:26:33,555
This is lovely.

340
00:26:34,759 --> 00:26:36,692
- Oh.
- Oh, it's just your coloring.

341
00:26:36,727 --> 00:26:40,093
A little loud. I'd prefer
something plainer.

342
00:26:40,129 --> 00:26:43,791
What's the point in plain?
We shall take it.

343
00:26:43,832 --> 00:26:45,628
But this one...

344
00:26:46,634 --> 00:26:48,190
Oh!

345
00:26:51,002 --> 00:26:53,663
Divine. Oh, divine.

346
00:26:53,703 --> 00:26:57,433
Antony will love this.
He likes me in Eastern styles.

347
00:26:57,473 --> 00:27:00,236
- How much for both?
- 5,000.

348
00:27:00,275 --> 00:27:03,333
- You are a thief.
- Four and a half then.

349
00:27:03,376 --> 00:27:05,366
Three.

350
00:27:06,645 --> 00:27:09,272
Can we afford such expense?

351
00:27:09,313 --> 00:27:11,507
Things as they are
with Caesar in Greece,

352
00:27:11,548 --> 00:27:13,413
surely we should
be more prudent?

353
00:27:13,450 --> 00:27:15,246
Don't worry about
a thing my dear,

354
00:27:15,284 --> 00:27:18,251
I'm thinking ahead.

355
00:27:18,285 --> 00:27:20,718
Titus Pullo is here, dominus.

356
00:27:20,753 --> 00:27:24,017
Oh. Tell him
I am unwell.

357
00:27:25,256 --> 00:27:27,450
He may come back
next week perhaps.

358
00:27:27,491 --> 00:27:29,924
Tell him nothing
of the sort.

359
00:27:29,959 --> 00:27:32,553
Octavian will be ready
to see him in one moment.

360
00:27:32,595 --> 00:27:33,890
And give him a purse.

361
00:27:33,928 --> 00:27:36,191
You've put off this moment long
enough, my dear.

362
00:27:36,229 --> 00:27:37,719
Mother...

363
00:27:37,764 --> 00:27:39,958
You will penetrate
someone today or I will

364
00:27:39,998 --> 00:27:42,864
burn your wretched
books in the yard.

365
00:27:42,900 --> 00:27:45,493
Off with you.

366
00:27:57,242 --> 00:28:00,006
Coming through. Noble coming through.
Make way there.

367
00:28:12,618 --> 00:28:15,950
Don't worry, young master.
There's nothing to it.

368
00:28:15,987 --> 00:28:19,352
If there is nothing to it,
why is such a fuss made of the thing?

369
00:28:19,388 --> 00:28:22,185
You'll soon find out.

370
00:28:32,130 --> 00:28:33,789
Vai, vai!
Be off with you!

371
00:28:33,830 --> 00:28:36,321
This isn't no infantry fuckhole,
thank you very much.

372
00:28:36,366 --> 00:28:38,663
Now now, my honey,
calm your stomach.

373
00:28:38,701 --> 00:28:40,668
We've come for
the young master here.

374
00:28:40,702 --> 00:28:43,135
And we're well coined.

375
00:28:43,170 --> 00:28:46,263
Oh well,
excuse me, of course.

376
00:28:46,305 --> 00:28:48,273
I meant no disrespect.

377
00:28:48,307 --> 00:28:51,502
We're honored to service
you, young master.

378
00:28:51,542 --> 00:28:54,237
And what would be
the young master's pleasure?

379
00:28:57,513 --> 00:29:00,413
First timer.
Nothing too savory.

380
00:29:02,048 --> 00:29:04,412
I'm sure we have
just the thing.

381
00:29:13,055 --> 00:29:16,455
Something exotic, perhaps?

382
00:29:18,526 --> 00:29:20,424
Or else something young?

383
00:29:20,459 --> 00:29:23,586
Light, simple.

384
00:29:23,628 --> 00:29:27,028
Little bit skinny,
isn't it?

385
00:29:27,063 --> 00:29:30,156
Won't know he's
been, will he?

386
00:29:30,199 --> 00:29:32,928
Won't know you've been.

387
00:29:32,967 --> 00:29:35,126
More substance,

388
00:29:35,167 --> 00:29:38,533
yet still nymphlike,

389
00:29:38,570 --> 00:29:41,231
graceful.

390
00:29:42,673 --> 00:29:45,903
This one's fresh
off the boat...

391
00:29:45,942 --> 00:29:48,569
- That will be fine.
- Hold on, young master.

392
00:29:48,610 --> 00:29:50,473
No point hurrying.

393
00:29:50,510 --> 00:29:52,444
Big decision, this.

394
00:29:52,479 --> 00:29:55,072
- Let's have a look at...
- This one is perfectly adequate.

395
00:29:55,114 --> 00:29:57,707
You will be utterly
satisfied, I assure you.

396
00:29:57,749 --> 00:30:01,377
Egeria, go prepare yourself.

397
00:30:02,552 --> 00:30:05,678
If we might dispense
with the pecuniary details...

398
00:30:05,719 --> 00:30:07,311
Eh?

399
00:30:07,354 --> 00:30:09,651
Oh, right.

400
00:30:09,689 --> 00:30:12,088
- What's your price then?
- 1,000.

401
00:30:12,124 --> 00:30:14,217
Gerrae!

402
00:30:14,259 --> 00:30:17,227
I could have half the whores
in Narbo for that, and their mothers.

403
00:30:17,261 --> 00:30:19,990
We're not in Narbo,
whatever that might be.

404
00:30:21,262 --> 00:30:23,230
All right, my dove.

405
00:30:23,264 --> 00:30:25,390
We'll pay.

406
00:30:25,432 --> 00:30:28,992
But the girl better fuck him
like Helen of Troy with her ass on fire,

407
00:30:29,035 --> 00:30:31,093
or I'll know
the reason why.

408
00:30:43,843 --> 00:30:47,573
- Speak.
- Gnaeus Pompey Magnus sends greetings.

409
00:30:47,613 --> 00:30:49,603
He hopes you find
his house satisfactory.

410
00:30:51,347 --> 00:30:53,338
It'll do.

411
00:30:54,516 --> 00:30:56,609
- Get to his point.
- His point.

412
00:30:56,651 --> 00:30:59,118
Caesar is doomed
and you with him,

413
00:30:59,153 --> 00:31:02,019
- unless you make a separate peace.
- And?

414
00:31:05,057 --> 00:31:07,023
If you do, Pompey will
be merciful and generous.

415
00:31:07,057 --> 00:31:09,650
How?

416
00:31:09,692 --> 00:31:11,990
He will give you your life.
A province.

417
00:31:12,027 --> 00:31:14,221
Money enough to preserve
your dignity.

418
00:31:16,063 --> 00:31:19,054
What makes him think
I value my life so high?

419
00:31:20,900 --> 00:31:23,526
Why have you
not left for Greece?

420
00:31:23,567 --> 00:31:25,727
Do not smile at me.

421
00:31:28,337 --> 00:31:30,896
Return tomorrow. I will give
Pompey his answer then.

422
00:31:34,908 --> 00:31:36,897
Not that way.

423
00:31:42,212 --> 00:31:44,202
And disguise yourself.

424
00:32:00,357 --> 00:32:02,483
Dismissed.

425
00:32:14,231 --> 00:32:16,256
You take clothes down?

426
00:32:18,501 --> 00:32:21,367
That's an interesting accent.

427
00:32:21,403 --> 00:32:24,165
No understand.

428
00:32:28,707 --> 00:32:30,731
Where...

429
00:32:30,775 --> 00:32:32,833
are you from?

430
00:32:32,876 --> 00:32:35,742
Oh. Where from.

431
00:32:35,778 --> 00:32:37,507
Don't know.

432
00:32:37,546 --> 00:32:40,536
You don't know
where you're from?

433
00:32:44,250 --> 00:32:46,242
Rome take me very young.

434
00:32:47,820 --> 00:32:51,154
Kill mother, father,
brother,

435
00:32:51,191 --> 00:32:53,090
take me.

436
00:32:55,194 --> 00:32:57,185
Oh. I see. Sad.

437
00:33:16,950 --> 00:33:18,975
Turn over, would you?

438
00:33:23,656 --> 00:33:25,648
On your hands and knees.

439
00:33:34,000 --> 00:33:35,991
Ah!

440
00:33:41,774 --> 00:33:43,640
Nice place, this.

441
00:33:43,677 --> 00:33:45,669
Clean.

442
00:33:50,387 --> 00:33:52,686
I don't suppose,

443
00:33:52,723 --> 00:33:54,622
seeing as I'm
with the quality...

444
00:33:54,658 --> 00:33:56,649
Not a chance.

445
00:34:05,039 --> 00:34:07,508
No no no. No, do it for real.
Fight.

446
00:34:12,047 --> 00:34:14,482
Oh, come on, fight,
damn you! Fight!

447
00:34:14,517 --> 00:34:17,612
That's better!

448
00:34:17,654 --> 00:34:21,351
Mmm, good.

449
00:34:27,232 --> 00:34:29,029
Brava, Cynthia! Brava!

450
00:34:31,237 --> 00:34:34,001
Oh, don't be so silly,
it's just a scratch now.

451
00:34:38,948 --> 00:34:40,812
There there.

452
00:34:40,849 --> 00:34:42,784
Yes, Posca, what is it?

453
00:34:42,819 --> 00:34:45,754
I am to remind you
of your dinner tonight

454
00:34:45,788 --> 00:34:47,951
with Atia of the Julii.

455
00:34:47,993 --> 00:34:49,984
Sons of Dis.

456
00:34:51,530 --> 00:34:53,521
Now, run along.

457
00:34:57,270 --> 00:35:00,069
Where is he?
Where can he be?

458
00:35:00,108 --> 00:35:01,666
Busy man. Politics.

459
00:35:01,709 --> 00:35:03,803
Politics? He promised
he would come.

460
00:35:03,846 --> 00:35:06,612
Castor!

461
00:35:06,650 --> 00:35:08,139
Send a man to Pompey's...

462
00:35:08,184 --> 00:35:11,211
I mean, Mark Antony's villa
and enquire his whereabouts.

463
00:35:11,255 --> 00:35:13,381
Antony's whereabouts,
immediately, domina.

464
00:35:13,423 --> 00:35:15,723
Do not say it is
I who sends to ask.

465
00:35:15,761 --> 00:35:17,626
Not you sends to ask.

466
00:35:17,662 --> 00:35:19,688
Stay. He'll know
it is I who asked.

467
00:35:19,732 --> 00:35:22,497
Send no one.

468
00:35:22,536 --> 00:35:24,937
I will send no one.

469
00:35:24,973 --> 00:35:27,032
If he comes,
he comes, I don't care!

470
00:35:48,068 --> 00:35:50,060
Halt!

471
00:35:51,473 --> 00:35:53,704
Welcome, dominus.

472
00:36:22,512 --> 00:36:25,346
Sorry to be so horribly
late. Endless business.

473
00:36:26,950 --> 00:36:29,647
- Will you forgive me?
- Of course.

474
00:36:29,687 --> 00:36:32,054
I confess, I had quite
forgotten you were coming.

475
00:36:32,090 --> 00:36:34,321
So this is
a lovely surprise.

476
00:36:34,360 --> 00:36:37,023
Excuse me a moment,
I will go and dress correctly.

477
00:37:25,458 --> 00:37:28,120
Mmm. Here he is,

478
00:37:28,161 --> 00:37:30,130
young Apollo!

479
00:37:30,164 --> 00:37:32,861
- How was it?
- It was pleasant.

480
00:37:32,901 --> 00:37:36,393
Pleasant?
I should say so.

481
00:37:36,438 --> 00:37:39,932
- How was he?
- Like bull.

482
00:38:07,411 --> 00:38:09,379
What's wrong?

483
00:38:09,413 --> 00:38:11,405
Nothing.

484
00:38:13,517 --> 00:38:15,510
Tell me.

485
00:38:21,963 --> 00:38:25,330
Mark Antony does not intend
to go to Greece to help Caesar.

486
00:38:27,104 --> 00:38:29,833
I have sworn loyalty
to a man of no honor.

487
00:38:31,842 --> 00:38:35,040
Well you don't have
to go to Greece then.

488
00:38:35,079 --> 00:38:38,071
- We'll be together.
- It's true, but still.

489
00:38:39,719 --> 00:38:42,085
Haven't you always said
Caesar's cause is wrong?

490
00:38:43,856 --> 00:38:45,848
That is not the point.

491
00:38:45,892 --> 00:38:48,828
There is a moral
principle involved.

492
00:38:54,270 --> 00:38:56,569
What an idiot you are!

493
00:39:10,792 --> 00:39:12,885
Not hungry?

494
00:39:12,927 --> 00:39:16,055
Oh, after so many years of
soldier's porridge, I am easily sated.

495
00:39:17,799 --> 00:39:19,701
Well, this last
news from Greece

496
00:39:19,736 --> 00:39:21,704
cannot have improved
your appetite.

497
00:39:21,738 --> 00:39:23,603
Hardly.

498
00:39:23,640 --> 00:39:26,839
And is it really so bad? Caesar
always finds a way to win.

499
00:39:26,878 --> 00:39:30,939
Pompey has gathered 10 men
for every one of Caesar's.

500
00:39:30,982 --> 00:39:33,817
Arithmetic has no mercy.

501
00:39:33,854 --> 00:39:36,186
I'd feared it was so.

502
00:39:37,257 --> 00:39:39,590
What do you
intend to do then?

503
00:39:48,371 --> 00:39:50,432
I don't know.

504
00:39:52,977 --> 00:39:56,608
You've become a powerful man.
The people love you.

505
00:39:56,649 --> 00:39:58,982
Only because
they don't know me.

506
00:39:59,019 --> 00:40:02,614
You could be the first man
in Rome, if you wanted.

507
00:40:02,656 --> 00:40:04,851
I hadn't thought
about it like that.

508
00:40:06,428 --> 00:40:08,420
Well, you should.

509
00:40:09,432 --> 00:40:11,264
You should
think about that.

510
00:40:13,238 --> 00:40:16,832
I'm thinking about
something entirely different.

511
00:40:16,874 --> 00:40:18,866
Mmm.

512
00:40:45,777 --> 00:40:47,768
Water.

513
00:41:10,175 --> 00:41:12,076
I could sleep for a week.

514
00:41:19,987 --> 00:41:21,979
I've been thinking.

515
00:41:26,195 --> 00:41:28,892
We should get married.

516
00:41:31,534 --> 00:41:34,096
Married?

517
00:41:34,138 --> 00:41:36,801
Why should we want
to do that of all things?

518
00:41:39,111 --> 00:41:42,047
- Perhaps I love you.
- Ah.

519
00:41:42,082 --> 00:41:44,415
You're joking.

520
00:41:44,452 --> 00:41:47,079
For a moment there
you had me worried.

521
00:41:47,120 --> 00:41:49,317
I am not joking with you.

522
00:41:50,692 --> 00:41:52,855
Oh, my dear woman.

523
00:41:52,897 --> 00:41:54,865
Please don't worry,

524
00:41:54,899 --> 00:41:56,730
I'm not going
soft on you.

525
00:41:56,767 --> 00:41:58,633
I'm thinking strategically.

526
00:41:58,670 --> 00:42:01,299
If Caesar is defeated,

527
00:42:01,340 --> 00:42:04,572
I can't very well form
an alliance with the Pompeians.

528
00:42:06,345 --> 00:42:08,473
- I need protection.
- True.

529
00:42:12,187 --> 00:42:14,883
What's in it for me?

530
00:42:14,924 --> 00:42:16,620
If Caesar is defeated...

531
00:42:16,660 --> 00:42:18,924
Then I will be defeated also.

532
00:42:18,962 --> 00:42:21,396
Only if you join
him in Greece.

533
00:42:21,431 --> 00:42:23,696
But if you stay in Rome,

534
00:42:23,734 --> 00:42:25,532
you will be
very well situated.

535
00:42:25,571 --> 00:42:27,665
You have the people
with you,

536
00:42:27,707 --> 00:42:29,732
you have possession
of the city.

537
00:42:29,776 --> 00:42:31,267
You only lack money.

538
00:42:31,312 --> 00:42:33,677
And whilst your name
is perfectly respectable...

539
00:42:33,713 --> 00:42:36,615
- I am no patrician.
- Exactly.

540
00:42:36,650 --> 00:42:39,780
But allied with my house, you
would have both coin and nobility

541
00:42:39,822 --> 00:42:41,949
to make yourself king
if you wished it so.

542
00:42:41,991 --> 00:42:44,518
And you would be queen.

543
00:42:44,562 --> 00:42:47,828
I would be your loving
and obedient wife.

544
00:42:49,032 --> 00:42:51,593
If only I were willing
to desert a friend.

545
00:42:51,637 --> 00:42:54,368
A man of your own blood.

546
00:42:54,407 --> 00:42:57,308
- Oh, too honorable for that, are you?
- I like to appear so.

547
00:42:57,344 --> 00:43:00,405
But I don't think you'll die
for the sake of appearances.

548
00:43:04,586 --> 00:43:07,579
- Will I not?
- Caesar will die in any case.

549
00:43:08,993 --> 00:43:12,520
But you are far too clever
to share his fate needlessly.

550
00:43:18,205 --> 00:43:20,866
I had not
realized until now...

551
00:43:22,075 --> 00:43:26,035
what a wicked old
harpy you really are.

552
00:43:39,631 --> 00:43:41,258
Get out!

553
00:43:42,635 --> 00:43:45,035
Get out!

554
00:44:02,794 --> 00:44:04,784
Thank you, Pullo.

555
00:44:06,999 --> 00:44:09,298
At attention!

556
00:44:43,846 --> 00:44:46,441
Ow.

557
00:45:05,240 --> 00:45:07,264
Abed in daylight,
what luxury.

558
00:45:07,307 --> 00:45:09,833
Wickedness.

559
00:45:09,878 --> 00:45:12,849
Father, that dwarf
is asking for you.

560
00:45:15,485 --> 00:45:17,510
Excellency Mark Antony

561
00:45:17,554 --> 00:45:20,024
orders 13th Legion to muster
on the Field of Mars.

562
00:45:20,058 --> 00:45:23,357
- Why? Where are we going?
- Greece.

563
00:45:53,466 --> 00:45:55,401
Tribune!

564
00:45:56,470 --> 00:45:59,406
- What shall I tell Pompey?
- Oh!

565
00:45:59,441 --> 00:46:01,932
Of course.

566
00:46:01,977 --> 00:46:04,208
Excuse me.
I had forgot you.

567
00:46:29,980 --> 00:46:31,949
His skin is a little dry.

568
00:46:31,983 --> 00:46:34,817
Have him well-oiled
before he is presented.

569
00:46:34,853 --> 00:46:37,377
Bona dea.

570
00:46:37,421 --> 00:46:40,414
- I am afraid to ask.
- Gifts for Servilia.

571
00:46:45,666 --> 00:46:47,931
How fine you look.
Let me see.

572
00:46:50,306 --> 00:46:53,468
I am so proud of you. You're a
real man at last, eh?

573
00:46:53,508 --> 00:46:55,238
Why are we giving
gifts to Servilia?

574
00:46:55,278 --> 00:46:57,975
The old crow stands in
well with Cato and the rest.

575
00:46:58,015 --> 00:47:00,007
- When Caesar and his dog Antony are
defeated...

576
00:47:00,051 --> 00:47:01,540
- If they are defeated.

577
00:47:01,585 --> 00:47:04,988
When they are defeated,
we'll need her good will.

578
00:47:05,024 --> 00:47:08,391
- And this will buy it, you think?
- I do not see why not.

579
00:47:08,427 --> 00:47:10,397
A large penis
is always welcome.

580
00:47:10,431 --> 00:47:12,922
- You think it's not enough?
- After what you did to her?

581
00:47:12,967 --> 00:47:16,665
- What I did? What did I do to her?
- Please! I'm not stupid.

582
00:47:16,705 --> 00:47:18,697
It was you made
Caesar renounce her.

583
00:47:18,741 --> 00:47:21,438
- What if I did? She doesn't know it.
- Does she not?

584
00:47:21,478 --> 00:47:25,209
- She's not stupid either.
- Servilia has no guile in her.

585
00:47:25,249 --> 00:47:27,810
If she knows it, we would certainly have
heard about it.

586
00:47:27,852 --> 00:47:29,684
You know best,
I'm sure.

587
00:47:29,722 --> 00:47:31,952
In any case, you will
take the gifts to her

588
00:47:31,991 --> 00:47:34,427
and see what
she's thinking.

589
00:47:34,462 --> 00:47:37,431
She's always been
very fond of you.

590
00:47:38,565 --> 00:47:40,500
And you will
go to Mediolanum.

591
00:47:40,535 --> 00:47:42,697
- Timon will take you.
- Mediolanum?

592
00:47:42,738 --> 00:47:44,865
Yes, they have a very
good academy there.

593
00:47:44,907 --> 00:47:47,376
- I don't understand.
- You're a man now.

594
00:47:47,410 --> 00:47:50,040
Rome's not safe
for men of the Julii.

595
00:47:52,818 --> 00:47:55,013
His toenails are ugly.

596
00:47:55,053 --> 00:47:58,319
Have them cut and painted and
put some flowers on his head.

597
00:47:58,358 --> 00:48:00,451
Oh, and send over some ice.
Six barrels, say.

598
00:48:00,493 --> 00:48:02,587
Six barrels of ice.

599
00:48:06,936 --> 00:48:09,404
Well, don't
look so foolish.

600
00:48:09,438 --> 00:48:10,803
I know what I'm about.

601
00:48:20,720 --> 00:48:22,711
Your mother's too kind.

602
00:48:25,692 --> 00:48:28,183
To what do I owe
this generosity?

603
00:48:28,229 --> 00:48:30,459
It's a gesture
of friendship.

604
00:48:30,498 --> 00:48:33,161
Friendship.

605
00:48:34,637 --> 00:48:37,607
Thank your mother
for her... friendship.

606
00:48:37,641 --> 00:48:40,805
I hope one day
to reciprocate her...

607
00:48:40,845 --> 00:48:42,744
friendship.

608
00:48:46,886 --> 00:48:48,878
I will go then.

609
00:48:52,460 --> 00:48:55,053
Excuse me.

610
00:48:55,095 --> 00:48:56,792
Wait.

611
00:48:58,200 --> 00:49:00,432
Please, forgive
my ill humor.

612
00:49:02,138 --> 00:49:04,505
There's nothing
to forgive.

613
00:49:04,542 --> 00:49:07,842
I have known you since you were
a little girl. You have a good soul.

614
00:49:09,880 --> 00:49:12,077
I know that whatever
others might do,

615
00:49:12,118 --> 00:49:14,609
you are blameless.

616
00:49:14,654 --> 00:49:17,283
I know that.

617
00:49:17,324 --> 00:49:19,725
I... I do not...
that is, I cannot...

618
00:49:19,761 --> 00:49:21,696
Shh shh shh shh.

619
00:49:21,730 --> 00:49:23,961
It's all right.
There's no need.

620
00:49:28,305 --> 00:49:30,831
Tell your mother

621
00:49:30,875 --> 00:49:33,868
that I am grateful
for the gifts

622
00:49:33,912 --> 00:49:37,313
and that I treasure her
friendship as always.

623
00:49:42,957 --> 00:49:46,620
You must come and visit
me again. Will you?

624
00:49:46,660 --> 00:49:49,028
- I will.
- Promise?

625
00:49:50,399 --> 00:49:53,198
I want there to be no
ill feeling between us.

626
00:49:53,237 --> 00:49:55,501
I promise.

627
00:50:06,753 --> 00:50:08,949
You be a good girl.

628
00:50:10,492 --> 00:50:12,483
Do as you're told.

629
00:50:20,538 --> 00:50:22,770
I'll wait
for you outside.

630
00:50:24,810 --> 00:50:26,800
Shh shh shh.

631
00:50:48,906 --> 00:50:51,501
Bellona protect you.

632
00:50:52,812 --> 00:50:55,338
And Juno keep you.

633
00:52:29,100 --> 00:52:31,069
A fleet of ships

634
00:52:31,103 --> 00:52:33,162
has set sail for Greece

635
00:52:33,205 --> 00:52:35,766
carrying the army
of General Mark Antony.

636
00:52:38,245 --> 00:52:40,213
This month's public bread

637
00:52:40,248 --> 00:52:43,218
is provided by the Capitoline
Brotherhood of Millers.

638
00:52:43,252 --> 00:52:46,687
The Brotherhood uses
only the finest flour.

639
00:52:46,722 --> 00:52:49,420
True Roman bread,

640
00:52:49,460 --> 00:52:51,451
for true Romans.

641
00:53:09,151 --> 00:53:11,712
This is cac, this is!
I'm wet through.

642
00:53:11,755 --> 00:53:13,690
We're perfectly safe.

643
00:53:13,724 --> 00:53:15,749
A very good offering
was made to Triton!

644
00:53:15,793 --> 00:53:19,024
If Triton can't keep me drier
than this, he can suck my cock!

645
00:53:21,533 --> 00:53:24,628
Why can't you learn to
keep your fat mouth shut?!

