1
00:01:46,197 --> 00:01:48,290
Three more gone this morning.

2
00:01:49,967 --> 00:01:52,697
Outcasts and idiots.

3
00:01:52,737 --> 00:01:54,932
They all get restless.
With the fighting done,

4
00:01:54,972 --> 00:01:57,202
they want to be home with
money in their pockets,

5
00:01:57,241 --> 00:02:00,438
not sitting in this dismal cold and wet.

6
00:02:00,478 --> 00:02:02,571
None of the good men have run.

7
00:02:02,613 --> 00:02:04,342
Nor will they.

8
00:02:04,382 --> 00:02:06,646
Nor will they follow you to Rome.

9
00:02:06,684 --> 00:02:08,413
Not yet.

10
00:02:08,453 --> 00:02:10,353
Time is running out.

11
00:02:10,388 --> 00:02:13,050
We cannot wait here forever.

12
00:02:13,091 --> 00:02:16,492
This is a very precarious position.

13
00:02:16,527 --> 00:02:20,827
What happens in January
when your term runs out

14
00:02:20,865 --> 00:02:22,560
and we're still sitting here?

15
00:02:26,537 --> 00:02:29,836
The business of motivating men to fight
is a tricky matter, Posca.

16
00:02:29,874 --> 00:02:33,708
I would not expect a slave
to understand the subtleties.

17
00:02:33,745 --> 00:02:37,875
I trust an education in these subtleties will
begin shortly.

18
00:02:42,220 --> 00:02:44,120
500,000?
What's this?

19
00:02:44,155 --> 00:02:46,646
I put Mark Antony up for election
as People's Tribune.

20
00:02:46,691 --> 00:02:49,626
There were a lot of votes needed buying.

21
00:02:49,660 --> 00:02:52,686
Mark Antony for People's Tribune?

22
00:02:52,730 --> 00:02:54,664
But he is...

23
00:02:54,699 --> 00:02:57,099
- Um...
- You may speak.

24
00:02:57,135 --> 00:03:00,104
I had understood the Tribune
to be a sacred office

25
00:03:00,138 --> 00:03:02,299
with the power of veto
over the Senate.

26
00:03:02,340 --> 00:03:03,739
So it is.

27
00:03:03,775 --> 00:03:05,936
An office of great dignity
and seriousness.

28
00:03:05,977 --> 00:03:09,435
Perhaps you're right.

29
00:03:09,480 --> 00:03:13,883
We shall send Strabo along
to make sure Antony behaves himself.

30
00:03:26,931 --> 00:03:28,330
How far now?

31
00:03:28,366 --> 00:03:30,664
Three hours at pace.

32
00:03:30,701 --> 00:03:33,795
Ah- Hi!
Here I come, girls.

33
00:03:33,838 --> 00:03:35,772
I'm going to drink all the wine,
smoke all the smoke

34
00:03:35,807 --> 00:03:38,503
- And fuck every whore in the city.
- Show some dignity.

35
00:03:38,543 --> 00:03:41,273
- You're under the standard.
- Well, talk to him.

36
00:03:43,047 --> 00:03:45,038
He's not
under the standard.

37
00:03:46,551 --> 00:03:49,019
Three hours away from a wife
he hasn't seen in eight years.

38
00:03:49,053 --> 00:03:52,079
- The man's terrified.
- Surely a reunion is a happy event.

39
00:03:52,123 --> 00:03:53,954
- Talk of something else.
- Terrified.

40
00:03:53,991 --> 00:03:56,824
What if she's lost her teeth?
What if she's gotten skinny?

41
00:03:56,861 --> 00:03:58,988
What if she's been letting
other men between her legs?

42
00:03:59,030 --> 00:04:00,657
Silence!

43
00:04:35,066 --> 00:04:37,626
- They love him, eh?
- No matter.

44
00:04:37,668 --> 00:04:40,068
We are all men
of substance.

45
00:04:40,104 --> 00:04:43,198
Let them have the love of the plebs
and the proles.

46
00:04:53,017 --> 00:04:54,848
This won't take long,
will it?

47
00:04:54,886 --> 00:04:56,945
We can hope, Dominus.

48
00:04:56,988 --> 00:05:00,116
- Vorenus, you may dismiss the men.
- Sir.

49
00:05:00,157 --> 00:05:02,955
And then you may dismiss yourself
until I send for you.

50
00:05:02,994 --> 00:05:04,461
Have some fun.

51
00:05:04,495 --> 00:05:07,987
But first, take the boy
back to Atia.

52
00:05:08,032 --> 00:05:10,023
Get your reward, eh?

53
00:05:10,067 --> 00:05:13,434
Boy, tell your lovely mother
I will see her later.

54
00:05:15,373 --> 00:05:17,534
Let's get this over with.

55
00:05:24,815 --> 00:05:26,476
Shh!

56
00:05:33,291 --> 00:05:35,725
You, leave this house
this moment.

57
00:05:35,760 --> 00:05:37,728
I will not.
Octavia is my rightful wife.

58
00:05:37,762 --> 00:05:40,390
- You defy Caesar?
- A fig for Caesar!

59
00:05:40,431 --> 00:05:42,456
By the five furies,
if I were not a genteel woman,

60
00:05:42,500 --> 00:05:46,027
I would have you flayed
and hung from a bracket at the door!

61
00:05:46,070 --> 00:05:47,594
- Castor?
- Domina?

62
00:05:47,638 --> 00:05:49,469
Fetch the dogs!

63
00:05:53,477 --> 00:05:55,707
Insolent wretch!

64
00:05:55,746 --> 00:05:58,579
I tell you, my honey,
you are well rid of that one.

65
00:05:58,616 --> 00:06:00,015
I hate you.

66
00:06:00,051 --> 00:06:01,985
I hate you!
I hate you!

67
00:06:02,987 --> 00:06:04,511
Silly girl.

68
00:06:16,300 --> 00:06:18,962
I'm only trying to do my best for her.
Why can't she see that?

69
00:06:19,003 --> 00:06:20,527
She is young.

70
00:06:20,571 --> 00:06:22,869
- Master Octavian!
- Baby boy!

71
00:06:22,907 --> 00:06:25,375
My poor rabbit!

72
00:06:25,409 --> 00:06:27,434
Oh!

73
00:06:28,713 --> 00:06:32,672
So thin.
Was it very horrible?

74
00:06:32,717 --> 00:06:34,480
Of course it was,
I can't even imagine.

75
00:06:34,518 --> 00:06:36,076
We shan't even
talk about it.

76
00:06:36,120 --> 00:06:38,588
We should just put it
totally out of our minds.

77
00:06:38,623 --> 00:06:40,488
You're back
safe at home now.

78
00:06:43,628 --> 00:06:45,095
But who are those?

79
00:06:45,129 --> 00:06:47,427
You are to be very good
to them, Mother.

80
00:06:47,465 --> 00:06:49,865
They are particular
friends of mine.

81
00:06:49,900 --> 00:06:52,368
Friends?
In what particular?

82
00:06:52,403 --> 00:06:54,598
These are the men
that took me from captivity.

83
00:06:54,639 --> 00:06:57,608
First Spear Centurion
Lucius Vorenus.

84
00:06:59,243 --> 00:07:01,438
And Legionary Titus Pullo.

85
00:07:01,479 --> 00:07:04,642
So, we embrace you.

86
00:07:04,682 --> 00:07:06,809
Good fearsome
specimens you are.

87
00:07:06,851 --> 00:07:09,877
I wonder it took you so long
to subdue those odious Gauls.

88
00:07:09,920 --> 00:07:11,615
There was a great many
of them, ma'am.

89
00:07:11,656 --> 00:07:14,352
Great many...very good.

90
00:07:14,392 --> 00:07:15,882
We'll be away then, sir.

91
00:07:15,926 --> 00:07:17,894
Oh, but you must be
rewarded before you go.

92
00:07:17,928 --> 00:07:20,226
- Castor, bring me my purse.
- That won't be necessary.

93
00:07:20,264 --> 00:07:22,198
Will it not?
I don't want to break any regulations...

94
00:07:22,233 --> 00:07:23,700
They shall stay
and eat, Mother.

95
00:07:23,734 --> 00:07:25,793
Of course! There shall be bread
and meat put out in the kitchen.

96
00:07:25,836 --> 00:07:27,428
I mean,
they shall eat with us.

97
00:07:27,471 --> 00:07:30,338
Obliged, sir,
but I must go to my wife.

98
00:07:30,374 --> 00:07:33,741
Your wife has waited eight years.
She can wait a little longer.

99
00:07:33,778 --> 00:07:35,712
Caesar has given them
honorary horses,

100
00:07:35,746 --> 00:07:37,646
and they ride
with the standard.

101
00:07:37,682 --> 00:07:40,276
It's perfectly acceptable
to eat with them.

102
00:07:40,317 --> 00:07:42,512
Splendid idea.

103
00:07:42,553 --> 00:07:47,547
It's symbolic. We shall
all dine together as equals.

104
00:07:51,629 --> 00:07:53,961
- What's that?
- Oh, it's just your sister.

105
00:07:53,998 --> 00:07:56,262
- Is she all right?
- Women's troubles.

106
00:07:56,300 --> 00:07:58,268
Nothing a good leeching
won't cure.

107
00:08:06,944 --> 00:08:11,574
Jupiter Fulgor, we ask you to guide
and protect this man,

108
00:08:11,615 --> 00:08:15,642
Marcus Antonius,
newly elected Tribune of plebs,

109
00:08:15,686 --> 00:08:17,313
champion of the people.

110
00:08:17,354 --> 00:08:20,255
How many dead
altogether?

111
00:08:20,291 --> 00:08:24,022
I don't know.
I lost count ages ago.

112
00:08:24,061 --> 00:08:25,653
Lots though.

113
00:08:25,696 --> 00:08:27,425
And you, Lucius?

114
00:08:27,465 --> 00:08:30,491
309 fighting men.
I don't keep count on civilians.

115
00:08:30,534 --> 00:08:32,695
- You're very exact.
- The war temple requires

116
00:08:32,737 --> 00:08:34,898
an exact number
when you make an offering.

117
00:08:34,939 --> 00:08:36,907
That's a lot
of wine and goats.

118
00:08:36,941 --> 00:08:41,310
The priests offer
a discount when you pass 100.

119
00:08:41,345 --> 00:08:43,540
Priests!
Crooks, many of them.

120
00:08:43,581 --> 00:08:46,277
I just talk direct to whatever God
I'm doing business with.

121
00:08:46,317 --> 00:08:48,285
Bugger the priests!

122
00:08:48,319 --> 00:08:50,617
Too few people can be
bothered to do things

123
00:08:50,654 --> 00:08:52,747
the proper,
all- Roman way.

124
00:08:52,790 --> 00:08:56,055
- I commend you, Lucius.
- Vorenus is a strict Catonian.

125
00:08:56,093 --> 00:08:57,890
I believe in the divinity
of the Republic.

126
00:08:57,928 --> 00:09:01,830
If Cato believes the same,
then I suppose I am a Catonian.

127
00:09:01,866 --> 00:09:04,061
But Cato represents
the rights of the nobility.

128
00:09:04,101 --> 00:09:07,332
Surely a plebian like yourself
would like to see some changes made.

129
00:09:07,371 --> 00:09:11,330
It should remain as it was
at the founding of the Republic.

130
00:09:11,375 --> 00:09:12,637
Why should that change?

131
00:09:12,676 --> 00:09:14,268
Because the Roman people
are suffering.

132
00:09:14,311 --> 00:09:16,609
Because slaves
have taken all the work.

133
00:09:16,647 --> 00:09:18,512
Because nobles
have taken all the land,

134
00:09:18,549 --> 00:09:21,211
and the streets are full of the homeless
and the starving.

135
00:09:21,252 --> 00:09:23,413
Well, I had no idea my son
was such a firebrand.

136
00:09:23,454 --> 00:09:25,615
The nobles say
that Caesar is a war criminal.

137
00:09:25,656 --> 00:09:28,147
They say that he wishes to march on Rome
and make himself king.

138
00:09:28,192 --> 00:09:31,093
That is sacrilege.
No man of honor would follow him.

139
00:09:31,128 --> 00:09:34,825
Well, I'm no man of honor then, 'cause
I say that Caesar should ride in here

140
00:09:34,865 --> 00:09:38,801
with elephants and squash Pompey
and Cato and anybody else that wants it.

141
00:09:38,836 --> 00:09:40,463
Never mind the law.
That's what I say.

142
00:09:40,504 --> 00:09:42,301
You say that because
you govern your reason

143
00:09:42,339 --> 00:09:44,000
no better
than you govern your tongue.

144
00:09:44,041 --> 00:09:47,738
Forgive me, it's my fault
for mixing politics and wine.

145
00:09:47,778 --> 00:09:50,975
More tench?
A dormouse perhaps?

146
00:09:51,015 --> 00:09:52,607
Thank you, I won't.

147
00:09:52,650 --> 00:09:54,709
Don't mind my saying it,

148
00:09:54,752 --> 00:09:56,982
but you two make
unlikely friends.

149
00:09:57,021 --> 00:09:59,489
We are not friends.
I am his superior officer.

150
00:09:59,523 --> 00:10:01,013
By virtue of rank,
if nothing else.

151
00:10:01,058 --> 00:10:03,492
That is enough
from you!

152
00:10:05,696 --> 00:10:07,425
Please forgive
our vulgar ways, madam.

153
00:10:07,464 --> 00:10:09,329
We are not fit
for your presence.

154
00:10:09,366 --> 00:10:11,834
Not at all. I've enjoyed
your company immensely.

155
00:10:11,869 --> 00:10:13,769
It's been most refreshing.

156
00:10:13,804 --> 00:10:15,795
And with your permission,
we shall...

157
00:10:15,840 --> 00:10:17,671
leave you.

158
00:10:20,110 --> 00:10:21,907
Do come
and visit us again.

159
00:10:21,946 --> 00:10:24,039
Octavian needs
reliable friends.

160
00:10:24,081 --> 00:10:25,946
He may depend on you,
I trust.

161
00:10:25,983 --> 00:10:27,450
As you say, madam.

162
00:10:36,227 --> 00:10:39,560
- Say again?
- I did not speak.

163
00:10:39,597 --> 00:10:41,565
I go this way.

164
00:10:41,599 --> 00:10:44,363
My home is behind the street
of the cloth dyers, if you...

165
00:10:44,401 --> 00:10:46,665
Go with fortune, sir.

166
00:10:49,673 --> 00:10:51,800
The cleaner brothels
are in the Suburra,

167
00:10:51,842 --> 00:10:54,140
next to
the Venereal Temple.

168
00:11:25,943 --> 00:11:27,433
Niobe.

169
00:11:39,556 --> 00:11:41,456
You're alive.

170
00:11:44,094 --> 00:11:45,823
What child is that?

171
00:11:47,531 --> 00:11:49,362
Answer me.

172
00:11:49,400 --> 00:11:51,800
What child is that?

173
00:11:53,170 --> 00:11:55,229
He's your grandson.

174
00:11:55,272 --> 00:11:58,503
Speak sense, whore.

175
00:11:58,542 --> 00:12:00,567
Wait, now.

176
00:12:00,611 --> 00:12:03,444
Your grandson...
the son of your daughter.

177
00:12:03,480 --> 00:12:06,074
- My daughter is only...
- She's 13, near 14.

178
00:12:06,116 --> 00:12:09,176
- A son by who?
- Crito, a Drover's boy.

179
00:12:10,788 --> 00:12:13,552
His name is Lucius.

180
00:12:13,590 --> 00:12:15,649
Niobe, stop.

181
00:12:15,693 --> 00:12:18,594
I order you to stop!

182
00:12:22,599 --> 00:12:24,362
Your father's home.

183
00:12:33,277 --> 00:12:35,268
Girls,
this is your father.

184
00:12:39,950 --> 00:12:43,613
Daughters, I'm very pleased
to find you healthy and good looking.

185
00:12:43,654 --> 00:12:45,451
A benefice you favor
your mother, eh?

186
00:12:45,489 --> 00:12:48,356
Now you see how ugly
your father is.

187
00:12:48,392 --> 00:12:50,087
Come here.

188
00:12:51,929 --> 00:12:54,762
She's not simple,
is she?

189
00:12:54,798 --> 00:12:58,666
Greet your father properly
as you've been taught to do.

190
00:13:39,977 --> 00:13:42,309
Your pay stopped coming
a year ago.

191
00:13:43,680 --> 00:13:45,147
The paymaster said
you must be dead.

192
00:13:45,182 --> 00:13:47,082
They said they don't
make mistakes.

193
00:13:48,786 --> 00:13:51,152
Damned fools!
I'll have it seen to.

194
00:13:53,323 --> 00:13:55,223
A bit of a surprise
to see me then?

195
00:13:56,393 --> 00:13:58,554
A bit surprised
to be called "whore."

196
00:14:00,464 --> 00:14:04,059
That was...wrong.

197
00:14:04,101 --> 00:14:06,569
I am sorry for it.

198
00:14:06,603 --> 00:14:08,969
- A whore in front of everybody.
- I said sorry.

199
00:14:26,890 --> 00:14:30,121
- Is it as you like it?
- Less salt next time.

200
00:14:34,198 --> 00:14:37,793
So, how did you manage
for money?

201
00:14:37,835 --> 00:14:40,827
My sister Lyde
and her husband helped us out.

202
00:14:42,139 --> 00:14:44,505
Well, you won't need
their help anymore.

203
00:14:47,010 --> 00:14:50,502
The big phallus is off
a Suevi I killed in the Rhinelands...

204
00:14:50,547 --> 00:14:54,074
a very strong
and fierce people.

205
00:14:54,118 --> 00:14:56,279
Nice.

206
00:14:58,322 --> 00:15:00,552
My official spoils
I've put into slaves.

207
00:15:00,591 --> 00:15:02,821
They're at the market.

208
00:15:02,860 --> 00:15:05,454
I should clear
10,000 denarii.

209
00:15:06,463 --> 00:15:08,488
That's good news.

210
00:15:19,243 --> 00:15:21,643
Come with me, sir.

211
00:15:54,011 --> 00:15:57,879
By grace of Roma,
for twelve moons hence,

212
00:15:57,915 --> 00:16:01,214
thou art Tribune
of Plebs.

213
00:16:01,251 --> 00:16:04,118
About time.

214
00:16:04,154 --> 00:16:07,419
- I need a drink.
- Indeed, sir.

215
00:16:07,457 --> 00:16:09,652
Perhaps after the meeting.

216
00:16:09,693 --> 00:16:11,354
Cicero.

217
00:16:11,395 --> 00:16:14,990
My dear Atia,
a pleasure.

218
00:16:15,032 --> 00:16:18,297
Forgive us for imposing
at such a ludicrous hour.

219
00:16:18,335 --> 00:16:22,601
Not at all, I adore it. The secrecy,
the intrigue...it's most thrilling.

220
00:16:22,639 --> 00:16:26,075
Comprehend, woman,
this meeting is invisible.

221
00:16:26,109 --> 00:16:29,340
Be assured, Cato,
I do not see you.

222
00:16:33,750 --> 00:16:35,217
General Antony, we are...

223
00:16:35,252 --> 00:16:38,813
Oh God,
your beauty is painful.

224
00:16:38,855 --> 00:16:41,688
You are the crucifix
of Venus.

225
00:16:43,627 --> 00:16:45,117
Let me die in your arms.

226
00:16:45,162 --> 00:16:48,154
'Sist, Antony.

227
00:16:48,198 --> 00:16:50,894
- Good evening to you all.
- General Antony.

228
00:16:50,934 --> 00:16:53,368
Tribune Antony,
if you please.

229
00:16:53,403 --> 00:16:56,201
You're inside the sacred
precincts of Rome,

230
00:16:56,240 --> 00:16:59,175
but yet you wear
the bloody red cloak of a soldier.

231
00:16:59,209 --> 00:17:01,507
Che brutta figura!

232
00:17:01,545 --> 00:17:03,376
It completely fell
from my mind.

233
00:17:03,413 --> 00:17:07,645
I'm most extremely sorry.
Will you forgive me, friend Cato?

234
00:17:09,286 --> 00:17:11,948
Atia, please, will you
take this and burn it?

235
00:17:11,989 --> 00:17:16,483
- That's not necessary.
- Is it not? Oh, bene.

236
00:17:16,526 --> 00:17:19,427
Then let's stop all this blathering
and get down to business.

237
00:17:19,463 --> 00:17:20,896
Blathering you say?

238
00:17:20,931 --> 00:17:24,731
What a congerie of heroes.
Such vim!

239
00:17:24,768 --> 00:17:27,032
I feel
like Helen of Troy.

240
00:17:27,070 --> 00:17:29,368
Would you adjourn
to the courtyard?

241
00:17:29,406 --> 00:17:32,273
Speak, young Marcus.
What have you to tell us?

242
00:17:32,309 --> 00:17:35,972
I have been delegated by Caesar
to negotiate a compromise.

243
00:17:36,013 --> 00:17:37,913
Caesar wishes
to avoid bloodshed.

244
00:17:37,948 --> 00:17:41,440
He wishes to be seen
as a man of reason and probity.

245
00:17:41,485 --> 00:17:44,613
Therefore, when his present term
as governor of Gaul has ended,

246
00:17:44,655 --> 00:17:48,284
he is willing to accept command
of a single legion province.

247
00:17:48,325 --> 00:17:50,623
Illyria, by preference.

248
00:17:50,661 --> 00:17:54,392
- I don't understand.
- Command of a province...

249
00:17:54,431 --> 00:17:56,456
so he will have
legal immunity.

250
00:17:56,500 --> 00:18:00,937
So that none of you rascals
can go dragging him through the courts.

251
00:18:00,971 --> 00:18:03,371
We're here
to discuss the terms

252
00:18:03,407 --> 00:18:05,875
of Caesar's resignation.

253
00:18:07,010 --> 00:18:09,410
He could have
avoided prosecution

254
00:18:09,446 --> 00:18:11,607
by accepting
a few years banishment.

255
00:18:11,648 --> 00:18:13,582
Banishment for what?

256
00:18:13,617 --> 00:18:15,278
For fomenting a tyranny.

257
00:18:15,319 --> 00:18:17,810
Illegal warfare,
theft,

258
00:18:17,854 --> 00:18:19,651
murder, treason!

259
00:18:19,690 --> 00:18:22,090
And what shall be
your punishment, Pompey,

260
00:18:22,125 --> 00:18:24,025
for betraying a friend,

261
00:18:24,061 --> 00:18:25,688
for deserting the cause
of your people,

262
00:18:25,729 --> 00:18:28,721
for allying yourself
with these so- Called noblemen.

263
00:18:28,765 --> 00:18:31,791
- What punishment for you?
- Impudent whelp!

264
00:18:31,835 --> 00:18:35,965
The man's term of office
ends in two weeks.

265
00:18:36,006 --> 00:18:38,873
- We say six months.
- Two weeks!

266
00:18:38,909 --> 00:18:41,400
He sits alone in Ravenna

267
00:18:41,445 --> 00:18:43,845
with one mutinous skeleton
of a legion

268
00:18:43,880 --> 00:18:46,610
and he dares
to dictate terms to me?!

269
00:18:46,650 --> 00:18:49,312
Caesar has many more legions
than the 13th.

270
00:18:49,353 --> 00:18:51,446
On the far side
of the Alps.

271
00:18:51,488 --> 00:18:53,388
Winter does not
last forever.

272
00:18:53,423 --> 00:18:56,449
Spring comes,
snows melt.

273
00:18:56,493 --> 00:18:58,961
- That's a threat!
- I assure you, it is no threat.

274
00:18:58,995 --> 00:19:02,396
Snows always melt.

275
00:19:02,432 --> 00:19:04,229
If he does not
get a province?

276
00:19:04,267 --> 00:19:08,294
Caesar will take
all measures required

277
00:19:08,338 --> 00:19:11,136
to protect
both his interests

278
00:19:11,174 --> 00:19:12,903
and those
of the Republic.

279
00:19:12,943 --> 00:19:15,070
I am grieved
and surprised.

280
00:19:15,112 --> 00:19:18,878
I had hoped we would have
a rational negotiation.

281
00:19:18,915 --> 00:19:21,850
If that is his last word,
we shall go.

282
00:19:26,356 --> 00:19:28,517
Then we have
no more business.

283
00:19:28,558 --> 00:19:30,185
Caesar is bluffing.

284
00:19:30,227 --> 00:19:32,525
He wishes to appear
supremely confident.

285
00:19:32,562 --> 00:19:35,759
Evidently he is desperately weak,
weaker than we'd thought.

286
00:19:35,799 --> 00:19:39,257
This is a last ditch attempt
to frighten us into making concessions,

287
00:19:39,302 --> 00:19:41,634
while he still has
the semblance of an army.

288
00:19:41,671 --> 00:19:43,639
He's weak, Cicero.
Dying.

289
00:19:43,673 --> 00:19:46,801
Is that not when all the proverbs
tell us to be wary?

290
00:19:46,843 --> 00:19:51,109
Does not the dying serpent
bite deepest?

291
00:20:09,266 --> 00:20:10,756
Let's play.

292
00:20:10,801 --> 00:20:13,292
- Where are you from, friend?
- 13th.

293
00:20:13,336 --> 00:20:15,736
Better keep that quiet.

294
00:20:15,772 --> 00:20:18,502
This is deep
Pompeian territory.

295
00:20:18,542 --> 00:20:20,510
So, we're all Romans, eh?

296
00:20:30,520 --> 00:20:32,420
Come on, ladies,
hear me now.

297
00:20:32,456 --> 00:20:35,254
Furies and River Gods
for five.

298
00:21:22,005 --> 00:21:24,269
"You will be pleased
to hear

299
00:21:24,307 --> 00:21:27,140
that General Antony was
as blithely arrogant

300
00:21:27,177 --> 00:21:29,975
and provocative
as one could hope for.

301
00:21:31,548 --> 00:21:34,813
And Pompey and Cato
were deeply offended

302
00:21:34,851 --> 00:21:38,617
by your negotiating
position."

303
00:21:38,655 --> 00:21:41,647
Wise Men and Graces
on four!

304
00:21:43,159 --> 00:21:45,059
Those Graces don't like you,
I think.

305
00:21:45,095 --> 00:21:48,861
- They piss on your face.
- They piss on my face?

306
00:21:48,899 --> 00:21:52,528
- They piss on my face?!
- Calm, brother.

307
00:21:52,569 --> 00:21:54,935
Man has an ill way
with him.

308
00:21:54,971 --> 00:21:58,771
He's lost a lot of money.
He means no offense...

309
00:21:58,808 --> 00:22:00,708
- Do you?
- None at all.

310
00:22:03,813 --> 00:22:05,644
Twin River Gods over two.

311
00:22:05,682 --> 00:22:07,809
Come on,
you mumping cunnies!

312
00:22:16,660 --> 00:22:18,127
Graces...

313
00:22:18,161 --> 00:22:19,719
over four.

314
00:22:23,867 --> 00:22:27,234
How do you feel now, soldier?
Feel good?

315
00:23:44,047 --> 00:23:46,675
- Who is this man?
- Run and get a doctor!

316
00:23:46,716 --> 00:23:48,047
I don't want
people dying in my house!

317
00:23:48,084 --> 00:23:49,642
Do as I say, woman!

318
00:24:11,641 --> 00:24:13,006
Oh!

319
00:25:12,936 --> 00:25:17,396
There will be copious pus...
first putrid, then wholesome...

320
00:25:17,440 --> 00:25:20,204
and mayhap
fits of the spleen,

321
00:25:20,243 --> 00:25:22,609
but that will be
all to the good.

322
00:25:22,645 --> 00:25:25,739
A purging of the malignancy
will follow.

323
00:25:25,782 --> 00:25:28,342
This is brass.

324
00:25:30,386 --> 00:25:32,251
Come.

325
00:25:32,288 --> 00:25:34,051
When will he wake up?

326
00:25:34,090 --> 00:25:37,389
Today, tomorrow,
maybe never.

327
00:25:40,830 --> 00:25:43,264
You might try
an offering to Spes.

328
00:25:43,299 --> 00:25:45,665
A white rabbit
often works.

329
00:25:45,702 --> 00:25:49,160
I'll send my boy tomorrow
to check the dressings.

330
00:25:52,142 --> 00:25:55,077
- What misery!
- It's only blood.

331
00:25:55,111 --> 00:25:57,306
It'll wash.

332
00:25:57,347 --> 00:25:59,076
Where are you going?

333
00:25:59,115 --> 00:26:00,742
I have business.

334
00:26:00,784 --> 00:26:02,911
Business?
What business?

335
00:26:04,254 --> 00:26:06,814
I understand that you are upset,
but I will ask you

336
00:26:06,856 --> 00:26:09,324
do not question me
in that tone.

337
00:26:13,396 --> 00:26:15,728
Tone.

338
00:26:15,765 --> 00:26:17,630
My father's cock!

339
00:26:17,667 --> 00:26:19,430
How's that for tone?!

340
00:26:21,337 --> 00:26:23,965
50, 50.
55.

341
00:26:24,007 --> 00:26:26,999
55, 55.
60.

342
00:26:27,043 --> 00:26:29,011
60, 60...sold!

343
00:26:29,045 --> 00:26:32,503
40.
40, 40, 45.

344
00:26:32,549 --> 00:26:36,144
45, 45, 45.
50.

345
00:26:36,186 --> 00:26:39,553
50.
50, 50. 55.

346
00:26:39,589 --> 00:26:44,492
This is bona stock,
but it's all skin and bone, eh?

347
00:26:44,527 --> 00:26:46,119
You want a good price.

348
00:26:46,162 --> 00:26:49,427
Let us feed them up,
put some fat on them.

349
00:26:49,465 --> 00:26:53,765
Couple weeks of easy living, and these
puppies will sell like duck hearts.

350
00:26:53,803 --> 00:26:55,794
Is that expensive,
fodder and storage?

351
00:26:55,839 --> 00:26:59,070
No! You'll recoup feed
and storage double.

352
00:27:05,181 --> 00:27:08,150
Beautiful, neh?
A real showman.

353
00:27:08,184 --> 00:27:10,846
I am no judge
of the sand,

354
00:27:10,887 --> 00:27:14,379
but sure,
anyone can see

355
00:27:14,424 --> 00:27:18,053
he is rare large
and aggressive.

356
00:27:20,697 --> 00:27:23,427
When the Senate
meets tomorrow,

357
00:27:23,466 --> 00:27:27,527
Scipio will propose
an ultimatum be put to Caesar.

358
00:27:27,570 --> 00:27:30,937
I ask you as a friend
to support the proposal

359
00:27:30,974 --> 00:27:33,636
and to enjoin your many friends
to do the same.

360
00:27:33,676 --> 00:27:36,736
Oh, I have not
so many friends as all that.

361
00:27:36,779 --> 00:27:39,145
Ah, the moderates
follow you like sheep.

362
00:27:39,182 --> 00:27:41,980
- Your vote is critical.
- The ultimatum is?

363
00:27:42,018 --> 00:27:44,486
Caesar's term
of office is over.

364
00:27:44,520 --> 00:27:46,545
He must immediately
disband his men,

365
00:27:46,589 --> 00:27:49,057
resign his command,
and return for trial...

366
00:27:49,092 --> 00:27:52,619
else be considered an Enemy
of the Senate and People of Rome.

367
00:27:52,662 --> 00:27:55,426
But he cannot accept that.

368
00:27:55,465 --> 00:27:57,296
Not without dishonor.

369
00:27:57,333 --> 00:28:01,360
Once declared hostile, he has nothing
to lose...he will fight at any cost.

370
00:28:01,404 --> 00:28:02,666
You are declaring war!

371
00:28:02,705 --> 00:28:06,232
Caesar will not have to
accept or refuse the terms,

372
00:28:06,276 --> 00:28:10,235
because Mark Antony
will immediately use Tribune's Veto.

373
00:28:10,280 --> 00:28:11,770
But then,
what is your purpose?

374
00:28:11,814 --> 00:28:13,782
If the Senate votes
against him,

375
00:28:13,816 --> 00:28:16,307
Caesar will
finally understand

376
00:28:16,352 --> 00:28:18,980
that he is alone
against all.

377
00:28:19,022 --> 00:28:21,786
Of course, anything but
an overwhelming vote

378
00:28:21,824 --> 00:28:24,588
encourages Caesar to think
he still has friends and hope.

379
00:28:30,733 --> 00:28:33,930
I am no friend to Caesar,
nor any tyrant,

380
00:28:33,970 --> 00:28:35,870
but I cannot vote
for a proposal

381
00:28:35,905 --> 00:28:38,703
I do not wish to see realized.
It would be highly irreligious.

382
00:28:38,741 --> 00:28:41,266
I have made
a vow to Jupiter.

383
00:28:41,311 --> 00:28:44,337
Unless I get the full backing
of the Senate tomorrow,

384
00:28:44,380 --> 00:28:47,781
I and all my legions
will sail for Spain

385
00:28:47,817 --> 00:28:50,650
and leave you gentlemen
to your own defenses.

386
00:29:01,230 --> 00:29:03,027
This is he?
Crito?

387
00:29:03,066 --> 00:29:05,796
He's a good boy
from good family.

388
00:29:05,835 --> 00:29:08,235
Good enough to seed
a child of the Vorenii

389
00:29:08,271 --> 00:29:10,398
who fought
at Magnesia and Zama?

390
00:29:10,440 --> 00:29:13,273
- I don't rightly know, sir.
- You don't rightly know?!

391
00:29:13,309 --> 00:29:15,470
Do you know that
this girl is my property?

392
00:29:15,511 --> 00:29:17,342
That you should have
asked my permission

393
00:29:17,380 --> 00:29:19,041
before you coupled
with her?

394
00:29:19,082 --> 00:29:21,312
- I'm sorry, sir.
- I am within my rights

395
00:29:21,351 --> 00:29:23,080
to kill you
here and now.

396
00:29:23,119 --> 00:29:25,178
- Papa, please.
- Don't you start sniffling.

397
00:29:25,221 --> 00:29:27,917
You should have thought of this
before you spread your legs.

398
00:29:27,957 --> 00:29:29,891
They meant you
no disrespect.

399
00:29:29,926 --> 00:29:31,655
What they did
was only natural.

400
00:29:31,694 --> 00:29:33,389
They're young
and they love each other.

401
00:29:33,429 --> 00:29:34,953
That's no excuse.

402
00:29:34,998 --> 00:29:37,592
His mother's family are well- Found
in Ostia for many generations,

403
00:29:37,633 --> 00:29:40,431
and his father is
a successful drover.

404
00:29:40,470 --> 00:29:42,665
They have a house
in the southern crossroads.

405
00:29:42,705 --> 00:29:45,071
A house built from
cattle dung no doubt.

406
00:29:45,108 --> 00:29:47,872
It's very hygienic, sir.
There's no smell.

407
00:29:49,012 --> 00:29:50,980
Huh!

408
00:29:51,014 --> 00:29:53,505
There's money
in droving, at least.

409
00:29:53,549 --> 00:29:55,107
Good money, sir.

410
00:29:55,151 --> 00:29:57,415
I'm on the Capua run mostly...

411
00:29:57,453 --> 00:29:59,853
that's 5,000 head
a week sometimes, sir.

412
00:30:01,124 --> 00:30:04,116
He cannot be but what he is.
When are you a man?

413
00:30:04,160 --> 00:30:07,095
- Next month, sir.
- Next month.

414
00:30:10,666 --> 00:30:12,896
Very well,
you may marry my daughter.

415
00:30:12,935 --> 00:30:16,837
Assure your good people that
the dowry will be appropriate.

416
00:30:26,082 --> 00:30:28,448
He really is
a good boy.

417
00:30:28,484 --> 00:30:31,351
You should be pleased.

418
00:30:31,387 --> 00:30:34,618
My daughter's virginity
has been taken

419
00:30:34,657 --> 00:30:38,787
and my first grandson spawned,
by an ill- Favored prole.

420
00:30:38,828 --> 00:30:40,819
How can I be pleased?

421
00:30:40,863 --> 00:30:42,831
- He makes her happy.
- She's an idiot then.

422
00:30:42,865 --> 00:30:44,856
What a brute you are!

423
00:31:21,304 --> 00:31:26,241
The Senate will hear
Metullus Scipio.

424
00:31:26,275 --> 00:31:28,641
Speak! Speak!

425
00:31:28,678 --> 00:31:33,809
Conscript fathers,
I propose a formal motion.

426
00:31:33,850 --> 00:31:36,444
Unless Gaius Julius Caesar

427
00:31:36,486 --> 00:31:40,047
immediately lays down
his command,

428
00:31:40,089 --> 00:31:44,116
disbands his legions
and returns to Rome for trial,

429
00:31:44,160 --> 00:31:48,597
this sacred assembly
will declare him a public enemy

430
00:31:48,631 --> 00:31:51,794
of the Senate
and People of Rome!

431
00:31:51,834 --> 00:31:55,565
After which time
it will be the duty

432
00:31:55,605 --> 00:31:59,405
and the obligation of every Roman
to do him harm

433
00:31:59,442 --> 00:32:02,741
or to kill him
if they are able!

434
00:32:11,521 --> 00:32:14,581
A motion is proposed.

435
00:32:14,624 --> 00:32:17,593
Those in favor,
make it known.

436
00:32:50,960 --> 00:32:55,226
The motion is carried
by clear numbers.

437
00:32:57,567 --> 00:32:59,626
Antony!

438
00:32:59,669 --> 00:33:02,194
Veto the motion!

439
00:33:02,238 --> 00:33:05,469
Stand up!
Veto the motion!

440
00:33:07,410 --> 00:33:11,540
I demand the floor!
I demand the floor!

441
00:33:11,581 --> 00:33:14,778
- Give him the floor!
- I veto the motion!

442
00:33:14,817 --> 00:33:16,808
Tribune vetoes
the motion!

443
00:33:20,056 --> 00:33:22,081
Scipio's motion
against Caesar...

444
00:33:22,124 --> 00:33:24,251
it doesn't stand,
does it?

445
00:33:24,293 --> 00:33:26,090
Stands.

446
00:33:26,128 --> 00:33:28,221
Entered in the annals.

447
00:33:28,264 --> 00:33:32,496
Despite that Tribune
raised his veto?

448
00:33:32,535 --> 00:33:36,938
Not heard,
not fully admitted.

449
00:33:36,973 --> 00:33:39,305
No weight.

450
00:33:39,342 --> 00:33:41,503
The motion stands.

451
00:33:41,544 --> 00:33:43,478
Let me be clear
with you.

452
00:33:43,512 --> 00:33:45,912
I do not wish

453
00:33:45,948 --> 00:33:48,075
that a motion
as important as this

454
00:33:48,117 --> 00:33:50,813
should stand
on a mere trick of procedure.

455
00:33:50,853 --> 00:33:52,582
Trick, you say?

456
00:33:52,622 --> 00:33:55,557
This is
a religious matter.

457
00:33:55,591 --> 00:33:58,355
There are no tricks
in religion.

458
00:34:00,463 --> 00:34:04,661
Session was not
formally ended, correct?

459
00:34:05,735 --> 00:34:09,034
- Correct.
- So, when we reconvene,

460
00:34:09,071 --> 00:34:11,869
it will formally
be the same session.

461
00:34:11,907 --> 00:34:13,374
Mm- Hmm.

462
00:34:13,409 --> 00:34:16,674
Then Tribune Antony
may use veto on the motion.

463
00:34:16,712 --> 00:34:18,407
Um...

464
00:34:23,552 --> 00:34:25,042
That is so.

465
00:34:26,155 --> 00:34:29,886
Juno Inferna!
Senile old fool,

466
00:34:29,925 --> 00:34:31,756
why didn't you say so
to begin with?

467
00:34:31,794 --> 00:34:35,787
Mark Antony must not be harmed
or hindered in any way.

468
00:34:35,831 --> 00:34:37,230
- But...
- In any way!

469
00:34:37,266 --> 00:34:39,257
It is vitally important
that he be allowed

470
00:34:39,302 --> 00:34:40,929
to veto the motion.

471
00:34:40,970 --> 00:34:43,768
If he does not,
Caesar is declared a traitor.

472
00:34:43,806 --> 00:34:46,297
Then he has no choice
but to oppose me openly,

473
00:34:46,342 --> 00:34:49,539
which means civil war.
Antony must not be harmed!

474
00:34:49,578 --> 00:34:51,603
Dominus, good news.

475
00:34:51,647 --> 00:34:54,673
The Senate
will reconvene tomorrow.

476
00:34:54,717 --> 00:34:56,981
Formally,
it is the same session,

477
00:34:57,019 --> 00:35:00,250
so you may yet exercise
your veto on the motion.

478
00:35:00,289 --> 00:35:03,156
Hmm. Unless Pompey
tries to stop me.

479
00:35:03,192 --> 00:35:06,684
True, he may
very well try.

480
00:35:06,729 --> 00:35:08,754
Rally the men together.

481
00:35:09,832 --> 00:35:11,493
Vorenus...

482
00:35:11,534 --> 00:35:13,502
all of them.

483
00:35:14,704 --> 00:35:19,631
** Run and hide **

484
00:35:21,210 --> 00:35:23,940
** The 13th are coming **

485
00:35:23,979 --> 00:35:27,278
** And your men
are all dead! **

486
00:35:28,718 --> 00:35:30,811
I put extra nutmeg in,
as you like it.

487
00:35:30,853 --> 00:35:33,219
Oh, marry me, goddess.

488
00:35:33,255 --> 00:35:36,224
What, a porcine object
like you?

489
00:35:36,258 --> 00:35:39,523
Besides, I am already wed,
thanks be to evil spirits.

490
00:35:39,562 --> 00:35:42,360
You are wrong, friend- Wife.
He is a good man, your man.

491
00:35:42,398 --> 00:35:44,559
A good man you say?

492
00:35:44,600 --> 00:35:46,500
For years and years,
I'd lie awake at night

493
00:35:46,535 --> 00:35:49,163
and beg all the Gods
to send him home.

494
00:35:49,205 --> 00:35:52,470
I'd hear of this battle
or that battle and...

495
00:35:52,508 --> 00:35:54,408
I'd see him,
clear as a glass,

496
00:35:54,443 --> 00:35:56,877
lying dead and bloody
in the mud somewhere.

497
00:35:59,815 --> 00:36:02,010
I was lonely.

498
00:36:02,051 --> 00:36:03,916
I was so lonely.

499
00:36:03,953 --> 00:36:06,387
For eight years I wept.

500
00:36:06,422 --> 00:36:10,290
Every day, the girls asking,
"When is Papa coming home?

501
00:36:10,326 --> 00:36:12,988
Is it today? When?"

502
00:36:14,864 --> 00:36:17,662
And now he's home,
and I wish he was in Gaul.

503
00:36:17,700 --> 00:36:19,531
He's a cold, mean brute.

504
00:36:19,568 --> 00:36:21,832
Not one loving word
to me or his daughters,

505
00:36:21,871 --> 00:36:23,668
not once since
he has been home.

506
00:36:23,706 --> 00:36:26,800
He is no skilled hand
with the women.

507
00:36:26,842 --> 00:36:30,278
But in all these years I fought
with him, he never took a woman.

508
00:36:30,312 --> 00:36:33,543
"Pullo," he'd say to me,
"Pullo, my old friend,

509
00:36:33,582 --> 00:36:35,777
I have a wife back home,
Niobe is her name

510
00:36:35,818 --> 00:36:38,582
and she's worth more to me
than all the women of Gaul."

511
00:36:40,456 --> 00:36:42,583
I thank you for your kind words,
but I know you lie.

512
00:36:42,625 --> 00:36:45,185
Shh, shh.

513
00:36:45,227 --> 00:36:47,752
He's no friend of yours.
He told me so.

514
00:36:47,797 --> 00:36:50,527
Why, he has a...
an ill temper, him.

515
00:36:50,566 --> 00:36:53,228
He'd say anything.

516
00:36:55,271 --> 00:36:57,102
Antony needs every man.

517
00:36:57,139 --> 00:36:59,130
If you can walk, we rendezvous
at the house of Atia.

518
00:37:07,216 --> 00:37:08,911
This is all I have left.

519
00:37:08,951 --> 00:37:11,215
There will be more
when I sell the slaves.

520
00:37:11,253 --> 00:37:14,848
Get the girls indoors and stay indoors until
you know it's safe.

521
00:37:21,964 --> 00:37:24,626
It saddens me
that you are unhappy,

522
00:37:24,667 --> 00:37:26,692
because I have
a deep affection for you.

523
00:37:28,504 --> 00:37:30,301
When I return,
we will talk.

524
00:37:44,220 --> 00:37:46,586
Well, this is
a merry do.

525
00:37:49,091 --> 00:37:51,992
Octavia, my honey,
look alive at least.

526
00:37:52,027 --> 00:37:55,986
Poor Antony must think himself dead
and swimming in Lethe water.

527
00:37:56,031 --> 00:37:59,125
Talk to the poor man,
ask him questions.

528
00:38:00,269 --> 00:38:02,499
One would think she'd been
raised by Germans.

529
00:38:02,538 --> 00:38:06,838
General Antony,
does my mother's screaming irritate you?

530
00:38:06,876 --> 00:38:08,537
Excuse me?

531
00:38:08,577 --> 00:38:11,137
When you and my mother
are in coitus,

532
00:38:11,180 --> 00:38:13,114
there is
a deal of screaming.

533
00:38:13,148 --> 00:38:15,378
I find it
extremely irritating.

534
00:38:15,417 --> 00:38:18,079
I wondered
whether you did also.

535
00:38:18,120 --> 00:38:19,678
Or perhaps you like it?

536
00:38:19,722 --> 00:38:21,622
A testament
to your skills.

537
00:38:21,657 --> 00:38:24,217
So spiteful,
and for what?

538
00:38:24,260 --> 00:38:25,784
You shame only yourself.

539
00:38:50,319 --> 00:38:52,685
She has you exact.

540
00:38:55,124 --> 00:38:57,183
We show our strength.

541
00:38:57,226 --> 00:38:59,126
We show them
who owns the Forum,

542
00:38:59,161 --> 00:39:00,958
but we do not touch them.

543
00:39:00,996 --> 00:39:02,896
Antony must not
be touched!

544
00:39:02,932 --> 00:39:05,162
- Kill them all, I say.
- None of that!

545
00:39:05,200 --> 00:39:07,031
Pompey's strict orders.

546
00:39:07,069 --> 00:39:10,766
Him who starts trouble
will be on a cross at nightfall.

547
00:39:10,806 --> 00:39:12,535
So no blood!

548
00:39:20,583 --> 00:39:23,051
Make a lane there!
Make a lane there, I said!

549
00:39:23,085 --> 00:39:24,950
Come on, you bastards!

550
00:39:53,282 --> 00:39:57,218
Rally to me.

551
00:39:57,252 --> 00:39:59,277
Rally to me!

552
00:40:07,997 --> 00:40:09,794
No blood!

553
00:40:27,483 --> 00:40:30,350
You have
what you wanted, Cato.

554
00:40:30,386 --> 00:40:33,082
Caesar has
no choice now.

555
00:40:33,122 --> 00:40:35,989
Come the spring,
he will cross the Alps

556
00:40:36,025 --> 00:40:39,756
with his legions
and march on Rome.

557
00:40:49,304 --> 00:40:52,239
Five dead:
three from flux, two from fighting.

558
00:40:52,274 --> 00:40:56,210
10 under medics.
Eight absent, believed fled.

559
00:40:56,245 --> 00:40:59,214
- Sir.
- Fighting strength: 236 head.

560
00:40:59,248 --> 00:41:02,445
Seventh Cohort.
12 dead:

561
00:41:02,484 --> 00:41:04,384
six of flux,
six of fighting.

562
00:41:04,420 --> 00:41:06,115
Three on the medics.

563
00:41:06,155 --> 00:41:08,020
Three absent,
believed fled.

564
00:41:08,057 --> 00:41:10,457
Fighting strength: 242.

565
00:41:10,492 --> 00:41:14,155
Soldier, how far behind you
is Mark Antony?

566
00:41:14,196 --> 00:41:16,255
No more than an hour, sir.

567
00:41:20,669 --> 00:41:23,797
- Sound assembly!
- Sir!

568
00:41:23,839 --> 00:41:25,568
By order of the Senate,

569
00:41:25,607 --> 00:41:28,303
Gaius Julius Caesar

570
00:41:28,343 --> 00:41:30,811
is declared
an enemy of Rome.

571
00:41:30,846 --> 00:41:32,746
All good citizens
are bound

572
00:41:32,781 --> 00:41:35,682
to do him harm
if they are able.

573
00:41:54,403 --> 00:41:56,234
I've got him.

574
00:41:57,740 --> 00:42:02,370
After all these years,
Pompey surprises me.

575
00:42:03,846 --> 00:42:06,542
I had hoped to provoke
some kind of aggression, sure,

576
00:42:06,582 --> 00:42:09,710
but to try
and kill a Tribune?

577
00:42:09,752 --> 00:42:12,312
In the Forum?

578
00:42:12,354 --> 00:42:15,289
The man's found some hard
black iron in his soul.

579
00:42:15,324 --> 00:42:19,260
I'm sure it was yon demented little worm
Cato who put him up to it.

580
00:42:19,294 --> 00:42:22,092
It's excellent, this.

581
00:42:22,131 --> 00:42:23,928
So, what next?

582
00:42:23,966 --> 00:42:26,560
Let's see what the men
have to say.

583
00:42:28,537 --> 00:42:30,835
Oh, don't do that!

584
00:42:32,007 --> 00:42:34,601
You look just right
as you are.

585
00:42:34,643 --> 00:42:37,771
Like Leonidas
at Thermopylae.

586
00:42:39,648 --> 00:42:41,639
Attention!

587
00:42:45,788 --> 00:42:47,949
Any of your people
I can mention?

588
00:42:49,291 --> 00:42:50,758
Titus Pullo.

589
00:42:50,793 --> 00:42:53,455
Took the head off
the first man that came at me.

590
00:42:59,868 --> 00:43:04,202
Soldiers,
Pompey and the Senate

591
00:43:04,239 --> 00:43:06,799
have formally declared

592
00:43:06,842 --> 00:43:09,936
that Gaius Julius Caesar

593
00:43:09,978 --> 00:43:11,673
is an enemy of Rome.

594
00:43:11,713 --> 00:43:13,442
No!

595
00:43:13,482 --> 00:43:17,179
They have declared that
I am a criminal.

596
00:43:17,219 --> 00:43:19,119
They have declared,
in effect,

597
00:43:19,154 --> 00:43:22,521
that all of you
also are criminals!

598
00:43:22,558 --> 00:43:24,822
No!

599
00:43:24,860 --> 00:43:27,795
The Tribune's veto
was not exercised.

600
00:43:27,830 --> 00:43:30,162
Peoples Tribune
Mark Antony

601
00:43:30,199 --> 00:43:32,724
and 50 men of the 13th

602
00:43:32,768 --> 00:43:36,295
were assaulted by 1,000 head
of Pompeian scum.

603
00:43:36,338 --> 00:43:38,397
No!

604
00:43:41,476 --> 00:43:45,071
A Tribune of the plebs

605
00:43:45,113 --> 00:43:47,638
assaulted on the steps

606
00:43:47,683 --> 00:43:49,480
of the Senate House!

607
00:43:49,518 --> 00:43:52,510
Can you imagine
a more terrible sacrilege?

608
00:43:52,554 --> 00:43:56,046
Our beloved Republic is
in the hands of madmen.

609
00:43:56,091 --> 00:43:58,150
This is a dark day,

610
00:43:58,193 --> 00:44:00,627
and I stand at a fork
in the road.

611
00:44:00,662 --> 00:44:03,688
I can abide the law
and surrender my arms to the Senate

612
00:44:03,732 --> 00:44:05,700
and watch
the Republic fall

613
00:44:05,734 --> 00:44:07,224
to tyranny and chaos!

614
00:44:07,269 --> 00:44:09,737
Or, I can go home

615
00:44:09,771 --> 00:44:12,103
with my sword
in my hand

616
00:44:12,140 --> 00:44:13,971
and run those maniacs

617
00:44:14,009 --> 00:44:15,977
to the Tarpeian Rock!

618
00:44:16,011 --> 00:44:18,741
Yeah! Yeah!

619
00:44:25,220 --> 00:44:28,621
Legionary Titus Pullo,
step forward!

620
00:44:33,295 --> 00:44:35,889
Titus Pullo!

621
00:44:41,103 --> 00:44:43,503
When 50 brave men
of the 13th

622
00:44:43,538 --> 00:44:46,006
fought Pompey's 1,000
in the Forum

623
00:44:46,041 --> 00:44:48,168
and saved the Tribune,

624
00:44:48,210 --> 00:44:51,646
it was Legionary Titus Pullo
who drew first blood!

625
00:44:53,081 --> 00:44:56,778
Here is 500 denarii!

626
00:44:57,953 --> 00:44:59,284
Very grateful, sir.

627
00:44:59,321 --> 00:45:02,051
Are you with me,
Titus Pullo?

628
00:45:02,090 --> 00:45:04,923
- Will you come with me to Rome?
- Yes.

629
00:45:04,960 --> 00:45:06,951
Yes, sir!
Certainly!

630
00:45:06,995 --> 00:45:10,328
Titus Pullo
is with me!

631
00:45:10,365 --> 00:45:12,731
And you?
Are you with me?!

632
00:45:12,768 --> 00:45:16,898
Yeah! Yeah!

633
00:46:09,725 --> 00:46:11,352
Ah, you're awake.

634
00:46:11,393 --> 00:46:13,258
Water?

635
00:46:14,463 --> 00:46:16,124
We're moving.

636
00:46:16,164 --> 00:46:17,825
Mmm.

637
00:46:19,301 --> 00:46:21,769
The whole legion, sounds like.
Where to?

638
00:46:21,803 --> 00:46:24,067
It's a river.

639
00:46:24,106 --> 00:46:25,971
What river?

640
00:46:29,378 --> 00:46:31,938
- This is the Rubicon.
- Stay calm.

641
00:46:31,980 --> 00:46:33,971
This is rebellion
and treason,

642
00:46:34,016 --> 00:46:35,608
and I am no traitor!

643
00:46:35,650 --> 00:46:37,709
It's too late now.
We're across. We're in Italy.

644
00:46:37,753 --> 00:46:39,584
You're a rebel whether
you like it or not.

645
00:46:39,621 --> 00:46:42,112
Caesar. Caesar,
what have you done?

646
00:46:42,157 --> 00:46:44,182
He had no choice,
had he?

647
00:46:44,226 --> 00:46:46,126
Pompey did try to kill
Mark Antony after all.

648
00:46:46,161 --> 00:46:48,254
You of all men should not dare
make that argument.

649
00:46:48,296 --> 00:46:51,163
- How's that?
- You know who was being attacked.

650
00:46:51,199 --> 00:46:53,394
I don't know
what you mean.

651
00:46:55,470 --> 00:46:57,597
It doesn't matter now.

652
00:46:57,639 --> 00:46:59,504
We are all
dead men any way.

653
00:46:59,541 --> 00:47:02,237
We'll be hanging from crosses
in the Appian Way before the week's out.

654
00:47:02,277 --> 00:47:03,801
We'll be all right.

655
00:47:03,845 --> 00:47:06,245
- Have some more water.
- Better to die of thirst.

656
00:47:06,281 --> 00:47:09,114
Don't be foolish.
Drink.

657
00:47:13,221 --> 00:47:16,156
Caesar is in Italy!

658
00:47:19,895 --> 00:47:22,989
Caesar is in Italy!

659
00:47:25,934 --> 00:47:28,334
- Have you heard?
- I heard.

660
00:47:47,789 --> 00:47:49,347
What's going to happen?

661
00:47:49,391 --> 00:47:51,518
War is going to happen.

662
00:47:58,433 --> 00:48:00,833
Who's my greedy
little piglet?

