1
00:01:56,500 --> 00:01:58,021
The day was hot,

2
00:01:58,066 --> 00:02:01,789
but the night turns chilly fast,
it seems, for the time of year.

3
00:02:01,828 --> 00:02:04,485
Day after tomorrow,
we shall be in Capua

4
00:02:04,526 --> 00:02:07,080
and you will sleep
in a good warm house.

5
00:02:07,122 --> 00:02:09,087
Though goatskin
has its virtues.

6
00:02:09,121 --> 00:02:12,174
Here we are, refugees
in our own land.

7
00:02:12,217 --> 00:02:16,305
We are not refugees.
We are maneuvering.

8
00:02:16,347 --> 00:02:19,605
As you say,
here we are maneuvering,

9
00:02:19,643 --> 00:02:22,107
while the tyrant sits
in Rome.

10
00:02:22,141 --> 00:02:24,468
Yes, in my tent,

11
00:02:24,505 --> 00:02:26,765
I sleep sound
and deep as a child.

12
00:02:28,801 --> 00:02:33,286
- Though perhaps not tonight.
- I'm sorry it bothers you.

13
00:02:33,330 --> 00:02:35,556
He'll be finished
soon enough.

14
00:02:35,595 --> 00:02:38,318
Quintus has a knack
for this kind of thing.

15
00:02:38,357 --> 00:02:40,322
Well, I hope so.

16
00:02:40,356 --> 00:02:44,647
Your son Quintus,
I did not know he was with us.

17
00:02:44,685 --> 00:02:46,581
Arrived this morning
from Brindisi.

18
00:02:49,779 --> 00:02:52,936
Ah, that's better.

19
00:02:52,976 --> 00:02:56,132
Screaming makes poor sauce,
I find.

20
00:02:56,172 --> 00:02:58,295
Quintus has
his faults,

21
00:02:58,337 --> 00:03:01,198
but he is loyal
and fearless.

22
00:03:01,234 --> 00:03:03,823
A father cannot ask more.

23
00:03:03,865 --> 00:03:07,793
I've never heard
nor thought otherwise.

24
00:03:07,828 --> 00:03:11,279
The dog confessed at last.

25
00:03:11,324 --> 00:03:14,048
- Torn up good and red.
- Blood on your face.

26
00:03:14,088 --> 00:03:16,075
Wash yourself.

27
00:03:18,249 --> 00:03:21,508
Where is Durio?
Where is the gold?

28
00:03:21,547 --> 00:03:25,498
He killed Durio
as you suspected.

29
00:03:25,543 --> 00:03:29,495
And they took the gold north
on the Via Flaminia,

30
00:03:29,539 --> 00:03:32,297
ran slap into
Caesar's scouts.

31
00:03:32,836 --> 00:03:34,857
Pair of Romans,
20 head of Ubian.

32
00:03:34,899 --> 00:03:36,989
Too many for our boys.

33
00:03:37,032 --> 00:03:39,688
They ran, the filth
that they are.

34
00:03:39,728 --> 00:03:41,692
Left the gold
to the scouts.

35
00:03:41,726 --> 00:03:44,846
Can't be so. I've heard
from Rome this last hour.

36
00:03:44,888 --> 00:03:46,851
Caesar has not
got the gold.

37
00:03:46,885 --> 00:03:50,279
My man Volpe always
gets the truth, Father.

38
00:03:50,315 --> 00:03:53,971
If Caesar does not have it, then his scouts
must have kept it for themselves.

39
00:03:54,012 --> 00:03:55,974
- Go find these scouts.
- I will.

40
00:03:56,008 --> 00:03:58,698
Now!

41
00:04:02,667 --> 00:04:04,789
You see,
the tide turns already.

42
00:04:04,831 --> 00:04:07,692
Without the gold,
Caesar will find Rome

43
00:04:07,728 --> 00:04:09,816
a little harder
to subdue.

44
00:04:09,858 --> 00:04:14,649
Without the gold, we're not
very well placed, either.

45
00:04:14,686 --> 00:04:17,343
Without gold,
he will have to use violence.

46
00:04:17,384 --> 00:04:19,971
Once he starts
spilling blood,

47
00:04:20,013 --> 00:04:23,806
the people will turn
on him with a vengeance.

48
00:04:23,842 --> 00:04:28,270
Without the people,
he has nothing.

49
00:04:38,391 --> 00:04:40,753
"Martial law
is in effect

50
00:04:40,789 --> 00:04:43,910
for the safety
of all citizens.

51
00:04:43,951 --> 00:04:46,710
Groups of more than
three men

52
00:04:46,749 --> 00:04:50,573
shall not congregate
in public spaces.

53
00:04:50,609 --> 00:04:52,938
A curfew is in effect.

54
00:04:52,974 --> 00:04:56,401
Any person found
on the street after dark

55
00:04:56,435 --> 00:04:58,956
will be subject
to summary judgment.

56
00:04:59,000 --> 00:05:03,654
Long live
General Gaius Julius Caesar,

57
00:05:03,695 --> 00:05:07,247
savior of our Republic."

58
00:05:12,918 --> 00:05:15,506
Order, halt!

59
00:05:24,735 --> 00:05:44,205
Jupiter Optimus Maximus.

60
00:05:45,773 --> 00:05:49,392
Jupiter Optimus Maximus.
Jupiter Optimus Maximus.

61
00:05:59,021 --> 00:06:02,107
Name yourself, citizen.

62
00:06:02,150 --> 00:06:04,272
Gaius of the Julii,

63
00:06:04,313 --> 00:06:06,141
called Caesar.

64
00:06:06,179 --> 00:06:08,640
Speak then.

65
00:06:08,674 --> 00:06:10,830
I humbly ask that
auguries be taken

66
00:06:10,872 --> 00:06:13,164
that Rome might know

67
00:06:13,201 --> 00:06:15,255
that the gods favor
my actions.

68
00:06:15,298 --> 00:06:18,918
You've entered the city
under arms.

69
00:06:18,960 --> 00:06:22,150
I must warn you
that seldom augurs well.

70
00:06:22,189 --> 00:06:25,174
The gods know my
intentions are peaceful.

71
00:06:25,220 --> 00:06:27,738
The people must
know it also.

72
00:06:32,176 --> 00:06:35,137
So be it.

73
00:06:35,171 --> 00:06:37,033
Auguries will be taken

74
00:06:37,070 --> 00:06:40,689
on the first clean morning.

75
00:06:40,731 --> 00:06:43,921
Let the birds fly
where they may.

76
00:06:58,672 --> 00:07:00,898
How be, paisan?

77
00:07:00,937 --> 00:07:03,557
Miserable.

78
00:07:03,598 --> 00:07:05,562
Slave of a rebel.

79
00:07:05,596 --> 00:07:07,922
A successful rebel
at least.

80
00:07:07,959 --> 00:07:09,923
The jury's still out.
And you, my child?

81
00:07:09,957 --> 00:07:12,920
For true misery,
try bondage

82
00:07:12,954 --> 00:07:14,313
to a bloody-minded woman.

83
00:07:17,080 --> 00:07:21,303
This dinner tonight,
Caesar asks no shellfish.

84
00:07:21,341 --> 00:07:24,066
Here is a guest list.

85
00:07:27,799 --> 00:07:29,764
I hope your lady
is aware

86
00:07:29,798 --> 00:07:31,759
of the honor done to her.

87
00:07:31,793 --> 00:07:35,188
She's very aware.

88
00:07:35,224 --> 00:07:37,345
Caesar's hostess
is first woman

89
00:07:37,387 --> 00:07:40,371
- of the city, in effect.
- Excepting Caesar's wife.

90
00:07:40,415 --> 00:07:44,172
Calpurnia. Caesar requires
that she's still and handsome

91
00:07:44,210 --> 00:07:46,765
and dignified and...
no more.

92
00:07:46,807 --> 00:07:50,733
She is a species
of statue.

93
00:07:55,262 --> 00:07:58,052
A very fancy list
of people.

94
00:07:58,091 --> 00:08:00,384
Every aristo and optimate
left in the city.

95
00:08:03,250 --> 00:08:05,769
He's not planning
on killing them, is he?

96
00:08:05,814 --> 00:08:08,368
I shouldn't think so.

97
00:08:10,041 --> 00:08:13,595
My mistress doesn't
like surprises.

98
00:08:13,636 --> 00:08:18,325
Servilia...
why invite her?

99
00:08:18,364 --> 00:08:20,451
Can there still be
something between them?

100
00:08:20,493 --> 00:08:23,785
A rattled old sandal like her?
Surely not.

101
00:08:23,823 --> 00:08:26,512
Some juice in her yet.

102
00:08:26,551 --> 00:08:29,639
I'll not let that woman
get between me and Caesar.

103
00:08:32,110 --> 00:08:34,767
Why is Servilia invited
to the party?

104
00:08:34,808 --> 00:08:35,931
Hmm?

105
00:08:35,973 --> 00:08:39,196
Servilia of the Junii,
why is she invited?

106
00:08:39,235 --> 00:08:43,390
On account of her son,
obviously.

107
00:08:43,430 --> 00:08:46,017
For this, you wake me?

108
00:08:46,059 --> 00:08:50,381
Of course. He needs to keep Brutus
as his symbolic friend.

109
00:08:50,418 --> 00:08:52,575
That's all.

110
00:08:52,616 --> 00:08:55,305
It would look ill with the people
if Brutus were his enemy.

111
00:08:55,345 --> 00:08:58,774
There's no love there.
It's just politics.

112
00:08:58,808 --> 00:09:02,734
Dear gods, woman,
would you let me sleep?

113
00:09:25,971 --> 00:09:27,935
The goat's testicles,
domina.

114
00:09:27,969 --> 00:09:30,828
Not for me, fool,
for Octavian.

115
00:09:33,394 --> 00:09:35,879
Fetch Demeter.

116
00:09:35,924 --> 00:09:37,887
Eat them while
they're warm, my dear.

117
00:09:37,921 --> 00:09:40,439
- It puts oak in your penis.
- I'd rather not.

118
00:09:40,484 --> 00:09:42,311
Nonsense, you must.

119
00:09:42,348 --> 00:09:44,642
You've been developing
a distinctly feminine anima,

120
00:09:44,680 --> 00:09:46,835
and I do not like it.

121
00:09:46,876 --> 00:09:48,839
I am only a boy.
It is entirely natural...

122
00:09:48,873 --> 00:09:51,699
When my mother's father was your
age, there was not a slave girl safe.

123
00:09:51,734 --> 00:09:55,323
The men of the Julii are masculine men.
Now do as I say

124
00:09:55,365 --> 00:09:57,326
- and eat them.
- I will not.

125
00:09:57,360 --> 00:09:59,380
You'll not leave
this room until you do.

126
00:09:59,424 --> 00:10:03,408
Demeter, the banquet
this evening,

127
00:10:03,453 --> 00:10:06,177
no shellfish. And be sure
the lampreys are not overcooked.

128
00:10:06,216 --> 00:10:09,143
Boil them long enough
to kill them, no more.

129
00:10:11,275 --> 00:10:13,264
I'm waiting.

130
00:10:21,362 --> 00:10:23,348
That's my brave boy.

131
00:10:35,943 --> 00:10:38,460
- Brother.
- Hmm?

132
00:10:38,505 --> 00:10:41,093
Did Mother have
Glabius killed?

133
00:10:41,135 --> 00:10:43,689
Of course not.

134
00:10:43,731 --> 00:10:45,694
You're sure?

135
00:10:45,728 --> 00:10:48,191
Well, I cannot prove a negative,
but I'm sure as can be.

136
00:10:48,226 --> 00:10:50,744
You swear on
Jupiter's stone?

137
00:10:52,019 --> 00:10:54,210
I swear on
Jupiter's stone.

138
00:10:57,146 --> 00:10:59,234
If she did,

139
00:10:59,276 --> 00:11:02,431
if she did kill him,

140
00:11:02,472 --> 00:11:06,627
by the furies, I'll open her throat
with my teeth.

141
00:12:13,341 --> 00:12:16,497
In Narbo, I can buy
10 feasts for this.

142
00:12:16,537 --> 00:12:18,625
Narbo isn't full of
corpses and soldiers,

143
00:12:18,668 --> 00:12:21,495
and decent people too scared
to come out of their houses.

144
00:12:21,531 --> 00:12:23,890
No time to throw a do
if you don't mind me saying.

145
00:12:23,927 --> 00:12:27,979
I cannot start a business
without a feast, can I?

146
00:12:28,022 --> 00:12:31,779
Today is auspicious,
and it's perfectly safe.

147
00:12:31,817 --> 00:12:34,676
I remember the last time when Sulla
had soldiers in the city.

148
00:12:34,712 --> 00:12:37,970
- Blood, you could paint houses with it.
- Caesar's not Sulla.

149
00:12:38,008 --> 00:12:42,095
He's declared martial law, not
to spill blood, but to keep the peace.

150
00:12:42,135 --> 00:12:44,032
We'll see, won't we?

151
00:12:44,068 --> 00:12:46,756
I invoke Ceres and Bacchus,
you'll not be dissatisfied.

152
00:12:46,796 --> 00:12:48,850
You find me a pig, and I'll
make you a feast,

153
00:12:48,893 --> 00:12:50,857
in Hades, if need be.

154
00:12:50,891 --> 00:12:53,910
- And charge according.
- Musa, the oilman's wife,

155
00:12:53,954 --> 00:12:56,508
served whelks instead of oysters
at her womb funeral,

156
00:12:56,550 --> 00:12:58,739
and nobody would
let her forget it.

157
00:12:58,780 --> 00:13:00,834
Laughed at in the street.

158
00:13:14,794 --> 00:13:17,810
Divine Janus, we offer
this feast to you.

159
00:13:17,854 --> 00:13:19,976
I humbly beg that you
will be gracious

160
00:13:20,018 --> 00:13:22,444
and merciful
to me and my house,

161
00:13:22,478 --> 00:13:24,464
and you will smile upon
this new business venture

162
00:13:24,508 --> 00:13:26,232
I begin today.

163
00:13:28,168 --> 00:13:32,287
Lucius Vorenus, his honor
Mark Antony orders your presence.

164
00:13:32,327 --> 00:13:35,515
- Now?
- Of course not. Next year.

165
00:13:38,484 --> 00:13:42,601
Vorenus, my dear comrade.

166
00:13:42,642 --> 00:13:45,365
Barely recognize you without
a bloody sword in your hand.

167
00:13:45,404 --> 00:13:47,887
Off with you now, Cato.

168
00:13:49,331 --> 00:13:52,019
Amusing, eh?

169
00:13:52,059 --> 00:13:54,645
- Cato.
- As you say.

170
00:13:54,687 --> 00:13:58,306
Of course you don't all
find it amusing.

171
00:13:58,347 --> 00:14:00,535
So...

172
00:14:00,577 --> 00:14:03,662
how is civilian life
treating you, huh?

173
00:14:03,704 --> 00:14:06,427
Well enough so far,
sir.

174
00:14:06,467 --> 00:14:08,486
You know, of course,

175
00:14:08,529 --> 00:14:11,613
I could have you nailed
to a cross for desertion.

176
00:14:11,656 --> 00:14:14,447
I am no deserter.
My time was served.

177
00:14:14,485 --> 00:14:16,278
I abided my sacrament.

178
00:14:16,316 --> 00:14:18,936
It is you that...

179
00:14:18,977 --> 00:14:22,028
It is I that what?

180
00:14:22,072 --> 00:14:25,691
Once over the Rubicon,
Romans are citizens, not soldiers.

181
00:14:25,732 --> 00:14:27,559
I could not legally do
other than I did.

182
00:14:27,596 --> 00:14:29,385
Foolish.

183
00:14:29,424 --> 00:14:33,011
Like a priest
blinded by a cowl.

184
00:14:33,053 --> 00:14:34,571
Since the founding
of Rome...

185
00:14:34,615 --> 00:14:37,339
Oh, please, spare me
the founding, Vorenus.

186
00:14:37,377 --> 00:14:39,465
Things change.

187
00:14:39,508 --> 00:14:41,527
Life is water, not stone.

188
00:14:41,570 --> 00:14:43,532
Then I suppose
I will drown.

189
00:14:43,566 --> 00:14:46,616
Do you not see that
your precious Republic

190
00:14:46,659 --> 00:14:48,248
has long since died?

191
00:14:48,291 --> 00:14:51,874
Do you not see that Caesar
is trying to save Rome from ruin?

192
00:14:51,916 --> 00:14:53,404
I do not see that.

193
00:14:55,312 --> 00:14:56,865
Enough.

194
00:14:59,205 --> 00:15:01,825
And what wretched trade

195
00:15:01,866 --> 00:15:04,191
is it you intend
to follow then?

196
00:15:04,228 --> 00:15:07,019
Imported goods from Gaul.
Slaves, truffles, wine.

197
00:15:07,057 --> 00:15:09,678
- That sort of thing.
- A grocer?

198
00:15:09,719 --> 00:15:12,680
An honest fighting man
like yourself

199
00:15:12,714 --> 00:15:15,300
counting cartons,

200
00:15:15,342 --> 00:15:17,703
scribbling accounts?

201
00:15:17,738 --> 00:15:20,994
- You will swift go mad.
- That may be.

202
00:15:24,061 --> 00:15:26,520
I need you, Vorenus.

203
00:15:26,554 --> 00:15:29,210
Caesar needs you.

204
00:15:29,251 --> 00:15:33,006
There is no better man in the legion,
none more respected by the men.

205
00:15:33,044 --> 00:15:36,299
- We have hard fighting ahead.
- Hard fighting against Romans.

206
00:15:36,337 --> 00:15:38,096
Blood is blood.

207
00:15:38,135 --> 00:15:40,098
Would you really have
the 13th

208
00:15:40,132 --> 00:15:43,523
fasten their crest
without you?

209
00:15:45,123 --> 00:15:48,105
You come back
to the legion,

210
00:15:48,149 --> 00:15:51,634
you shall be inducted
into the Evocati as a prefect.

211
00:15:54,838 --> 00:15:58,128
Of the first grade,
with a signing bonus.

212
00:15:58,165 --> 00:16:00,422
Say, uh...

213
00:16:00,461 --> 00:16:02,515
10,000 sesterce.

214
00:16:06,883 --> 00:16:10,740
I chose this path.
I will follow where it leads.

215
00:16:13,337 --> 00:16:17,695
You grieve me, Vorenus.

216
00:16:17,730 --> 00:16:20,918
You grieve me deeply.

217
00:16:20,958 --> 00:16:22,852
Go on.
Off with you.

218
00:16:25,585 --> 00:16:27,547
Good day, citizen.

219
00:16:27,581 --> 00:16:30,062
Vorenus...

220
00:16:32,202 --> 00:16:35,558
next time I see you,
I may not be so kind.

221
00:16:48,234 --> 00:16:50,125
What does it say?

222
00:16:50,161 --> 00:16:52,180
Shh.

223
00:16:56,047 --> 00:16:59,529
It's not certain,

224
00:16:59,573 --> 00:17:02,125
but I'd say your
secret's safe.

225
00:17:02,168 --> 00:17:04,357
Not certain?

226
00:17:04,396 --> 00:17:06,683
The signs are mixed.

227
00:17:06,721 --> 00:17:08,152
What good is that?

228
00:17:08,186 --> 00:17:11,146
Tell me what
it is you're hiding

229
00:17:11,180 --> 00:17:14,231
and I can be
more precise.

230
00:17:16,335 --> 00:17:18,319
There's a child involved.

231
00:17:21,125 --> 00:17:24,343
A male child?

232
00:17:24,382 --> 00:17:26,437
The baby.

233
00:17:26,480 --> 00:17:28,566
Never mind.
Best leave it.

234
00:17:28,608 --> 00:17:30,591
As you please.

235
00:17:33,098 --> 00:17:35,523
If it's any help,

236
00:17:35,558 --> 00:17:40,141
it does say your husband
is going to be rich.

237
00:17:40,183 --> 00:17:43,698
Rich as Croesus.

238
00:17:45,770 --> 00:17:48,025
Well, that's something,
isn't it?

239
00:17:49,394 --> 00:17:51,254
Thank you.

240
00:18:10,478 --> 00:18:13,031
Good. Done.

241
00:18:17,530 --> 00:18:19,515
Water.

242
00:18:33,661 --> 00:18:36,846
What did I look
like eight years ago?

243
00:18:36,885 --> 00:18:38,870
Just the same.

244
00:18:38,915 --> 00:18:43,099
- Eight years.
- Eight years...

245
00:18:43,138 --> 00:18:45,156
of leathery
Gallic trollops.

246
00:18:45,200 --> 00:18:47,854
When did he last see
a real lady, hmm?

247
00:18:47,895 --> 00:18:49,948
And such
a beautiful one?

248
00:19:02,262 --> 00:19:05,483
- Flowers.
- In bloom?

249
00:19:14,367 --> 00:19:17,918
50,000 to each of
the magistrate's clerks.

250
00:19:17,961 --> 00:19:20,148
So much?

251
00:19:20,189 --> 00:19:23,305
I wish to buy their
allegiance outright, not lease it.

252
00:19:23,346 --> 00:19:25,637
Have them sign
for the money.

253
00:19:25,675 --> 00:19:28,534
And how much for
the sub-praetors?

254
00:19:28,570 --> 00:19:30,224
Nil.

255
00:19:30,265 --> 00:19:33,952
When they hear how much
the clerks got, they'll come begging.

256
00:19:33,992 --> 00:19:36,643
And leave us penniless without
means to run the city.

257
00:19:36,683 --> 00:19:40,268
We must kill some rich men
and take their money very soon,

258
00:19:40,310 --> 00:19:43,665
else the well
will run dry

259
00:19:43,702 --> 00:19:45,289
very soon.

260
00:19:45,332 --> 00:19:47,621
I plan on killing no one
unless absolutely necessary.

261
00:19:47,658 --> 00:19:50,244
A fine novel strategy,

262
00:19:50,286 --> 00:19:52,441
an element of surprise
no doubt.

263
00:19:52,482 --> 00:19:54,773
Later you may nag me.

264
00:20:02,925 --> 00:20:07,437
I believe this is
appropriate.

265
00:20:07,479 --> 00:20:09,500
Exactly right, my dear.

266
00:20:09,544 --> 00:20:13,330
Regal, but not
excessively so.

267
00:20:13,367 --> 00:20:16,294
Fine start to a business
this'll be if nobody comes.

268
00:20:16,329 --> 00:20:18,583
Don't worry.
They will come.

269
00:20:24,209 --> 00:20:26,670
Maybe I should have
waited as you said.

270
00:20:26,705 --> 00:20:28,689
They will come.

271
00:20:32,091 --> 00:20:35,108
And mind now,
when they do come,

272
00:20:35,151 --> 00:20:37,704
try to smile occasionally.

273
00:20:37,746 --> 00:20:40,727
And don't bark at them.

274
00:20:40,771 --> 00:20:42,732
Who's this?

275
00:20:42,766 --> 00:20:45,987
Erastes Fulmen. Remember?
Our guest of honor.

276
00:20:46,026 --> 00:20:48,453
Building trades,
fire insurance, olives.

277
00:20:48,487 --> 00:20:51,571
Lucius Vorenus.

278
00:20:51,614 --> 00:20:55,096
Niobe.

279
00:20:55,140 --> 00:20:57,123
Thank you for your coming, honest
neighbor.

280
00:20:57,168 --> 00:20:58,858
I know it can't be easy
on such a day.

281
00:20:58,898 --> 00:21:01,154
What's a few
soldiers, eh?

282
00:21:01,192 --> 00:21:03,050
Wife, Phyllis.

283
00:21:03,086 --> 00:21:04,847
Please.

284
00:21:04,886 --> 00:21:08,104
- Sit down and take a cup of wine.
- I will.

285
00:21:08,143 --> 00:21:09,697
Thirsty road, eh?

286
00:21:15,459 --> 00:21:16,447
Sister.

287
00:21:17,721 --> 00:21:19,740
All right?

288
00:21:19,783 --> 00:21:21,871
All's right.
Don't worry.

289
00:21:21,912 --> 00:21:24,305
- Thank you.
- This can't be little Lyde.

290
00:21:24,341 --> 00:21:27,495
- Surely not. Long time, eh?
- Salve, Lucius.

291
00:21:29,035 --> 00:21:31,318
This is my husband, Evander Pulchio.

292
00:21:31,348 --> 00:21:33,907
With all the shops shut,
we would have whistled for meat.

293
00:21:33,949 --> 00:21:35,937
Happy to be of service.

294
00:22:11,591 --> 00:22:14,455
- Thank you so much for inviting me.
- My pleasure.

295
00:22:14,493 --> 00:22:16,248
My pleasure, Servilia.

296
00:22:16,287 --> 00:22:19,115
I insisted you come.

297
00:22:19,152 --> 00:22:21,881
Whatever misfortune
befalls you,

298
00:22:21,920 --> 00:22:24,540
we're still friends, neh?

299
00:22:34,243 --> 00:22:36,367
She has a good cosmetics slave,
I'll grant you.

300
00:22:36,409 --> 00:22:40,531
But a lover for Caesar?
Absurd.

301
00:22:57,363 --> 00:23:00,886
Make way for the pro-consul
Gaius Julius Caesar,

302
00:23:00,930 --> 00:23:02,914
Son of Venus,

303
00:23:02,958 --> 00:23:06,153
Imperator of
the Gallic Legions.

304
00:23:06,193 --> 00:23:08,781
Stand aside and open up.

305
00:23:21,345 --> 00:23:25,071
Please, you mock me. It's
only your Uncle Gaius. Lift your heads.

306
00:23:29,173 --> 00:23:33,105
All of you,
lift your heads.

307
00:23:37,336 --> 00:23:38,962
My dear niece.

308
00:23:39,004 --> 00:23:40,831
Revered uncle,

309
00:23:40,869 --> 00:23:43,888
welcome, welcome home.

310
00:24:04,256 --> 00:24:06,980
Servilia of the Junii,
a pleasant honor it is.

311
00:24:08,387 --> 00:24:10,077
Delightful.

312
00:24:10,117 --> 00:24:12,514
Your pleasure is mine.

313
00:24:12,550 --> 00:24:16,477
I am very sorry your son
is not here with you.

314
00:24:19,044 --> 00:24:21,007
I'm sorry also.

315
00:24:21,041 --> 00:24:25,267
I hope you will forgive
his absence.

316
00:24:25,306 --> 00:24:28,962
He is ever your friend.

317
00:24:31,068 --> 00:24:34,689
I understand completely.

318
00:24:34,731 --> 00:24:37,219
Please send Brutus
my best regards

319
00:24:37,264 --> 00:24:39,487
and assure him he will
never have reason

320
00:24:39,525 --> 00:24:42,423
to regret our friendship.

321
00:24:42,458 --> 00:24:45,148
Nor will any of you,

322
00:24:45,188 --> 00:24:47,946
regardless of where
your allegiances

323
00:24:47,985 --> 00:24:51,106
may have lain
in the past.

324
00:25:00,543 --> 00:25:02,697
- Any weapons?
- None, sir.

325
00:25:02,737 --> 00:25:05,199
- Where you coming from?
- Come from Aternum, dominus.

326
00:25:05,234 --> 00:25:07,927
- In what trade?
- Corpse collectors, bone grinders.

327
00:25:07,967 --> 00:25:09,660
Dead business in general.

328
00:25:09,701 --> 00:25:11,990
You've come
to right place then.

329
00:25:12,027 --> 00:25:13,493
What people are they?

330
00:25:13,527 --> 00:25:17,387
Scythians, chief.
They don't speak our language.

331
00:25:17,422 --> 00:25:19,819
On your way then.

332
00:25:23,317 --> 00:25:25,544
Please let me in!

333
00:25:27,747 --> 00:25:29,646
You!

334
00:25:29,682 --> 00:25:33,543
Tell your brutes to stay away from decent
women.

335
00:25:33,578 --> 00:25:35,700
I'll do that.

336
00:25:39,671 --> 00:25:42,531
Fine bit of plunder and rapine you
made off them bloody Gauls,

337
00:25:42,567 --> 00:25:44,864
- I bet.
- I'll not complain.

338
00:25:44,901 --> 00:25:47,863
Handy to have cash
in these uncertain times.

339
00:25:47,896 --> 00:25:49,951
A man can't flee with
his house and fields

340
00:25:49,994 --> 00:25:51,983
if he's chosen
the wrong side.

341
00:25:52,028 --> 00:25:53,989
True.

342
00:25:54,023 --> 00:25:55,991
Who do you reckon will
come out on top?

343
00:25:56,025 --> 00:25:57,985
It's hard to say.

344
00:25:58,019 --> 00:26:00,676
You'll be hoping it'll be
your man though, eh?

345
00:26:00,716 --> 00:26:03,378
If you mean Caesar,
he's not my man anymore.

346
00:26:05,445 --> 00:26:08,435
So your spoils,

347
00:26:08,479 --> 00:26:11,267
you'll be lending
the proceeds, I expect.

348
00:26:11,305 --> 00:26:13,102
I won't.

349
00:26:13,140 --> 00:26:16,260
I am buying back this
insula so I'll not have spare cash.

350
00:26:16,301 --> 00:26:19,994
I plan to take over the trading
space for an import business.

351
00:26:20,033 --> 00:26:23,985
- Slaves mostly.
- Slaves?

352
00:26:24,030 --> 00:26:26,822
Well, listen,

353
00:26:26,860 --> 00:26:29,153
I have friends,

354
00:26:29,191 --> 00:26:31,211
bona friends.

355
00:26:31,255 --> 00:26:35,447
If you want any help,
you come to me, eh?

356
00:26:36,487 --> 00:26:39,813
More wine here, sweetie.

357
00:26:43,112 --> 00:26:45,769
There are even
those unwise men

358
00:26:45,810 --> 00:26:49,238
who say that a white bird
in the southern quadrant

359
00:26:49,272 --> 00:26:52,462
is neither indicant
nor negation.

360
00:26:52,502 --> 00:26:56,364
Such are the barbarous innovations of our
day.

361
00:26:56,400 --> 00:26:58,093
Barbarous.

362
00:26:58,132 --> 00:27:00,687
We might as well
be Syrian.

363
00:27:00,729 --> 00:27:03,714
- Point to pommel, I agree.
- Syrians, indeed.

364
00:27:03,759 --> 00:27:05,726
Scythians even.

365
00:27:05,760 --> 00:27:09,912
As Chief Augur,
I'm gratified to hear you say so.

366
00:27:09,952 --> 00:27:12,941
It was heard
you are a man

367
00:27:12,985 --> 00:27:17,104
- of modish opinion.
- Oh, that's pure scandal.

368
00:27:17,145 --> 00:27:20,669
I believe that religion
is the province of our worthy priests.

369
00:27:20,712 --> 00:27:24,162
Mere soldiers like myself
best not interfere.

370
00:27:24,208 --> 00:27:26,569
That's very gratifying.

371
00:27:26,605 --> 00:27:28,660
Octavian, don't sit there
like a prole.

372
00:27:28,703 --> 00:27:31,428
- Say something witty.
- I have nothing such to say.

373
00:27:31,468 --> 00:27:33,430
You know I cannot
talk small, Mother.

374
00:27:33,464 --> 00:27:35,689
You then.

375
00:27:35,728 --> 00:27:37,819
Some poetry, neh?

376
00:27:37,861 --> 00:27:41,085
She can rattle off pages
of the stuff.

377
00:27:43,857 --> 00:27:46,680
"Easy it is to go
down into Hell.

378
00:27:46,716 --> 00:27:48,946
The gates of death
are ever open.

379
00:27:48,984 --> 00:27:52,504
To climb back out again,
that's the difficulty."

380
00:27:58,109 --> 00:28:00,833
It's a touch dark,
my love, but never mind.

381
00:28:00,872 --> 00:28:04,393
She lost her husband,
you know.

382
00:28:29,680 --> 00:28:32,108
Best get your sister gone.

383
00:28:32,143 --> 00:28:33,633
I told you it was a mistake
to let her come.

384
00:28:33,678 --> 00:28:35,140
I had to let her come.

385
00:28:35,174 --> 00:28:37,467
It would look odd
if she wasn't here.

386
00:28:37,505 --> 00:28:41,299
Speak to Evander,
will you?

387
00:28:43,732 --> 00:28:45,924
Butcher man, time
to take your wife home.

388
00:28:45,965 --> 00:28:47,951
She doesn't want to go.

389
00:28:47,996 --> 00:28:49,982
Best make her
go then, eh?

390
00:28:55,289 --> 00:28:57,379
- Time to go.
- Not yet.

391
00:28:57,421 --> 00:28:59,849
- I like it here.
- Time to go.

392
00:28:59,885 --> 00:29:02,509
- Let me go, my love.
- Lyde, please.

393
00:29:02,551 --> 00:29:04,512
Let me go

394
00:29:04,545 --> 00:29:07,272
or I'll tell our brave soldier
such a good tale.

395
00:29:07,312 --> 00:29:10,004
Kill us all?
Is that what you want?

396
00:29:11,772 --> 00:29:15,463
I love you.
Why don't you love me?

397
00:29:17,370 --> 00:29:20,424
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.

398
00:29:22,496 --> 00:29:25,222
- Lyde, please.
- I'm your wife.

399
00:29:25,262 --> 00:29:28,225
We had an agreement!
You vowed to Persephone.

400
00:29:28,259 --> 00:29:29,983
You vowed you would
hold your peace!

401
00:29:30,022 --> 00:29:32,885
- Have I not held my peace?
- If my husband...

402
00:29:32,922 --> 00:29:36,147
Your husband is
a blind fool!

403
00:29:36,186 --> 00:29:39,114
Did you hear me?
He's a blind fool!

404
00:29:42,477 --> 00:29:45,135
Get off me!
Get off me!

405
00:29:47,074 --> 00:29:49,402
Get off me!

406
00:30:01,529 --> 00:30:03,583
Wife?

407
00:30:07,090 --> 00:30:09,212
Caecilia.

408
00:30:13,683 --> 00:30:15,649
Tell me,

409
00:30:15,683 --> 00:30:18,974
how is Caecilia?

410
00:30:19,011 --> 00:30:22,131
- She's healthy, I thank you.
- Good.

411
00:30:22,173 --> 00:30:25,829
I recall I forgot
her last birthday.

412
00:30:27,306 --> 00:30:29,131
- Her birthday?
- Remiss of me, I know.

413
00:30:29,168 --> 00:30:32,927
Perhaps she would forgive my rudeness
were I to send her a gift.

414
00:30:32,965 --> 00:30:35,486
Really,
that's not necessary.

415
00:30:35,529 --> 00:30:38,253
Hard to find the right
gift for a woman, neh?

416
00:30:38,293 --> 00:30:40,723
What one loves,
another scorns.

417
00:30:40,759 --> 00:30:43,482
Perhaps she would accept
some money.

418
00:30:43,521 --> 00:30:45,053
There's an idea.

419
00:30:45,887 --> 00:30:50,212
100,000 sesterce, say?

420
00:30:50,249 --> 00:30:52,141
Oh, that's very kind
of you.

421
00:30:52,177 --> 00:30:56,196
I'm afraid my wife is
a woman of expensive tastes.

422
00:30:56,240 --> 00:30:58,360
The best women
often are.

423
00:30:58,402 --> 00:30:59,993
150,000.

424
00:31:00,036 --> 00:31:04,328
She would dress her slaves
in silk if I would let her.

425
00:31:04,365 --> 00:31:09,120
She eats oysters
for breakfast daily.

426
00:31:10,889 --> 00:31:13,477
She should be
most careful.

427
00:31:13,519 --> 00:31:16,243
People often choke
on oysters.

428
00:31:16,283 --> 00:31:18,974
200,000.

429
00:31:19,014 --> 00:31:21,632
That is a very generous,
and I may say,

430
00:31:21,673 --> 00:31:23,370
appropriate gift.

431
00:31:25,038 --> 00:31:27,502
She would be under great
obligation to you.

432
00:31:27,537 --> 00:31:29,796
To think well of me would
be her only obligation.

433
00:31:29,834 --> 00:31:33,283
She's always
thought well of you.

434
00:31:33,328 --> 00:31:37,846
It is not unethical
she continue to do so.

435
00:31:39,584 --> 00:31:41,914
We understand
each other.

436
00:31:46,380 --> 00:31:48,897
Make a note of it.

437
00:31:48,941 --> 00:31:52,427
200 to the Chief Augur.

438
00:31:52,472 --> 00:31:55,660
Thinks he's Midas,
the loon.

439
00:31:55,700 --> 00:31:59,129
- Go past the cloth works.
- Thank you very much.

440
00:32:05,253 --> 00:32:07,776
We'll go to the priests of
Janus tomorrow first thing,

441
00:32:07,822 --> 00:32:10,837
and have the day absolved.
It's costly, but...

442
00:32:10,881 --> 00:32:13,104
An omen is an omen. And
this is as bad as they come.

443
00:32:13,142 --> 00:32:15,237
No point throwing
money at it.

444
00:32:17,607 --> 00:32:20,696
Your sister and her husband
can never come here again.

445
00:32:20,738 --> 00:32:22,392
As you say.

446
00:32:22,433 --> 00:32:25,190
Must not bend.

447
00:32:26,229 --> 00:32:28,214
Salve, pleb.

448
00:32:30,189 --> 00:32:32,339
Centurion Lucius Vorenus?

449
00:32:32,380 --> 00:32:34,677
Who asks?

450
00:32:34,714 --> 00:32:36,730
His honor Quintus Pompey.

451
00:32:36,775 --> 00:32:38,827
You best have good reason
for this insult.

452
00:32:38,871 --> 00:32:42,297
Tell me where the gold is,
and quick about it, dog.

453
00:32:42,331 --> 00:32:44,314
What gold?
Speak sense.

454
00:32:46,351 --> 00:32:49,439
- Sense enough?
- Not near.

455
00:32:49,481 --> 00:32:53,308
- I ask again, what gold?
- Stubborn is he?

456
00:32:55,899 --> 00:32:59,500
This trollop we can
assume is your wife.

457
00:32:59,600 --> 00:33:01,888
Hold her.

458
00:33:05,953 --> 00:33:07,911
I cannot speak
what I do not know.

459
00:33:07,945 --> 00:33:09,434
I do not know of any gold.

460
00:33:09,478 --> 00:33:11,768
You know very well
I seek the treasury gold

461
00:33:11,805 --> 00:33:14,634
you took
from my father's men.

462
00:33:14,671 --> 00:33:17,756
I took no gold from any man.
You are misinformed.

463
00:33:17,799 --> 00:33:20,762
Misinformed.

464
00:33:20,795 --> 00:33:24,378
You are not chief
of scouts 13th legion?

465
00:33:24,419 --> 00:33:26,505
I was.

466
00:33:26,548 --> 00:33:29,014
And last week, did you
not stop a grain wagon

467
00:33:29,049 --> 00:33:32,406
- on the Via Flaminia?
- We did.

468
00:33:32,443 --> 00:33:34,566
Driven by soldiers disguised.

469
00:33:34,608 --> 00:33:37,895
We chased the soldiers
and left the wagon.

470
00:33:37,932 --> 00:33:39,558
You never thought
to look inside?

471
00:33:39,600 --> 00:33:41,890
There was no time.
We had orders.

472
00:33:41,927 --> 00:33:44,615
Your wagon is still there
for all I know.

473
00:33:45,989 --> 00:33:47,451
Lies. Cut her.

474
00:33:49,582 --> 00:33:51,636
Come on, give it to me!

475
00:33:51,677 --> 00:33:54,367
Boys, a clamor for my
beloved friend Lucius.

476
00:33:58,633 --> 00:34:00,892
Why so glum and gloomy?

477
00:34:09,550 --> 00:34:11,510
Who's this then?

478
00:34:11,544 --> 00:34:14,765
His noble honor Quintus Pompey,
commander of Tyrrhenian fleet.

479
00:34:14,804 --> 00:34:16,790
Neptune's scourge.

480
00:34:16,834 --> 00:34:19,552
Oh, Neptune's scourge.

481
00:34:19,592 --> 00:34:23,177
Looking for a wagon
of treasury gold.

482
00:34:23,219 --> 00:34:25,207
Treasury gold?

483
00:34:25,251 --> 00:34:28,434
How exciting!

484
00:34:28,474 --> 00:34:31,490
Do not test
my patience, peasant.

485
00:34:31,534 --> 00:34:33,684
You be off now,
short ass.

486
00:34:33,725 --> 00:34:35,245
Take these scum
with you.

487
00:34:51,485 --> 00:34:53,880
The way I see it,

488
00:34:53,916 --> 00:34:56,371
we put little Quintus here
in the Tiber right off,

489
00:34:56,406 --> 00:35:00,594
get us a wagon, sneak out
to where the gold's buried.

490
00:35:00,633 --> 00:35:03,520
Dig it up, ride like
Zephyrus for the coast,

491
00:35:03,556 --> 00:35:06,980
- and get the first tide for Spain.
- I'm trying to think.

492
00:35:07,014 --> 00:35:09,768
- What was wrong with that?
- What's wrong?

493
00:35:09,807 --> 00:35:12,566
Even if it were not
a monstrous sin

494
00:35:12,604 --> 00:35:15,154
to steal sacred property
of Rome...

495
00:35:15,195 --> 00:35:17,123
I wasn't to know, was I?

496
00:35:17,157 --> 00:35:19,382
...you then ride through
the streets on a litter,

497
00:35:19,421 --> 00:35:22,573
shouting and singing
and broadcasting your theft

498
00:35:22,613 --> 00:35:24,403
to all and sundry.

499
00:35:24,441 --> 00:35:27,994
By sunrise, everyone in Rome will know
what you did and where you are.

500
00:35:28,035 --> 00:35:30,084
Here, in my house.

501
00:35:32,386 --> 00:35:34,353
So what's to be done then?

502
00:35:34,387 --> 00:35:37,366
You will have to
give it back.

503
00:35:37,410 --> 00:35:39,665
If you go direct
to Caesar now,

504
00:35:39,703 --> 00:35:43,256
bring him Pompey's son as a
sweetener, he might show mercy.

505
00:35:43,298 --> 00:35:45,918
Give it back?
I don't think so.

506
00:35:45,959 --> 00:35:47,978
That's not advice.
That's an order.

507
00:35:48,022 --> 00:35:50,344
Here's me come to share
a god-sent gift...

508
00:35:50,381 --> 00:35:52,776
An order!

509
00:35:52,811 --> 00:35:54,361
Damn you.
My home was invaded

510
00:35:54,407 --> 00:35:57,884
and my wife near killed
on your account.

511
00:36:01,685 --> 00:36:06,169
All right.

512
00:36:06,211 --> 00:36:08,036
But you'll come
with me though, eh?

513
00:36:08,073 --> 00:36:11,466
This is your mess.
You get yourself out of it.

514
00:36:12,963 --> 00:36:14,652
Fine then.

515
00:36:17,085 --> 00:36:19,069
I'll be off then.

516
00:36:24,035 --> 00:36:26,055
Good luck to you, sir.

517
00:36:43,654 --> 00:36:46,549
Forgive me. I will try
to return swiftly.

518
00:36:48,248 --> 00:36:51,035
Excuse me, my dear.

519
00:37:09,932 --> 00:37:12,353
Pullo, you scoundrel.

520
00:37:13,621 --> 00:37:16,272
What have you done now?

521
00:37:16,313 --> 00:37:18,933
Your honor, uh...

522
00:37:18,975 --> 00:37:20,492
Lucius Vorenus said
I should come to you and...

523
00:37:20,537 --> 00:37:21,899
Easy, soldier.

524
00:37:21,935 --> 00:37:23,862
Who is this?

525
00:37:23,897 --> 00:37:25,588
Quintus, son of Pompey.

526
00:37:25,627 --> 00:37:28,712
So it is!

527
00:37:29,981 --> 00:37:32,566
Quintus, my old cock,

528
00:37:32,608 --> 00:37:34,897
how good to see you so.

529
00:37:34,934 --> 00:37:36,525
Explain.

530
00:37:36,569 --> 00:37:39,526
Well, it's like this,
your honor.

531
00:37:39,560 --> 00:37:41,520
He, this one
come to find the gold.

532
00:37:41,554 --> 00:37:43,348
What gold?

533
00:37:43,387 --> 00:37:47,502
The gold that Pompey's boys
stole from the treasury, sir.

534
00:37:57,319 --> 00:38:00,176
Pompey does not have it?

535
00:38:00,212 --> 00:38:01,867
He doesn't, sir.

536
00:38:03,335 --> 00:38:05,799
Now I meant no disrespect,

537
00:38:05,833 --> 00:38:08,416
and had I known the gold
was from the treasury,

538
00:38:08,458 --> 00:38:12,282
I'd not have touched it. But there was
this girl here, sir...

539
00:38:12,319 --> 00:38:15,071
Never mind the girl.
Speak to the point.

540
00:38:15,109 --> 00:38:17,297
Where is the gold?

541
00:38:17,337 --> 00:38:20,265
It's all safe, sir.

542
00:38:20,300 --> 00:38:22,814
I buried it

543
00:38:22,859 --> 00:38:25,408
deep in the woods

544
00:38:25,450 --> 00:38:28,503
a couple miles
from the Flaminian gate.

545
00:38:31,606 --> 00:38:33,566
Thank you.

546
00:39:07,801 --> 00:39:09,517
You will pay for this!

547
00:39:09,557 --> 00:39:12,845
- Surely you can do better than that.
- Leave him be.

548
00:39:12,883 --> 00:39:15,536
I'm sorry we meet
like this, Quintus.

549
00:39:15,577 --> 00:39:19,157
I have only deep respect for
your father and his family.

550
00:39:19,198 --> 00:39:22,587
Kiss my ass,
you traitorous dog.

551
00:39:22,623 --> 00:39:24,673
Elegant little fellow,
isn't he?

552
00:39:26,409 --> 00:39:28,868
You need not fear.
Your life is yours still.

553
00:39:28,902 --> 00:39:30,693
I'm sending you back
to your father

554
00:39:30,731 --> 00:39:33,210
- with an offer of truce.
- A truce?

555
00:39:33,257 --> 00:39:34,843
Quiet.

556
00:39:34,886 --> 00:39:37,040
Are you run mad?

557
00:39:37,081 --> 00:39:39,832
When we have them on
their backs in the sand?

558
00:39:39,869 --> 00:39:41,854
Be quiet.

559
00:39:44,026 --> 00:39:47,504
An offer of equable truce
on good terms.

560
00:39:47,549 --> 00:39:49,837
If violence continues,

561
00:39:49,874 --> 00:39:53,128
it will not be my doing, but
that of your father and his allies.

562
00:39:53,164 --> 00:39:56,351
My father needs no truce.

563
00:39:56,388 --> 00:40:00,039
Two full moons will see you
on a spike in the Forum.

564
00:40:00,080 --> 00:40:03,463
- You wretch!
- Put him on a horse.

565
00:40:11,445 --> 00:40:13,426
You naughty woman.

566
00:40:15,231 --> 00:40:19,380
Never told me Caesar had
such a passion for you.

567
00:40:19,420 --> 00:40:21,472
Not so.

568
00:40:21,515 --> 00:40:25,231
I saw the way
he looked at you.

569
00:40:25,271 --> 00:40:28,457
Like the bull that
tupped Europa.

570
00:40:29,490 --> 00:40:32,177
I can't blame him.

571
00:40:32,217 --> 00:40:35,196
Such...

572
00:40:35,241 --> 00:40:37,032
beauty.

573
00:40:38,530 --> 00:40:40,857
Such beauty.

574
00:40:42,354 --> 00:40:45,103
Too kind.

575
00:40:45,142 --> 00:40:48,396
Far too kind.

576
00:40:48,435 --> 00:40:51,053
Caesar has no
inclination to me.

577
00:40:51,095 --> 00:40:53,609
Nor I to him.

578
00:40:55,116 --> 00:40:57,234
And such modesty.

579
00:40:59,399 --> 00:41:02,721
Is she not beautiful,
Calpurnia?

580
00:41:02,758 --> 00:41:05,049
She has none
of the goatishness

581
00:41:05,086 --> 00:41:07,070
one normally sees
in women her age.

582
00:41:08,144 --> 00:41:10,601
She has some secret
potion perhaps.

583
00:41:10,634 --> 00:41:13,494
You are attempting levity,
I believe.

584
00:41:13,530 --> 00:41:17,471
Forgive me if I do not indulge
in such talk.

585
00:41:25,364 --> 00:41:27,908
You're sure to regret
letting that one live.

586
00:41:27,950 --> 00:41:31,234
He has a malevolent
spirit.

587
00:41:31,272 --> 00:41:34,915
There's many left undead
I'll regret before I'm done.

588
00:41:36,878 --> 00:41:40,195
Take Pullo
and retrieve the gold.

589
00:41:40,232 --> 00:41:42,282
Legionary Pullo.

590
00:41:44,979 --> 00:41:47,630
You are a thief.

591
00:41:47,671 --> 00:41:51,415
A foolish,
incompetent thief.

592
00:41:51,453 --> 00:41:53,600
But you have served
us well in the past.

593
00:41:53,641 --> 00:41:56,224
So we will pretend your foolishness
is a species of honesty,

594
00:41:56,265 --> 00:41:58,584
and let you go unpunished.

595
00:41:58,622 --> 00:42:02,896
In fact, I think we
shall reward you.

596
00:42:02,934 --> 00:42:05,722
I do not like to quarrel
with Fortune,

597
00:42:05,758 --> 00:42:08,307
and clearly she's
taken you for a pet.

598
00:42:08,350 --> 00:42:12,058
When you find the trove,
give him 100 gold pieces.

599
00:42:12,097 --> 00:42:14,078
Thank you, sir.

600
00:42:14,122 --> 00:42:16,104
As you wish.

601
00:42:21,387 --> 00:42:24,177
By the by, Antony,
never question my judgment

602
00:42:24,216 --> 00:42:27,430
in the presence
of our enemies.

603
00:42:27,469 --> 00:42:31,406
You have a good memory,
so you will remember that.

604
00:42:31,451 --> 00:42:33,928
- I will remember.
- Dismissed.

605
00:42:35,301 --> 00:42:37,776
Men, horses!

606
00:42:37,821 --> 00:42:40,573
- Quick about it!
- Forward!

607
00:42:44,827 --> 00:42:47,179
Why do you frown,
little owl?

608
00:42:47,215 --> 00:42:49,266
Marc Antony speaks sense.

609
00:42:49,306 --> 00:42:52,852
Truce now does not seem
tactically correct.

610
00:42:52,895 --> 00:42:54,314
Depends on terms.

611
00:42:54,349 --> 00:42:56,208
- Ah.
- Ah.

612
00:42:56,244 --> 00:42:58,362
You offer terms that
Pompey cannot accept

613
00:42:58,404 --> 00:43:00,589
but Cicero
and the Senate can.

614
00:43:00,630 --> 00:43:03,083
Swift...

615
00:43:05,306 --> 00:43:07,628
Hold up, dominus,
there's people watching.

616
00:43:07,665 --> 00:43:10,445
Sir, take us somewhere
none can see us.

617
00:43:20,879 --> 00:43:22,833
What's in him?
Is he poisoned?

618
00:43:22,868 --> 00:43:25,516
He has the Morbus Comitialis.
It will pass in a moment.

619
00:43:25,557 --> 00:43:28,510
Please, dominus,
shut the door.

620
00:43:31,229 --> 00:43:34,511
Should we not
fetch a doctor?

621
00:43:34,549 --> 00:43:36,170
We should not.

622
00:43:36,211 --> 00:43:38,859
At all costs, he cannot
have his affliction known.

623
00:43:38,900 --> 00:43:41,119
No one will follow a man

624
00:43:41,158 --> 00:43:44,836
whom Apollo has cursed
with the Morbus.

625
00:44:38,950 --> 00:44:43,053
Vow to Orcus,
never speak of this.

626
00:45:20,300 --> 00:45:22,714
Are you quite well,
husband?

627
00:45:22,749 --> 00:45:24,794
Nothing serious.

628
00:45:26,159 --> 00:45:27,810
Come.

629
00:45:30,368 --> 00:45:34,330
Atia, I'm growing tired.
I think we shall leave you.

630
00:45:34,374 --> 00:45:36,985
Oh, well.

631
00:45:37,025 --> 00:45:41,091
- As you wish, of course.
- Good night, my dear.

632
00:45:48,423 --> 00:45:50,467
Did you have
a pleasant evening?

633
00:45:50,510 --> 00:45:52,321
I did.

634
00:45:52,359 --> 00:45:54,894
Your niece Atia
is most polite,

635
00:45:54,937 --> 00:45:58,574
and the Chief Augur made
many edifying remarks on religion.

636
00:45:58,613 --> 00:46:03,136
I regret I will not be coming home
with you immediately.

637
00:46:03,177 --> 00:46:04,601
But you're not well.

638
00:46:04,635 --> 00:46:06,584
Really,
I am quite recovered.

639
00:46:06,618 --> 00:46:09,526
I have urgent business
with my marsupial clerks.

640
00:46:09,560 --> 00:46:13,486
Business at night?
It is not proper.

641
00:46:13,531 --> 00:46:16,535
Not proper, but necessary.
I have to be ready to leave the city

642
00:46:16,577 --> 00:46:20,340
and pursue Pompey as soon
as he refuses truce.

643
00:46:20,378 --> 00:46:22,329
He will refuse?

644
00:46:22,363 --> 00:46:24,607
I believe so.

645
00:47:40,600 --> 00:47:43,257
What's wrong, Mother?

646
00:47:56,022 --> 00:47:57,966
I'm alone.

647
00:49:02,303 --> 00:49:05,011
- What does he say?
- Ridiculous!

648
00:49:05,053 --> 00:49:06,751
- What does he say?
- Nothing.

649
00:49:06,792 --> 00:49:09,103
Nothing worth repeating.

650
00:49:12,828 --> 00:49:14,096
But he offers a truce.

651
00:49:14,134 --> 00:49:16,075
On what terms?

652
00:49:16,109 --> 00:49:18,611
Truce with that scum?
Are you women?

653
00:49:18,655 --> 00:49:20,795
I'll have them raped
by dogs!

654
00:49:20,838 --> 00:49:22,505
Silence.
Get out!

655
00:49:22,545 --> 00:49:24,856
Excuse him.
He's been ill-used.

656
00:49:24,893 --> 00:49:26,925
But he is right.
There can be no truce.

657
00:49:26,968 --> 00:49:28,465
Of course not.

658
00:49:28,511 --> 00:49:31,584
But Caesar does not ask
for so much.

659
00:49:31,627 --> 00:49:35,544
- Legal immunity. Mutual disarmament.
- I must disarm? I?

660
00:49:35,579 --> 00:49:38,754
I am lawful Consul of Rome.
He is a criminal.

661
00:49:38,795 --> 00:49:41,208
There is nothing mutual
in it.

662
00:49:41,244 --> 00:49:42,949
He may be a criminal,
but he has the city.

663
00:49:42,990 --> 00:49:46,059
- We must deal with facts.
- Fact is, he is a traitor!

664
00:49:46,102 --> 00:49:48,306
Let us be fair.

665
00:49:48,346 --> 00:49:53,135
Consul, he has been
remarkably peaceable.

666
00:49:53,173 --> 00:49:56,552
He has not killed your allies
or violated your property.

667
00:49:56,588 --> 00:49:59,261
We should look
on this offer seriously.

668
00:49:59,301 --> 00:50:01,279
Do you not see
his stratagem?

669
00:50:01,313 --> 00:50:04,090
He is trying to drive
a wedge between us.

670
00:50:04,130 --> 00:50:07,544
- A truce would buy us time at least.
- Quintus is right!

671
00:50:07,580 --> 00:50:09,786
You are women!

672
00:50:11,027 --> 00:50:13,065
Fools.

673
00:50:27,586 --> 00:50:29,564
Tell me you love him.

674
00:50:29,599 --> 00:50:32,875
Tell me that
and I will go away,

675
00:50:32,914 --> 00:50:35,621
and I will never
come back.

676
00:50:37,134 --> 00:50:39,270
I love him.

677
00:50:39,312 --> 00:50:42,424
On the souls of my children,
I love him.

678
00:50:46,152 --> 00:50:50,331
Titus Pullo, what joy!

679
00:50:50,371 --> 00:50:52,345
- They let you go alive then?
- They did.

680
00:50:52,378 --> 00:50:54,914
Where's Vorenus?

681
00:50:54,961 --> 00:50:58,639
He's gone to make amends
at the shrine of Janus.

682
00:50:58,683 --> 00:51:02,692
You know Evander Pulchio,
my brother-in-law, my sister's husband.

683
00:51:05,080 --> 00:51:06,852
Evander, you say?

684
00:51:07,964 --> 00:51:10,500
Good health, soldier.

685
00:51:10,544 --> 00:51:12,780
And you.

686
00:51:15,937 --> 00:51:17,911
Will you take water?

687
00:51:17,946 --> 00:51:20,324
- I will.
- Sit you down.

688
00:51:34,668 --> 00:51:38,518
Great Jupiter, graciously
give us clear signs

689
00:51:38,555 --> 00:51:41,803
within the bounds
I have traced.

690
00:52:06,000 --> 00:52:09,952
The auguries are good.

