1
00:03:00,297 --> 00:03:03,789
Perhaps if we retreat
to the coast via Thessaly

2
00:03:03,834 --> 00:03:05,961
we could hold out
until the rains come.

3
00:03:06,003 --> 00:03:09,029
If we go eastward,
they'll be able to cut us off here.

4
00:03:09,072 --> 00:03:11,097
Oh, of course.

5
00:03:11,141 --> 00:03:12,972
It will not do.

6
00:03:13,977 --> 00:03:16,275
Ready.

7
00:03:16,313 --> 00:03:17,780
Mmm.

8
00:03:18,815 --> 00:03:20,442
Maps never
redraw themselves,

9
00:03:20,484 --> 00:03:22,349
if that's what
you're waiting for.

10
00:03:22,386 --> 00:03:25,219
He's right.

11
00:03:25,255 --> 00:03:28,122
We shall just have to fight the wretches
here where we stand.

12
00:03:28,158 --> 00:03:30,023
And beat them.

13
00:03:30,060 --> 00:03:33,029
Oh, we shall crush them, doubtless.

14
00:03:34,398 --> 00:03:38,061
Dinner for worms,
the whole damn lot of 'em.

15
00:03:38,101 --> 00:03:39,261
Dinner for worms.

16
00:03:56,386 --> 00:03:59,287
Try to avoid
bloodshed this time.

17
00:03:59,323 --> 00:04:02,622
Wait a while and
Pompey can shave you instead.

18
00:04:02,659 --> 00:04:05,253
Torquatus should
have something, no?

19
00:04:05,295 --> 00:04:07,286
A Praetorship perhaps.

20
00:04:07,331 --> 00:04:09,265
If Torquatus is
given high office,

21
00:04:09,299 --> 00:04:12,097
then Varro must be given same,
else we'll see no end of trouble.

22
00:04:12,135 --> 00:04:14,501
But then what
do we give Labienus?

23
00:04:14,538 --> 00:04:18,167
- Macedonia?
- Bythnia. Macedonia to Libo.

24
00:04:18,208 --> 00:04:21,405
Plums for your people and
porridge for the rest, eh?

25
00:04:21,445 --> 00:04:26,109
Macedonia and Bythnia
are not yet ours to bestow.

26
00:04:26,149 --> 00:04:29,141
You are cooking rabbits
that have not been caught.

27
00:04:29,186 --> 00:04:31,746
Our particular rabbit
is cornered, starving,

28
00:04:31,788 --> 00:04:34,621
and has lost
near 2,000 men.

29
00:04:34,658 --> 00:04:37,354
I think
we may safely say

30
00:04:37,394 --> 00:04:40,056
that here is a rabbit
ready for the pot.

31
00:04:42,165 --> 00:04:45,293
- Why so melancholy, Brutus?
- Oh, do I seem so?

32
00:04:45,335 --> 00:04:46,927
- Mmm.
- Forgive me.

33
00:04:46,970 --> 00:04:49,700
No, Caesar's defeat
is a glory...

34
00:04:49,740 --> 00:04:53,836
we cannot endure tyrants...
but I cannot celebrate it.

35
00:04:53,877 --> 00:04:57,142
He was
as my father to me.

36
00:04:57,180 --> 00:05:00,809
I feel for you.
When do we strike?

37
00:05:00,851 --> 00:05:02,842
Strike?
We have already struck.

38
00:05:02,886 --> 00:05:05,116
We have him down,
but he is not dead yet, eh?

39
00:05:05,155 --> 00:05:08,318
- When do we strike the final blow?
- There will not be one.

40
00:05:08,358 --> 00:05:11,725
If we simply keep him bottled up
a month or so more,

41
00:05:11,762 --> 00:05:15,698
the remains of his army will
disintegrate and disappear,

42
00:05:15,732 --> 00:05:17,723
- at no cost to us.
- Is that honorable?

43
00:05:17,768 --> 00:05:20,168
- Mmm?
- Caesar has driven us from Rome,

44
00:05:20,203 --> 00:05:23,695
chased us out of Italy,
killed our friends,

45
00:05:23,740 --> 00:05:25,640
usurped our Republic.

46
00:05:25,676 --> 00:05:28,941
Surely, dignity and honor demands
we walk in his blood.

47
00:05:28,979 --> 00:05:30,503
Certainly, knee deep.

48
00:05:30,547 --> 00:05:32,105
But you would have hunger
do our work for us!

49
00:05:32,149 --> 00:05:35,812
We must attack Caesar
and kill him under the eyes of Mars,

50
00:05:35,852 --> 00:05:38,685
- else our victory is empty.
- He has sense.

51
00:05:38,722 --> 00:05:41,418
It will look better
at home if we win by force.

52
00:05:41,458 --> 00:05:43,653
You are Pompey Magnus.

53
00:05:43,694 --> 00:05:47,994
You conquer and crush your enemies
as if they were insects.

54
00:05:48,031 --> 00:05:51,432
People will be disappointed
by anything less.

55
00:05:53,570 --> 00:05:56,505
News from Greece.

56
00:05:56,540 --> 00:05:59,839
Mark Antony is safe,
but most of the ships in his fleet

57
00:05:59,876 --> 00:06:05,007
sent in aid of Gaius Julius Caesar
have been lost at sea.

58
00:06:05,048 --> 00:06:10,008
Caesar is now surrounded
and severely outnumbered.

59
00:06:10,053 --> 00:06:12,248
The forces
of the Republic and Senate

60
00:06:12,289 --> 00:06:14,814
and of Pompey Magnus
confidently expect

61
00:06:14,858 --> 00:06:18,350
a decisive victory
to follow shortly.

62
00:06:23,600 --> 00:06:25,966
- There you are.
- Here I am.

63
00:06:26,002 --> 00:06:27,936
I ask Timon
for protection,

64
00:06:27,971 --> 00:06:31,134
and he sends me a bunch
of half wits and clowns!

65
00:06:31,174 --> 00:06:33,233
- Dear me.
- Caesar will soon be dead

66
00:06:33,276 --> 00:06:35,369
by every account,
and we shall be undefended.

67
00:06:35,412 --> 00:06:37,778
We may as well be lying
naked in the street!

68
00:06:37,814 --> 00:06:40,806
You must go to Servilia
and ask for a few of her men

69
00:06:40,851 --> 00:06:43,342
- to stand outside for us.
- Why?

70
00:06:43,386 --> 00:06:46,617
So that they can guard
our doors in her name, silly.

71
00:06:46,656 --> 00:06:48,590
I mean why must I go?

72
00:06:48,625 --> 00:06:50,616
Well, as if I would
go begging to Servilia.

73
00:06:50,660 --> 00:06:53,288
- I think not.
- I'll not go begging for you.

74
00:06:53,330 --> 00:06:55,730
Oh, don't be so childish.
It's not as if she'll refuse.

75
00:06:55,766 --> 00:06:57,893
- You think?
- Why would she?

76
00:06:57,934 --> 00:07:00,459
Those lovely gifts
I gave her?

77
00:07:02,839 --> 00:07:05,774
- What did she say?
- Nothing.

78
00:07:06,777 --> 00:07:08,301
- Nothing.
- She said something.

79
00:07:08,345 --> 00:07:10,404
She said nothing.

80
00:07:10,447 --> 00:07:13,348
You're very arrogant,
that's all.

81
00:07:13,383 --> 00:07:16,284
Think you can buy her friendship
with stud slaves and tortoises?

82
00:07:16,319 --> 00:07:17,809
And six barrels of ice.

83
00:07:17,854 --> 00:07:19,685
I'd rather not go.

84
00:07:19,723 --> 00:07:21,918
You'd rather not go.

85
00:07:21,958 --> 00:07:24,188
You'd rather be gang-raped
by slavering proles

86
00:07:24,227 --> 00:07:26,058
while your mother's house
burns down around you.

87
00:07:26,096 --> 00:07:27,586
Frankly, I'm past caring.

88
00:07:27,631 --> 00:07:30,566
One day Caesar is winning
and you crow happily,

89
00:07:30,600 --> 00:07:33,228
next day he is losing,
and I must go a-begging?

90
00:07:33,270 --> 00:07:36,535
I just want this vile war
to be over,

91
00:07:36,573 --> 00:07:39,406
- one way or the other.
- Octavia, it is over.

92
00:07:39,442 --> 00:07:41,706
That is why you must go
to Servilia's house.

93
00:07:41,745 --> 00:07:44,805
It's a bore, I know,
but there we are.

94
00:08:01,264 --> 00:08:02,822
Lyde.

95
00:08:06,703 --> 00:08:09,103
Very nice.

96
00:08:10,106 --> 00:08:11,733
Don't.

97
00:08:14,611 --> 00:08:16,670
I'm glad to see you.

98
00:08:16,713 --> 00:08:18,772
I've been worried
about you.

99
00:08:19,950 --> 00:08:21,850
No need.

100
00:08:21,885 --> 00:08:24,080
I'm doing very well.

101
00:08:24,120 --> 00:08:26,350
Not as well
as you, obviously.

102
00:08:28,625 --> 00:08:30,559
Do you need money?

103
00:08:31,728 --> 00:08:33,753
I've got money
if you need some.

104
00:08:33,797 --> 00:08:35,765
I'm sure you have.

105
00:08:35,799 --> 00:08:38,495
Turns out your man
backed the right horse.

106
00:08:41,071 --> 00:08:43,733
Fortune loves you.

107
00:08:45,508 --> 00:08:48,739
I don't know if Vorenus
is alive or dead.

108
00:08:53,717 --> 00:08:56,083
I'm sorry.

109
00:08:58,755 --> 00:09:00,689
I'm sorry.

110
00:09:00,724 --> 00:09:03,591
I didn't want
to be like this.

111
00:09:04,628 --> 00:09:08,655
I'm so tired, Niobe.

112
00:09:09,699 --> 00:09:12,998
I'm tired
of being angry.

113
00:09:13,036 --> 00:09:15,937
I'm tired of...

114
00:09:15,972 --> 00:09:17,963
hating you.

115
00:09:22,846 --> 00:09:25,076
You're all I've got.

116
00:09:31,788 --> 00:09:33,779
I'm sorry.

117
00:09:38,662 --> 00:09:40,755
Do you want
some honey water?

118
00:10:10,694 --> 00:10:13,254
You're wasting
your time!

119
00:10:13,296 --> 00:10:16,788
We'll die of thirst
long before we die of hunger.

120
00:10:24,107 --> 00:10:26,098
We could drink
their blood.

121
00:10:26,142 --> 00:10:29,077
- Repeat?
- All these dead men,

122
00:10:29,112 --> 00:10:31,603
we can drink
their blood.

123
00:10:31,648 --> 00:10:34,014
Too salty.

124
00:10:34,050 --> 00:10:36,348
Only make you
more thirsty.

125
00:10:37,354 --> 00:10:39,720
Putrid by now anyway.

126
00:10:43,059 --> 00:10:44,993
Doesn't matter.

127
00:10:45,028 --> 00:10:47,588
Everything will be fine.

128
00:10:49,132 --> 00:10:51,327
This is where we die.

129
00:10:53,303 --> 00:10:55,533
What are you writing?

130
00:10:55,572 --> 00:10:57,972
A message to Niobe.

131
00:10:58,008 --> 00:10:59,999
All right.

132
00:11:00,043 --> 00:11:01,510
Good idea.

133
00:11:03,046 --> 00:11:05,537
Send my best to Eirene,
will you, while you're at it?

134
00:11:06,583 --> 00:11:09,017
If there's space.

135
00:11:20,163 --> 00:11:22,961
Graces,
don't we look lovely.

136
00:11:22,999 --> 00:11:25,866
If I am to be a beggar,
I will not look like one.

137
00:11:25,902 --> 00:11:27,733
Oh, I am not
objecting, my honey,

138
00:11:27,771 --> 00:11:31,172
though you will remind Servilia of
what an old trout she has become.

139
00:11:31,207 --> 00:11:34,142
I'm just happy to see you
looking so pretty for once.

140
00:11:34,177 --> 00:11:36,543
You do so often insist
on playing the frump.

141
00:11:52,729 --> 00:11:55,664
- I hope your mother thrives.
- She does.

142
00:11:55,698 --> 00:11:58,292
- And your son?
- Also.

143
00:12:07,143 --> 00:12:10,943
- My mother sends me to ask a favor.
- Mm-hmm?

144
00:12:12,115 --> 00:12:13,844
She fears
the consequences

145
00:12:13,883 --> 00:12:15,646
of this last battle
in Greece.

146
00:12:15,685 --> 00:12:18,483
Understandably.

147
00:12:18,521 --> 00:12:22,184
She has enjoyed her ascendancy
a little too well.

148
00:12:23,927 --> 00:12:26,225
She asks you
to lend her some men

149
00:12:26,262 --> 00:12:29,698
to protect our door
in your name.

150
00:12:31,568 --> 00:12:33,763
Of course.

151
00:12:34,871 --> 00:12:38,398
Eleni, send Ajax
and three or four others,

152
00:12:38,441 --> 00:12:41,467
- whoever he thinks best.
- Thank you.

153
00:12:41,511 --> 00:12:45,311
It's very kind of you.
I told my mother

154
00:12:45,348 --> 00:12:47,407
- she should not presume...
- Please.

155
00:12:47,450 --> 00:12:49,509
She shall have
what she needs.

156
00:13:00,730 --> 00:13:03,790
Forgive me.
You are so good to us.

157
00:13:03,833 --> 00:13:06,802
- We do not deserve it.
- Don't.

158
00:13:12,976 --> 00:13:14,910
I mu... I must look
a fright.

159
00:13:14,944 --> 00:13:16,809
Mmm.

160
00:13:17,847 --> 00:13:20,042
No, not really.

161
00:13:21,084 --> 00:13:23,075
You look lovely.

162
00:13:29,192 --> 00:13:31,023
I better go home.

163
00:13:31,060 --> 00:13:33,494
So soon?

164
00:13:33,530 --> 00:13:35,794
My mother
will be worried.

165
00:13:38,134 --> 00:13:40,466
Well, if you feel
you should.

166
00:13:47,377 --> 00:13:49,675
Octavia...

167
00:14:23,213 --> 00:14:25,181
Thank you.

168
00:14:42,966 --> 00:14:44,627
Send to Rome.

169
00:14:44,667 --> 00:14:46,498
Tell them...

170
00:14:47,537 --> 00:14:49,505
the decisive battle

171
00:14:49,539 --> 00:14:52,007
begins today.

172
00:15:02,485 --> 00:15:05,648
Sir! Pompey's legions
are in the field in battle array!

173
00:15:05,688 --> 00:15:08,054
Thank you, Fulvio.
Have you forgotten how to salute?

174
00:15:08,091 --> 00:15:10,059
I haven't, sir.
No excuse, sir.

175
00:15:10,093 --> 00:15:12,493
Gracchus,
sound assembly!

176
00:15:12,528 --> 00:15:15,759
- Have Xeno saddle my horse.
- Sir!

177
00:15:17,767 --> 00:15:21,066
We will accept battle?

178
00:15:21,104 --> 00:15:22,901
Certainly. Why not?

179
00:15:22,939 --> 00:15:26,067
We are outnumbered

180
00:15:26,109 --> 00:15:29,875
three to one on foot
and five to one on horse.

181
00:15:29,912 --> 00:15:32,039
What uninjured men
we have

182
00:15:32,081 --> 00:15:34,413
are scared
and hungry and desperate.

183
00:15:34,450 --> 00:15:37,214
That is the advantage
we must press home.

184
00:15:37,253 --> 00:15:39,778
I was not aware
irony had military usage.

185
00:15:40,823 --> 00:15:42,882
We must win or die.

186
00:15:43,993 --> 00:15:46,928
Pompey's men
have other options.

187
00:17:03,272 --> 00:17:05,502
Goodbye, Posca.

188
00:18:05,134 --> 00:18:09,969
Caesar!
Caesar! Caesar!

189
00:18:27,857 --> 00:18:29,825
Send to Rome.

190
00:18:29,859 --> 00:18:31,850
Tell them
Caesar has won.

191
00:19:08,731 --> 00:19:12,030
Sir! Caesar's men
are coming!

192
00:19:12,068 --> 00:19:14,127
I've cut my hand.

193
00:19:14,170 --> 00:19:17,662
We have to go, sir!
They'll catch you.

194
00:19:17,707 --> 00:19:21,541
It's not deep,
but it hurts.

195
00:19:22,578 --> 00:19:24,944
They will kill you!

196
00:19:24,981 --> 00:19:27,916
It's of no consequence.

197
00:19:34,423 --> 00:19:37,915
Our forces are routed.
What are we to do?

198
00:19:37,960 --> 00:19:40,952
We shall fight again
another day I do not doubt...

199
00:19:40,997 --> 00:19:42,988
- And prevail!
- ...and prevail.

200
00:19:44,267 --> 00:19:46,360
But for the present
we must look to our safety.

201
00:19:46,402 --> 00:19:48,097
Our safety is nothing.

202
00:19:48,137 --> 00:19:51,265
We must leave Greece
and look to fresh levies.

203
00:19:51,307 --> 00:19:53,867
- And may one ask where?
- Africa.

204
00:19:53,910 --> 00:19:55,878
We must rally
the cities of Africa.

205
00:19:55,912 --> 00:19:57,971
Africa. Dear gods,

206
00:19:58,014 --> 00:19:59,709
we are fast running out
of continents.

207
00:19:59,749 --> 00:20:01,216
And coin!

208
00:20:01,250 --> 00:20:04,014
We have taxed
every last coin from Greece

209
00:20:04,053 --> 00:20:05,486
and spent it all.

210
00:20:05,521 --> 00:20:07,648
What shall we use
to buy Africa's loyalty?

211
00:20:07,690 --> 00:20:09,988
- Seashells?
- We need buy nothing!

212
00:20:10,026 --> 00:20:11,516
We are
the Senate of Rome!

213
00:20:11,561 --> 00:20:13,722
We are old men
with mud on our shoes!

214
00:20:13,763 --> 00:20:15,958
We are not beaten
until we are dead.

215
00:20:15,998 --> 00:20:18,762
The Republic lives
as long as we do!

216
00:20:18,801 --> 00:20:20,428
You may fight on
as you wish.

217
00:20:20,469 --> 00:20:22,437
As for me,

218
00:20:22,471 --> 00:20:26,100
I will go from here
and surrender myself to Caesar.

219
00:20:26,142 --> 00:20:28,770
Have you no dignity?
No honor?

220
00:20:28,811 --> 00:20:30,608
Some little I hope.

221
00:20:30,646 --> 00:20:33,080
Not so much
as you of course.

222
00:20:33,115 --> 00:20:36,278
- Caesar will kill you.
- That may be.

223
00:20:37,320 --> 00:20:39,652
I'm not afraid to die.

224
00:20:40,690 --> 00:20:42,749
I'm tired.

225
00:20:44,427 --> 00:20:46,987
I want to go home.

226
00:20:52,301 --> 00:20:54,929
Yes. My feelings exact.

227
00:20:54,971 --> 00:20:57,769
Brutus, without the force of your name,
the cause of the Re...

228
00:20:57,807 --> 00:21:02,005
Do not! Do not talk
to me of the Republic.

229
00:21:02,044 --> 00:21:04,911
If I had known
what wretched company

230
00:21:04,947 --> 00:21:06,847
and rotten food
I would endure,

231
00:21:06,882 --> 00:21:10,750
if I had known what
an old fool is Pompey,

232
00:21:10,786 --> 00:21:13,516
I would never
have left Rome.

233
00:21:19,362 --> 00:21:21,694
Forgive my anger.

234
00:21:23,299 --> 00:21:26,530
- I am not myself.
- Think nothing of it.

235
00:21:26,569 --> 00:21:29,470
I merit
your disappointment.

236
00:21:31,540 --> 00:21:34,100
I propose we make
for Amphipoli.

237
00:21:34,143 --> 00:21:36,008
I have men
and money there,

238
00:21:36,045 --> 00:21:37,774
and we can go
by sea to Egypt.

239
00:21:37,813 --> 00:21:40,941
Ptolemy's children are
loyal friends of mine.

240
00:21:40,983 --> 00:21:43,247
Perhaps...

241
00:21:45,354 --> 00:21:47,288
Perhaps it's better

242
00:21:47,323 --> 00:21:50,019
we do not travel together.

243
00:21:55,931 --> 00:21:58,024
Perhaps you're right.

244
00:21:58,067 --> 00:22:00,126
Better.

245
00:22:01,604 --> 00:22:03,595
No doubt.

246
00:22:34,870 --> 00:22:36,838
I don't understand it.

247
00:22:36,872 --> 00:22:39,500
Something should have
turned up by now.

248
00:22:39,542 --> 00:22:41,510
I'm not meant
to die this way.

249
00:22:41,544 --> 00:22:44,877
- You were misinformed.
- Doesn't seem right.

250
00:22:47,983 --> 00:22:49,951
Still...

251
00:22:49,985 --> 00:22:53,614
it'd be good
to see my mother again.

252
00:22:53,656 --> 00:22:55,624
Do you think
they have a system

253
00:22:55,658 --> 00:22:57,626
- for finding people?
- What?

254
00:22:57,660 --> 00:23:00,424
In the afterlife... how do you
go about finding people?

255
00:23:00,463 --> 00:23:04,024
- There must be millions of them.
- Must be.

256
00:23:10,272 --> 00:23:13,332
She won't recognize me,
probably.

257
00:23:13,375 --> 00:23:16,208
I was very young
when she died.

258
00:23:29,558 --> 00:23:32,584
Probably give her
a big scare though, huh?

259
00:23:32,628 --> 00:23:36,291
Big, ugly brute coming along
and giving her a hug.

260
00:23:37,633 --> 00:23:39,601
- Look at that.
- What?

261
00:23:39,635 --> 00:23:41,466
That corpse.

262
00:23:42,638 --> 00:23:45,766
See how high it rides
in the water?

263
00:23:45,808 --> 00:23:48,777
The plutonic aether
inflates him.

264
00:23:48,811 --> 00:23:50,802
What of it?

265
00:23:51,981 --> 00:23:54,506
You've not been drinking
seawater, have you?!

266
00:25:49,465 --> 00:25:52,628
- Husband, eat.
- Oh, yeah.

267
00:25:54,203 --> 00:25:56,171
Over here, my dear.

268
00:25:56,205 --> 00:25:57,695
Here.

269
00:25:59,308 --> 00:26:02,243
- Little salty.
- Not at all. It's good, neh?

270
00:26:03,245 --> 00:26:05,213
Delicious, Mama.

271
00:26:05,247 --> 00:26:07,977
Bona Dea,
look at your faces.

272
00:26:09,285 --> 00:26:12,254
Oh, sillies.

273
00:26:57,466 --> 00:26:59,434
Helen?

274
00:26:59,468 --> 00:27:01,026
Helen!

275
00:27:01,070 --> 00:27:03,664
Husband, wake up!
Our people are leaving.

276
00:27:13,749 --> 00:27:15,717
Now now, my darlings.
Don't be scared.

277
00:27:15,751 --> 00:27:17,719
We're on
an adventure, eh?

278
00:27:17,753 --> 00:27:20,381
The first one
to see the sea and cry out

279
00:27:20,422 --> 00:27:22,754
will have a peach
when we get to Amphipoli.

280
00:27:31,934 --> 00:27:33,902
You, your name again?

281
00:27:33,936 --> 00:27:36,063
Eh...

282
00:27:36,105 --> 00:27:38,903
- Lysandros.
- Lysandros, how far to Amphipoli?

283
00:27:38,941 --> 00:27:40,909
Oh, very close.
Close.

284
00:27:40,943 --> 00:27:43,912
We will continue there
as planned.

285
00:27:43,946 --> 00:27:48,076
You're not to announce my identity
to those that we meet.

286
00:27:48,117 --> 00:27:49,709
And if they ask?

287
00:27:51,787 --> 00:27:53,755
Mella.

288
00:27:53,789 --> 00:27:56,451
- Aeneas Mella.
- Hear and obey, Captain.

289
00:27:56,492 --> 00:27:58,460
And who'll pay?

290
00:27:58,494 --> 00:28:00,394
Pay?

291
00:28:00,429 --> 00:28:02,397
You've been paid already.

292
00:28:02,431 --> 00:28:04,831
For guiding,
not for protection.

293
00:28:04,867 --> 00:28:06,835
I have many men
and supplies

294
00:28:06,869 --> 00:28:08,962
and ample coin
in Amphipoli.

295
00:28:09,004 --> 00:28:12,030
- You will be paid there.
- None with you now? Coin?

296
00:28:12,074 --> 00:28:15,168
None! I'll tolerate
no more of your impudence!

297
00:28:15,210 --> 00:28:17,838
No disrespect, Captain.
Only asking.

298
00:28:17,880 --> 00:28:20,713
We go.

299
00:28:58,287 --> 00:29:01,688
You drive me insane
with your wretched muttering.

300
00:29:01,723 --> 00:29:04,715
What is wrong that you must
harass the gods so?

301
00:29:05,727 --> 00:29:07,217
Nothing.

302
00:29:07,262 --> 00:29:09,230
Well, stop it then.

303
00:29:09,264 --> 00:29:12,358
Servilia sends to invite you
to weave with her tomorrow.

304
00:29:12,401 --> 00:29:13,993
Oh.

305
00:29:14,036 --> 00:29:17,164
- I cannot.
- Of course you can.

306
00:29:17,206 --> 00:29:18,969
- I've already accepted.
- I cannot!

307
00:29:19,007 --> 00:29:21,100
I know she's tedious.
I mean really,

308
00:29:21,143 --> 00:29:22,405
weaving,

309
00:29:22,444 --> 00:29:25,436
but we must keep her happy
for the time being.

310
00:29:27,082 --> 00:29:28,447
But...

311
00:29:42,431 --> 00:29:44,558
The sea!
The sea!

312
00:29:44,600 --> 00:29:47,262
Unison. You shall
both have a peach.

313
00:30:00,616 --> 00:30:02,607
Look, Mama.
Dead people.

314
00:30:24,206 --> 00:30:26,367
It's good, huh?

315
00:30:26,408 --> 00:30:28,933
Where do you come from?

316
00:30:28,977 --> 00:30:30,274
Brindisi.

317
00:30:30,312 --> 00:30:32,507
Romans?

318
00:30:35,450 --> 00:30:37,077
I know you.

319
00:30:37,119 --> 00:30:39,644
Where do I know you from?

320
00:30:42,824 --> 00:30:44,792
I have not
seen you before.

321
00:30:44,826 --> 00:30:46,794
I'm sure I've
seen you somewhere.

322
00:30:46,828 --> 00:30:49,023
Leave them water and bread,
we need to be going.

323
00:30:49,064 --> 00:30:51,624
Leave them?
Weak as they are?

324
00:30:51,667 --> 00:30:53,999
I have no time to waste.

325
00:30:55,337 --> 00:30:58,135
Soon be dark anyhow.

326
00:30:58,173 --> 00:31:00,733
We camp here, get to Amphipoli
in the morning.

327
00:31:00,776 --> 00:31:02,744
I insist we go on.

328
00:31:02,778 --> 00:31:04,211
Relax, old man.

329
00:31:04,246 --> 00:31:06,237
We get there.

330
00:31:11,119 --> 00:31:13,087
You rest easy now, boys.

331
00:31:13,121 --> 00:31:15,589
Eat, drink,
get your strength back.

332
00:31:15,624 --> 00:31:17,524
You and me
will be good friends.

333
00:31:20,629 --> 00:31:23,427
Hey! You want
my cock up you

334
00:31:23,465 --> 00:31:25,433
or are you going to
build a damn fire?

335
00:31:25,467 --> 00:31:28,129
I told you
we'd be all right.

336
00:31:30,439 --> 00:31:32,964
There's no pleasing some.

337
00:31:42,484 --> 00:31:44,452
We stop here?

338
00:31:44,486 --> 00:31:46,283
Why so early?

339
00:31:46,321 --> 00:31:49,313
Best to, I think.
It'll be dark soon.

340
00:31:51,159 --> 00:31:53,286
- Who are they?
- How should I know?

341
00:31:53,328 --> 00:31:55,455
Who cares who they are?

342
00:31:55,497 --> 00:31:58,466
Sorry. Sorry.

343
00:31:58,500 --> 00:32:00,400
I...

344
00:32:00,435 --> 00:32:02,403
all will be well,

345
00:32:02,437 --> 00:32:05,099
I assure you.

346
00:32:05,140 --> 00:32:07,131
All will be well.

347
00:32:11,913 --> 00:32:14,245
Pompey Magnus.

348
00:32:14,283 --> 00:32:16,751
That man looks exactly
like Pompey Magnus.

349
00:32:16,785 --> 00:32:18,753
That's why I thought
I'd met him.

350
00:32:18,787 --> 00:32:20,812
Don't point.

351
00:32:24,793 --> 00:32:27,261
- Never.
- It's hard to believe, eh?

352
00:32:27,296 --> 00:32:29,287
His wife
and sprouts too.

353
00:32:29,331 --> 00:32:32,630
Caesar's going
to drown us in gold.

354
00:32:32,668 --> 00:32:33,828
Thank you.

355
00:32:39,975 --> 00:32:41,465
Cac!

356
00:32:45,981 --> 00:32:47,710
What do we do?

357
00:32:49,318 --> 00:32:51,980
I don't know yet.

358
00:32:52,020 --> 00:32:54,352
Thank you for coming.

359
00:32:56,491 --> 00:32:59,085
Mother insisted.

360
00:32:59,127 --> 00:33:01,789
I understand you want me
to do some weaving with you.

361
00:33:05,434 --> 00:33:07,834
I'm sorry you are upset.

362
00:33:07,869 --> 00:33:09,837
The last time
we saw each other...

363
00:33:09,871 --> 00:33:12,203
It's of no consequence.

364
00:33:14,876 --> 00:33:16,537
Are you fond of weaving?

365
00:33:19,881 --> 00:33:22,543
So did I.

366
00:33:27,456 --> 00:33:29,424
And how is your brother?

367
00:33:29,458 --> 00:33:31,449
- Is he still in Mediolanum?
- He is.

368
00:33:32,961 --> 00:33:35,759
Lovely town,
so I'm told.

369
00:33:35,797 --> 00:33:37,059
- Healthy air.
- Domina?

370
00:33:37,099 --> 00:33:39,090
What is it, Eleni?

371
00:33:43,138 --> 00:33:45,538
Word from Greece.

372
00:33:45,574 --> 00:33:47,064
Caesar has won.

373
00:33:48,810 --> 00:33:52,302
And Pompey's armies
are completely destroyed.

374
00:33:59,154 --> 00:34:01,088
And my son?

375
00:34:04,092 --> 00:34:05,582
No word.

376
00:34:35,957 --> 00:34:37,948
Don't cry.

377
00:35:02,751 --> 00:35:04,742
Oh.

378
00:36:07,082 --> 00:36:10,210
Halt!
In the name of Rome!

379
00:36:10,252 --> 00:36:13,619
Calls himself Rome, now,
does he? Shameless.

380
00:36:13,655 --> 00:36:16,021
Who are you
and what's your purpose?

381
00:36:16,057 --> 00:36:18,025
We are Rome, boy,

382
00:36:18,059 --> 00:36:20,027
what's left of it.

383
00:36:20,061 --> 00:36:24,088
Come to surrender
to your chief.

384
00:36:37,946 --> 00:36:39,208
Brutus!

385
00:36:39,247 --> 00:36:41,215
Cicero!

386
00:36:41,249 --> 00:36:43,774
How happy I am
to see you.

387
00:36:43,818 --> 00:36:46,343
I thought
you were dead.

388
00:36:46,388 --> 00:36:48,356
Sir, I...

389
00:36:48,390 --> 00:36:51,257
I am come here
honorably,

390
00:36:51,293 --> 00:36:53,921
with no request
for mercy,

391
00:36:53,962 --> 00:36:56,829
to surrender my arms
and my horses

392
00:36:56,865 --> 00:37:01,734
- as is...
- Ssh. We'll have no talk of surrender.

393
00:37:01,770 --> 00:37:04,762
We've merely quarreled a little.
Now we are friends again, eh?

394
00:37:04,806 --> 00:37:08,037
That is
most generous of you

395
00:37:08,076 --> 00:37:10,271
and natural
to your manly nature,

396
00:37:10,312 --> 00:37:13,213
- but I cannot...
- My poor boy.

397
00:37:13,248 --> 00:37:15,216
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.

398
00:37:15,250 --> 00:37:17,218
Not at all.

399
00:37:17,252 --> 00:37:19,117
It is I am sorry.

400
00:37:19,154 --> 00:37:22,453
I presented you
with an impossible dilemma.

401
00:37:22,490 --> 00:37:25,789
You did only
what you thought honorable,

402
00:37:25,827 --> 00:37:28,022
I'm sure.

403
00:37:28,063 --> 00:37:30,054
I kiss you for it.

404
00:37:32,767 --> 00:37:34,735
Thank you.

405
00:37:34,769 --> 00:37:36,737
I will not forget
this grace.

406
00:37:36,771 --> 00:37:39,763
- As I was saying, a most generous...
- But what of Pompey?

407
00:37:39,808 --> 00:37:41,673
Tell me he lives.

408
00:37:42,777 --> 00:37:44,369
He lives.

409
00:37:44,412 --> 00:37:46,573
Thank the gods.
Where is he?

410
00:37:48,783 --> 00:37:50,774
He...

411
00:37:52,287 --> 00:37:54,585
He does not plan
to surrender.

412
00:37:56,124 --> 00:37:58,558
That is insane.

413
00:37:58,593 --> 00:38:00,823
He cannot escape.
Where can he go?

414
00:38:00,862 --> 00:38:02,830
Is Scipio with him?

415
00:38:02,864 --> 00:38:04,195
Cato?

416
00:38:05,767 --> 00:38:07,758
They have fled
to Africa.

417
00:38:09,771 --> 00:38:11,762
What am I thinking of...

418
00:38:12,774 --> 00:38:14,742
asking you questions
when you must be

419
00:38:14,776 --> 00:38:16,801
so hungry and thirsty?

420
00:38:16,845 --> 00:38:18,813
Come.

421
00:38:18,847 --> 00:38:22,146
I, uh...

422
00:38:22,183 --> 00:38:25,175
- I think I would rather...
- I insist.

423
00:38:26,221 --> 00:38:28,212
Come.

424
00:38:31,092 --> 00:38:33,560
So with this hand,
otherwise engaged

425
00:38:33,595 --> 00:38:35,722
I had to take
that worm and beat him

426
00:38:35,764 --> 00:38:38,062
with my fists
over and over

427
00:38:38,099 --> 00:38:39,999
and over again!

428
00:39:27,916 --> 00:39:31,682
His father King Ptolemy
Auletes the 12th

429
00:39:31,720 --> 00:39:33,950
was a close
friend of mine.

430
00:39:33,988 --> 00:39:36,923
I was always assured
a loving welcome

431
00:39:36,958 --> 00:39:39,392
in Egypt. I remember
on one occasion

432
00:39:39,427 --> 00:39:42,089
I was out hunting
with the King.

433
00:39:42,130 --> 00:39:44,223
We were hunting lions,
you see.

434
00:39:46,935 --> 00:39:49,733
Only the King
was rather a poor bowman,

435
00:39:49,771 --> 00:39:52,740
and we couldn't tell

436
00:39:52,774 --> 00:39:56,904
if the lion
was wounded or dead.

437
00:40:12,127 --> 00:40:14,095
Hello, friends.

438
00:40:14,129 --> 00:40:16,290
Feeling better, neh?
Strong?

439
00:40:16,331 --> 00:40:18,322
Strong enough.

440
00:40:20,802 --> 00:40:24,431
Tell me something.
What's the name of that Roman?

441
00:40:24,472 --> 00:40:26,440
His name is, uh,

442
00:40:26,474 --> 00:40:30,377
Aeneas Mella.

443
00:40:30,411 --> 00:40:33,209
That's what he said.

444
00:40:33,248 --> 00:40:35,910
What do you hear
of Caesar and Pompey?

445
00:40:35,950 --> 00:40:39,010
They fought,
I heard.

446
00:40:40,321 --> 00:40:42,289
And?

447
00:40:42,323 --> 00:40:45,121
You know who won.

448
00:40:45,160 --> 00:40:47,151
Tell us.

449
00:40:48,496 --> 00:40:50,464
Pfft!

450
00:40:50,498 --> 00:40:52,466
I was going
to let you in anyway.

451
00:40:52,500 --> 00:40:56,231
- What's he talking about?
- You boys are clever fellows, I bet.

452
00:40:56,271 --> 00:40:58,239
Know how to fight.

453
00:40:58,273 --> 00:41:02,505
Me and my boys can't take
his people alone.

454
00:41:02,544 --> 00:41:05,104
Us and you together,
no problem.

455
00:41:05,146 --> 00:41:07,842
We go down middle
on the reward.

456
00:41:07,882 --> 00:41:09,850
Not a bad idea.

457
00:41:09,884 --> 00:41:11,852
You can have
the wife and children,

458
00:41:11,886 --> 00:41:13,877
I take the slaves.

459
00:41:16,958 --> 00:41:18,926
Walk away...

460
00:41:18,960 --> 00:41:21,758
- and do not speak of this again.
- I see.

461
00:41:21,796 --> 00:41:23,764
Think you don't
need me, eh?

462
00:41:23,798 --> 00:41:26,596
Think you can keep
the reward for yourself?

463
00:41:26,634 --> 00:41:29,034
- Fuck you. Not going to happen.
- Don't.

464
00:41:29,070 --> 00:41:32,836
Fuck you! I gave you
your lives back,

465
00:41:32,874 --> 00:41:34,842
I can take them
away again, easy.

466
00:41:36,878 --> 00:41:38,846
When I am
finished speaking,

467
00:41:38,880 --> 00:41:41,508
you will turn
and run

468
00:41:41,549 --> 00:41:43,517
- that way.
- That way?

469
00:41:43,551 --> 00:41:45,041
What about
this way?

470
00:41:45,086 --> 00:41:47,054
Do not stop until
you are out of my sight

471
00:41:47,088 --> 00:41:49,579
and do not delay,
or I will kill you.

472
00:41:50,825 --> 00:41:52,793
What is wrong
with him?

473
00:41:52,827 --> 00:41:55,022
I am finished speaking.

474
00:42:10,111 --> 00:42:12,341
A bit harsh,
isn't it?

475
00:42:12,380 --> 00:42:15,178
Fair enough deal
he was offering, I thought.

476
00:42:15,216 --> 00:42:17,343
- What is the meaning of this?
- Sir...

477
00:42:17,385 --> 00:42:19,410
Speak up! This man
was in my employ!

478
00:42:19,454 --> 00:42:21,513
- He planned to assault you.
- How do you know?

479
00:42:21,556 --> 00:42:23,524
He asked us
to participate.

480
00:42:23,558 --> 00:42:26,755
You refused, stabbed him
to death on my behalf.

481
00:42:26,794 --> 00:42:28,921
A good friend to me
on such short acquaintance.

482
00:42:28,963 --> 00:42:31,761
- What is your name?
- I am Lucius Vorenus.

483
00:42:31,799 --> 00:42:35,758
Prefect and Evocati of
the 13th Legion of Galius Julius Caesar.

484
00:42:35,803 --> 00:42:37,771
Titus Pullo,
legionary of same.

485
00:42:37,805 --> 00:42:39,773
Salve, Lucius Vorenus.

486
00:42:39,807 --> 00:42:42,435
I am...

487
00:42:42,477 --> 00:42:44,445
Aeneus Mella...

488
00:42:44,479 --> 00:42:46,470
of Pergamum.

489
00:42:50,151 --> 00:42:52,142
Aeneus Mella.

490
00:42:54,489 --> 00:42:56,753
You must consider yourself
under my charge.

491
00:42:56,791 --> 00:42:58,759
I do not understand.

492
00:42:58,793 --> 00:43:00,693
Consider yourself
a prisoner

493
00:43:00,728 --> 00:43:03,219
of the 13th Legion.

494
00:43:03,264 --> 00:43:05,232
I'm just a merchant.

495
00:43:05,266 --> 00:43:08,258
We know
who you are, sir.

496
00:43:10,772 --> 00:43:13,240
I own you now!
Understand?!

497
00:43:13,274 --> 00:43:15,242
You, you,
bury him.

498
00:43:15,276 --> 00:43:17,403
The rest of you...

499
00:43:17,445 --> 00:43:20,903
- don't let them leave.
- Lucius Vorenus.

500
00:43:20,949 --> 00:43:22,940
I must speak
with you alone.

501
00:43:24,786 --> 00:43:26,879
Stay here.

502
00:43:28,623 --> 00:43:30,591
Of course
I do not say I am

503
00:43:30,625 --> 00:43:32,115
who you think I am,

504
00:43:32,160 --> 00:43:34,754
but I have spent
some years in the army.

505
00:43:34,796 --> 00:43:37,924
Perhaps we met
on some campaign or other.

506
00:43:37,966 --> 00:43:40,594
Perhaps that's why
I seem familiar.

507
00:43:40,635 --> 00:43:42,330
Perhaps.

508
00:43:45,306 --> 00:43:47,206
I recall the 13th...

509
00:43:48,810 --> 00:43:51,005
- was at Alesia.
- We were.

510
00:43:51,045 --> 00:43:55,106
There's a battle I've always
wished to have seen.

511
00:43:55,149 --> 00:43:57,447
25 miles of works,
wasn't it?

512
00:43:57,485 --> 00:43:59,953
- Nearer 30.
- 30?

513
00:43:59,988 --> 00:44:02,115
- How many men did you have?
- 60,000.

514
00:44:02,156 --> 00:44:04,556
Against...
whoa...

515
00:44:04,592 --> 00:44:07,584
almost double
the Gauls.

516
00:44:07,628 --> 00:44:08,754
At least double.

517
00:44:08,796 --> 00:44:11,162
The best men
of every tribe in Gaul.

518
00:44:11,199 --> 00:44:13,167
Ah.

519
00:44:13,201 --> 00:44:15,169
Caesar can fight.

520
00:44:15,203 --> 00:44:16,830
I'll give him that.

521
00:44:16,871 --> 00:44:18,839
I remember...

522
00:44:18,873 --> 00:44:20,841
when he was
not much older than you.

523
00:44:20,875 --> 00:44:23,366
I sent him
to winter Quarters in...

524
00:44:23,411 --> 00:44:25,743
in, uh...

525
00:44:25,780 --> 00:44:28,772
Oh, where was it?

526
00:44:30,451 --> 00:44:32,749
No matter.

527
00:44:32,787 --> 00:44:34,778
Long time gone.

528
00:44:41,896 --> 00:44:44,228
I must ask you, sir,
if I may.

529
00:44:45,800 --> 00:44:48,200
How did you
come to this road?

530
00:44:49,303 --> 00:44:51,271
Surely...

531
00:44:51,305 --> 00:44:53,773
Pompey had Caesar
at greater disadvantage.

532
00:44:53,808 --> 00:44:57,778
He did.

533
00:44:57,812 --> 00:44:59,803
It didn't seem
possible to lose.

534
00:45:01,416 --> 00:45:03,407
That's always a bad sign.

535
00:45:04,752 --> 00:45:08,552
The battlefield
was on a plain

536
00:45:08,589 --> 00:45:10,716
by a river,
at the foot of some...

537
00:45:12,260 --> 00:45:14,228
low hills.

538
00:45:14,262 --> 00:45:16,230
Like this, you see.

539
00:45:16,264 --> 00:45:18,892
The lines met here.

540
00:45:18,933 --> 00:45:22,733
My men held
their ground well,

541
00:45:22,770 --> 00:45:24,863
so I sent my horses

542
00:45:24,906 --> 00:45:26,874
at his right flank.

543
00:45:26,908 --> 00:45:29,433
Which is
perfectly correct,

544
00:45:29,477 --> 00:45:31,069
- you'll agree.
- I do.

545
00:45:31,112 --> 00:45:34,570
Only the cowards
were repulsed.

546
00:45:34,615 --> 00:45:38,073
Repulsed by a single cohort
of reserves.

547
00:45:38,119 --> 00:45:41,088
Turned and fled,
200 horses.

548
00:45:41,122 --> 00:45:44,250
Crashed directly
into my left flank.

549
00:45:44,292 --> 00:45:47,420
Rolled up my line

550
00:45:47,462 --> 00:45:49,430
like a carpet.

551
00:45:49,464 --> 00:45:52,627
Put the whole
damned army to flight.

552
00:45:54,135 --> 00:45:56,103
And here I am.

553
00:45:56,137 --> 00:45:58,105
That's how Pompey Magnus

554
00:45:58,139 --> 00:46:01,199
was defeated.

555
00:46:01,242 --> 00:46:04,006
That's how
the Republic died.

556
00:46:16,591 --> 00:46:18,752
- Good night, sir.
- Wait.

557
00:46:19,927 --> 00:46:21,918
I will not...

558
00:46:24,265 --> 00:46:26,233
I will not ask favor

559
00:46:26,267 --> 00:46:28,235
or mercy for myself.

560
00:46:28,269 --> 00:46:30,260
But I beg you...

561
00:46:31,439 --> 00:46:33,430
consider the fate...

562
00:46:34,642 --> 00:46:36,633
of my wife
and children.

563
00:46:39,780 --> 00:46:42,248
Let me
take them to Egypt

564
00:46:42,283 --> 00:46:44,649
where they
will be safe...

565
00:46:46,654 --> 00:46:48,645
among friends.

566
00:46:51,459 --> 00:46:53,450
Consider them.

567
00:48:04,398 --> 00:48:06,389
Go back to sleep.

568
00:48:20,748 --> 00:48:24,206
Unwise and unfriendly,
I call it.

569
00:48:24,252 --> 00:48:26,220
Unwise and unfriendly.

570
00:48:26,254 --> 00:48:28,222
And for why?

571
00:48:28,256 --> 00:48:30,224
Why?

572
00:48:30,258 --> 00:48:32,249
We had him.
We had him.

573
00:48:33,928 --> 00:48:36,396
Horses.
Never mind, horses.

574
00:48:36,430 --> 00:48:38,398
Never mind gold.

575
00:48:38,432 --> 00:48:41,060
Caesar would have
given us farms

576
00:48:41,102 --> 00:48:44,401
and fields and orchards
and great flocks of slaves

577
00:48:44,438 --> 00:48:46,406
and cattle
and Dis knows what...

578
00:48:46,440 --> 00:48:50,433
'Sist! Pompey Magnus is no
damn slave to be sold for money.

579
00:48:53,781 --> 00:48:56,614
- Don't see why not!
- There's a great deal you don't see.

580
00:48:57,818 --> 00:49:00,252
There's a great deal
he doesn't see neither.

581
00:49:12,233 --> 00:49:16,226
You and only 12 other men
survived that storm.

582
00:49:17,238 --> 00:49:19,570
Out of 5,000.

583
00:49:19,607 --> 00:49:21,575
You're being kept alive

584
00:49:21,609 --> 00:49:25,136
- for some great purpose, no doubt.
- Ah, well.

585
00:49:25,179 --> 00:49:27,170
You know, sir...

586
00:49:31,085 --> 00:49:33,986
- He has some interesting news.
- Indeed?

587
00:49:34,021 --> 00:49:35,989
Sir, in course
of our journey here,

588
00:49:36,023 --> 00:49:38,548
we encountered
Gnaeus Pompey Magnus with his family

589
00:49:38,592 --> 00:49:41,561
- and a party of servants.
- Where?

590
00:49:41,595 --> 00:49:43,529
On the road to Amphipoli,
with a mule train.

591
00:49:43,564 --> 00:49:46,897
A mule train.
It's priceless.

592
00:49:46,934 --> 00:49:49,232
He intends to take ship
for Egypt, sir.

593
00:49:49,270 --> 00:49:51,636
Family and servants,
you say.

594
00:49:51,672 --> 00:49:53,640
- No soldiers?
- None, sir.

595
00:49:53,674 --> 00:49:55,471
Not one man left,
not one.

596
00:49:55,509 --> 00:49:57,340
Oh, poor wretch.

597
00:49:59,447 --> 00:50:01,108
Why then,
be that so,

598
00:50:01,148 --> 00:50:03,776
- did you not apprehend him?
- Now here's the onion.

599
00:50:05,786 --> 00:50:09,244
I thought it would be
wrong to do so.

600
00:50:09,290 --> 00:50:11,121
Explain yourself.

601
00:50:12,960 --> 00:50:14,928
His hands trembled, sir.

602
00:50:14,962 --> 00:50:16,361
His clothes were dirty,

603
00:50:16,397 --> 00:50:20,094
there was water in his eyes...
he is broken.

604
00:50:20,134 --> 00:50:22,102
I saw no need
to apprehend him.

605
00:50:22,136 --> 00:50:24,104
I'd like to add
that Legionary Pullo

606
00:50:24,138 --> 00:50:26,003
took no part
in my decision, sir.

607
00:50:27,975 --> 00:50:29,966
You saw no need.

608
00:50:31,479 --> 00:50:33,276
Do you not see
that Pompey may be broken

609
00:50:33,314 --> 00:50:37,045
like a Dacian catamite
and still be dangerous?

610
00:50:37,084 --> 00:50:38,711
If he is still living,

611
00:50:38,753 --> 00:50:40,880
he will be a standard
around which

612
00:50:40,921 --> 00:50:43,651
our enemies will gather!

613
00:50:43,691 --> 00:50:45,989
As long as he can be
propped on a horse,

614
00:50:46,026 --> 00:50:47,994
he's dangerous!

615
00:50:48,028 --> 00:50:51,054
- But you saw no need to apprehend him?
- I did not, sir.

616
00:50:51,098 --> 00:50:54,226
Who by the sons of Dis gives you
the right to make such judgment?

617
00:50:54,268 --> 00:50:56,236
Sir, I am aware that
I have not done my duty,

618
00:50:56,270 --> 00:50:58,738
and I respectfully ask
your pardon.

619
00:51:00,307 --> 00:51:02,468
My pardon, he asks.

620
00:51:04,612 --> 00:51:07,604
I ought to have you
scourged and crucified.

621
00:51:16,123 --> 00:51:18,921
In future you will remember
that it is I

622
00:51:18,959 --> 00:51:21,553
that offers mercy.
No one else.

623
00:51:21,595 --> 00:51:22,721
Clear?

624
00:51:22,763 --> 00:51:25,596
Clear, sir.

625
00:51:25,633 --> 00:51:28,329
Dismissed.

626
00:51:31,739 --> 00:51:33,730
I do not like
to disagree with you,

627
00:51:33,774 --> 00:51:37,141
but you are being
far too lenient with him.

628
00:51:37,178 --> 00:51:40,807
He let Pompey go
and you let him live?!

629
00:51:40,848 --> 00:51:43,112
The man should be made
an example of!

630
00:51:43,150 --> 00:51:45,778
Any other man,
certainly.

631
00:51:45,820 --> 00:51:48,118
But those two...

632
00:51:48,155 --> 00:51:50,123
they found
my stolen standard.

633
00:51:50,157 --> 00:51:51,988
Now they survive a wreck

634
00:51:52,026 --> 00:51:56,019
that drowned an army and find
Pompey Magnus on a beach.

635
00:51:57,665 --> 00:52:01,123
They have powerful gods
on their side,

636
00:52:01,168 --> 00:52:05,161
and I will not kill any man with
friends of that sort.

637
00:52:06,874 --> 00:52:08,171
Posca.

638
00:52:08,209 --> 00:52:11,838
Tell Fulvio to start
breaking camp.

639
00:52:11,879 --> 00:52:13,870
We're going to Egypt.

640
00:53:04,632 --> 00:53:06,600
General Pompey, sir.

641
00:53:06,634 --> 00:53:09,694
Remember me? Lucius Septimius.

642
00:53:09,737 --> 00:53:12,706
Centurion Septimius,
as was.

643
00:53:12,740 --> 00:53:14,537
I was with you in Spain.

644
00:53:14,575 --> 00:53:16,202
Fourth legion,
third cohort.

645
00:53:16,243 --> 00:53:19,212
Lucius Septimius,
of course.

646
00:53:19,246 --> 00:53:21,214
What are you doing here,
of all places?

647
00:53:21,248 --> 00:53:23,307
- Working for the Gyppoes, sir.
- Huh?

648
00:53:23,350 --> 00:53:25,978
I know, sir. It's not
the fourth by no means.

649
00:53:26,020 --> 00:53:28,580
- A man's got to earn his salt, eh?
- True enough.

650
00:53:28,622 --> 00:53:31,352
What's all this then,
soldier?

651
00:53:31,392 --> 00:53:33,360
Not much of a welcome party.

652
00:53:33,394 --> 00:53:37,694
Oh, you know Egyptians, sir,
it's just their way. Funny people.

653
00:53:37,731 --> 00:53:39,756
That they are.
Well...

654
00:53:39,800 --> 00:53:41,700
onward friend.

655
00:53:55,649 --> 00:53:57,583
I'm sorry, sir.

