1
00:01:58,552 --> 00:02:03,455
"My dear friend Gaius,

2
00:02:03,490 --> 00:02:05,754
how are we come

3
00:02:05,792 --> 00:02:08,659
to this absurd position?

4
00:02:09,696 --> 00:02:15,134
In the interests
of peace and equity,

5
00:02:15,168 --> 00:02:18,467
- I accept..."
- The Senate and People of Rome

6
00:02:18,505 --> 00:02:21,497
have authorized me
to accept.

7
00:02:21,541 --> 00:02:24,203
"...the Senate
and People of Rome

8
00:02:24,244 --> 00:02:27,077
have authorized me
to accept a truce..."

9
00:02:27,113 --> 00:02:28,774
No, not truce.
That would imply

10
00:02:28,815 --> 00:02:31,409
that he is a sovereign
rather than a criminal entity.

11
00:02:31,451 --> 00:02:34,386
Quite right.
A criminal.

12
00:02:34,421 --> 00:02:37,549
"...have authorized
me to accept

13
00:02:37,591 --> 00:02:40,754
a cessation of hostilities...

14
00:02:40,794 --> 00:02:45,493
on the terms offered
in your last letter.

15
00:02:45,532 --> 00:02:47,762
I await your answer."

16
00:02:47,801 --> 00:02:49,860
- Good enough.
- Good enough?

17
00:02:49,903 --> 00:02:52,895
This abject humiliation
is good enough?

18
00:02:52,939 --> 00:02:55,737
We are not men.
We are worms.

19
00:02:55,775 --> 00:02:57,766
Worms is harsh.

20
00:02:57,811 --> 00:03:01,440
Worms cannot run away
as speedily as we do.

21
00:03:01,481 --> 00:03:04,041
Caesar has not
even left Rome,

22
00:03:04,084 --> 00:03:05,881
Gods know why not,

23
00:03:05,919 --> 00:03:08,820
yet his legions
chase us

24
00:03:08,855 --> 00:03:11,790
from town to town
with great ease.

25
00:03:11,825 --> 00:03:14,555
We're more like sheep
than worms.

26
00:03:14,594 --> 00:03:17,722
If our levies had not failed,
if we had money to pay troops...

27
00:03:17,764 --> 00:03:20,426
Yes, but they have
and we don't.

28
00:03:20,467 --> 00:03:23,129
Let us cleave to the matter at hand.
Pompey, you must give

29
00:03:23,169 --> 00:03:25,637
some notion of when you will agree
to meet him in person.

30
00:03:25,672 --> 00:03:28,140
- Never.
- There is no reason for them to meet.

31
00:03:28,174 --> 00:03:30,108
The dispute is between
Caesar and the Senate.

32
00:03:30,143 --> 00:03:33,237
- It is the proper form.
- I'll not meet the man.

33
00:03:33,280 --> 00:03:36,374
Never. Like a son,
he was to me.

34
00:03:36,416 --> 00:03:38,577
What he was like
to you is immaterial.

35
00:03:38,618 --> 00:03:40,779
It is only
by Jupiter's mercy

36
00:03:40,820 --> 00:03:43,789
that he has not already
put our heads on pikes.

37
00:03:43,823 --> 00:03:46,815
Mercy? Jupiter has
no mercy for cowards.

38
00:03:46,860 --> 00:03:50,125
- Cato, be careful.
- You'll accept abject surrender...

39
00:03:50,163 --> 00:03:52,358
This is not surrender!

40
00:03:53,900 --> 00:03:57,097
Pompey Magnus
does not surrender.

41
00:04:00,440 --> 00:04:02,908
I need time.

42
00:04:02,943 --> 00:04:05,707
A truce gains us
that time.

43
00:04:22,195 --> 00:04:25,062
Verrus Horta sends
three jars of amber

44
00:04:25,098 --> 00:04:27,760
and informs us he has
left the standard of Pompey.

45
00:04:27,801 --> 00:04:30,827
He entrusts his living
to your abundant mercy.

46
00:04:30,870 --> 00:04:34,101
- Horta?
- Pederast, waxy skin, red hair,

47
00:04:34,140 --> 00:04:36,768
- estates in Tusculum.
- I have him, the wretch.

48
00:04:36,810 --> 00:04:39,836
Send a small bag of money
with a fulsome letter

49
00:04:39,879 --> 00:04:41,676
and make him
a Quaestor or something.

50
00:04:41,715 --> 00:04:44,377
Show such mercy
to every man that deserts Pompey,

51
00:04:44,417 --> 00:04:47,386
you will pauperize yourself.
There's dozens of them coming every day.

52
00:04:47,420 --> 00:04:50,617
Judicious use of mercy
is worth 10,000 men.

53
00:04:50,657 --> 00:04:54,093
And if my last coin buys
me a throne, it's a fair price.

54
00:04:54,127 --> 00:04:56,857
- A throne?
- Poetic license. What else?

55
00:04:56,896 --> 00:04:58,796
Atia invites you
to dinner tonight.

56
00:04:58,832 --> 00:05:00,857
Again? Bona Dea.

57
00:05:02,635 --> 00:05:05,900
- Not tonight in any case.
- What excuse shall I give?

58
00:05:05,939 --> 00:05:07,634
- None.
- This is the second time

59
00:05:07,674 --> 00:05:09,369
you have refused
an invitation from her.

60
00:05:09,409 --> 00:05:11,536
I need not account
for myself to Atia.

61
00:05:11,578 --> 00:05:15,776
As you say. Not a sapient choice,
perhaps; but brave, sure.

62
00:05:15,815 --> 00:05:19,148
They say slaves talk of bravery
as fish talk of flying.

63
00:05:19,185 --> 00:05:21,813
They say that, do they?
How very witty of them.

64
00:05:23,423 --> 00:05:26,483
"Seeking only justice
and peace

65
00:05:26,526 --> 00:05:30,656
and to avoid the unnecessary
shedding of Roman blood,

66
00:05:30,697 --> 00:05:34,793
Gaius Julius Caesar
has publicly implored

67
00:05:34,834 --> 00:05:37,359
the renegade
Gnaius Pompey Magnus

68
00:05:37,404 --> 00:05:40,771
to accept truce
and lay down his arms."

69
00:05:43,143 --> 00:05:45,373
What are you doing?

70
00:05:45,412 --> 00:05:48,404
It's rather fun, and there's
quite an art to it.

71
00:05:48,448 --> 00:05:49,972
Strange boy.

72
00:05:52,552 --> 00:05:54,315
I have just heard
a very strange tale

73
00:05:54,354 --> 00:05:56,185
about you
from the kitchen staff.

74
00:05:56,222 --> 00:05:57,883
For what possible reason
I wonder,

75
00:05:57,924 --> 00:06:00,552
would you and Caesar
be skulking about in a cupboard?

76
00:06:00,593 --> 00:06:03,460
What? We were...
it was nothing.

77
00:06:03,496 --> 00:06:05,657
Nothing? It doesn't
sound like nothing.

78
00:06:05,698 --> 00:06:08,531
You seduced him,
you sly little fox.

79
00:06:08,568 --> 00:06:10,729
- I did not.
- I am not clear it is decent,

80
00:06:10,770 --> 00:06:13,136
him being your great uncle,
but who's to say what's

81
00:06:13,173 --> 00:06:17,075
decent in times like these?
In any case, well done.

82
00:06:17,110 --> 00:06:20,773
Let's see Servilia compete
with a soft young boy like you.

83
00:06:20,814 --> 00:06:24,113
- What power we shall wield.
- You have it wrong.

84
00:06:24,150 --> 00:06:26,641
A good lover
is a discreet lover.

85
00:06:26,686 --> 00:06:29,416
He was taken ill. I was helping him
to recover, that's all.

86
00:06:29,456 --> 00:06:32,448
Of course he was, my dove. Now in the
future you must not appear too eager.

87
00:06:32,492 --> 00:06:34,551
A man likes it if you
play hard to get.

88
00:06:34,594 --> 00:06:37,256
- Why don't you leave him alone, mother?
- Now, I have invited

89
00:06:37,297 --> 00:06:39,356
Caesar and Mark Antony
for dinner tonight.

90
00:06:39,399 --> 00:06:40,866
We'll be sure you look especially
handsome...

91
00:06:40,900 --> 00:06:42,265
I am not his lover!

92
00:06:42,302 --> 00:06:44,270
Do not lie to me.

93
00:06:44,304 --> 00:06:46,829
- You know I detest it.
- I am not lying.

94
00:06:46,873 --> 00:06:49,000
He has an affliction.
A terrible affliction.

95
00:06:49,042 --> 00:06:51,237
Affliction? What affliction?
By whom?

96
00:06:52,679 --> 00:06:54,806
I... I will speak no more
of it. I swore an oath.

97
00:06:54,848 --> 00:06:56,748
Oath be damned!
I am your mother. Tell me.

98
00:06:56,783 --> 00:06:58,808
Excuse me.
I will not.

99
00:07:04,124 --> 00:07:06,820
Well, that's
very disappointing.

100
00:07:12,999 --> 00:07:16,230
Caesar sends to say
he cannot come this evening.

101
00:07:16,269 --> 00:07:17,964
No matter.

102
00:07:19,172 --> 00:07:22,630
- Why not?
- He doesn't say.

103
00:07:41,728 --> 00:07:44,663
Titus Pullo is sleeping
on the stairs again.

104
00:07:44,697 --> 00:07:48,394
- Has he nowhere else to go?
- He won't be in Rome much longer.

105
00:07:48,434 --> 00:07:53,098
Tell me, when is the youth
returning? Your husband.

106
00:07:53,139 --> 00:07:56,040
- Crito.
- When does he return from his droving?

107
00:07:56,075 --> 00:07:58,839
- November. Why?
- I'm selling my slaves today.

108
00:07:58,878 --> 00:08:00,903
There'll be money enough
spare for your dowry.

109
00:08:00,947 --> 00:08:03,677
So when Crito comes home,
you and Lucius can go to him

110
00:08:03,716 --> 00:08:06,378
- and start your married life proper.
- Thank you, Father!

111
00:08:06,419 --> 00:08:08,046
- Thank you.
- We'll be sorry to see you go.

112
00:08:08,087 --> 00:08:09,884
November?
It's so soon.

113
00:08:09,923 --> 00:08:12,391
- They have to go at some time.
- Of course, of course,

114
00:08:12,425 --> 00:08:15,019
- but November.
- It's hard, but it has to be done.

115
00:08:15,061 --> 00:08:17,621
They'll be so far away.
You know how these drovers live.

116
00:08:17,664 --> 00:08:20,030
But Mama, I want to go.
I want to be with my husband.

117
00:08:20,066 --> 00:08:21,727
I know. I know.
Of course.

118
00:08:21,768 --> 00:08:23,633
You must go.

119
00:08:23,670 --> 00:08:25,467
It's just hard.

120
00:08:27,907 --> 00:08:30,000
Morning.

121
00:08:30,043 --> 00:08:31,943
Trouble you
for some water?

122
00:08:31,978 --> 00:08:33,741
Sit down.

123
00:08:35,582 --> 00:08:38,745
- You should be in camp.
- Nothing to do there.

124
00:08:38,785 --> 00:08:41,720
- It's boring.
- Take some bread.

125
00:08:41,754 --> 00:08:43,847
I'll not, thanks.

126
00:08:43,890 --> 00:08:46,188
I'm not feeling too well.

127
00:08:46,226 --> 00:08:49,195
You're drinking too much.

128
00:08:49,229 --> 00:08:51,254
No, it's not that.

129
00:08:51,297 --> 00:08:54,824
I ate some
depraved oysters.

130
00:08:54,867 --> 00:08:57,392
- Where's your girl?
- Girl?

131
00:09:00,607 --> 00:09:02,370
Cac!

132
00:09:08,014 --> 00:09:10,505
I know it's one of these.
I know it!

133
00:09:10,550 --> 00:09:12,040
Stop worrying.

134
00:09:12,085 --> 00:09:14,212
Even if we can't find her,
you can get another.

135
00:09:15,255 --> 00:09:18,315
I don't want another.
I want Eirene.

136
00:09:18,358 --> 00:09:20,053
You'll be off south after Pompey
before long.

137
00:09:20,093 --> 00:09:21,617
You can't take her
soldiering.

138
00:09:21,661 --> 00:09:23,720
Maybe I won't
go back to camp.

139
00:09:23,763 --> 00:09:25,731
My time is
nearly done anyway.

140
00:09:25,765 --> 00:09:27,460
Leave the 13th? Why?

141
00:09:29,102 --> 00:09:31,400
- You did.
- You are not me.

142
00:09:31,437 --> 00:09:33,166
You have no talent
for peace.

143
00:09:33,206 --> 00:09:35,401
I can't just leave her.

144
00:09:35,441 --> 00:09:38,672
- You think with your penis.
- It's not like that.

145
00:09:38,711 --> 00:09:41,145
- I've not touched her.
- Then what purpose does she serve?

146
00:09:41,180 --> 00:09:44,638
I just like to look at her.
Makes me calm.

147
00:09:47,987 --> 00:09:50,217
Here she is.

148
00:09:51,224 --> 00:09:53,055
Thank you, Apollo.

149
00:09:54,394 --> 00:09:55,986
The girl is his.

150
00:09:57,563 --> 00:10:00,225
No trouble.
Pay what's owed,

151
00:10:00,266 --> 00:10:02,530
- and the girl is all yours.
- What's owed?

152
00:10:02,568 --> 00:10:05,696
You should be paying me to drink
the pond filth you serve here.

153
00:10:07,473 --> 00:10:08,701
Pullo!

154
00:10:10,910 --> 00:10:12,502
How much?

155
00:10:15,982 --> 00:10:18,075
I'll pay you back
soon as I can.

156
00:10:18,117 --> 00:10:19,607
Do that.

157
00:10:20,653 --> 00:10:22,644
So what will
you do with her?

158
00:10:28,361 --> 00:10:30,852
- I don't want her.
- Say again?

159
00:10:30,897 --> 00:10:32,990
I don't want her. It's nice of
you to think of it...

160
00:10:33,032 --> 00:10:34,932
But you want a slave.
You keep asking for one,

161
00:10:34,967 --> 00:10:37,959
and here she is. Pullo can't keep her,
and it costs us nothing.

162
00:10:38,004 --> 00:10:39,596
Can't I have one of
your Gaulish slaves?

163
00:10:39,639 --> 00:10:41,266
I've told you,
my Gauls are unseasoned.

164
00:10:41,307 --> 00:10:43,070
Cut your throat as soon
as sweep your floor.

165
00:10:43,109 --> 00:10:44,736
This one's trained up
nice and docile.

166
00:10:44,777 --> 00:10:46,506
What is wrong with her?

167
00:10:49,015 --> 00:10:52,348
- She has strange eyes.
- You drive me insane!

168
00:10:53,553 --> 00:10:55,418
The girl stays.

169
00:11:03,896 --> 00:11:07,297
Keep calm, sweetie.
Keep calm.

170
00:11:07,333 --> 00:11:10,461
How can I be calm when Pullo's
put that little witch to spy on me?

171
00:11:10,503 --> 00:11:12,596
He knows, Rissa,
he knows.

172
00:11:12,638 --> 00:11:14,196
Big simple brute
like that?

173
00:11:14,240 --> 00:11:16,105
If he even
suspected anything,

174
00:11:16,142 --> 00:11:18,667
he'd go straight to Vorenus
and tell him, wouldn't he?

175
00:11:18,711 --> 00:11:20,611
- Course he would.
- You really think?

176
00:11:20,646 --> 00:11:23,012
- He doesn't know nothing.
- Really?

177
00:11:23,049 --> 00:11:26,780
Sure of it. So he saw Evander
round your house.

178
00:11:26,819 --> 00:11:28,684
So what? He's family.
He's allowed.

179
00:11:28,721 --> 00:11:31,986
- That's true.
- You're getting worried over nothing.

180
00:11:33,626 --> 00:11:35,526
Gods, let it be so.

181
00:11:35,661 --> 00:11:38,459
Poor sad wretch gives
everything you asked for.

182
00:11:38,498 --> 00:11:41,058
The Senate
will ratify your status,

183
00:11:41,100 --> 00:11:43,591
you get your triumph,
stand for consul,

184
00:11:43,636 --> 00:11:46,366
and Pompey
shall withdraw to Spain.

185
00:11:46,406 --> 00:11:49,398
He'll suck Posca's cock
if asked nicely.

186
00:11:49,442 --> 00:11:51,842
Too generous by far.
I never thought for an instant

187
00:11:51,878 --> 00:11:54,779
- Pompey would accept such terms.
- You think it's a stratagem?

188
00:11:54,814 --> 00:11:57,214
I doubt it.

189
00:11:57,250 --> 00:11:59,650
He and what few forces
he has are trapped.

190
00:11:59,685 --> 00:12:02,518
He's weak and growing
weaker every day.

191
00:12:02,555 --> 00:12:04,819
We might
crush him at will.

192
00:12:04,857 --> 00:12:07,792
But now that
he has offered truce,

193
00:12:07,827 --> 00:12:11,558
I will look like the
worst kind of tyrant if I attack him.

194
00:12:11,597 --> 00:12:16,034
Posca here thinks
I should accept the truce.

195
00:12:16,068 --> 00:12:17,933
- Make peace.
- In exchange for what?

196
00:12:17,970 --> 00:12:21,235
- Peace is it's own reward.
- Snivelry.

197
00:12:21,274 --> 00:12:24,505
The ram has touched
the wall. No mercy.

198
00:12:24,544 --> 00:12:27,342
Pompey has no great army,
but he has the Senate with him.

199
00:12:27,380 --> 00:12:30,543
- He has legitimacy.
- In Rome they are the Senate.

200
00:12:30,583 --> 00:12:33,074
Beyond the walls
they are just 300 old men.

201
00:12:33,119 --> 00:12:35,644
As you say, Antony,
but others will agree with Posca.

202
00:12:35,688 --> 00:12:37,986
They have made
this shameful surrender public.

203
00:12:38,024 --> 00:12:39,924
It will be read
all over Italy.

204
00:12:39,959 --> 00:12:42,553
If I am not a tyrant,

205
00:12:42,595 --> 00:12:44,358
if I merely seek legitimacy,

206
00:12:44,397 --> 00:12:46,922
why would I not accept
such favorable terms?

207
00:12:48,434 --> 00:12:52,234
He refuses
to meet us...

208
00:12:52,271 --> 00:12:53,966
in person?

209
00:12:58,377 --> 00:13:01,608
Very good. Simple.

210
00:13:01,647 --> 00:13:03,615
Hoi polloi can understand
a reason like that.

211
00:13:03,649 --> 00:13:06,174
He refuses to meet me
face to face.

212
00:13:06,219 --> 00:13:08,187
Man to man.

213
00:13:08,221 --> 00:13:10,553
He refuses to meet me.

214
00:13:10,590 --> 00:13:13,150
Right, that's it.

215
00:13:13,192 --> 00:13:16,218
No truce.
Let's be after them.

216
00:13:16,262 --> 00:13:17,991
Patience.

217
00:13:19,065 --> 00:13:20,692
He's well caught.

218
00:13:22,134 --> 00:13:24,432
We'll leave when
the time is right.

219
00:13:27,206 --> 00:13:28,696
When?

220
00:13:30,042 --> 00:13:32,533
When the time is right.

221
00:13:32,578 --> 00:13:34,773
But we should have
left Rome long ago.

222
00:13:34,814 --> 00:13:36,475
The apple is ripe
for the plucking,

223
00:13:36,516 --> 00:13:39,349
and we just sit here
doing nothing?

224
00:13:40,786 --> 00:13:43,448
Pompey is not an apple

225
00:13:43,489 --> 00:13:46,424
and I am not a farmer.

226
00:13:46,459 --> 00:13:48,393
Call for my guard.

227
00:14:08,381 --> 00:14:10,872
First Spear Centurion
Lucius Vorenus.

228
00:14:10,917 --> 00:14:12,612
I have been looking
for your return.

229
00:14:12,652 --> 00:14:14,279
I'm no longer
in the army, citizen.

230
00:14:14,320 --> 00:14:16,083
I've come
to sell my stock.

231
00:14:16,122 --> 00:14:18,113
Ah, well...

232
00:14:38,010 --> 00:14:41,241
Black blood flux.
Nothing to be done.

233
00:14:41,280 --> 00:14:44,807
- Flux?
- I kept 'em here despite the stink

234
00:14:44,850 --> 00:14:47,284
so you'd know I'd done
you nothing dodgy.

235
00:14:47,320 --> 00:14:49,413
Nobody to blame.

236
00:14:49,455 --> 00:14:52,083
Fortune left you
one at least.

237
00:14:52,124 --> 00:14:56,424
- Auspicious boy that is.
- How much will he fetch?

238
00:14:56,462 --> 00:14:59,226
Oh, a respectable price.

239
00:14:59,265 --> 00:15:02,132
More than enough
to pay the feed bill.

240
00:15:02,168 --> 00:15:05,001
- Feed bill?
- They didn't starve to death.

241
00:15:12,078 --> 00:15:13,807
Move!

242
00:15:22,321 --> 00:15:24,846
- Nothing?
- Not nothing. The boy will fetch

243
00:15:24,890 --> 00:15:26,915
- a good price when he's healthy.
- What's that?

244
00:15:26,959 --> 00:15:29,621
Your father brought him back from
Gaul. What will we do till then?

245
00:15:29,662 --> 00:15:30,788
To keep?

246
00:15:30,830 --> 00:15:32,320
We're selling him as soon
as he gets some color.

247
00:15:32,365 --> 00:15:34,629
- What will we do after that?
- What's his name?

248
00:15:34,667 --> 00:15:36,362
He hasn't got one!

249
00:15:36,402 --> 00:15:38,336
We'll call him Rubio
after my pigeon that died.

250
00:15:38,371 --> 00:15:40,032
We've nothing saved.

251
00:15:40,072 --> 00:15:42,302
Don't worry. I will
think of something.

252
00:16:12,438 --> 00:16:15,168
And again.

253
00:16:15,207 --> 00:16:16,697
This is a rout.

254
00:16:18,244 --> 00:16:21,077
Shall I be merciful?

255
00:16:26,185 --> 00:16:28,415
I think not.

256
00:16:35,528 --> 00:16:37,689
How will you pay
your debt?

257
00:16:41,801 --> 00:16:45,259
All that I have
is already yours.

258
00:16:45,304 --> 00:16:46,737
What else can I give you?

259
00:16:46,772 --> 00:16:48,740
Don't leave me again.

260
00:16:49,742 --> 00:16:51,209
I never left you.

261
00:17:14,366 --> 00:17:17,096
The men are going
mad from boredom.

262
00:17:17,136 --> 00:17:20,572
Just today I had to cut the hands off
a perfectly good Legionary

263
00:17:20,606 --> 00:17:22,631
for murdering a civilian.

264
00:17:22,675 --> 00:17:27,476
Then I had to listen
to a jumped up freedman

265
00:17:27,513 --> 00:17:29,879
raving for hours

266
00:17:29,915 --> 00:17:34,750
about one of my centurions seducing his
daughters.

267
00:17:34,787 --> 00:17:38,985
- It all sounds very tedious.
- It is your uncle's fault.

268
00:17:39,024 --> 00:17:42,289
He should've taken
the legions south after Pompey.

269
00:17:42,328 --> 00:17:46,162
The men know it,
and it makes them restless.

270
00:17:48,734 --> 00:17:50,599
Of course...

271
00:17:52,705 --> 00:17:55,970
he pretends
it is a stratagem.

272
00:17:58,277 --> 00:18:00,837
But every dog in camp

273
00:18:00,880 --> 00:18:03,940
knows that Servilia
has unmanned him.

274
00:18:04,950 --> 00:18:07,316
He will not
be parted from her.

275
00:18:09,054 --> 00:18:11,750
I...

276
00:18:11,791 --> 00:18:14,055
as you can tell,

277
00:18:14,093 --> 00:18:17,119
am not unmanned.

278
00:18:33,546 --> 00:18:35,776
Intolerable.
Intolerable!

279
00:18:35,815 --> 00:18:38,340
Calm yourself, Mother, please.
You've become unbalanced.

280
00:18:38,384 --> 00:18:41,353
Why care so much who
he beds? It is trivium.

281
00:18:41,387 --> 00:18:43,651
How you take after
your father... simple as milk.

282
00:18:43,689 --> 00:18:47,386
If he were not mewling in bed with that
witch he would be chasing down Pompey.

283
00:18:47,426 --> 00:18:50,725
It is not trivium.
The Republic is at stake.

284
00:18:50,763 --> 00:18:53,197
Since when do you care
about the Republic?

285
00:18:53,232 --> 00:18:55,223
I care deeply
about the Republic.

286
00:18:55,267 --> 00:18:57,497
It would be very unwise
to cause trouble about this.

287
00:18:58,504 --> 00:19:01,439
Of course.
I wouldn't lower myself.

288
00:19:03,676 --> 00:19:07,339
Such sordid couplings have
a way of turning out badly anyhow...

289
00:19:07,379 --> 00:19:10,280
by no one's special doing.

290
00:19:10,316 --> 00:19:13,649
- Tutor has arrived.
- Oh good.

291
00:19:15,554 --> 00:19:18,819
Your tutor has arrived
and waits in the rear yard.

292
00:19:18,858 --> 00:19:20,553
Tutor?
What tutor?

293
00:19:20,593 --> 00:19:23,721
It's high time you learned
the masculine arts.

294
00:19:23,762 --> 00:19:27,289
How to fight and copulate
and skin animals and so forth.

295
00:19:27,333 --> 00:19:29,767
There's plenty of time yet
for all that.

296
00:19:29,802 --> 00:19:32,396
Plenty of time for you to bury yourself
in worthless scribbles.

297
00:19:32,438 --> 00:19:34,338
You may read
those old Greek fools

298
00:19:34,373 --> 00:19:37,308
until blood runs from
your eyes, you'll be none the wiser.

299
00:19:37,343 --> 00:19:40,210
I cannot agree. The Greek
philosophers have much to teach us.

300
00:19:40,246 --> 00:19:42,612
Well, here's a Greek
philosopher for you.

301
00:19:44,450 --> 00:19:47,044
I've engaged
that soldier of yours.

302
00:19:47,086 --> 00:19:49,520
- Vorenus?
- Was that it?

303
00:19:49,555 --> 00:19:52,217
Not the sullen Catonian one,
I don't like him.

304
00:19:52,258 --> 00:19:55,352
- The cheerful brutish one.
- Pullo.

305
00:19:55,394 --> 00:19:58,852
That's it. What extraordinary
names these plebs have.

306
00:19:58,898 --> 00:20:01,332
Pullo.

307
00:20:01,367 --> 00:20:04,598
Defend! Shield.

308
00:20:04,637 --> 00:20:06,229
Shield.

309
00:20:06,272 --> 00:20:07,796
Don't wave it about.

310
00:20:10,075 --> 00:20:12,202
Shield.

311
00:20:12,244 --> 00:20:14,212
Enough!

312
00:20:15,915 --> 00:20:18,349
Water.

313
00:20:29,595 --> 00:20:32,223
This is absurd.

314
00:20:33,299 --> 00:20:35,062
I have no soldiery
stuff in me.

315
00:20:35,100 --> 00:20:37,295
And this exertion
brings on a fever.

316
00:20:37,336 --> 00:20:39,634
- I feel it in my spleen.
- You're just not used to it.

317
00:20:39,672 --> 00:20:43,301
It takes time.
I've seen you kill.

318
00:20:43,342 --> 00:20:46,470
- There's plenty of soldier in you.
- It's not the killing.

319
00:20:46,512 --> 00:20:49,072
It's the waving about
of swords I find tedious.

320
00:20:49,114 --> 00:20:50,979
I dare say I can kill
people readily enough,

321
00:20:51,016 --> 00:20:52,643
as long as they're
not fighting back.

322
00:20:52,685 --> 00:20:55,245
Never fear, young Dominus.
We'll make a regular terror of you.

323
00:20:55,287 --> 00:20:57,187
At best I will be
a middling swordsman.

324
00:20:57,222 --> 00:20:59,190
- It's better than nothing.
- There you are wrong.

325
00:20:59,224 --> 00:21:01,749
The graveyards are full
of middling swordsmen.

326
00:21:01,794 --> 00:21:04,729
Best to be no swordsman
at all than a middling swordsman.

327
00:21:07,199 --> 00:21:08,962
Don't do that.

328
00:21:10,002 --> 00:21:11,663
Excuse me.

329
00:21:18,243 --> 00:21:19,608
Young Dominus...

330
00:21:19,645 --> 00:21:22,478
I need your advice
on a delicate matter,

331
00:21:22,514 --> 00:21:24,539
- if you'd be willing?
- I am.

332
00:21:24,583 --> 00:21:27,780
Suppose you saw something
which made you suspect something...

333
00:21:27,820 --> 00:21:29,617
something terrible.

334
00:21:29,655 --> 00:21:31,885
Would you tell the husband
of the suspicious article?

335
00:21:31,924 --> 00:21:34,449
Suppose suspicion of what?

336
00:21:36,662 --> 00:21:39,153
- Another man.
- Ah.

337
00:21:39,198 --> 00:21:41,393
We are speaking of Vorenus
and his wife, I presume.

338
00:21:41,433 --> 00:21:43,424
I never said that.

339
00:21:45,404 --> 00:21:48,999
It seems to me that suspicion alone
is not enough to speak.

340
00:21:49,041 --> 00:21:52,204
Once spoken out, the suspicion
of such depravity

341
00:21:52,244 --> 00:21:54,678
is real enough to do
the work of truth.

342
00:21:54,713 --> 00:21:56,840
And what if
you are mistaken?

343
00:21:56,882 --> 00:21:59,851
Then Vorenus is
dishonored by error.

344
00:21:59,885 --> 00:22:03,082
Facts are necessary.
Without facts, you must remain silent.

345
00:22:05,057 --> 00:22:07,548
I knew you'd hit
the jugular.

346
00:22:31,417 --> 00:22:33,248
Refuses truce.

347
00:22:33,285 --> 00:22:35,412
What now?

348
00:22:36,488 --> 00:22:38,080
What now?

349
00:22:41,427 --> 00:22:43,554
How happy, eh?

350
00:22:43,595 --> 00:22:45,859
To be a slave.

351
00:22:46,899 --> 00:22:48,696
To have no will.

352
00:22:48,734 --> 00:22:50,634
To make no decisions.

353
00:22:50,669 --> 00:22:52,864
Driftwood.

354
00:22:52,905 --> 00:22:55,874
How very restful
it must be.

355
00:23:08,020 --> 00:23:11,114
- Erastes Fulmen.
- Centurion.

356
00:23:14,526 --> 00:23:16,585
I have come
to seek your counsel.

357
00:23:16,628 --> 00:23:18,858
Always happy
to help a friend.

358
00:23:18,897 --> 00:23:20,728
I need to borrow
some money

359
00:23:20,766 --> 00:23:23,257
and I am told you have
friends in the lending trade.

360
00:23:23,302 --> 00:23:25,395
I do.

361
00:23:25,437 --> 00:23:29,168
I do. I only hesitate
because I'm surprised.

362
00:23:29,208 --> 00:23:31,472
You was well found.

363
00:23:31,510 --> 00:23:34,911
My slaves were taken
by the black flux.

364
00:23:34,947 --> 00:23:38,007
But once I raise capital,
I'll go up North and buy some more.

365
00:23:38,050 --> 00:23:39,950
I have good contacts
in Narbo.

366
00:23:39,985 --> 00:23:42,180
- Be needing a big chunk then?
- I will.

367
00:23:44,823 --> 00:23:46,313
I cannot.

368
00:23:46,358 --> 00:23:49,521
Wrong to lead a citizen
like yourself down that path.

369
00:23:51,130 --> 00:23:53,064
Rough business,
moneylending.

370
00:23:53,098 --> 00:23:55,362
Man can't pay,
he may have to suffer.

371
00:23:55,400 --> 00:23:57,527
Was I to introduce you
to a lender,

372
00:23:57,569 --> 00:24:01,130
I would be putting
two wolves into one cage.

373
00:24:01,173 --> 00:24:03,198
To neither's benefit.

374
00:24:04,243 --> 00:24:06,609
You're right.
You're right.

375
00:24:06,645 --> 00:24:07,976
Thank you for your time.

376
00:24:08,013 --> 00:24:10,777
Centurion, there are other
ways to make money.

377
00:24:10,816 --> 00:24:13,216
Man like you,
there's situations

378
00:24:13,252 --> 00:24:15,015
his simple presence
would be valuable.

379
00:24:15,053 --> 00:24:17,578
- A man like me.
- A hard man.

380
00:24:17,623 --> 00:24:20,649
First Spear Centurion
in Caesar's mighty 13th.

381
00:24:20,692 --> 00:24:22,626
- I'm no longer in the army.
- No matter.

382
00:24:22,661 --> 00:24:24,629
Your bearing is enough.

383
00:24:26,231 --> 00:24:29,325
You would lend dignity and
strength to business transactions.

384
00:24:29,368 --> 00:24:31,598
If you like,
I could use you myself.

385
00:24:31,637 --> 00:24:33,571
Show you the onions.

386
00:24:33,605 --> 00:24:35,903
That's good of you,

387
00:24:35,941 --> 00:24:38,239
but I still don't see
what I would do exactly.

388
00:24:40,212 --> 00:24:44,171
You would come with me
to discourage trouble.

389
00:24:44,216 --> 00:24:47,617
No one's going to mess with
a First Spear Centurion.

390
00:24:47,653 --> 00:24:50,121
I'd be a bodyguard.

391
00:24:55,460 --> 00:24:57,451
Good money.

392
00:24:59,631 --> 00:25:01,189
I told you!
I told you!

393
00:25:01,233 --> 00:25:03,895
I'm sorry, I couldn't
help it. I can't...

394
00:25:03,936 --> 00:25:06,734
Damn you! Damn her!
I am your wife.

395
00:25:06,772 --> 00:25:09,366
Me. I am your wife.

396
00:25:09,408 --> 00:25:11,239
Lyde!

397
00:25:31,463 --> 00:25:33,693
That's lovely.

398
00:25:33,732 --> 00:25:35,927
It's not too army-like?

399
00:25:35,968 --> 00:25:37,936
Like a man
of deep business.

400
00:25:37,970 --> 00:25:40,131
I'm no business man.
I'm just a bodyguard.

401
00:25:41,607 --> 00:25:43,097
It's a start.

402
00:25:59,725 --> 00:26:02,489
Please please,
just for me.

403
00:26:15,841 --> 00:26:18,002
What is the matter
with everybody?

404
00:26:22,748 --> 00:26:26,047
Lock him up, girls!
Lock him up!

405
00:26:26,084 --> 00:26:28,075
Ohh! Oy, Calpurnia!

406
00:26:28,120 --> 00:26:29,678
Ooh, yes!

407
00:26:40,165 --> 00:26:42,895
- Calpurnia...
- Do not trouble yourself with denial.

408
00:26:42,934 --> 00:26:45,459
- I did not intend to.
- Be rid of her and we'll say no more.

409
00:26:45,504 --> 00:26:48,200
- Let us not...
- Or divorce will follow.

410
00:26:49,474 --> 00:26:51,669
Perhaps that is not
enough to deter you.

411
00:26:51,710 --> 00:26:54,474
Be that as it may,
I am indifferent.

412
00:26:57,749 --> 00:26:59,717
We cannot divorce now.

413
00:26:59,751 --> 00:27:01,480
Her family's influence will be critical...

414
00:27:01,520 --> 00:27:03,215
I know it.

415
00:27:03,255 --> 00:27:06,190
Bring me out
the smaller scales.

416
00:27:06,224 --> 00:27:09,819
- Centurion, you're right on time.
- Citizen.

417
00:27:11,430 --> 00:27:13,421
Why do we not meet
in the Forum?

418
00:27:13,465 --> 00:27:16,593
Forum's only for closing deals,
putting a hand on it public-like.

419
00:27:24,209 --> 00:27:26,336
Enough of that
Teuton droning!

420
00:27:26,378 --> 00:27:28,608
If you want to whistle
like someone's bum boy,

421
00:27:28,647 --> 00:27:30,638
whistle a good Roman
song at least.

422
00:27:33,385 --> 00:27:35,512
And she complained
I was like an elephant.

423
00:27:35,554 --> 00:27:38,182
Tanjit, my honey duck,

424
00:27:38,223 --> 00:27:40,657
- you're looking well.
- Erastes Fulmen.

425
00:27:40,692 --> 00:27:43,058
I kiss your mother's feet.

426
00:27:43,095 --> 00:27:45,427
Please, sit.

427
00:27:45,464 --> 00:27:48,126
Would you like
something to eat, drink?

428
00:27:48,166 --> 00:27:51,829
- Wine will do.
- We do not have wine. Milk, perhaps?

429
00:27:51,870 --> 00:27:54,134
Milk?!
Run out of piss, did you?

430
00:27:55,941 --> 00:27:58,967
Humor.
Very good.

431
00:27:59,010 --> 00:28:01,171
I'm sad to have
to come here, Tanjit.

432
00:28:01,213 --> 00:28:03,443
I'm very depressed.

433
00:28:03,482 --> 00:28:05,245
I thought we were
businessmen.

434
00:28:05,283 --> 00:28:07,581
I thought we understood each other,
yet here we are.

435
00:28:07,619 --> 00:28:09,985
Here we are.

436
00:28:10,021 --> 00:28:12,615
I'm only going
to ask once.

437
00:28:12,657 --> 00:28:14,557
Where's my money?

438
00:28:14,593 --> 00:28:16,060
Where's my truffle pigs?

439
00:28:16,094 --> 00:28:18,119
50 pigs you have
as ordered.

440
00:28:18,163 --> 00:28:20,791
50 diseased
and scrofulous pigs.

441
00:28:20,832 --> 00:28:23,665
- And one knows how to find truffles.
- Tricky beasts.

442
00:28:23,702 --> 00:28:25,966
Haven't been eating
acorns, have they?

443
00:28:26,004 --> 00:28:28,029
Fucks them for truffling,
too much acorns.

444
00:28:28,073 --> 00:28:30,735
I will give you one quarter price.
Out of friendship.

445
00:28:30,776 --> 00:28:33,677
You'll give me
every mumping denarius

446
00:28:33,712 --> 00:28:35,942
- you cac-faced cunny!
- Really,

447
00:28:35,981 --> 00:28:37,972
there is no call
for rudeness.

448
00:28:38,016 --> 00:28:40,450
I'm told Hindus live on
after death. Is that true?

449
00:28:40,485 --> 00:28:43,352
Our bodies die
and decay as yours will.

450
00:28:43,388 --> 00:28:45,481
But our souls
live on eternally.

451
00:28:45,524 --> 00:28:47,515
Well, that's nice
arrangements.

452
00:28:47,559 --> 00:28:50,119
- You're not afraid to die then?
- Not at all.

453
00:29:01,873 --> 00:29:03,898
Break his arm.

454
00:29:05,677 --> 00:29:07,668
Break his arm.

455
00:29:31,703 --> 00:29:35,139
Give me my money,
you monkey's cunt.

456
00:29:35,173 --> 00:29:37,198
Kiss my ass.

457
00:29:38,343 --> 00:29:40,243
Cut his throat.

458
00:29:46,318 --> 00:29:48,309
Cut it!

459
00:30:11,276 --> 00:30:13,437
What are you doing?

460
00:30:28,560 --> 00:30:31,188
What happened?

461
00:30:31,229 --> 00:30:33,220
What's wrong?
Tell me.

462
00:30:35,166 --> 00:30:37,930
Erastes Fulmen asked me
to kill a man.

463
00:30:38,937 --> 00:30:41,064
You refused him?

464
00:30:42,207 --> 00:30:44,266
What else was I to do?

465
00:30:44,309 --> 00:30:46,300
- I am no bandit.
- Of course you're not.

466
00:30:46,344 --> 00:30:48,175
You couldn't do
other than you did.

467
00:30:48,213 --> 00:30:50,738
But how are we
to pay the rent?

468
00:30:50,782 --> 00:30:52,477
How are we
to feed the children?

469
00:31:02,994 --> 00:31:04,655
He's here!

470
00:31:05,830 --> 00:31:08,890
I'm so glad!
I thought you might not...

471
00:31:08,934 --> 00:31:10,561
I regret
I cannot stay.

472
00:31:12,304 --> 00:31:14,295
I've come
to say goodbye.

473
00:31:16,141 --> 00:31:17,472
Goodbye?

474
00:31:17,509 --> 00:31:20,239
I'm going south
in pursuit of Pompey,

475
00:31:20,278 --> 00:31:22,269
and we shall not
see each other again.

476
00:31:24,182 --> 00:31:26,616
- What, never?
- Never.

477
00:31:28,753 --> 00:31:30,721
Don't joke so.

478
00:31:30,755 --> 00:31:32,916
I am not joking.

479
00:31:32,958 --> 00:31:34,858
Is this because of some
foolish graffi...

480
00:31:34,893 --> 00:31:37,987
Servilia,
we are done.

481
00:31:46,771 --> 00:31:48,762
How can you say that?

482
00:31:53,645 --> 00:31:55,613
We love each other.

483
00:31:55,647 --> 00:31:57,638
Be assured,

484
00:31:57,682 --> 00:32:00,173
it is not that I
do not love you.

485
00:32:00,218 --> 00:32:02,083
I do this against
my own inclination.

486
00:32:02,120 --> 00:32:05,317
There are, however,
larger issues at stake,

487
00:32:05,357 --> 00:32:08,793
and I must do what is right
for the Republic.

488
00:32:08,827 --> 00:32:10,522
The Republic?!

489
00:32:47,332 --> 00:32:49,323
Why so happy, Mother?

490
00:32:49,367 --> 00:32:51,335
No reason.

491
00:32:51,369 --> 00:32:52,836
None at all?

492
00:32:52,871 --> 00:32:54,600
No clever little plan
bearing fruit?

493
00:32:54,639 --> 00:32:56,630
None at all, my poppet.

494
00:32:56,675 --> 00:32:59,075
Nor should you
suggest otherwise...

495
00:32:59,110 --> 00:33:00,975
to anyone.

496
00:33:06,718 --> 00:33:08,379
What's all the fuss?

497
00:33:08,420 --> 00:33:11,184
- We go south tomorrow.
- Excellent.

498
00:33:11,222 --> 00:33:14,385
If we move fast, Pompey will
be eating dust by the Kalends.

499
00:33:14,426 --> 00:33:16,860
You'll remain here
with the 13th to keep the peace.

500
00:33:16,895 --> 00:33:18,692
Keep the peace?

501
00:33:18,730 --> 00:33:22,257
The city will be in your charge.
I'll leave Posca to assist you.

502
00:33:22,300 --> 00:33:25,098
That's ridiculous! I'm a soldier,
not a peacekeeper.

503
00:33:25,136 --> 00:33:27,127
You will follow orders,
damn you.

504
00:33:45,990 --> 00:33:48,424
I was considering...

505
00:33:48,460 --> 00:33:52,419
I'm sick and tired...

506
00:33:52,464 --> 00:33:55,092
...I have a farm near here.

507
00:33:57,235 --> 00:33:59,601
Lovely at this time
of year.

508
00:33:59,637 --> 00:34:02,834
I was considering
that I might go there.

509
00:34:05,443 --> 00:34:07,809
Stay for the harvest.

510
00:34:09,881 --> 00:34:11,712
Perhaps you'd like
to join me?

511
00:34:11,750 --> 00:34:14,275
That is very kind,

512
00:34:14,319 --> 00:34:16,310
but I think
I will stay here.

513
00:34:21,760 --> 00:34:24,092
No good will come
of staying.

514
00:34:24,129 --> 00:34:26,120
I don't know.

515
00:34:26,164 --> 00:34:28,098
The sea air is
bracing at least.

516
00:34:28,133 --> 00:34:31,967
If you do not go then
I cannot go, I suppose.

517
00:34:32,003 --> 00:34:33,994
It would look cowardly.

518
00:34:34,038 --> 00:34:36,506
What matter? You would
know it were not so.

519
00:34:36,541 --> 00:34:38,873
Oh, I would know,
certainly.

520
00:34:39,878 --> 00:34:41,869
But I do not have

521
00:34:41,913 --> 00:34:45,178
a grand shining
old name like you.

522
00:34:46,384 --> 00:34:49,012
I must keep my name
well-polished,

523
00:34:49,053 --> 00:34:51,180
else it looks very dull.

524
00:34:56,127 --> 00:34:59,096
- I must stay then
- I'm sorry, old man.

525
00:35:56,387 --> 00:35:58,378
Soldier!

526
00:35:59,757 --> 00:36:02,453
You're on duty.

527
00:36:02,493 --> 00:36:04,484
The general
will see you now.

528
00:36:21,212 --> 00:36:23,203
Copy this.

529
00:36:38,897 --> 00:36:41,331
What do you want,
citizen?

530
00:36:43,468 --> 00:36:46,062
I've reconsidered
my position, sir.

531
00:36:46,104 --> 00:36:49,232
I wish to accept
your offer.

532
00:36:49,274 --> 00:36:51,435
My offer?

533
00:36:53,044 --> 00:36:55,035
Of entry into Evocati.

534
00:36:55,079 --> 00:36:57,070
If same terms
still apply.

535
00:36:57,115 --> 00:37:00,278
I said you could
join Evocati?

536
00:37:02,220 --> 00:37:04,211
With respect, sir,
you did.

537
00:37:12,964 --> 00:37:15,626
What terms did I offer?

538
00:37:15,667 --> 00:37:17,635
Evocati Prefect
first grade,

539
00:37:17,669 --> 00:37:19,660
10,000 sesterces.

540
00:37:21,072 --> 00:37:24,872
That's a generous offer.
One which you declined.

541
00:37:30,315 --> 00:37:34,274
Normally, I would never
make the same offer twice,

542
00:37:34,319 --> 00:37:36,310
but you're lucky.

543
00:37:36,354 --> 00:37:38,345
Cesar is away,

544
00:37:38,389 --> 00:37:40,380
and I am here alone.

545
00:37:41,926 --> 00:37:44,451
And I shall need
good men.

546
00:37:44,495 --> 00:37:47,020
So I give it you,

547
00:37:47,065 --> 00:37:48,862
promotion to Prefect

548
00:37:48,900 --> 00:37:51,630
and 9,000 sesterces.

549
00:37:55,773 --> 00:37:57,673
Thank you, sir.

550
00:37:57,709 --> 00:38:01,440
In return
for my generosity,

551
00:38:01,479 --> 00:38:03,606
Lucius Vorenus,

552
00:38:03,648 --> 00:38:06,014
I expect loyalty.

553
00:38:06,050 --> 00:38:08,041
Loyalty unto death.

554
00:38:10,521 --> 00:38:12,512
Unto death, sir.

555
00:38:19,764 --> 00:38:21,755
Welcome home.

556
00:38:29,407 --> 00:38:31,398
Dismissed.

557
00:38:36,280 --> 00:38:39,044
Put him here.
Domina...

558
00:38:39,083 --> 00:38:42,348
this is one of them that drew
the filthy pictures.

559
00:38:42,387 --> 00:38:44,378
Didn't take long
to make him speak.

560
00:38:44,422 --> 00:38:46,947
Eh?
Creature!

561
00:38:46,991 --> 00:38:48,982
Who hired him?

562
00:38:49,027 --> 00:38:50,722
Timon,
the Horse Jew.

563
00:38:51,729 --> 00:38:53,697
Atia's man.

564
00:38:53,731 --> 00:38:55,392
Dress me.

565
00:39:09,781 --> 00:39:12,477
- It's done.
- They'll have you back?

566
00:39:12,517 --> 00:39:14,508
They will.

567
00:39:40,378 --> 00:39:42,369
Evocati Prefect
first grade,

568
00:39:42,413 --> 00:39:44,404
9,000 sesterces.

569
00:39:46,851 --> 00:39:48,842
I've sold myself
to a tyrant.

570
00:39:55,226 --> 00:39:57,217
It had to be done.

571
00:39:58,963 --> 00:40:00,954
Thank you.

572
00:41:17,175 --> 00:41:19,166
Gods of the Junii,

573
00:41:19,210 --> 00:41:22,668
with this offering
I ask you to summon

574
00:41:22,713 --> 00:41:26,581
Tyche, Maegara
and Nemesis,

575
00:41:26,617 --> 00:41:29,142
so that they witness
this curse.

576
00:41:31,589 --> 00:41:34,149
By the spirits
of my ancestors,

577
00:41:34,192 --> 00:41:36,183
I curse

578
00:41:36,227 --> 00:41:40,596
Gaius Julius Caesar.

579
00:41:40,631 --> 00:41:43,498
Let his penis wither.

580
00:41:43,534 --> 00:41:47,527
Let his bones crack.

581
00:41:47,572 --> 00:41:51,030
Let him see his legions
drown in their own blood.

582
00:41:51,075 --> 00:41:53,270
Gods of the inferno,

583
00:41:53,311 --> 00:41:56,610
I offer to you
his limbs,

584
00:41:56,647 --> 00:41:58,638
his head,

585
00:41:58,683 --> 00:42:00,674
his mouth,

586
00:42:00,718 --> 00:42:02,709
his breath,

587
00:42:02,753 --> 00:42:04,744
his speech,

588
00:42:04,789 --> 00:42:06,780
his hands,

589
00:42:06,824 --> 00:42:08,917
his liver,

590
00:42:08,960 --> 00:42:12,396
his heart,
his stomach.

591
00:42:12,430 --> 00:42:14,421
Gods of the inferno,

592
00:42:14,465 --> 00:42:17,559
let me see him
suffer deeply,

593
00:42:17,602 --> 00:42:19,593
and I will rejoice

594
00:42:19,637 --> 00:42:21,764
and sacrifice to you.

595
00:42:56,907 --> 00:42:58,898
By the spirits
of my ancestors,

596
00:42:58,943 --> 00:43:01,503
I curse Atia
of the Julii.

597
00:43:01,545 --> 00:43:04,742
Let dogs rape her.

598
00:43:04,782 --> 00:43:06,773
Let her children die

599
00:43:06,817 --> 00:43:08,808
and her houses burn.

600
00:43:08,853 --> 00:43:11,879
Let her live
a long life

601
00:43:11,922 --> 00:43:14,720
of bitter misery
and shame.

602
00:43:15,726 --> 00:43:18,194
Gods of the inferno,

603
00:43:18,229 --> 00:43:21,756
I offer to you
her limbs,

604
00:43:21,799 --> 00:43:23,790
her head,

605
00:43:23,834 --> 00:43:26,496
her mouth, her breath,

606
00:43:26,537 --> 00:43:30,098
her speech, her heart,

607
00:43:30,141 --> 00:43:33,633
her liver, her stomach.

608
00:43:33,678 --> 00:43:36,579
Gods of the inferno,

609
00:43:36,614 --> 00:43:38,673
let me see her
suffer deeply,

610
00:43:38,716 --> 00:43:40,946
and I will rejoice

611
00:43:40,985 --> 00:43:42,976
and sacrifice to you.

612
00:44:24,562 --> 00:44:27,793
- Here we are then, friend.
- What do you want?

613
00:44:27,832 --> 00:44:30,733
- Tell us what's between you and Niobe.
- Eh?

614
00:44:30,768 --> 00:44:33,669
Niobe?
Nothing. Never.

615
00:44:33,704 --> 00:44:36,332
I swear by Jupiter,
never!

616
00:44:36,374 --> 00:44:38,171
Furies tear my eyes out
if I lie!

617
00:44:38,209 --> 00:44:41,144
What were you doing
when I saw you with her?

618
00:44:41,178 --> 00:44:44,545
My wife...
we were fighting.

619
00:44:44,582 --> 00:44:48,018
I went to Niobe
for advice, that's all.

620
00:44:48,052 --> 00:44:50,282
I was crying, if you want
to know the truth,

621
00:44:50,321 --> 00:44:52,516
and Niobe
commiserated with me.

622
00:44:52,556 --> 00:44:54,615
I would never...
I would never...

623
00:44:59,930 --> 00:45:01,898
- Maybe he's telling the truth.
- Lying.

624
00:45:01,932 --> 00:45:03,729
I'm not!
I'm not!

625
00:45:03,768 --> 00:45:06,066
Lying.

626
00:45:06,103 --> 00:45:09,334
If he says you're lying,
then I believe him.

627
00:45:09,373 --> 00:45:12,809
This boy is clever
like you don't know what.

628
00:45:12,843 --> 00:45:14,674
- No, please, I beg you!
- Hush.

629
00:45:14,712 --> 00:45:16,703
Don't embarrass yourself.

630
00:45:26,290 --> 00:45:29,555
We know you're lying.
We know it, you understand?

631
00:45:29,593 --> 00:45:31,584
We have to kill you.

632
00:45:31,629 --> 00:45:34,496
- I never touched her.
- Evander, move forward.

633
00:45:34,532 --> 00:45:37,194
Your life is over.
The only question is,

634
00:45:37,234 --> 00:45:39,896
how do you want to die?

635
00:45:39,937 --> 00:45:41,404
We need to hear the truth.

636
00:45:41,439 --> 00:45:43,737
If you persist in lying
to us, we'll torture you.

637
00:45:43,774 --> 00:45:46,902
You'll die only after many hours
of agony and horror.

638
00:45:46,944 --> 00:45:49,845
But give us honesty now,
and you'll go swiftly, painlessly.

639
00:45:49,880 --> 00:45:53,145
- Please.
- Evander, tell the truth.

640
00:45:58,155 --> 00:46:01,613
- Torture him.
- Juno's cunt, but you're salty.

641
00:46:01,659 --> 00:46:03,490
And I was worried
about bringing you.

642
00:46:03,527 --> 00:46:05,654
Go on then.

643
00:46:06,797 --> 00:46:09,664
I've never actually
tortured anyone.

644
00:46:09,700 --> 00:46:11,998
- I don't know how.
- You don't know how?

645
00:46:12,036 --> 00:46:15,631
- They have specialists!
- Why not cut off his thumbs?

646
00:46:15,673 --> 00:46:17,834
That's good enough.
It's a start.

647
00:46:17,875 --> 00:46:21,709
Niobe and I were lovers.
I confess it.

648
00:46:23,647 --> 00:46:25,808
Kill me if you must.

649
00:46:28,018 --> 00:46:29,576
Hold.

650
00:46:32,156 --> 00:46:34,056
What else?

651
00:46:34,091 --> 00:46:37,356
Nothing else.
Kill me.

652
00:46:37,394 --> 00:46:39,624
You're lying again.

653
00:46:39,663 --> 00:46:43,190
You stand at Pluto's door.
Will you sully his threshold with lies?

654
00:46:43,234 --> 00:46:45,668
- I am done talking.
- Cut off his thumbs.

655
00:47:31,282 --> 00:47:34,513
The child!

656
00:47:34,552 --> 00:47:37,851
- The child is mine!
- Child? What child?

657
00:47:37,888 --> 00:47:40,721
Lucius.

658
00:47:40,758 --> 00:47:42,521
The baby.

659
00:47:42,560 --> 00:47:44,755
Please, kill me now.
Please.

660
00:47:44,795 --> 00:47:49,061
- Lucius, Vorenus' son?
- Niobe's son.

661
00:47:49,099 --> 00:47:51,090
My son.

662
00:47:57,074 --> 00:48:00,874
It's mine.

663
00:48:55,699 --> 00:48:58,463
We have buried
this evil now.

664
00:48:58,502 --> 00:49:01,528
You must never speak
of it again.

665
00:49:01,572 --> 00:49:03,403
Vorenus must never know.

666
00:49:03,440 --> 00:49:07,470
Never.

667
00:49:11,315 --> 00:49:13,510
Father Mars Strider,

668
00:49:13,550 --> 00:49:17,509
this man has done
faithful vigil for you.

669
00:49:17,554 --> 00:49:20,455
We therefore ask you
to take him under your protection.

670
00:49:20,491 --> 00:49:23,949
May his enemies flee
from him.

671
00:49:23,994 --> 00:49:26,861
May their
city walls crumble.

672
00:49:26,897 --> 00:49:29,957
May their cattle
and women be taken.

673
00:49:30,000 --> 00:49:31,900
This man...

674
00:49:31,935 --> 00:49:34,369
is now Evocati.

675
00:50:00,464 --> 00:50:04,059
Sir, they've sailed
for Greece.

