It's quite good,
but they are far more handsome
in real life.
What are you doing?
Sorry, sir. Sorry, sir.
Just taking your likeness, sir.
Taking my likeness?
What do you mean?
Speak, thief!
Sir, Aventine Cloth Dyers
Association
are paying me
to do a mural of you
and Lucius Vorenus
in the arena, sir.
Explain yourself.
Why would anybody do that?
Why, sir?
You're famous, sir.
There's paintings of you
all over.
Not good accurate ones
like I'm gonna do, sir.
- Famous?
- Certainly.
- Me?
- The whole city loves you, sir.
You and Magistrate Vorenus
are symbols of brotherly love
and redemption.
If you were in Rome today,
I doubt there's a lady in the city
wouldn't open her doors
for the mighty Titus Pullo.
- Would you let me go, please, sir?
- Hmm? Oh.
Hmm.
Beautiful, hmm?
We own all of it,
as far as the river.
Lovely.
Best get used to it.
Caesar might well
exile me
from the city.
- Just for saving Pullo?
- We'll live off the land like peasants.
- He wouldn't be so mean.
- He might do far worse.
- Like what?
- Nothing.
I'm joking.
I don't suppose we can
lay down a blanket.
I shouldn't think so.
Well, if we ever
do this again,
I'm not wearing my best.
Too soft,
you city girls.
Hush you, I'm down
here, aren't l?
Get on with it
before I die of cold.
How long like this?
Um, till the priest
rings his bell.
Juno help me.
- It's good earth, this.
- It's wet earth.
Dark, loamy,
not much clay.
You can grow anything
in soil like this.
Where should we build
the farmhouse?
That ridge over there. Close
to the water and wood,
good command
of the valley.
In case we get
attacked by Gauls?
You never know.
You're meant
to be pretending.
I am.
You're not.
Shh shh.
Come to Papa.
Bitch.
Well, how was the farm?
Oh, Clarissa, wait till you see it.
It's beautiful.
Oh, it's very fine,
I'm sure.
What's wrong?
- You'll never guess.
- We'll never guess.
- Pullo ran away from the hospital.
- What?
Some carters found him
lying half dead by the Appian.
- He asked to be brought here.
- Here?
He's inside.
Gods beneath us.
He should not have been on his feet,
never mind on a horse.
All his wounds have opened
up, fresh as flowers.
- Poor stupid thing.
- I've given him
henbane to dull the pain
and immobilize him.
If by any chance
he lives,
he shouldn't move
on any account
for at least
10 days and nights.
I'll send him back to the country
as soon as he is mobile.
He won't cause any trouble,
not like this.
Like old times.
Pullo.
Lucius Vorenus, sir.
What are you doing here?
- Where am l?
- Rome, in my house.
You should be
in the hospital at Avernum.
And miss all the fun?
Why am I tied up--
What fun is that?
We're famous, aren't we?
Heroes.
Songs, plays,
pictures on walls, eh?
Damn foolish fuss.
What of it?
You are a slow one,
aren't you?
Women.
They like nothing better
than a man with a big name.
Please. You are lucky
to be breathing.
Even if you survive your wounds,
Caesar will probably
throw you back in the arena,
and me with you.
Do you think he'll do that?
Throw us back in?
I'll find out tomorrow.
I've been summoned.
Oh.
"Women," he says.
If you took
a woman now,
you'd come apart
like an old sack.
Ow!
Just like old times.
I don't mind.
It's good to hear your father
laughing for a change.
Eirene,
it's good to see you.
Fair enough.
If you can't do it,
that's all right too.
Eirene,
- what are you doing?
- Nothing. Nothing.
Don't lie.
What's that in your hand?
We were just talking.
- Talking?
- Catching up.
You fool! What if you killed him?
What then?
Everybody would know
it was you.
A freedwoman who killed
her old master-- very nice!
And where would
you go, hmm?
- What would you do with yourself?
- She has a point.
Go to bed. We'll say
no more of this.
She's looking well.
Good night, Pullo.
Juno protect you.
Don't worry.
I can't keep
Caesar waiting.
Eirene, when you finish that,
check on Pullo's dressings
- and change them if need be.
- Me?
You.
And feed him
some porridge.
Thank you.
As of this day,
the Kalends
of February,
our beloved
father dictator...
Gaius Julius Caesar
has decreed
that 100 new men
be raised
to the Senate
of the Republic.
The third day
before Nones,
a public banquet
will be held
to celebrate
those senators.
Slaves and freedmen
are not eligible.
Any repetition
of recent disorders
will be punished
with severity.
I shall divert
the river here, you see,
by digging a canal
to the Vatican hills.
Splendid. You shall
divert the river.
Splendid and useful,
I have no doubt.
Indeed. It will
prevent flooding
and give easier access
to the Fields of Mars.
And on the reclaimed land
I shall build
new civic offices
for the courts.
I shall also construct
a temple
to Venus Birthgiver.
Another temple--
excellent.
But if we might
for the moment speak
of this expansion
of the Senate?
- We might.
- Ah.
Gauls and Celts,
old boy.
Long-haired Gauls
and blue-faced Celts.
You're joking,
of course.
He is not joking.
Gauls and Celts?
In the Senate?
From the tribes that have
served Rome longest,
- the best of their nobility.
- I'm astonished.
Good.
Astonishment is my intent.
Ah, here comes
the hero of the hour.
What, no wreath
of oak leaves?
Shh.
Well now, Vorenus,
what am I to do with you?
Defying my express orders,
you dared interfere
in a legally sanctioned
execution--
an act of gross criminality
and disobedience.
I humbly apologize, sir.
I have no excuse.
You present me
with a dilemma.
By right, I could have you
thrown off the Tarpeian rock.
But the people, simple souls
that they are,
have made great heroes
out of you and Pullo.
If I were to punish you,
the people would be made
extremely angry.
I do not wish to make
the people angry,
ergo, I cannot
punish you.
If I cannot punish you,
I must reward you,
else I shall seem weak.
Listen to this now,
Cicero.
By popular acclaim,
I shall name
Lucius Vorenus
a Senator of Rome.
Good, eh?
Now you're all
astonished.
Vorenus, you look like you've
seen the Gorgon.
Excuse me, sir,
I'm stunned.
What do you say? Will you speak
for your people in the Senate?
I'd be honored to do so,
if you think me worthy.
There's none worthier.
You shall make
an excellent senator.
Very touching.
For the first few weeks,
you will stay close by me.
- Learn the drill.
- Thank you, sir.
Forgive me, but really
I must, as a friend--
I must protest!
A lowly pleb
in the Senate?
That's going too far.
No offense to you,
Vorenus.
I do not wish to jump
in any arenas, Cicero.
I must please the people
in some other fashion.
Build yet another temple.
Kill someone.
The people are
easy to please.
- Not this.
- I wish the Senate
to be made of the best
men in ltaly,
not just the richest
old men in Rome.
An intriguing notion.
You'll make a lot of men
very angry
with your Gauls
and your Celts
and your plebs and such.
I'll have to double
your guard.
That's what I told him.
Will he listen?
Guards can keep my enemies away.
They can do nothing
- about my friends.
- You don't mean me, do you?
I can assure you,
I have no ill intentions.
I know.
Not that you were not
perfectly capable
- of any manner of wickedness.
- Thank you.
But if you were going to betray me,
you would have done it long ago.
Don't think
I wasn't tempted.
So, no more guards then.
You will trust Fortune.
- Very good. Very pious.
- Stop your grizzling,
you old woman.
Who will dare
raise a hand to me
with the ferocious
Lucius Vorenus at my side?
Ah. Clever.
All these years together,
and it still surprises you
I can tie my sandals.
Sleep sound, little man.
Your mother and l
have been thinking
about finding you
that husband.
Hmm?
A senator'sdaughter
cannot be running
around unattached.
Oh, there's no hurry.
Don't worry, we'll find you
a good rich old man
you can wrap
around your little finger.
Beauty like you
can have your pick.
I told you, I don't want
a rich old man.
Of course you do.
Just think of all those
fine dresses and jewels
and slaves you'll have.
I don't care about
such trivial things.
Trivial?
When I was your age,
I had to eat bones
from the gutter.
Dresses and jewels
are not trivial.
They show others
that your people
are rich and powerful
and that you are
Ioved and protected
and valued.
But I want to marry
someone I love.
Love doesn't come unbidden,
you have to work for her.
Strange marriage it would be
if you loved him from the start.
That's right. It takes a while.
Now you be a good
virtuous wife,
and love will come.
Your mother and l, we had our
troubles, didn't we?
- Look at us now.
- Happy as you like.
I suppose.
So...
a good rich old man
it is then.
Hmm?
I was about to wake you.
Wherever you were,
you were not enjoying yourself.
It was another
dream of omens.
You're becoming
quite the oracle.
Shall I send
for some willow water?
- You'll sleep better.
- I was in the country.
Please, I have had
such dreams for years.
Bloody rain,
black dogs,
hooded ferrymen--
for years.
Here I am,
still alive and well.
I've never had
such dreams before now.
What am I to do?
Should I quit Rome
and hide
because you have
bad dreams?
Why not?
I'm serious.
Are you not weary
of this toil?
I am. I am
extremely weary.
But there is
much more to be done,
I'm afraid.
Much more.
There's always
more to be done.
To what end?
What end?
Good question.
I shall ask Posca.
Go to sleep, my dear.
Ancestors of the Junii,
we ask for your blessing
on this man
of your blood.
Let his arm be strong.
Let his aim be true.
Let his heart be filled
with sacred rage.
Good boy.
Hello.
Hey, Venus,
I have a question
for you.
Guess who I am.
Thanks very much.
It was nice
to meet you.
I can manage from here.
Wait.
So, where is everybody?
I'm sure I saw that one
selling fish in the Forum.
At leasthe Roman
A good Roman fishmonger
is a fine nobleman
compared to some of these
Belgian and Celts
that call themselves
chiefs.
There's one over there
with earrings.
It's good to see you.
It's the end, eh?
The Gauls have invaded.
Well, don't be so glum.
They will return
to their ghastly
mountain hovels soon enough.
Caesar will only
summon them back
when he needs their support
for some fresh outrage.
The red man
shadowing Caesar is
the famous Lucius Vorenus,
one assumes.
- lndeed.
- Affectionate, aren't they?
Might be father and son.
Caesar would have
the humble people think so.
He keeps the wretched man
by his side constantly.
This beast of the fields
is a Senator of Rome!
Do not fret so, Casca.
We timid subjects
of King Caesar
must learn to be
tolerant, hmm?
I believe I shall go home
and stupefy myself
with wine.
Good day to you all.
Old fool.
He knows, I'm sure of it. He knows.
You saw how he looked at us.
Be calm, Cimber. If he knew,
we would be dead already.
He's playing the blind man.
He's waiting for us
- to betray ourselves.
- Exactly.
He's not worried about us!
He thinks we are cowards.
Well, in any case,
we must act soon.
Today he brings in Gauls
and Celts and low plebs.
Tomorrow it'll be Belgians
or freedmen, and he won't rest
until he's turned the Senate
into a bawdy house!
We good noblemen will be
outnumbered by foreign rabble.
We will be degraded,
powerless.
- We must act soon.
- What about bloody Lucius Vorenus?
- Lucius Vorenus is a son of a whore.
- You know him personally, it seems.
I know him.
Who is Lucius Vorenus?
You remember, Mother,
the low soldier
that jumped into the arena
to save a comrade?
I remember something
of the sort.
Well, Caesar's pandered to the mob
and made him a senator.
And when Caesar's
in the Senate,
the dog never leaves
his master's side.
And  a fearsome dog  it is.
So, if we are to reckon
with Caesar
on the Senate floor,
we must reckon
with Lucius Vorenus also.
Kill him as well.
What's it matter?
He is a popular man.
- So? I'll kill him.
- It is most important
that we keep the people
on our side.
We cannot kill
one of their heroes.
That would sully
the whole business.
- Only the tyrant dies.
- Kill Caesar in his bed then. He
- doesn't sleep with this man, does he?
- Quintus.
It's not such a bad thought.
We could bribe
some of his slaves.
Buy off his cook. Buy off his taster.
Poison him.
Gentlemen, this is not
some cheap murder!
It is an honorable thing
that we do,
and it must be done honorably.
In daylight.
On the Senate floor.
With our own hand.
With my hand.
You're right, of course.
Forgive me.
That's all very well,
but how?
How?
What's wrong?
Are you still awake?
You were worrying
very loudly.
I feel like everything
seems to be moving so fast.
It feels like--
I'm--
I'm scared sometimes.
- Lucius Vorenus, was that his name?
- What?
The low soldier
that Caesar made a senator.
Was that his name?
Lucius Vorenus.
Why?
I have heard
the name before.
"My dear friend,
I regret I have not seen
you or yours for some time.
Two families
as entwined as ours
must not be strangers.
Would it be
convenient for you
to come and
visit me tomorrow?
With great affection,
Servilia."
How strange.
Is it?
Why would she want to see me?
She hates me.
So do l. It's no bar
to friendship.
What is she thinking?
Nothing to your benefit.
- What will you do?
- I shall accept, of course.
- Is that wise?
- Probably not.
Her rage amuses me.
You shall come
with me.
- Why?
- To be my protector, of course.
Who knows what the mad
old turtle will do?
Please don't
speak of her so.
Well she is
a mad old turtle.
Anyway, I thought you were above
such petty emotions nowadays.
I am.
I try to be.
Oh...
you still have
feelings for her.
- There's nothing wrong with that.
- I feel nothing
but pity for her.
And for myself as I was then.
And for you.
Me?
You silly goose.
- Why are you dressed so?
- I'm going to the country--
just for the day,
to get some fresh air,
stretch my legs.
I was thinking of stopping
by the shrine of Sacred Rusina,
asking her if she'll forgive me
for all the bad things I've done.
You think she might?
Forgive me?
Who knows
what the gods will do?
Come along,
if you like.
Senate in session today.
No assemblies
in the vicinity.
No gaming.
No prostitution.
May all the gods
bless our sacrosanct father
Gaius Julius Caesar.
- Good day, Senator.
- Good day.
Sir, sir, a moment
of your time!
Read my petition!
Caesar! Caesar!
Caesar!
My dear Atia,
how wonderful to see you.
Wonderful indeed.
And  Octavian!
You're practically
a man!
I like to think so.
And so handsome.
Come in, come in.
It's looking lovely here.
Have you redecorated?
Pull!
Senator Vorenus,
I come about your
grandson Lucius.
...Servilia of the Junii,
and what I tell you now
is the truth.
You're alive!
Answer me,
what child is that?
Where is Vorenus?
He was with us
a moment ago.
Never mind.
Mark Anthony, why don't
you give us a moment?
You must be wondering
why I invited you here today.
I am rather puzzled.
Well, it's important to me
that I be the first
to tell you
what has happened.
Why?
What has happened?
- Trebonius.
- Great Caesar.
I know, Barca, I know.
I have not forgotten.
If I may,
gracious Caesar,
you were going to consider
revoking my brother's exile.
I'm still considering it.
Take your hand off me.
What are you waiting for?
Now! Now!
- Now.
- Now!
- Wait!
- Get off me!
Do it.
Stop it!
What's wrong?
- Where is he?
- Who?
Your son!
Tell me it's not true.
Tell me!
Tell me.
I thought you were dead.
Oh Lucius.
Lucius.
Lucius,
the boy is blameless.
Thus ever
for tyrants.
No!
So you see,
the tyrant is dead,
the Republic is restored,
and you are alone.
Would you like
some honey water?
I won't, thank you.
Please don't be afraid.
I won't harm you.
Not yet.
Harm?
Why would you
wish us harm?
We've always been
great friends.
- Politics is for the men, I always--
- Not yet.
I will make you
suffer slowly.
Slowly and deeply,
as you made me suffer.
First, I want
to see you run.
Run for your life.
Run to some rathole
in Greece or lllyria,
wherever you like.
I shall come
and find you.
Thank you for the visit.