We should go.
Night is coming.
They sleep
standing up, you know.
Elephants.
On account once laid down,
they cannot rise again.
Is that so?
I was not aware.
We should go.
Where?
Utica is not far.
Utica.
What's there for us?
Shelter. Food.
I need neither.
Sleep, then.
Sleep would be pleasant.
So...
Utica then.
Dear me.
Really, Aquinas, is this
the best we can do?
No matter.
Bring water
for washing.
And bread...
and wine.
I think I shall make
myself drunk tonight.
Perhaps just this once
you will join me.
I think not.
Cheer up.
We live.
We do.
And where there's life,
there's hope.
I'm afraid if we have
done anything, old friend,
we've disproved
that proverb.
Aquinas, this bread
is stubborn.
Give me your knife.
Scipio...
you have
a tolerant spirit.
If you can,
you should...
make your peace
with Caesar.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I shall do whatever you do.
I wouldn't do that.
- Go your own way.
- In any case, let's not discuss it now.
There'll be plenty of time
for such sad talk.
If you'll excuse me.
I need to urinate.
There's a pisspot
through there, I believe.
Help! Help!
Send them away.
Do it now.
Cut deep, boy.
Goodbye, sir.
We thank you so much.
We hope you have enjoyed
our humble efforts
on this happy day!
Happy day on which our
glorious father has returned!
Happy day on which
the Julian sun has risen
and banished
Pompeian night forever!
Happy day on which
our brave soldiers
have come home
to their families!
Happy day!
- Salve.
- Welcome back.
- Are you home for good now?
- I am. I am.
No more soldiering for me.
Bona Dea.
It's nice, isn't it?
It is.
- Who are these?
- I bought them last year.
Four slaves we have now?
They were a good price.
On a soldier's wage?
The butcher shop paid
for them with plenty to spare.
The butcher shop?
Me and Lyde have made
a nice business out of it.
Five hundred head
a week sometimes.
Pigs mostly, but some sheep
and cows for the religious trade.
Eirene!
- It's very good to see you.
- It's good to see you too, master.
- You speak our words!
- If it pleases you.
Oh, it does.
Of course it does.
Can I get you anything?
A bit of water
would be nice.
Ah!
I brought you something.
Here, let me.
Lovely.
"Parentalia begins
on the ldes.
Temples will be shut,
and no wherein
celebrated.
Public festivals shall be
at the fifth hour in the circus.
Wine to be provided
by the Capitoline fraternity,
and cakes by
the Guild of Millers.
The Guild of Millers uses
only the finest grains--
True Roman bread,
for true Romans."
The fat old bitch
herself eh?
Must be good
to be home.
What is it, two years
you've been gone?
Are you still
fucking my mother?
When she'll have me.
That would explain
your excessive familiarity.
- Excuse me.
- That's all right.
I was merely curious,
and you're correct.
It does feel good
to be home.
My darling boy.
Oh!
So handsome.
- Sister, I hope you're well.
- Let me hug you.
Come inside and wash.
Let's get rid of the stink
of horse off you.
Timon, I'll, uh...
see you later.
Please, Mother,
we will be late.
Oh, we must not be late.
That would never do.
I do not want to go to dinner
any more than you do,
but Caesar has treated me
extremely well,
and we must go if asked.
- Honor demands---
- Honor?
- Honor.
- Not honor then,
common sense.
I cannot ask mercy
of Caesar,
accept rank
and favor from him,
and then refuse
his friendship.
What sort of man asks
for mercy in the first place?
I assure you, Mother,
I am not proud
of myself.
I am not proud at all.
In lieu
of a noble suicide,
you shall have to
be content with that.
Bring me my shawl.
Please, do not come.
I shall make
your excuses to Atia.
Certainly not.
I will go.
Not to be there
would be seen as weakness.
Perhaps it will
do you good to see him.
See that he is
just a man.
The loss of his affection
is not worth
this endless
raging sorrow.
I feel neither
rage nor sorrow.
My objection to Caesar
is purely political,
not personal.
The Pontic troops
ran so fast
I don't know
if they ever stopped.
It is no wonder Pompey
took Pontius so readily.
A child with a stick
might have done so.
What next, sir?
Germany perhaps?
I'm afraid I must put on
a triumph this next month,
and they're damnable
beasts to organize.
Still, the people
love a good parade
and we must not
disappoint them.
How lovely to see you both.
- It's been far too long.
- We are joyful to be here.
- Joyful, indeed.
- Is this a mourning shawl?
It's very pretty.
Has someone died?
A great  many have died.
How true.
But it's all over now,
and we're
still alive, neh?
It's not possible.
Octavian?
Gods, you make me
feel old.
Come.
It is the height
of four men,
with a long neck
like a goose,
spots like a leopard,
and the speed of a horse.
I don't believe it.
A new Chimera.
I assure you,
it is quite real.
With any luck, you may
see one at my triumph.
I have been trying to bring
one over for months now,
but the wretched creatures
keep dying on the way here.
- They do not like the sea.
- It all sounds very tiring.
After this
infernal triumph is done
- you must go to the country and relax.
- I should like that,
but then my work
begins in earnest.
I must set about putting
the Republic to rights.
Splendid notion. How shall
you proceed, do you suppose?
I have a few ideas,
but I am open to suggestion.
Yesterday, I saw Malchio
the baker in a litter.
A baker! I'd put a stop
to that sort of thing immediately.
I shall have it
looked into.
- Octavian?
- Hmm?
How would you proceed,
were you me?
- Uh, proceed with?
- Putting the Republic to rights.
Ah.  Um...
how to proceed.
I would start a large program
of public works--
employ citizens
and free men,
repair the aqueducts,
levee the river-- that sort of thing.
I would create at least
100 or so new senators,
that I could be sure were my creatures
rather than my secret enemies.
What is your point,
Octavian?
I did not mean you, Brutus,
you're a man of honor.
I believe that your
capitulation is sincere.
How nice of you
to say so.
I just had a thought.
Did not your man
Aelius Siculus die recently?
I'm afraid he did.
In Thapsus, in fact.
Just so. You shall take his seat
at the pontiff's table.
Pontiff? So young?
I was not so much older
- when I entered the college.
- Very true, but--
I believe I have
the authority
- to appoint whom I like.
- lndeed, yes.
This is a great honor.
Kiss your uncle's hand.
I kiss your hand, Uncle,
but truly I would make an ill pontiff.
Don't be ridiculous.
You'll make a lovely pontiff.
You'll see to it, right?
I had rather thought to concentrate
on my poetry for a while.
- He'll make a lovely pontiff.
- Poetry can wait.
It should not wait
too long.
Poetry is
a young man's calling...
don't you think?
There's us with the walls
of Thapsus at our backs
and your father
was just here.
Now coming towards
us on the plain
with all their
legions, cavalry
and 900 war elephants,
Scipio and Juno.
"Hold fast," says General Caesar,
"let the bastards come!"
- I'll do it.
- Please, don't, master.
This is my work.
Lady will be angry.
Who's master, eh?
...ballistas on the city walls,
and the front line thinks
they've heard the order to advance,
so before the officers can stop it,
the whole fucking army charges
on Scipio's men double tempo.
Now, the elephants--
elephants see us
come running and screaming
and they turn tail and charge
on their own lines--
boom! Chaos!
Oh, don't cry,
it was just a game.
You must be bored,
sitting around here all day.
I don't mind it.
- You've been discharged a month.
- I know.
I mean, there's no hurry. We're
all right for money and everything--
But I can't be loafing
around here forever.
So you don't want to take up
the butchering trade?
Shopkeeping?!
It will give you
something to do.
This is fine work
for a prefect, eh?
- Smells like old times.
- It does that.
You remember that little
siege at Avaricum?
You'll not learn a trade
sitting on your pugas.
There's plenty more
carcasses to be hung.
Tomorrow! You'll have
your money tomorrow!
- Let's take his nose off.
- No, not me no--
- Don't-- don't fuss.
- Hey, stop that!
Take your business
elsewhere.
- What's it to you, you bastard?
- It's bad for trade.
And who the fuck are you,
little man?
- I am Lucius Vorenus,
- I know you.
Soldier boy, isn't it?
Up by the dyeworks, tasty wife.
Do not speak of my wife.
Get gone.
That's an order.
No no no. Orders?
Orders? No no no.
You're not a soldier now.
You're a fucking shopkeeper's clerk.
- You're dead, you are.
- Walk away now
and do not let me see you
on this street again.
Both of you...
dead.
Get back
to your business.
You shouldn't
have done that.
Those were
Erastes Fulmen's people.
He won't take disrespect
like that.
- You hit him.
- It was nothing.
Erastes Fulmen
will kill you.
- He's just a crook.
- He used to be.
Since Pompey's gangs left
he's had the run of the hill.
He's a big man now.
He kills whoever he wants!
I'm no prole
to be abused!
I was prefect
in the Evocati!
Caesar himself
gave me a horse.
Thank you, sir.
I hope that dinner was
not too painful for you.
Oh, I'm used to pain.
I don't mind it.
I wish you didn't care
for him so much.
I wish I didn't care
for you so much.
Stop.
That brother of yours
has become quite the pretty man.
Caesar seems
very fond of him.
Very much.
Mother claims Caesar
took him for a lover.
Really?
The cook said she heard them
going at it in a closet.
Octavian insisted
it was not so.
He said the noises
she heard were
some terrible affliction
of Caesar's.
Mother wouldn't have it.
Once she gets an idea--
Affliction?
What affliction?
- I don't know.
- Did he not say?
He was sworn to secrecy.
But he said terrible?
He said terrible affliction?
You must find out exactly
what this affliction is.
You must find out
which god has cursed him.
How can I do that?
It's a secret.
You must find it out.
This is the weapon I seek.
With the god's help,
I can destroy him.
Please don't talk this way.
Would you rather
I lied to you?
I would rather that
you think of something
other than the destruction
of my uncle.
I have never lied to you.
He still has
some terrible hold over me.
I wish it were not so,
but he will not let go.
Will you ask your brother?
Would that make you happy?
Yes, it would.
What are you reading?
A guide to the
interpretation of prodigies.
Is it good?
It's dull
beyond conception.
If I am to be a pontiff, I must be familiar
with their ludicrous jargon.
- Mustn't let down Uncle.
I'm bored.
- I could read to you.
- If you like.
"Little sparrow,
my love is love,
with whom she plays,
permits to lie within her lap,
to nip her finger,
biting quickly with that bill,
I should like to play with you as
she and soothe my troubled heart."
- Very nice.
- You do not like it?
No, you recite well,
but...
I'm tired of poetry.
- Tell me a secret.
- A secret?
Something shocking
and dangerous that nobody knows.
I don't know
any secrets like that.
I know.
What about Caesar
and his mysterious affliction?
What affliction?
Don't lie. The one
you told Mother about.
Oh, it was nothing.
I was just making it up.
- So you were lovers?
- Of course not.
Either you were lovers, or some
god has cursed Caesar, which is it?
- Sister, there are no gods.
- Don't be horrid.
There is doubtless
a Prime Mover of some sort,
but a community of beings that
look like us and meddle in our affairs?
- Highly improbable.
- You don't trust me.
I do trust you.
You are my dearest friend.
- Then tell me!
- Why this in particular?
Why do you care
if Caesar has an affliction?
I don't care
the slightest bit.
Only that it would be a terrible
secret and something worth hearing.
And I doubt very much that
you have any terrible secrets
of your own worth telling.
- You'd be wrong.
- Oh please, like what?
- I've tortured and killed a man.
- Liar.
Do you remember
Lucius Vorenus?
One of the soldiers
who rescued me in Gaul?
- You killed him?
- Of course not.
He has a wife
who deceived him.
A child he thinks is
his daughter's son is in fact
his wife's child
by a low half-Greek butcher.
How sordid.
It was the butcher I killed.
Helped kill, anyway.
Oh. Bravo, I suppose.
You asked
for a terrible secret.
Try again.
What?
Get out of the way!
Centurion!
Lucius Vorenus!
Niobe, looking
as lovely as ever.
Phyllis sends
her best regards.
Very pretty family
you have.
It's good to see you
again after so long.
So, back from the wars.
Civilian life, eh?
Must be hard to adjust.
Different rules.
Different fucking rules!
My man Urbo here says
you slapped him in the face.
- Did you do that?
- I did.
Perfect example--
different rules.
You see, I'm allowed
to chastise my people.
Regular citizens like
you are not allowed to touch them.
If someone does touch them,
they have to be punished.
Rules.
Get to your point.
This is the second time
that Lucius Vorenus
has shown me disrespect.
Next market day
at noon,
he will find me
in the Forum.
He will kneel down
before me.
He will kiss my feet
and he will apologize to me.
If he does not do this,
I will come here and kill him.
But before he dies, he will
see his wife and daughters raped.
And then I will burn
down this building.
Hold.
- You've said your piece?
- I have.
Then leave now.
Good day to you.
So the wife of this Lucius Vorenus
is a whore. What's that to me?
I'm sorry,
that's all he told me.
- He swears Caesar has no affliction.
- He's lying.
Is it not enough then?
If Caesar has
an affliction,
he has it and suffers,
whether you know it or not.
He suffers,
but he is not destroyed.
You must go back to your
brother and get the truth from him.
- How? I tried.
- Try again.
Promise him something.
You do have
something he wants.
What do you mean?
A young man will tell
his lover anything.
You can't be serious.
How can you...?
You know he wants you.
I would be betraying
my brother.
my family.
Your family is a nest
of snakes.
You have no
obligations to them.
They are my family!
They love me, l--
As I love you.
You call this love?
I can't.
- Where are you going?
- Home.
Don't go.
Your mother
killed Glabius!
My people caught
one of the men that did it.
One of Timon's men.
I'm sorry.
- Do as Lyde says.
- Please, Mama, come with us.
My place is here
with your father.
But what
if you're killed?
Then you must stay in the country,
don't come back to the city.
You understand?
Don't come back!
You'll be country girls. Mm-hmm?
Your cousin will find you good
handsome farmers to marry.
Go ask the gods
for blessing.
Can't you get Vorenus
to do as Erastes asks?
If you begged him--
To kiss a man's feet?
I'd never ask such a thing,
and he'd never agree to it.
Always remember that you
are children of the Vorenii,
an old and respected name.
And always remember
that we love you.
I love you very much.
Now go on.
Go, go.
Goodbye, sister.
Eirene, are you going to
leave this mess on the table?
Please, Niobe,
please, go with them.
I will not
and stop asking.
Good bread this.
I bought the better kind.
Hang the expense, eh?
Get back.
Make way there.
Run and hide.
Here comes the Consul
Gaius Julius Caesar,
Son of Venus, lmperator
of the Gaelic Legions.
Salve, Lucius Vorenus.
Your wife is
very beautiful.
Her name?
Niobe, sir.
Rise, Niobe.
Would you honor us
by drinking our water, sir?
I'm happy to do so.
Please, sit.
I have always held you
in high regard, Vorenus,
and I am told you are a man
of respect among your people here.
- I hope so.
- That being so, I've come to ask you
to stand for magistrate
of Lower Aventine...
on my slate.
Thank you.
Well?
I am deeply honored by your
presence here, sir, deeply honored.
But... respectfully,
I must decline.
So you still disapprove
of my actions?
Sir, with respect,
your politics
are not mine.
I am aware of that.
Were I a magistrate,
I would have to speak.
And you will not speak
in favor of a tyrant?
I will not speak
against my beliefs.
Delicious.
You misjudge me.
I am no tyrant.
I have taken dictator's
powers legally.
And I will return those powers
to the people and the senate
as soon as I am able.
I will not rest
until Rome is as it was
in the golden age.
I cannot succeed alone.
Will you join me?
Hail Caesar! Hail!
Hail Caesar!
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
A little  more,  I think
No, the sleeves are fine,
leave those alone.
You just be careful what
you're doing with that pin.
Yes. Now, if you could
go around the side--
at the hem,
at the bottom--
that needs taking up
a little bit there.
There.
No, that's fine.
I don't know.
That just isn't working for me.
Were you looking
for anything in particular?
Oh... not really.
Do you have
anything comical?
Um, I don't think so.
You.
Why send him away?
It's hot.
I don't like that one.
He looks at me.
Does he?
Have Castor beat him.
Maybe I will.
- I'll call for another one.
- Don't.
It's nice to be alone.
Isn't it?
- I suppose.
- Come lie down with me.
Lie down with you?
Why?
I would like it.
- Why?
- Why not?
I can think
of several reasons.
When you were little, you would
come to my bed every night.
Not every night.
Only when I was scared.
You were scared
a great deal.
I'm not scared now.
- Pretend.
- I have no skill at pretending.
I'm embarrassed now.
I thought you wanted me.
You're a man now,
aren't you?
You can take
what you want.
Brother,
tell me something...
Ah.
What do you mean, "Ah"?
Now comes the price.
- What do you mean?
- You're a virtuous woman,
so you must know that seducing
your own brother is wrong.
You and I are above such
petty social convention.
But incest is not merely
wrong by convention.
It's wrong in essence.
It must be,
else why so many idiots and
monsters among the children of incest?
- Don't.
- Don't worry.
It's unlikely
I've seeded you.
Not with the moon
in transit.
The point is, you're not the woman
to do such wrong out of mere lust.
Ergo, you must
have another purpose.
I suspect you shall renew your
strange interest in Caesar's health.
Wha-- what have I done?
What have I done?
What?
What have you done?
Tell me.
Promise.
Promise you won't
tell Mother.
Look at you.
You look like laundry.
There.
- Does it look well?
- Very well.
It feels strange.
No, don't,
you'll dirty it.
Does it hang properly
at the back?
I think so.
Calm down,
Mother, really.
Calm down? I have not
even begun to get angry!
Enough!
I am your son
but not your child.
- You will not strike me anymore.
- Will I not?
You fucked your sister,
you little pervert!
Don't tell me what
I will and will not do!
- Be quiet!!
- You wouldn't dare.
How could you
do this to me?
My own child.
- You killed my husband.
- I told you, didn't l?
- I told you I didn't kill him!
- You're a liar.
Servilia caught one
of the men that did it.
- One of Timon's men.
- And where is this man?
Did you speak to him?
Look at me.
Look at me!
I swear on the spirits
of my ancestors,
on the stone of Jupiter,
I did not kill your husband!
You abased yourself
for a stupid lie!
- I don't know.
- Servilia is the liar, you fool!
She lied to turn you
against me.
My poor lamb.
Eirene?
Eirene!
Coming, master.
Sit down.
Have a drink with me.
My mother
had hair like yours.
Grey eyes though.
Big grey eyes.
Slave... on one
of those farms up north.
Smelled of pine trees.
Worked in
the wood yards, probably.
That's what I think.
Explains the pine smell.
Don't know
who my father was.
Just another slave probably.
Some timid cunt shoveling shit
with a collar around his neck
because he didn't have
the courage to die like a man.
I'd cut my fucking heart
out of my chest
and eat it before
I knelt down to anybody!
- Cunt!
- Quiet!
Keep it down!
Suck my cock,
the lot of youse!
I'm Titus Pullo, right?
Right?
Right, master.
You're a good girl.
You don't smile
much though.
You want me to smile?
I want you
to be happy.
That's better.
Have some wine.
Come here.
Closer.
Take off your dress.
What's the hat for?
Yom Kippur.
Oh, is that today?
You call yourself a Jew?
What, are you
my Rebbe now?
- Move! Move!
- Vos!
No!
Quick, grab her!
Strip her!
No! No!
Somebody help her!
...keep and protect me.
Keep and protect me.
No!
Let's go!