-lwasthinking--
- Hmm?
I was thinking...
you and I might
go away to Baia.
Hmm? After
next market day.
It's supposed
to be nice there
- and seeing how crowded it's been--
- That's a lovely idea, but--
But what?
I can't leave Lyde alone.
- She needs me.
- She needs you.
Evander's been missing for two months.
Something bad has happened.
Very likely something
bad has happened.
Very likely he is dead!
Pullo, awake!
Wake up!
Mark Antony's waiting.
Mump off and die,
you pigfucker.
Right.
Aw, thank you,
my honey.
You shouldn't
thank slaves.
- No harm in it.
- It's bad for discipline.
Happy again
this morning?
Niobe, then?
- How's she going?
- I don't understand her.
All the hoo over her
sister's damn husband.
Women, eh? Maybe
she's-- she's--
She's what?
I don't know.
Women, eh?
Mighty vice-conqueror
of Gaul,
Mars and Bellona swell
with pride at your doings.
- And I say--
- Oh, good Juno, what cac you speak.
Would you just get on
with your point, man?
Immediately,
Your Honor. I--
Publius Servilius
is here.
Ah, good. That'll do
for this crowd then. Off with you.
- l--
- No, off with you!
Master of Horse and People's
Tribune Mark Antony
will receive
your petitions tomorrow.
Vorenus!
Out!
Cynthia,
a pear, my love, hmm?
Servilius,
my dear old friend.
- How are you?
- Healthy healthy, I thank you.
Forgive me,
have we met before?
Have we not?
No idea.
I always pretend so
with civilians.
It's more politic, nay?
And this must be
your beautiful wife,
whose name escapes me.
Poppaea.
A flower.
You'll excuse
all the bustle.
I found Pompey's taste
in decor rather dull.
I like a little more color.
- As you say.
- You shall make it lovely, we are sure.
You'll forgive me if I talk
business with your husband?
Of course.
- Pretend I am not here.
- lmpossible,
but I shall try.
Now then...
I'm sure you're
aware that Caesar
has left me in charge
whilst he is in Greece.
Yes.
Off having fun
chastising Pompey et al.
Left me here to scribble
and quibble like a damned civilian.
However, I am determined
to make the most of it.
I shall be
a good politician,
even if it kills me.
Or if it kills anyone
else for that matter.
So you are, it seems,
the most senior
senator left in Rome.
I have that honor.
- And a turnabout Pompeian to boot.
- l--
Which is why I thought
it could be amusing
if we made you consul
for this year.
Consul?
That's most kind--
Allow me to
finish speaking.
When the Senate
next meets,
there are a couple
of legislative items
I wish to see
enacted immediately.
I am sure you
will be happy to assist.
- l-- l--
- ltem one:
The Senate will ratify
Caesar's election as your
co-consul for the coming year.
But he is dictator
in any case.
It sounds so much
better if he is consul.
It's more amicable.
- You got that?
- l-- I do.
- l-- I have.
- ltem two: You will propose
the following law:
Forthwith, in every
province of ltaly,
one third of all
those employed
at laboring with
cattle or in agriculture
must be freedmen
or citizens.
I don't understand.
Too many slaves, you see?
They've taken all the work,
which causes unemployment
amongst the free populace.
Now, we need to create
more jobs for our citizens.
But it will be
hugely expensive!
Mmm. It will.
But only to
those few rich men
who own all the land.
And they shall
have the consolation
of having done something
eminently patriotic.
It seems rather...
extreme to say the least.
Ruinous even.
You may well be right.
But frankly, I do not care
whether it is the rich, poor,
or, indeed
both that suffer.
Caesar wishes
this law to be made.
He is my friend,
I will have it made.
If you prefer, I could
always bypass the Senate,
call an Assembly
of the People
and you can put your
arguments to them.
A fine orator like yourself
might just persuade them
that Caesar is wrong.
- That won't be necessary.
- Good.
Good.
That's it then.
- I don't know what to say.
- Say nothing then.
It's often best.
You know Posca of course,
Caesar's creature?
He'll take
all the details.
Poppaea...
my dove, if your
husband should die...
come to me,
we will marry, neh?
So, keeping their
promises, isn't he?
What?
Caesar and Mark Antony,
doing right by the people.
That was your
worry, wasn't it?
That Caesar'd turn out to
be just another tyrant sort?
But here's him
and Mark Antony
getting jobs
for the unemployed.
You can't complain
about that now, can you?
He negotiates with a whore
and a dwarf at his side.
Think you Cincinnatus
or Marius or even the Grachii
- would demean themselves so?
- Who?
Mark Antony has his odd ways,
there's no denying that.
I'm not going home.
I need a drink.
- Drink? You?
- l. Drink. What of it?
I'll not argue.
- Ouch!
- Sorry.
- You need to calm down.
- How can I be calm? Two months of this.
- Aren't you done yet?
- Will you sit still?
Won't catch a pretty new husband
with a sour face like that.
I don't want a new husband.
I want Crito.
You can't stay
married to a drover,
not now that your
father's a prefect.
- It wouldn't be right.
- I told her.
Far too low. Fortune blessed you,
you haven't paid out dowry.
Don't worry, we'll find
you someone nice,
- and proper status.
- I don't want anyone!
You can't be unmarried.
It wouldn't be decent at your age.
- Decent she says.
- What's that supposed to mean?
You know what it means.
- You hold your tongue.
- Or what?
What will you do?
It's all right, sweetie.
It's all right.
I thought it was going
well for a while, but now...
Maybe I should beat
her, do you think?
I don't know.
That only works if you keep at it.
A good thrashing
once or twice a day
till they're docile.
But then they
don't look so good.
Be a shame to mark up
a beauty like her.
She is, eh?
She's a beauty.
She is that.
I give her slaves, money,
everything. What do I get?
Nothing, that's what.
I get a house
full of wailing.
My wife won't
even couple with me.
Why not?
Says she can't while
her sister stays.
What's her sister
to do with it?
What difference
should that make?
What is wrong with her?
What is wrong with me
that I'm served this way?
You should
leave her, maybe,
seeing as she
makes you so unhappy.
No! I will
not leave her.
I'd rather die
than leave her.
It's all right, lamb.
It'll be all right.
Who, I say,
faced with the
overwhelming force
of the figures and the arguments
I have here marshalled
could resist their
overwhelming conclusion?
Therefore I ask you,
honored conscript fathers,
to support me in
this important and...
patriotic legislation
which will--
Does anyone wish to speak
against the motion?
No opposition voiced.
No division required.
Motion carried.
Empty.
Empty...
If there's no wine,
water will do.
Thank you, my dove.
So, Lyde, I was asking
around, you know,
about your man there,
Evander.
Asking  around?
See if I could find
out anything for you.
Only, I know a few
shady characters see?
Types that might know what's
what when a man's gone missing.
Anyroad,
they tell me
that he got himself
into some trouble
with some nasty Greek
boys across the river.
- Gambling debts they say.
- Gambling?
Evander never gambled.
Well sure, it's
the sort of thing
a man keeps quiet around
his wife, isn't it?
What are you saying?
I'm sorry to say it, but it looks like
he's not coming home.
Dead, looks like.
Are you sure?
So they tell me.
Dead. Killed.
It isn't true.
My advice,
best forget about him.
Best get on
with your life.
It isn't true.
It's not so bad.
You've still got
people that love you.
Look to them, eh?
Isn't that right Niobe?
Best she gets
on with her life.
Best she looks to
the people that love her.
Forget Evander.
Forget the past.
Well, I'm away.
Need a drop of wine
to set me up for the day.
Lyde, please don't.
Shh.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
It's too late for sorry, isn't it?
You weren't sorry when you
were fucking him, were you?
You weren't sorry then.
I piss on your sorrow!
- Shh!
- I will not shh. You shh!
You're a thief and a whore
and you stole my husband!
I stole nothing!
He came to me!
I never loved him. I love my husband!
And if you'd done--
if you'd been--
If I had done what?
If I had given him
a child. Is that it?
I am sorry. Please forgive me.
Please forgive me!
- Forgive me!
- I curse you, sister.
By grace of the Furies,
I curse you.
I'll keep your secret
for the sake of the child,
but don't you ever...
ever speak to me again.
Be careful!
Ah!
Bravo. Bravo.
A little blood lust
suits you, Octavian.
You look very handsome.
Does he not?
- He does.
- Titus Pullo is a good teacher.
Well it's a pity Caesar
isn't here.
He'd put you on his
staff immediately.
Perhaps you should go
and join him in Greece,
get some real Pompeian
blood on your sword.
- Don't be silly, Mother.
- Well why not?
If we are not quick, Pompey
and Cato and all those fools
will be dead before Octavian
gets his chance to shine.
- He's still a child.
- I am not.
He is not. He is quite
the little man now.
I should think there's more
to manhood than swordplay.
Octavian,
- have you penetrated anyone yet?
- Mother, please.
- Does that mean you have or haven't?
- Haven't, but--
Titus Pullo, didn't I tell
you to sort that out?
I'm sure I did.
I-- sorry, ma'am.
I'll see to it.
Do that.
Don't worry, darling.
There's really nothing to it.
Once you're in
the saddle, as it were,
it'll all come naturally.
Isn't that right, Pullo?
That's right ma'am.
And none of your sordid soldier's
she-wolves, mind you.
Something clean and pretty.
- Clean and pretty it is.
- Good.
I'll get Merula make you a toga.
What else?
Perhaps you can arrange
he kill someone.
Oh...
that will happen
in due course.
We Julii always have
the needful enemies.
Health to my child.
My daughter.
I wish for a son,
a healthy son.
- l, uh--
- Good night, then.
Good night.
Husband.
What's all this?
I thought it might please you
if we had some time alone.
I sent the girls
and Lucius to Clarissa.
- And Lyde?
- She's gone to a friend's.
- Please, sit down.
- I've already eaten.
Oh...
But--
I can have some more.
Excuse me.
Sit down with me.
- That's all right.
- Really, sit.
I can't finish
all this on my own.
The calendar is correct...
if you would like
to have me tonight.
I would.
I'd like that.
My dear Mark Antony,
I hope this finds
you in better health
than my hopes for victory.
I chased Pompey from one
end of Greece to the other
and he resolutely
refused to fight.
I thought this was
his usual obtuseness,
but the old man has
some sense left in him yet.
While avoiding battle,
he has gathered a good
10 legions from the east,
and I find myself
badly outnumbered.
Now the cat
barks at the dog,
and Pompey is chasing me.
I can outmaneuver
him for a while,
but not forever.
My men are tired
and ill-supplied,
and we shall soon
have to stand and fight.
I ask you to bring
the 13th here
as speedily
as you are able.
Damnation.
Shall I summon
the legion legates?
Hmmm.
No. Wait.
I must think on this.
This is lovely.
- Oh.
- Oh, it's just your coloring.
A little loud. I'd prefer
something plainer.
What's the point in plain?
We shall take it.
But this one...
Oh!
Divine. Oh, divine.
Antony will love this.
He likes me in Eastern styles.
- How much for both?
- 5,000.
- You are a thief.
- Four and a half then.
Three.
Can we afford such expense?
Things as they are
with Caesar in Greece,
surely we should
be more prudent?
Don't worry about
a thing my dear,
I'm thinking ahead.
Titus Pullo is here, dominus.
Oh. Tell him
I am unwell.
He may come back
next week perhaps.
Tell him nothing
of the sort.
Octavian will be ready
to see him in one moment.
And  give  him  a  purse
You've put off this moment long
enough, my dear.
Mother--
You will penetrate
someone today or I will
burn your wretched
books in the yard.
Off with you.
Coming through. Noble coming through.
Make way there.
Don't worry, young master.
There's nothing to it.
If there is nothing to it,
why is such a fuss made of the thing?
You'll soon find out.
Vai, vai!
Be off with you!
This isn't no infantry fuckhole,
thank you very much.
Now now, my honey,
calm your stomach.
We've come for
the young master here.
Andwe're well  coined.
Oh well,
excuse me, of course.
I meant no disrespect.
We're honored to service
you, young master.
And what would be
the young master's pleasure?
First timer.
Nothing too savory.
I'm sure we have
just the thing.
Something exotic, perhaps?
Or else something young?
Light, simple.
Little bit skinny,
isn't it?
Won't know he's
been, will he?
Won't know you've been.
More substance,
yet still nymphlike,
graceful.
This one's fresh
off the boat...
- That will be fine.
- Hold on, young master.
No point hurrying.
Big decision, this.
- Let's have a look at--
- This one is perfectly adequate.
You will be utterly
satisfied, I assure you.
Egeria, go prepare yourself.
If we might dispense
with the pecuniary details...
Eh?
Oh, right.
- What's your price then?
- 1,000.
Gerrae!
I could have half the whores
in Narbo for that, and their mothers.
We're not in Narbo,
whatever that might be.
All  right,  my dove
We'll pay.
But the girl better fuck him
like Helen of Troy with her ass on fire,
or I'll know
the reason why.
- Speak.
- Gnaeus Pompey Magnus sends greetings.
He hopes you find
his house satisfactory.
It'll do.
- Get to his point.
- His point.
Caesar is doomed
and you with him,
- unless you make a separate peace.
- And?
If you do, Pompey will
be merciful and generous.
How?
He will give you your life.
A province.
Money enough to preserve
your dignity.
What makes him think
I value my life so high?
Why have you
not left for Greece?
Do not smile at me.
Return tomorrow. I will give
Pompey his answer then.
Not that way.
And  disguise yourself.
Dismissed.
You take clothes down?
That's an interesting accent.
No understand.
Where--
are you from?
Oh. Where from.
Don't know.
You don't know
where you're from?
Rome take me very young.
Kill mother, father,
brother,
take me.
Oh. I see. Sad.
Turn over, would you?
On your hands and knees.
Ah!
Nice place, this.
Clean.
I don't suppose,
seeing as I'm
with the quality...
Not a chance.
No no no. No, do it for real.
Fight.
Oh, come on, fight,
damn you! Fight!
That's better!
Mmm, good.
Brava, Cynthia! Brava!
Oh, don't be so silly,
it's just a scratch now.
There there.
Yes, Posca, what is it?
I am to remind you
of your dinner tonight
with Atia of the Julii.
Sons of Dis.
Now, run along.
Where is he?
Where can he be?
Busy man. Politics.
Politics? He promised
he would come.
Castor!
Send a man to Pompey's--
I mean, Mark Antony's villa
and enquire his whereabouts.
Antony's whereabouts,
immediately, domina.
Do not say it is
I who sends to ask.
Not you sends to ask.
Stay. He'll know
it is I who asked.
Send no one.
I will send no one.
If he comes,
he comes, I don't care!
Halt!
Welcome, dominus.
Sorry to be so horribly
late. Endless business.
- Will you forgive me?
- Of course.
I confess, I had quite
forgotten you were coming.
So this is
a lovely surprise.
Excuse me a moment,
I will go and dress correctly.
Mmm. Here he is,
young Apollo!
- How was it?
- It was pleasant.
Pleasant?
I should say so.
- How was he?
- Like bull.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Tell me.
Mark Antony does not intend
to go to Greece to help Caesar.
I have sworn loyalty
to a man of no honor.
Well you don't have
to go to Greece then.
- We'll be together.
- It's true, but still.
Haven't you always said
Caesar's cause is wrong?
That is not the point.
There is a moral
principle involved.
What an idiot you are!
Not hungry?
Oh, after so many years of
soldier's porridge, I am easily sated.
Well, this last
news from Greece
cannot have improved
your appetite.
Hardly.
And is it really so bad? Caesar
always finds a way to win.
Pompey has gathered 10 men
for every one of Caesar's.
Arithmetic has no mercy.
I'd feared it was so.
What do you
intend to do then?
I don't know.
You've become a powerful man.
The people love you.
Only because
they don't know me.
You could be the first man
in Rome, if you wanted.
I hadn't thought
about it like that.
Well, you should.
You should
think about that.
I'm thinking about
something entirely different.
Mmm.
Water.
I could sleep for a week.
I've been thinking.
We should get married.
Married?
Why should we want
to do that of all things?
- Perhaps I love you.
- Ah.
You're joking.
For a moment there
you had me worried.
I am not joking with you.
Oh, my dear woman.
Please don't worry,
I'm not going
soft on you.
I'm thinking strategically.
If Caesar is defeated,
I can't very well form
an alliance with the Pompeians.
- I need protection.
- True.
What's in it for me?
If Caesar is defeated--
Then I will be defeated also.
Only if you join
him in Greece.
But if you stay in Rome,
you will be
very well situated.
You have the people
with you,
you have possession
of the city.
You only lack money.
And whilst your name
is perfectly respectable--
- I am no patrician.
- Exactly.
But allied with my house, you
would have both coin and nobility
to make yourself king
if you wished it so.
And you would be queen.
I would be your loving
and obedient wife.
If only I were willing
to desert a friend.
A man of your own blood.
- Oh, too honorable for that, are you?
- I like to appear so.
But I don't think you'll die
for the sake of appearances.
- Will I not?
- Caesar will die in any case.
But you are far too clever
to share his fate needlessly.
I had not
realized until now...
what a wicked old
harpy you really are.
Get out!
Thank you, Pullo.
At attention!
Ow.
Abed in daylight,
what luxury.
Wickedness.
Father, that dwarf
is asking for you.
Excellency Mark Antony
orders 13th Legion to muster
on the Field of Mars.
- Why? Where are we going?
- Greece.
Tribune!
- What shall I tell Pompey?
- Oh!
Of course.
Excuse me.
I had forgot you.
His skin is a little dry.
Have him well-oiled
before he is presented.
Bona dea.
- I am afraid to ask.
- Gifts for Servilia.
How fine you look.
Let me see.
I am so proud of you. You're a
real man at last, eh?
Why are we giving
gifts to Servilia?
The old crow stands in
well with Cato and the rest.
- When Caesar and his dog Antony are
defeated--
- If they are defeated.
When they are defeated,
we'll need her good will.
- And this will buy it, you think?
- I do not see why not.
A large penis
is always welcome.
- You think it's not enough?
- After what you did to her?
- What I did? What did I do to her?
- Please! I'm not stupid.
It was you made
Caesar renounce her.
- What if I did? She doesn't know it.
- Does she not?
- She's not stupid either.
- Servilia has no guile in her.
If she knows it, we would certainly have
heard about it.
You know best,
I'm sure.
In any case, you will
take the gifts to her
and see what
she's thinking.
She's always been
very fond of you.
And you will
go to Mediolanum.
- Timon will take you.
- Mediolanum?
Yes, they have a very
good academy there.
- I don't understand.
- You're a man now.
Rome's not safe
for men of the Julii.
His toenails are ugly.
Have them cut and painted and
put some flowers on his head.
Oh, and send over some ice.
Six barrels, say.
Six barrels of ice.
Well, don't
look so foolish.
I know what I'm about.
Your mother's too kind.
To what do I owe
this generosity?
It's a gesture
of friendship.
Friendship.
Thank your mother
for her... friendship.
I hope one day
to reciprocate her...
friendship.
I will go then.
Excuse me.
Wait.
Please, forgive
my ill humor.
There's nothing
to forgive.
I have known you since you were
a little girl. You have a good soul.
I know that whatever
others might do,
you are blameless.
I know that.
I-- I do not--
that is, I cannot--
Shh shh shh shh.
It's all right.
There's no need.
Tell your mother
that I am grateful
for the gifts
and that I treasure her
friendship as always.
You must come and visit
me again. Will you?
- I will.
- Promise?
I want there to be no
ill feeling between us.
I promise.
You be a good girl.
Do as you're told.
I'll wait
for you outside.
Shh shh shh.
Bellona protect you.
And Juno keep you.
A fleet of ships
has set sail for Greece
carrying the army
of General Mark Antony.
This month's public bread
is provided by the Capitoline
Brotherhood of Millers.
The Brotherhood uses
only the finest flour.
True Roman bread,
for true Romans.
This is cac, this is!
I'm wet through.
We're perfectly safe.
A very good offering
was made to Triton!
If Triton can't keep me drier
than this, he can suck my cock!
Why can't you learn to
keep your fat mouth shut?!