-What's wrong, Mother?
- Ruined.
Ruined!
That idiot
has ruined us all!
We shall have
to leave Rome!
Caesar has crossed
the Rubicon.
He's on ltalian soil
under arms.
It's an act
of gross treason.
With a single legion,
if you please.
So not merely treason,
but suicidal treason.
Will that be all, Domina?
- Have you heard?
- Mmm. Strange.
Afoolishthingtpdo.
One legion.
I wonder what
he's thinking.
I remember back when I destroyed
the lllyrian pirates,
there was one particular
old sea snake--
a Liburnian,
if I recall.
Never mind
the lllyrian pirates.
What is to be done?
I have already
given word.
My legions
are gathering.
And you'll
crush him, yeah?
Without question.
The poor man is dead.
You are to take
our Ubian cavalry and scout
all roads and defensive strongpoints
between here and the city.
Advance until
resistance is met.
If and when civilians
are encountered,
deliver the enclosed
proclamation.
If you encounter no resistance,
go directly to the Forum
and nail it
to the Senate door.
Sir.
There will be no rapine,
pillage or burning.
- Any questions?
- None, sir.
That will be all.
What makes your man
Vorenus so morose?
He is stonewall Catonian.
He thinks we've committed
a terrible crime,
a mighty sacrilege,
and shall be severely
punished by the Gods.
- He may be right.
- It's a crime if we lose.
If we win, it isn't.
I am merely pursuing
my legitimate rights, Antony.
- Of course.
- Do you think we can trust him?
- Who?
- Lucius Vorenus.
Oh.
Deep 13th, him.
He'd follow the eagle
up Pluto's ass.
I told you
not to come here.
I had to see my son.
You've seen him.
Now go.
And stay away.
Help me, Niobe.
I'm going insane.
You can't forsake me.
I do.
I won't give up.
Don't think I will.
You loved me once,
you will love me again.
I never loved you.
Lie to yourself if you want,
but don't lie to me.
Stay away.
You know you will never
see your husband now,
you know that, eh?
Him and all the rest
of them are doomed.
You don't know that.
Everybody knows that.
That may be,
but I made a vow.
Go.
I swear to Dis,
if you don't go--
It's all right.
He's going.
Just go.
You promised you would
never see him again.
I didn't want him here.
I told him to go.
It didn't look like that.
You could tell Papa the truth.
It's not your fault.
If you and I spoke to him--
Never.
You have sworn.
You thought he was dead.
Papa will understand.
He will kill us all.
You-- you often say that you are
adept with women.
No idle boast neither.
There are girls from Nabo to Thebes
that scream my name by night.
I have no need
of your coital expertise.
My question more concerns
their... affections.
I'm your man
for that to boot.
My wife, she...
You heard what she said,
she hates me.
What's your question?
How do I stop her
from hating me, obviously?
It's not obvious.
I thought you were making her
hate you with a purpose.
That was not my intent at all.
Why would I do that?
I don't know.
You're the clever one, you.
There might have been
1,000 reasons.
I love her,
and I require
that she love me also,
else I am merely her slave.
I cannot tolerate that.
Well, what care you
what she feels for you
if we're all going
to die this week or next?
And so we are, but who will honor
my name when I am gone?
Who will pay Proserpina
and Pluto for my keep?
Who will pour wine
upon my grave?
If it comes to that,
I shall do the honors.
It's the least
I could do.
Thank you.
But it's not
the same thing.
Besides...
you'll be dead too.
I'm planning on having a small party
this evening and I'll need you to--
Are you wearing perfume?
Just a dab.
It's horrid.
Horseshit suits you
much better.
Now I need you to get more men
to stand guard outside
to greet my guests
when they arrive.
A party? Is that wise,
given how things are?
Perfume, advice--
whatever next?
I'm just saying Pompey's mob
is out for blood.
- It's best to lay low.
- Lay low?
I'm not a lizard.
I will not be intimidated.
As you like.
Cost you extra though.
You've been paid
quite adequately already.
More men cost more.
I will tell Castor
to speak with you.
I don't want more money.
Well, what do you
want then?
You know what I want.
Something like that.
- You forget your place.
- My place is with my family.
Say the word,
and I'll go to them.
Do your job
to my satisfaction and...
I'll see that
you're properly rewarded.
Thank you, Domina.
Pompey's outriders.
His legions
won't be far behind.
Us and the rest of the 13th
will be on crosses by market day.
Thank the Gods my father didn't
live to see his son die a traitor.
Best to die now then, eh?
Go on.
Wait!
We're not here to fight.
"Advance until
resistance is met."
That is our orders.
That is what we do.
Why not? The boys are ready,
aren't you, boys?
Let's have a go.
Come on!
No fight!
No! No fight now!
Damned idiot!
Form up and defend!
Remember your training!
Shields!
- Hold your ground!
- Stand tall!
- Hold positions!
- Stay in place, you cowards!
Caesar's scouts are
only 30 miles from Rome.
30 miles?
His speed is uncanny.
Of course, he has
only a very few men,
which makes
a fast pace easier.
He is not leading an army
so much as an armed gang.
It is all highly irregular,
unethical even.
Gods, it is not even
the war season.
Surely he does not think
to attack Rome directly?
I think that is
exactly what he will do.
How can he hope
to succeed?
The problem is,
at this moment,
we have only three legions in arms
for the defense of the city.
Surely, three
is more than enough.
Normally that would be true,
but most of the men
are raw recruits like those
who fled from the scouts.
The rest
are veterans of Gaul.
Caesar's men--
not reliable.
Rome is undefended!
My legions are mustering
as swiftly as possible,
but it will take
at least four days
to assemble a force capable
of defending the city.
Caesar is
two days away.
You touch it
with a needle.
What do we do now then?
We must make a tactical
retreat to the south.
A tactical retreat,
mind you.
Leave the city?
Juno's cunt!
Do you run mad?
You cannot speak to me
in that tone.
My friends, let us cleave
to the matter at hand.
Is there no alternative
to retreat then?
None. We shall
withdraw to Corfinium
and rally
my legions there.
Once they are gathered
and in good order,
we will simply retake
the city.
Caesar has no hope
of reinforcement until spring.
The towns of ltaly will
close their gates to him.
We will have an unassailable
advantage in men and resources.
So in fact, this is not
a humiliating defeat at all
but a rare species
of victory?
Calm yourself, Cato. You lack
understanding of things military,
else you would see
that my actions
have been perfectly correct
at all times.
You have lost Rome
without unsheathing your sword.
You have lost Rome!
Pompeian scum
at our very door!
It's intolerable.
If Timon and his men weren't here,
they'd be burning down the house.
Oh, they are not
that energetic.
This suicidal rebellion
has turned everyone against us.
I swear,
if Caesar were here now,
I would stab him
in the neck.
- He has ruined us.
- I'm not so sure of that.
But I think Pompey's position
is deceptively weak.
Think think think-- that's all
you do, you silly boy.
All our friends
have abandoned us,
cowards that they are.
We Julii are lepers now.
Let us not exaggerate, not all of
your friends have deserted you.
Andthatwill be remembered.
You are good loyal people.
It's very tempting
to abandon Caesar,
but to do so now, well, that would
look like we're mere...
slaves to fashion.
You're staying
to protect the house
but don't think for a moment that
your master and I will not return.
We will be back by the Calends
at the latest.
And when I do return,
those of you I find
have not done their utmost duty
will pay with their lives.
General,
your escort is ready.
- Gnaeus.
- Mmm?
Durio,
is the escort ready?
- Ready, sir.
- Away then.
Husband,
the treasury?
Yes, of course.
Durio.
You must secure
as much of the treasury gold
as possible.
Take a detachment and open up
the Capitoline vaults.
There's not much time,
so do what you can.
Let's pretend we're
Odysseus and his friends,
creeping out
of the Cyclops' cave.
We must be quiet
as little mice, all right?
Come.
- Sorry about all this.
- Do not say so.
I don't mind
a little excitement.
All will be well,
I assure you.
I have no doubt.
Let's away.
And remember, nosound
Break it down!
Here's a mercy.
Instead of living out our lives
in shame and disgrace,
we are to be raped
and beaten
and torn limb from limb
by a raving mob.
These brutes will not
let you pass, I think.
You may stay
the night if you want.
We would be delighted,
thank you.
Wait wait.
Wrong way.
The Appian gate
is to the right.
We're not going
to the Appian.
What?
Of course, your best method
for pleasing a woman
is the warm, beating heart
of an enemy.
Women will say they don't like
it, but they do.
It makes them wet
as October.
That doesn't answer.
Well, failing that,
talk to her.
Talk.
- But of what?
- That doesn't matter.
It's all about
the tone of the voice.
You pretend like you're putting
a saddle on a skittish horse.
"There, honey.
Shh, come now."
You know,
that sort of thing.
- That's all?
- What else?
Oh! Tell her she is
beautiful all the time.
Tell her she's beautiful
every time you see her,
even when she's not.
And what else?
Oh! Also,
very important...
when you couple with her, there's
a spot just above her cunny--
it's like a little button.
Now, attend
to that button,
and she will open up
like a flower.
How do you know this
of her?
Allwomen  have them.
Ask anyone.
Ho ho ho, very pretty.
Come up behind!
- Come with us!
- Sit up here!
You can make me happy!
It'll make me happy.
Here you go.
Up you go.
Come on!
I will kill Octavia,
and Merula tends to me,
but if she cannot, and I am
taken alive, then you must kill me.
And then you must
kill yourself.
Your survival
would be inappropriate.
I would not think
of living, Domina.
Octavian, who would you
prefer kills you?
I am old enough
to take care of myself.
Oh, that's
my brave little man.
Servilia...
can my people be
of any assistance to you?
Thank you but I'm sure we
can manage by ourselves somehow.
Very well.
Mother, I would rather
it were not you killed me
if you have
no objection.
Why ever not? You can't still
be angry with me.
- Is that an order?
- Bona Dea!
I feel like you have
never listened--
Cerberus is howling for us,
and still you plague me
with your
ridiculous feelings?
If you had only let
Glabius and I remarry--
Oh, always Glabius!
I spit on Glabius!
I piss on the wretch!
Oh, that's right, Mother,
die as you have lived--
- poison brimming in your soul.
- Listen!
I'll not argue with you. Castor,
be sure to cut Octavia's throat
- before you cut mine.
- Please, Castor, let Mother do it.
I won't deny her
one last pleasure.
- It would be undaughterly.
- Listen!
Consul Gnaeus Pompey Magnus
has left the city.
He commands all noblemen
and knights to do likewise.
Those that remain
will be considered
- enemies of Rome.
- Cowards!
You heard, then.
Don't know what good
that will do.
Anyone wants to get in,
they'll get in.
Give us a hand,
will you?
So your man will be back
after all, looks like.
It looks like.
You don't sound
too happy about it.
- Of course I'm happy. He's my husband.
- If you say so.
I'm sorry.
I was just talking.
I talk too much.
I don't know, Rissa.
I try my best
to love him, I do.
I don't know whether
I want him to come back.
I would not credit it
if I had not seen it myself.
Pompey's men deserting
the city, deserting Rome,
half the Senate ahorse.
A comical sight
no doubt.
Gods.
We are in a damned
awkward position.
If we stay...
we are declaring
for Caesar, for rebellion.
And if we go, we-- we are
with Pompey and the Senate.
- There is no middle ground.
- So what is the answer?
Caesar is our dearest friend,
but what he is doing is--
I do not know.
You must decide.
Pompey then.
We must go with Pompey.
The Republic is more important
than any friendship.
- Do you agree?
- It's your decision.
Pompey then.
We have no time to lose.
Tell your women to be ready
to leave as soon as possible.
I'm not leaving.
What do you mean?
I've waited eight years
for Caesar.
I cannot leave now.
You cannot stay,
not if I go.
Of course I can stay.
I can do as I wish.
Mother, all who stay
are enemies of Rome.
- Pompey has declared it.
- Caesar might prevail.
Yes, he might rule Rome for a week,
a month, a year even,
but then some other
ambitious man
will kill him
and take his place,
and you then will be
the mistress of a dead tyrant.
Mother, we know
what happens to them.
That is
for the gods decide.
I cannot help
loving him.
A va, Mother!
You-- you are blinded
by untapped lust.
I'll get you a good big Cyrenian
at the market and have done with it.
You'd better go.
Don't be angry with me.
We may be parted
for a long time.
Come.
Goodbye, Mother.
Goodbye, my love.
Your daughter left.
When?
Just now. I put a boy
to following her.
I'll put a stop
to this nonsense.
- Fetch your men.
- What?
Now.
Why have you not
left the city?
I could not leave
without seeing you.
It's not safe for you. Everyone
knows you're with Pompey.
Don't fret.
I'll be gone by sunrise.
- That's all I have.
- Thank you,
but this is not
a robbery.
- Atia.
- I'll give you a moment,
if there are gods
you'd like to speak to.
One favor--
let my men live.
Sorry.
It's orders.
Give me your sword.
What are they,
the stars?
Stars? Holes in
the celestial spheres.
Holes through which the light
of the heavens shine.
How big
are these holes?
They're big.
They only seem small to us because
they're hundreds of miles away.
Big enough for a man
to climb through?
I suppose.
But man would never be able
to get up there in the first place.
- I don't see why not.
- How?
He could hold
onto a giant bird.
It doesn't work
like that.
- Why not?
- It's philosophy.
It's hard to explain.
Really, Numa,
that's quite unnecessary.
I beg you stand.
There shall be
no formality here,
not between
old friends like us.
A thousand gratitudes
Atia.
We humbly seek the protection
and friendship of your family.
Sadly, there are some
people who say
that I am
of the Pompeian faction.
Are you not?
All of Pompey's faction
have long since fled.
You stay for fear your factories
and storehouses will be looted.
I assure you,
that's not true--
Castor.
- 5,000 denarii.
- That much?
- l-l--
- Please, let us not be vulgar.
I'll make the arrangements
immediately.
Where is your man Durio?
He is long overdue now.
Durio is
the best man I have.
He won't fail.
But if not, what then?
How do we pay the legions?
How do we feed them?
I have not the least idea.
You fret like a woman, Cato.
Durio will return with more than
enough gold to feed and pay the legions.
By any road we'll be back
in Rome before spring,
so stop worrying.
It makes no sense.
We should have been
stopped by now.
Why is Rome
not defended?
Our boys
scared 'em off, eh?
Soldiers of the Republic
do not run,
- so it must be a stratagem or trick.
- Then it's a good trick.
Unless the gods
have abandoned Rome.
If Mars was watching,
he would not allow
such a disgrace.
Well, maybe he was having
a crap and missed it.
It's that sort of disrespect that has
led us to this sad pass.
If the gods are not respected,
then why should they help us?
Still no troops.
They will have flanked us,
I expect.
Perhaps these drovers
know something.
Whoa.
- Salve, citizens.
- Captain.
- You come from the city?
- We do.
- How goes it there?
- You're Caesar's men.
- We are.
- Fortune spreads her legs for you.
Pompey has fled.
The city is yours.
- Why would Pompey flee?
- You boys were too fast for him.
He couldn't raise
his armies quick enough.
Him and his men are retreating south,
and the Senate with 'em.
See?
Wrong for once.
Well, uh, enjoy
your victory boys.
- How much do you want for the girl?
- Not for sale.
What's in the wagon?
- Grain.
- Show us, soldier.
There's no soldiers here.
My mistake. You all wear
the soldier's boot,
so I assumed you are
soldiers, but I'm wrong.
But why would nine good
soldiers be guarding a grain wagon?
I don't have
to show you nothing.
Hyah!
My fidelity always,
Domina.
I do not like
to doubt you, Proculus,
but it's an age since I have seen
you at my morning levy.
Perhaps you have been unwell.
Goiters is it?
Ah, uh--
goiters, as you say.
Fat, greedy men
often find it so.
I shall kill an owl that
your good health continue.
Speak sense,
you creature.
What vile trade is this,
bringing corpses to honest doors?!
Take it away!
See what you have done?
The city's unguarded.
It's true then.
The Republic is fallen.
Yet the sky is still above us,
and the earth still below.
- Strange.
- The gods are in no hurry.
They will take their time
in tormenting us.
Let's go back and see what's in
that wagon. Untie that girl.
Not our concern.
We follow orders.
Advance until
resistance is met.
- But that poor girl--
- You will do your duty.
You are a mean bastard,
that's your problem.
You've no love in you.
You can talk sweet as you like to
Niobe, it won't do you any good.
She won't believe a word.
Ercule,
you wake at last.
I was worried.
Water?
My poor baby.
Oh, it was
not a dream then.
Glabius is dead.
He is.
I'm sorry.
Why do you look
at me like that?
Like what?
As  if I--
- Did you?
- How can you ask me that question?
Did you?
I did not!
And I'm tortured
that you would harbor
- such a horrible notion.
- Look at me!
Daughter, I swear on the masks
of all my ancestors
that I had nothing--
nothing to do with the
killing of Glabius.
Who do you think
did it, Mother?
The streets are full
of corpses.
It could have
been anyone.
"These are the words
of Gaius Julius Caesar,
direct descendant of Venus,
Proconsul of Gaul,
Glorious lmperato
of the northern legions.
Citizens,
I have returned to ltaly
with the sole intention of claiming
my legal and moral rights.
I have no desire
for unlawful powers.
I will name
no man an enemy
who does not
so declare himself.
Even so, the property of
those enemies will not be appropriated
and their person
will remain inviolate
as long as their opposition
be peaceful.
Moreover, to any man that
has taken arms against me
and now regrets it,
I gladly offer total amnesty.
However, those that continue
to use violence
to oppose my legal rights,
they shall receive that
which they seek to give.
Under the auspices
of Jupiter Capitolinus,
these are the words
of Gaius Julius Caesar."
What are you doing?
I have done my duty
and I have sinned enough.
I resign.
That's desertion.
I am a traitor and a rebel,
why not
a deserter as well?
You can't just leave
the 13th.
Goodbye, Pullo.
To Venus, the birth giver,
I make this sacrifice.
I am Lucius of the Vorenian
clan, tribe of Stellatina,
formerly First Spear Centurion
to the Prime Cohort
of the 13th Legion.
I have a wife.
Her name is Niobe.
Venus, let her love me
as I love her.
I give my blood
to make it so.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to scare you.
You're very beautiful.
I've come to see that
it may be, through ignorance,
that I have not
treated you as I should.
- As I should treat you.
- Please, don't.
When we married
you had only 13 summers,
and soon enough
I was gone.
But now you are a woman,
and I know nothing of women.
Soldiering is all I know.
Which is not useful.
I have been sullen
and untrusting and cold.
But I am not made
of stone.
I can change.
I will swear on the life
of my daughter's son.
I will change,
if you would have it so.
Please, speak if you
would not have it so,
and I will leave
without rancor.
- It is I have done wrong.
- How so?
I am...
I have not been...
The past is gone.
Can we start again?
Ha!
I applaud you.
You're about to enter Rome
as a bloodstained conqueror,
and yet you look as calm
as a cup of water.
I am glad I appear so.
Gracchus,
something more cheerful.