Dear me,
I've never seen
so many long faces.
It is customary
to be sad at a funeral.
Well, the Republic
is old and infirm.
Death can be a merciful
release in such cases.
You do not mean that.
You don't believe that.
You of all people
shouldn't lay jokes
- about tyranny.
- Oh, I am deadly serious.
It is in all our
interests
to be reconciled
with Caesar now,
for the good of Rome.
The good of Rome indeed.
As soon as this...
farce is done,
I shall retire
to the country
and wait for the city
to come to its senses.
It is the only
honorable thing to do.
My dear friend,
we have no honor.
If we had honor,
we would be
with Cato and Scipio
in the afterlife.
First, Senate will hear
Marcus Tullius Cicero.
On this eve of his
most glorious triumph,
I move that
Gaius Julius Caesar
be made lmperator
and granted absolute
power over Rome
for a period
of 10 years.
As some of you know,
Caesar and I have
had our disagreements.
However that may be,
he has shown himself
to be as wise
and merciful in victory
as he was
invincible in battle.
Let this be an end
to division
and civil strife.
I willingly pledge
my loyalty to him,
and I urge you all
to do the same.
I heartily commend
the motion proposed
by Marcus Tullius Cicero.
The motion
is carried unanimously.
Many of you here today
fought against me.
Many of you
wished me dead.
perhaps still do.
But I hold no grudges
and seek no revenge.
I demand only this--
that you join with me
in building a new Rome,
a Rome that offers
justice, peace and land
to all its citizens,
not just
the privileged few.
Support me
in this task,
and old divisions
will be forgotten.
Oppose me...
and Rome will not forgive
you a second time.
Senators...
the war is over.
Domina.
Mmm?
Atia of the Julii
is here.
Atia?
Here, now.
She wishes
to see you.
Atia...
in my house?
My dear Atia.
How lovely to see you.
Bona dea.
My poor friend.
What have they
done to you?
You're so sweet.
Come sit down.
I'm very sorry
I haven't visited sooner,
but to be honest, I was far
too upset to face seeing you.
The very idea, it's--
it's too sinister.
A noblewoman stripped
naked and beaten on the streets--
horrible. Horrible.
Tell me truly,
how are you now?
I'm recovering
very well.
Have they found
the culprits yet?
They have not, but justice
will find them eventually.
I'm quite sure
of that.
Would you have
some lemon water?
That would be lovely.
- Brutus is well, I hope.
- He is.
It's so wise of him to choose
submission to my dear uncle.
I was very afraid
he might try
some foolish act
of bravery.
Men are so silly
about their honor. No?
I've come to ask you
if you will sit with me
at the triumph.
Even though I'm being
besieged by sycophants
asking for space,
I thought, "No,
if someone were
to have first choice,
it should be
my dear friend Servilia
who's been
through so much pain."
That is very
thoughtful of you...
but I think I shall not
be well enough.
Well, that's a pity.
- Are you sure?
- I am.
- Well, if you change your mind--
- I will let you know.
People tell me that
Octavia's left the city,
but no one knows where.
I hope there's
nothing amiss.
Not at all.
She's staying at my
cousin's villa in Paestum,
mooning over some young
fool of a poet she's met there.
She'll be back
in time for the triumph.
Brother.
What are you doing here?
I've come
to take you home.
- This is my home.
- This? This is not your home.
I'm happy here.
I don't believe you.
In any case, your
place is with your family.
Bad enough
to run away,
but to these people?
This isn't the healthy way of life.
You call
our family healthy?
Our corruption stinks
in the nostrils of Mother Earth.
This is your
foreign priests talking.
They are frauds.
They only want your money.
Priests are nobody.
They are just servants here.
This is
the Great Mother's house.
The Great Mother
wants nothing from me.
- I'm a worm in her sight.
- You are not a worm.
You are a daughter
of the Julii.
It looks very ill,
you running away like this.
Reflects badly
on the whole family
if it were known publicly.
For a moment I thought
you wanted me back
- because you missed me.
- Don't be silly.
We've missed you
terribly.
Your mother
has missed you.
I believe even
the servants and animals
- have missed you.
- And you?
And I.
I've missed you.
I can't go back.
What's done is done.
I forgive you.
Your mother forgives you.
You forgive me?
Mother forgives me?
What if I don't forgive?
Whatever you think
she may have done,
consider the possibility
she did it
out of love for you.
I'll never forgive her.
Be that as it may,
your forgiveness is irrelevant.
You must come home.
I'm sorry,
I will not.
I don't want
to use force.
The priests
will protect me.
They won't.
I've bought them.
Quite cheaply.
I beg you,
Iet me stay here.
What have you done?
Fellow citizens
of the Aventine!
Fellow citizens!
Fellow citizens
of the Aventine!
My name is
Lucius Vorenus,
tribe of Stellatina,
veteran of the 1 3th Legion.
Some of you
may know me.
I bring you
good news.
Caesar has put an end
to patrician tyranny,
and will ensure
that the common people
- be heard once more.
- Go back to Gaul, ginger knob.
I'll not deny it, friend,
I have a Gallic look about me,
but I'm as solid Roman
as you are.
I've shed blood
for Rome.
My father shed blood
for Rome,
as did his father
and his father before him.
My wife-- my wife was
born here in the Aventine!
I am as solid a Roman
as any man here!
If I am elected
as your local magistrate,
I promise
on Jupiter's stone
to strive to make this
an era of peace,
prosperity and justice
for all Aventine.
Tomorrow
Caesar holds a triumph,
a symbol of his love
for the people of Rome.
- Cac!
- Why don't you shut up, you--
Ladylike, madam,
ladylike.
Five days
of feasting and games
as appreciation
for the trust and support
the people of Rome
have given Caesar.
Freedom, more like!
We've given him our freedom
and our honor!
I would not be standing
here on Caesar's slate
if I did not believe,
if I did not know
that he has
only the Republic's
best interests at heart.
"A new era."
"Tomorrow's triumph,
a new era."
With tomorrow's triumph,
a new era begins.
For all Aventine.
For all Rome.
- It was good. You did well.
- Thank you.
King of all the Gauls.
Makes you think,
doesn't it?
It does.
Goodbye, old friend.
Do your best to tidy him up.
He looks dead already.
Found you at last,
you bastards.
I've been through
the whole damned army.
The famous Titus Pullo.
To what do we owe this honor, citizen?
Do you come to wish us luck?
Listen, I've got most of my kit,
but I've lost my crest.
Surely someone's got
a spare, you think?
It's only a crest.
It's not like I lost my sword.
Well, you can't
march with us.
You've left the Legion.
You signed yourself out.
I know, but...
13th forever, eh?
It's enlisted men only
in the triumph. You're a civilian.
Civilian?
I'm the hero of the whole
mumping Legion, I am.
I saved your skin more than once.
Shouldn't have to remind you of that.
If you want to sign up
for a few more years,
that's a different story. You can
march with us till your feet are nubs.
Haven't I spilled enough
blood for the 13th?
Don't be like that.
I don't fucking make
the rules, do l? I follow them.
It's enlisted men only.
Don't push it.
If you come by after,
I'll stand you some drinks, eh?
Stand me some drinks?
I've got better things
to do than go drinking
- with the likes of you.
- Well, walk on then, citizen.
Walk on!
Right, ladies,
on your feet!
Time to look
like soldiers!
Is this too much?
- Just enough, I'd say.
- I don't know.
I think it's too purple.
I want to suggest purple
without actually
wearing it.
It will look less loud
in direct light.
- What do you think?
- Jupiter in life.
Resemblance is uncanny.
What do you find
amusing?
It's absurd, isn't it?
Dressing up,
playing at being God?
Playing?
I'm not playing.
This is not a game.
As you wish.
It is not a game.
Something more red.
- Is the canal around the circus filled?
- It is.
It was not last night.
- I saw to it at first light.
- Very good.
Make sure the elephants are
given their emetics in good time.
I don't want my chariot
slowed by giant turds.
You are looking
much better.
I am not better,
however.
Well, I must get you
out to the country, perhaps.
Some fresh air and sunshine
would do you good.
This lying abed
is not healthy.
I rise when I have
reason to do so.
Don't loiter here
pretending to be solicitous.
Go to your friend's
obscene display.
Mother...
Go.
Do you want some color
on your cheeks?
Please, darling,
say something.
This horrid
silent business,
it's most upsetting.
- What did they do to you?
- They did nothing.
She speaks.
There's a start.
They were
very kind to me.
Kind enough to let you
hack away at yourself
Iike a side of pork.
My poor little grump.
Oh, I didn't realize
until now how much I missed
your gloomy presence
around the place.
Domina...
there's a beggar at the door
who says he is Quintus,
natural son of Pompey.
He asks for your son's
protection.
Send him away.
- Take your hands off me!
- Get out!
Brutus!
Scared to talk to me,
eh, coward?
You're a coward,
Brutus!
I swear by Janus,
Jupiter and Juno,
I swear on the grave
of my father,
I, Quintus Valerius Pompey,
I'm going to kill
that son of a whore tyrant!
I'll get Ajax
to deal with him.
- He's a bastard traitor to Rome...
- Wait.
and you're
a traitor too, Brutus!
Pompey's
natural son, eh?
I am.
I gather at least you're
still no friend to Caesar.
I'll burn him alive.
- I will pluck out his eyes, l--
- Shh shh.
Be calm.
You're among friends.
All will  be well.
Have him washed and fed.
Caesar! Caesar!
Glorious Caesar!
The gods
favor you, Caesar!
Caesar! Caesar!
"Tables for 5000 men
will be set up
in the cattle forum.
Slaves and freedmen
are not eligible.
Those citizens
that cannot find
a proper seating place
must leave
when ordered
by the civic officers.
Gaius Julius Caesar
has decreed
in tribute
to their virtue,
each and every
citizen of Rome
will be issued
from the public treasury
the sum
of 100 denarii."
"Further,
20,000 deserving
families
will be given farms
on the public lands
around Capua."
"Further,
for the coming year,
all rents--
all rents
on low dwellings
in the city
will be paid in full
by Gaius Julius Caesar."
Very noble
and very nicely expressed,
if I may say so.
Might I have
a quiet word?
Of course.
A quiet word.
Oh, you may speak
in front of Quintus.
As you wish.
It is of Quintus I speak.
The good man has been here
several days now.
Perhaps he grows weary of
entertaining us with his happy presence.
Do not mind him, Quintus.
He has no manners.
He shall stay
as long as it pleases me.
Well, that's
the thing, Mother.
I do not see
in what way he could
possibly please you.
What is his purpose?
Does he help you
to write poetry?
- He has a good ear.
- lndeed? Hmm.
- You surprise me.
- He has fire in him.
It warms me.
Light more lamps
if you are cold!
It looks very ill to keep
a son of Pompey in our house.
And we should strike
such fine figures otherwise!
So you see,
the fourth clause
of the previous statute only
applies in cases of fire and flood,
unless otherwise stipulated
in the appendix.
- Do you see?
- Not clearly.
I'm not sure I can
explain it in simpler terms.
Surely this can wait
until after the election.
There's no point
learning all this if I lose.
You will not lose.
You're very sure of that.
There are other candidates.
I believe I warned you
about mocking me.
Forgive me, sir. I had thought
you understood the system.
The other candidates
are straw men.
Straw men?
It saves a great deal
of useless strife
if there's no opposition,
but it would look ill
if Caesar's man was
the only one standing.
These facts
disturb you somehow?
The elections are sanctioned
by Jupiter Capitolinus.
They are sacred.
Caesar also is sanctioned
by Jupiter, is he not?
By augury,
by triumph,
by acclaim
of the people.
Anything he does
is sacred.
In a way,
he is a demigod.
For one day only.
For the rest, he is
a mortal man like you and me.
Mortal or not, he is trying
to save the Republic.
By corrupting
the elections?
The Roman people are not
crying out for clean elections.
They are crying out
for jobs.
for clean water, for food,
for stability and peace.
You can do great things
for your people.
You can help
save the Republic.
Or you can go back to your shop
and resume selling mutton and pig,
have dirty hands
but a clean conscience.
So what do you say?
Say to what?
You haven't heard
a word I've been saying.
Is everything all right?
Forgive me.
So what was it
you needed?
I want to free Eirene,
take her off to the country,
- if you'll lend me some money.
- Of course.
And I'll need you to come
with me to the slave registry,
- to vouch your name for my ownership.
- Slow down. Why are you freeing Eirene?
- Can't marry her otherwise.
- Marry her?
Look, I've--
I've been feeling
strange and low
and empty
these last months, and...
anyway, I've puzzled it out,
and I realized what it was.
I love Eirene.
I love her, and I want her
to bear my children
and be my wife, and...
Congratulations,
I suppose.
So you'll be going
to the country, you say?
Leaving Rome?
Rome's no place for me.
I need clean air,
room to move.
And what will you do
when you get there?
There's always work
for a good man with a sword.
Well, as long
as you're sure.
Oh, I've thought it
through.
I've never been so sure
of anything in my life.
I'm happy for you.
I hope you find
your path.
Still here?
I thought you were
retiring to the country
as a point of honor.
You do right
to mock me.
You make me feel small.
A joke, old man, a joke.
I'm always happy for your company.
So, why didn't you
tell me beforehand?
I could have been
of assistance perhaps.
What are you
talking about?
Everyone is reading it!
I saw some temple
prostitutes with a copy.
"A call to virtue."
The writing is... adequate,
which is something
we should talk about,
but the sentiments are
full of grace
and bravery.
"Sons of the Republic,
the blood of our forefathers
calls you to honor the memory
and emulate the deeds
of Porcius Cato,
the last true Roman."
Who wrote this?
You did.
Gods beneath us!
Mother!
Mother, have you seen this?
This lunacy?
Of course I've seen it.
It's not lunacy.
It is a cogent defense
of Republican principles
against the forces
of tyranny.
I am rather
proud of it.
You wrote this?
In my name?
Cassius contributed
several nice
turns of phrase.
You know Cassius,
of course.
Of course.
Delighted.
Quintus.
It's lovely
to see you again.
- It's been too long.
- lndeed.
You will excuse me
if I speak
with my mother privately?
I'm deeply sorry
you feel I have failed you,
but this--
this is going too far.
My name is not yours
to be used--
You haven't failed me.
You can't fail me,
I'm your mother.
- You have failed the Republic.
- Dear gods!
Bring me a pen and paper.
It's bad enough
that you keep that little
madman Quintus in this house,
but this-- this!
- I don't know what to tell him.
- Why don't you
fall on your knees and
kiss his feet and beg for mercy?
- It served you in the past.
- But not you.
Eh? Perhaps you did not
beg hard enough.
You...
you do understand...
he might have me
killed for this?
Rome has fallen into
the hands of a corrupt monster.
You, direct descendant
of the father
of the Republic,
what do you do?
What would you
have me do?
What would
your father have done?
What would his father have done?
Would they bend their knees
- to a tyrant?
- They would take account
of the specific
circumstan--
They would chase him
out of the city like any mad dog.
Chased him out?
And how am l
to do that exactly?
You would not be alone.
Ah, these fine men
in the house
are very very good.
I am reassured.
They are good men.
And there are many others,
men of rank and wisdom.
It is not
a dog gone mad.
I would rather be mad
than disgrace our name.
No more!
You send your fool
henchmen away...
and forget
this insanity.
- Brutus.
- Ah, Cassius, it's lovely to see you,
but, as you can see--
Of course,
forgive the intrusion.
Perhaps I may visit
another time.
Good. Certainly.
On Jupiter's stone,
you're a full Roman citizen,
and you attest to this man's
ownership of listed property?
I am. I do.
Sign here.
Any kind of mark
will do.
I can write my name
as good as the next man.
Done.
42. 42 up.
Eirene.
Come over here.
I want to talk to you.
I'll leave you to it.
I've been to the registrar
of slaves. You're no longer my slave.
You've sold me?
Oh, please don't sell me.
Don't send me away.
I beg you.
I'm setting you free.
You're free.
It says so here.
Thank you.
You're the kindest man alive.
I love you, sir.
Here. Here.
It's a dress.
Um, go try it on.
Let's see
how it looks.
Titus Pullo, sir.
I cannot thank you enough.
Thank me? What are you
thanking me for, boy?
For freeing her. We have
been saving to buy our freedom,
but we never--
to happen so soon.
I cannot tell you
what a gift it is.
You've both been saving?
You and Eirene?
We thought to take
the Vorenus name as ours
when we became freedmen,
but Eirene says
it must be under your name
she becomes my wife.
Wife?
Legal wife, I mean.
We are already married
in our hearts.
Eirene?
My Eirene?
Sir?
Sir!
- Dead?
- Looks like.
- What happened?
- I killed him. I did it.
I can see that, but why?
Why did you do this?
- It doesn't matter.
- It does matter, though.
It matters to me.
This boy was my property.
- He angered me.
- He angered you?
He-- he and Eirene,
they were--
So what does that matter?
Did you think she was a virgin?
She's still yours
to use as you wish.
I love her.
This is
how you prove it?
This is no charnel house
to kill people as you want.
This is my home.
My home!
Shh.
You do this violence
before my children?!
I'm sorry.
- Shh, shh.
- Silence!
I'll pay you back.
Pay me back with what,
you damn fool?
You've got no money
but what I've given you.
But please...
do not call me a fool.
I'll call you what I like.
You're a damn fool.
I don't care
about the money.
It's the disrespect.
Look at what you did!
Look at him!
Shh.
Maybe you're right.
Probably am a fool.
Never was a clever one
like you.
Never demoted, you,
never flogged, never locked up.
Straight to the top.
And here you are,
with your nice, clean,
white toga.
Lovely cloth, that.
Stays clean
no matter how much
you wade in the filth.
- Speak your mind.
- As you will.
Time was, you said Caesar
was a rebel and a traitor.
And now, today, he tosses
you some coin and some farmland,
and he's savior of the Republic,
and you're kissing his royal ass.
You stand up.
Stand up! Stand up!
I'll not fight you.
Then go.
Go and do not
come back here.
Go. Go! And do not
Eirene, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Stay away from her.
Right.
Sorry.
I had no idea.
I must go now.
You-- you do
believe me?
My dear friend,
of course I believe you.
You have never
lied to me.
Besides, why would you
put your name to a thing
- and then deny it?
- Well, exactly.
And anyone-- anyone may
forge my name to a thing
to give it weight.
We shall just have
to become used to it, no doubt.
I wonder who it was
that wrote it.
I wish I knew.
Someone of talent.
Anyhow, I've seldom seen
a bad case so well put.
I shall have
to write a reply.
Well, as long as you
and I know where we stand.
Where do we stand?
I hope we are the best
of friends. Are we?
We are, we are.
Brutus, I have
never doubted
your friendship
or fidelity.
Even when
we were enemies.
Titus Pullo.
You look tired,
my friend.
- I'm drunk.
- These are hard times for war veterans.
You're right there.
Too many soldiers
back in Rome.
Not enough work to go round.
It's a sad situation.
But it's a crime
to see a man of
your ability unemployed.
I'm doing fine.
I have plenty
of irons in the fire.
Well, if your prospects
don't work out,
you can ask on any street
in the Aventine
for Erastes Fulman.
I will always have
a job for you.
I'm a soldier,
not a murderer.
These days, Pullo,
is there really any difference?
Have a drink on me.
When you've sobered up,
come and see me.
We'll talk
a little business.