To be honest with you, I can't...
see myself dating, like,
women in the future.
- Wow.
- Yeah, I would date a man...
and it's kind of nice just to
get that kind of off your chest.
Like, I moved
out here with a guy, and
then when things got rough, he...
was abusing. Your pool of men,
it gets thinner as you... once you
tell them that you're... you're trans.
Like, I've failed relationship
after failed relationship,
and I can't figure out why.
- He's cute.
- Gorgeous.
Miss Candis has a date tonight.
I'm alone, waiting
for somebody with a drink,
and nobody's showing up.
I got to go back to New York
to get the Glamour
Woman of The Year Award.
Caitlyn!
Kylie was supposed to be my date,
but she's had a wardrobe malfunction.
My vagina was out.
Not my boob, my vagina.
It has been so
long since I have performed,
so I am a little nervous.
Chandelier!
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Hello.
- Hi!
- Good morning.
- We're in winter wonderland
- this morning.
- I know.
Full snowstorm in New Mexico.
- Yeah.
- Of course.
This is like home
in New York. This is fine.
I'm good with this.
- Breakfast!
- Good morning.
Morning.
Great. I
believe Miss Candis Cayne
has a date tonight.
- Tonight?
- Tonight.
I took the liberty of creating a profile.
- Mm-hm.
- I just wanted to make an announcement
that we've succeeded...
finding a date for Candis Cayne.
Go, CC.
- So, what's your type, Candis?
- The A type.
- A pulse.
- So you're looking for tall,
dark and handsome?
I can't believe that even Candis,
an absolutely gorgeous woman,
has to do online dating.
I've never realized, or
certainly have experienced,
the issues, uh, when it
comes to trans women dating.
Uh, Candis has been out
there for a long time,
uh, never been married but had
some very long relationships.
But right now, she doesn't.
She's kind of footloose
and fancy free, so, if that's
really important to her,
hey, Candis, go for it.
- I'm disillusioned with it all.
- Are you not excited?
Uh, not really.
After the stimulating conversation
we've had over politics...
- Yes!
- ... that would be like nothing!
That would be nothing!
It would be like sleeping.
You might find it more of a relief.
I have to say that my online
dating experience so far
has been dismal. I don't go out to clubs,
I don't really do anything
but work or go home,
and so I thought online
dating would be a good way
to meet guys and meet somebody that
I'm compatible with, that I like.
We got a couple
things to open here,
and it's extraordinarily significant.
Drumroll, please.
Drumroll!
Everybody ready! Whoa...
Whoa!
It's official!
We're legal!
In the trans community,
proper identification is a big issue.
To get a job, to travel.
I cannot believe you came
all the way down here,
early in the morning, to support me.
Do you understand how important a...
DMV photo is?
Hey, guys.
You're here for the big day!
Okay, guys, we got the picture.
I need to add some good lighting
and light you the right way.
Yeah, baby.
Look straight ahead.
Congratulations!
Congrats.
For Kourtney and Kim to come in
to kind of be at my side,
and to have that process done
for me was really important.
The picture came out great!
Yeah.
Yeah, that's...
You know what?
I noticed it when my social
security card came through.
It's almost, like,
a whole part of my life.
Like kind of throwing old Bruce...
out the door.
You know, he was a very good person.
Did a lot of
good things in his life.
And sometimes I feel like
maybe he didn't deserve to be...
gone.
And I probably held
that in for a long time.
But at some point in your life,
after all of the other things
you're... you gotta say, "Aw,
(bleep), I gotta move forward."
Yes.
And, uh...
it's not that I ever wanted to
throw him away...
but, uh...
anyway, it's just a
significant... you know?
You look at this,
and not only done a gender
marker, name's changed,
the picture's changed,
all that sort of stuff...
- it's a totally... different person.
- Mm-hmm.
And certainly not that
that old person was a bad person,
- just wasn't me.
- Right.
So when you see this...
pretty significant.
You know?
- Yeah.
- Congratulations.
- Well, thank you.
It is kind of symbolic that
I get my driver's license
a couple of days before,
uh, I have to fly to New York
to get Glamour's Woman of the Year Award.
Which, to me, is, unbelievable.
So I'd like to take,
in the future, all the great
qualities that he had, and, um,
put him into her, and move forward.
Remember, this award is for all of us,
it's not just about me, that is for sure.
Hi, ladies.
- Hi.
- Some tequila?
- Why not? Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- She certainly would.
- Oh, absolutely.
- Thank you.
_
You need more moral
support? You know what to do.
You would think, but I don't know.
Yeah.
Where's the picture of this guy?
You gotta be hard to get, girl.
Your biggest problem is, you
gotta get this guy past me.
You know? And so...
- I'm watching.
- That might be kind of awkward with the...
I've never been, in my entire
life, a, like, a big dater,
like I was going out all the time.
So for me in the future,
dating as a trans woman,
I don't see myself, like,
obsessed, with something like that.
I see the girls being rejected
a lot, when it comes to dating,
and I don't want that in my life.
And so yeah, the rejection
thing kind of scares me.
I keep on looking at that door.
Why aren't you just sitting at the bar?
- What time is he coming?
- I should be sitting at the bar, waiting.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I think I'm gonna go
find a seat somewhere and
wait for him to arrive.
- Where is he?
- He's ten minutes late already.
Honestly, I feel kind of embarrassed.
I'm alone, waiting for
somebody with a drink,
and nobody's showing up. It's insulting.
Why am I doing this to myself again?
Girl.
- Oh, yes, honey.
- You are a vision.
I just messaged him and said,
"When are you coming by?"
- And what did he say?
- Um, he hasn't responded yet.
- Did he show up?
- He didn't show up.
Could you be stood up?
You're laughing?
- No, no, no, no...
- You're laughing.
I'm not laugh... I'm not laughing.
- You're totally laughing.
- No, I'm not laughing.
- No.
- I got stood up.
I would be devastated.
I think it takes a lot of guts for Candis
to be sitting at the bar, waiting
for this "date" to show up;
it is not easy at all.
I think, for me, at this point,
I... I don't even want to deal with it.
Was he supposed to show up
at a certain time, or no?
- Yeah, and he never did.
- He's a dog!
- As most of them are.
- We don't like him already.
- Aren't they all?
- Yeah.
We're in the new millennium.
I'm sick and tired of men who feel like
they have the upper hand on trans women.
- you.
- Right.
- I'm sorry. I'm over it.
- I like that attitude.
I love it when you cuss.
Let's go.
Have you guys ever
been around chickens before?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Not Silkie chickens.
To help your mind/body
experience healthy living,
this resort does animal therapy.
So we're just gonna pet Silkie chickens.
They're really, really soft...
- it's almost like petting a cat.
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm. Come on out.
- All right. Oh, my God.
Wow.
So, chickens are part of
our animal interaction here,
'cause they've actually
shown that lowers your anxiety
and your stress levels. Each one
has a really different personality.
Just like our group of trans women.
_
These guys are notoriously hard
to actually tell who are boys and girls.
Story of our life.
Well, it really got me thinking
about petting cocks.
But you should...
- Hey, Cayne!
- Yeah?
- Are you ready to get it down?
- I am ready.
- We are going dancing, girl.
- Yes. For our, you know,
two-woman show that we're gonna do.
I, uh...
I really wanted to
have us all go to salsa
class, but mostly Caitlyn,
because I want her to start getting
in touch with her feminine side.
- Hi, ladies.
- Hi! Hello!
And it would be a bonus
if there are some really cute guys there.
My name is Carlos Mora,
and I'm gonna be the instructor today,
and I will explain to
you the steps of salsa
which are very, very simple,
and then we'll just line up in couples.
Okay, so we're gonna start the class.
- Can anybody tell me when salsa dancing was invented?
- _
_
- With what?
- _
_
Whatever makes you feel comfortable.
I lost my appetite
when that went down. I was like, ugh!
- Oh, well...
- The restaurant owner didn't want us there.
He found out what show it was for,
and he said, "No, you
can't film here anymore."
What is holding you back from...
just going on a date with someone?
Thought about bringing up to Kylie,
"I should start dating or
doing something like that."
I just, I... I can't
even bring the subject up.
_
With what?
Whatever makes you feel comfortable.
_
Honestly, Caitlyn hasn't really embraced
those sides of her feminine self yet.
But this isn't like speed
dating, this is a dance class,
we're doing salsa, and that's usually
pretty normal to have male dancers.
Which way do we start with?
Which way do we start?
- Is it this way or am I that way?
- It's this way, yeah.
... and five, six, seven.
And one, two, three...
and five, six, seven.
Come on, I can shake
it just as good as you can.
I was too busy on shaking it.
First of all, who wouldn't
want to dance with Candis?
She's a great dancer, great, perfect.
I was too back on my heel.
I
just feel uncomfortable,
especially if you get
some guy who I don't know
who the heck he is.
I am just not ready to
put myself out there.
- I'm gonna stick with Candis.
- Rotate.
We're not rotating.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
- That was fun.
- You did it.
- That was so much fun.
- That was fun.
I think I'm ready.
First commercial road trip.
God, it's great!
You get to use your driver's
license for the first time.
All those people,
all those people, yeah.
- You have your license?
- Oh, I got it.
Okay. Just making sure.
All right. I
got to leave the trip.
I got to go back to New York
to get the Glamour
Woman of the Year Award.
- Have a great journey. You're gonna be great.
- Thank you.
- Okay. I'll get through it, I promise you.
- You're gonna be great.
I'll represent.
I'm quite nervous about this.
Kylie's gonna meet me in
New York... she's my date.
- It's a really big deal.
- You'll do well,
- and we'll... we'll be here for you
- I appreciate it.
- ... when you come back.
- Oh, don't worry, I'll find you in Chicago.
- Good.
- Okay.
So, Jason, where we headed to?
- Into Tulsa.
- Tulsa?
Tulsa, Oklahoma?
The trans guy, I don't
know if guys you're familiar,
Arin Andrews, lives there.
- He was on Barney's with his...
- The fashion spread.
Yeah. And he's really (bleep) cute.
Oh, we love it!
- Hella.
- Yeah.
Well, if we can figure
it out, you should definitely
hang out with him. That would be great.
That would be awesome.
I'm super excited, really,
to go to Chicago, to see Mimi.
She's one of my best friends.
She's a showgirl.
She's been working at the
Baton for, like, 25 years.
- Nothing like a good drag show.
- Yeah.
All the rigmarole
- and kinky things that go on...
- Yes.
... back there,
I really miss those days.
I was thinking that maybe
we can go and see her at the Baton.
Maybe I would do a number
with her and Chandi.
Oh... oh, yes, please.
No. I'm here to support you girls.
I know, but you were
saying you were kind of missing
- the old Chandelier days.
- You used to do drag?
- I did!
- Oh, my goodness!
I used to. I think
about those days a lot.
And I would love to
perform again someday soon.
Performing is such a great outlet for me.
Not all performers are men.
Just like Candis Cayne.
She's a trans woman
who likes to perform and entertain.
I feel such happiness when
I'm on that stage, shining,
- getting my life.
- I've never been to a drag show.
Oh, my goodness, you are in store
for a treat.
Who's hungry?
Oh, this is perfectly okay.
_
They wouldn't allow us in here,
which is horrible for them, because, um,
you know, a lot of people
see this show, so it would be
some good promotion for them.
I lost my appetite when
that went down. I was like, ugh!
Oh, well...
But, you know, it is, what it is.
It is really kind of a bummer the
restaurant owner didn't want us there.
Um, we were allowed to film, and then...
he found out what show
it was for and he said,
"No, you can't film here
anymore," he's not interested.
We're so used to living
in our... our bubble...
- Our bubble of acceptance.
- ... that everything is happy and accepting.
But this is something we
can look forward to experiencing,
being down this way, though.
In the South.
It's a little weird, you know?
C'est la vie.
- All right, let's do it.
- Oh, God.
- He's cute.
- Gorgeous.
I know, right?
Laith is getting it in!
Kylie says she's coming,
but we'll see. She
hasn't made it here yet.
So I got to do the red
carpet all by myself,
and to be honest with
you, that is very scary.
Caitlyn! Caitlyn!
What's going on?
You're on speaker now, Mom.
- We're in the van.
- Hi, Mom.
- Oh, okay.
- There's Candis, and there's Ella,
JB's up there, too.
_
We're on our way rock climbing.
Oh! Okay.
- You guys take care. Okay.
- All right.
- Bye-bye.
- Hi.
- How are you? Candis.
- Hi, Candis. Laith.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, Candis. I'm Arin.
- Hi. Ella.
- Nice to meet you.
So, actually, Arin told me that
Laith Ashley, another trans guy who
he did his Barney's campaign with,
is also in town, so we're gonna
get two for the price of one, so...
Whoo, whoo!
I'm so glad this all worked out.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Are you all gonna be climbing as well?
Well, we're all curious.
That's safe, that's safe.
All right, let's do it.
Laith is getting it in!
We need you all the way at
the top, Candis, like Laith.
- Laith is beefy.
- Am I?
- Yes, he is.
- All right, Ella.
- Oh, God.
- He's cute.
- Gorgeous.
- I know, right?
- They both are.
- Think you're up.
I think so, too, Arin.
You live here?
No, no, no, I'm visiting Arin.
I'm from New York, born and raised. Yeah.
- I worked at Callen-Lorde in Chelsea,
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
- I'm done. I broke a nail.
Well, are we gonna do
this wall over here?
- I'll let you take the lead on this one.
- No.
_
I mean, it's a good view
from below.
Um, I was gonna ask you and Arin
if you guys wanted to
maybe meet for dinner later.
- Oh, absolutely, yeah. I'd love to, yeah.
- Cool.
Um, I'll let you know when
- and where and all that stuff.
- Okay, cool. Sounds good.
Okay, good.
- Have fun.
- We're at Legends.
_
- You got the bull set-up right here.
- I know!
_
Be gentle with me!
Yee-haw!
Candis is running
around, dancing and... oh!
I never thought about dating
somebody who's trans, ever, and then,
you know, meeting Laith...
he's really beautiful.
So I should, maybe,
open myself up to a bigger pool
of guys that I'm willing to date.
_
- _
- That's right, I am.
That's great.
You're so cute.
Do you think it's elegant?
- The whole thing?
- It's more than elegant.
That's it, babe. You're so good.
- Are you my date tonight?
- Of course.
Of course you're...
Well, thank you for
making it here for this.
Oh, my goodness, my pleasure.
- Wouldn't miss it for the world.
- I know!
- It's the Glamour Awards.
- Caitlyn, when did youfind out
- you were getting the award?
- Yeah, a couple of months ago.
I was kind of shocked and
extraordinarily honored.
- Why were you shocked?
- You don't grow up your whole life
as being me, and think that
your biggest fear is that
you would be thought of
as an absolute freak and weirdo, and...
- Right.
- To be so welcomed,
by not only the trans community, but,
uh, Glamour magazine,
womanhood in general,
it's, um...
uh, it's a wonderful, wonderful feeling.
Perfect.
Cinderella!
_
You got it.
- Caitlyn!
- Going to a big event like this,
it's always more fun to go and
share it with somebody else.
So, of course, I wanted
Kylie to go with me.
But she's had a wardrobe malfunction.
So I gotta do the red
carpet all by myself.
And to be honest with
you, that is very scary.
Caitlyn! Caitlyn! Caitlyn... !
I wanted you right by my side.
- My dress ripped all the way down my ass.
- Okay.
I wouldn't want to be on a red carpet
- with my vagina out.
- Uh...
I'll say good-bye to Chandi
and come back and say
hello to Miss Chandelier.
- All right, will do.
- Hello.
You got it. Till then, bye.
Hi, baby. Can I say something?
On the red carpet, you
were supposed to be my date.
Honestly, I wanted you right by my side.
My dress was completely see-through
and then my option "B" ripped
all the way down my ass.
- Okay.
- I wouldn't want to beon a red carpet
with my vagina out.
- Uh...
- My vagina was out. Not my boob,
not my butt crack, my vagina.
I didn't know all that, but,
hopefully, we could've
worked around that somehow.
And my option "B," my whole
zipper ripped down, so...
- Okay.
- And I had a tailor there,
- trying to fix it.
- Okay.
Kind of disappointed in Kylie,
but at least she showed
up for the actual show.
Of course, I wanted her to
go with me to the red carpet,
but I need to feel comfortable
just doing them on my own.
Okay, well, then next time...
- I'm dragging your ass there.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hi! Are you ready for the drive?
Ready, ready. Born ready.
- _
- To Chicago.
It's a red eye!
Look, see? Red.
- What's the hardest part of road life?
- There's not enough marijuana.
#boomboom.
Ha ha! Hello, Chicago!
- It's the woman of the year!
- Woman of the year!
Hey, babe,
- there you go, Chandi, how you doing?
- Incredible!
- I'm loving the hair.
- Zackary, you're back!
I think we need to go have some
pizza and talk about all that.
Yes.
I've heard about this for years.
It's delicious. The
best pizza in the world.
We are in Chicago, and
you know, Chicago's known
for the Baton Show Lounge.
Mimi Marks works there,
and so I asked her if I could
come and do a number with her...
- Ooh!
- And you guys
could come and watch the show...
- We gotta see the show.
- ... and see the other performers.
And trans people have
been performing in drag
- bars since the beginning of time.
- Oh, I... I agree.
It totally saved me and
helped me figure out who I was.
I look at it a, um, a beautiful thing.
I don't see you going to drag shows.
Um, it's not... it's not really my thing.
Some of my sisters and brothers,
it's important for them to see
their lives not as a performance,
but as... as reality.
I'm totally confused
with how some of your,
um, brothers and sisters, who
identify with our community,
separate themselves from the world
in which some of us began.
Drag doesn't do a lot for me.
I'm not pretending to be anything.
So there are people in the drag
community who find this, uh,
a great source of fun and
love and celebration of life.
And then there are other people who say,
"This is about performance,
and our lives are not about performance,
our lives are about the
reality." Some of us come from,
uh, a drag or a performance
or... or showgirl universe.
- Mm-hmm.
- And some of us don't.
I would never expect
you to be able to identify
with the world that we've come from,
because it has never been your
stilo. It wasn't your introduction.
I totally respect the fact
that Jenny sees things
from that perspective.
But she should be able to see the
connection between our communities.
Jenny and Cait
processed it differently,
- they hid differently.
- If it wasn't for drag,
maybe I would be a
miserable gay boy, trapped.
Would it be harder
for you to be dating a man,
- as opposed to a woman?
- I think it might be a little bit tougher on the
girls if it was, um, a guy.
If I was dating some
guy, they would go, "Wow!"
Hi, honey. Can I come in?
Sounds like what I was
doing at your door the other day.
Ooh, you have
it chilly up in here!
- I was gonna pop this champagne open.
- Oh!
Mm-hmm. I couldn't get over JB.
If it wasn't for drag
and being able to do...
do those shows, maybe I would
be a miserable gay boy, trapped,
right now.
A lot of times,
like Jenny and Cait,
they come from a different side,
they processed it differently,
they hid differently.
That used to be a stress
reliever for me, and I miss...
- I miss it. I really do.
- We all know how much you love
- your work and you love your kids.
- Mm-hmm.
But there is... You will
not survive if you don't clock out.
Right. Clocking out
is a big issue for me. Because I feel like
I need to be there for them.
And my mom, she's dealing
with a lot right now.
My dad was one
of the best people that...
... any person could really ask for.
And he has been dealing with dementia
and my mom is always, always, always
not thinking about herself
because she's so worried about him.
And that's where I get it from.
When you talk all day and you have to,
you know, try to fix things for people,
and you're... you're trying to find
housing and you're trying to find food,
it's one of those things
that gets really crazy for me,
because it makes me
want to do so much more.
I know, honey.
Chandi is amazing.
She comes across, always,
as really happy and
she's always a really
positive person, and she
works non-stop with on-the-edge youth.
Hi!
We do get into heavy discussions.
You know. We lay it all on the line.
They asked me for my I.D.
and then it was like,
um, "She's a tranny."
Some people look at me as a human,
and some other people
look at me as an animal.
It's extremely important that we're heard.
And we say thank you for
everybody coming to group.
But you know, I think that
she has a lot more going on
than any of us even realize.
All I say is it's gonna be okay, Candis.
Here we go. You look bodacious.
For some of the girls,
finding love, it's a challenge.
One drink. Are you buying?
- Of course you are.
- Yes, I'll buy.
- Okay, right, okay.
So we are all gonna have
cocktails at the hotel.
I'm hoping to exercise
my matchmaking skills.
There's a lot of boys around.
All right.
I think Zackary and Candis went to mingle.
There's this whole
table of guys back here.
_
It's in the middle of such a public place.
- Yeah.
- Oh, really?
Yeah.
For me, the big problem I have
in a lot of things is rejection.
That's why, probably, one of the
reasons I didn't date that much.
- I'm Scott.
- Hi, nice to meet you, Patrick.
- Scott.
- Scott. Nice to meet you.
- We're staying in this hotel.
- Okay.
So we're just hanging out.
- Nice.
- You know?
- What's your name?
- I'm a friend of Taylor's. Joe.
- Okay.
- Caitlyn doesn't really know
how to talk to guys at all.
With a flirt, with something
more than just who she is.
And so she doesn't know how
to... follow. She wants to lead.
Well, Joe, it was nice meeting you.
What do you do for, uh,
work? What do you do?
I own, uh, a real estate
office and I'm a developer.
- Oh, so, residentials or commercial?
- Little of both.
- Whatever.
- Commercial.
Wherever there's...
- wherever you can make a buck.
- That's right.
Sometimes, when you're talking
to guys, you have to take
the back seat a little bit.
I don't know if she's ready to do that.
I'm outta here.
Did Jenner leave?
Jenner's... Jenner's left the building.
- Hello?
- Oh!
Coming in the back door?
- I realized that we have adjoining rooms.
- We have adjoining rooms, I know that,
yeah. I know, I know.
They're gonna talk.
Now, you need any hair?
- Uh, well...
- Courtney's got the hair.
- Oh, that's cool.
- You should, actually,
put some dark streaks in there.
Well, how are you doing?
I'm good. I was gonna say that, um,
you wouldn't dance with the
guys when we went dancing.
- You only wanted to dance with me.
- I just didn't feel comfortable.
Which is fine. I'm not trying
to push you into anything.
- Yeah.
- I'm just...
just, you know, trying to get you
trying new things as far as dating.
I look at you girls and I listen
to you about all the challenges
- of dating as a trans woman.
- Right.
Okay? How guys, like,
want to have sex with you, but then
they don't want to be seen with you.
Yeah. I... I would have
a hard time with that.
Yeah.
What is holding you back from...
just going on a date with someone?
You know, the other I
thought about bringing it
day, up to Kylie.
You know. "I was, uh...
maybe I should start dating
or doing something like that."
And I was thinking about
it, and I thought: I can't.
I just... I... I can't
even bring the subject up.
Hey, we all ready for a good time?
Chandi!
So much fun for me to watch
my little Chandi up there,
letting it go.
You know, the other day,
I thought about bringing it up to Kylie.
You know. "I was, uh...
maybe I should start dating
or doing something like that."
And I was thinking about
it and I thought: I can't.
I just... I... I can't
even bring the subject up.
Would it be harder for
you to be dating a man,
as opposed to a woman,
on the kids or visa versa?
I think it might be a little bit tougher
on the girls if it was, um, a guy.
Yeah. I think,
yeah, if I was dating
some guy they would go,
"Wow."
Yeah. Yeah.
- Have you ever dated a woman?
- No.
No. See, okay.
I'm not looking forward to
having conversations about
dating with my kids.
I think if I were to date a man,
I think it would be confusing for them.
And, uh, I don't want to confuse them.
You have to get to the root of what
- you are going through.
- Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
You're allowed to go out
there, have fun, experiment.
There's no one... no
one's judging, anymore.
Because you are living your truth.
You know?
Maybe if I think of it as an experiment.
Yeah.
I need to start new and fresh, also.
- Like going out on... on a group date...
- Yeah.
... with Laith and Arin
kind of showed me that I have
to broaden my horizons, too.
- I think we both need to.
- Yeah.
A double experiment.
That's why we call 'em experiments.
- Salsa!
So are you going to the thing tonight?
Of course.
We're gonna go see Candis
and Chandi perform...
- at a drag show!
- Are we?
I'm feeling pulled in a lot
of different directions here.
You know, I had this kind of...
ambivalent relationship toward drag.
And I think a lot of people who come
from a different part of the community
have this unease with some aspects
of drag because there's a sense of,
"Here we are, pretending to be women."
And I know that that's not the
best way to describe drag, but
it's one way to describe
drag, and, you know, so...
I'm not pretending to be anything.
The trans community is
so diverse, you know?
And each one of us has
such a different story.
I want to celebrate
everybody's way of being,
but I also want to fight
for my own identity,
which was hard won.
- And, um...
- Until it...
isolates you from the
people that you love.
Jenny's not wrong here,
but neither is Chandi.
The trans community as a
whole is split on this issue.
So it's a complicated
thing, but bottom line,
friends need to be there
to support each other.
I think the higher road
to take is to, you know,
go and experience it.
I'm being asked to do something here
that I probably wouldn't normally do
and I still don't think that many of
my sisters understand my resistance.
And we're not all gonna
agree on everything,
but I know they have good hearts.
You know, embracing difference is...
that's your challenge here, today.
Hey, girl! It's good to see you.
It's good to see you, too. Oh!
- Hi, how are you?
- Hi, I'm Regine.
- How are you?
- Hi, Regine, I'm Chandi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh, no! No, no!
Okay, everybody follow me.
I've come to understand that, for Chandi,
the drag world saved her life, literally.
So how can anyone stand in the way of that
and not celebrate that? Yeah,
don't... don't flash them, Jenner.
Hey... we don't want to... there we go.
Don't flash 'em, Jenner.
After all the controversy, for Jenny,
it was great that she
went to the drag show.
So I think it's going to be a fun night.
Thank you.
Oh.
I am totally nervous.
_
It has been so long
since I have performed.
So I am a little nervous,
but I've received nothing but love
from Candis and Mimi.
And that does help calm anyone's nerves.
Hopefully.
- All right, I'll see you in a minute.
- Have fun.
I'll say good-bye to Chandi
and come back and say
hello to Miss Chandelier.
Oh, right!
So, we all ready for a good time?
You know my pretty girl swag
Don't hate miss sis 'cause I'm bad
My head back, yep, newly bad
-  My handbag, that's...
- We have like,
six numbers, and then you go on.
- Okay, babe.
- Okay? You're gonna tear it up.
_
Tonight I'm doing it big
Might switch it up, rock a wig
Hear them say "Oh,
no, she didn't... "
_
We've had such an amazing cast tonight.
Yes, but we have one entertainer that...
She hasn't done a show in a long time.
She said "decades." "Decades."
Without further ado...
For her return back to the stage...
- of Miss...
- Chandelier!
Without further ado...
For her return back to the stage...
- Of Miss...
- Chandelier!
Sit back and put your feet up
Yes, sir, and feel the rhythm
You know we going crazy
All turned up like Patrick Swayze...
Miss Chandelier was incredible.
When she went on stage,
it was like... she was meant to be there.
You know how to rock it...
It was so much fun for me to
watch my little Chandi up there,
letting it go. All these girls are, like,
taking risks all over the place.
Jenny Boylan, who
didn't even want to go...
there she was, stuffing
dollar bills down Chandi's bra.
So I think she had a lot of fun.
Hey!
Chandi!
Being able to hit that stage
and unleash Chandelier,
was... a moment
that I hadn't experienced
in a very long time.
I really let go.
It was totally a reconnecting
moment with myself,
because I forgot how good it felt.
You should be famous...
It doesn't matter what
walk of life you're from,
you can enjoy drag.
There was so much love in the air.
And it was beautiful.
You should be famous.
Caitlyn Jenner,
you're an insult to all trans people.
You know, nobody in the trans movement
is required to love any of us.
How did you go about your
transformation and everything, like,
and still acknowledging
God in your life? Because,
like, religion and everything...
I'm going to Des Moines...
Democratic debate.
Oh, my God.
- Is that Hillary Clinton?
- Oh, my gosh!
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -