CAITLYN: Here we go.
Well, a month ago...
I left on a trip with the girls,
hoping to meet a bunch of trans people,
learn about their stories,
and what happened is I...
is, honestly, I... I wound up
learning probably more about myself
than anything.
CHANDI: Would you consider
yourself to be lesbian?
CAITLYN: Uh...
I am slowly coming into my womanhood,
but it's a work in
progress. Old Bruce...
did a lot of good things in his life.
Not that that old person was a
bad person, he just wasn't me.
I thought I knew a lot more
than I actually turned out to know.
What did I say now?
CANDIS: That if you look
like a man in a dress
it makes other people uncomfortable.
JENNY: People need to know that
you're fighting for everybody,
not just the pretty ones.
WOMAN: Caitlyn Jenner, you're
an insult to all trans people.
CAITLYN: I've made mistakes along
the way, I've been criticized for 'em.
CHANDI: How can you focus
on trying to get a job
when you don't where
you're gonna sleep at night?
JENNY: It's not about the
issues. We're telling you,
we were scared.
CAITLYN: Sometimes it got pretty heated.
JENNY: You're telling me Republicans
support rights for transgender people.
CAITLYN: Every conservative guy out
there believes in everybody's rights.
JENNY: That is a lie.
CAITLYN: I have to keep
an open mind politically,
socially, on trans issues, on womanhood.
I have to learn from my
girls, learn from society.
I don't want to hurt anybody.
CANDIS: Don't you really mean you
don't want to get hurt yourself?
CAITLYN: Hey!
- CANDIS: Hey!
- CAITLYN: But also we had somuch fun
on this trip that I
never, ever expected.
- You're voted in, I know.
- KRIS: Aw, thanks, guys.
- (cheering)
- CAITLYN: It was a growing process for me,
and we all still loved each
other when it was all over,
and that was by far the
most important thing.
♪ ♪
(knocking)
CAITLYN: Oh, my God!
Jenny Boylan is in the house!
- Look at you, you look so nice.
- JENNY: Hi, sweetie.
CAITLYN: Baby doll.
How are you doing?
- JENNY: Totally psyched.
- CAITLYN: I know, good. I am too, s...
JENNY: So, what, so you think
I've just been goofing off
these last six months?
CAITLYN: Today's a big
day. I'm getting ready to
start this next chapter.
- It's so good to have you with us.
- KATE: So good to see you.
- CAITLYN: I was so excited. Jenny.
- JENNY: Auntie K.
- KATE: Miss Jenny.
- Hi, darling.
- CAITLYN: All of the girls have come to town
because we came up with this idea:
let's go on the road.
- CHANDI: I... I want to say thank you, first of all.
- CAITLYN: You got it, baby, you got it.
CAITLYN: I have this platform,
but I still have to learn so much more
to be a great representative,
uh, for our community.
I really want to kind of
get out of my comfort zone
and immerse myself in trans issues,
find out more about the
people that are out there
in these small towns across America.
I think it's just going to be wonderful.
I'll learn a lot and I hope
everybody else learns a lot.
CANDIS: Hi, gorge.
JENNY: Scarecrow, I've
missed you most of all.
CAITLYN: Our newest arrival is here.
- Ella, baby.
- ELLA: Hi, how are you?
- CAITLYN: Here we go.
- KATE: Hello.
- ELLA: Hey, how are you?
- KATE: My baby girl.
ELLA: I already... I already have
you as "Auntie Kate" in my phone.
CAITLYN: Right after I transitioned
I had a friend from many years ago
calls and says, "You'll never guess...
you knew my son very little,
well, now is my daughter."
ELLA: My name is Ella Giselle.
I was 16 when I started
transitioning and I'm 18 now.
Junior year, school ended,
and then I just kind of
explored myself that summer.
And then senior year came and
I came back myself, um, as Ella.
- KYLIE: Hey.
- CAITLYN: My little Kylie.
Mm, baby doll.
- JENNY: What a pleasure to meet you.
- KATE: Hi.
- CAITLYN: And Kate Bornstein.
- KYLIE: How are you?
KATE: Hello, baby, say your name again.
KYLIE: Kylie.
CAITLYN: This is my other
daughter, everybody, Kendall.
- KENDALL: I'm Kendall. How are you?
- CAITLYN: That's Ella.
My girls... all my kids, but
especially Kendall and Kylie...
have to deal with, you
know, a father transitioning.
It's a very, very difficult process,
with all this history
you have in your life.
Am I doing it right?
You can never do this right.
Okay?
The last thing in the world I want to do
is hurt any one of you.
CHANDI: Can I say... I know this has not
been the easiest thing for you guys to
wrap your heads around, but you
guys are being real troopers,
real troopers about it.
And we appreciate all
the love you give to Cait
and to our full community,
because we need it.
- We totally need it.
- KENDALL: Of course.
- KYLIE: Thank you.
- KENDALL: She got pretty lucky...
we're all very, like,
open, accepting, like,
non-judgmental people.
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
- KENDALL: Like, our whole family.
- CAITLYN: I agree...
- KENDALL: You're welcome.
JENNY: It's a thing that... it's
a thing that people need to learn...
that transgender people have families.
KATE: Miss Kylie,
Kendall, I wanted to know
when did you know you were a girl?
KENDALL: Um...
I mean, I've al... I feel
like I've always known.
I feel like that's just, like, a...
like, I mean...
KYLIE: You know, I feel
like it was never a question,
'cause I had so many sisters and
I wanted to be exactly like that.
ELLA: And I think that's something
that people don't even realize
that they have a gender.
- Some people...
- CAITLYN: First... Yeah, like,
I would look at guys...
and think,
"Wouldn't it be nice
to be just, like, a guy
and not have this issue?"
CANDIS: I remember thinking that too.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, you remember thinking that too?
- CANDIS: Totally.
CAITLYN: For people in my community,
that question of gender is in
your head every day, all the time.
I want all my kids, but
especially Kendall and Kylie,
to think about their gender.
When did I know? You
know? When was that?
KYLIE: Well, you know what's so interesting
is I feel like a year before her transition...
I feel like there was
just a lot on her mind,
and we didn't really connect.
Like, I feel like my whole life,
it just wasn't genuine or...
Now I feel like we connect a lot more
and we spend a lot more time together.
So I actually almost like it more.
The only thing... when
I post photos of my dad
or if I say "Dad", people
will be like, "You mean Mom?"
And I just want to be like,
- "Absolutely not", like...
- CHANDI: Absolutely not.
KYLIE: That... Like, that
is not my mom, you know?
JENNY: I think that Caitlyn
is cool with that, but for me,
it made me a little crazy
when my kids would say "Dad"
in, like, a public place,
and I'd be like, "Oh... "
But... but it's... but
it's... In the end, we let them
pick a name, and they came up
with... with Maddie, you know?
KENDALL: Yeah, her name
in my phone is "Mad".
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
- KYLIE: Yeah.
KENDALL: 'Cause she...
she's a little mad.
- Bye.
- CHANDI: Bye-bye.
KENDALL: Hope to see you guys soon.
CAITLYN: I'm glad you had a
chance to meet all the girls.
Really one of the most interesting group
of girls you'll ever meet, you know?
- Love you.
- KENDALL: Bye, love you.
CAITLYN: I'll be calling
you from the road.
JENNY: Are you psyched?
CHANDI: Yeah, what's going on?
You... you just seem like...
CANDIS: No, I mean, I...
the idea of it is so amazing.
Um, I just... it's just,
like, overwhelming, you know?
CHANDI: Yeah.
CANDIS: I do have a
little apprehension because
I know that it's not gonna all be,
you know, rainbows and unicorns.
We've seen the reaction, mostly
within our community, at Caitlyn.
- Me and the girls have talked about
- _
- giving Caitlyn a reality check...
educating her about certain things.
So we're... we're gonna be hard on
her, we're gonna tell her the truth, um,
even though she might not like it.
JENNY: It's up to us, her friends,
to push her... to push her
out of her comfort zone,
- to encourage her to look within.
- CANDIS: Right.
CAITLYN: Candis, where's the map?
- You have the map.
- CANDIS: I have the map for the trip.
CAITLYN: Okay, put it right there.
Um, we have, starting
here to the Grand Canyon,
which will be tomorrow.
And then off to Santa Fe.
- CHANDI: Cool.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
CANDIS: We could go to Des Moines.
- CAITLYN: Ugh, no, we don't.
- CANDIS: Yeah, we do.
The Democratic debates
are going to be there.
- CHANDI: Yay! (Whoops)
- CAITLYN: Yeah, yeah, right, right, right.
They're all Democrats, I'm the only
conservative Republican on the bus,
and we are in an election year,
so I think it's going to
be kind of interesting,
from that standpoint.
KATE: How many months
we gonna be on the road?
CAITLYN: A long time, yeah.
All right, early morning tomorrow.
- (birds chirping)
- JENNY: Careful.
(laughs)
CAITLYN: It is 6:30 in the morning...
unbelievably, we're on time.
I've got a lot of stuff.
We go pick up some more people,
then we hop on the bus
and we're off to the Grand Canyon.
Should be fun.
ELLA: No, no, no, this is not...
This looks very bad, but my bags
are only... these ones. So don't...
CAITLYN: Do you have your wallet?
COURTNEY: Kipsy, shut the door, and
I was like, "Kipsy, I'm in here."
- CAITLYN: There they are.
- KIP: Double trouble.
- JENNY: All aboard. Ready?
- (Imitates train whistle)
- CAITLYN: Oh, no!
- JENNY: Here, blow in there.
- Just go...
- (imitates train whistle)
(laughing)
- You want to blow?
- CAITLYN: Well, I can see it's gonna be tough.
- KIP: I do have...
- JENNY: I didn't mean this.
(laughter)
KIP: Oh, my paws and whiskers!
WOMAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Candis Cayne.
CAITLYN: Candis Cayne! Yay!
Next... Chandi...
- Zackary...
- KIP: And then we are out of town!
- ZACKARY: I love you.
- MAN: I love you, too.
ZACKARY: I feel so fortunate to have
a boyfriend who loves me and whom I love
and who treats me amazing.
But I know that that's the exception.
Men who love transwomen
come forward very rarely.
- CAITLYN: We have everybody!
- (Cheering, whooping)
Let's go get the big bus,
and we're out of town!
WOMAN: To the bus, to the bus!
- WOMAN 2: To... the... bus.
- CAITLYN: Let's go do it.
ZACKARY: Wow!
WOMAN: Oh, my God,
there are sparkles.
WOMAN 2: It's the glam!
CHANDI: The bus is totally amazing,
and being in that type of confinement,
there's never gonna be anyplace
for Cait to run on this trip.
Being around so many girls
for that length of time
is going to make her or break her.
- (whooping, clapping)
- WOMAN 2: Grand Canyon!
- ZACKARY: You look stunning, honey.
- CHANDI: As usual.
(Shutter clicks)
CAITLYN: Oh, Zackary, no way you can put
individual lashes on in a bus.
ZACKARY: You've got to be able
to paint yourself out of a box.
It's a necessary survival strategy.
- (laughing)
- (train whistle blows)
_
ZACKARY: Okay. I can't
imagine actually being
18 years old and having,
like, your first romance.
ELLA: My boyfriend is amazing.
It's really nice to
have someone, like...
understand.
CANDIS: Everybody has
a boyfriend but me.
(laughing): I'm the old
battle-ax that has no boyfriend.
- (fake snoring)
- JENNY: We're approaching lunch.
CAITLYN: I'd like to stop somewhere,
- like in the middle of nowhere...
- WOMAN: Yeah, let's do it.
- CAITLYN: ... and take over some restaurant.
- WOMAN: Let's take over!
CAITLYN: Let's go do it!
- It's the River Cafe, guys.
- WOMAN: Juicy's Famous.
CHANDI: Oh, my goodness.
- WOMAN: I'll follow you.
- (Knocking)
CHANDI: Hey!
CANDIS: Oh! We're in Needles.
WOMAN: Isn't that
better? You're in Needles.
(knocking) (laughs)
- WOMAN: Where is Chandi?
- WOMAN 2: Where is Chandi?
JENNY: Did she not get off the bus?
WOMAN: Oh, sorry, sorry... I
trapped you in there for so long.
CHANDI: Oh, my goodness! (Laughs)
I'm off the bus! Yay!
- WOMAN: There she is!
- (Happy shouts)
CHANDI: I could not get off
the bus. I was freaking out.
CAITLYN: You were locked on the bus?
CHANDI: People were moving
around, and I'm like,
"Hey... !"
Nobody could hear me.
Everybody was just
waving. So then I'm like...
- COURTNEY: A soundproof bus!
- CHANDI: Damn.
CANDIS: Damn.
CAITLYN: On the bus! Load 'em up!
- WOMAN: On the road again.
- WOMAN 2: Home sweet home.
CAITLYN: We got wine, beer...
CHANDI: That's just
what the doctor ordered.
CAITLYN: Let the conversation begin.
(Cheering, whooping, shouting)
JENNY: This bus trip was Caitlyn's idea.
I think part of her motivation was
she thought it was gonna be fun.
And, of course, it is fun,
but it's about more than having fun.
She needs to realize she's
not gonna get a pass anymore,
that some of the hardest
work for her lies ahead.
CAITLYN: Uh-oh.
- When she gets this close...
- COURTNEY: Scoot over.
CAITLYN: Yeah, when she gets
this close, this is not good.
COURTNEY: Are you getting nervous?
- CAITLYN: I'm getting nervous.
- JENNY: Cait, there's something I wanted to ask you
about, and I don't quite
know how to get in here.
- CAITLYN: All right.
- JENNY: I think you said...
- CAITLYN: Uh-oh.
- JENNY: ... um, the other day
that you consider yourself heterosexual.
When you were a straight
guy, so to speak...
- CAITLYN: So to speak.
- JENNY (laughs): So to speak.
Um, did you ever appreciate what
was beautiful about other men?
- Was that on your radar?
- CAITLYN: Other men?
JENNY: Yeah. Was on that your
radar? Did you... could you see men?
I'm not asking you to
make you uncomfortable.
Six months in,
I remember feeling like I was
seeing men for the first time.
Whing! You know,
something in me suddenly
was... was... thrilled by men.
- CAITLYN: Have you ever been with a guy?
- JENNY: No.
WOMAN: Have you?
CAITLYN: You didn't have the guts to...
oh, don't go like this
with me. (Laughter)
- COURTNEY: Oh, well, I'm so sorry!
- CAITLYN: My question's to her.
- No, I never have.
- CHANDI: If you were to date
someone female, because that's
what you're attracted to,
would you consider
yourself to be lesbian?
CAITLYN: Uh...
- Boy, this gets heavy.
- WOMAN: It does.
CAITLYN: Um, I'm trying
to think all this out.
Talking about my sexuality's
really difficult for me,
and I want to literally shrivel
up and just kind of hide inside me.
I really don't want to go there,
but I am totally
outnumbered in this bus.
To be honest with you, I can't...
see myself dating, like,
women in the future.
WOMAN: Wow.
CAITLYN: Do you know
your way around men?
- CANDIS: I do a little bit.
- CAITLYN: If we go on, like, a double date,
what about our affair?
Like, would it be over?
WOMAN: You're telling me Republicans
support rights for transgender people?
CAITLYN: Every
conservative guy out there
- believes in everybody's rights.
- JENNY: That is never gonna happen.
CAITLYN: To be honest
with you, I can't...
see myself dating, like,
women in the future.
- WOMAN: Wow.
- WOMAN 2: Wow.
CAITLYN: I just... I've
been there, done that.
- CHANDI: Right.
- CAITLYN: Got three very strong ex-wives.
I just don't see it.
JENNY: So now you can
have an ex-husband.
CAITLYN: That's right, now
I can have an ex-husband.
- JENNY: That's something to look forward to.
- CAITLYN: Um...
COURTNEY: Well, maybe now you are that,
so you don't need to be
that or be around, you know?
CAITLYN: Yeah. And I don't see a woman
being attracted to me, so... you know...
- COURTNEY: Oh, they're attracted to you.
- WOMAN: Oh, you'd be surprised.
JENNY: I beg your pardon.
WOMAN: There might be
women in this room
- who are attracted to you, Caitlyn.
- CAITLYN: Oh, they're in here!
(laughter)
COURTNEY: That's big. You have never...
that's big, 'cause you've
never said that before.
But this morning my
boyfriend dropped me off and
he, like, goes around and he's like,
"Cait needs to roll
her window up in her car
before she leaves, it's
gonna rain," and she goes,
"I'd like that, I got
to get me one of those."
She said, " I got to get me
one of those," and I was like...
I think you were attracted to, like,
that, like somebody who's just doing...
- taking care of it and, like...
- CAITLYN: Yeah, right, yeah,
yeah, there is factors of that.
To be honest, if I was in
a relationship with a guy,
I would enjoy being treated like that...
opening doors for you,
uh, doing all what you would
think the traditional stuff
in a guy-and-a-girl relationship.
It'd have to be a very special
guy to be able to do that,
but, uh... yeah, I
would be open to that.
KATE: What tickles us
isn't always the gender
of our partner. It
might be, you know, like,
sapiosexuals are all into
people who are smart, you know?
There are people who are into power.
Like, there's a powerful person,
I don't care what gender they are.
CAITLYN: In most cases, I've
been attracted to powerful girls.
KATE: Okay.
CAITLYN: I've always been
with very strong women.
If there was a female in my life,
it would be more like a
friendship than it would be...
a real, you know, a
serious relationship.
You would never have these conversations
anywhere else but in this bus.
Yeah. With everybody being so open.
WOMAN: Are we, like, here?
- CHANDI: We should be.
- WOMAN: All right, let's go.
- WOMAN 2: Is it cold out?
- CAITLYN: I think I got everything.
(indistinct chatter)
CAITLYN: A little chilly.
CANDIS: Welcome to the Grand Canyon.
Are you gonna stay in for the night?
CAITLYN: I am, uh, not going anywhere.
- CANDIS: Thank you.
- CAITLYN: Thank you.
- CANDIS: All right.
- CAITLYN: I will see you in a bit.
ZACKARY: Sweet dreams, Mama.
CAITLYN: All right.
Okay, I said what everybody wants to
hear, that, yeah, I would date a man.
I, you know... And it's kind of nice
just to get that kind of off your chest.
Maybe now they might
leave me alone for a while.
(Crickets chirping)
CANDIS: Have this whole
piece, 'cause I'm done.
So you need to eat that
whole gorgeous piece.
Right there. It's all...
No, take the piece,
(bleep) damn it. Take the (bleep) piece.
Thank you.
JENNY: So, can I just say?
That was kind of an amazing
bus ride, an amazing
conversation we had.
CANDIS: Yeah, it was fun.
JENNY: W... was I the only one who was
caught a little off guard by Caitlyn
allowing us how she
sees men in her future?
CANDIS: Yeah, that was interesting.
'Cause I always just assumed
because she's been with women
that that's who she would...
ELLA: I was definitely kind of like...
JENNY: Boy, it was like...
ELLA: "Wow."
JENNY: She did not want
to go there, and I felt bad
pushing her so hard. I really
don't like doing that with her.
On the other hand, I feel like
this is the journey that we're on.
ELLA: But, see, you got her to
say something she hasn't said.
You know? I... I would
have never guessed.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- JENNY: Maybe it sounds like I'm harshing on her,
but Caitlyn often
gives us that, you know,
"I don't want to go
there. Don't go there.
I don't want to talk about it." And
then she'll just kind of, you know,
flit away. Well, she
can't do that anymore,
and it's up to us, her friends,
to keep pushing to...
find some answers to questions
she may not have asked herself yet.
CAITLYN: The Democratic National Debate.
CANDIS: Great. Front row! (Chuckles)
CAITLYN: The last place I want to be.
CHANDI: I know. I know.
CAITLYN: And if we're unfortunate enough
to get Hillary as our next president,
- we need her on our side.
- CHANDI: Right.
CAITLYN: Although she won't be.
JENNY: Which Republican would?
CAITLYN: She could
care less about women.
She cares about herself.
JENNY: I think we're
at a tipping point now
where the religious right and
some socialist conservatives
are using fear of people like us
to repeal and to prevent equality.
CAITLYN: Oh, please. It's
not... Don't go there.
Just as much the Democrats. With me...
JENNY: You need to look
at it, Cait. CAITLYN:
No, I'm not gonna identify that.
I'm not blaming it on
Republicans and conservatives.
- CANDIS: Good morning!
- CAITLYN: Morning!
CANDIS: I'm so excited about
seeing the Grand Canyon.
CAITLYN: Of course.
Who wouldn't be excited?
CANDIS: I have never seen it.
CAITLYN: I am. I'm...
I've never seen it either.
- Yeah.
- CANDIS: I think it'll be good.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, no, I'm actually very excited.
- CANDIS: We made it here.
- The bus ride was fun.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
CANDIS: And I'm super proud of you
for opening up and... and, like...
- CAITLYN: Jesus Christ, I have no choice.
- CANDIS: Well, just a little bit.
I know. But you're
with all these girls,
and everybody was kind
of like... (growls)
Which, you know, you
handled it really well.
And now maybe you and I
can go out on a double date.
(laughs)
- CAITLYN: At this point, what the hell?
- CANDIS: Why not?
CAITLYN: Why not? D... double date, yes.
- Do you know your way around men?
- CANDIS: I do, a little bit.
CAITLYN: Okay, good.
- But here's the big question.
- CANDIS: What?
CAITLYN: If we go on,
like, a double date
- with, like, guys...
- CANDIS: Yeah.
CAITLYN: ... what about our affair?
Like, would it be over?
- CANDIS: Well, I mean...
- CAITLYN: I mean, the tabloids have been running
wild with this stuff.
Everybody has been pushing
right from the beginning
Candis and I getting together.
And I love her to death,
but I don't see the relationship,
from my standpoint,
going any farther than
what it's, you know...
where it is right now.
- CANDIS: To the end of our affair.
- CAITLYN: No.
(Candis laughs)
All girls have girlfriends, right?
You know, Candis will
always be in my life.
ZACKARY: Good morning. Oh, my God,
everybody looks so fresh and so beautiful.
CAITLYN: I know. Isn't that great?
We just got a... a court ruling.
Kind of on the bathroom and
changing and this and that.
This girl in Chicago
identifies as female,
but they just had a big article
in The New York Times today.
JENNY: "Federal education authorities
found that an Illinois school district
violated antidiscrimination
laws when it did not allow
a transgender girl who
identifies as a girl
and participates on a girls' sports team
to change and shower in
the girls' locker room
without restrictions.
Education officials say the
decision is the first of its kind
on the rights of transgender students,
which are emerging as a
new cultural battleground."
- CAITLYN: Yay!
- (cheering)
- JENNY: Ah, love that.
- CAITLYN: That's good, it's all good.
That's progress for us.
And it starts small and
hopefully will spread.
My goal is to make a difference
for the next generation.
This is part of humanity,
and I want it to be treated that way.
Did you guys get your orders in?
- ZACKARY: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Now, Ella, what are you doing about...
Are you continuing on in school or what?
ELLA: I think if I'm
going to pursue school,
I definitely need some
time to just, like,
- you know, take off...
- CAITLYN: Live your life.
- ELLA: Yeah.
- JENNY: I don't know what your experience
with high school is like. I
know for a lot of trans people
school, including for me,
school was really horrible.
ELLA: I was very lucky to
have the school behind my back.
In a little cute town
right outside L.A. that is kind of familiar
to difference in one way or another.
I was definitely one of the
fir... I think the first person
to kind of bring this up.
CAITLYN: Wore a dress for the
first time to school at the prom.
ZACKARY: At the prom. I
wore a dress to my prom
- I wasn't, like...
- CAITLYN: Yay!
JENNY: The experiences
people have in schools now
are so all over the place.
Was it St. Louis where...
where a school board
allowed a trans girl to
play on the women's team,
and the students protested.
It's just so different,
depending on where you are.
And... and being able to live your life
with dignity should not
be a matter of geography.
- CHANDI: Right.
- JENNY: Right?
ELLA: It's sad.
JENNY: Laws are different
from state to state
regarding transgender
people, and a lot of
how you live in this
world as a trans person
is dependent upon the
community you find yourself in.
I think it's one reason we need to pass
nationwide laws protecting our people.
We've made tremendous progress
over the last five years,
but there are many, many people
who still just don't get it
and still wish we'd go away.
CANDIS: I think that we need to
stop and maybe talk to Hillary.
CAITLYN: Democratic National Debate.
- CHANDI: Right.
- CANDIS: Can't wait.
Front row! (Laughter)
CHANDI: We're so excited
that Cait's even gonna go.
- CANDIS: I'm excited for Cait.
- CHANDI: Right.
And sit and listen to the Democrats.
- CAITLYN: It's the last place I want to be.
- CHANDI: I know. I know.
One of those things you're... you're
being open to and listening to...
CAITLYN: We need both sides.
CHANDI: Right. We need both sides.
CAITLYN: And if we're unfortunate enough
to get Hillary as our next president,
- we need her on our side.
- CHANDI: Right.
CAITLYN: Although she won't be.
JENNY: Which Republican would?
CAITLYN: She could care less about
women. She cares about herself.
JENNY: Which... which
Republican candidate do you think
would be most supportive
of transgendered people?
CAITLYN: Um... all of them.
(Chandi laughs)
Yeah. They don't... The Republi...
"Oh, I hate trans
people" or "I hate gays."
And you don't... nothing of that.
They do more, "I want every...
I want a thriving economy so
every trans person has a job."
CANDIS: (sighs) Caitlyn,
what am I gonna do?
I... I don't understand
why she thinks that.
That doesn't make sense to me.
Democrats are more open
to transgendered views.
And, in general, Republicans
are more conservative about that
and they don't want to give
LGBT rights to our community.
- CAITLYN: Another adventure.
- CANDIS: Yes.
CHANDI: We're off to the races.
- ELLA: Oh, my gosh.
- CHANDI: Let's do this.
(Squealing, laughing)
- CANDIS: Like a Disney ride!
- ZACKARY: Oh, my God.
CAITLYN: One day, this guy
comes running up behind me
and he goes, "Oh, I
just love trans women."
KATE: This whole notion of chasers
has got to get out of the
field of being perverted.
(wind blowing)
- MAN: Hello.
- CAITLYN: How you doing today?
- Are you freezing?
- MAN: I'm not.
- I want to shake your hand.
- CAITLYN: Well, nice to meet you.
- How are you?
- MAN: You were an idol of mine
- back in the '70s.
- CAITLYN: Back in the old days, huh?
So much fun on this trip to
just be out meeting people,
shaking hands. Well, we're
open to people's minds now.
- MAN: There you go.
- CAITLYN: There you go. These people are just nice,
fun. I'm having a great
time. Nice meeting you.
I love it.
ELLA: I'm impressed.
- They have Ella.
- JENNY: Caitlyn.
CAITLYN: Oh, here we go.
ELLA: You're gonna love that.
JENNY: "Someone who is held
in high-esteem by her peers... "
- ELLA: Oh.
- CAITLYN: Like that.
- ELLA: Like that.
- JENNY: "... makes some mistakes
and learns from them."
- CAITLYN: Yeah, well, that's true.
- JENNY: And finally, "Caitlyn
- encourages others."
- CAITLYN: I like that.
- Perfect name.
- (Laughter)
MAN: Ready to go flying
and have some fun today?
CHANDI: Oh, I'm thinking about it.
MAN: 'Cause today, of course, we're
gonna fly over the Grand Canyon.
This is a site-seeing tour.
It's not a thrill ride,
so it is a very smooth, steady flight.
KATE: Thank you. That's
what I needed to hear.
ELLA: Oh, my gosh.
MAN: All right, are we finally
ready to go? We are ready.
Let's do this.
- (laughter, sighing, gasping)
- CANDIS: Oh, my God.
It's like a Disney ride!
CAITLYN: Okay, guys, out in
front of us is the big hole.
- MAN: Is everybody ready?
- CANDIS: I'm ready!
- CAITLYN: All right.
- MAN: That's good because it's happening.
- CAITLYN: It's happening!
- MAN: Welcome to the Grand Canyon, everybody.
ALL: Whoa!
CHANDI: Wow.
- ZACKARY: Oh, my gosh.
- CAITLYN: There it is... the Grand Canyon.
ZACKARY: Oh, my God.
MAN: How is that view?
- CAITLYN: Not a bad view.
- CHANDI: Not a bad view at all.
JENNY: The canyon
takes your breath away.
It makes you think about
the meaning of our lives and
how insignificant we are.
It was very emotional up there.
(birds singing)
CANDIS: So, you guys, I
think our table's ready.
CAITLYN: Let's go get something to eat.
Am I at the head of the table?
- Scary.
- JENNY: You are at the head of the table.
CANDIS: Hi, honey. You look gorge.
- (overlapping chatter)
- I love it.
- Yay!
- JENNY: The memo I got was casual dinner.
Cait and I might be the only two
- who got the memo.
- (Laughter)
KATE: You are rocking Moschino.
CAITLYN: I am rocking
the Moschino tonight.
KATE: Moschino. See, I don't
even know how to pronounce this.
COURTNEY: She's trying to look like
a designer school teacher right now.
- CAITLYN: She's right.
- (Laughter)
KATE: If you were my school teacher,
- I would be so crushed out on you.
- (Laughter)
- But you went to an all-boy school, too, right?
- CAITLYN: I did.
KATE: Cross-dressing was really
difficult until my senior year.
I got my own room. I was a hall monitor.
And then I could lock my door,
- and that's when I dressed up.
- CAITLYN: But you never went out?
KATE: Oh, no.
Stared at the door, wouldn't
do it. That took a long time.
- JENNY: How long did it take?
- CAITLYN: You're telling me?
- (Kate chuckles)
- CAITLYN: Yeah, well, as time went on,
I got more and more daring.
I never used to get caught,
and then, one day, when
I was at the Marriott
years ago in Orlando,
went through the lobby, went down, got in
the car, drove around for while, came back.
- COURTNEY: What, as Caitlyn?
- CAITLYN: Yes.
Was walking through the lobby,
and this guy comes running up behind me.
"Hello! Hello! Hello!"
And he goes, "Oh, I
just love trans women."
And I went, "(Bleep)!"
I'm going, "Just keep walking."
And he stayed out of the elevator.
That was the closest I
ever got to anybody ever.
He goes, "I date 'em all the
time. I love trans women."
- And this and that. And I'm going,
- CANDIS: He was chasing.
"Oh, (bleep), on the
wrong guy." (laughter)
Yeah. Scared me to death.
Got into the room, locked the
door. I didn't go out again.
KATE: You know what's gonna have
to happen for more acceptance
is, this whole notion of chasers
has got to get out of the
field of being perverted.
It's got to become as
beautiful to love a trans person
as it is to love a cis person.
There's the natural leap.
When our desirability
- is natural, you know?
- JENNY: But the men who...
and women... but the men who
love us need to be the ones to stand up
- and take responsibility and testify to that.
- KATE: Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
JENNY: Rather than it being
some shameful thing, you know?
CAITLYN: I can't even imagine
some guy going out with me,
and then being absolutely
scrutinized by the tabloids.
Can you imagine if I
actually had a date and, like,
walked out of a movie theatre on a
quiet Wednesday night
holding hands with somebody?
I think they would
be really tough on me,
and certainly would be
tough on the guy. Like,
"Why are you dating her?"
You know? "What are your motivation?"
It just gets so complicated,
because of the media,
that I don't know any
guy that would ever
even want to go through
something like that.
JENNY: There is a
faction of people who uses
fear of trans people, fear of gay people
to bring people to
the polls, and it's...
- CAITLYN: We're not going there, and...
- JENNY: We are going there.
- That's why we're on this trip!
- CAITLYN: Oh, God.
Every conservative guy out there
believes in everybody's rights.
WOMAN: Well, do you
think... ? Did you say... Whoa.
CHANDI: Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
ZACKARY: You know I
have a great boyfriend...
- CHANDI: Oh, amaze balls.
- ZACKARY: ... who just worships me.
CHANDI: She's got a good man.
CANDIS: They all start out that way.
- (laughter and groaning)
- KATE: Well, well, well.
- (overlapping chatter)
- COURTNEY: Don't be a man hater.
- ZACKARY: Bitter party of three?
- (Laughter)
KATE: The world is changing, honey.
There are more guys
going, "Oh. Oh, okay."
- You know that.
- CANDIS: Yeah. No.
I've never had a
problem finding someone.
It's finding the right
person and, you know...
- CAITLYN: Oh, that's tough in any relationship.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- CHANDI: Right. Not only at night.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
ZACKARY: And I think sometimes,
like, well, we're really rare.
- We're not like all the other girls.
- CHANDI: Right.
ZACKARY: There's only so many of us.
CANDIS: Yeah. No. Yeah, no, for sure.
CAITLYN: We just have to
create understanding with them.
We have to explain this issue
in a way that they understand.
- COURTNEY: I...
- JENNY: And maybe we'll get there.
Maybe we'll get there
because we are being visible,
and we're, um... and
we're doing this work.
- (birds singing)
- (rooster crows)
(crow caws)
JENNY: What day is
today? Thursday, isn't it?
- ZACKARY: No, it's Wednesday.
- JENNY: Today's Wednesday?
ZACKARY: Yeah.
JENNY: This is not what I need.
- Ugh.
- ZACKARY: What?
JENNY: So, news broke
that something really
disturbing had happened in Houston.
An act called "The Hero Act,"
which guaranteed, um, equality,
not just for LGBT people, but for
all people, was, in fact, repealed.
There was a campaign for
the repeal that was run
by a group of ministers and
conservative Republicans.
The tactic that was used
against our community
to have this equality act repealed
was the threat that there would be
sick men in dresses
preying upon our children
in restrooms. It scared people.
Um, it was a lie, and
it happened to work.
While we were enjoying each
others' company, something
rather discouraging happened.
Yesterday in Houston, an
ordinance protecting LGBT people
was repealed. The lead slogan was,
"No men in women's bathrooms."
CAITLYN: Well, I'm all for that, too.
- It's how you define men and women.
- CHANDI: Right.
- CAITLYN: That's all we're arguing over here.
- JENNY: Well,
what the people behind this repeal
managed to convince people
was that people like you
and you and you and you and you and me
are men in the ladies room.
CAITLYN: They just passed
this ordinance in Santa Fe.
It'd be very interesting
to talk to the mayor...
who's all for this... um,
you know, some of the obstacles that he
had to go through to get this through.
JENNY: If I understand correctly, the
thing in Santa Fe was the mayor just did it.
Whereas in Houston, it
was a popular referendum.
- CAITLYN: Right.
- JENNY: And, um,
I think we're at a tipping point
now where the religious right
and some social conservatives
are using fear of people like us,
telling lies about
people like us, to repeal
and to prevent equality,
and we have to push back on it.
- I mean, I'm just seeing this real division...
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
JENNY: ... because there's all
this support and love for you.
You're being celebrated
by Glamour magazine
as one of the most
influential women in the world.
And meanwhile, voters are pushing back.
CANDIS: And it takes one group saying
that... that trans people are molesters,
uh, to spook the rest of the community.
I mean, I don't even think about
ever not going
into the ladies room.
I've always been a strong believer
that you just hold your head up high
and live your life the
way you're supposed to.
ZACKARY: You hold your
head up high and pee.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- (laughter)
JENNY: So, Caitlyn, I want to
come back to you on this because
it's worth asking you how you
feel, as a conservative, about this.
CAITLYN: I don't think it was
presented well to the public.
JENNY: But it was Republicans
and conservatives who said...
CAITLYN: Oh, please,
it's not, don't go there.
Just as much the Democrats.
It was not, please, please,
- please, please.
- JENNY: Caity, no, Caity, it... it's true.
- Caity, why are you insisting that?
- CAITLYN: No, it's not!
No, it's not.
- JENNY: It's not the truth?
- CAITLYN: Republicans and the conservatives
are not these horrible people out there
- trying to oppress people.
- JENNY: I didn't say they were terrible people.
- In this particular,
- CAITLYN: They're... they're
- they're not.
- in this... No, I know that.
I... I come from a Republican family.
CAITLYN: Sometimes these girls
think now that I've transitioned
that I, everything has to change.
You can't be conservative anymore.
You have to be a liberal.
Um, no, I don't believe that. I think,
uh, I can keep, um,
all of my views the same,
uh, 'cause I feel in my heart
that that's the best way to go.
I don't know anything of
what they said down there,
but I'm not blaming it on
Republicans and conservatives, okay?
JENNY: Well, I think you
need to take a look at that.
CAITLYN: Yeah. Oh, please.
- JENNY: No, you, please.
- CAITLYN: That's why you
- all need to go with me...
- JENNY: No, you... you, please!
- You need to look at it, Caity.
- CAITLYN: This is why you all need... No.
No, I'm not gonna identify that.
- We're not going there.
- JENNY: We are going there.
- That's why we're on this trip.
- CAITLYN: And... Oh, God.
JENNY: You're telling me Republicans
support rights for transgender people?
- You're telling me that the people...
- CAITLYN: I think they believe
in the Constitution and the
freedom of the Constitution.
- JENNY: So who overturned... ?
- CAITLYN: The... the public!
Because they're uninformed!
The politicians didn't even vote on it.
They just put it on the ballot.
KATE: Wait, there was an
ad that was put forward
by the former head of
the Republican party
in some county in Texas,
and it's a horrible ad about a man
who's standing outside the bathroom
- waiting for a little girl to go in.
- CAITLYN: Oh, yeah, I know, yeah, they, they use
the fear factor big time.
Now, he may have been Republican,
I don't know, he might've been
a Democrat. I don't know and so...
JENNY: No, it was not a Democrat.
"No men in women's bathrooms."
CAITLYN: Yeah, I agree. It just so
happens he happened to be a Republican.
I wish he was a damn Democrat.
That would've made my
argument much easier.
- CHANDI: It would've made your argument a lot easier.
- CAITLYN: A lot easier.
- If the guy was a...
- CANDIS: Yeah, but there's never been a Democrat
who's really stuck
her neck out like that
to take a stand against trans people.
It might not be a coincidence.
CAITLYN: This is not a
Democrat or Republican issue.
- This is a humanity issue
- JENNY: It is, but so far,
it's been a Republican issue to...
- to turn people...
- CAITLYN: It has not.
JENNY: We have 15 Republicans
running for president,
none of whom had stated publicly
that they're for trans rights
and many whom have stated
- that they are against us.
- CAITLYN: They're just not talking about it.
For the Republicans,
it's not a big issue.
The economy's the big issue.
They're just worried
about $18 trillion of debt.
Those are all those, much bigger issues.
JENNY: There is a
faction of people who uses
fear of trans people, fear of gay people
to bring people to the polls and...
- and it's generally...
- CAITLYN: But the Republicans, I don't feel like
they're out to get us.
CAITLYN: Every conservative guy out
there believes in everybody's rights.
JENNY: That has never
happened! That is a lie!
That has never happened!
CANDIS: I mean, it is
frustrating to me that Cait
doesn't see the obvious.
I mean, it's not like we're
saying, "No, the sky's pink.
No, really the sky is pink."
I don't know how to show
her without demeaning her
or making her feel less than,
because her party that she represents
doesn't believe in who
we are as trans people.
JENNY: You said you
wanted to know what is, uh,
your life as a woman gonna be like?
What does it mean to be a
woman besides hair and make-up?
It means support for a woman's life.
It means women's health care.
CAITLYN: No, uh, the
Republicans just look at it very
much differently. They're
just worried about much
bigger issues than the trans issues.
JENNY: The stakes are
very high. If she doesn't
listen to the rest of the community,
I think she's gonna find
herself isolated and irrelevant.
As a leader, you need to embrace
the fight for women's,
for women's lives.
CAITLYN: Yes, but we're 18 and
a half trillion dollars in debt...
our economy is going to collapse.
(Candis sighs)
The Democrats are
destroying the country.
- They should be really careful.
- KATE: Oh, dear.
CAITLYN: Okay?
CAITLYN: Our economy
is going to collapse.
The Democrats are
destroying the country.
- They should be really careful.
- KATE: Oh, dear.
CAITLYN: Okay?
ZACKARY: I really believe
the feminist slogan
"The personal is political."
And the thing that's
most important to me
is advocating for my
trans brothers and sisters.
ZACKARY: And from what I've
seen, the Democratic party
has advocated for trans people
- in a way that the Republicans have not.
- CAITLYN: No!
People look at the Democrats
as they are this
open-minded liberal group
who's gonna sit around
and help everybody.
Free education, free health
care, social programs, welfare,
disability, insurance...
free this, free that.
Well, right now, all those things
are just killing our economy.
I think what they don't
realize is this country
could collapse over this at some point.
And if our country collapses,
it doesn't make any difference
if you're gay, trans...
whatever issue... you're on
social programs, it's over.
JENNY: I do not want to argue about
the government from here
to San Francisco, okay?
CANDIS: I just think that
she's been living in this
conservative bubble for so long that
she doesn't really have any desire to...
- COURTNEY: To bring in any new information.
- CANDIS: ... to bring in any new information or ideas.
When it comes to debating politics
with Caitlyn, it's not a debate.
She just talks
what she believes in and she
doesn't listen to the other side,
which worries me. I'm at a loss.
You know?
WOMAN: Caitlyn Jenner,
you don't speak for us!
We didn't ask for your help!
CAITLYN: I had no idea how
difficult this trip would be.
JENNY: "No one wants to see a man in a
dress" sounds like you are putting down
people who look that way.
Did she tell you early on?
- KRIS: No.
- CAITLYN: Oh, I did, too.
KRIS: I didn't know until all of this.
- CAITLYN: Wait, let me finish.
- KRIS: I couldn't have given you the definition
of transgender.
CAITLYN: Besides the hair and
the make-up and the clothes,
what does it mean to be a woman?
(Paparazzi clamoring)
- CANDIS: We're all married!
- CAITLYN: We're all married!
KIM: Do you understand how
important a DMV photo is?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, baby.
CAITLYN: The fun part for me
is dragging all the girls along.
To see them broaden their horizons
and have some fun with this.
CHANDI: Oh.. Uh, uh...
(laughs) Okay, okay.
KYLIE: I wouldn't want
to be on a red carpet
with my vagina out.
- CAITLYN: Uh...
- KYLIE: My vagina.
(Crowd cheering)
KRIS: You guys have all
gotten a major ten from me.
Not you, Jenner, just your friends.
- (laughter)
- CAITLYN: I agree, I agree.
CANDIS: I could totally kiss you.
MAN: I don't think I
could really go there.
CANDIS: 'Cause of the trans thing?
MAN: It's a big issue, yes.
Candis.
CAITLYN: This is about
life and who you are.
It's almost like throwing old Bruce
out the door.
KATE: I know life is hard,
but that's what happens. You
build the world. It falls apart.
WOMAN: Today is the
Transgender Day of Remembrance
that honors those lives we've lost
in acts of anti-transgender violence.
CHANDI: Sometimes I feel like
I'm not there for her enough.
MAN: I see my daughter
blossom like a flower.
Your father's blossoming for you.
- ELLA: I love you.
- MAN: I love you.
CAITLYN: I need to evolve as a person
and deal with my issues head on.
There's just too much
at stake to get it wrong.
CANDIS: Oh, my God, I
think that's Hillary.
- CAITLYN: Hillary, come and meet my family...
- HILLARY: Oh, my gosh!
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -