He messaged back. So we're meeting.
Yeah, I have his number.
My high school crush...
I had called him and told him my feelings.
Just thinking that he's gonna
be out there is kind of weird.
Ella might get lucky.
You know we're going to Lamoni,
where I went to college.
It is a church-affiliated school.
I'm quite nervous about this.
Caitlyn Jenner,
you're an insult to all trans people.
- You don't represent us.
- _
Oh. Is that Hillary Clinton?
Oh, my God.
- Caitlyn.
- Hillary.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
You, like,
you want to pick a color
and we'll get you seated down there?
- Okay.
Should we all
go for the same color,
- for solidarity?
- Oh.
- That would be great.
- I love that idea.
A deep red?
See, she says a
deep red. Do you ever go red?
Never.
- Never, never.
- Then it's time, baby.
- Get out of your comfort zone.
- No, don't make me do it!
Oh, my gosh, look at these chairs.
Everybody, at the same time,
- turn on your vibrator.
- Oh, oh, yes.
- I know you will.
- Oh, yes.
_
The same color. The same color.
Because I... I, as far as, like...
I feel paralyzed by
the inability to make a decision.
I know. That's perfect.
- I feel the same way.
- Paralyzed.
- You know we're going to Lamoni...
- Mm-hmm.
... uh, where I went to college.
We're going to Iowa. First, Dubuque.
We're gonna meet this
wonderful lady, uh, Rachel,
who's really organized
her town on gender issues.
Then we're off to Des Moines,
where the Democratic debates are.
Should be interesting.
And then my old alma mater,
Graceland University. Iowa, here we come.
We're gonna do a presentation
to the student body.
Now, this is a church-affiliated school.
It's basically a branch
off of the Mormon religion.
But here's the deal:
I want to leave it open
to the student body to ask questions.
I mean, I've gotten a lot
of letters since coming out
and out of the religious side,
uh, about 50% are very positive.
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh, but on the other half,
there's a lot of negative
people. We've all seen it.
So they can ask any question they want.
You know we gonna be ready.
If we're speaking in front
of the student body, I
am actually gonna know
somebody going there.
- Oh...
- From my high school, yeah.
- No way. Went from your high school?
- Yeah.
My high school crush...
I... I had called him, um, junior year,
before my transition,
and told him my feelings.
_
Um... yeah. I, um,
I had been waiting for, like,
all of high school to
have a class with him.
Then I have it, senior year,
after I told him liked him
and I come back as Ella,
so it's this whole crazy thing.
Uh, it definitely was, like,
a weird... it was like, oh...
'Cause I didn't know we
were going to be speaking
in front of the student
body, and just thinking
that he's going to be out
there is kind of weird.
Are you okay? Or are you feeling...
You sound a little worried.
I'm...
I'm kind of nervous, you know?
If I were to, let's say, run into him,
it would be interesting to hear how...
'Cause I never talked to him about it.
How long ago was this?
- Uh, last year.
- Last year. So it's pretty recent.
(bleep)'s best... sorry, that's his name.
(bleep)'s best friend, um,
Michael... they're both at Graceland.
- They're both at Graceland?
- Oh, they're both there.
Yeah, it's really strange. Michael, um...
he was probably the only
guy who wrote in my yearbook,
and he wrote,
"I hope our paths cross again."
Ooh.
So this is the friend of the crush.
- The friend.
- No way.
Strange.
We gotta stay overnight in Lamoni.
- Yes, we gotta stay overnight.
- We can't just go through.
- I think we...
- No.
- Yeah, I think...
- Ella might get lucky.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Let's do it.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, Shannon.
Nice to meet you, also.
Chicago House, they asked me to come in.
They're having a big fund-raiser.
It is really a great organization.
They provide, uh, medical services,
uh, employment opportunities
and housing for our people
who are living on the streets,
who have, basically, no place to go.
And that is a huge
problem in this community.
Thank you.
It is so my pleasure to
be here for Chicago House.
My experience is not even close
to being the normal
experience in this community.
Yesterday, we got the
opportunity to go visit
a, kind of a subdivision of Chicago House
and it's the TransLife Center,
which really spotlights, um,
homelessness in the trans community.
When I got here, I was in a dark place.
I was in a domestic relationship.
I was 13, he was 21.
And I dated him... he
beat the crap out of me.
I finally got away and I started
doing drugs and drinking a lot.
I mean, even trying to
take care of myself...
I started sex work. I
did get raped before,
and I just want girls
younger than me to know that
you don't have to do it.
You know what, everybody
needs a break in life.
Everybody needs a chance in life.
And hopefully, by continuing
on this conversation,
we can make it better for
the next generation coming up.
Because there's lives at stake, here.
There are so many great
people in this community
and it's a pleasure to be part of it.
Thank you so much for having me
and letting me tell my story.
Huzzah!
Did I do okay?
- You did great.
- Nailed it, nailed it.
Thank you.
Caitlyn Jenner,
you're an insult to all trans people.
- You don't represent us.
- _
You're a disgrace to our community.
You have no right to speak for us.
_
Caitlyn Jenner, get away from us!
We don't get jobs, we don't get any money,
but you get all these awards.
It isn't all fun and games.
You don't care about the
real trans women of America.
_
You only care about
what you look like on TV.
We don't need you, we don't
want you. We don't want you here.
_
- _
We're going to the
Democratic debate tonight.
It's time to address
the elephant in the room.
Why is everybody looking at me?
He messaged back. So we're meeting.
Yeah, I have his number. I don't know
what people would think, seeing
one of the football players
sitting at lunch with Ella.
We don't want you. We don't want you here.
_
- _
Don't you (bleep) touch her!
- What the (bleep) is this?
- Leave!
Leave!
_
- I would love for you...
- _
_
Police want us to get in the car.
Have a good day.
Everybody in the van.
_
Baby, you can't even show your face,
so how are you gonna speak about
what's an insult to our community
and you can't even represent
yourself and show who you are?
What are you doing to
further our community?
If you're out here, willing to
invest your energy and your time
into trying to tear someone down,
you could be using that same
energy to lift someone up,
and you're not doing anything,
so what... what is the issue?
All trans people are convinced they have
the truth about trans,
- and nobody else is trans but them.
- Yeah. Right. Yeah.
- Uh, you know?
- You're doing it wrong.
I... I was trying to calm her down.
"Calm down, calm down,
calm down," you know?
It was the first time for Caitlyn
that she saw, in the flesh,
people's reservations about her.
Um, and I think that's
actually good for her.
There are a lot of people with very, um,
reasonable objections to her privilege,
um, maybe her sense of
womanhood or politics.
You know, Caitlyn is a public
figure for transgender people,
but she's a problematic figure,
and she needs to pay attention.
Time to get out of here.
Going back to good old Iowa.
- The bus.
- Hey!
So this is it.
So Mimi is from Iowa,
and I thought it would be
really cool if she came along.
I don't get to see her very often.
So any time spent with
my sister, I'm all for.
Hi, everyone. I had this dream.
I was on this trip
with, like, two serial killers.
Stop it.
I had, like,
this crazy nightmare.
I know, I hate that.
Next on the stop,
we're going to Dubuque,
Iowa. I live in Los Angeles.
Tons of resources.
People to help, programs to help.
But what happens if
you're in Dubuque, Iowa,
and you're trans? What
programs are available to you?
Oh, my God, look at this town.
- Is this Dubuque?
- Main Street, USA.
I've been through this...
these roads right here many times.
Ah, the sweet smell
Oh, it's so cute. Gorgeous. Of Iowa.
We made it to Dubuque.
- I... I love it already.
- I know.
Let's go shop.
- "Lingerie and jammies."
- Lingerie.
Lingerie. Let's go there.
- This way?
- Yeah. First stop.
Wait, why are we buying lingerie?
- Why not?
Silly question.
Jenny, do you have any lingerie?
Like, for... for Deedie?
Um, I have... I have lots of flannel.
I have logs of gingham.
Wait, I think the pink and black
would be good for you. Yeah.
You think... you think it would...
- kind of, open up a new door for me?
- Yeah, I think we need to... Yeah.
- Uh, it looks tremendously comfortable.
- Look-it,
look at how gorgeous,
these thigh-high stockings.
Oh yeah, 'cause, you know, I could
wear these when I'm shoveling snow.
You know, for me...
lingerie is... is not simple.
It's a fairly complicated thing.
But have you ever worn a garter?
I'm trying to think. I think...
I think one time when I was bear huntin'.
- Goddamn you.
- But I kind of like this.
And I'm sure Deedie will too.
_
I think so too.
Well, let's... let's participate.
Is it me?
It could be.
Jenny Boylan's got a secret.
- Oh, I don't know what you're t...
- She's got a naughty secret.
I got some candles. I got some candles
and some, uh, playing cards.
I think what all the
girls should sample...
their first time with mountain oysters.
Oh, what is that? Something weird.
Like, balls or something.
Isn't it balls?
- Bulls' testicles.
- Yes.
- Let's not and say we did.
- Yeah.
- I like the way you think, Chandi.
Right.
Come on in! Hello, babe.
- Hi. How are you?
- Have a seat right here.
- These are all the girls.
- Hello, gang. Nice to meet you.
Now, you probably have never had this many
- girls like us in this town...
- Yeah, no.
- This... this is a first, for sure.
- Isn't that good?
- Yay!
- Great.
- I like firsts.
- Nice to see you all.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I like firsts.
So what are we... what
are gonna do tonight?
Well, I was a dealer at the casino...
I still am... and we're gonna
have some blackjack tables.
You're gonna get to deal
to the people in Dubuque.
How rad is that? That's like a Bond movie.
One of my doctors
mentioned to me when I was going
through transition here in Dubuque,
uh, why didn't I move to somewhere larger
that I might be more accepted there?
I was pretty much the only one
in this area when I came out.
Um, and I said, "Because
people need to be aware
that there's transgender
people everywhere."
So I knew that's why I had
to stay here in Dubuque.
You are just a gutsy little
thing, aren't you? I love that.
Usually what changes a person's mind
about trans in general is
the moment they meet a trans person.
So Caitlyn and all of us ladies in tow
coming to Dubuque, now they got to meet...
any number of us and see that...
we're sweet.
Put your money on the table. Let's go.
Are you ready? I'm taking your money.
Okay, let's deal you up and you up.
And then we flip one over.
Just want you to know
I've been counting cards.
_
I'm Rachel. By the
way, welcome to Dubuque.
Nice to meet you, Rachel;
come on in the middle.
You get in the middle.
You got it.
Thank you. Nice to meet you.
- Hey, thank you.
- _
_
With... with what? With coming out?
- Yeah, and I just...
- How old are you?
I'm 13. You're how long?
13.
Surround yourself with positive people.
Uplifting people. People
who want to see you do well.
Anybody give you any trash in your life,
get them the hell out of your life.
There's a lot of great,
loving people out there.
Pick your friends wisely.
- Be yourself.
- That was really amazing meeting Caitlyn.
She's such an inspiration to
everyone in the LGBT community.
I just wanted to thank her
so much for being herself.
Look at all these people in this room.
You know, there's so many
good people out there.
Find the right ones.
- Life will be good.
- I'm so glad I got to meet her,
and it was just one of
the best days of my life.
You got it. Good luck to you.
- Thanks.
- Okay?
- Let's move it.
- Let's move it out.
Good-bye, Dubuque.
Howdy, Des Moines.
May... may I kindly have
your attention, please.
We're approaching Des Moines.
Um, it's time to address
the elephant in the room.
- We're going to the Democratic...
- There's an elephant in the room?
There is an elephant in the
room, Miss Caitlyn, there is.
We're going to the Democratic
debate tonight, and...
there we're gonna be sitting in a room
with young Republicans...
and young Democrats.
I would like to see if we can
come to some agreed-upon guidelines
- so that the firestorm last time in Santa Fe...
- Hey! Okay...
... doesn't happen again.
I would like to suggest a safeword.
Like, if I blow up or go,
"Gah! I hate Trump!"
You're not allowed to say it like that.
Safeword: "God bless America."
- God bless America.
♪ God bless America ♪
♪ Our home sweet home... ♪
Great!
So anyone of...
in this group says, "God bless America,"
we immediately go, "Holy
(bleep), am I being off the wall?"
- And we back... back down.
- Why is everybody looking at me?
In a room full of people we don't know,
we don't want to insult anybody there.
We don't want to get into
fights with the Republicans.
We don't want to get into fights
with the Democrats, Caitlyn.
- Let's also take into account that college students...
- We're, we have to show ourselves
as higher human beings.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
We've, we've been such a loving group,
and I would like to see us continue that
under what could be some stress.
I'm a little nervous,
uh, that... that Caitlyn will
not be able to meet in the middle
when it comes to her political beliefs,
because I think people don't
really want to hear about
Caitlyn being a Republican.
And so it makes me nervous that
she's gonna go off on a rant
and, um, I won't know how
to protect her from that.
I'm practicing right now
by keeping my mouth shut.
Is that Hillary Clinton?
Caitlyn.
He doesn't really appreciate this country.
God bless America. God bless America.
Now you're talking someone down.
Look at the bulldog.
Hi, I'm Lucille from Drake University.
- Welcome back.
- It's nice to meet you,
- thank you. Thank you.
- It's nice to meet you as well.
The Democratic debates
are at Drake University
in Des Moines, Iowa. In
1970, at that university,
I ran my first decathlon.
1978 inductee.
- _
- Holy wow...
This, this is where I ran
my first ever decathlon.
- This is where it all began.
- This is the old place.
Oh, my God, no!
Oh, the old, the old Drake Relays.
There we go, baby!
You know, even though I'm transitioned
and my life is so different today,
I'm proud of that aspect of my life.
Should we all line up like we're racing?
No. You'll be okay, don't worry.
I don't want you to hurt yourself.
I'm not moving. I'm just getting down.
Okay, well, I'm hoping you
can get back up again...
- that's the problem.
- Right.
You know where the debates are?
They're right here. So we got to
get home, back and get changed?
- Yeah!
- Let's get it going!
Let's do it!
So, we'll give you a few
instructions to get started.
Over here on the tables,
you can make your name tags.
Um, we have blue if you
identify as Democrat,
red for Republicans and
white for anything else.
This will be fun tonight.
- It will be interesting.
- Yeah, it should be fun.
You know?
See all the free stuff
Hillary's gonna give out.
- You know, it's gonna be good.
- What do you mean "free stuff"?
- Well, that's all she does.
- Uh-huh.
Uh, she never says how we're
gonna pay for it, but...
Yeah?
Caitlyn's conservative politics
are a concern for all of us.
And I wonder how she'll be received.
All right, everyone, uh,
it's just a couple of minutes
until the debate starts, so
if you want to find your seats.
Remember if you want to
sit on the Democratic side,
it's over here, the Independent
side is in the middle
and the Republicans over there.
Hi!
- Hi, Cait!
- Hi!
- I'm a Republican tonight.
Okay,
go Auntie Kate!
Please welcome to Drake University,
former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton.
_
God bless America.
Now you're talking someone down.
- I haven't said that all...
- I'm talking his policy,
_
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
But think about it...
God bless America.
_
Senator Sanders, in you said
a previous debate, the greatest
threat to national security
was climate change. Do
you still believe that?
_
He's an idiot.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Sorry, sorry.
- What he just said was stupid, I agree.
- He's misinformed.
- I agree.
_
- Okay, okay.
- _
- I like this. Okay, great.
- Yeah, really.
- _
- Okay.
_
- It is.
- Yeah.
I'm... I'm going yay.
I... I give her a B-plus
for really trying to listen
and... and communicate.
I think we really are coming to a point
where we can talk with each other. I mean,
you saw what happened in
Santa Fe... we could not
talk with each other.
I had to leave the room.
I have not had to leave the room
and I've only had to sing "God
Bless America" three times.
I want to ask some of
guests that are with us today
what do you think's been good so far
and what would you maybe critique?
I think people are being a little
tough on Hillary, personally.
I'd be happy to have any of
these people as president.
Okay, Caitlyn, do you, you got a red one,
so from the Republican side...
Coming out trans was like nothing,
until I said I was a Republican.
Um, it's kind of an
interesting situation for me.
They keep talking about the top 1%,
the top one... Oh, these
terrible people, okay?
I'm in the top 1%.
I don't even have Obamacare
and I had to put $450,000 in there.
The healthcare's going to be worse, so
I think we need a better tax structure.
Oh, I know, all my girls down here.
I got all my girls down here!
How we settle all our problems
at the end... are you ready?
♪ God bless America. ♪
That's it, okay. But
that's how we settle it,
- because we all love our country.
- Thank you.
- But I'm being very good!
- You are, you are,
- you are, you are.
- Aren't I doing good?
- You're doing much better.
- Thank you.
You're doing great.
Is that Hillary Clinton?
Oh, my God!
Caitlyn.
Hillary.
It is a church-affiliated school.
So, Chandi,
if we say something and
they come after you...
I can't just sit there
and... and... and take that.
You should sit next to 'em.
Ask good questions, 'cause I
don't think I'll be able to talk.
Okay.
It's just, like, that
nervous, like, why him?
Hi.
Oh, my God!
Is that Hillary Clinton?
Caitlyn.
Hillary.
Oh, my gosh!
Good to see you. What are you doing here?
Did you come for the debate?
- Yes.
- Of course we did.
How funny is that?
We are on the road.
These are all my girls.
- There's Candis...
- Hi, guys.
- How are you all?
- Great job tonight.
Thank you so much!
We're cheering you on.
_
Oh, that's great.
- Yes.
- So anything you can do to help.
Yeah, we're trying to figure
out a way we can do that.
- Good.
- So we're, uh, we're moving along, you know?
And these are the most
fun girls to be with.
_
- _
- Likewise.
With Hillary Clinton, we
were all so star struck,
and Caitlyn was, too.
You know, even though she
kind of wanted to deny it,
it was so palpable to me that I
was like, "Oh, she's loving this.
She's meeting a
presidential front-runner."
- Got it?
- Yep, we got it.
- Excellent.
- All right.
Thank you all. Great to see you.
- Say hello to your family, too.
- I will.
- Yeah!
- That was so awesome.
_
- _
- Not me.
_
You know, Hillary
Clinton, she's very sweet.
Very nice. And who, like, two
minutes later comes by but...
Bill.
_
He volunteered for a picture.
- Overall, I thought it was great.
- _
Wow, that was pretty monumental.
I'm gonna have a Strawberry Bitch.
Come on. Boom.
I mean, if anything, it's fun to order.
We also have a Jackass.
Every bar has one of those.
So I just got the guts to message Michael.
And I said, "Hey,
Michael, long time no talk,
uh, but I'm actually going
to be in Graceland tomorrow
with Caitlyn and, um, I was
wondering if you'd want to meet."
And, like, he, like... he messaged back.
He gave me his number and he said, "Yeah,
it would be totally awesome. "
He's like, " (bleep) is sleeping,
but I'll ask him when he wakes up."
- Ooh.
- So we're meeting.
- Yeah, I have his number.
- Bravo.
So, Cait, we're gonna be on your
old stomping grounds tomorrow.
No idea of what we're
gonna be up against, or... ?
Well, I heard they're also gonna open
it up to questions from the student body.
It is a church-affiliated school.
So, Chandi, if we say something
and they come after you,
- you gotta...
- I don't know, Cait.
I can't say that I
won't say it and mean it.
Don't scare me like this.
I really can't say that,
in... in... in order...
I can't just sit there
and... and take that.
You gotta realize that that's the college
where I graduated and those...
those people were very good.
To be honest with you, going
back to Graceland, I'm... I'm
quite nervous about this.
I can see where the girls are coming from.
You know, if somebody would
come after 'em, they're gonna...
you know, they're fighters,
all of these girls are fighters.
But what they have to realize
is also that I have a
relationship, uh, with this school.
I was very good
and treated Hillary Clinton
with a lot of respect and I...
I want them to treat the student body
and the teachers here
with this same respect,
uh, in the way they handle these issues.
As long as they don't
tell me that I'm a sinner
for being who I am, I'll be okay.
But if they do...
If they do, that's another problem.
Guys, hold it. This is big.
The coaches while I was there...
I was really wondering what
their reaction is going to be.
Are you ready?
- We're ready!
- Ready.
Let's do it.
This conservative school...
What are people gonna think?
I see you're getting nervous.
I'm nervous for them,
because they're gonna be so overwhelmed
with all these beautiful trans women
and, like, so much to, you know, take in.
And how sweet are you,
to be worrying about them
when you should be worrying about you?
I wasn't necessarily the...
the coolest person in high
school. I don't know what
people would think, seeing
one of the football players
sitting at lunch with Ella.
Men in general, when it comes to
putting yourself in that
situation, where you're
publically viewed either
intimately with a trans woman
or just friendly with a trans woman.
This conservative school...
What are people gonna think?
Oh, you're coming with your posse, girl,
- you gotta get over it.
- Yeah.
- With your girl gang.
- You right.
You coming with your
posse and you're all good
and that's the zone you
need to focus and be in.
Out of anyone that I went to school with,
it had to be him
and his best friend at Graceland.
- They're gonna be so excited.
- Like Zackary said,
you should be looking at it
as an opportunity to shine.
Everybody on their best behavior.
- (bleep) A.
I like that attitude, girls!
Actually, I was doing pretty
good on the whole ride down here.
Now I'm actually kind of nervous.
Yeah, I never wore heels at Graceland.
- I'm John Sellars.
- Caitlyn. How are you doing?
Caitlyn, great to have you here.
- My pleasure.
- We've been looking forward to it.
Yeah, this is pretty cool.
Guys, hold it. This is big.
- This is Jerry Hampton.
- Oh, God, it's good to see you.
- How you doing?
- I'm doing good, really.
You're still here!
And Bill Dudek. How are you doing?
Hey, good to see you. Good to see you.
When I was at Graceland,
as far as my identity, I
had my diversions in life
and I found sports and I
could be "the guy" in sports.
And Jerry Hampton was one of
the coaches while I was there,
and Bill Dudek, one of the other
coaches. I was really wondering
what their reaction is going to be.
They were sure bragging
on you in my office.
- Oh, really?
- They were talking about you
as a student and how
proud they are of you.
I know they're gonna be telling you that.
Yeah, well, I appreciate that.
Should I sit on the other
side, or sit here, next to them?
No, you should sit next to 'em.
Ask good questions, 'cause
I don't think I'll be able to talk.
Okay.
I'm... I don't even
have feelings anymore,
it's just like that nervous, like,
"Why him?" You know? But I need to
remember that high school's over,
we're all adults here, and, um, I hope
that we'll have a nice conversation.
Thank you.
Hi.
- Michael. Hello, Michael, how are you?
- Hey, Ella, how you doing?
I'm doing good. How are you?
Good, I'm doing awesome. This is Jenny.
- Hi, Jenny, nice to meet you.
- Hi. What's your name?
- Michael. Nice to meet you.
- Michael, it's a pleasure to meet you.
- Pleasure meetin' you.
- Now, did you have another friend that was coming?
We had a class together
today and he didn't go.
And when I went back to
the room, after my class,
he wasn't there. And I texted
him, like, "Hey, where are you?"
No reply and... I haven't
gotten a reply. Yeah.
How did you go about, like,
keeping on to your transformation
and still acknowledging God in your life?
Chandi.
- How?
- I got this one.
Now, did you have another
friend that was coming?
We had a class together
today and he didn't go.
And when I went back to
the room, after my class,
he wasn't there. And I texted
him, like, "Hey, where are you?"
No reply and...
I haven't gotten a reply. Yeah.
The fact that (bleep) didn't
come kind of showed me that...
I mean, it didn't... I don't even
know if it really showed me anything.
He might have just been
nervous, you know? Um...
you can't blame him for that.
Uh, I definitely do want to give
full kudos to Michael though,
for him to kind of come in there,
knowing that he was going to
be in front of a camera alone.
What was it like for you when
Ella went through her transition?
Um, I think my first time I saw her,
uh, at the Ventura County Fair.
I came in my high-waisted shorts
and a little crop top. No, terrible.
First thing I thought was,
"Oh, maybe she transferred
from a different school, like,
out of state or something like that,
and everybody just happens
to know her but me."
I was like, "Okay." Then when
I made eye contact with her,
I was like, "Wow." I was
kind of, like, in awe,
like, that she, like, came out like that.
- I thought that was very bold.
- Mike.
- Yes.
- You're a gentleman.
- Thank you.
- Gentleman, yes.
You are.
- Ready to go do this, babe?
- Let's do it.
I hope that the girls respect
that this is my school,
this is where I went to college,
this is where my name is
on the whole sports complex.
I just don't want to do
anything to upset anybody.
I want this to be informative
for the students and the faculty
to learn something about our community.
- Are you ready?
- We're ready.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
- We got your back.
Today Graceland students have
a great opportunity to
have a discussion about
gender identity, so
I'm very, very excited.
There are no wrong questions.
I, I thought I was nervous
before we got to Graceland College, but
my stomach is just dropping.
You know, after having the
lunch with Michael and, um,
the other boy not showing up,
I don't know what to expect.
You ask what you feel you should ask.
It's very nerve-racking.
My question is,
how did you go about keeping
onto your journey of, like,
your transformation and still
acknowledging God in your life?
Because, like, religion and everything.
How?
- Chandi?
- I got this one.
Well, it actually was hard.
I grew up in a very religious family.
Many years I heard that
my life was an abomination.
So I lost touch with God for many years.
I had to recognize the fact that
God knew who I was before I did.
So how can I be falling out of touch
with God when he knew before I did.
It's a connection that I've made
that now that I have,
I'll never let it go again.
My daughter is a high-ranking
executive in the Church of Scientology.
And to Scientologists, my trans-ness
is proof that I am an evil person
and should not be talked with. So
I haven't seen her since she was nine.
She's now 42, 43 years old.
I haven't completely given up hope.
I haven't, and especially
getting some strength from the
women I'm traveling with now.
And just being able to say this to you.
Look for the heart of the
doctrine you're following.
And if it's at all mean,
think twice before
following it any further.
Thank you.
So, my question is
what kind of pronouns should we
be using when referring to you?
Uh, for me the pronoun thing changed
immediately when Vanity Fair came out.
- Now I go by, uh, "she."
- I prefer the pronoun "they."
I don't mind "she."
I go by Beyonc pronouns.
Boom!
Okay, so my question is
how has living as a woman
and facing the woes in life,
living as a woman, affected you?
I, I don't know. I feel
ten times more powerful as a woman.
I do.
I always felt
nothing made sense before,
and as soon as I transitioned,
I had a light inside me that
nobody's gonna (bleep) with me.
I'm sorry.
I think that the... the
power is... is great,
but I think in relationships,
it allows me to think like he's thinking.
I still can recognize game.
- And I love that part.
- Yeah!
Can I get a witness?
Um, I honestly think being a woman
has nothing to do with the
physicality of our beings.
Um, I am the same exact person
I was, uh, before my transition.
Your life is always evolving and
not every day is going to be the best day.
- Right.
- But you know,
you can make it the best
day as possible, so...
I totally love Ella,
and before we left on the trip,
I told her, "Ella, we
want you to be a sponge
and we want you to absorb all
this knowledge that is around you."
And in that moment, she
was just so poised and
just being able to see her grow around us
and see how we're all
individually rubbing off on her
makes that so beautiful.
I just want to get your input
on how happy you guys are right now?
'Cause you guys look happy.
Honestly, for years
and years, I struggled.
I would literally go to my house,
uh, never really coming
out. That was really,
really tough times for me.
And I had lost that spirit for life,
because I just didn't know who I was.
I have to admit today...
I can't wait...
I can't wait for the day to get started.
I'm excited about life.
I got things to do.
I love myself.
That was a long struggle.
In Graceland College,
I think in some ways
the tables were turned.
I think that it was Caitlyn's turn to be
a little bit afraid of what we might say.
But everybody on that stage
was remarkably eloquent.
We didn't know how we were gonna
be received when we got there.
And people were not just respectful,
but interested and
supportive, which I think
- caught us all by surprise.
- What a privilege it has been
to talk to all my little
brothers and sisters of Graceland.
Go out there, be your true self.
And kick butt and work hard.
_
- I figured.
- It's always about the bad stuff,
so thank you for that.
Did I do okay, buddy?
_
- Thank you.
- _
_
- No, there's, there's mostly great...
- _
_
Those girls I got with me
are just phenomenally good.
I think probably the most
important thing of of my story
is that no matter what your situation is,
that... that they can live
their lives authentically.
They can overcome the obstacles
that they have in life.
'Cause everybody has them.
That's my mission. Team
Caitlyn, you guys did good!
- You guys did so good!
- You were really great.
I'm so proud of you!
It's not just trans issues.
It's about dealing with all
of our stuff that we have.
Thank you for bringing me there.
I was a little nervous and I was a
little hard on you and I... I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay.
And I'm gonna be more open to...
Say it.
I'll be a little bit more open
to your conservative views.
Ooh, I like that.
I love that.
- We still got a long ways to go.
- We do.
- We're only in Lamoni.
- I know!
We have plenty of time to discuss.
Pick it up. Squat down.
This trainer, he's really yummy.
And he seems like he's flirting back.
This is the longest I've
been without a relationship.
I think it might be
just around the corner.
- Disick is in the house.
- Hello!
Scott is kind of unpredictable.
I... I hope we see the good side.
I haven't talked to you all night.
I know.
_
No, I'm not ignoring him...
- he's over there.
- I'm gonna put myself to bed.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -