- KENDALL: Her name in my phone is "Mad."
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
- KENDALL: 'Cause she's a little mad.
- KYLIE: Yeah.
(laughter)
- CAITLYN: Road trip, baby.
- CANDIS: Wow!
JENNY: This bus trip was Caitlyn's idea.
She thought it was gonna be fun.
(cheering)
She needs to realize that
she's not gonna get a pass anymore.
- CAITLYN: Democratic National Debate.
- CHANDI: Right.
We're so excited that
Cait's even gonna go.
- CANDIS: I'm excited for Cait.
- CHANDI: Right.
And sit and listen to the Democrats.
- CAITLYN: It's the last place I want to be.
- CHANDI: I know. I know.
CAITLYN: They're all
Democrats. I'm the only
conservative Republican on the bus.
We're 18 and a half
trillion dollars in debt.
Our economy is going to collapse.
(Candis sighs)
The Democrats are
destroying the country.
KATE: Oh, dear.
- CAITLYN: Okay?
- JENNY: I do not want to argue about
the government from here
to San... to Santa Fe.
The stakes are very high.
If she doesn't
listen to the rest of the community,
I think she's gonna find
herself isolated and irrelevant.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
(steady wiping)
(music playing faintly)
CAITLYN: Yay!
We made it to New Mexico,
the Land of Enchantment.
Whatever that means.
- (Kip laughs)
- Um, yeah, m...
And where's everybody?
They're in the back.
After all the political talk,
they went to the back and went to sleep.
- KIP: It tuckered 'em out.
- CAITLYN: I think I just... Yeah.
- Put 'em right to sleep.
- (Kip laughs)
CANDIS: (sighs) It just
frustrates me sometimes.
But at the end of the
day, I realize that, like,
we have a lot of differences.
But this trip is gonna help
girls that are coming up and
seeing all of us together.
And somebody, like, of your age
- can learn a lot from all of us women.
- ELLA: Yeah.
I'm definitely at an age where
I am soaking everything up.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- ELLA: Definitely. Yeah.
You know, just graduating high
school, I definitely feel like
I am getting more than an abundance
of education from all the women
about our issues and,
um, politically as well.
CANDIS: Who do people
tell you you look like?
ELLA: Who do you think I look like?
- CANDIS: Natalie Portman.
- ELLA: It's weird, 'cause my whole family,
they all look like Natalie Portman.
It's... it's really strange.
You remind me of a really
gorgeous, gorgeous, gorgeous actress.
Candis Cayne. That's
who you remind me of.
- CANDIS: Stop it.
- (Ella laughs)
- Stop.
- ELLA: There goes Candis with her hair.
(Candis laughs)
(Ella chuckles)
CANDIS: Oh, my God, the
bathroom smells so bad,
but I really have to pee.
Ooh, that is so bad.
Jesus Christ!
Oh, my God, that's awful!
- (laughter)
- Ugh!
CHANDI: The bus is totally great,
although the bathroom
doesn't smell that great.
ELLA: The sewage isn't
really working that well,
so it smells like a...
- (Candis coughing)
- _
CANDIS: Jesus.
KATE: The bathroom on the bus,
goodness, goodness, goodness.
- (exhales)
- CANDIS: Oh.
- CAITLYN: Oh, my God.
- CANDIS: (laughs)
Excuse me!
You got a lot of nerve callin' me out!
No privacy in this damn bus.
It's like...
Oh. Oh, my God, that is hideous.
- ELLA: Okay, but let me go.
- CANDIS: Good luck.
- (spraying)
- Really?
- KATE: We have been room freshened.
- CHANDI: Right.
You smell mangos and peaches.
- (laughter)
- CANDIS: Oh, that is so bad up in that.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
- That is one wrong bathroom.
- (laughter)
KATE: Courtney, question,
"tranny" has been around
as a word since the '70s.
- COURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
- KATE: I don't call myself a woman;
I do call myself a tranny.
And transgender women have
a lot of problems with that.
COURTNEY: So it used to
be an acceptable term?
KATE: "Tranny" was a family word.
COURTNEY: But now
that's, like, derogatory.
KIP: Is that... So is it okay between
trans women to still use that word?
Or it's just better not to say it?
KATE: No. No. I don't think so.
The people who object to the
word "tranny" are people who...
are very invested in being
women, not trans folk.
COURTNEY: Even some trans women
think that word's offensive,
even for them to use as well.
- JENNY: And I would... I would be one of them.
- COURTNEY: Yeah.
JENNY: Kate and I have
known each other for decades.
I've taught her books
even before I came out.
I taught, um, Gender Outlaw.
You know, I've been a fan of her work
forever, but we see
things very differently.
If I hear that word, I will
generally leave the room.
I find it really hurtful.
And I recognize that there are other
people who own that word proudly,
and that is fantastic for them.
Um, it's not fantastic for me.
For me, it is like... like
saying the F-word to a... a gay man
or the N-word to...
to a person of color.
It's a word I associate with
beatings, being diminished,
being on the receiving end of violence.
KATE: Did you have an experience?
Were you attacked and...
and yelled at and hurt?
- I'm so sorry, baby.
- JENNY: Yeah, more than once.
JENNY: Somebody, um...
uh, uh, grabbed me by the neck,
used that word, um, and other
words, dragged me around, um,
you know, by my neck
for about a half an hour
and finally dropped me.
And I lay there on the
ground, kind of unable to move.
Words can hurt as much as...
um, violence can.
For... for me, it's
still a triggering word.
KATE: We... we developed
the word "tranny" ourselves.
JENNY: Yeah, I'm not sure the
guys who were beating me up
- thought of it in those terms.
- KATE: No.
Our word got stolen. We are using it
in the way we've always used
it, with love and respect.
And you need to hear the
love and respect in my voice
when I say the word casually
and you happen to hear it.
JENNY: And I hope you
know you're asking a lot.
For me, Kate.
That's... that's not an
easy thing for me to do.
KATE: Ask a lot from me.
Yes, I know I'm asking
a lot. It's my name.
It's who I am.
It's... it's the love I have
for my queer, queer trans family.
JENNY: And I love you,
but it's not my name.
KATE: Oh, I get that. I get that.
CAITLYN: I'm, you know,
obviously new to the community.
I heard a lot of people
call it, in the past,
"tranny" or this or that.
Fortunately, I had never
developed the habit,
so it was easy to change. Jenny Boylan,
Kate Bornstein look at
this issue very differently.
They've both written books on it.
They're both very smart.
And so for me, it's great, 'cause
I love taking a little bit here,
taking a little bit there, put it
in my little computer in my head,
and find out what works for me.
KATE: We're on the same side
but a totally different track.
ELLA: I think that's...
that's evident, but...
JENNY: You think... Is it evident? I
don't... I don't think of myself as being
really so far from... from
Kate, but I think that we...
ELLA: No, you guys are very alike.
I think you both are so
intellectually on the same level...
JENNY: Well, we're both...
we're both brilliant.
ELLA: Kate,
I love her freedom.
And she has this perspective
that can sometimes
be dangerousterritory,
- especially for Jenny.
- JENNY: I think that Kate
celebrates people who
don't fit into any...
compartment, and particularly
binary compartments.
I don't think of myself as an
outlaw because of my gender.
And my identity as a woman
is a... is much more
important to me than my
identity as... as a trans woman.
KATE: I think what I opened the doors to
is my notion that
gender is more than two.
- JENNY: Yeah.
- KATE: And gender doesn't
rely on anatomy or biology.
When I let my hair
down, I'm... you know,
tranny this, tranny
that, let's go, trannies!
And I don't, to this day,
claim to be a woman.
And this is where we kind of differ,
because as far as I know, I'm the
only not-man-not-woman on this bus.
I identify myself as a
non-binary trans person.
I call myself a tranny.
I've been a tranny for 30 years.
If you want me as part of
your family, you say my name.
ELLA: We're all trying
to get to the same place.
JENNY: Are we gonna be having this
conversation for the next month?
KATE: I will probably come back to it.
To be the object of disgust...
that's how I spent my first 20 years
as a trans person.
I was disgusting to people.
And I still am an object of disgust.
It really gets me in the gut
to receive that from L, G, B or T.
ELLA: Have you ever played fluffy bunny?
- (Candis laughing)
- (exclaiming)
(laughing)
KATE: Hillary Clinton or Donald Trump?
CAITLYN: Oh, my God, I would
never, ever, ever vote for Hillary.
JENNY: Kill me now. Someone kill me now.
CAITLYN: If Hillary becomes president,
the country is over.
CANDIS: Tell me the things
she's horrible about.
CAITLYN: Look at all the things
that are going on in the Middle East,
all because of what she did.
She's a (bleep) liar.
(phone rings)
CAITLYN: Hey, guys.
It's my mother, the winner of the
PFLAG Betty DeGeneres Award
for outstanding support.
- Say hi!
- (cheering)
- CANDIS: Hi, Mom!
- CAITLYN: They all say hi.
All right, Mom. Love
you. Have a good night.
(beep)
- My mother called me. You know why?
- ELLA: Why?
CAITLYN: She's telling me how much
she's really starting
to like Donald Trump.
COURTNEY: What?
- (Caitlyn laughs)
- (groaning)
- CHANDI: Wah, wah, wah.
- JENNY: Wah-wah.
COURTNEY: What?
'Cause you're the... you're
the only person she could call
- that was gonna celebrate that.
- CAITLYN: I know.
COURTNEY: That's why.
CAITLYN: She just hates what's going on.
She's seeing this country...
- All of her husbands fought in World War II.
- CANDIS: No, no, no, no!
CAITLYN: You know, land
in Omaha Beach. My dad
fought for this country.
And now we're giving it away.
CHANDI: What do you
think of Donald Trump?
CAITLYN: Um, I'm not a big fan,
because I think of his macho attitude.
I think he would have
a hard time with women,
when he doesn't even realize it.
And it doesn't mean he wouldn't
be good for women's issues.
I think he would be very
good for women's issues.
- COURTNEY: What?
- JENNY: Kill me now.
Someone kill me now.
CAITLYN: I don't think he's
out there to destroy women
or take things away or do
any of that kind of stuff.
I don't think my views have changed
politically since transitioning.
You know, we're talking
about the economy.
We're talking about
our country surviving.
We're talking about an economic
system that can prosper.
Just because I'm a woman now
doesn't make me all of a sudden liberal.
KATE: Hillary Clinton or Donald Trump?
CAITLYN: Oh, my God,
I would never, ever,
ever vote for Hillary. We're done.
If... if Hillary becomes president,
the country is over.
- CANDIS: Oh, my God.
- CAITLYN: You can't
fix immigration. You
can't fix the economy.
- CANDIS: Oh, my God.
- CAITLYN: You know?
CANDIS: The Kool-Aid.
- The Kool-Aid.
- CAITLYN: We don't have a country.
- And Hillary will not do it.
- CANDIS: She's an amazing woman.
CAITLYN: Tell me what she's
done that's good. Tell me.
- _
- CAITLYN: Please.
- CHANDI: So you're a Republican up there, too?
- _
- CHANDI: Okay.
So he's cosigning for Cait.
CAITLYN: No, he's... he's
a conservative American.
He's an American, yeah. Yeah.
CHANDI: Nothing against you.
Boo, I still love you, too, but
I just needed everybody to
know that you're cosigning.
(chuckles)
CANDIS: But, you know, there
is a lot to love about Hillary.
She's an amazing woman.
Things that she's done in
her life have been incredible!
- To go through...
- CAITLYN: What has she done in her life?
- What has she done...
- CANDIS: With the rights that... that...
of women that she's gone through,
it's been incredible!
She's become a lawyer when it
was so hard to become a lawyer.
- CAITLYN: What has she done?
- CANDIS: She has served our Senate.
She was our Secretary of State.
CAITLYN: And she was a lousy senator.
- CANDIS: She wasn't a lousy Senator.
- CAITLYN: She was horrible!
- CANDIS: Tell me!
- CAITLYN: Look at all the things that are going on
- Tell me the things she was horrible about!
- in the Middle East.
All because of what she did. Look at...
look at Benghazi. She lied to us.
- CANDIS: She didn't lie to us.
- CAITLYN: She's a (bleep) liar.
CANDIS: When it comes to
debating politics with Caitlyn,
it's not a debate.
She just talks and is yelling at us.
That's an uncomfortable situation.
CAITLYN: You want a person
that's gonna lie to you?
And then lied again about it
- and lied again about it?
- _
CANDIS: I'm gonna go to the other room.
CAITLYN: And then all of her e-mails.
- CHANDI: Okay, okay.
- CAITLYN: She's a political hack.
KATE: Oh, boy.
CAITLYN: That's all she
is. She's done nothing.
CHANDI: Okay. I... I have
to... I have to listen.
I think, in a position where
there were so many people
against Republicans,
made her really defensive.
CAITLYN: Cleared this room out.
CHANDI: Cleared it out.
Nobody wants to talk
to you right now, Cait.
(horse neighs)
CAITLYN: Today, the next adventure.
- CHANDI: Ooh. Uh, uh...
- (horse neighs)
Whoa. I don't know what I'm doing.
(horse neighs)
CAITLYN: I look at all the issues,
I think, in a much different way
than most people in this
room look at the issues.
JENNY: It's not about the
issues. We're telling you,
we were scared.
Oh, where's Candis?
I just got into a full
screaming match with Caitlyn.
- With Caitlyn.
- KIP: You did?
What did we miss?
- CANDIS: About Hillary Clinton.
- COURTNEY: What?
(Candis sighs)
CANDIS: I think Cait,
she was disrespecting us
in the way she was talking to us.
I mostly got upset that
she wasn't listening
to what we were saying.
She was talking down to us
about our views and what
she knew to be true,
- um, and was yelling at us.
- COURTNEY: She screamed?
She screamed? How loud?
- CANDIS: I don't know.
- JENNY: Loud enough for Candis to come back here.
CANDIS: Yeah.
CAITLYN: Tell me one
good thing she's done.
ZACKARY: Where is
this anger coming from?
- CAITLYN: Where's the what?
- ZACKARY: This anger coming from.
You seem like you're
really angry about this.
CAITLYN: It's so upsetting
to me to see where this...
where this whole thing is headed.
ZACKARY: You know, I
really appreciate debate,
um, but I'm really reticent
to engage ifsomebody's
at an escalated pitch with their voice.
You know, I try to be as,
like, diplomatic as possible,
and especially when
it comes to politics.
Um, Hillary Clinton, when
she was Secretary of State,
was the person who
spearheaded the effort
to make it easier for trans people
to change their gender
marker on their passports.
CAITLYN: That is very good for us, okay?
But we are .8% of the population,
and that is a very small thing.
ZACKARY: Listen, she's somebody
who's dedicated her life
- to gender equality.
- CAITLYN: In the scheme of things,
that is, like,
itty-bitty, teeny-weeny...
ZACKARY: I can go on, but I won't
go on if I'm beinginterrupted.
I'm listening to everything
that you're saying, and...
- CAITLYN: If you look at it...
- ZACKARY: But I unfortunately
don't feel, you know, comfortable
or safe enough to disagree with you.
And I think that that's...
that's unfortunate.
CAITLYN: You know what, I... I
appreciate your candor and your
calm voice. And you've calmed me down.
But it's just...
very upsetting to me.
ZACKARY: You know, I'm aware
that those ideas are out there,
but I've never really been
in the same room with somebody
who's trying to kind
of, like, come for me
or come for, you know,
my girlfriends, and
sort of try to convince us that
we're wrong. I mean, I think
that probably comes from 65 years
of being a Republican man.
JENNY: She has a kind of
bring-it-on sense of politics.
What she doesn't know
is how much it really
hurts us, and it hurts us as her
friends, and it hurts us as women.
- COURTNEY: She needs to listen.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
JENNY: When we we first
got on this bus, I thought,
"Wow. This is huge." Now I'm thinking,
this bus is small.
This bus has never felt so small.
- CAITLYN: Fluffy bunny.
- COURTNEY: Bunny.
- CAITLYN: Bunny.
- ZACKARY: Just put it in your cheek.
ELLA: Oh, my God, I'm dying.
- CHANDI: Fluffy bunny.
- CAITLYN: Fluffy bunny.
(laughter)
KATE: I didn't come out
until after my father died.
I got up the courage to tell my mom,
and she goes, "Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
You get out of here
right now, young man!
And if you go through with this,
if you really go through with this,
don't bother coming back,
because you're not welcome here.
_
WENDI: Welcome to Sunrise Springs.
CAITLYN: Hi. Nice to meet
you. What's your name?
- WENDI: Wendi.
- CAITLYN: Wendi. Caitlyn.
- Nice to meet you.
- WENDI: Welcome to have you here.
How was your trip?
- CAITLYN: Uh, a little long, but not bad.
- WENDI: Yeah?
CAITLYN: It wasn't bad at all.
WENDI: What we were gonna do
is take you directly to your rooms.
- CAITLYN: Let's do it.
- KIP: Let's do it. It's cold.
- WENDI: And then, we're gonna go to dinner.
- CAITLYN: Let's go to... let's.
- CAITLYN: Where did Candis go?
- WENDI: We'll start walking this way.
CAITLYN: Hey, Candis?
KIP: Candis Cayne,
Caitlyn's calling for you.
- CHANDI: Paging CC.
- CANDIS: Sorry.
CHANDI: Paging CC.
- CANDIS: Is Cait upset?
- CHANDI: Yes, she is.
CANDIS: Is she? What did she say?
CHANDI: She said, "Where's Candis?"
CANDIS: Oh.
- CHANDI: She said, "Did I clear the room?"
- (laughter)
CANDIS: Oh, honey, I can't.
I... I'm sorry, I just couldn't
hear her talking... just...
Ooh.
WENDI: Zackary?
COURTNEY: What about Zackary, 409?
ZACKARY: You know, up until today,
granted, it was day three, right,
and it was very balanced, but when
politics came up the second time around,
it went from zero to 100
in, like, a second, and
it felt really hostile.
- WENDI: Jenny.
- JENNY: Jenny.
- WENDI: Okay, so you're in 419.
- JENNY: Okay.
WENDI: There you go, 419.
JENNY: This is what I was afraid of.
Kate Bornstein and I are
having the very conversation
that I least wanted to have.
Caitlyn Jenner is holding
forth about politics.
I'm thinking, "Get me out of here."
(people sigh)
JENNY: May I suggest we all join hands?
I'm not gonna say grace. I'm just gonna
accept the grace of
being with all of you.
Today was a hard day, I thought,
- um, and, uh...
- CAITLYN: It was a long... It's a long ride.
JENNY: I'm grateful for all of you
and for all that lies ahead.
- CHANDI: Amen.
- COURTNEY: Amen.
CANDIS: Amen.
CAITLYN: I love talking about politics
and listening to other peoples'
views and expressing my views,
but it does cause tension.
And maybe a good idea would
be to change the subject.
Five, six days from now,
I accept Glamour
magazine's Woman of the Year,
and I've been kind of
struggling with this thing.
Besides the hair and the makeup
and the clothes and this and that,
to each person in this room
who's had to work very, very hard
to be the woman that they are,
what is it to you to mean to be a woman?
CHANDI: Mm. Being 100%
comfortable in your
skin and being confident.
ELLA: I agree with Chandi.
I think it's just being yourself.
I think there's so
many ways to be a woman.
ZACKARY: Yeah, for me, I
think being a woman is...
being powerful
and being aware of your power.
- CAITLYN: Okay, that's an interesting question...
- ZACKARY: Mm.
- JENNY: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: ... from my standpoint. You know why?
Because a lot of people don't understand
why would you ever transition
from the strong, powerful person
that a male is into a weak female.
Now that's the peoples' perspective,
okay? I don't believe that.
I mean, I watch Kris,
who's a very powerful woman,
and she... she knew
how to play the game.
JENNY: The first thing I thought of
was a quote by Simone De Beauvoir,
who said one is not born
a woman... one becomes one.
CAITLYN: Where do you come
up with all this stuff?
- ELLA: I know.
- CAITLYN: I love it. I mean,
- I... I mean, I love it, but...
- JENNY: That's a great quote,
and I think each of us
have had to become women...
or except for... for Kate... um,
each of us have had to
become women in ways...
- CAITLYN: They've struggled.
- JENNY: I mean that... I mean that respectfully.
- KATE: I... I got it respectfully.
- JENNY: Which means
that we've each had to... to find,
um, womanhood on our own terms.
CAITLYN: I don't know if I'll
ever really figure it out,
what it is. Is it
grace? Is it compassion?
Is it looking at life
in a different way?
I... Honestly, I go down the street
and I look at a billboard and for,
you know, all these years, as
a guy, I was looking up and go,
"Oh, man, there's a hot chick." And so
now I go down the street
and I... I can't identify that
I'm part of that community,
"female," you know?
I've been kind of the
other way for so long,
it's kind of tough for
me to grasp that that's
my sister up there.
But I think the more time I spend in it,
you know, and the more I'm around it,
- you kind of blend into that.
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
ZACKARY: When you're
transitioning, your mind...
is sometimes ahead of your body.
And then there's other times when
your mind has not caught
up to your social position.
It's tough. Like, I really love Caitlyn.
She is six months in. But
she hasn't quite caught
up to herself yet.
KATE: I didn't come out
until after my father died.
I was supposed to be the perfect son.
If I had told him this, he
would've done the Jewish thing
of tearing his clothing, turning
his back, and "I have no child."
- CAITLYN: Really?
- KATE: Oh, yes.
- CAITLYN: Wow.
- KATE: Yeah.
So shortly after my dad died,
I got up the courage to tell my mom,
"Mom, do you know
what a transsexual is?"
"Transvestite?"
And my father was a doctor.
She knew the difference. She
didn't want to know the truth.
"No, Mom, a transvestite
wants to wear women's clothing.
Me, I'll be getting surgery.
I'll be taking hormones."
And she goes, "Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
You get out of here right now, young man.
You get out of here right now.
And if you go through with this,
if you really go through with this,
don't bother coming back,
because you're not welcome here."
I was... I was dizzy.
I never expected that. We'd had such...
we had a mother-son relationship.
That's a great thing.
And...
I threw it in her face.
The last thing she said, "Wait a minute,
what do you think you're
gonna call yourself?"
I said, "Kate.
Kate Bornstein." "'Kate'?!
Your name was Albert.
That was my father's name.
I will never call you Kate.
If I have to call you Kate,
you can call me Mrs. Bornstein."
She went back to her iced tea.
(chuckling)
Three months pass, a big hurricane
hit the Jersey Shore, and...
which is where my mom was living,
so I called to see how she was doing.
We talked for a while on the phone.
It was the first time
we talked in months.
And, uh, she very
pointedly called me Albert.
But we were polite to each other.
Finally, she asked me, "How are
you doing?" I said, "How am I doing?
They're making, uh...
making it terribly hard for me at work.
That's how I'm doing, Mom.
It's really, really hard.
I... I can't talk
anymore." I hung up on her.
Ten minutes, 15, the phone rings.
She goes, "Kate... "
That was it.
And it was beautiful.
I said, "I love you, Mom."
She said, "I love you, too, Kate."
She told me something I'll never forget.
She said, "Look, I know life is hard,
but that's what happens, baby.
You build a world... it falls apart.
But remember this, when
your world falls apart,
you always have the kind
heart you were born with.
And I will always love you, Kate.
You're my daughter."
(others exhaling)
JENNY: My mother used to say
it's impossible to hate
anyone whose story you know.
Kate Bornstein and I have...
fought really hard to get where we are.
I don't want difference of opinion
to take away from the
progress that we've made and...
and the progress that the
whole community has made.
Kate and I need to come together.
KIP: Cait, she got a special package.
(laughter)
- ELLA: It looks like a little vacuum cleaner.
- (whirring)
COURTNEY: I never can use it now.
I can never use it.
- CAITLYN: Off to the horses!
- CANDIS: Yay.
CAITLYN: You've never ridden a horse?
- CHANDI: Never ridden a horse.
- COURTNEY: You're devirginizing Chandi once again.
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
- COURTNEY: Popping another cherry of hers.
(laughter)
CAITLYN: There has been a
lot of tension on this bus.
Maybe the right thing to do
is take all the girls horseback riding.
Just get out of the bus,
get on a horse,
go up into the mountains,
look at the beautiful views,
and maybe even blow off a little steam.
ELLA: Have you ever played Fluffy Bunny?
- CHANDI: No. I don't even...
- ELLA: But usually you do it with marshmallows.
Like, you put a marshmallow in
and you say, "Fluffy bunny."
- CANDIS: Oh.
- ELLA: What if I tried...
CHANDI: Fluffy Bunny
with... with powdered donuts.
ELLA: Powdered donuts,
yeah. I'm doing it.
At some point, the
politics can only go so far.
So we just needed a little
lightening up and some laughing,
so I did not hesitate to bring
out that bag of powdered donuts.
Oh.
Fluffy bunny.
(laughter)
CANDIS: Does someone know
the Heimlich maneuver?
(laughter)
- COURTNEY: Suck 'em back.
- (laughter)
- CHANDI: Ooh...
- ELLA: Fluffy bunny.
- (laughter)
- CANDIS: This'll be five.
- CHANDI: Fluffy bunny!
- (laughter)
- ZACKARY: She's out.
- KATE: Yay!
- ZACKARY: Yay!
- CHANDI: Yay!
- (laughter)
- COURTNEY: All right, Cait, it's your turn.
Caitlyn, you have to do six.
- CAITLYN: What?!
- (laughter)
COURTNEY: Well, Ella did five.
- I'm gonna put these on for protection.
- CAITLYN: Lovely...
- COURTNEY: Fluffy.
- CAITLYN: Lovey?
- CAITLYN: Fluffy...
- COURTNEY: Bunny.
- CAITLYN: ... bunny.
COURTNEY: Yes.
ELLA: Just put it in your cheek.
COURTNEY: There's one. Fluffy bunny.
- CAITLYN: Fluffy bunny.
- (laughter)
- COURTNEY: Here's two.
- KIP: Watch out, this is the backsplash area.
CAITLYN: Fluffy bunny.
- (laughter)
- ELLA: Oh, my God, I'm dying.
- CHANDI: Fluffy bunny!
- CAITLYN: Fluffy bunny.
- (laughter)
- (cheering)
- Fluffy bunny.
- (laughter)
ZACKARY: These... these are
some sorority antics, for sure.
- (horse neighs)
- WOMAN: This is Bishop's Lodge...
we want to welcome you this morning.
CAITLYN: Okay, Chandi,
your first lesson.
- This is what you got to watch out for.
- CHANDI: Ooh.
CAITLYN: Ooh, yeah. Ooh!
CHANDI: Wow, that's a big dump.
(chuckling) CAITLYN: Let's do it.
- Today, the next adventure.
- CHANDI: Ooh.
- MAN: Pistol Pete. Anybody can ride him.
- CHANDI: Pistol Pete.
JENNY: Toes up, heels down.
CAITLYN: Some never ridden before.
Some have done a lot of riding.
I've done a lot of riding in my day.
- JENNY: You're looking good, Chandi.
- CHANDI: Oh.
MAN: All right. Everybody follow me.
CAITLYN: Get that head
pointed in the right direction
- and give him a little kick.
- ZACKARY: Yes. That way.
- (horse neighs)
- CHANDI: Um... Oh.
- Uh, uh...
- (horse neighs, sputtering)
Uh... Uh...
let's come get him.
- Okay. Tell them to come get him.
- (horse sputters)
Okay.
Oh, Pistol Pete.
Whoa. I don't know what I'm doing.
- I'm... I'm trying to be calm.
- (horse sputtering)
Okay.
(horse neighs)
Yes.
Okay.
Good job, Pistol Pete. (Chuckles)
MAN: You sure you never ride before?
- CHANDI: I'm positive.
- MAN: Oh, you're doing a very good job.
- CHANDI: Oh, well, great.
- MAN: It's like natural.
- CAITLYN: Hey, Zackary.
- ZACKARY: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: First time riding with boobs.
- ZACKARY: Yeah. Really.
CAITLYN: That's why you
need a good sports bra.
- (Zackary laughs)
- (horse neighs)
JENNY: I don't want
to be a nay-sayer...
- (chuckling)
- ... but, um,
there's gonna be trouble
if we don't come together.
I'm loving doing this.
Knowing Caitlyn Jenner means
going on wonderful adventures,
but it's... it's about
more than having fun.
There really are things that
should be called into question,
because Caitlyn has been...
I hate to say it, but
she's been kind of a bully.
- CAITLYN: How pretty is this, huh?
- ZACKARY: This is beautiful.
(insects trilling)
KIP: Look what we
got! Cait, she got a...
- COURTNEY: What is this?
- KIP: She got a special package.
COURTNEY: What do you think it is?
A tennis bracelet? Diamonds?
Better.
- CAITLYN: Better?
- COURTNEY: Better than diamonds.
It's my favorite thing in the world.
CAITLYN: Oh, God. I'm learning so much.
CANDIS: The color's so pretty.
- CHANDI: The color is gorgeous.
- CAITLYN: A vroom-vroom.
COURTNEY: A... a what?
What did you just call it?
You're just gonna grab it?
- CHANDI: Vroom!
- CAITLYN: Vroom.
COURTNEY: You're just grabbing it.
- ELLA: Wait, this is amazing.
- CAITLYN: Mm-hmm.
CANDIS: Show me.
COURTNEY: Why is everyone
touching it like that?!
- ELLA: Does it vibrate?
- COURTNEY: I'm gonna have to wash it!
- CANDIS: Hello?
- (laughter)
H... hello?
COURTNEY: I never can use
it now. I can never use it.
(laughter)
- CANDIS: It's like lipstick.
- CHANDI: Oh!
- (whirring)
- (laughter)
(indistinct chatter)
CHANDI: We are gonna toast to
- the Glamour Woman of the Year.
- ELLA: Cheers.
COURTNEY: Caitlyn Jenner.
- CAITLYN: This award is for all of us.
- (cheering)
KATE: I have a happiness
thing I'd like to share.
- CAITLYN: Good.
- KATE: I had
many second thoughts
about coming on this trip.
I... I didn't know whether
I could do it health-wise.
But the other, uh, stumbling block
was Boylan.
JENNY: And... and it was mutual. Right?
KATE: We are each other's evil twin.
All right? We're both
committed to trans...
supremacy! (Laughs)
(laughter)
Our tactics and our ideologies
are loggerheads.
- We had a long talk.
- JENNY: Oh, we did.
KATE: We did. What we ended up with is,
"Some of your stuff is hard to hear
and I know some of what
I say is hard to hear
and I'm trying to throttle
it back in your presence.
But I know you listen to me and
I promise I'll listen to you."
JENNY: And we came to a good place.
Is there any way that our friendship,
the fact that we disagree on so much
but that we love each other so much,
can we use the thing that we have
to open her up a little?
KATE: If she allows us in.
So this brings me to my mea culpa...
- CAITLYN: Okay.
- KATE: ... and my olive branch to you.
(sighs)
The other day on the bus,
I was a smartass.
I said to myself, "Oh, I
know Caitlyn's a Republican.
Let's see if we can
get a rise out of her."
- And I said, "Hey, Caitlyn... "
- CAITLYN: Did it work?
KATE: "Caitlyn... Donald
Trump or Hillary Clinton?"
- CAITLYN: Yeah, I know, yeah.
- KATE: And we were off to the races.
I walked out of the room
while you were talking,
and I want you to know it wasn't
because of what you were saying.
- I want to know more about that.
- CAITLYN: Right.
KATE: The kind of anger
- that was coming... anger's a healthy...
- CAITLYN: It's passion.
KATE: And I hear it as anger
and I go, "Uh-oh, scared
little boy, Daddy's angry."
And I leave.
JENNY: Caitlyn, I want
to make sure that you hear
that it made not just Kate
but many of us uncomfortable.
CAITLYN: Yeah, I... I look
at all the issues, I think,
in a much different way than most
people in this room look at the issues.
JENNY: It's not about the issues...
we're asking you to hear the
fact that we're telling you
we were scared.
CAITLYN: Yeah, I... I look
at all the issues, I think,
in a much different way than most
people in this room look at the issues.
JENNY: It's not about the issues.
We're asking you to hear the
fact that we're telling you
we were scared.
CANDIS: For me, it
was the idea that I...
I listen to you and
what you... what you say,
but sometimes you don't listen to me
- when I'm talking.
- CAITLYN: I... I agree with that, yes.
- CANDIS: So, that... that's what it is...
- CAITLYN: Or I disagree...
- and I get a little bit excited for the extreme.
- CANDIS: You do, yeah.
CHANDI: When you're a sister
and you're coming from a good place,
these things should be received.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- CHANDI: They don't have to be liked,
but they should be received,
and that's the important thing.
JENNY: When you talk to us,
we hope that you will
speak with gentleness
and with love. And I... I...
CAITLYN: Um, I... I agree with that...
sometimes I get very passionate
about it and I kind of
feel Bruce comes in and I go... (grunts)
- JENNY: And that's the thing to pay atten...
- CAITLYN: Would you listen to me,
- what I have to say?
- JENNY: But that's the thing
- to... to pay attention to, because...
- CAITLYN: Oh, I totally agree with that.
- JENNY: It's... It was scary.
- CAITLYN: And I totally agree
with you from that standpoint...
I was a little rough, yeah.
CHANDI: I didn't think you was
rough... you know, I sat there with you.
I'm a rider, mm-hmm.
CAITLYN: I admit I get very...
uh, upset... uh, not upset, I get,
I become very aggressive
when it comes to politics.
And listening is always
something I have to work on,
okay? That's the feminine side of me
that I'm working on, yeah.
ZACKARY: You know, I really,
actually think, with all due respect,
our community has been
prone to infighting
- and division and conflict.
- CAITLYN: Oh, yeah.
ZACKARY: And a lot of anger.
And I think that, as a
community, the fact that
we can all feel safe to kind
of explore our differences
in the most respectful way possible
is modeling behavior
for the trans community
- and for the world community.
- KATE: Well said.
CAITLYN: Yeah, well, we need
that conversation in this country,
big time.
ZACKARY: Minds are made to change.
We are all evolving all the time.
For me, having a friend like
Caitlyn, I've evolved, you know?
So I can't help but think that
with her having, you
know, five or six friends
who have really different
ideas about things is...
We can help her evolve too.
- CAITLYN: By the way, Candis.
- CANDIS: Yeah?
CAITLYN: On the Hillary Clinton issue...
I know you walked out
and I felt really bad,
and I just want to apologize.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: I did not mean to upset you.
- I might even take a picture with Hillary.
- (group gasps)
I haven't... You and me and Hillary,
- um, but I didn't mean to upset you and I apologize.
- CANDIS: That actually means a lot.
I d... I didn't mean to
raise my voice, either.
- CAITLYN: You know I love you.
- CANDIS: I love you too.
CAITLYN: How do we get
on the bus for 30 days
and, uh, not go... not
go after each other?
Um, I need to be calmer.
I think I could get more accomplished.
Let little Caitlyn carry the
conversation in a calm way.
Well, I have to try that.
Yeah.
- JENNY: Mr. Mayor, it's a pleasure.
- JAVIER: Welcome, and I'm glad you're here,
because we are actually
gonna do something.
It's a very small effort
to send a powerful message.
KATE: My honor, Mr. Mayor.
And now we're going
to meet the mayor. Yay!
- Caitlyn Jenner, hi, how are you?
- JAVIER: How are you, Caitlyn?
- Welcome to Santa Fe.
- CAITLYN: Very nice to meet you.
- JAVIER: I'm Mayor Gonzalez.
- JENNY: Mr. Mayor, it's a pleasure.
JAVIER: Over the last
year we passed a important,
uh, ordinance... a
gender-neutral bathroom ordinance.
A very small thing to do to change out,
uh, the signs of a bathroom,
but it sent out a very powerful message.
It wasn't easy.
There was a lot of
fear-mongering that went on.
- CAITLYN: That's exactly, yeah.
- JAVIER: People trying to
distort what we were trying to do,
but I knew, because of Chloe and so
many other people in our community,
that we could not give up.
KATE: The Santa Fe bathroom ordinance
was a big step in the right direction.
A single seater was labeled female.
Another single seater was labeled male.
What is the point in that?
So they... they so wisely put up,
okay, this is gender neutral.
Whoever gets in here
can use the bathroom.
That makes so much sense.
CAITLYN: Kate has been an
activist in this community for
- 30 years.
- KATE: 30 years.
And you've given me a place to pee.
- Thank you so much.
- (applause)
JAVIER: Thank you.
And I'm glad you're here, because
we are actually gonna do something...
CAITLYN: Hey!
- we're actually gonna change out the signage...
- KATE: Come on.
- JAVIER: ... of the bathrooms.
- CAITLYN: And I think you should do it.
- KATE: I didn't know that. Oh!
- JAVIER: Would you do it,
would you help me do it?
CAITLYN: I had a chance to
talk to Kate about her issues
over the last 30, 35 years,
with, just the simple thing
as the good old bathroom.
And she told me some
horrifying stories about
how she was treated.
So I thought it would
really be appropriate...
because I think it would
mean a lot to her...
if she changed the sign on the bathroom.
JAVIER: And so, as a I said, it's a...
it's a very small, uh,
effort to send a powerful message
to you and everyone
else living in Santa Fe.
So if you would help me put this up,
- I would be honored.
- KATE: My honor, Mr. Mayor.
- CAITLYN: Yay!
- (applause)
KATE: More than safe... because "safe"
is always relative... more
than safe, I feel included.
I feel acknowledged, I feel respected.
Putting the sign on the door
that said "gender neutral"
was surreal. But the fact is there
are gonna be more signs like it,
and Caitlyn was generous enough to say,
"Kate, you do that."
That's the generous spirit I want
to touch in Caitlyn, right there.
She was so sweet to give that to me.
CAITLYN: Got it.
CAITLYN: Kylie was
supposed to be my date,
I get a phone call from her saying
she's had a wardrobe malfunction.
KYLIE: My vagina was out. Not my boob,
not my butt crack, my vagina.
ZACKARY: Candis Cayne
has a date tonight.
CANDIS: I'm waiting for
somebody, nobody's showing up.
CHANDI: It's official.
(cheering, applause)
CAITLYN: It's almost, like,
kind of throwing old Bruce...
out the door.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -