- CAITLYN: Disick is in the house.
- SCOTT: Hello!
CAITLYN: I don't think Scott
and I have ever really "bonded."
SCOTT: Come on, girls.
JENNY: The purse, can I just
say, it's a slippery slope.
- Be careful.
- SCOTT: I know.
CAITLYN: Come on, let's ride!
(revs engine)
CHANDI: Back in the day,
I was running around with the wrong crowd,
and I ended up going to prison.
CANDIS: You're cute. I
could totally kiss you.
It's really nice to be able to, like,
have something with somebody that I like.
What are you thinking?
Being on this trip, it's so so weird,
- I can't remember what day it is.
- CHANDI: Is it Monday?
- JENNY: Today is "Mundy" night.
- CHANDI: Exactly.
CANDIS: Monday? "Mundy"?
- JENNY: "Mundy" night.
- CANDIS: "Mundy."
- JENNY: "Mundy."
- CHANDI: "Mundy"?
JENNY: Do I say other things
with... with an accent?
- "Mundy." "Mundy" night.
- CHANDI: "Mundy." "Mundy."
JENNY: Mon... Mon-day. What do you say?
- CANDIS: Monday.
- JENNY: "Mundy."
- CHANDI: "Mundy." (laughing)
- JENNY: What?
- Wait, you say it.
- CHANDI: Monday.
- JENNY: "Mundy."
- CHANDI: "Mundy." (laughs)
- She's like, "What?"
- ELLA: "Toosdy."
- JENNY: Mon... Monday?
- CHANDI: Monday.
- JENNY: Mon... Monday.
- CHANDI: "Mundy."
- JENNY: Is that how you say it, "Mon-day"?
- CHANDI: "Mundy"?
(laughs)
We got our lives on "Mundy."
(laughter) JENNY: You're killing me.
(laughter) CHANDI: J.B.!
- (Candis laughing)
- Whew!
- ELLA: It's "Mundy."
- CHANDI: Well, actually, it's Tuesday.
It's Tuesday now.
(laughter)
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
(phone ringing)
- CAITLYN: There you are!
- KOURTNEY: How's it going?
CAITLYN: It's going, actually, very well.
I'm on Highway 70 to St. Louis, Missouri.
KOURTNEY: Oh, nice!
- CAITLYN: And guess who called me.
- KOURTNEY: Yeah. Who?
CAITLYN: Scott.
- KOURTNEY: Oh, really?
- CAITLYN: He kind of reached out.
Kind of wanted to talk,
hang out, so he's on his...
"supposably" on his way to St. Louis. So,
he's gonna meet us there tomorrow.
KOURTNEY: Oh, no way!
CAITLYN: So, yeah. So, I just
kind of wanted to check with you
- KOURTNEY: Yeah, that's fine with me.
- CAITLYN: Oh, okay.
I hear he's sober.
Is that what you hear?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, he's been sober.
He's been seeing the kids every day.
CAITLYN: Yeah, well,
good. I... I'm glad he's,
you know, doing well.
I have not seen Scott since
he got back from rehab.
You know, he's been through a lot, so
I would love for him
to be around the girls,
who have been through
so much in their life
and have come out so well.
So I think he's gonna spend a
day with... with me and the girls.
- KOURTNEY: Okay, fun!
- CAITLYN: Okay. Good, good.
All right, then it should begood.
Love you! Bye!
KOURTNEY: Love you! Bye!
KATE: Who is Scott?
CAITLYN: Scott is my stepdaughter
Kourtney's baby daddy.
KATE: Oh...
CAITLYN: They never got married,
but they just had three kids together.
Wonderful little kids.
Scott is not a bad guy, but he's got...
he's had a huge drinking problem.
And it's really had a
major impact on his life.
So he's trying to get
his life back together.
You know, he's been through a lot.
So, uh, anyway, he's
gonna meet us in St. Louis.
- Chandi, to get back on a serious note...
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
CAITLYN: As you know better
than anybody, we had a bad year.
21 hate crimes towards trans women.
So many of these women,
- especially in the homicide side of it...
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
- CAITLYN: ... uh, are trans women of color.
CAITLYN: Why?
CHANDI: Well, a lot of them don't
get the love that they need at home.
It's a lot easier for... for parents
to accept their children being gay.
Being trans is taking things
to a whole nother level.
That's... a little bit
harder for them to accept.
They choose to,
in most cases, put their children
out. That's why they have to turn
to, um, survival sex
and survival situations
in order for them to be able to
navigate themselves through life.
CAITLYN: Do they understand
the dangers of doing it,
- what they're doing?
- CHANDI: They don't care about the danger.
CANDIS: They know the dangers,
- but they don't care.
- CAITLYN: They don't care?
- CANDIS: They don't care.
- CHANDI: ... on the street.
- CANDIS: They need to survive day to day.
- CHANDI: They need a...
a roof over their head at night.
They need to know where their
next meal is coming from.
It's all about making money
to survive on the streets.
CAITLYN: Why is it so difficult
for trans women of color
- to get a job?
- CHANDI: A lot of times,
- race plays a big part of it.
- CANDIS: It really does.
- CHANDI: It does.
- CAITLYN: That's shocking to me.
- CHANDI: That's how it's been.
- CAITLYN: I... I... No. O... obviously.
I... I've never seen it, so... but
I... obviously, you lived through this.
- But I... I...
- CHANDI: I do feel like Cait needs to embrace
the issues that African-American
trans women go through
a little more, but it's still a
journey that she'll never relate to
in any way.
CANDIS: Oh, the Arch! The St. Louis Arch.
- CAITLYN: The Arch of St. Louis!
- ELLA: Oh, my golly!
- CAITLYN: There it is, right over there. See it?
- KIP: Oh, wow, look at it!
ELLA: Oh, yeah!
♪ ♪
KATE: Oh, golly, we're here.
ELLA: We made it!
KATE: Good evening to you.
(birds chirping)
(treadmill whirring)
ANDREW: I told you I was
gonna push you, didn't I?
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- ANDREW: Yeah.
See, now you started
out liking me, loving me,
and now you just kind of like, uh, uh...
now it's got a love/hate relationship.
CANDIS: So I've been
feeling a little blah lately
because I haven't been working out.
So I found a trainer,
and he's super cute so I'm
excited about our workout.
ANDREW: Good job. Take a break,
minute break. Here you go.
So what do you have planned
for the rest of the day?
CANDIS: Maybe walk down here
and see the sights or something?
ANDREW: Perfect.
- CANDIS: If you're bored, you could join me.
- ANDREW: Okay, yeah.
- Take a little walk.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
I'm not somebody who
usually asks somebody out,
so I kind of was like, "Let's just
kind of take a chance and...
- see what happens."
- ANDREW: I'll see you at the lobby.
- All right.
- All right. Bye.
I'll have a cappuccino.
CANDIS: You're gonna make me eat alone?
- ANDREW: Okay. I'll eat.
- CANDIS: Thank you.
(Andrew chuckles)
- ANDREW: Um...
- CANDIS: See? I get my way.
ANDREW: You do, you do, you do.
CANDIS: It's just so cute,
this little alley there,
- with, like, the restaurants and...
- ANDREW: So, question.
'Cause I'm curious.
- And, of course, you can stop me if you want.
- Yeah.
- Um, you've dated other guys, right, in the past?
- CANDIS: Yeah.
ANDREW: Like, 'cause you've
totally been open with them.
- Like, "This is who I am and..."
- CANDIS: This is who I am.
- ANDREW: Right.
- CANDIS: For me, personally,
I'm always open about my
transition when I'm dating somebody.
ANDREW: How... how have they taken that?
CANDIS: Well, the guys that I've dated,
obviously, are fine with it, you know?
I guess it depends on the guy
and how comfortable they are
with their own masculinity. And
this is the longest I've
been without a relationship,
and it's been nice to finally
date myself for a while.
You know what I mean?
- And I think I've discovered what I like and...
- ANDREW: What do you like?
- CANDIS: Tall, dark, and handsome.
- ANDREW: Tall, Dar... Oh, really?
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- ANDREW: Interesting.
- I think it might be just around the corner.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
Andrew is kind of surprising me,
because we're actually really connecting
and I'm attracted to him and he
seems like he's flirting back.
So that's kind of cool.
ANDREW: There anything you
would want to know about me?
CANDIS: How did you get that
perfect skin and that gorgeous body?
ANDREW: Well, I was born this
way, and so thank my parents.
(both laugh)
- (birds chirping)
- (doorbell rings)
- (door opens)
- CAITLYN: Hey, babe.
- CHANDI: Look at you!
- CAITLYN: Look at you. Look at you!
- My God, girl.
- CHANDI: Well, you know?
CAITLYN: This time in the morning, and
you're just all dressed up, ready to go.
- Let's take this day on.
- CHANDI: I think I felt a little...
unresolved, like there was
something that I needed to say
to Cait so that she can
identify better with where
African-American trans women come from.
CAITLYN: I hear Mama's
coming to St. Louis.
- CHANDI: She adores you.
- CAITLYN: Mmm, I know.
(both laugh)
Anyway, you said you wanted to talk.
CHANDI: Yeah, I wanted to talk to
you because I wanted to tell you
a little bit about my
past. Back in the day,
before I got into doing all of
this work that I've been doing,
I was running around with the wrong crowd.
Because I was going through
trying to figure out who I am
and I didn't necessarily want to
deal with explaining it to my family,
so I wanted to try to see if I
could figure it out on my own.
I got into some heavy stuff, you know,
doing some white-collar crimes and
writing checks and doing credit
cards and stuff like that,
and I ended up going to prison.
- CAITLYN: Disick is in the house.
- SCOTT: Hello!
- Look at this!
- CAITLYN: This is unbelievable.
I don't think Scott and I
have ever really "bonded."
(motorcycles rumbling)
Come on, let's ride!
CHANDI: I ended up going to prison.
I was scared to death.
And, um, at that time, like, maybe
ten of us who were openly homosexual...
as that's... 'cause that's
what they called us... um,
up against maybe 1,500 men.
CAITLYN: For me, I... I can't see
little Chandi, you know, in jail.
I can't even visualize that,
'cause she's such a good person.
What were you using
that money for, just...
CHANDI: Survival. Um, food,
hormones, a place to stay.
'Cause none of us had jobs.
We were all living from day to day.
You know, it wasn't a
easy road getting here.
I wish someone would've
told me back then that
if I became a felon that I
wouldn't be able to work at a bank
or how it would be a problem
for me to get a passport.
That was me back in that
day before I became who I am.
CAITLYN: Your parents
were not there for you.
CHANDI: They weren't there only
because I didn't want to tell them.
- CAITLYN: About being trans?
- CHANDI: About being trans.
I just didn't know how
they would accept that.
Me and my mom struggled through
my transition because we...
just didn't know how
we would come together
on the fact that I was changing
from who she bore as a child.
CAITLYN: Did you have anybody
to confide in, at that point?
CHANDI: Well, my friends that I was
running around with at that time,
um, we all, you know, talked about
it, because there was a couple of us
who were going through the same thing.
We were just living it from day
to day, performing in the clubs,
trying to make tips, and, um,
trying to support ourselves in those ways.
And so that was fast money.
For us. Back then.
- But fast money doesn't last long.
- CAITLYN: No, it doesn't.
It's so interesting to me to see
what she's been through in her life
and so many trans women go through
and that is survival crimes.
She was trying to survive
and didn't know any other way to do it.
And to hear that from somebody
that you love and adore,
I think, for me, it helps
understand the issues better.
(horn blowing)
Scott Disick.
I don't think Scott and I
have ever really "bonded,"
in the sense that... I think
we're just different people.
(doorbell rings)
- Disick is in the house.
- SCOTT: Hello!
- CAITLYN: How the hell are you doing?
- SCOTT: How you doin'?
CAITLYN: Can't believe the family
member here. This is unbelievable.
- Yeah!
- SCOTT: Good livin'.
- CAITLYN: Have a seat.
- SCOTT: Nice boots!
- CAITLYN: Well, thank you, thank you.
- SCOTT: What's going on?
CAITLYN: Well, just
hanging out with the girls.
SCOTT: How's it being in a bus?
CAITLYN: A lot of very
interesting conversations.
- SCOTT: I'm sure.
- CAITLYN: Transitioning, dealing with gender...
all of that. And, um,
I... I think, for you,
being around all these girls with
their stories and their stuff,
- I think can only be very positive for you.
- SCOTT: Yeah, well, that's what I was thinking.
CAITLYN: Yeah. These girls have
overcome so many obstacles in their life
that hopefully it'll be inspiring for him
to be around this really
great group of people.
CANDIS: Hi.
- SCOTT: Hi. Scott.
- CAITLYN: Oh, you haven't met!
SCOTT: Hi. How are you?
- CANDIS: Nice to meet you.
- SCOTT: Nice to meet you.
- How you doin'?
- CANDIS: I'm good.
- ELLA: Hello, ladies!
- CHANDI: How's it going?
Hey, Lord Disick, I do hugs. I do hugs.
- SCOTT: There you go.
- CHANDI: How you doin'?
- SCOTT: Not bad.
- CHANDI: Great.
JENNY: Scott, Jenny. How are you?
- CAITLYN: Jenny Boylan.
- JENNY: Pleasure.
I feel like I know you, but...
- SCOTT: Well, you're gonna get to.
- (laughter)
- CAITLYN: Let's go.
- SCOTT: Are we riding there?
CAITLYN: Yeah, we got to bus out there.
SCOTT: Come on, girls.
- JENNY: Disick, it's a slippery slope.
- CAITLYN: I used to give him a hard time
- about his purse...
- SCOTT: Yeah.
JENNY: The purse, can I just
say, it's a slippery slope.
- Be careful.
- SCOTT: I know.
- A few more days here, God knows.
- (Kate chuckles)
(birds chirping)
- ELLA: Okay, let's go.
- CAITLYN: Let's check it out.
CHANDI: Now, Scott, don't get quiet on us,
- 'cause we know you're not shy.
- SCOTT: Okay.
(Van shouts)
- CAITLYN: God!
- VAN: Caitlyn!
CAITLYN: We came to you! We came to you!
Aren't you so happy? We're here.
VAN: Oh, my God, I so
wasn't ready for that.
- CAITLYN: You weren't ready for that.
- VAN: Oh, my God.
Everyone, this is my husband Rick.
- CAITLYN: Hello, Rick.
- RICK: Hi. Nice to meet you.
- VAN: Welcome to St. Louis.
- CAITLYN: It's been
quite a long journey to
get here, but we're here.
So excited to see Van Barnes.
She's a friend of all of us.
Uh, uh, very close to Zackary.
She works on Transparent with her.
And she's happily
married to a cisgender...
which means not
transgender... male, big daddy.
- SCOTT: This pool table is, like, for a child.
- COURTNEY: Just focus.
SCOTT: There you go.
CANDIS: Oh, my God, I had the best
time with the trainer that's, like...
VAN: You got a trainer in St. Louis?
- CANDIS: Yeah, well, he's...
- VAN: You're such a liar.
- Okay, start the story over.
- CANDIS: No, so we have...
CHANDI: Uh, oh! You want to see him?
VAN: I thought there were...
Is he one of the bodyguards?
- CHANDI: That's her new husband.
- VAN: Oh, right, honey.
- CHANDI: Uh-huh.
- VAN: And does Cait know you're cheating on her?
- CANDIS: Shh...
- CHANDI: No.
- WOMAN: Say cheese!
- CANDIS: Scott.
- SCOTT: Yes.
- CANDIS: Come join us!
SCOTT: All right, what did I miss?
VAN: We need you to, um, kind of mediate
this whole piece on the side
issue that Candis has right now.
CANDIS: No, uh, we were just talking about
- wanting you to be in our group.
- SCOTT: Yeah.
CANDIS: You're an honorary trans woman.
SCOTT: I been here ten minutes.
VAN: If you did, we might
even let you join our club.
SCOTT: Stop! Well, now, when you say that,
I'd be open to changing around town.
VAN: You would be in training
though for, like, a little while.
SCOTT: Well, of course.
It's gonna be a long journey.
- CANDIS: (laughs) It is.
- CHANDI: He's trying to wrap his head
around being around all these girls.
SCOTT: I'm used to being
around a lot of women.
I'm just not used to
being asked to become one.
(laughter)
CAITLYN: All right. Come on, let's ride!
(motorcycle rumbling)
This is not my first rodeo.
- VAN: I bet it isn't.
- (Caitlyn laughs)
CANDIS: I'm riding behind your man.
- VAN: Go easy on him.
- (Candis laughs)
(motorcycles rumbling)
CANDIS: I'm gonna go
grab a drink with Andrew.
CAITLYN: Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
- CANDIS: You have ten children.
- (both laugh)
- SCOTT: I haven't talked to you all night.
- COURTNEY: _
CAITLYN: No, I'm not ignoring him.
- He's over there!
- SCOTT: I'm not that far.
CAITLYN: But, for me, with my ears...
SCOTT: Is it really your ears,
or you just don't want to listen?
(motorcycles rumbling)
CANDIS: Oh, my God.
RICK: _
- CANDIS: I did?
- RICK: Yeah.
- You okay?
- CANDIS: Yeah.
I don't know what happened.
- VAN: You got road rash, girl?
- CANDIS: I got road rash.
I did not lean on that motorcycle.
It was not my fault.
- VAN: Look at Miss Cait.
- COURTNEY: Do you want to get back on, or no?
You don't have to, you don't have to.
- VAN: Here, I'll take your spot.
- CANDIS: I think you should go, yeah you're used to it.
COURTNEY: What's happening?
CANDIS: I knew I shouldn't have
gotten onto his (bleep) motorcycle, no!
- ELLA: Candis, are you okay?
- JENNY: Sweetie, what happened?
- CANDIS: I'm okay.
- ELLA: I just heard the news.
- JENNY: Do you need a Band-Aid or something?
- CANDIS: No, I'm okay.
- I need a drink.
- JENNY: Okay. We need a drink for this injured
- motorcycle rider.
- (Candis laughs)
♪ ♪
VAN: Lead the way, girl.
- (whoops)
- CAITLYN: Hey!
SCOTT: What is tomorrow, exactly?
ZACKARY: It's the
Transday Remembrance, so,
you know, trans people are murdered,
- at... at an alarming rate in some way...
- SCOTT: Really?
ZACKARY: So, the Transday
Remembrance sort of
celebrates the lives that have been lost
over the past year. It's
been happening for 16 years.
Even the numbers that we have
are not necessarily accurate
because so much of it is not reported,
or people are misgendered in the news.
It's tough.
- Here they come.
- SCOTT: Oh, yeah. Hell's Angels.
CAITLYN: Hey, there.
VAN: You're an old pro, girl.
- CAITLYN: Oh, thank you. That was fun.
- RICK: It was fun.
- VAN: All right.
- CAITLYN: I know.
RICK: Most of it was.
CAITLYN: What age were
you when you transitioned?
VAN: I transitioned twice, actually.
The first time around,
I just found it so hard
to find gainful employment
that I, uh, regressed,
and went back to, uh, presenting male
- in order to make a, uh...
- CAITLYN: Pay the bills.
VAN: Yeah, basically.
Pay the bills honestly.
But it's hard to have to do that twice.
After the first time, I actually had, uh,
liposuction on my torso,
on my breasts, because
I'd grown them naturally.
CAITLYN: I had the exact same thing.
VAN: Oh, really, when you were in hiding?
CAITLYN: '80s, uh, I was on hormones
for four and a half years.
- SCOTT: Oh, by the way, you know...
- No more secrets. I must be so boring.
CAITLYN: Because I just don't
even have any more secrets.
- I'm a lot happier.
- VAN: No, honey.
- ELLA: None?
- CAITLYN: What else can I tell?
- CAITLYN: So, when it was Kim's birthday,
- and Kendall and Kylie...
- SCOTT: Cait... Caitlyn, you know what?
CAITLYN: ... really nice gifts.
- SCOTT: Caitlyn?
- CAITLYN: I figured they'd feel guilty,
they wouldn't mind spending
it, you know, on me.
- SCOTT: Caitlyn.
- CAITLYN: This year, for my birthday,
I told these girls,
"If I get one more goddamn
golf shirt, you're dead."
- SCOTT: She gets to talk and she gets to talk.
- JENNY: Yeah, right, also...
- SCOTT: That hasn't changed.
- JENNY: I think she can't,
- she can't always hear.
- SCOTT: Yeah, it's true.
- JENNY: Just a little.
- SCOTT: Especially with the hair. Just saying.
JENNY: You said you had some
questions about family stuff.
SCOTT: Well, yeah, I just kind of...
I mean, I feel like
Caitlyn has been so busy
running around and traveling and,
you know, bringing awareness...
- JENNY: Mm-hmm.
- SCOTT: ... that, you know, my kids
don't really know exactly what's gone on,
I don't know if they're old
enough. You know, my daughter
has met her and was totally okay,
didn't really, I don't think,
grasp exactly that... that
was grandpa, now it's grandma.
My son was a little nervous.
JENNY: They get the message you send them.
So, if you talk about it with them
like you're on tenterhooks
and you're all jumpy,
- they'll get that.
- SCOTT: Yeah.
JENNY: I sat down with
my children and said,
"You've probably noticed that
I've been looking more and more
like a girl recently,
and I have this condition
where my insides don't match my outsides."
"Um, I know that might be weird for you,
but you know I'm always gonna love you."
And I think my son said
something like, "Well,
if you're always gonna
love me, it won't be weird."
In my experience, it
seems like a bigger deal,
I think, to grown-ups than it is to kids.
CAITLYN: Oh, is that adorable?
We've spent so much time in that bus
in very close quarters that
it did get a little heated,
that it's time to kind of,
like, just take a break,
uh, get on a riverboat cruise
where we can see the city,
the Arch, everything. It should be fun.
COURTNEY: Ooh, it's chilly.
VAN: If we had to like,
jump out right now and swim,
could you do it?
- ZACKARY: Yeah.
- VAN: Yeah, me too.
(horn blows)
CANDIS: Oh, my God. I think they...
- they did that on purpose.
- ZACKARY: I think I got to change my panties.
CANDIS: Jesus Christ.
CAITLYN: It's too cold
here, let's go inside.
I'm freezing.
JENNY: All right, let's get in.
CHANDI: You know, there's a new term
now, maybe you've heard it: pansexual.
- ELLA: Pansexual.
- SCOTT: What the hell is that?
CHANDI: Okay, pansexual means
that you're open to all genders.
- That you're just...
- SCOTT: Oh, just testing waters.
CHANDI: Just testing
waters, trying whatever.
SCOTT: Now, one other question,
is that a talked-about thing...
who's gone full circle and who hasn't?
CHANDI: Not all transwomen
choose to have the surgery
to have a vagina.
SCOTT: It's unbelievable
that the body can do this.
It's almost like,
you know, when you build a car,
you can change the wheels up.
- CHANDI: Right.
- SCOTT: It's like God made
the body, and able to do it.
JENNY: It's like a car,
that's right. It's like a car.
SCOTT: I'm just saying...
- JENNY: I appreciate...
- SCOTT: It's like a pit stop. (Imitates electric drills)
JENNY: That's exactly
right. That's exactly it.
- SCOTT: Boom.
- JENNY: That's what it was like for me.
We have to find a way
of talking about surgery.
And joking about it
isn't the solution, but
I get that this is Scott's way
of trying to find a way to relate
to something that's so new to him.
SCOTT: Is there any maintenance?
JENNY: Not particularly. There's some.
SCOTT: You don't have
to go in for tune-ups?
- JENNY: So, here... here's the thing...
- SCOTT: I need it to relate to cars.
- COURTNEY: Oil change?
- SCOTT: An oil change.
JENNY: There's an oil
change, definitely, yeah.
The... I guess the
important thing, though, is
we're not about an
operation. We're about soul.
SCOTT: Obviously, the
soul part is the first,
- and the most important...
- JENNY: Yeah.
SCOTT: But the other stuff
comes along with the territory.
- CHANDI: Right.
- SCOTT: I just kind of want to have knowledge.
Just because, don't forget,
people ask me these type of questions,
and I would love to be able
to have the right answers,
especially for the straight person
that's not understanding, to... anything.
JENNY: I don't generally
talk about down below,
because, you know, that's private.
SCOTT: I mean, listen, I like to know the
interior color on a car, like, I mean...
- COURTNEY: Pick out the accessories.
- JENNY: It's pink.
SCOTT: Oh! I... I'm being inappropriate.
CHANDI: Yeah, right.
SCOTT: Anything else?
- (horn blows)
- (Candis whoops)
CAITLYN: Chandi's mom is in town, baby.
- Hello, baby, how're you doing?
- TINA: You look so beautiful!
CAITLYN: Thank you, baby, so do you.
- TINA: Baby, you look beautiful.
- CAITLYN: Look at you, you are just...
- TINA: Come get my hug.
- CANDIS: Hi!
- TINA: Hi, honey.
- KATE: Hello.
TINA: Hi. Give me my other...
- KATE: Absolutely.
- TINA: How are you?
KATE: I'm good, I see now where
Chandi gets her good looks.
TINA: Oh!
- KATE: Right?
- CHANDI: You didn't meet Scott.
- TINA: Hi, Scott.
- SCOTT: I haven't transitioned yet.
- (Chandi laughs)
- TINA: Come give me a hug.
(kisses) Good to see you.
SCOTT: Next month, it's gonna be a new me.
CHANDI: Scott is not transitioning,
he's just playing games.
- TINA: Okay.
- SCOTT: I'm just playing.
CAITLYN: Let's go. Get something to eat.
(indistinct chatter)
SERVER: What you in the mood
for... you want to do beer, liquor?
Coc... specialty cocktails.
CAITLYN: In a mixed
drink that you would say,
"Oh, wow, this is a mixed drink for here."
SERVER: I have a hurricane...
- ANDREW: Hi.
- CANDIS: Have a seat.
- ANDREW: Thank you, thank you.
- SERVER: Um, I also have a sazerac.
- CANDIS: Do you want a drink?
- ANDREW: Sure.
- CHANDI: I got the pictures with Bill Clinton.
- TINA: Yeah, look at you with Clinton... okay.
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
- TINA: Please save that.
CHANDI: I... Of course.
ELLA: That's a gorgeous dress, too.
CAITLYN: Look at that. He's the designer.
JENNY: Scott, where are
you from, originally?
- SCOTT: Uh, New York state.
- JENNY: Near a city?
- I lived in Maine for ten years.
- SCOTT: I lived in Vermont for a while.
JENNY: Yeah? Are you the guy, who,
when talking about your own, like,
- pain and trouble and suffering...
- SCOTT: Yeah.
JENNY: ... you're the, "Oh, no, it's
not a big deal" guy, are you that guy?
SCOTT: No, I'm pretty open with...
that I've gone through things
that have hurt me a ton.
JENNY: Tell me if you don't want to go...
go down this rabbit hole
of, like, getting divorced.
SCOTT: Yeah, no, I was never married.
JENNY: Yeah, but you were...
but you were a couple.
- SCOTT: Yeah.
- JENNY: And now you're not a couple
- and that's... that's got to... that's got to hurt.
- SCOTT: Yeah.
Well, yeah, no, it's very tough.
You know, I made a lot of decisions
that weren't great, you know?
JENNY: So, do you think you can...
I don't want to say "win her back", but
- do you think you can...
- SCOTT: Oh, I don't know.
I have absolutely no control over
an... everybody and anybody else,
other than myself. And
all I can do is just
stay on the right path, and
if things fall into place
and they're meant to be, I
believe that they will be.
JENNY: Right. Scott made a real effort
to come all the way, to... to be with us,
and I'm glad I got to
bond with him a little.
But it's just kind of ironic.
I'm not the person he
came there to bond with.
KIP: Oh, my God! Wow!
JENNY: Have you ever had an oyster?
- CANDIS: Chandi likes oysters.
- SCOTT: Caitlyn,
I haven't talked to you all night.
CAITLYN: I know.
- JENNY: She can sit over here.
- SCOTT: No, no.
COURTNEY: _
CAITLYN: No, I'm not
ignoring him. He's over there.
SCOTT: I'm not that far.
CAITLYN: But, for me, with my
ears, you are that far, yeah.
SCOTT: I... Is it really your ears,
or you just don't want to listen?
CANDIS: You're cute. I
could totally kiss you.
What are you...
thinking?
SCOTT: I'm here for you. I'm
not here for just your people.
- CAITLYN: I know. Have a seat.
- SCOTT: You know what I mean?
CAITLYN: I know, I know.
SCOTT: I've spent more time
with them than I have with you.
SCOTT: I haven't talked to you all night.
CAITLYN: I know.
- JENNY: She can sit over here.
- SCOTT: No, no.
COURTNEY: _
CAITLYN: No, I'm not
ignoring him. He's over there.
SCOTT: I'm not that far.
CAITLYN: But, for me, with my
ears, you are that far, yeah.
SCOTT: Is it really your ears,
or you just don't want to listen?
CAITLYN: Well, maybe two...
Yeah, one of two things, yeah.
- SCOTT: I always wondered.
- CAITLYN: Combination.
SCOTT: Okay. I'll settle with both.
CAITLYN: Boom, you got it.
SCOTT: Good night, ladies and...
- gentlemen.
- CAITLYN: "Ladies" is enough.
KATE: I think he's upset
or embarrassed or something.
He went bam.
CAITLYN: Yeah. Yeah, I have... I've
known Scott for a long time, yeah.
And I would much rather deal
with something like that,
which is a little strange, than
having to deal with him being,
you know, hammered, you know,
all the things that go along with that.
(crickets chirping)
CANDIS: I'm gonna go
grab a drink with Andrew.
CAITLYN: Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
CANDIS: You have ten children.
(both laugh)
- CAITLYN: I'll see you guys later.
- CANDIS: Gonna go have a drink.
Have a good night, you guys!
ELLA: Love you.
- ANDREW: Let's have a drink.
- CANDIS: Let's have a drink.
- ANDREW: Have you ever had a Moscow Mule?
- CANDIS: I did recently.
ANDREW: You want to try some?
CANDIS: Yeah, I'll try it.
- ANDREW: It's good.
- CANDIS: The ginger is a nice flavor.
ANDREW: I know.
So you haven't seen the Arch yet.
This is... this is the
closest you've been so far.
CANDIS: Yeah. This is,
like, the best view.
- Let's go out and look.
- ANDREW: Let's go.
Man, it's windy.
CANDIS: It is kind of windy.
- I'll be fine.
- ANDREW: Are you sure? You want my jacket?
- CANDIS: Okay.
- ANDREW: All right.
There you go. Okay.
CANDIS: Are you cold now?
ANDREW: I'm good.
As long as you're warm.
- CANDIS: Here.
- ANDREW: Oh.
- CANDIS: Yeah.
- ANDREW: I'll get under the jacket?
CANDIS: You have to share it
with me. You're gonna get cold.
There's no denying there is a
little bit of chemistry there,
and so it's really nice
to be able to, like,
actually have something
with somebody that I like.
I have to say, you're a very sweet guy.
ANDREW: Well, thank you. You're amazing.
- CANDIS: Thank you.
- ANDREW: You are amazing. You're sweet.
CANDIS: Are you nervous?
- Am I making you nervous?
- ANDREW: No, you're not making me nervous.
- You're not making me nervous.
- CANDIS: Okay, good.
Um...
well, I'm just kind of, like, one of those
people that kind of goes with the flow.
You know what I mean? Just like...
What... what are you...
thinking?
ANDREW: Are you meaning like more than...
what's going on right here?
CANDIS: Well, I mean,
of course. I'm, like...
You're cute. I could totally kiss you.
- You know, that kind of thing.
- ANDREW: Mm-hmm.
I don't think I really
could go there just yet.
You know?
CANDIS: Okay.
Okay, well, I've... (laughs)
- On that note, I'm gonna go to bed.
- ANDREW: Okay.
You okay?
CANDIS: No, I'm good.
- I'll see you...
- ANDREW: So, tomorrow morning?
CANDIS: I'll... I'll call you.
ANDREW: Candis.
CANDIS: I just felt like
maybe we had a connection,
and then I just assumed it was 'cause
- of the trans thing.
- ANDREW: It's, um... I just...
CAITLYN: What were your big concerns?
TINA: I'm a person
that's, uh, very religious.
I was very hurt.
CAITLYN: All right, we're recording.
You know, tough day coming up.
This is my first day to participate in the
Transgender Day of Remembrance.
Uh, we've lost a lot of very good people
that should be with us here today.
Um, it's a very emotional
time for my community
and for people all around the world.
So, tough day for everybody,
but, uh, we need to do it.
- (doorbell rings)
- CANDIS: Hello?
- ANDREW: Hey.
- CANDIS: Hey.
- Come on in.
- ANDREW: How's it going?
- CANDIS: It's going good.
- ANDREW: Good. Do you have time to talk?
CANDIS: Yeah, sure.
- How are you? What's up? What's going on?
- ANDREW: Good.
Uh, nothing, just getting ready.
Got to head out later on today.
Some things came up, so I have to fly out.
- CANDIS: Okay.
- ANDREW: Yeah. But, um...
So, last night, what happened?
CANDIS: I don't know. I
just was kind of over it,
- to be honest with you.
- ANDREW: But over what?
CANDIS: I don't know. We
were talking and I was like,
"What's going on with you?"
And you were like, "I can't do this."
ANDREW: Right, right.
CANDIS: I just felt
like we had, you know...
- ANDREW: Like, something.
- CANDIS: ... something.
- ANDREW: Like a spark?
- CANDIS: So, I... I don't know.
I mean... I... And then I
just assumed it was 'cause
of the trans thing and...
ANDREW: It's, um... I just...
You could say yes. That could be...
Uh, uh, but, honestly,
that's a big issue, yes.
Um, but at the same time, like,
there's noth... there's no judgment,
there's no anything like that, um,
by all means. It's just something that...
it's just not me.
CANDIS: All right.
Um...
I kind of knew it was the trans thing.
It's like the... the tables
are stacked against you,
you know, your whole life.
It's tough, because you
never have a break, you know?
Sometimes you get glimmers of that
moment that could be,
and then most of the
time it doesn't happen.
It really hits home.
(indistinct chatter)
CAITLYN: Good morning. There you are.
TINA: How's my baby doing today?
CAITLYN: Mama, I'm doing good.
Let's get some breakfast going.
CAITLYN: The other night,
when I was, uh, in Chicago,
- we went to the Baton...
- TINA: Uh-huh.
CAITLYN: ... and Chandi
was bringing the house down.
TINA: Uh-huh, yeah, looking
like Patti LaBelle, huh?
- CAITLYN: Have you been to her shows?
- TINA: Oh, yeah. Mm-hmm.
CAITLYN: Since today is
- Transgender Day of Remembrance...
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
CAITLYN: I kind of heard
that, at the beginning,
it was tough on you.
What were your big concerns?
TINA: At first, I was very hurt.
I questioned myself as a mom.
KATE: We are the first generations
who are actively bringing
about the end of transphobia.
(cheering)
CAITLYN: I have been
isolated my entire life.
I... I never felt like I fit in anywhere.
And I know that's probably the
feeling that you get sometimes.
SCOTT: Yeah, that's for sure.
TINA: At first, I was very hurt.
I questioned myself as a mom.
Took me a while to get
my grips on this here.
'Cause first of all, I'd never...
CAITLYN: I was gonna
say, you had no idea what
even the word "transgender" was, did you?
A... and... which is most cases, yeah.
TINA: When I started looking at the fact
and I'm seeing the
things around my child...
young ladies getting murdered,
young ladies are being abused...
would I want my child like that?
No. No.
CAITLYN: Did you have fear for
her safety at the beginning?
TINA: Yes, I did.
And yeah, I still fear.
- CAITLYN: You still feel that way?
- TINA: Yes. Yes.
CAITLYN: It's hard for me to accept that
Chandi could actually be at risk
just being out in the public.
Unfortunately, this is the reality
of living in a transphobic world
that doesn't accept trans people.
TINA: You know, I am a person that's, uh,
very religious, and I
think what really keeps me
on the positive side is
that just because my child
might not be like me...
but they're still my child.
So that's what God said
in his word. He said,
your, uh, situations may be a
little different, but guess what?
- He made us all.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
TINA: We have to learn
how to love and accept them
for what they are. You can't
be pulling against them,
- you got to pull for 'em.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
TINA: Especially when...
when you have a child that's
- about doing something positive.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
You just have to be so
proud of what she's doing.
TINA: I'm very proud.
- CAITLYN: You know?
- TINA: I'm very proud.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- TINA: I really am.
(elevator beeping) (elevator bell dings)
CAITLYN: Chandi's mom
is such an inspiration,
'cause she never gave up on her child.
And look how Chandi has turned out...
she's doing so much good.
Kind of the same way I feel with Scott.
I always wanna be there for him.
I don't wanna give up on Scott,
and hopefully, he can
turn his life around.
SCOTT: Coming!
- Com...
- CAITLYN: It's locked!
- Scotty.
- SCOTT: If you're a woman now,
I think you need to tone down your knock.
CAITLYN: You think so?
It should be more gentle?
- (Scott pounding on door)
- Not like that?
SCOTT: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: How you doin'?
- SCOTT: What's happening?
CAITLYN: Well, I heard you were
thinking about leaving, number one.
And I don't think you should.
We have this ceremony tonight,
I think it would be good for you.
SCOTT: Yeah, but again, I'm here for you.
I'm not here for just...
your people.
- CAITLYN: I know. Have a seat.
- SCOTT: You know what I mean?
- CAITLYN: I know, I know,
- SCOTT: I've spent more time with them
than I have with you.
SCOTT: I'm here for you.
I'm not here for just...
- your people.
- CAITLYN: Have a s... have a seat.
- SCOTT: You know what I mean?
- CAITLYN: I know, I know,
SCOTT: I've spent more time
with them than I have with you.
CAITLYN: But...
I know. But...
all of these people have
a lot in common with you.
I have been isolated my entire life.
I... I never felt like I fit in anywhere.
When I finally decided to be
true with myself and come out,
I surrounded myself with
some really great people...
all these girls that have
so much in common with me.
My life changed around immediately.
And I feel like you're kind
of in the same place here.
The... the whole, you
know, drinking thing and
all that kind of stuff...
it just... it's not good.
And you certainly don't
find happiness there.
SCOTT: Mm-mm. I used to always think that
when I was drunk
the real me came out.
And I always thought the
real me was a bad person.
And I've realized that, you know,
substances make people something else.
It's not really who they are.
So I've been able to kind of
forgive myself for all the things,
and now I'm just focusing
on actually being me.
I've just been happy for the
first time in a long time.
CAITLYN: You got to
make some major changes,
but it's all for the good. Now,
I mean, I look at my life now,
I've never been in a better
place in life than I am right now.
Better than the Games,
standing on top of a platform.
SCOTT: You know, whatever you want to do,
and I'm there to do with you.
CAITLYN: I want you to know
that I'm there for you, too.
It seems like Scott is
getting his act together.
He seems more self-aware.
To me, that's progress.
I've been through a lot.
He's been through a lot.
And it's not going through these issues,
it's how you come out the other side.
It's all good. Life's
very short, as we all know.
SCOTT: Yeah, that's for sure.
CAITLYN: Yeah. Don't throw it away.
- Yeah.
- SCOTT: Listen, now that we've had this talk,
I mean, I feel more
comfortable. I just felt like...
I felt a little bit of
an outsider, even here,
so it kind of got me down. But I can...
I can push the flight a little
and go with you to this...
- remembrance thing.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, no I think... I think it'd be good, yeah,
- I think it would be good to go.
- SCOTT: All right.
CAITLYN: Give me a hug.
Good.
All right, we'll see you. Get ready.
SCOTT: You may need to tone
down your hugs, too, with the...
- CAITLYN: It's good.
- SCOTT: It's like the door knock.
CAITLYN: I know.
- CANDIS: Hi. Hi. How are you?
- LEON: Hi!
- CANDIS: Candis.
- MISS LEON: Hi. I'm Miss Leon.
Nice to meet you.
Here you go.
CAITLYN: Hello. How are
you doing? Nice to see you.
CHANDI: Having my mom here for Transgender
Day of Remembrance is so amazing.
And it will be great for her to be amongst
all these trans people who are
paying homage to those who
have been lost this year.
SPEAKER: So, now we will hear the names
and the stories of some of those lives.
WOMAN: _
_
CANDIS: We've had a really tough year.
(crying): But when you read the names,
it really hits home.
- CAITLYN: _
- VARIOUS VOICES: _
_
CANDIS: Any one of us
could be in a situation
where we could be just like
our brothers and sisters who are murdered
because you are trans.
_
MISS LEON: We must remember
that out of tragedy comes hope,
resilience and triumph.
I'm here to support, maintain and
nurture this trans memorial garden,
which, again, is the very
first of its kind in the nation.
We are making history
right here, in The Grove,
in St. Louis, in the Midwest.
- (cheering)
- Hey, yes!
History is being made.
KATE: Well, thank you, St.
Louis, for putting this here.
I want to acknowledge that
we are the first generations
who are actively bringing about
the end of transphobia.
KATE: Thank you so much!
(cheering, whooping)
MATT BEILIS: ♪ 'Cause
whatever we are, we are... ♪
CAITLYN: Trans Day of Remembrance was
actually a very beautiful experience.
Having an opportunity to
pay respect to these
people for who they were,
for me, is very important.
And it's nice to kind of be reminded
of what the issues are out there.
SPEAKER: And we claim this space
as living and sacred.
BEILIS: ♪ Whatever
we are , we are... ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
- KRIS: Hi!
- CANDIS: Still to come this season
on I Am Cait...
CAITLYN: Candis!
CANDIS: That's a big stick.
CAITLYN: Nobody's told
me that in a long time.
(laughter, cheering)
- JENNY: That's what I'm talking about!
- ELLA: Kiss.
- (laughter)
- CAITLYN: Hand hug!
SCOTT: How much are trees? $100?
Aye, aye, aye.
CANDIS: We have to talk about something.
"Presidential hopeful Ted Cruz
opposes equality for transgender people
because he thinks trans kids
will molest his daughters."
CAITLYN: Wow.
MARA: There is a partisan slant to this.
Watch your candidates this year.
When they do messed up
stuff, you call them out.
JENNY: Republicans, your people,
they don't like us.
CAITLYN: They're not my people
if they're against this issue.
I think he's just totally misinformed.
CANDIS: That was a huge step.
CAITLYN: You're absolutely right.
I just want to apologize
for the way I acted.
It didn't have to be that way.
A little disobediance, girls?
- What do you say?
- KATE: Seriously, that could mean arrest.
- You're becoming a leftist activist.
- (cheering)
You found out how to
express yourself as a woman
and listen, and for that,
you've earned my respect
and complete support.
CAITLYN: I love you all.