CAITLYN: You're actually
trying something on?
CANDIS: Why not? I've never
tried on wedding dresses.
CAITLYN: Either have I!
CANDIS: For almost all of existence,
- that wasn't even an option for trans women.
- CHANDI: Yeah.
CAITLYN: My ex-lover is coming into town.
JENNY: Do you feel a
little on the defensive,
or self-conscious with her at all?
CAITLYN: I always felt
on the defensive with her.
- JENNY: Did she tell you early on?
- KRIS: No.
CAITLYN: Oh, I did, too!
KRIS: There was no "I am transgender."
CAITLYN: I certainly told
her what was going on.
We are doing it in New Orleans.
- Yes we are.
- (indistinct chatter)
KRIS: _
_
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
(birds chirping)
- CANDIS: Hi, good morning!
- CHANDI: Good morning!
- JENNY: Made it back.
- CHANDI: Yes, we did.
- ELLA: Are you guys ready?
- CANDIS: We are ready!
- ELLA: 'Cause we are off.
- KATE: We're ready. (Laughs)
(all clamoring)
- CAITLYN: This is our last bus trip.
- (all cheering)
CANDIS: I think we have to
have some fun in New Orleans.
CAITLYN: Oh, I totally agree.
My sister will be there, just
about the time we get there.
CANDIS: She'll want to party all night.
CAITLYN: I am so glad that my sister Pam,
yes, is coming to New Orleans!
I love my sister Pam.
She's been great, she's known about me,
Caitlyn, for ever and ever.
And, all those issues are in the
past, and to be honest with you,
it's just to have a good
time with your sister.
She's... she's looking for a good time.
- CHANDI: She's got the right batch of girls.
- (laughs)
♪ ♪
KATE: There's something
about trans men, I love.
- CHANDI: Yeah.
- KATE: They're so handsome.
And in the same way we embody "lady,"
they embody "gentleman."
Most people think that it's genitals
- that make you a man or a woman.
- CANDIS: Right.
KATE: And that's why
one of the very first things when
people think of well, trans women,
what does she have down there?
Trans man, what does he have down there?
That comes up for people.
- CHANDI: It's a natural thing.
- KATE: Yeah.
CHANDI: Although, everybody
shouldn't ask that question.
KATE: I don't know why not.
- You know?
- CHANDI: It's not a problem to discuss
genitals if it's appropriate, you know?
I just don't feel like someone
who I meet on the street
and... and we discuss the
fact of me being trans,
that should be their first question.
- KATE: So, it's a matter of manners, and...
- CHANDI: Right!
- For me, it's better...
- KATE: For good, good manners.
CANDIS: I don't think
there's any time at all.
I think your privates are
your privates, personally.
ELLA: Yeah, you know what,
that's true, at the same time.
- CHANDI: That's, that's true, too.
- CANDIS: And I don't want to discuss my genitals
with anybody and I don't want
anybody asking me about mine.
There's so much more to talk about.
ELLA: But I think also part of that
education is important to let them know that
- that's not the important part at all.
- CHANDI: Right.
- CANDIS: Right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- ELLA: That's not validating my gender at all.
- CHANDI: Right.
- KATE: In the '80s, when I got my surgery,
it was just assumed that
that's what you would do.
There was no... nobody saying, "Well,
you know, you want to
think about it for a while?"
CAITLYN: Gender confirmation surgery
is something I think anybody in
my position, or the girls'
position, of course, you look into.
For me, I have no idea
what the future holds.
But it is really interesting
to listen to all the girls,
because when it comes to this,
every person has a different way
to be authentic to themselves.
ELLA: I think, for different
people, it might be different.
But personally me, I
always say, "Well, really,
if I'm gonna get it, it's for the
reason I want to wear a bathing suit,
and not have to worry
about certain things."
- CAITLYN: Right.
- ELLA: For simple, simple things.
CHANDI: But you can put on
a bathing suit now, mama.
- ELLA: Yeah, I know.
- CHANDI: And rock it, right.
JENNY: You know, for me, it was,
like, that was the thing I wanted.
I didn't want anything else.
What I wanted was... was in
fact a body that was the home
that I... I'd never been to,
that I was always homesick for.
- CHANDI: Right.
- JENNY: You know, for me,
it's... it's... it makes me really happy,
um, and, uh, in all kinds of ways, um,
but it took me a while to figure
out how to work it, actually.
(laughter, clamoring)
(birds chirping)
♪ ♪
(bell rings)
KATE: Give it here, girls.
- Oh, you are so cute!
- ELLA: Gorg.
CAITLYN: Interesting development
in the last few hours.
- CHANDI: Oh.
- KATE: Yeah?
CAITLYN: That, it looks like
we'll have another guest.
- CANDIS: Who?
- CAITLYN: Actually, someone I know intimately.
- CANDIS: Oh.
- CHANDI: Ooh, ooh.
- CAITLYN: Really intimately.
- CANDIS: Kris.
- Really?
- KATE: Really?
CANDIS: Really?
- CHANDI: Really?
- CANDIS: Kris is coming?
CAITLYN: Now, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. The way you said that.
Okay, you went, like, "Huh?"
- CHANDI: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Why?
Why would you, why was
your reaction like that?
CHANDI: Well, I'm just surprised that
Kris would be willing to
come hang out with all of us.
She's still learning about you,
- and that's...
- CAITLYN: And I think...
- I... I get that.
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
CAITLYN: Um, I think it
would be very good for her.
- CHANDI: Mm-hmm.
- KATE: But okay, at this point,
in your relationship,
is she being good to you?
CAITLYN: She's been fine.
But she has not over the
last year really called or,
you know, I've reached out
to her on a few occasions.
We spent some time
together. But Kris is...
Kris is Kris, you know?
CANDIS: But when you came out,
she had, that's a lot
for someone to go through.
- CAITLYN: Oh, I totally agree.
- CANDIS: And the fact that she's coming
to meet all your girls, and
to hang out is pretty cool.
CAITLYN: Yeah, it's good. No,
I... I think it's very cool.
ELLA: I mean, I don't think
she's had a chance to really be
around trans women, like, has
she had that experience, yet?
- CAITLYN: No, no.
- ELLA: No?
CAITLYN: Uh, she hasn't
been around me that much.
ELLA: No, then this'll
be a, this'll be great.
CAITLYN: Kris Jenner is coming to town!
I am excited about her coming to town.
Uh, I think it'll be fun.
Because I think it's really
good that she has an opportunity
to hang around and actually spend
some time with all the girls. 'Cause,
honestly, I think she's
gonna love them. The last...
- CANDIS: Your situation.
- CAITLYN: ... time I actually had a
conversation with her,
she looked at me and goes,
- "Are you dating that girl?"
- CHANDI: Right.
CAITLYN: That was you.
- CANDIS: But now, we get to meet face to face.
- CAITLYN: I know, I know.
Should we go in our
own hotel room together,
like, make sure she sees
us go in the room together?
CANDIS: Right, yeah. Just take...
CAITLYN: Really, really
screw with her, yeah.
(laughter)
- CHANDI: Cait?
- CAITLYN: That would be neat, yeah.
- CHANDI: You are picking up shade so well.
- CAITLYN: I know, I know.
CHANDI: You are picking
up shade so well! (Laughs)
ELLA: Oh! Candis,
- are you thinking what I'm thinking?
- CANDIS: What are you thinking?
ELLA: Bridal Boutique.
- Hi.
- CANDIS: Hi, how are you?
- CAITLYN: Oh, my God, look at it.
- CANDIS: I know, it's amazing.
ELLA: I need to find the
right one for you, Candis.
CAITLYN: You're actually
trying something on?
CANDIS: I'm gonna do it, why not?
- CAITLYN: God...
- CANDIS: I've never tried on wedding dresses.
- CAITLYN: Either have I!
- CANDIS: (laughs)
ELLA: What do you see yourself,
- like, rocking?
- CAITLYN: A wedding dress?
CHANDI: What type of bride
do you think you'd be?
- CAITLYN: I... I have, I haven't gone that far.
- ELLA: Well, we're gonna go there.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- ELLA: We're going there today.
ELLA: I think epic would be
an understatement of
a bunch of trans women
in wedding gowns. Which one
would look great in Hawaii?
(chuckles) 'Cause I think
that's where the wedding is.
Let go of the fact that we're trans
and just kind of realize that
we're all just having fun.
CANDIS: All right, here we go.
CAITLYN: Challenge is
on. Who wore it best?
KATE: I would wear a rhinestone tuxedo.
- CHANDI: Ooh!
- KATE: With a top hat.
CHANDI: I would probably never
go inside a wedding dress store
and ever try on a wedding
dress, so this is like,
- a great moment.
- ELLA: Should I come and help?
- Oh, my gosh!
- CANDIS: I'm ready.
- CHANDI: Oh...
- KATE: Oh...
CHANDI: I love it.
- Yes!
- KATE: Oh!
What a glimpse of an angel!
CANDIS: This is crazy!
For me, trying on this wedding dress,
I kind of am seeing it as a
little bit of an affirmation
of what I could possibly
want have happen to me.
For almost all of existence,
that wasn't even uh, uh,
- an option for trans women.
- ELLA: Honey, come out!
ALL: Oh!
CAITLYN: How do they do the walk?
CANDIS: (chuckles) No.
- Just natural.
- CAITLYN: Want to know something...
Oh! Jesus Christ!
- (Candis laughs)
- Oh, my God!
What do you think?
ELLA: That is flippin' stunning, yeah.
- I think it looks great.
- CAITLYN: I think we need to pose.
CHANDI: Yes.
CAITLYN: Yeah, here we
go. Oh, thank you, Chandi.
- You can be my bridesmaid any day.
- CHANDI: Okay, babe.
CAITLYN: Did I ever think
this day would come? No.
I've been at three weddings,
okay, with the most boring
clothes on in life, okay?
Uh, finally I get to wear something...
- comfortable.
- KATE: Candis... Caitlyn...
I now pronounce you
trans-bride and trans-bride.
CAITLYN: Yay!
ELLA: Kiss her!
(Caitlyn laughs)
ELLA: Oh, here we go.
- CAITLYN: T-shirts.
- CANDIS: Oh, T-shirts?
CHANDI: T-shirts.
WOMAN: _
CAITLYN: How about an alligator head?
Like, we could put this on the hood...
- (Ella laughs)
- ... of a car or something.
- ELLA: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
ELLA: Cait, do we need Mardi Gras masks?
CAITLYN: Actually, that's not a bad idea.
CANDIS: Ooh, I like the teal one.
WOMAN: _
CANDIS: Wow, there's a
whole crowd of people.
(laughs) We're completely circled.
- ELLA: Yeah, I know, this isn't...
- WOMAN: _
_
- CAITLYN: Hello, how are you?
- MAN: _
- CAITLYN: Thank you.
ELLA: That was insane.
Being on the bus with Caitlyn,
I forgot what it's like to
see her from the outside.
And every single time we were
in public, just the reaction
that she got from anyone
who came in her path...
that reaction shocked me, every time.
Because it kind of brought me back to
what she really has
done, you know, for us.
- CHANDI: What's your name?
- KAITLYN: Kaitlyn.
- I know!
- CHANDI: Kaitlyn?
(laughs)
- How are you, Kaitlyn?
- KAITLYN: I'm good,
- I just want to meet...
- CHANDI: Great to meet you.
KAITLYN: I see Candis.
I've been trying to wave.
CHANDI: You've been trying to wave at...
Candis? Kaitlyn wants to say hi.
- CANDIS: Hi, girl.
- KAITLYN: This is my sister.
- CANDIS: Nice to meet you.
- CHANDI: Hi, sweetie. Mwah!
- PAM: Party time!
- CANDIS: Oh, my God!
CAITLYN: Oh, no! Sister Pam is here!
- Oh, God...
- PAM: Look at all these.
CAITLYN: Oh, you got the beads going...
What is this? Is this the Welcome Wagon?
- You don't even say hi?
- PAM: Hi.
CAITLYN: My sister Pam is here and
I'm excited about her spending some
quality time with all the girls,
so, uh, it'll be fun.
- Ready?
- CHANDI: Yes, let's go.
- PAM: Cait, what car do you want?
- CAITLYN: We're going back in the van.
CANDIS: Note to self, leave
Caitlyn at home. (Laughter)
And we can go shopping.
(bells jingling)
PAM: Cafe Du Monde. This is a classic.
- (Candis gasps)
- CANDIS: Look at the size of those!
- I might need a doggy bag.
- PAM: I know.
- CAITLYN: Don't inhale when you take a bite of that.
- PAM: Oh, yeah, I know.
- The powdered sugar.
- CANDIS: You have a, like, a full sugar high.
- CAITLYN: Mm-hmm.
- CANDIS: Literally.
My parents have been married for 54 years.
And I always thought of that as the goal,
but then I realized, later, no...
that can't be the goal. It has
to be meeting the right person
in order to ever have that goal fulfilled.
Are there any negatives
about being married?
PAM: I think, many times, when you have
had a failed marriage, you learn so much
and you're a lot more tolerant
the next time. You learn
from those mistakes.
You give each other
a little wider berth...
- CAITLYN: Yeah.
- PAM: ... to be your own person.
CAITLYN: A very important aspect
of a long-term relationship
is you have to let the
other person live their life.
Now, you can enjoy everything together,
- a lot of things...
- CANDIS: Right.
CAITLYN: ... but like Pam just said,
we both have things we like
to do and we go do them.
CANDIS: I thought it
was really interesting,
hearing Cait talk about the relationships.
But I haven't stayed
friends with any of my exes,
so I don't know how it's
going to be with Kris.
It's just an awkward situation.
- CANDIS: These were really good.
- CAITLYN: You need a sugar daddy.
- (Candis laughs)
- Are you gonna eat this or not?
- PAM: You can be that.
- CANDIS: I'm not.
- CAITLYN: Oh, my God.
- PAM: Sugar momma.
CANDIS: They were really good.
CAITLYN: My ex-lover is coming into town.
JENNY: What has to happen
to improve your relationship?
- CAITLYN: I... I don't know.
- (knock at door)
(cheering)
KRIS: _
_
(bell rings)
JENNY: God, you've trashed the place.
CAITLYN: I'm trying to figure
out what the hell do I wear?
Put it this way, Jenny: my
ex-lover is coming into town.
JENNY: Wait, is this, is this the,
uh, this is your confessional cam?
How... how do you turn this
on? You know how to, turn it on?
- CAITLYN: Want me to show you how to do this?
- JENNY: Yeah, okay,
'cause we're gonna do,
we're gonna do a thing.
CAITLYN: Oh, we're gonna
do a thing, together?
- Oh, my God.
- JENNY: We're gonna do a confessional, a confessional.
CAITLYN: All right. There's a lot of work.
- Sit down, right here.
- JENNY: All right, all right.
CAITLYN: You got to get it...
'cause you got to get the lighting
good, 'cause there's no lighting.
JENNY: Yeah. Yes, I know.
I know how important it is for you.
CAITLYN: As Kim says, it's
all about the lighting.
- Ah, the red dot's on.
- JENNY: Okay.
- CAITLYN: It's working.
- JENNY: All right, so...
CAITLYN: This is the first time
I've ever done it with anybody.
- JENNY: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: Hold on. Hold on.
JENNY: We're here with Caitlyn Jenner.
So, Caitlyn: how are
you feeling about your
ex-wife meeting your
new lover, Candis Cayne?
CAITLYN: Oh, what... ? Candis
is not... she's my friend.
JENNY (reporter voice): So I just
want to know how it feels to have your
ex-wife meet you new lover?
(Caitlyn laughing)
CAITLYN: This is going downhill
right from the beginning.
- JENNY: I'm trying my best.
- CAITLYN: Uh...
I don't know. I'll find out. Um...
no, uh... actually, I'm looking
forward to, uh, Kris coming.
JENNY: And when was the last time
you... you, like, really talked?
- CAITLYN: Oh, we really talked?
- JENNY: Yeah.
CAITLYN: I don't... How did that go?
KRIS: I was struggling and
having a really hard time...
CAITLYN: With what?
KRIS: Your transition.
And this, like, leaving us in the dust.
- CAITLYN: Nobody's leaving you guys in the dust.
- KRIS: You left us...
you left us in the dust.
- CAITLYN: What... who... ?
- KRIS: Basically, I'm just saying
- I went through a hard time.
- CAITLYN: Nobody's leaving anybody...
I'm not going anywhere.
KRIS: You know, it was
like, what happened to...
just... the life we had together?
It's like you don't,
you just threw that away.
CAITLYN: I thought it went pretty good.
But then, after it was
over with, I kind of...
uh, I... I kind of struggled with it a lot.
'Cause, you know, there's
a lot of emotions there.
- JENNY: Well, yeah.
- CAITLYN: There's 23 years of life together.
Mmm... that's tough stuff.
- Yeah.
- JENNY: Do you... do you feel a little on the, on the
defensive or self-conscious
with her at all?
CAITLYN: I always felt
on the defensive with her.
- JENNY: Okay, then, different question.
- CAITLYN: Um...
There's just another
element here that I don't
quite understand what she...
Hopefully, have some time
to talk to her about it.
I... I feel sometimes,
now, she gets more upset
than she was when we were together.
You know? Um... uh...
And I don't understand why.
Because she was... I was very
honest with her and open with her.
- Now, sure...
- JENNY: Upset about trans stuff?
- CAITLYN: About... yeah, about gender issues.
- JENNY: If I was your ex-wife and I loved you,
it would hurt my feelings.
What has to happen
in order to improve your relationship?
CAITLYN: I... I don't know.
JENNY: You know, most couples
who get divorced, they're...
they're kind of done with each other. So
I'm more than a little worried
about what's going to happen.
(Caitlyn sighs)
♪ ♪
KRIS: Okay. (Exhales)
I'm here in New Orleans because
Cait has been a little MIA
and I've heard all about
these shenanigans going on,
so I decided to come out.
I'm looking forward to seeing
what the excitement is all about.
COURTNEY: Are you excited
for Kris to arrive?
CAITLYN: Um, yeah. As a matter of fact,
she just texted me.
She is...
one floor below.
(giggles) I think I should
probably go down and just say hi.
- COURTNEY: Of course you should.
- CAITLYN: Yeah,
break the ice.
KRIS: I forgot how pretty New Orleans was.
PRODUCER: _
(both laughing)
KRIS: Oh, boy.
CAITLYN: A little
nervous, a little nervous.
JENNY: Hang on, so, hi. Welcome
once again to another episode of...
I Am Jenny, the new spin-off show.
KRIS: When you talk to
somebody about your view,
you could get a little cranky.
No one wants to sit around
and listen to this (bleep).
So shut the (bleep) up and relax.
CAITLYN: A little
nervous, a little nervous.
KRIS: Uh... Coming.
Hello!
Welcome to the view of the
- whatever this is.
- CAITLYN: You got candles? Wait a second.
- KRIS: Yeah, it's...
- CAITLYN: Well, hi there. Say hi.
- KRIS: Hi, how are you?
- CAITLYN: You went basic brown...
- I like that.
- KRIS: Are you getting taller?
Oh, it must be the heels.
- CAITLYN: Well, they're not big heels, yeah.
- KRIS: Where are all your girlfriends?
CAITLYN: We're gonna
meet everybody tonight.
KRIS: Oh, okay, for dinner or something?
CAITLYN: Uh, yeah, we're gonna
go to dinner and then, uh...
KRIS: What does that
mean? What are you... ?
- What is this?
- CAITLYN: Party time!
- KRIS: Oh, my God, do I need a nap?
- CAITLYN: Um...
- KRIS: For a person who never stayed up past 9:00?
- CAITLYN: I know, no.
- I... I've been doing... I know, I know, I know.
- KRIS: And now you're, now it's party time?
CAITLYN: We have been on the road
for like about a month right now,
- I...
- KRIS: Wow.
CAITLYN: Yeah, it's been a long trip.
- But I'm very glad you're here.
- KRIS: We were all wondering
why you were MIA, and we hadn't
heard from you in a bit, so...
- CAITLYN: Well, I've been on the road.
- KRIS: Somebody's got to come figure this out.
CAITLYN: Please do.
- KRIS: I'm gonna, um, put some things away.
- CAITLYN: Okay.
KRIS: And maybe take a catnap.
CAITLYN: Okay, we'll just have
a quick little glass of wine,
and then, uh, we'll go to dinner
and you'll meet all the girls...
- it'll be fun.
- KRIS: Okay, oh, I can't wait!
What are you gonna wear, Jenner?
CAITLYN: I've got something for you.
KRIS: Oh, boy. I can't wait.
- CAITLYN: All right. I'll see you in a bit.
- KRIS: All right.
- CAITLYN: Bye.
- KRIS: Bye.
(chuckles, groans)
(knocking) JENNY: Hello?
ELLA: Jenny?
JENNY: It's time for Jenny
Boylan cam... in you go.
ELLA: Oh, oh.
JENNY: Come a little closer, you ready?
Hang on, so,
hi. Welcome to once again
to another episode of...
I Am Jenny, the new spin-off show.
We're here with our,
with today's next guest.
- ELLA: Hello.
- JENNY: Uh, Ms. Ella Giselle.
- ELLA: Hi.
- JENNY: So, Ella,
uh, what would you like to say to
your, to your new, to your people?
- ELLA: Thank you for supporting me.
- (Jenny snores)
JENNY: Oh, I'm sorry. I just
dozed off there for a second.
- What do we not know about you?
- ELLA: I survive
off of one drink.
- Chocolate milk.
- JENNY: Chocolate milk.
What do you, how do you feel if you
can't get chocolate milk? What happens?
ELLA: Um, angry.
JENNY: What's the most amount of
chocolate milk you've had in a single day?
- ELLA: Six... probably more.
- JENNY: Six glasses and...
- what were you like then?
- ELLA: Uh...
- Not feeling very well.
- JENNY: Well, you know what?
The first step in solving the problem
is admitting that it is a problem.
- ELLA: Is it a problem though?
- JENNY: Well...
That's about all the
time we have for today on
- I Am Ella.
- ELLA: I am Ella.
- I like this. Do I get, like, a deal?
- (Jenny laughs)
(knocking)
- KRIS: You look nice.
- CAITLYN: Oh, thank you. I went brown.
KRIS: Yeah, well, you certainly
did. It looks good with your hair.
- CAITLYN: I know.
- KRIS: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: What is that?
- KRIS: It's a cape.
- CAITLYN: Cool.
- PRODUCER: _
_
KRIS: Pull our tops up?
Well, you can pull your top up.
- Mine's staying right where it is.
- CAITLYN: No, that's okay.
- Well, no, yours is staying where your... ?
- KRIS: Your boobs are a little
- fresher than mine.
- CAITLYN: Mine are staying in the exactly same place, too.
- KRIS: You just got a boob job.
- CAITLYN: Yeah, maybe throw some,
maybe throw some beads,
beads out or something,
- but that's as far as we go.
- KRIS: No, your boobs are perky
- and mine aren't, yeah.
- CAITLYN: Well, they are, yeah, okay.
KRIS: So let's start there.
CAITLYN: I got his number.
KRIS: All right, yeah, well,
- anyway.
- (indistinct chatter)
- CAITLYN: Oh, girls?
- KRIS: Hi, I'm Kris.
- How are you?
- CAITLYN: Candis.
- BOTH: Nice to see you.
- KRIS: Boy, all this glam...
I love it!
I never thought an evening
in New Orleans would
turn out to be me and a group
of transgender women, but
you know what, why not?
- This is so exciting.
- CAITLYN: These are everybody
that's been on the bus. Jenny?
JENNY: Jenny, I live with my wife Deirdre.
We have been married for 27 years...
12 as husband and wife,
and 15 as wife and wife.
KRIS: Oh, wow, she's a really good sport.
- I like that. (Laughs) That's amazing.
- CAITLYN: She's a saint...
KRIS: She's a lot better than I am.
No, I'm kidding.
- KATE: I thought I saw it all until I met Caitlyn.
- (laughter)
My eyes have been opened.
CAITLYN: When you have an,
like an eight-hour bus ride,
the conversation gets very
interesting, doesn't it?
KRIS: So, if you spend
that much time with Caitlyn,
and you guys are in a closed quarters...
what is the most annoying
thing about Caitlyn
- that you could possibly... ?
- CAITLYN: That I'm a Republican... okay, let's get over it.
KRIS: Yeah, politics, right?
Oh, I could relate to that.
KATE: For me, it's not
that you are a Republican.
It's how
I experience you expressing
your Republican views.
JENNY: Exactly.
KRIS: Oh, hallelujah.
- JENNY: We went to the Democratic debates in Iowa.
- KRIS: Oh, boy.
CAITLYN: I went and I got a
picture with Hillary Clinton.
- KRIS: That's awesome.
- CAITLYN: I know.
KRIS: How did that feel?
CAITLYN: Um, how did it feel?
Uh, it was good. She was very nice.
She's a politician.
KRIS: Yeah, I know, but
you're not a politician,
but you think you're a
politician sometimes, I think.
- CAITLYN: That, I... I... I... I enjoy politics.
- JENNY: I am just gonna sit back.
- CAITLYN: I... I enjoy politics.
- KRIS: Yeah, you do,
but sometimes, sometimes when you talk
to somebody about your view,
not everybody's gonna always agree.
And sometimes,
you could get a little cranky.
- CAITLYN: Oh, I agree, I agree.
- KRIS: But because you're so, um...
- CAITLYN: I, I get it.
- KRIS: ... crazy about this one thing...
you are really crazy about this one thing,
and no one wants to sit around
and listen to this (bleep)
so shut the (bleep) up and relax!
(laughter)
I can't wait to see you guys again.
Not you, Jenner, just your friends.
Don't get excited!
(all cheering)
- JENNY: Did she tell you early on?
- KRIS: No.
- CAITLYN: Oh, I did, too.
- KRIS: There was no "I am transgender."
CAITLYN: I certainly told
her what was going on.
KRIS: I just have to share one story
that when it got really crazy...
when I met Bruce,
there was no politics ever.
And then it just got a little bit more...
CAITLYN: They're learning
way too much about me.
KRIS: ... and a little bit
more and a little bit more,
and over the years, someone got very upset
some certain person was
- president of the United States.
- CHANDI: Uh-huh?
KRIS: And would wake me up
at like 5:00 in the morning
so upset and realizing
that I was maybe on somebody else's side.
And, but I really, I'm kind of neutral.
- I just go with what I... I...
- CAITLYN: You're giving away all of my secrets.
- KRIS: I'm sorry.
- CANDIS: I love it!
CHANDI: A lot of people
are having a hard time
trying to figure out how
Caitlyn can be a Republican
when, in most cases, Republicans
really don't support our community.
- KRIS: Yeah.
- CHANDI: But we've had to listen
to the things that Cait has had to say.
There's work in both areas that
need to be, that need to be done.
CAITLYN: It's an educational experience.
KRIS: But you're unwilling,
I think at times...
- CHANDI: Yes! (Laughs)
- KRIS: ... to listen to somebody else's view
- and meet in the middle.
- CAITLYN: No, I... don't,
don't don't everybody
start agreeing with her!
KATE: Well, part of the issue
has been that we outnumber
Caitlyn on the bus,
and we just don't want to
end up bullying her or
putting her on the defensive.
KRIS: Take it from me,
who was one person
- with one person.
- CAITLYN: 23 years.
KRIS: You need that many people
against that with this subject matter.
Trust me, you guys are gonna be just fine,
- but you need...
- CAITLYN: I think we need, need to go to dinner.
Is it time to go to dinner?
KATE: God bless America,
let's go to dinner!
CAITLYN: I have to
admit it is kind of hard
to listen to all these people in the room
come up with their notes on me...
their likes and dislikes, okay?
I got my ex-wife and my friends
all comparing notes. Not easy.
I don't think I'm gonna come
out of this, you know, very good.
CANDIS: That's really
nice of you to come and,
- like, meet all of us.
- KRIS: I wanted to see what was going on out here.
He was a little...
she was a little MIA.
- CAITLYN: Who?
- KRIS: You.
CAITLYN: Where did you get those earrings?
I don't remember them in the old days,
when I used to steal your earrings.
- (Candis laughs)
- KRIS: These are Cartier,
and you would have been in big trouble.
- CAITLYN: Oh, okay.
- (Laughter)
What else is new? I was in big
trouble all the time anyway.
KRIS: You know what we found?
You stole the key to my
closet and you hid it.
CAITLYN: I thought I hid it so well.
KRIS: Yeah, we... I found it.
- CAITLYN: Really?
- KRIS: Yeah, that was very tricky, Jenner.
- CAITLYN: I know, it was good.
- KRIS: Yeah.
- (Candis laughs)
- CAITLYN: It was good.
I had to steal yours, go
get it made and then...
KRIS (laughing): You had one made?
- CAITLYN: Had one made, yeah.
- CANDIS: Oh!
It's nice that you guys are laughing
and are together as friends.
It's a really good thing.
KRIS: I'm going to kill him after dinner.
- (Candis laughs)
- CAITLYN: Right.
You'll kil lher.
- KRIS: Kill her after dinner, sorry.
- CHANDI: Right.
KRIS: Got to keep correcting me.
CAITLYN: I certainly
said I had gender issues.
KRIS: I didn't know. Until all of this,
I couldn't have given you the
definition of "transgender."
- CAITLYN: Let me finish.
- KRIS: Okay, you're being stubborn; that's fine.
- (indistinct conversations)
- KRIS: I'm gonna have that.
CANDIS: You have a black napkin? (Laughs)
JENNY: What napkin goes
bestwith your clothes?
- CANDIS: Yes, of course.
- JENNY: Candis Cayne...
- (Kris laughs)
- Although I've got this
- unsightly white napkin.
- (Candis laughs)
- May I have a black napkin also, please?
- WAITER: How many more black napkins?
- JENNY: I think it's just the two of us.
- (laughter)
CAITLYN: That's amazing, that
you've gotten to the point
where you want a matching
napkin to your outfit.
CAITLYN: We have so gotten
you out of the woods of Maine.
JENNY: So Caitlyn's been
out for six months now...
- KRIS: Mm-hmm.
- Six months?
JENNY: Where are you now as opposed to
where you were six months ago?
KRIS: Probably more tolerant
and I have more acceptance and probably
understand it a little bit more.
JENNY: But did it...
did you take it per...
I mean, I know, speaking from
personal experience, my wife...
my wife, I think, in some ways took it
- personally when I first came out.
- KRIS: I definitely took it personally.
JENNY: I think she felt
like, "Wait, I wasn't enough?"
KRIS: No, I feel like
she was very unhappy.
Very, very unhappy for a very long time.
CAITLYN: I was surviving, but I was...
- KRIS: Yeah.
- CAITLYN: ... dealing with a lot of things.
- KRIS: Forever.
- JENNY: So when you look at her,
do you see Caitlyn?
Or do you see the person that she was?
KRIS: I see great eyebrows...
- (laughter)
- ... and high cheekbones.
No, I see the present.
I can't see Bruce in this, right now.
But I have memories of that.
- CAITLYN: It's a million miles away.
- KRIS: Yeah.
So I don't see that anymore.
You just get used to it,
it's weird, you just see...
- JENNY: The new normal.
- KRIS: Yeah.
How old were you when you realized that
- you were transgender?
- JENNY: I knew I was trans from a very early age.
Four, five, six.
It's one of my earliest memories.
And I tried everything I could
to make the boy thing work.
You come out when
you're ready to come out.
KRIS: So, wait, so I have a question,
but with no disrespect.
So I just really want to know this.
- CHANDI: How else will you know if you don't ask?
- KRIS: No, but... so
if you're trans... a transgender woman...
what do you do with the bits and pieces
that are below the belt?
CAITLYN: Oh, my God!
KRIS: People wonder, when
they look at somebody.
I seriously want to
know. I mean, you know,
- Caitlyn...
- CAITLYN: I know.
KRIS: ... but they are
asking the question like that.
Am I getting way too crazy?
JENNY: If you knew ten years
ago what you know now...
do you think you would still be married?
CAITLYN: There's one more
thing I really need to do
before she leaves: have a
one-on-one conversation with her.
Because I... I feel like
I have a lot to say to her.
- (knocking gently)
- KRIS: Coming.
KRIS: People wonder,
when they look at somebody
and they say, okay, well,
what happens to, like...
I seriously want to
know. I mean, you know,
- Caitlyn...
- CAITLYN: I know.
KRIS: ... but they are
asking the question like that.
Am I getting way too crazy?
- (talking over each other)
- KRIS: I mean, I'm sorry.
I just wondered, like, what...
Does everybody do the same thing?
- KATE: Okay.
- CAITLYN: You're sitting next to Kate.
- There you go. Listen to Kate.
- KRIS: Okay.
- All right.
- KATE: It used to be understood
that if you have a penis, you're a man.
If you have a vulva and
vagina, you're a woman.
Genitals really have very little to do
- with who you think you are.
- KRIS: Inside.
- KATE: Yeah.
- KRIS: Okay.
- KATE: So...
- KRIS: That makes sense.
KATE: ... it really doesn't matter
what a person has down there.
You're still interested.
KRIS: It does to me.
- No, I'm kidding.
- KATE: It does to you, and because you're so close...
KRIS: No, no, I mean, no,
but it's the, it's the...
I think the knee-jerk curiosity of...
- CHANDI: Well, can I tell you something first?
- KRIS: Yes.
CHANDI: All trans people
don't choose to do that.
- KATE: Exactly.
- CHANDI: And that's the important thing for...
for us to be able to share
with someone who is an ally.
KRIS: So every person
decides what's best for them.
- KATE: That's right.
- KRIS: ... for... like a case-by-case.
- Okay, got it.
- JENNY: Having been married
- those 23 years...
- KRIS: Mm-hmm.
JENNY: ... now that she has
done the presto-change-o,
does it in any way make you question
yourself and who you
were during that time?
KRIS: No.
I don't know why, but it doesn't.
- JENNY: She tell you early on?
- KRIS: No.
CAITLYN: Oh, I did, too.
KRIS: She keeps saying she
told me, but she didn't.
- (Chandi laughs)
- I think what happened was...
KRIS: ... a conversation in a driveway.
He says to me,
"Do you ever want to have more
kids?" And I said, "Oh, God, no."
So he says, "Oh, neither do
I. That's, like, that's great.
And I couldn't have any
more kids if I wanted to."
And I went, "Wait. What?" And he goes,
"Oh, geez, you know, back in the '80s,
I messed around with this or
that and it kind of screwed up
my sperm count and, you
know, but whatever... "
It could've been, like,
steroids for all I knew,
'cause he was an athlete. Never
said estrogen, never said...
- He just said, "I took some (bleep) in the '80s... "
- JENNY: "Some (bleep)"?
KRIS: I mean, whatever word.
There was no "I am transgender."
It was "I took some stuff in the
'80s and my sperm isn't good."
CAITLYN: I said I had a condition
that I had been dealing with forever.
I said that I was on hormones
and that's the reason it
might be tough to get pregnant.
KRIS: And my friends said,
"Have a bottle of wine
and go have great sex." And
we did, and we had Kendall.
And then a minute later, we had Kylie.
- But none of that was "I want to be a woman."
- CAITLYN: I certainly
told her what was going on.
My version of what happened at the
beginning is obviously very different
than her version. I certainly
said I had gender issues
and that I was on hormones and, you know,
I had boobs and, you
know, the whole thing.
KRIS: You didn't have boobs. I
didn't know until all of this.
- I couldn't have given you the definition of "transgender"...
- CAITLYN: Let me finish.
- KRIS: ... until six months ago.
KRIS: Okay, you're being
stubborn. That's fine.
JENNY: I don't know that Kris
and Caitlyn have ever really had
this conversation. It may be that Caitlyn
really did tell Kris and
Kris just didn't want to hear it.
It might also be that Caitlyn
didn't say anything.
I... I've seen Caitlyn do this.
She says, like, one little thing,
and then it's like, "Oh, we're all done!
There. Thank goodness that's all over
and now we can go do something else."
I think I spilled the beans with my wife
a half a dozen times. We had the big talk.
And the very next time we talked
about it, she was like, "What?"
And then, you know, a little
while would go by and I would...
the next time would
come around and I'd say,
"Remember when I was talking about
the whole transgender thing?"
And she was like, "The what?"
Maybe we're not being clear.
Maybe we're just kind of mumbling
in a kind of a... (mumbles)
KRIS: Maybe you're doing it
in your sleep or something.
JENNY: But our loved
ones also, to be fair,
don't want to hear it.
KRIS: Well, I think with Caitlyn,
I kept saying, "Why are you so...
unhappy? Like, what's going on?"
I would sit you down on the
couch in the bedroom and go,
"Tell me what's wrong. There's
something really wrong. I can handle it.
Just tell me. Just please tell me."
And she would say, "You
wouldn't understand.
You just won't... you
just wouldn't under... "
"Well, try me." "No, you're
just not that kind of a person."
You know. So it was this back
and forth for a long time.
JENNY: You have two people
who are not communicating on,
oddly... (stammers) and tragically,
what's actually the most
important thing in their lives.
The reason I didn't tell my
wife before we got married
was because I wanted to
protect the people that I loved.
I didn't want to cause
harm to the people that I loved.
I didn't want to be a source of trouble.
I wanted to protect them.
I wanted to stand between them
and the trouble of the world.
- CAITLYN: And that's exactly where I was.
- KRIS: Protecting everybody, yeah.
CAITLYN: I never wanted to hurt anybody.
JENNY: If you knew ten
years ago what you know now,
do you think you would still be married?
- KRIS: I don't know.
- CAITLYN: Ooh, good question.
KRIS: That's a really good question.
- MAN: Ma'am, your entre.
- CAITLYN: Thank you.
KRIS: I probably would have turned into
the world's greatest best friend.
JENNY: Is it too late for you
to be the world's best friend?
- KRIS: No. Never.
- JENNY: Good.
The bottom line for Kris and Caitlyn
to be able to move forward is forgiveness,
and forgiveness is no small thing.
It's clear to me, even now, they have
a relationship that goes very deep.
It sure feels to me
like they are going to be
part of each other's
lives for the long term,
but they each have work to
do if that's gonna be true.
CANDIS: You've decided
to change your life to...
to truly honor who you
are as a human being,
and have your kids stand by your side,
and have your ex-wife...
which is super rare...
- to be here...
- JENNY: It's amazing.
CANDIS: ... but with
all us, your girlfriends,
so I think we all have to do a toast.
- CHANDI: We should.
- KRIS: Oh!
- CANDIS: To Caitlyn.
- JENNY: Let's do it to Kris Jenner.
- CANDIS: And to Kris.
- KRIS: Oh, no, no, no.
KATE: And to Kris.
- CHANDI: Yeah.
- KRIS: Thanks, guys.
- CHANDI: To the new normal.
- CANDIS: To the modern family.
- PAM: Cheers.
- CAITLYN: Yes. I love that.
- (crowd chatter)
- MAN: Good evening, ladies.
CANDIS: Good evening.
CAITLYN: We are doing it in New Orleans.
This is Bourbon Street, baby.
COURTNEY: This is Bourbon?
- KIP: Yeah.
- COURTNEY: I've never been here. I love it!
CAITLYN: Doesn't help, if you try
to stay inconspicuous, with a camera.
- They're everywhere.
- CANDIS: Oh, but they can't see
- your face so that's good.
- CAITLYN: I know.
(crowd chatter)
KIP: _
CANDIS: They would.
- (song ends)
- (applause and cheering)
CANDIS: Chandi!
COURTNEY: Jenny is up there, too.
CHANDI: Never in a million
years would I think going out
on the dance floor to
dance with Jenny Boylan.
That's being checked off my bucket list.
Jenny Boylan was feeling herself.
- Oh, she was feeling herself.
- (Crowd chatter)
♪ ♪
KRIS: _
_
It's so awesome.
CANDIS: _
_
KRIS: _
KRIS: What I've witnessed
here tonight firsthand,
I never would have imagined
that she could experience
this kind of friendship and happiness.
And I think that that's what it...
life is all about. Life is really short,
and I think that you have to go out
and grab your true purpose,
and I think that she's well on her way.
- Cheers!
- CANDIS: Cheers!
- Great to meet you!
- KRIS: Great night. You, too.
CANDIS: We have beads to throw.
COURTNEY: Just keep your shirt on.
- CAITLYN: My people! Oh!
- (whooping)
- KRIS: Oh, you got it, baby.
- KIP: Yes!
- (Whooping and hooting)
KRIS: Yeah!
_
CAITLYN: _
- MAN: Kris Jenner!
- _
_
- KRIS: What?
- MAN: Yo, Kris!
- KRIS: Aah!
- CAITLYN: Hit 'em.
_
- MAN: Yo, Kris!
- KRIS: _
CAITLYN: _
KRIS: _
CAITLYN: I know. All the
way to there. Here we go.
(whooping)
_
- (whooping)
- Hey!
KRIS: _
_
CAITLYN: Oh, well, you
know, I agree with that.
Here we go way back there.
(crowd chatter)
- (whooping)
- (indistinct chatter)
MAN: _
(Caitlyn laughs)
- CAITLYN: What did he say?
- JENNY: He said, "Bruce, go straight."
- CAITLYN: Oh, God.
- JENNY: I think that ship sailed.
CAITLYN: I know.
CANDIS: That was so much fun.
KRIS: You look really beautiful.
CAITLYN: It is absolutely
amazing what a blow-dry will do.
- JENNY: A blow what?
- CAITLYN: A blow dry, yeah.
- JENNY: Dry. Blow dry.
- CAITLYN: A blow out.
- CAITLYN: A blow out will do.
- COURTNEY: Blow job.
- CAITLYN: No.
- CANDIS: This is a very Doctor Zhivago jacket.
JENNY: That's the coolest jacket.
CHANDI: Tens, tens, tens.
You've gotten tens across
the board, Kris Jenner. Ten.
KRIS: Tens, tens, tens. Good tens.
You guys have all gotten
a major ten from me.
- CHANDI: Oh, my goodness.
- KRIS: You're all so delicious.
- CANDIS: Oh, thank you.
- CHANDI: Oh. We love it from you.
- KRIS: Pretty fab.
- JENNY: Delicious.
KRIS: Really pretty fab, honest to God.
I can't wait to see you guys again.
- CHANDI: Yes.
- KRIS: I mean that.
Not you, Jenner. Just your friends.
- (laughter)
- JENNY: We're going right now.
- CAITLYN: Mmm.
- (cheering)
CAITLYN: Little red light's on.
(sighs)
That...
was a crazy night.
Honestly, I feel good about it.
I'm glad Kris had such a
good time with all the girls.
Um, there certainly was a little tension.
But I really feel like
there's one more thing
I really need to do, and that is...
before she leaves, have a
one-on-one conversation with her,
uh, because I feel like I
have a lot to say to her.
(insects trilling)
CAITLYN: There's really a lot
I want to get off my chest with Kris.
The girls have taught me a lot on
this trip about being more kinder,
gentler, softer approach.
I just hope I don't...
kind of resort to the old habits,
uh, of being defensive and loud.
I've got a lot to say,
and I'm afraid if I don't have it now,
um,
I'll probably never have the conversation.
KRIS: Coming.
KRIS: You changed your birth certificate?
Does this mean that you didn't exist?
JENNY: I've never regretted
having surgery for one day,
not one hour, never.
CAITLYN: Right now, I'm...
I'm not interested in
- doing something like that.
- JENNY: I don't believe it.
I know she's thinking about it.
WOMAN: In an independent adoption,
you're gonna have to disclose
that you're transgender.
You've got to be matched
with a birth mother
- that says I want my child raised by you.
- CANDIS: Wow.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -