- Huh? Is that amazing?
- That is...
- Unbelievable story!
- You know what?
None of it
would have happened
if I didn't intercede on that
guy's behalf in the restaurant.
- Unbelievable, Larry.
- It saved your life.
- Saved my life.
- What if he hadn't wanted seconds?
None of this
would have happened.
- None of it would have happened.
- Bashert.
The fatwa is over!
- Yes!
- The fatwa is over!
Let's drink to that, huh?
It's a new me.
Well, whatever.
We're glad you're back, Larry.
- Thank you, Susie.
- Welcome.
I didn't even tell you
the biggest news.
"Fatwa! the Musical"
is back on.
- It is?
- Whoa, wait... wait a second.
You're jumping the gun
a little bit.
We're having a meeting with
Lin-Manuel Miranda this week,
and if he wants to do it, then...
You're meeting with
Lin-Manuel Miranda? Oh, my...
It's the only way it can go
forward... is if he's in it.
He's in LA now, right? Isn't it...
aren't they doing the show here?
Yeah, they're doing "Hamilton."
Yeah, can you get us tickets?
I mean, it's here.
No, it's here and we can't
even get tickets to it!
Already with the "Hamilton"
tickets? Are you kidding?
- I would love some, too.
- Huh?
I don't know if I can
get you tickets.
I haven't even met the guy yet.
- You saw it, right?
- Yeah, I saw it in New York.
- Fantastic.
- Isn't it so fantastic?
Oh, my God, I love that show.
Incredible.
I saw it and I played...
36 holes of golf that day.
And, uh, I fell asleep before
the second act of "Hamilton."
- You're kidding.
- I slept through...
I slept through the intermission.
- No!
- You fell asleep? Wait a minute.
Only you would fall asleep at
the hottest show on Broadway.
- Hey, hey. Guys, guys.
- How did you fall asleep?
- It's so exciting and interesting.
- The Shucker.
- Excuse me, the Shucker.
- Oh, the Shucker.
- Hey, how's everybody doing?
- Hello.
- Taste good?
- Fantastic.
It's all good? No grit?
- No grit.
- Okay, no grit.
Just shuck and awe.
Okay, well, that's great.
I've got a...
I got a whole bunch of bluepoints.
Got some Kusshis for you all.
- Whoo!
- Hope you left some room.
- Okay.
- I know he did.
Fantastic.
Cute as could be.
- Ay, God.
- Shucking?
- What's the matter?
- What happened?
- He overheard that entire story
about me sleeping
through "Hamilton."
What do you care?
What difference does it make?
I just hope it doesn't
get back to... to Lin.
I doubt that, Larry.
You're paranoid.
He shucks all over town. I don't
know what circles he shucks in.
He could shuck and tell.
- I'll be back.
- Do you think we can still get the tickets?
Who's ringing the bell
this time of night?
It's Lin-Manuel Miranda.
I think he heard about the...
Hello, I'm Rose Shapiro.
Remember me?
No.
I sold you this house
five years ago.
Oh, okay.
Um, well, what can I do for you?
Well, I was in the neighborhood
and I thought I'd just pop in
and see how my house is doing
if that's okay with you.
Actually, I'm... sorry,
I've got some dinner guests, so.
Well, I won't take but a minute.
I was so happy in this house.
I lived here for 50 years.
Raised all my children here.
Is that okay?
- Yeah, I... yeah, okay.
- Oh, oh, thank you.
But it can't be too long,
though, okay?
It won't be, I promise you.
I'll be very discreet.
What have you done here?
You've covered up that cut
stone from Italy with a rug!
Yeah, well, it needed
a little warming up in here.
It was very cold and
I happen to like it.
And you know what?
It happens to be my house, so...
And what have you done in here?
Where's the wonderful
wallpaper I put up?
The wallpaper with the pirates?
Are you kidding?
It was the first thing
I took down when I moved in.
Well, I guess it's your house.
You can do anything you want to.
- Yeah, oh, yes!
- I think I'll check over here.
That's true! That...
I can do anything I want to!
What are you doing...
what the fuck?
I'm checking the master bedroom.
I don't want you to.
It's my house.
Well, all right.
If you wanna be that way.
Yeah, I think I do
wanna be that way.
I do. All right,
you know what?
I think it's time to go.
Let's go. Come on.
- All right.
- Come on.
- I guess I better go.
- Enough. I've had enough.
- Oh!
- Ay-ay-ay.
Look at this poor ficus!
What have you done?
I left this with you in good
faith to love and cherish.
Yeah, no, I've taken
very good care of it.
- It's old.
- It's dropping all its leaves. Do you water it?
Of course I water it. All right,
come on, I got some people here.
You've got to go.
Come on.
There's the door.
Time to go. Thank you.
Good-bye.
Thank you for stopping by.
- Don't do it again.
- No, I know, I know.
And then, Todd,
this other guy,
had... what's the male
equivalent of bush?
- Man bush.
That, like... so, finding
his penis was like...
I'm searching for the
baby bird in the...
- In the nest.
And then I'm, like, looking.
I couldn't even find the goods
because the Afro was so intense.
Yeah, okay, all right.
I think... I think we've heard
enough of that story.
- Sorry, Lar.
- But, Larry,
she has so many funny
stories about her exes.
I've been hearing
them for years.
- They're hilarious.
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- Yeah.
- Remember the one you told me about?
- The guy who... the leaner?
- Yeah, the leaner.
- Yes.
- The Leaning Tower of Pisa?
- That guy?
- The Leaning Tower of Peter.
Yeah, oh, that's...
that's a good one, too.
- That was a good one.
- I know, I know.
And then Todd,
this other guy...
Oh, yeah. Oh, that was
so many years ago.
Oh, my God.
I don't believe it.
This room used to be
so warm and inviting.
Mrs. Shapiro, what are...
what are you doing?
- Well, I just...
- I thought you left.
Well, I was just
looking around.
- It used to be so different.
- She used to live in the house.
Uh, she wanted to look around.
And the house was so much
better when I had it.
- I don't know what he's done with this.
- Okay, you need to go now.
- Well, you don't have to be rude about it.
- You're the one being rude.
You come in here and
you're criticizing my house.
You don't live here anymore.
That's right, keep going.
Yeah, and now close it.
Close it.
- Go... go back to the leaner.
- Okay.
The Leaning Tower of Peter?
Oh, and he was a biter, too.
He used to bite me on the ass.
- Which was not as bad as...
- A bite on the damn nipple!
Oh, my God, totally.
'Cause that hurts.
Well, that's it, everybody.
- I'm all done for the night.
- Whoo!
Thanks. It's been a privilege
working for you tonight.
And I hope you agree with me
that this has been
a spectacular "shuck-cess."
- Whoa!
- Oh, nice. Okay.
- Thank you.
- I'll... I'll walk you out.
- He's adorable.
- Yeah.
- Bridge, what was the guy...
- Anyway, um,
it was great having
you here tonight.
Everybody really enjoyed it.
I hope so. I hope so.
- Had a great time.
- Yeah. Yeah, it was great.
Um, I just wanna say one thing.
You know, earlier when I was
talking about "Hamilton,"
what... what you didn't hear
me say was that I played,
uh, 36 holes of golf that
day and I was exhausted.
And that's one of the
reasons I was so tired,
uh, during the performance.
I mean, I... I loved
what I... what I saw.
Sure. What I heard
was that you fell asleep.
Yes, I did fall asleep,
but what you didn't hear
is why I fell asleep,
why I was so tired.
- I loved the show.
- Sure.
You can paint it
or dress it up
anyway you want,
but sleep is sleep.
- And you fell asleep.
- Yeah.
- All right?
- True, I did.
But, uh, I would hope
that as you shuck
from house to house that, uh,
you can afford me some shucker
discretion in this matter.
- I understand.
- Oh.
- And I appreciate that.
- Good. Thank you.
And I would also appreciate, um,
two tickets to "Hamilton."
- Oh. Really?
- Yeah.
Well...
I don't have any access
to getting you tickets
to "Hamilton," okay?
- It's most unfortunate.
- And why is... why is that?
It'd be a shame
if Lin-Manuel Miranda
ever found out that someone was
falling asleep in his show.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Super.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I like that guy.
- Oh, he was adorable.
- He was adorable.
- What? Who?
- This cake is unbelievable.
- I know.
- Oh, it's the best cheesecake.
Um, all right.
I think, uh...
I think we're good here.
I think that's enough.
- What?
- That's enough.
- What are you talking about?
- Time to go.
We're having afterdinner
conversation, Larry.
- It's enough.
- You know, this is so typical of you.
I don't like all the
lingering after dinner.
You had your dessert. Get...
get the hell out. Come on, get out.
All right, thank you for
ruining a lovely evening.
On the contrary, didn't ruin it.
Saved it.
- Uh-huh. Bridget, call me tomorrow.
- I saved it.
- Mwah. Cheryl, Ted.
- Mwah. I'll call you.
All right, okay, come on.
Time to go, people.
- Hey.
- This is your Larry.
- Whose is this?
- Oh, I don't know.
Maybe... maybe the
Shucker left it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Man, this is cool.
- Ooh.
- You know what?
- Ooh, Jeffrey.
- Keep it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Oh, definitely keep it.
I love it.
- You do?
- It looks fantastic on you.
- Really?
- Looks good.
How about that?
Look at me. I'm the sheriff.
Now let's go home, Sheriff.
Come on.
- Yeah.
- All right, people.
- Okay, yep.
- Let's go.
- Time to go.
- We're getting kicked out.
She's showing me
love and affection
that I've never felt before.
- 'Cause of the hat.
- All 'cause of the hat.
She listens to what I say.
She takes suggestions.
And all she wants
to do is have sex.
- Susie?
- Yes.
So I have to keep
the hat on during sex.
- That's her thing.
- What?
Yeah. I haven't had
this much sex since college.
- Wow.
- It's almost like, you know,
she's got a thing for cowboys
from her past or something.
She's got a real perversion,
doesn't she?
Yeah, she loves the Old West.
Where are the women who
have a bald perversion?
I wonder if there's, like,
a place they all hang out.
You just walk in and, you know.
I wonder if it's
worth investigating.
You wonder?
I would have already
investigated it.
I would have... I would have blown
up Google with... if I were you.
- Hey, by the way.
- Yeah?
Today with...
with Lin...
- Yeah.
- Okay?
You don't think he's gonna
wanna write the songs, do you?
Hmm, I hadn't thought of that,
but I... I don't know.
They're my songs.
I don't wanna...
Your songs.
And can I say something?
- Yeah.
- I love those songs.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Yeah.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Lin isn't here yet, but if
you'd like to go upstairs
to Aaron's office, you can.
Oh.
Ma'am.
How you doing?
- Larry! Hey.
- Hey!
Come on in, come on in.
Jeff, hi.
- How you doing, Aaron?
- Aaron Warden.
- Yeah. I know you.
- Nice to meet you.
Hello, hello. Nice hat.
- Thank you.
- You're just coming back from Vegas?
Uh, no. This is my new look.
I like it. I like how you think.
Lin's very excited, by the way.
I read the play personally.
Great.
- Laughed a lot.
- Really?
- Great moments, great comedy.
- Wow.
We're really excited, seriously.
And you think that he's interested
in... in playing Salman?
I think so.
The only issue... he's so busy.
So busy right now.
You know, the world is after him.
What's that? "Judge Judy"?
- Oh, you like Judith?
- Oh, I love Judge Judy.
- Are you kidding?
- Good. Good, good. She's my client.
If I ever had to go to court,
I would like for
her to adjudicate.
- That's how good she is.
- But she's tough.
- I'm so sorry I'm late.
- Oh, there he is!
- Our national treasure.
- Hey! Jeff. How are you?
Jeff, Lin. Larry, Lin.
Nice to see you.
- How did it go? Good?
- It was good.
- Yeah, I think we're done.
- Good. I'm excited.
All right, I was just telling
them how excited we are.
Thank you so much
for bringing this to us.
- It's so exciting.
- Oh, oh, thank...
you know, I loved "Hamilton,"
needless to say.
- I saw it with you.
- Oh, great. Awesome.
You know, I know the show's in
LA right now. Everybody's loving it.
I was wondering, would it be possible
to get two tickets for my shucker?
For your shucker?
Like an oyster shucker?
Yeah, yeah, oyster shucker. Yeah.
Fantastic shucker. So fast.
- He's your personal shucker?
- No. He... he shucks for me from time to time.
Hey, if he's important to you,
sure, I'll... I'll...
- no promises, but I'll ask.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
All right, I'll let
you chat together,
and my office is your office.
Have a great time.
I'm excited about this.
- Great work again, Larry.
- Thanks again.
Thanks for letting us
use the office.
Appreciate it.
Let's have a seat, guys.
Okay, let's see.
Where do you want...
Right.
So, "Fatwa! the Musical."
Where do you guys wanna do it?
Well, you know, we're thinking...
- Broadway.
Broadway? All right.
I think you're gonna wanna
try it out of town first.
You know, why not LA?
I think you should do it here.
- Okay.
- Nice.
And who do you see for a cast?
Obviously, we'd like you
to play, um, Salman.
- Oh, "Salmon."
- Salman.
Yeah, "Salmon" Rushdie.
"Salmon," yeah.
And, um, Mandy Patinkin
for, uh...
- No one but Mandy Patinkin.
- ...for the ayatollah.
F. Murray Abraham.
- Yeah. Good idea. Let's do that.
- Yeah. I'm telling you.
The "F" is for
fucking awesome.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting a...
I'm sorry, guys, this is London.
Can I just have you guys step outside
for a second? Thanks so much.
This is really going well.
Hello?
What the hell's wrong with you?
- You said yes to everything.
- Yeah.
You were so determined downstairs.
What the hell happened?
- It's the desk.
- The desk?
Yes. It's the power of the desk.
He's up high, I'm down low.
Everything he says, I say yes to.
He's in the boss chair.
- He's... he's like... it's like he's my boss.
- This is not good.
We gotta do everything we can to
get him out from behind the desk.
- Okay.
- Hey, you guys can come on back in.
Please, make yourselves
comfortable.
I got an idea.
Why don't you sit over here?
Yeah, no. I'm comfortable.
Thank you so much.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm great.
I gotta tell you, we could have a real
nice, intimate discussion over here.
You know, we'll be able to
kind of really kick it around.
Yeah, I feel like we're
at a nice, wide angle.
This is a nice bird's-eye
view of the piece.
I gotta tell you something,
I'm getting laryngitis
screaming across the room,
you're so far away.
Well, I'm enthusiastic
about it, too.
I think we're on the same page.
Listen, not only do I wanna play
"Salmon," I wanna write the songs.
- Yeah, but I... I've written all the songs.
- Yeah.
- That's all done.
- It's a great starting point for us.
You know, what you've written
is... it's a great bedrock.
It's a great foundation
for... for me to...
you know, 'cause it's
inspiring me so much.
You know, let's start
with the opening.
What? The opening?
Come on, the opening's
terrific as is.
♪ There's a fatwa,
there's a fatwa ♪
♪ Gotta run, I think I oughta,
gotta hide ♪
- ♪ I think I gotta... ♪
- ♪ Got a pinspotta ♪
- There... there's more. I'm not done...
- Yeah, there's more.
♪ Pinspotta on our hero ♪
♪ All alone, blood clotta ♪
♪ A fatwa, un, deux, trois, caught ♪
♪ Why am I in the middle of this? ♪
♪ I'm Biggie and 'Pac,
who shot ya? ♪
♪ I'm at the top of the rock
and I'm hotter than guac ♪
♪ What's going on?
I gotta stop ya ♪
♪ Can I... ♪
Where are you going?
No, I was just checking out
the whole area here.
No, have a seat. I'm not done.
Oh, okay... okay.
Yeah. No, have a seat over here.
Yeah, right where you were.
Have a seat.
Make yourself comfortable.
We're in a flow right now.
You're doing great.
Listen, I feel like
I have a lot of ideas
and maybe we should
call another meeting
where I can really download
everything that's in my head,
'cause I'm just scratching
the surface here.
I love what we've all
come up with together,
so let's have
another meeting
in a couple weeks
to keep working.
Okay.
Great.
I have a couple of calls to make
to the West End before it closes.
Yeah, all right, give me the room.
Thanks.
- This is just the beginning.
- Yeah.
- Awesome.
- See you.
- Thank you.
- Okay, thank you.
Ugh, how can you eat
that thing, Riggs?
Hey, it's breakfast, the most
important meal of the day.
What's the name of this show?
- "Chicago Homicide."
- Oh, my God, you poor kid.
It's not that bad.
- People love it.
- Two bullet wounds to the chest...
- People love this?
- Mm-hmm.
People will watch anything
with "Chicago" in the title.
- It's been proven.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Ow. Could this couch
be any more uncomfortable?
- You could have a new couch.
- And that's gonna require people...
- Oh, that's annoying.
- ...lugging something
up the stairs, lugging this out.
I can't stand to see people doing
manual labor in front of me.
- Movers in particular.
- Right. Right.
- Wow.
- A piano.
- Nightmare. Tears.
- Oh, my God.
I wouldn't get a
piano just because
I wouldn't want them to move
the piano into my house.
- That's so stupid.
- It is, but it's true.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Interesting,
the things I'm learning.
Just like talking to all your
friends the other night.
They were so, uh, nice.
That was fun.
- Yeah, it was fun.
- Mmm.
Except maybe...
at the end when you were
talking about those guys.
Susie loves those stories.
- I don't know why.
- Yeah.
I guess I kept thinking...
what if... what if that was me
she was talking about?
Well, I won't talk about you, Larry.
Don't worry.
Is there anything you've
observed thus far or noticed
that you might wanna talk
about at a dinner party?
No. Everything's
completely just regular.
They're too much trouble.
I'm officially done dating.
- "Regular."
- If I get lonely, I'll just rent a penis.
Ah! That is a...
an unapproved "penis."
I'm so sorry,
I gotta call this in before they...
It's Bridget for Bill.
No, he knows why I'm calling.
You hear something?
Sorry, I didn't... I...
Yeah.
No, tell him
I'm holding for him.
Don't let him get away.
- You're so thirsty.
- Oh, my... what?
What?! What are you doing here?
Well, obviously, I'm keeping
this plant alive.
- It's dying here.
- How did you get in here?
I have my own keys.
You forgot to change the locks.
Okay, I want that key back, okay?
And you need to go.
This is not a college dormitory
where you can visit years later
and catch up on things.
We don't have
alumni weekends, okay?
I never should have
sold this house to you.
You're destroying it and you're
certainly destroying this plant.
Okay, you listen to me,
Shapiro, all right?
- Get out!
- All right.
It's not your house!
It's my house!
I live here, not you!
What a fucking psycho.
Fuck me, Tex!
You know how she got in?
She used her key.
- You didn't change the locks?
- I never changed the locks.
So crazy.
- Speaking of crazy.
- Yeah, I know.
- I mean, what the fuck?
- It is the new me. I am all in.
- The boots, too?
- The boots, too.
I'm going for the whole thing.
Women love it. They go nuts.
The only downside is I
gotta keep fucking my wife.
- Sick of it?
- Oh, so sick of it.
Yeah. Hey, we gotta talk about
this... this meeting with Lin.
- Yeah.
- I gotta sit behind the desk today.
- Oh, yeah.
- Change the whole dynamic.
Well, you just don't wanna piss
him off, that's all I can say.
I'm not gonna piss him off, but,
you know, I need... I need...
to wrest creative control
from him somehow.
He's taking over the
whole goddamn thing.
Did... did you...
- Did you overhear what I...
- Yes, I did.
I hope you'll exercise
some receptionist discretion...
Just gotta keep it down.
Everybody's got
such a big mouth.
Yeah.
Nobody can hear anything
and keep it to themselves.
- Hey!
- Oh, look at you.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you can pull that off.
- You're with this agency?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know
why I bother, though.
Yeah, it's enough
with the acting already.
How long do you have
to do it for?
- Why don't you quit? Huh?
- Nah, I got a few more parts in me, come on.
Every time I turn on the television,
I have to see you.
It's enough. Retire.
Why don't you retire?
- Yeah. Maybe I...
- Huh?
We gonna see you this weekend?
Uh, no, actually,
I... I'm not...
Cheryl and I are
going up to Tahoe.
- Oh, we... we went there once.
- Yeah, I know.
She, uh... she told me.
Something funny
happen in Tahoe?
No. Uh-uh.
- Something weird?
- No. Nope.
- I think something happened in Tahoe.
- Nothing happened in Tahoe.
- What happened in Tahoe?
- Nothing happened in Tahoe, Jeff, okay?
Can you look at me and tell
me nothing happened in Tahoe?
- Nothing happened in Tahoe!
- Something happened in Tahoe!
- Nothing happened!
- Trust me, something happened.
- Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
- Oh! Hey.
- Great to see you.
- Good to see you.
Oh, great to see this.
This is developing.
I like it.
It's working really well.
Keep workshopping. It's great.
- Hey, did you get the tickets for the shucker?
- Oh, I asked.
They weren't...
they weren't able to do it.
- I'm sorry.
- They? Who's they?
Yeah, well, you know, I mean,
if it were for you...
no problem.
You'd go as my guest.
It's my pleasure.
But a shucker you met once
who's good at shucking...
Well, he's not just good at shucking;
he's great at shucking.
Again, for you, no problem.
In a second.
Anytime you wanna go,
please let me know.
Okay. Yeah, okay, I'll go.
I'll... I'll take
the tickets.
- You'll take them?
- Yeah.
- For the same day that the shucker was...
- Now they're for you?
- Yeah.
You'll be there at the show?
Yeah. Yeah.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Are you really sure?
I'm really sure.
- Okay.
- Gentlemen, Aaron just left the office.
You can have it
for your meeting.
- Let's go to work.
- Great.
I gotta get that desk.
So, um,
how do you like LA?
I like it okay.
Getting used to driving.
- Yeah. Oh, d... you drive?
- Yeah.
You... do you have
a car in New York?
No, not in New York,
but I have one here I've been renting.
- It's pretty great.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, I'm getting used
to the traffic.
Yeah. How come you don't
have a car in New York?
Oh, you don't need one
with the subway.
I know. I wish they'd
get some kind of...
You know, I pretty much
take the train...
"Fatwa!"
"...the Musical."
Yeah, have a seat, guys.
I had a couple of
questions about act two
and a couple of ideas that I
think are really gonna help us.
You know, there's always a bit of
a drag in the middle of act two
and I think we can attack that
in a really innovative way.
- Do you have a pad and a pen?
- Yeah, sure.
I'll have, uh, Lucy
get that for you.
Lucy?
Come on, Larry.
Spit that shit out.
What happened in Tahoe?
Listen, you can ask as many
questions as you want.
You are not going to find out
from me what happened in Tahoe.
If you really wanted to
find out, go ask Ted Danson.
Okay? Let me tell you something.
There's just no
discretion anymore.
I had to give that fucking shucker
two tickets to "Hamilton."
Who knows if he's gonna
keep his trap shut?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and by the way,
you were at the table
the other night.
Bridget... you heard that,
what she was going on about.
- That's some good-ass dick stories, man.
- Horrifying.
She could be talking
that way about me.
If you're so goddamn
worried about it,
make her sign an agreement
that she won't fucking talk.
What do you mean,
like a nondisclosure agreement?
Fucking non-disclosure.
Make her sign that shit.
You know, they have it
for housekeepers.
You know, then...
so they can't talk about it.
They should have that for sex.
They should have it for sex,
but they don't have it for sex.
People don't sign
"fuck documents."
If you nervous
about your johnson...
...make her sign
some shit.
- Take it.
- Huh?
I'm done.
- You all right?
- No, I'm not. I'm not all right.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Can we sit down?
- Yeah, yeah. Come in here.
- All right.
Susie sprained my dick.
What?
Wearing that hat has been
nothing but a curse for me.
She took my dick to places
it wasn't meant to go.
So far to the right,
so far to the left.
- Back and forth.
- You need a dick chiropractor.
- Dick chiropractor? There's dick chiropractors?
- Yeah.
- Of course there are.
- Really?
You know how many times
I fucked my dick up?
- Several times.
- Oh, it's just...
it's the worst thing
I've ever experienced.
I'm taking these.
I'm popping these.
This just cuts the pain.
- Do you have any extra?
- Yeah, sure.
- Lin-Manuel landed on my shoulder.
- I remember.
- I'm in terrible pain.
- Yeah, I remember.
- But be careful.
- Thank you.
Those are really strong.
Take them only
if you need them.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay?
Hey! Great news.
I've been so focused on my dick,
I forgot to tell
you the good news.
The good news is
I talked to his agent.
Lin-Manuel Miranda is in.
- Oh! Wow, yeah. Hey. Great.
- Yeah! Yeah!
- Yeah, all right.
- I'm not surprised.
- I told you, I said it was a sure thing.
He's getting everything he wants.
Why shouldn't he be in?
I got Funkhouser invested.
I got Lewis invested.
Of course, I'm still invested.
- Oh, yeah!
- Wow.
- Huh? What do you think?
- Oh, yeah!
- Wow. Fab.
- You like it?
- I gotta check it out in the mirror.
- Check it out.
He looks like a smart sheriff
who's also a doctor.
He'll shoot you, then he'll
stitch your ass up.
Oh, my God!
She took the plant!
- Fuck!
- Mrs. Shapiro took the plant!
- That's fucked up.
- Oh, my God, that is insane!
She didn't put her
old-ass foot on the door,
but that's still
a home invasion.
Yeah. No, I know what it is,
but, I mean, she is...
you know, she's mental.
- She's out of her mind.
- She didn't have to steal.
A home invasion's a fucking
home invasion, you know?
That's a home invasion.
She came in your house
without permission.
You... you better
get rid of the do-rag.
Black man showing up
at her door with a do-rag?
- She'll have a heart attack.
- She'll be fine.
It's in the same family as a scarf,
as a ascot, as a pocket square.
- Same fucking family.
- I don't think
that's in the scarf, ascot,
pocket square family.
The same goddamn family.
Are you kidding me?
I don't like the optics.
She's gonna be fine.
I promise you, man.
Fuck that. Knock on
that shit aggressively.
The hell you give a fuck about...
this some bullshit.
Oh! What are you doing here?
Two of you?
- Hey! My plant.
- Wait... wait a minute.
That's not your plant.
- Yeah.
- That's my plant.
Oh, no, it's not your plant.
You came to my house and
you stole my plant. Come on.
I'm saving this plant.
I'm letting it live
and flourish.
- You were letting it die.
- Oh, come on.
Don't give us that
green thumb shit.
Oh!
See, my dog doesn't
like you at all.
Bella will bite you
on the ankles.
I'll tell you what. We're gonna
take that dog or this plant.
Oh, no, you're
not taking my dog.
- You're not touching my dog.
- What? No, you're not taking the dog.
- Why not?
- You think I want that dog in my house?
- I take the dog...
- What?
- What are you, crazy?
- Why not?
- Who's gonna walk it?
- We'll take turns.
I'm not taking turns.
I'm not walking the dog.
You gonna pick up its shit?
- I'll take care of it.
- You'll take care of it?
Yeah, that's what 8-year-olds
say when they wanna get a dog.
"I'll take care of it."
And they don't do a goddamn thing.
See, you guys can't
even make up your minds
what you're gonna do,
so why don't you just leave?
Wait, who's that?
That's Myron,
my dearly departed husband.
You know what?
Let's take his hat.
No, you're not taking his hat.
No, take the whole goddamn head.
Take the whole fucking head.
- The head? The whole head?
- The whole goddamn head.
- You think I want that head in my house?
- I don't want the fucking hat.
The hat is dumb as hell.
I'm... big shot, I'd rather
have the hat than the head.
I'm not gonna take the head. I don't
want that monstrosity in my house.
He's a lot better
looking than you.
- Oh, is that so?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm an Uber four, okay?
- Well, Myron was an Uber five.
He's not a five.
- Hey.
- Let's get the fuck out of here.
Okay, you know what?
You haven't heard the last
of me about this, all right?
Don't go into people's homes
and steal their plants.
- I'll see you in court.
- The hell you will!
Hello?
- Hi, Larry. It's Lin Miranda.
- Oh, hey.
I'm sure you heard it from...
from Jeff already, but I'm in.
- That's great news.
- I'm clearing my schedule.
It's gonna be you and me
writing this thing toe to tip.
You know what, Lin, I think
we're in pretty good shape.
We don't need to get into
the weeds on this thing.
- The weeds are where the good stuff is.
- Very dangerous in the weeds.
You can get Lyme disease in
there if you're not careful.
There's treasure in the weeds
and we'll pick for ticks after.
The verses are gonna be satanic.
- Okay.
- Well, the other piece of good news
is that my wife, Vanessa,
and her friend
are gonna be at "Hamilton"
the same night as you.
Oh.
So, she'll be sitting right
next to you at the show.
She's going?
Yeah, she's using the other
half of my house seats,
so you'll be right next to her.
And, I mean, she's gonna see
you 'cause you're going.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, if she's going,
she'll see me because I'm going.
Of course. The ticket's for you.
Yes, you got the ticket for me
and... and I will use
the ticket you got for me,
and as a result,
I... I will be there.
I'm really excited
for you guys to meet.
"Fatwa!"
See you in the weeds, buddy.
Ah, Shucker.
No, I'll be right there.
I'll be right there.
Oh, hi.
What's going on here?
Oh, it's just
a little party.
- How come I wasn't invited?
- To the party?
Yeah, why wasn't I invited?
You just had dinner at my house.
I know. That was so nice
and we had a great time.
Okay, so how come
you're not inviting me?
Where's the reciprocity?
Well, I'm gonna reciprocate,
but not this one.
You're gonna reciprocate?
This was the opportunity to reciprocate.
Come to the party! I want you to
come in and really warm it up.
I don't wanna go...
I don't wanna go to the party.
- Now you have to go.
- I wouldn't have come even if I was invited.
- Then what are you doing here?
- What did you tell Ted about Tahoe?
Tahoe?
Because, um, he told me that
you two were going to Tahoe.
- We are going to Tahoe.
- And I said we had been there.
Right.
And he said, "Yeah, I know,"
and he snickered, okay?
Leading me to believe that
you discussed it with him.
No offense to you,
but Ted and I don't
need to sit around
talking about what you
and I did in hotel rooms.
I just don't understand why
you're talking Tahoe to Ted.
- I wasn't talking Tahoe to Ted.
- No, you did talk Tahoe to Ted.
Otherwise there'd be no
reason for Ted to talk Tahoe.
- What did he say?
- He... he said you two were going.
So what?
That is not talking Tahoe.
That is mentioning a trip
that's about to happen.
- Is he here?
- No, he's shooting.
More shooting? Another job?
When's it gonna end?
Who's that?
Is that the Shucker?
Oh, yeah. That's the Shucker
from your party.
Ah, I gotta talk to him.
- Hey, there he is.
- Hey. Yeah.
I just wanna thank you
for those "Hamilton" tickets.
I cannot wait.
Over the moon.
Um, guess what.
I got your hat.
Oh, thank God, because I've
been sick without my hat.
- Where is it?
- Yeah, it's... it's in my car.
So, um, if you can get
a little break,
we can go take a walk,
and I'll give it to you.
Sure, that'd be great.
And, uh, I got another little
thing I wanna talk to you about.
Ted is shooting a limited
series in Vancouver.
I'm borrowing your Shucker
for two minutes.
Ma'am.
There it is.
- Oh, baby.
- Oh, fuck.
Come to Papa.
Oh, I have missed you.
Well, got my hat.
Thanks again for those tickets.
Yeah, that's kind of what
I wanna talk to you about.
Um, Lin called me up,
told me his wife was gonna
be sitting next to me.
He thinks the tickets are for me,
and so I have to go now.
So, I need... sorry to say,
I need the tickets back.
Well, what do you mean? That's... that's
like a... that's like a bad horse trade.
- What are you talking about?
- How are you gonna show up and sit there?
Because if she sees you there,
I am gonna be in a lot of trouble.
- All right.
- Come on.
- All right, I'll get you your tickets.
- Yeah?
For $2,500.
Take it or leave it.
You're quite a prick, aren't you?
It's the Shucker's way.
I don't have that
kind of cash on me.
It's okay,
e take credit cards.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Jarvis isn't living up
to his potential.
What's on?
"Chicago Teachers."
- No!
- Yeah!
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
It's worse than the other
thing we were watching.
They don't try
to curse that much
on that one, though,
so it's okay.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's good.
- What do you wanna do?
- What do I wanna do?
- Mm-hmm.
- You mean right now?
Oh.
I mean, if we could do
anything right now,
what would it be?
Sexually.
- Well...
- Mm-hmm?
- Uh...
- What?
- You know.
- Tell me.
I just like to get an erection,
put it in a vagina.
- That's a...
- That's it?
That's about it, yeah.
That's your biggest fantasy?
I would just get on the top
and thrust until orgasm.
- Hmm.
- I'm sexually a very simple man.
Oh.
Hmm.
But there is something
that can change that.
Oh.
- I got something. I got something...
- There we go.
- Ooh! Oh!
- ...that's pretty interesting.
There you go.
This is a relationship
nondisclosure agreement?
- Yeah.
- Is this a joke?
No, no.
You... this is a
nondisclosure agreement
that you want me to sign?
Yeah, we both...
we both have to sign it.
This is terrible!
This is... what's wrong with you?
It's... it's just a discretion
thing. You know, it's a...
"Partners prohibited from disclosing
the quality of the sexual experience
or the degree of
satisfaction attained"?
- It's fairly boilerplate.
- There is no boilerplate, Larry.
This has never
existed before.
- This is insane.
- I know, it's brilliant.
- It's not brilliant.
- It locks in discretion, it's...
"Partners shall not
divulge any details
including the use of toys,
lotions, ointments..."
What are you talking about?
- Fantastic idea.
- Larry, you are out of your mind.
- No, uh...
- This is horrible.
It'll be great
for our sex life.
- We can... we can go wild.
- No, it won't.
This is a great idea. I...
I wish I thought of it years ago!
I wish my ex-wife had signed one,
I can tell you that!
'Cause I know she's talking,
she's blabbing.
She's telling
Ted Danson everything.
What happened in Tahoe...
she's told him what
happened in Tahoe!
You're presenting me
with a legal document.
It's the least sexy thing
anyone has ever done, ever!
- It's like a prenup!
- Bye.
You're not thinking
this through!
This is a good... good idea!
Bridget! Bridget!
Bridget, if we had this,
it'll take the boredom away!
Sign this and you'll have the
wildest sex you ever imagined!
- No.
- Just sign it!
- Orgasms galore!
That's what
I'm promising you, baby!
Orgasms galore!
You won't regret it!
I'm not signing your dumb
piece of paper, Larry.
Should've known
this was not gonna work out.
Eddie never liked you!
Oh, the... the kid
you pretended has Asperger's?
It is not pretend.
He has Asperger's.
What's your excuse?
You're missing out
on Tahoe Larry!
You are about to enter
the courtroom
of Judge Judith Sheindlin.
This is "Judge Judy."
Larry David
is suing Rose Shapiro
for trespassing at his home
and stealing his ficus plant.
Larry David says
that Mrs. Shapiro
has made him feel unsafe
in his own home.
The defendant is
countersuing Mr. David
for sole custody of the plant
on grounds of plant abuse.
All rise.
Oh, my God.
Your Honor, it's case number 249 on the
calendar in the matter of David vs. Shapiro.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, Judge.
Parties have been sworn in.
You may be seated.
Oh, my fucking God!
- When was that?
- Five years ago.
Subsequently,
several weeks ago,
you, without invitation,
- came into the house.
- Oh...
That's him!
That's the guy. That's the guy
I was telling you about.
This is the guy you had
all those sex stories about?
Yes, that's Larry Long Balls.
Finally, I shoo her away.
She comes back
another time, uninvited,
uses her key,
steals the plant.
Miss Shapiro, I see that
you have some evidence here.
This is the way
the plant looked
when I found it in his house.
- I wanna object. Objection.
- Yeah.
- Total objection to that plant.
- Just a second.
Who are you?
This is Leon Black.
He's... he's my witness.
Does he have any
relevant information
that would help...
that would help your case?
I do. This plant is like a person.
Certain parts of the year,
that plant turns darker, like myself.
When I go to Florida,
I turn a little darker, a shade darker.
Most of the time I carry myself
in a mocha tone,
but there are some... some parts of
the year when I'm more mahogany.
Let's get finished with the
various tones of Mr. Black
and let's move on
to something else.
Your Honor,
is it possible I could pace
while you're asking me
the questions?
Would you put him
in his seat?
- Mrs. Shapiro.
- Yes?
You have another exhibit
underneath that
to show me what the plant
looks like now?
- Yes, I do.
- Anybody want a cough drop?
You want one, Judge?
Judge Sheindlin?
You want a cough drop?
It's so hard to be fair.
Byrd, give her
a cough drop.
So, this is the guy
you're working with?
- Go... shh! Uh!
- Yeah.
You went back to
Mr. David's home...
...and you stole the plant.
I would say rather
than stole, rescued.
Judge, yoo-hoo!
Is this filtered?
I don't know.
What is he asking me?
- If it's filtered, Judge.
- It's...
- Is it filtered?
- Yes, it's filtered.
I'm sorry.
That is not filtered water.
Don't drink it.
Don't drink it. Put it down.
What are you putting unfiltered water...
tap water on the table for?
That's it. That's it.
I'm done.
Mr. David, while I understand
that Mrs. Shapiro
did the wrong thing,
I can only say to you, sir,
that anyone who would
neglect a plant
in that fashion doesn't
deserve to have it.
Your case is dismissed.
We're done. There you go.
- This is... what?
- Good-bye.
Parties are excused.
You may step out.
This is crazy!
I'm... I'm shocked, shocked!
Are we no better than the...
the beasts in the field?
And by beasts, I'm not talking
about the... the chicken.
I'm talking about the oxen
and the... the donkey...
- Oh, un-fucking-believable.
- ...with its slack-jawed stare and...
- What's going on?
- Oh, nothing.
Come on into bed, cowboy.
Yes, ma'am.
Forget it, forget it.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Vanessa.
- Hi, Vanessa.
- So nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Larry David.
- Hi, Larry, yeah.
Hi. I'm bald, I wear glasses,
and... and this is my ticket.
Here to see the show.
I'm very excited.
I'm right here.
I'm sitting right next to you.
- How about that?
- Yeah.
This is my friend,
Joanna, from college.
- Hi.
- Hello, hi.
- Larry.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm not a shucker.
I enjoy clams. I do.
I like oysters,
but I don't shuck.
I know a shucker,
but that doesn't mean
that the shucker's
gonna be here.
I'm here, not the shucker.
Do you like clams
and oysters?
- They're okay.
- Yeah, okay.
Well, but if you eat them,
somebody's gotta shuck them.
Lin is so excited
about "Fatwa!"
- Oh, "Fatwa!" Come on!
- Yeah.
This is gonna be
a big thing, though.
He's so excited.
He can't wait to
just get in there
and start rewriting.
He shouldn't be
getting into there,
he should be getting into you,
and I don't mean that
in a sexual way.
I mean it in terms of time.
Don't... don't get
into the weeds of the show.
Get into your weeds,
again not sexual,
but delve into you, you know.
And again, delve into you...
nonsexual delving
is what I'm saying.
A nonsexual delve.
Ay, gosh.
Shoulder. Killing me.
How'd you hurt your shoulder?
Wrestling with Lin
in his agent's office.
- He threw me to the ground.
- Seriously?
Yeah, yeah.
I've got pain pills.
My friend gave me pain pills.
- Fantastic!
- You want some water?
- Thank you.
- Here you go.
Oh, you can keep it.
♪ How does a bastard,
orphan ♪
♪ Son of a whore
and a Scotsman ♪
♪ Dropped in the middle
of a forgotten... ♪
♪ Spot in the Caribbean
by providence ♪
♪ Impoverished,
in squalor ♪
♪ Grow up to be a hero
and a scholar? ♪
- ♪ So, what happens if we win? ♪
- ♪ I go back to France ♪
♪ I'll bring freedom to my
people if I'm given a chance ♪
- ♪ We'll be with you when you do ♪
- ♪ Go lead your men ♪
♪ I'll see you on the other side... ♪
- ♪ Till we meet again ♪
- ♪ I am not throwing away my shot ♪
- ♪ I am not throwing away my shot... ♪
- Hey!
♪ Hey, yo, I'm just like my country,
I'm young, scrappy, and hungry ♪
♪ And I'm not throwing away my shot ♪
♪ I am not throwing away my shot ♪
♪ Till the world turns upside down ♪
♪ I imagine death so much,
it feels more like a memory ♪
♪ This is where it gets me, on my
feet, the enemy ahead of me ♪
♪ If this is the end of me, at least
I have a friend with me ♪
♪ Weapon in my hand, a command
and my men with me... ♪