Previously on "The Rookie"...
You both will receive
letters of reprimand.
Officer Nolan,
you have to pass
a review board test to advance.
Yes, sir.
Any hopes of making
detective should be abandoned.
What's going on?
Turns out I'm predisposed
to fragile X syndrome.
If my DNA --
Stop.
I'll make an appointment
to see your mom's doctor.
Get your hands off my wife!
Everybody on the ground!
We need a supervisor out here.
Code 3.
You questioned every move I
made. Don't let it happen again.
He's a disgrace to the badge.
He has to go.
So how do I get him?
Chronicle every offense.
When we get enough,
we go to I.A.
Doug Stanton. He was your T.O.
What about him?
Wondering if you liked
the way he does business.
Preserve the evidence.
I'm gonna take our
friend back to the shop.
Doug's about to beat
the crap out of a suspect.
I told you
to guard the drugs.
The last rookie did
everything I told him to.
Guy's name was Owens.
You know him?
I had to write a blue page up
on the kid.
I can personally attest to
Officer West being a solid cop.
It'd be such a waste to have him
wash out of the program.
I still can't believe Doug's
rookie threw you under the bus.
Can we please
not talk about it?
Like, I just want to watch some
trashy TV and shut my brain off.
Mm-hmm.
Food porn...
...house porn or...
...true crime.
True crime, for sure.
Oh. That's weird.
It's Sergeant Grey.
Sir.
Can I come in?
Sure. Yeah.
Officer Chen,
can you give us a minute?
Yes. Of course.
Hey, I'm just gonna fill her in
as soon as you leave, so...
That's your call.
So, uh, what's going on?
So, Officer Stanton
came by my office
at the end of shift
tonight.
He issued you a blue page
for disobeying an order
and leaving evidence
unattended.
He set me up. Look,
I only left that evidence
because I thought he was
gonna hurt our suspect.
Sgt. Grey: Doesn't matter.
You're still his rookie,
and you disobeyed his order.
As long as he's your T.O.,
he has the power to keep
issuing you blue pages
until you're bounced
out of the program.
So I'm pulling the plug,
assigning you
a new training officer.
No. Sir --
It's not
your decision, son.
I'm not gonna see your career
ended before it begins.
Not for the likes
of Doug Stanton.
I don't want a career
if it means making way
for cops like Stanton.
Just give me
one more chance.
I know this guy.
He -- He's a bully.
Like, if I act shook and beg for
forgiveness, he'll believe it.
Please, sir. We cannot
give up on this now.
Do you understand if
you're fired as a rookie,
you're radioactive?
No law-enforcement agency
will touch you.
You will neverbecome
a police officer.
Are you really willing
to risk that?
Without hesitation.
Sorry for the wait.
Do you have
the test results?
Your husband's
not joining us?
Fiancé.
And no. He thinks I'm taking
the test next week.
I don't understand.
I love him,
but he sprung this on me,
and I don't know
what I'll do if it's real.
Well, it's not.
Your amnio came back
negative for fragile X,
as well as all other
major genetic disorders.
So my baby's okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank God.
Tim: He gave Jacksona blue page?
It's not your fault.
Of course it is.
I'm the one that reachedout to Doug's
old rookieto get dirt on him.
What's a blue page?
Who's Doug?
It's a failed evaluation.
None of your business.
Any way I could get
some breakfast?
We arrested you
for stealing bagels.
Yeah, but I didn't
get to eat any.
Can you take her to processing?
Oh. Uh, de-escalate.
We do not want to makethings worse for Jackson.
Hey, Stanton, you ever
want to brush up on any
arrest-control techniques,
I'm available.
Any time.
Yeah? How about now?
Let's go.
We are on duty, so come on.
Aw. That's sweet.
Your hot little boot's
trying to rescue you.
You're the onethat's gonna need rescuing.
Are you threatening me?
Oh, I'm just saying.
I have a great
hair-pull takedown
that I have been
dying to try.
All right. Come on, Boot.
We got a suspect to book.
What a joke.
What happened
to "De-escalate,
we don't want to make things
harder for Jackson"?
I don't know.That was super weird.
I feel like I hada testosterone contact high.
All right. Look. Keep in close
contact with Jackson today.
If they call for backup
of any kind, we're there.
Agreed.
Hey. Hey!
Looking good.
Oh, I hate
dressing for court.
It reminds me of
custody hearings for Lila.
You are studying
down to the wire, I see.
My entire career depends
on how I do on this
disciplinary exam.
So if my locker is cleaned out
by the time you get back,
it's been nice knowing you.
Okay. The only way
that you fail at this
is if you let fear take over.
Anxiety, it --
it lives in your muscles.
So the only way to get rid of it
is to shake it out.
You mean literally shake?
Mm-hmm. It's what I do.
Come on. Try it.
Oh, come on. That's lame.
You want to ace this exam,
you got to shake it out!
Oh. Oh. Okay. So, you know what,
Detective Harper?
See, sometimes this
angelic countenance
betrays how devilishyou truly are.
Oh, that was good. Okay.
I got to go, but listen.
You are gonna kick ass at
this exam, I have no doubt.
Officer West.
Figured you would've
pulled the rip cord,
asked for a new T.O.
No, sir. That's, uh...
That's not what I want.
Really? 'Cause your friends
are sure looking for a fight.
Yeah. Well, I'm not.
Sir,
I've wanted to be a copsince I was a toddler,
and I can't afford
to stumble now.
So from here on out,
I've gotyour six no matter what, sir.
Sgt. Grey: Final question.
Duty Manual Volume One,
Section 210, Point 46,
Paragraph 2 states?
An employee's obligationto report and prevent misconduct
begins the moment that employee
becomes a member
of the Los Angeles
Police Department.
Congratulations,
Officer Nolan.
You passed. 98%.
Really?
Which one did I miss?
That's -- You know what?
Never mind.
That's -- Uh, sorry.
Thank you.
This is a relief
to have this behind me.
It's in your records
forever.
Yes, but certainly this mark
has to help my case.
In becoming a detective.
Your letter of reprimand
has been CC'd
to every lieutenant and captain
in the department.
Trust me.
They have long memories.
So for you to even
be considered for detective,
every one of them
would have to retire,
and most of those guys
are younger than you.
Well, I've beaten
the odds before.
Nolan, um...
you're a good cop with a --
a long...ish career
ahead of you.
But detective is no longer
in your path.
You need to make peace
with that.
Yes, sir.
Oh, one more thing.
Since Harper's in court
this afternoon,
you'll be working
the front desk.
Yes, sir.
Hi. I'm here to check some
evidence out for court.
And I need
to log some in.
Forms?
You're new, right?
Riley started a week ago.
We bonded
while I logged in
about a million
stolen credit cards.
You remember that, Ri?
You're so bad.
She'll get fired if command
catches her fraternizing
with cops.
Yeah, I know, but deep down,
I can tell she likes me.
Isn't that right, Ri?
You're right. It's palpable.
Sign here.
How long till these
lab results come back?
Not my job.
My body is creating life faster
than our lab processes evidence.
Jackson: So, what's
the plan for today?
Premise check some seedy SROs?
Maybe hit up warrant units,
see if they need any
violent felons picked up?
First we need to talk.
Off the record.
You mind?
It's, uh --
It's turned off.
We both know that once
you turn it back on,
the recording automatically
goes back two minutes.
I want this to stay
between us.
Look, I had no choice with
the blue page. You boxed me in.
Look, I know. I-I messed up.
I-I should've come to you.
I would've listened.
I'm sorry.
You know,
I've seen it before.
You think I'm too hard-core
because you're a millennial
full of kid-glove ideals and
everyone deserves a trophy.
But the streets don't work
like that. All right?
And you're too good a cop
to end up a security guard.
That's why I am begging you
for a second shot.
Look, I will be
the best rookie/partner
that you've ever had.
Please.
To a fresh start.
Fresh start.
Thank you, sir.
All right.
Stella: Excuse me.
Uh, can you help me?
Someone stole my bike.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's get you started.
Fill out one of these and
bring it right back to me.
Thanks.
You're being released
on an 849"b",
which means
we're not charging you.
Does this mean I get
the bagels back?
No. The bagels
were disposed of.
Do you know how bad that is
for the environment?
I'm a freegan. That goes
against my whole ethos.
Real freegans forage for food
in the Dumpster.
They don't steal
from bakeries.
Dumpsters are gross.
Look, could you at least call me
a cab? I don't believe in money.
No. Sorry.
It's against our ethos.
How was your exam?
Uh, passed.
Oh. Well....
don't sound so excited.
Oh. No.
It's just, um...
Grey confirmed
I'd never make detective.
You mean you still
thought you had a shot?
In my heart,
I just -- I hoped.
Hey! Some chick's trying to
steal a car in your parking lot!
Yes.
You're under arrest -- again.
Freegan rights.
Step over here.
Hands behind your back.
Stay there.
At least your mug shot
and your prints are still good.
Excuse me! Officer?
Nolan:
I'll take care of this.
Sorry.
Employee parking only.
You want public parking,
it's back --
Don't speak.
Do exactly as I say.
Right hand up. Left hand
takes out your radio.
Put it on the seat.
Hey. Eyes on me.
Radio. Now. Let's go.
Now both hands
unhook your belt.
Put it on the ground.
Your backup piece next.
Come on. I know you got one.
Climb in
and shut the door.
Into the back.
And don't even think about
trying to charge me,
Officer...
Nolan.
Let's go.
Is that a --
Big-ass bomb? Oh, yeah.
I set that baby off, everybody
in a two-block radius is dead.
You see those handcuffs on
the side wall? Put them on.
Tight. Let's go.
Tighter than that, man.
You know what this is?
That's a dead man's switch.
That's right.
Anything doesn't go my way,
I release this, we go boom.
You try and be a hero,
I release this, and we go boom.
Nolan, you so much as look at me
funny, I release this --
And we go boom. I get it.
You're not gonna get
any trouble from me.
I want to make it through this,
and I hope you do, too.
I'm imagining you have some
pretty powerful motivations
for doing this?
Shut up, man. You and I
are not gonna be friends.
Get your supervisor
on a private channel.
Sgt. Grey: So, Nolan
aced the test.
I knew he would.
Sergeant Grey,
this is Officer Nolan.
Go to channel 9.
Why is your rookie radioing me
from the front desk?
Nolan, this better
be important.
It sure is, buddy.
Who's this?
The guy
in your parking lot
with an ammonium nitrate
fertilizer bomb
powerful enough
to turn your station
and the surrounding
neighborhood into a crater.
If you think I'm lying,
you can ask Officer Nolan here.
I'm afraid
I can confirm that, sir.
Graham: Now, I know your first
instinct is going to be to
evacuate the building,
but that is not gonna happen.
I have cameras on every exit.
Do you understand me?
If anyone leaves, everyone dies.
I can confirm
the cameras, sir.
Secure all exits now.
Graham: Then your next instinct
will be to try
and neutralize me.
But tell him why that would be
a mistake, Officer Nolan.
Our bomber has
a dead man's switch, sir.
Okay. You have my attention.
Tell me what I can do for you.
Rectify an extreme  miscarriage of justice.
I demand the immediate release
of Donald Feltt
from the Primedale
Department of Corrections.
Hold on.
So, are we talking about
Donald Feltt who's serving
a life sentence for murder
and drug trafficking?
That's him.
And there's  not gonna be a backdoor  parole for my boy.
Feltt walks
out of there today.
Backdoor parole?
Jailhouse slang for
when you die in prison.
Our bomber's done time.
Most likely with Feltt.
All right. That's a big ask.
It'll take time.
Well, then get started.
We need someone on the outside
to go to Primedale.
I'll call Lopez.
She left already.
So, all units,
be advised we are going into
tactical alert
at Mid-Wilshire Station.
All civilians
and non-essential personnel
report to Level D
of the underground garage.
Level D? That's where
the station sheltered in place
during the missile alert.
What the hell is going on?
Uh, listen up. I need everyone
to get up and come with me.
Why? What's going on?
I'm sorry, ma'am. Someone will
explain everything shortly.
Right now I need you
to follow me.
Letting me go again?
This station's awesome!
We're going down to the bottom
of the parking garage.
Safety drill.
Yeah. I don't want to do that.
Tough.
Listen up.
We are in lockdown.
Head to the underground garage,
bottom level.
This is not a drill.
We can't.
Evidence-room employees
aren't allowed to interact
with police personnel.
Well, then, stand in a corner
and don't talk to anyone,
but you can't stay here.
You okay?
I'm fine.
You're really putting a lot on
the line for this Feltt guy.
He must be pretty important
to you.
Why do you say
he was wrongly accused?
I told you. You and I
are not gonna be friends.
I'm just trying to
make the best of this.
Well, stop.
That a chemo port
on your chest there?
My aunt had one.
Colon cancer.
Pancreatic.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Means I got
nothing left to lose.
So, what, you're dying,
and you want your last act
to be murdering hundreds
of innocent people?
Well, they only die
if your sergeant
doesn't hold up
his end of the deal.
See, it's a matter
of perspective.
Then help me
see your side.
I told you. You and I are
not gonna be friends,
so shut the hell up.
I'm sorry. I cannot be in here.
I get claustrophobic!
I understand, but this is
the safest place for you to be.
Yeah, until the bomb goes off
and the whole structure
collapses on us.
Hey. Okay.
That is not gonna happen.
This place was designed to be
a bomb and earthquake shelter.
Okay?
Just take a breath.
Ugh.
Of this stale-ass air?
Do you have any idea
the long-term health effects
of breathing
carbon monoxide?
No, but I bet it's
a hell of a lot better
than getting blown up.
And where are yougoing?
Back to work.
While we're stuck
in the station,
Jackson is out there with Doug
with no backup.
Did something happen?
Well, not yet.
I mean, Jackson feels like
he sold his apology to Doug,
but I don't trust it.
I don't, either. Tell Jackson
to keep his head down today
since we can't be there
for him.
We're gonna stay right here.
Big Mike.
What do you got?
Hostage barricade
with a mobile WMD.
Who's the hostage?
The trouble magnet.
That old rookie.
Nolan?
That's the one.
This is my boot, Jackson West.
He's interested in SWAT.
Well, if there's still
a Mid-Wilshire tomorrow,
hit me up.
Any friend of Dougie's.
Snipers, spotters.
You got your assignments.
Let's move out.
Let's go.
What should we do?
Support SWAT?
Negative.
We're the only patrol unit
left outside the building.
Now every thug, lowlife,
and banger in the city's
gonna know we're
vulnerable right now.
We got to
get back out there,
show them you can't mess
with the LAPD.
Hey!
Hey. Hey! Wake up!
Hey! Hey! Geez.
Wake up!
Wake up! Hey! Don't let go!
Wake up! Wake up!
Come on! Don't let go!
Wake up! Get up!
What happened?
Keep a grip on it.
Tighten your grip.
Tighten your grip!
Tighten it!
I got it. I got it! I got it!
Yeah. You passed out.
I've got it!
You passed out!
You almost killed everyone.
My blood pressure must've
bottomed out.
It happens sometimes.
Well, given that fun fact,
how about we disconnect
the dead man's switch?
It's not happening.
I'm fine.
Sergeant? You seeing this?
Van, rear window.
Got it.
Is that...
Morse code.
I'll look up
a dictionary.
Hold on.
S-C-R-L-I.
S-C-R -- is that "scar"?
Left eye.
Suspect has a scar
on his left eye.
Good man, Nolan.
Okay. So if we assume
our bomber
did time at Primedale
with Feltt,
we know that he's a white male
with a scar on his left eye...
Graham Porter.
Uh, he did three years
at Primedale,
and before that
a string of misdemeanors.
But nothing that screams out
"mad bomber."
How does a guy like this hook up
with a lifer like Feltt?
Let's hope Lopez can find out.
Donald Feltt came to us
nine years ago
for a murder that would have
made Dahmer blush.
Any friends?
Known associates?
Inmates like Feltt
don't have friends.
What about Graham Porter?
A former inmate of yours.
Doesn't ring a bell.
Huh.
What?
Well, he was in our level one
minimum-security unit.
Those inmates never cross paths
with guys in the SHU.
Then why is Graham risking
his life to save Feltt?
Unless...
Unless what?
This isn't about Feltt at all.
I need to know what happened to
Graham after he left prison.
You have been glued
to your phone.
Who you texting?
None of your business.
Someone you care about?
Someone you're
saying goodbye to?
You know,
everyone in that station
has someone they care about,
someone who loves them,
someone who's worried they won't
ever see them alive again.
Yeah. Well, we all got to die
someday, don't we, Officer?
Today's as good a day
as any other.
Time for a shot
across the bow.
Control, 7-Adam-07.
Show us on West Adams and 14th.
Code 6.
What are we
doing here?
Sending a message.
We want them to let all their
little homies know that
even though we're wounded,
we're not down.
But they don't
look like much to me.
Well, looks
can be deceiving.
Especially on a day like
this, we can't show
any signs of weakness.
Got to hit the bully
before they hit you.
Hey!
Fingers on the fender, boys.
Why?
We're not doing anything wrong.
Can't work on cars in
the street, ese.
Fingers on the hood.
We're not doing repairs, ese.
I'm just showing them
the engine.
Hands on the hood now.
Screw that.
You got no cause.
What are you,
some kind of lawyer?
Pre-law at SMC, actually.
Are you threatening me?
You know what happens when you
threaten a badge?
Doug.
Officer West, I thought you had
my six.
I do.
Then watch those two
while I deal with
Mr. Lawyer here.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop, stop.
Look, you three, back in your
car, have a nice day.
Sorry for the trouble.
You're done, Boot -- what you
just did is a fireable offense.
I'm going straight
to the city manager.
I don't care if your daddy
works for I.A.
He's not gonna be able
to save you now.
You know what, dumbass?
My daddy,
he doesn't work for I.A.
He runs it.
So if you're coming for my job,
he'll come for yours.
You know, I-I'm done tiptoeing
around your racist ass.
You're a dead man walking.
7-Adam-07. Status check.
Are you Code 4 on your stop?
Yeah.
All good.
How long did Graham Porterlive in your halfway house?
Almost three months.
Is he in trouble?
You could say that.
Doesn't surprise me.
Graham's the unluckiest man
alive.
Gets out of prison determined
to get his life on track.
Finds a job, falls in love,
then he gets hit with
Stage 4 cancer.
That's rough.
He has no money
for doctors, no insurance.
He started one of those
YouFundMe things,
but it barely covered
his first round of chemo.
Last I heard, he was in danger
of ending up on the street.
So, Graham Porter is in
desperate need of money.
So why not demand a ransom?
Why give us the head fake
on Feltt?
Well, maybe it's not
a head fake.
Maybe Feltt's paying Graham
to bust him out of prison.
No, Feltt's a murderer,
not a narco
with unlimited cash flow --
if this Feltt gambit is smoke,
we're chasing our tails trying
to free him.
Meanwhile, an accomplice robs
a bank or something.
Hollywood division did evacuate
the area around the station.
It's standard procedure,
and Graham would know that.
Bradford, Chen, make a list of
every high-value target
around here -- cash businesses,
high-end shopping...
There's a check-cashing place
two blocks south of here.
Contact Stanton and West.
Have them check it out.
I'm gonna call the chief, see if
we can get some extra units
around here to help out.
Doug: Look, I know we both
got heated back there,
said things
we didn't mean --
I meant what I said.
Listen, I got a wife,
two kids.
Everybody
you jacked up for no reason
has a family --
it didn't stop you.
The storefront looks empty,
but I'll check the doors.
Jackson says everything is
Code 4
at the check-cashing place,
there's no sign of trouble.
Not at any of the other
high-value targets, either.
Maybe we're going down
the wrong path.
Maybe this is not
about money at all.
What the hell is it about?
Uh, we did some digging
into Graham.
His YouFundMe was set up by
his girlfriend, Kelsey Adams.
Have Lopez run her down.
We did,
but there's no one home
at her apartment.
But there's something weird.
This whole thing is weird.
Kelsey is using
an assumed identity.
We ran her through the system.
Social Security number's a fake.
We can't find
a driver's license for her.
So we don't have a picture.
No, sir.
But according to Lopez,
Kelsey and Graham
have been inseparable
since they first met.
So it's likely she's involved
in this somehow.
Yeah, but how if it's
not about money or Feltt?
What if this is all
a distraction meant to pull
our focus outside the station,
when we should be focused
inside?
What kind of woman would be
crazy enough to be in a building
with her boyfriend
parked outside in a truck
full of explosives?
The kind that would get herself
arrested twice in one hour.
Freegan Frida.
Hey, what's going on?
We're just trapped in here.
Is it over yet?
Uh, not yet.
Tim: Chen.
Dude, please tell me you brought
snacks. I'm starving.
It's over, Kelsey.
Who's Kelsey?
You got yourself arrested
this morning,
but we let you go
too quickly.
That's why you had to break that
window to get yourself back in.
So you'd be in the station when
Graham made his demands.
Only we put you down here,
and you can't get
back in the station
without a key card.
The only question
left is why?
What's so important
in the station?
Dude, I have no idea what
you're talking about.
But I'm super intrigued.
Kelsey Adams!
Tim: Stop her!
She must've broken it.
Nolan: Come on.
Who have you been texting?
I mean, clearly, it's your
accomplice, but has to be
someone important to you for you
to risk your life like this.
Can't be a friend. No.
This scheme
is too dangerous.
Slim chance of escape.
Maybe family?
A brother perhaps?
Sister?
How about a girlfriend?
I don't know what you're
talking about, all right?
Girlfriend it is.
Okay.
I understand the hesitation --
you don't want her ID'd.
That's a good thing,
actually.
It means you think you'll
get away with this.
No, I don't.
But you think she will.
Sergeant, this is Harper --
Evidence room door
has been breached,
I'm starting a search.
Don't move.
Please, I have to find it!
Find what?!
He thinks I'm dead.
If they run my prints...
Are you trying to
destroy evidence
from a crime you committed?
No!
If he finds me,
he will kill me.
Who?
My husband.
He's a loan shark in El Paso.
He beat me up
on the regular.
So I ran away
three years ago.
I paid for a new identity --
birth certificate, the works --
just so he would
never find me.
But last week, there was
a robbery in the restaurant
where I work.
The cops took a bunch of
stuff into evidence,
things that I had touched.
And when they pull the prints,
they will get a hit
on the real you.
And he'll find me,
and he will kill me.
Why go through all this?
Why not just call the cops?
He's got cops
on his payroll.
They reported
me missing.
The minute my prints show up
in the system, they'll know,
and they'll tell him
where to find me.
Please...
do not let him find me.
All right.
I will try and help you.
But right now, you have
got to do the right thing,
and you have to tell
Graham to stand down.
Graham Porter.
You there?
How do you know my name?
I know everything.
I know this whole thing's about
trying to protect Kelsey.
She's here in custody.
Release her.
Do it now.
I can't do that,
but I'll make you a deal.
No!
You set her free
right now,
or I blow this bomb
and we all die.
Graham, she told us the truth.
The bomb is a fake.
It's over.
You're under arrest.
No.
No, I'm not.
Guys, get locked in.
We're going in five.
Tell your SWAT to back off
or I shoot your officer.
Do it now!
Sgt. Grey:
Okay, okay, just hold on.
Graham,
this has to stop.
You can barely stand.
I can still
pull a trigger.
You're not gonna shoot me.
You think I care about
going back to prison?
At least there my chemo
would be paid for,
instead of being left to
rot from the inside out.
That may be true,
but you wouldn't just be
condemning yourself to prison.
You'd be condemning
Kelsey, too.
If you kill me, she becomes
an accomplice to murder.
That's a life sentence.
For you, that might
not be very long.
But for Kelsey...
I just wanted to do
something good
before I died,
that's it.
She deserves
to be happy.
I know.
Right.
So, help her.
You -- Promise to
talk to the DA,
pull some strings,
something.
Graham, if I promised
you that, I'd be lying.
I don't have
any power.
I'm just a rookie.
No one's gonna listen to me.
Her fate's in
your hands now.
I -- I c--
Sergeant Grey,
this is Officer Nolan.
One in custody.
We're Code 4.
Units -- information only.
The hostage barricade
at Mid-Wilshire is Code 4.
Processing is open.
No injuries.
Complete Code 4.
You know, back in the day,
when something good like this
would happen, we used to
do mic clicks.
Three of 'em.
Go ahead.
Woman: Hey, attaboy!
It'd be nice to be applauded for
something other than
almost dying.
How are you feeling?
Uh, a little wobbly, sir,
but ready to hit the streets.
I appreciate your eagerness,
but you are end-of-shift.
As for everyone else,
back to work, people.
We're Code 4.
Pending calls are piled up.
Oh, and, Nolan...
good assist on the Morse code.
Oh. Eight years of Boy Scouts
finally paid off.
Dot-dot-dot-dash.
Morse code joke.
It's "V" for "victory."
It's -- It's...
So, I just got a text
from Jackson.
It looks like things
came to a head with Doug.
He pulled the dad card
and got him to back off.
Damn it.
We got to get out there.
Guys like Doug don't like being
backed into a corner.
Come on.
Could they have been
more obvious?
But I don't want you
and the PC police to accuse me
of profiling.
No, they were
suspicious as hell.
Missing plate means
the vehicle is likely stolen.
Let's take a look.
Dispatch, 7-Adam-07.
Show us Code 6
at the Manor Apartments.
Premise check.
Manor Apartments.
That's 6H -- why aren't
they calling for backup?
They think they
have it covered?
No, you don't step foot in that
place without hats and bats.
Jackson: 7-Adam-07.
We're 10-97 on the 11-54
at the Manor Apartments.
Five-oh!
They know we're here.
It's the five-oh!
We should call for more units.
Not yet.
Come in too strong, the whole
place will turn on us.
I got this way.
Okay.
Boot, you see anything,
call me.
Control, 7-Adam-07, A to B.
I'm out with three.
Copy. Right behind you.
Y'all live here?
All right, do me a favor,gentlemen,
keep your hands where I can see them.
Hey, stop where you are -- look,
you guys do not want to do this.
Look, stop where you are! Hey!
Aah!
Take this!
That's their shop.
Where do you think they are?
Someplace they shouldn't be.
7-Adam-07, what's your 20?
Control, 7-Adam-19.
Requesting additional units,
Manor Apartments, Code 3.
I lost Jackson.
We got separated.
He's still breathing.
7-Adam-19, we need an ambulance
to our location.
Officer down, 24-year-old male,
full body trauma.
Hey, partner, what happened?
What happened, partner?
Who did this to you?
What?
Camera.
I've seen enough.
On me.
...see what happened?
Oh, we got separated.
Okay.
Officer
Doug Stanton...
Got it.
Hold on. Hold on.
I want to see this.
I am hereby placing you under
administrative leave
effective immediately --
gun and badge.
Back off.
Give me a reason.
You will not
leave town.
You will not act as a police
officer in any capacity,
including court.
You will make yourself available
to the Chief of Police
within 30 minutes notice.
Pending review, you will be
brought up before
a board of rights.
This isn't over.
No.
But you are.
Hey, you heading
over to see Jackson?
Yeah.
Yeah. Me, too.
You okay?
Yeah.
Don't lie to your T.O.
I know what you went through
today was scary.
If you need any help,
don't be afraid to ask.
I won't, I promise,
but today actually
gave me a lot of
perspective.
Well, almost dying
will do that.
Right? I've actually been so
wrapped up in getting ahead,
promotions, making detective,
I think I lost sight as to
why I became a cop
in the first place.
To help people.
Well, you definitely
did that today.
Thank you, but maybe I can
help more from in here.
Guys like Doug Stanton
should not be training
our next generation of cops,
so maybe I should stop
thinking about catching bad guys
and start focusing on
training good ones,
the way you do.
Well, you know, if you had your
college degree, technically,
you would be able to be
T.O. in two years.
Without one,
you'd have to wait four.
Looks like I'm
going back to school.
Hey, Sarge.
You, uh,
just missed my parents.
Uh, yeah, yeah, I just
saw them in the hallway.
They said you're
gonna be okay.
Yeah -- cracked rib,
couple loose teeth.
CT was clean.
Who knew that
getting my ass kicked
would get this thing done?
You could've died.
Yeah, well,
it was worth it
to get the needle moving
in the right direction.
You shouldn't have to risk your
life to get a bad cop fired.
Hey, don't do that.
Look, if you cry,
then I'm gonna cry, and --
and I'll straight up
pop a stitch.
Ain't nobody crying.
And you better not tell
Officer Chen
that I got all
misty-eyed, either.
I'll, uh, keep that
between you and me, sir.
I appreciate that,
but here's something
you can tell everyone --
the honor and bravery
you've shown...
is an example
to all of us.
And I'm so damn
proud of you.
Thank you
so much, sir.
No, thank you, son...
for reminding me
what this job should be.
Look, you, uh --
you get some rest, okay?
Um...we still got
a lot of work ahead of us.
Yeah.
Hey, I, uh...
get to take tomorrow off,
though, right?
Yeah, if you're trying
to be a slacker.
Ow. Ow...
Uh, you just --
just get some rest.
Damn it!
.>.