Previously on "The Rookie"...Thanks again
for helping me with
the transitional housing
paperwork.
- What are you on?
- It's just a little Oxy.
You get my report
on Mack Daniels?
Are you sure this is the way
you want things to go?
He'll get fired.
Do you know why
they call me "La Fiera"?
You were caught in a narco
gunfight with baby Diego,
grabbed a gun and laid
everyone to waste.
When it comes to your child,
there is nothing you won't do
to protect them.
Feeling okay?
What happened?
My son was born with
Tetralogy of Fallot.
He collapsed 13 minutes ago.
He had five surgeries on his
heart before his first birthday.
Well, that's a severe case
of TOF.
Has he been short of breath
recently?
Nothing I noticed. Eh, Abigail?
He didn't mention anything.
He would have mentioned it,
right?
What -- What's happening to him?
Well, the surgeries
he had as a baby
helped to improve
the blood flow to his lungs,
but as a patient gets older,
those procedures can cause
the valve between the heart
and the lungs to leak.
It's called --
Pulmonary valve regurgitation.
When your baby's sick,
you become an expert.
What's going on?
Henry, we're at the hospital.
You -- You fainted at home
and again in the car ride over.
You're gonna be okay, kiddo.
Doctor's gonna
take great care of you.
That's right. My name is Maggie,
and we're gonna start with
a full battery of tests.
Dad? Yeah?
You haven't called me kiddo
since I was little.
♪ What if what we do
does not define us? ♪
♪ Define us
--Captions by VITAC--
Look, being in a hospital
in uniform is like asking
every rando to make
their problems yours.
We'll be in and out.
I just want to make sure
he's okay.
Brought you breakfast.
Oh. Thank you.
Um, not much
of an appetite right now,
but I'll hang onto that.
How's Henry?
Uh, just waiting on some,
uh, final test results.
Excuse me.
- Morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Can I get a minute
with Officer Nolan?
Of course, sir.
Text me if you need anything.
Right. Thank you.
Sir, I realize as a rookie,
I don't get vacation days --
Stop. Family trumps everything.
You're exactly where
you're supposed to be.
I squared it with the captain.
You're fine, so... sit down.
How's that new
garage conversion coming?
John, we don't need
to do small talk.
We can just sit here.
Thank you.
X-ray tech to Radiology.
That's crap.
I gave you a deposit.
I expect it back.
I just lost the venue for
Lopez's bachelorette party.
Where'd you have yours?
I eloped so I wouldn't
have to have one.
Well, if you were planning one
for a friend?
I try and stay out of
no-win situations like those.
- Cuts down on the drama.
- Great.
Concealed weapons, 12 o'clock.
What'd I tell you?
We haven't even been here
five minutes --
we're already getting pulled
into trouble.
Gentlemen, you know the drill.
Concealed carry permits, please.
Ah, ah, ah, slowly.
So, what?
They're recruiting cops
from the modeling schools now?
I can't tell
which one of you's prettier.
Clearly me. Who's your client?
Sorry. Not at liberty to say.
- We signed a non-disclosure.
- Yeah.
That's not really
how this works.
- It's La Fiera.
- Great.
Now we're gonna be here all day.
Are we cool?
Yeah.
What do you think
she's doing here?
Nothing good.
Please stop.
I don't want to know the gender
until the baby's born.
I spend my days trying to
figure things out.
I just want one mystery
in my life
that I'm not trying to solve.
Okay, but we can still have
a list of names on deck, right?
Fine.
But for every WASPy name
you pick,
I'm gonna pick something
so Mexican,
you'll never be able
to spell it.
Okay.
Uh, if it's a boy, Thatcher.
I'll raise your Thatcher
to a Cuauhtémoc.
And if it's a girl, Xochitl.
And we're not picking a name
until B-day.
Doing it now could jinx us.
I had no idea you were
this superstitious.
I'm not.
I just wear a talisman
a drug lord gave me
to keep evil spirits away
from my unborn child.
Better safe than sorry.
♪ Oh, ah
Ah. Hey, Sarge, what's up?
La Fiera's back in town.
Harper and Tim just spotted her
at Shaw Memorial.
I'm at Shaw Memorial.
What floor?
Eight. They have eyes on her.
Can you reassign them to me,
sir?
Until I figure out
what's going on?
Sure. I'll notify the on-call
watch commander.
Thanks.
I gotta step out
for a quick sec.
What? No, no. W-We're up next.
I'll be right back, I promise.
♪ Whoo!
Ms. Lopez? We're ready for you.
Control, show us Code 6
at Shaw Memorial.
Suspect needs medical attention
before transport to booking.
Copy that.
- We were pulling you over
for a rolling stop.
I still don't get
why you sped up.
It was involuntary.
When I get anxious,
my body always chooses flight.
And if you wouldn't have run,
we just would've
given you a ticket.
But now we gotta book you
for evading police
- and a hit-and-run.
- Damn my DNA.
Morning.
Who have you brought me today?
This is Billie Park.
She decided to start off our day
destroying city property.
I cut my arm.
Let's take a look. Could you...
Yeah.
♪ If it's a good time you want,
you know I got it ♪
♪ I got it
♪ 100-dollar bills keep
spilling out of my wallet ♪
Ooh. Yeah. Right over here.
♪ Like MJ, like game six,
I'm fresh to death ♪
Yeah, you're gonna need
stitches.
Better give me a few.
Alright.♪ Whoo!
Well, I'm gonna head
to the cafeteria.
- I didn't get any breakfast.
- What? You?
You never miss a meal.
Eh -- Are you calling me fat?
Yeah. That's what I'm doing.
Yeah, well, your girl
raided the kitchen
before she left for school,
and there was literally
nothing left.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I know that I kind of...
foisted Tamara onto you.
Look, you know that I respect
that she needs help,
but any idea how long
she's gonna be
camped out on our couch?
Not long. I hope.
I've been having a hard time
getting in touch
with the local
housing assistance program.
They give grants to teens
who age out of foster care,
you know, help them get into
transitional apartments,
but every time I call
to check on the status
of her application,
they have these
crazy-long hold times.
Well, I mean, we are gonna
be here for a minute, so...
Good point.
Thank you for calling Angels
West Extended Care Program.
There are... three --
callers ahead of you.
Only three?
Ooh! This is my lucky day.
Hey.  Our lucky day. Yeah.
I thought it was nothing.
I've been tired,
but we've been really busy with,
uh, my new job.
Everything's just
been fine for so long.
I guess I just stopped
thinking about it.
I don't buy it.
Mom.
I think this is
some kind of elaborate plan
to reunite me and your father,
"Parent Trap" -style.
God, no.
You guys are
so much happier apart.
Fair enough. Hi.
Hi. The day we dreaded.
Such a drama queen.
Okay. It's gonna be okay.
Are you in pain?
No, I just can't
catch my breath.
Results are in.
It's the pulmonary valve,
isn't it?
Yes, the valve is failing.
He'll need surgery to repair it.
Is it dangerous?
It can be. You have a choice.
We can do a minimally invasive
procedure
known as a percutaneous
pulmonary valve replacement
that's relatively safe.
Recovery time is about a week,
but the fix won't last.
You'll need to have open heart
surgery in about five years.
Or they could do the open heart
surgery right now, right?
Yes. He'll need to have
a live tissue valve replacement
that could last decades.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Sign me up for not wanting
to go through this again
anytime soon.
N-Not so fast.
We're talking about
a much riskier surgery, right?
Yes.
Henry could have a heart attack
on the operating table.
He could bleed into
his chest cavity
or have other complications
after we close him up.
But his age --
mortality rate for a procedure
like this is, what, 2%, 3%?
No, because of factors
related to his prior surgeries,
the risk of mortality is higher,
about 20%.
Okay. That's a lot to process.
Well, you'll need to
make a decision quickly.
Your heart is very unstable
right now.
- Nice meeting you.
- You, too.
Thanks for taking care of him.
Mm-hmm.
Obviously, you're having
the procedure
that doesn't have a 20% chance
of killing you.
I-I think we take the safer bet
and call it a day.
What if that's not what I want?
It's my choice.
- I'm an adult.
- Henry --
Okay, we don't have to decide
this instant.
I mean, let's just take
a breath, take a minute,
uh, walk through it,
and go over your options.
Sandra.
Look at you.
Motherhood suits you.
Didn't think you'd risk your
son's life coming back to L.A.
Actually, I'm here
to save my son.
Well, his knee, anyways.
Diego, what happened?
It was so cool.
I was playing fútbol
and went full Carlos Vela,
and pop --
partial tear of my ACL,
but I got the goal.
He's having surgery today --
top sports doctor in the world.
And that's the only reason
you're here in L.A.?
Of course.
- It was good to see you.
- You, too.
Good luck with the surgery.
Uh...
So, what are you really
doing here?
Hermana, don't be so suspicious.
Surely, you have better things
to worry about.
You're here for the baby, no?
I was, until I got a call
about you,
and now my fiancé
is cursing us both.
How is Wesley?
He must be so excited.
Relax.
I learned his name
when I was dropping off
the present for your baby.
And I see you're wearing
the ribbon.
I really hope you're only here
for your son.
'Cause if you're
up to something,
it's not gonna end well.
For you or Diego.
Oh, that's what you're having
for breakfast?
Hey, this happens to have 8%
of the recommended daily
allowance of riboflavin.
She's all yours.
Thank you.
Control, suspect is
medically cleared.
We are en route
-to lower booking.
Copy.
Angels West. How can I help you?
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
- Oh, she's running again.
- Oh, damn it!
Oh! Sorry!
10-15 is running.
Foot pursuit at Shaw Memorial.
♪ Free ppls livin' any place
I know of ♪
♪ Free ppls in another location
but the ♪
♪ Free ppls hate the ppl
who want to become ♪
♪ Free
Turn around. Put your hands up.
Something's wrong.
Mnh.
Yeah. No more running.
What happened?
You had severe abdominal pain
and passed out.
Doctor ordered a CT scan
and an X-ray.
- Uh, no, I don't want that.
- I bet,
'cause you've got a stomach full
of drug balloons.
No, I don't.
Okay. Billie, we are trained
police officers.
You had a ticket to Ibiza
in your pocket.
You ran from the cops,
and now you appear to have
serious intestinal issues.
We're gonna have proof soon,
so just tell us what kind
of drugs they are.
Can't you just leave me alone?
Please? No.
And right now,
getting busted for drugs
is the least of your problems.
The real concern is
if one of those drug balloons
in your stomach bursts.
Look, if it's filled with
cocaine or meth,
your heart rate will
rapidly accelerate
until full cardiac arrest,
and then muscles in your chest
will tear apart
as you slowly suffocate.
Yeah, and if it's heroin,
fentanyl, or an opioid,
you'll ride high for a while,
then you'll crash.
You'll lose all your
motor functions, and you will --
well, you'll vomit
until you're dead.
Well, then we're fine.
It was just Molly.
Those are happy pills.
Yeah.
How much?
Uh... four condoms.
Like... 80 pills each?
- Okay.
- I'll tell the doctor.
Control, notify
on-call narcotics.
We have a kilo-plus mule
in custody.
What's wrong?
Look, if even one of
those packets burst,
you'll start to hallucinate.
Your body temperature will rise
to 105 degrees,
and you'll die from
a heat stroke
during the worst nightmare
of your life.
There you are.
Sorry. It was a work emergency.
Is that true?
I want no part of this.
I had to beg to get
our appointment rescheduled.
The OB will see us
in 15 minutes.
You're the best.
- Thank you.
- Yes!
My buddy came through.
We're having
your bachelorette party
at his sports bar on Sunset.
Uh, I'm -- That's -- I'm joking.
That's not -- I would never.
I got surveillance footage
of La Fiera from security.
After you left her,
she snuck over to the ICU.
- That's Mack.
- Who?
Uh, Mack Daniels.
Uh, he worked undercover
until I got him suspended
for drug use on the job.
He's facing criminal charges.
And here he is,
talking to a major narco.
That can't be a coincidence.
Let's go ask him.
Can you reschedule our
appointment for a little later?
Thank you. I love you.
Oh, damn it.
Mack. What are you doing here?
Working. Private security.
- For Sandra de la Cruz?
- No.
So, who's your client?
- I don't know.
- Really?
That's how you want to
play this?
When you're clearly 5-50?
Come on, Mack.
You don't need any more
trouble right now.
I'm working for Tomás Madrigal.
You do know who that is, right?
The largest drug kingpin
in Southern California.
He is subject in multiple
ongoing investigations.
Yeah, he's dying of cancer.
He only has a few days
left on Earth,
and I lost my ability
to be picky
when my buddy Bradford here
snitched me out.
I lost my paycheck
and my pension.
I'm up to my eyeballs
in lawyer bills,
not to mention the alimony
and child support
I'm gonna owe
once Beth divorces me.
So, your solution is to go
work for the enemy?
I'm not breaking any laws.
I'm just standing watch,
making sure that nobody
interrupts an old man's
final moments.
Not even La Fiera?
We saw Sandra de la Cruz
come by.
- What was she doing here?
- Paying her respects.
The old man was sleeping.
She said she'd stop by later.
Mack, is there a problem?
No. No problem, Mr. Madrigal.
I'm just, uh, catching up with
some former colleagues.
Do it on your own time.
We're paying you to keep your
mouth shut and watch the door.
No, your old man's paying me.
And I'm gone the second he is.
Oh, that reminds me.
He, uh...
He was asking for you earlier.
Why didn't you call me?
- X-ray tech to Radiology.
- Whoops.
X-ray tech to Radiology.
Mack.
You sure pissing off the next
El Jefe is a smart move?
He's a punk wannabe.
That kid'll drive the whole
operation into the ground
within six months.
Now, if you don't mind, I, uh...
I gotta get back to work.
Med tech to CTU.
You alright?
He went after you pretty hard.
Yeah, I'm fine.
So, clearly, La Fiera is here to
meet with the dying drug lord.
We just have to find out why.
You know I happen to be
wiretap certified, right?
Team work makes
the dream work, baby.
Transition team to OR 2.
Transition team -- OR 2.
Alright, so I can listen
for exactly two minutes.
If they are not talking about
anything illegal,
I have to wait and shut it off
for 30 seconds,
and then I can turn it back on
and start the two-minute clock
again.
I wish we had video
inside the room
instead of just the hallway.
Eh, we're lucky the judge
granted the audio surveillance,
but we don't need a warrant
to film in the hallway,
and I managed to find
an interesting angle.
Nicely done.
Thank you.
Now we just wait
for something to happen.
It's been hanging over my head
my whole life, okay?
It's stupid to do
the short-term fix.
I don't want to be here again
in a few years.
I want this behind me
for as long as possible.
I get that. We get that.
It's just with a minimally
invasive procedure,
you'd be on your feet again
-in a week.
-Yeah.
Recovery from open heart
surgery, that'll take months.
You'll have to give up the job.
Then I give it up.
Alright? It's -- It's my life.
It's my choice.
Hey, it's -- it's gonna be okay.
Alright?
We're gonna grow old together.
I'll have dentures,
and you'll still be
as beautiful as you are
right now.
When you were born,
your skin was blue.
I've never been so scared
in my life.
Until now.
I know it feels like
the worst thing
is to have another surgery
in five years,
but, Henry, that is not
the worst thing.
Henry?
What's happening?
- Henry!
- What's happening?
Doctor!
Henry? Doc!
Hey, buddy. Just breathe.
Hey, just breathe,
nice and easy.
Hey. Henry, Henry. He was fine.
Everybody step away, please.
He was fine,
and then all of a sudden --
- He's in V-fib.
- Back, please.
Charge to 200.
I got rails
on this side.
Please, buddy.
Chest is clear.
Charging.
Down.
Okay, everyone, clear.
Okay, he's stable for now.
Let's prep him for surgery.
What's the decision?
We have to do what he wants.
No, we don't.
No, now's the time
to play it safe
a-and do
the least invasive surgery.
After that, we'll reassess.
What's the answer?
...tube.
Prepping your meds. 120...
What do you think?
I don't know.
We do what he wants.
Anything else will be
a betrayal.
Sarah, he'll be okay.
Do the open heart surgery.
Mm. Now we just have to wait
until she poops.
Who said being a cop
isn't livin' the dream?
Just look on the bright side.
We scored a solid drug bust. Mm.
And I bet we can get her
to give us her supplier
with the right pressure.
Alright, well, I am gonna make
good use of my time.
Thank you for calling Angels
West Extended Care Program.
There are... 46 --
callers ahead of you.
Okay, well,
you keep the faith.
I'll, uh, check on
the narco detective.
Control, please be advised
that we are still 10-6
at Shaw Memorial.
Was there, um, any updates
from the narcotics table?
Negative.
What are you watching?
Uh, just a TikTok.
Of our living room? Are --
Are you spying on Tamara?
No! No. I'm just trying out
a home security system.
You are a lying liar who lies.
Okay. Fine.
My Swarovski Baby Yoda figurine
disappeared, okay?
Eh -- Okay. And so, what?
You installed a nanny cam
because you think she stole
your stupid toy?
Okay, two things --
it's not stupid --
it's amazing.
And it's not a toy --
It's a rare collectible
of sorts.
I can't believe
you would do this.
Look, Tamara would never
take advantage of us.
I know her. Eh, do you?
I mean, yeah, she seems like
a great person,
and I love that
you want to trust her,
but it doesn't really
change the fact
that she's been,
you know...
What?
...living on the streets.
There's no telling what
she had to do to survive.
Why didn't you
talk to me about this?
Why didn't you talk to me before
inviting the Artful Dodger
to live in our apartment?
Baby Yoda is missing.
No, he's not, okay? I broke him.
It was an accident. I'm sorry.
I was gonna replace it
before you even noticed.
I never thought that you would
blame a traumatized teenager.
Where's my headset?
Officially, only I can listen,
but I'm allowed to use
a translator if needed,
and my Spanish is
a little rusty today.
Gracias.
Tomá Mijo, when I am gone --
Come on...
I don't want to go. Believe me.
There's nothing illegal about
talking to your father
about dying.
We gotta turn it off.
Hold on. We still got a minute.
Who let you in here? Get out.
Señor Madrigal,
with all due respect,
I would like a word in private.
Tomá I admire your
persistence, Señora de la Cruz.
Mijo, please.
Papá, she has no business
here --
Cesar.
Out.
I don't wish to create trouble
between you and your son,
but it's important
that we speak.
I came here to ask for your...
What the hell?
Hey. Turn that off.
- How much you gonna pay me?
- What?
The other lady --
she paid me to buff.
You gonna pay me to stop?
Shut it down. Now.
She knows we're up on a wire.
No doubt.
But with Madrigal dying,
this conversation
has to happen today.
I am aware of
my son's limitations,
as I'm sure you are aware
of your son's.
It's what we have in common.
We are not like our sons.
It's a shame. Not necessa--
That's time.
Part of me feels bad
for those boys.
Their future was set
before they were even born.
It's not fair. Ugh.
Being pregnant
is giving me feelings.
So, uh, I went out
on a date with James.
I thought you were into Alonzo,
the guy from
the community center?
Uh, community center guy
is James.
Alonzo is the guy that I hooked
up with on the camping trip.
Damn. I can't keep up.
Me, neither.
I was -- I was in a drought,
and now --
It's raining men.
I've always either been
in a relationship or married
or undercover.
I don't know.
It's kinda fun having options.
And that's time.
Perhaps your son's
talents could be put to use
in a less demanding field.
Does he play video games?
Tomá He's open to video games,
but can one earn a living
doing that?
There are guys that make so
much money playing video games
that they never have a want
for the rest of their lives.
They're clearly not talking
about video games.
No, she's making a play to take
over Madrigal's drug operation
in exchange for
paying his son a royalty.
That's a baller move.
How do I know I can trust you?
Because like you, I respect
the old ways of doing things.
And don't you want to
leave this life knowing
that no harm will ever befall
your only son?
Looking everywhere for you.
- What happened?
- No, nothing.
He's -- He's still in surgery.
Abigail's just waiting
in the room.
I just --
I needed to stretch my legs.
No, I get it.
I get it. I get it.
So, how's, uh, Roger?
- You mean Andrew?
- Right, Andrew.
It's...
- It's Roger, isn't it?
- Is it?
Okay, so, I just hope maybe
Roger is being good to you.
Yeah, he is.
Okay. You deserve it.
What?
You and me dating other people.
Right?
When does it stop being weird?
Maybe it won't.
I can't believe
we're back at a hospital.
It seems like both yesterday
and a million years ago
Henry went in
for his last surgery.
He's a fighter.
He's been fighting
since the day he was born.
This is just another hill
for him to climb.
He's gonna be fine.
I can feel it.
Could you stop?
Stop what?
The compulsive optimism.
It's exhausting.
What do you mean?
I-I never told you this...
...but every time our baby
went in for another surgery,
I was convinced
we were going to lose him.
Sarah, I always felt
the opposite.
I know.
But I couldn't go there.
I had to protect myself,
every time,
in case.
It was like flipping a coin.
Another surgery, another flip.
And he always comes up heads.
But maybe this time he won't.
Maybe we should have opted
for the other surgery.
Maybe this will wind up being
the worst day of our lives.
Sarah...
I can't think like that.
And I can't think like you.
I'm going back in.
- You coming?
- Right behind you.
I'm gonna get
a little more fresh air.
Tomá Selling video games
is a complicated business,
especially for someone
new to town.
It's clear to us
that they're talking about
her taking over
Ah, but I have made...
...but a jury might not be able to get past all
the code. ...some crucial connections already.
Luckily, they're gonna have to
get into the details
at some point.
There's no
second conversation. You'd be surprised.
This deal is getting made
today or not at all. You know how strong
my market share already is.
I appreciate your diligence.
One cannot be too careful where
family and money collide.
But it's important to have
protection in place.
And a good lawyer is crucial.
Have you ever heard of...
Wesley Evers?
He's made some interesting
connections of his own.
I have someone vetting him
as we speak.
That's a threat.
Hello?
- Who is this?
I'm a nurse in Dr. Etz's office.
A patient's husband
left this phone here.
I'm the patient. And a cop.
Where did he go?
I don't know, but he left
in a hurry with a detective.
A detective?
Wh-- Did you hear a name?
No, but he said you sent him.
You said Angela
needed to see me.
- Where is she?
- Just up here.
You're not a detective, are you?
I was.
A long time ago, in Guatemala.
I was like your Angela --
so desperate to do good.
But so naive.
I was made to understand
my failings the hard way.
Let's just hope your Angela
doesn't need to be
taught a lesson like I was.
Listen to me.
I have represented
hundreds of guys like you.
You all think
that you're pure evil
and willing to do
whatever your master asks,
but you don't know anything
about Angela or me.
If you hurt her,
I will call in every favor
I am owed,
and there's a lot.
Rabid animals who will burn you
to your component molecules
while you beg me for mercy.
Do you hear me?
I love it.
Such passion.
Let's just hope you never
have to follow through, huh?
Let's just hope your beloved
does the smart thing
for herself.
And for your baby.
See you soon, amigo.
If she hurts Wesley --She wouldn't dare.
It's too reckless,
even for La Fiera.
Alright, backup's on the way.
Security's scrubbing through
surveillance tapes.
We'll find them.
Oh, thank God.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you?
Yeah. What happened?
I was just given
a not-so-subtle warning
from your favorite cartel boss.
Did they hurt you?
No, but they can and they will.
You should hand La Fiera off
to someone else,
at least until after the baby.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
I just threatened
to go medieval on some guy
if he even looks at you funny.
You did? Of course.
Is it bad that I'm a little
turned on right now?
Angela, it's not funny.
I know.
But if you know anything about
me, it's that I don't back down,
and La Fiera just
overplayed her hand.
Someone's happy.
Today is a good day.
Hey!
Angela.
You're about to get curb-stomped
by a pregnant lady.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's not worth it.
Hermana.
You know the baby feels
all the stress.
It's no good.
Maybe you should
take some time off.
Get some rest.
Think she bought it?
Please tell me you got something
while we were out of pocket.
Oh, yeah. They talked a lot
after you left.
See, we now have a recording
of La Fiera
making a deal to take over
Madrigal's operation.
- Yes.
- Don't get too excited.
It's just the first step
in making the case against her.
The DA can't just rely
on a cryptic conversation.
But this will free up resources,
maybe even launch a task force.
Definitely.
And you'll want in, right?
Who hired you
to smuggle the drugs?
Technically, it was my idea.
This has been a really bad year.
I lost my job,
had to drop out of school
because I couldn't
afford tuition.
Then I heard about
this dude willing to pay
a small fortune
to move product to Ibiza, and...
It's just happy pills.
Like, who was it gonna hurt,
you know?
I'm so stupid.
No, you just made a mistake.
Look, I'm not gonna lie and say
you can get off scot-free,
but we can put in a word
with the D.A.
First offense,
intent to distribute --
it shouldn't be too bad.
You'd do that?
If you tell us
who gave you the drugs
and agree to testify
against them.
Well, it just sounds like a
different way of possibly dying.
Things can be done
to protect you.
Can I think about it?
You have until the drugs pass.
Uh, hey, hey!
We need help in here! Nurse?
- Coming in.
- Yeah, we got her.
What's happening?
Could be an obstructed bowel, or
one of the drug packets broke.
We gotta get her into surgery.
Alright. Let's go.
I can't believe you were my age
when Henry was born.
Babies having babies.
Yeah, we were only married
a few months.
Remember the house
we were renting?
Oh, my God. You say "house."
I say "rotting wooden corpse."
But you fixed it up,
worked 20-hour days
to get it all done in time
to bring Henry home.
Yeah, and then we spent
two months at the hospital.
Did you have any rituals
to help pass the time
while you waited like this
for the surgeries to be over?
I cried. John did push-ups.
Actually, I think that was
the other way around.
Oh, right, yeah.
I got mad upper body strength
by the end of it.
Henry didn't tell me
this could happen.
He mentioned the TOF,
but he acted like
it was all behind him.
I'm sure he believed it was.
Still, he owed you the truth.
You deserve to know
what you're signing up for.
I really hope I get to
tell him that.
I will, right?
He's gonna be okay?
Yes. He is.
Nice of you to see us off.
How's the knee?
Doctor says it'll be a year
before I'm back out
on the fútbol pitch.
Don't skimp on
the physical therapy.
It's gonna suck,
but if you push through it,
you'll be glad you did.
Thanks.
Do you need a minute
with my mom?
30 seconds.
Okay.
Are you going to
threaten me again?
No. I'm gonna give you
one last chance --
for Diego's sake.
Don't go through with this deal.
Fly home with your son.
Take the money
you've already made
and give him the life
he deserves,
not the one
you think you're owed.
Hermana.
In my line of work,
you don't get to retire.
There's no walking away,
even if I wanted to.
Which I don't.
Gun!
Diego!
Go, go, go!
Officer under fire.
Parking garage, level four,
Shaw Memorial.
At least three shooters.
Send backup.
Diego, por favor!
You have to let me get to him.
You can't right now. You can't.
Oh.
I'll take these two.
I got the big guy.
Not that big.
Aah!
Control, 7-Adam-19,
two in custody,
one active shooter remaining.
We need an RA.
Hispanic male,
gunshot wound to the torso.
Conscious and breathing.
Drop the gun.
Do it now.
Arms out.
Last suspect in custody. Code 4.
No!
Ahhhh!
So... And it was supposed to be
my day off.
No good deed, sir.
Any luck locating
Cesar Madrigal?
Not yet. Odds are
he's gone to ground.
It's not gonna help.
He took a shot at the Queen
and missed.
Yeah, well...
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
You can't come
into the crime scene.
When will I have
my son's body to bury?
In a few days.
After the autopsy.
Her son was her humanity.
With him gone...
War is coming.
Angels West. How can I help you?
Yes. Uh, yes, hi.
I would like to check the status
of an application for Colins.
Tamara Colins.
Yes. Yeah.
Ye-- Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh. She's in.
They're going to send Tamara
an e-mail confirmation
- by the end of the week.
- Well, tha-- that's amazing.
- Mm-hmm.
- Y-You're amazing,
and I am a suspicious idiot.
No. Well, maybe a little.
Yeah. You know what?
I'm gonna talk to Tamara,
beg for forgiveness.
No, you're not.
That would break her heart.
- How is she?
- Lucky.
A packet burst,
but only one pill ruptured.
So we're keeping her overnight
to make sure
there are no further
complications.
Hey!
Guys, I had the weirdest dream.
You were in it.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but that wasn't a dream.
The flying monkeys were real?
Oh, uh... You know what?
Why don't we talk more
about this when you come down?
Okay. Okay.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
So is the baby.
But they killed Diego.
La Fiera's son.
♪ Pas besoin d'eux
Angela -- I know.
But can we not talk about it
right now?
There's still a lot of...
paperwork and interviews.
I'm not leaving without you.
Good.
I don't want you to.
♪ Je sais que ça te fait mal
End of shift?
More like end of job.
They had to intubate
the old man.
He'll be dead in a day or two,
so, um,
I'm screwed again.
♪ Et même si tu insistes ♪
You need to go to rehab, Mack.
Are you kidding?
The pills are the only thing
moving me forward right now.
I can't afford to stop.
I'm too deep in the hole,
and I gotta get out
before I can get clean.
And how many times have you
heard a junkie say
that exact same thing?
Plenty.
And how many of them ever did?
None.
Look, you can hate me
all you want, Mack,
but I'm not giving up on you.
There's never an easy time
to get clean,
and you are about to go through
the worst year of your life.
You're not gonna survive this,
man, unless you're sober.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Yes, I do.
And so do you.
Come on, Mack.
It's time for you
to cowboy up, alright?
Own your mistakes, man.
Just take your lumps.
Be an example for your kids.
You're a better man than this.
♪ Mais même si tu insistes ♪
♪ J'ai pu le goût
de croire en rien ♪
Good. Alright?
Okay.
♪ Je serai le sauveur
Let's go.
♪ De mon simple bonheur
Hey, you, uh -- you wouldn't
happen to have any suggestions
on where I could throw
a bachelorette party, would you?
I mean, Jason's got
that sports bar on Sunset.
Yeah, that's a no-go.
Oh, good.
Lasagna is in the oven.
You cooked?
I tried. I couldn't totally
remember my mom's recipe,
but I think it's pretty close.
Oh, I got you something.
I know that Lucy broke
your Yoda thing.
- You told him, right?
- Wh-- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes.
Anyways, I couldn't afford
the fancy one, but...
I thought you'd like this.
- Oh.
- Aww.
It's, uh...
You did not have to do that.
I know, but you're letting me
stay here,
and for the first time
in forever,
I feel safe.
Tamara, look, um...
♪ Et le don de faire du bien
You are welcome to stay
as long as you want.
Now have you
seen "The Mandalorian"?
Because I am so down
to watch it again.
- For the third time.
- Okay.
That sounded judgy.
Mm.
Sure.
It's based on a movie, right?
- A mo-- Oh.
- Shh. Relax.
It's okay.
- Okay. Yep.
- It's okay.
Um, I gotta teach you
some stuff. Come on.
What if he never fully recovers?
What if the future is
me being his nurse?
You'll never be alone.
Promise you that.
The surgery went really well.
The damage wasn't as severe
as we thought,
and Henry will make
a full recovery.
Oh, thank God.
Thank you. Thank you.
Um, w-when can we see him?
Oh, in a few hours.
They're just getting him settled
in recovery.
Okay. Thank you.
Good night.
-Too soon for "I told you so" 's?
- No, bring it on.
- Okay. I told you so.
Come here.
Get in here.
- Get in here.
- Okay.
♪ Du début à la fin ♪