Previously on "The Rookie"...I'm gonna give you my car.
What's the catch?You have to keep checking in
with me until you're off
the street, or no deal.
-Thanks.
-Hey!
I am hereby placing you
under administrative leave.
Gun and badge.
Guys like Doug Stanton
should not be training
our next generation.
If you had
your college degree,
you would be able to be T.O.
in two years.
Looks like
I'm going back to school.
♪♪
Thanks for letting me
do my laundry here.
I swear my cousin's dryer
is possessed.
Any time.
Plus, it means I get to
make sure
you have avegetable
this month.
I told you -- all the cool kids
are getting scurvy.
Mm-hmm.
Listen --
I have to write a paper
for school
about gender roles
in the workplace,
and I'm supposed to
interview someone
who's working a job that was
traditionally considered male.
And you want to
interview...me?
If you're not busy.
I would be honored.
If you're gonna make this weird,
I'll just ask someone else.
No! I'm in.
We can --
We can do it after dinner
tonight.
I still have to get
the questions together.
Okay. Well, how about
tomorrow night?
I could pick you up
after my shift?
I should be done on time
for once.
My sergeant has us doing
site security
for the CCOA convention.
It's the California Covert
Operators Association.
Undercover cops
have a convention?
Yeah. At a hotel,
if you can believe it.
And it's advertised
on their website, so...
Well, sounds like
the opposite of covert.
Yeah, that's what I said.
But I guess it's a space for
them to share trade secrets.
And party
on the city's dime.
While we make sure no bad guys
get close enough
to ID an undercover cop.
Well, sadly,
I'll be missing the fun
because I'll be working
the Community Policing Center
with Smitty tomorrow.
Ah. Only 10 more days
until no more T.O.s.
Mm.
Hey.
I thought you were starting
college classes tonight.
Nolan: I'm actually just about
to head into
my Ethics and Criminal Law
class.
But I'm having
second thoughts about
identifying myself
as a police officer.
I mean, I should, right?
No.No.Yeah.
That's...not helpful.
Why shouldn't you?
Because it'll isolate him right away.
You think I introduce myself
as homeless at school?
Unless you want the class
to be about you,
I'd keep your head downand blend in.
Good evening.
I'm Professor Ryan,
and this is
Ethics and Criminal Justice.
Now, tell me, what do
those words make you think?
That...the two don't gotogether.
Why?
Because the criminal justice
system is inherently biased,
designed to punish poor people
and people of color.
Okay, so if that's a problem,
what is a solution?
Defund the police,
for starters.
Anyone disagree?
Uh, well, I don't think
it's quite that simple --
just defunding the police.
Defunding doesn't mean
get rid of cops.
It means
stop prioritizing them
over people
they're supposed to serve.
Yeah, no, I appreciate that,
and I agree.
I think a lot more money needs
to be invested in communities,
but it will take time
for those investments
to effect any realchange.
If we drastically cut policing
before that happens,
it would leave people
unprotected.
It can't be worse
than it is now.
Sure, it can.
Don't you agree?
Oh, I'm not here to agree
or to pick sides.
Ethics are often at odds
with the law.
What's right
and what is legal
are very often
all too different.
And that tension is what
we are here to explore.
And it is going to get
uncomfortable,
so y'all better strap in.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
♪ Like I know
you want me to do ♪
By then,
the class had ended,
and I still hadn't
identified myself.
Did I make a mistake?
I can't answer that
for you.
As a cop, you have to judge
social situations
on a case-by-case basis.
I just hate the feeling
like I'm hiding something.
Allof these people can't be
undercover cops, can they?
Okay, so, think of
the undercover world
like high school, right?
So, first,
you have your UCs.
They are like
the star quarterbacks.
No undercover operation
can happen without them,
and they know it.
They take
the most risk,
and they reap
the most reward.
Meaning?
They get laid.
A lot.
Oh.
Then you have
your Case Officers.
They're like
the debate team.
They think they're smarter
than everyone else,
and they see themselves
as puppet masters
who use UCs as just a tool
in their kit.
I'm guessing they don't get laid
near as much.
Correct. Then you have
your Tech Squad.
They're like the hackers.
They basically aresmarter
than everyone else,
but they have
a real criminal streak.
They commit legal burglaries
and break-ins,
planting
cameras and bugs.
Finally,
you have your Freshmen.
They're easily identifiable.
Just off patrol.
Still at
that awkward stage
of trying to let
their hair grow out,
where they're
mullet-adjacent.
So youwere
a star quarterback.
Oh, baby,
I was the Heisman Trophy.
Lucy: Alright, thanks.
You're good to go.
Hey, do you work the convention
every year?
No. L.A. hasn't hosted onein a long time.
But I did go
with Isabel once.
What kind of classes
do they teach?
No idea.
Patrol isn't allowed to know
UC trade secrets.
So I just ordered room service,worked on my tan.
♪ Don't talk, just listen
Bradford!Mack!
Ugh! You bastard!
You get prettier with age.
Yeah, and you're stillthe same part Neanderthal.
Lucy Chen, Mack Daniels.
Hey, how are you?
Oh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Beth, how are the kids?
Oh, uh, this is actually,
uh, my friend Candace.
Candace: Hi. Mack's right.
You are pretty.
Uh, Chen, why don't you goand get Candace's info?
Yeah.
Mack, come on
over here, bud.
Uh-oh.
Am I in trouble?
If you wanna run around on Beth,that's your business.
But did you really expect menot to notice?
Notice what?Your pupils, man.
They're pinpoints.
You're looking 5-50.
What are you on?
It's just a little Oxy.
Okay?
Relax,
I got a prescription.
Jacked up my shoulder on the jobabout a month back.
Pain's a, uh, mother.
Mack!
I got a spa appointment.
I gotta go.
Hey, it's good
seeing you, bro.
Yeah. You, too.
♪ Shut up more
and then listen ♪
♪ Some of y'all need
to just muzzle up ♪
♪ I got hits to throw,
you wanna muscle up ♪
He seems...nice.
Yeah, believe it or not,he used to be
the most clean-cut guyI ever met.
James, it's good to see you.
Am I, uh, still on for
Aaron and Michael tutoringtomorrow night?
Just Aaron.
Michael has drama club.
That boy's such a ham.I love him.
Who's this?This is Silas.
Silas, good to meet you.
I'm, uh, Jackson,
and this is Smitty.
Jackson.
Last name West.
Badge number, please?
For my records.
3-3-3-5-6.
Badge number?
2-8-7-1-7.
First name, please.
Smitty's sufficient.
Silas is the eyes and earsof the neighborhood.
He does a daily patrol,
gives me a heads-up
on problems
that need fixing.
Anything we should
know about?
Well, City Sanitation
neglected to empty
the Dumpster
in front of Matteo's Deli.
That will attract rodents.
And a Cadet Blue
1978 Dodge Aspen
is blocking
Sally Nelson's driveway,
and she has work
at 10:00.
Kid would make a good CI.
Forget it.
Silas is here becausehe wants to help his neighbors,
not make it easierfor you to hassle them.
Of course. That's notwhat
we're looking for.
Look, I can call the cityand have them tow away the Aspen
so Sally can get to work.
Is there anything else
we can help you with?
Um, I've actually
made a list of potholes,
and they can cause accidents,
car damage.
But the Bureau
of Street Services
doesn't return
my telephone calls.
Smitty, doesn't your uncle
work for City Services?
Ugh -- Artie. Yes.
Guy is sucha slacker.
Can you call him
about the potholes?
No.
I owe him money.
Okay, fine.
Give me the number,
and I'll call.
Do you really think
there could be trouble
at this convention?
Absolutely.
Criminals would killto infiltrate this place.
The damage thatundercover operations do
to their business
is incredible.
June!
Wh-- Are you here?
Oh, good.
You're at the convention.
I'm scheduled to teach
a seminar this morning,
but I can't get there.
Can you fill in for me?
It's the same class
you used to teach.
You could do it
in your sleep.
I can't.I'm working security.
Please. You still owe me
from that op in Bakersfield,
and you know I wouldn't ask
if I didn't have to.
Go ahead.
I got this covered.
Okay.
Uh, sure.
Thanks.
I'll text you the details.
You are the best.
What's the seminar on?
Women make up just 12%
of law enforcement.
But they're attacked almosttwice as often as male officers.
And yet, male officers are
three times more likely
to fire their weapon,
they are three times more likelyto get injured while on duty,
and they make up 95%
of citizen complaints.
Which begs the question,
are women just better cops?
Oh, you better believe it.
You're not supposed to be
listening.
Why? 'Cause they don't
trust patrol
with all their
Secret Squirrel stuff?
It doesn't matter why.
Rules are rules.
And I'm already on thin ice,
so I'm outta here.
This seminar today is about
being a female undercover cop
and the unique risks
that that poses.
Now, I will warn you, this is
not gonna be an easy ride.
Some of what you're about to see
is hard to watch.
But if we can learn from the UCs
who died in these videos,
then maybe
we can save some lives.
Are you with me?
♪♪
Chen.
Yes?
Thought you were running
to the bathroom.
I was. I am.
Sorry.
Jackson: Next time he calls
about potholes,
take it seriously, okay?
Yes, I work with Smitty.
Yeah. No.
No, I-I won'ttell him that.
Because it's disgusting.
No! No! No! No!
No! No!
My baby's in the back!
7-Adam-07, carjacking,
suspect headed westbound
on Fourth near Waverly.
I'm on foot.
I need any unit in the area.
♪♪
♪ Whacha got, whatcha got?
♪ Into the wild
and when you get up? ♪
♪ And in the morning
I guess you didn't need
that assist after all.
You're...?
A cop on a horse?
Yep.
Any other suspects?
No.
Can you watch him?
Victim said her baby
was in the car.
♪ Like an A-list star
in a movie ♪
Oh!
Ma'am, that'syour baby?
Yeah.
Oh!
Oh, I'm sorry.
So you were spying
on one of the seminars?
No.
Maybe a little bit.
I mean, what's the big deal?
I'm a cop, too.
The likelihood
of patrol officers
getting fired
or flaming out
are much higher
than ranked officers.
The information and tactics
the CCOA present
are so unique
and so sensitive,
they're literally
on a need-to-know basis.
Got it?
Yeah.
Tim?
Beth.
I'm here to surprise Mack.
He's barely been home
the last three months.
I bet. Yeah, undercover work's
a full-time gig.
Is he here yet?
Yeah. He rolled through
a few hours ago.
It's great seeing you.
You, too.
Seriously?
You're not gonna give her
a heads-up?
No way I'm getting
in the middle of that.
Tim.
Check this out.
Those cars belong to
the undercover cops.
Well, they'll have
switched-out license plates
so criminals
can't ID them.
But they can't cover
the VIN numbers.
If he gets those numbers,
he'll be able to identify them.
Gun.
Back pocket.
Hey! Police!
Hold up!
♪♪
All units, be advised,
we have a perimeter breach.
White male, blue ballcap,
gray jacket, blue jeans.
Made it in through
the south rear door.
Armed with a handgun,
and may be targeting police.
He won't get far.
Hotel's on lockdown,
and his description
just went out
to 200
armed police officers.
Really, he's trapped
in here with us.
Yeah, that description's
useless now.
Be advised, our suspect
no longer has on
a ballcap or jacket.
Which means we are searching for
a white guy in blue jeans.
Do you see that?
Yeah, that could be our guy.
Could just be a twitchy UC.
They're hardwired to avoid
uniformed cops.
You think you can tell if he's
a cop just by talking to him?
Is that a challenge?
Yep.
How's it going?
Ah.
Here for the convention?
I'm not really
supposed to say.
That's a yes.
I'd kill to work undercover.
God, me, too.
You must have
the best stories.
Nah.
Oh, come on.
Give us one.
I've only been
a year on the job.
I've never seen
any real action.
Alright, well, this one time,
a couple years back,
I get in with
this biker gang,
and we're movin'
a hell-ton'a smack.
Now, the buyer,
he smells a rat,
and suddenly, I've got
six sawed-off shotties
right to my grill.
Mm.
They wanted me to try the batch,
make sure it wasn't bunk.
What'd you do?
Man, I got high
as the Hindenburg
and came down
just as messy.
Sorry. Wrong answer.
Ah.
Real undercover cops
don't behave
like characters in movies.
Taste the drugs,
your case,
your career are shot.
Suspect in custody.
Thanks for the assist.Ah, no problem.
I was giving a talk at
the local elementary school.
Yeah, I gotta admit,
I've actually never seen
a cop on a horse before.
Well, not out on the street,
anyway.
It's...weird.
You must have been looking
in the wrong direction.
Yeah, well, I am not now.
Officer Jackson West,
badge number 3-3-3-5-6.
What's up, Silas?I don't know him.
Uh, this is Officer Young.
Isaac.
Badge number 2-9-1-9-6.
And this here's Ruby,
official police horse
of the West Adams
Mounted Patrol.
Does she have
a badge number?
No, but she lives in
stall number 11.
Uh, how's patrol?
Is there anything else
we can do?
Actually...
a sprinkler head
at Edgewood Park broke off
and is spraying the swings.
Okay.
Well, I am on it.
It's, uh --
it's nice to meet you.
Yeah, you, too.
You two are looking
at each other funny.
I am his wife!
Open the damn door!
He doesn't want
to see you!
Mack, I'm done.
Can you hear me?
You're never gonna see
your sons again!
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Mack's in there
with some stripper whore.
He's wasted
out of his mind.
♪♪
What's going on?Nothing.
We're just hanging out.
Get Mack.
I need to see him.
No, he's sleeping --
I think.
I don't know!
He won't talk to me.
Open the door.
No, I can't.Open --
Back up!
♪ Still ain't the crew Mack.
♪ Buy the same fits,
but you still ain't the crew ♪
He's not breathing.
What did you do?!Nothing.
We were just partying.
Control, 7-Adam-19,
send an RA
to the Augustin Hotel,
9212 West 6th Street,
Room 623.
Adult male,
possible OD.
♪ That ain't you,
that ain't you ♪
Come on, Mack.
♪ Guns out
Come on.
Wake up, Mack!
Come on.Tim. Narcan.
♪♪
♪ Got a team of boys, yeah
You're all right, man.
You're all right.
I'm here, okay?
Beth's here.
You're okay, bud.
Try and sit up.Beth...baby...
I can't do this anymore.
Wait, wait, wait.
Come back.
I love you.
You said Iwas the one
you loved.
♪ In a Lamborghini
♪ You could like the same,
but you still ain't the crew ♪
Okay,
tell me the truth.
Did working the convention
as a patrol officer
feel like a demotion?
At first, yes.
But then, I don't know.
I got a contact anxiety high.
I do not miss the constant fear
and the lying so much
you don't know
what the truth is.
Hey!
I know you.
Victor, right?
Hey.
How you doing?
Victor's
in my Ethics class.
You're a cop.
I can see why
you might think that.
Um, but to be fair,
this uniform could also mean
I'm a male stripper.
Whoa.
What's all that for?
To show everyone in class
we got a narc inside.
Victor. Hey.
It's a little harsh.
Victor.
Well...can't wait to hear
how class goes.
Hey.
Were you trying to
kill yourself?
God, Bradford, no.
Okay, then what the hell
were you thinking?
You told me you were taking Oxy
because you were injured.
I was. Alright?
I am.
It was a mistake.
A mistake?
Yeah.
You downed opioids
with whiskey.
Alright, that's not
pain management.
That is a problem.
I know.
I screwed up, okay?
Yeah.
I was just trying
to push through the pain
a-a-and keep working.
It got away from me.
Y-You know how it is.
I do.
And I know addicts
lie so much
they don't know
what's true anymore.
Hey, I am not your ex-wife.Really?
'Cause from where I'm standing,
you look exactly like Isabel.
Look, I'm not gonna make
the same mistake I did with her.
You are going
into a program.
Tomorrow.
You can't keep doing this
to your family, Mack.
I know.
I will.
I promise.
♪♪
Hello.
Hi.
Mm-hmm.
So, you know we're gonna have
to talk about it, right?
Look, it was a momentary
lapse in judgement,
and Tim has already scolded me
for listening in,
but I gotta say, um,
what I heard at your seminar
was amazing.
I was a little rusty,
but thank you.
Listen, I've been
thinking a lot
about what I want to do
once I'm eligible to test,
and...
I think I could be really good
at undercover work.
I would love to
pick your brain sometime --
not about tactics,
just...
what I should focus on
to prepare for the job.
I actually --
I...have time
for drinks right now,
if you want.
Yeah. Great.
Alright.
Uh...no.
I have a homework thing
with Tamara.
She won't mind if we do it
a little bit later.
Let me just
give her a call.
Hey, it's me.
Are we cool
if we do the interview
a little bit later
tonight?
Is 9:00
too late for you?
Okay. Great.
I will see you then.
I am all yours.
Hey. You know you owe me
big time, right?
Yeah, but can we keep
my tab open?
I could use another assist.
Uh, I was about
to go out for drinks
with a colleague of mine,
Lucy Chen.
Hey.
I'm in a bind.
Look, the real reason
I couldn't make
the convention today
is because
I spotted a tail
on my way down
from Sacramento.
Who? I think it's the buyer
in this op
I've been running.
They're sniffing around
a big batch
of liquid Fentanyl
I'm selling.
And you think
they're onto you?
I think there's
a lot of money in play
and they're paranoid as hell.
Are they still
surveilling you?
Yeah,
I couldn't lose them.
I think they put a tracker
on my car.
Look, I'm at The Smoke House
in Burbank,
but my whole team's
up in San Jose.
What are you driving?
Black Mustang GT.
They know me as Coco.
Alright,
I'm on my way.
Sorry.
I'm gonna have
to call Grey now,
and we're gonna have
to take a rain check
on our drinks, but --Totally.
Unless you wanna
come with?
♪♪
Narc.
Hey.
There's no call for that.
At least
let me explain first?
Explain what?That he's a cop.
Yeah, I know.
What do you mean,
you know?
Well, I saw it
on his application
when he signed up
for my class.
And you didn't tell us?
Oh, it wasn't
my decision to make.
How can you say that?
Cops have been spying
on people like us
for 200 years.
He could be taking this class
to get close to us,
to get into LULAC
or Black Lives Matter.
Oh, I'm not undercover.
I'm -- I'm actually
just a rookie.
Dude, stop lying.
I'm not.
Um...
Two years ago, I was working
construction back east.
I moved out here
to join the police
and make a difference.
I'm actually taking this class
to finally get my degree.
It's true.
I read his transcript.
Plus, do you really think
the LAPD's gonna send
a 40-something-year-old
white guy to infiltrate BLM?
Come on, now.Probably not.
He still should have
told us he's a cop.
Hmm.
Who here thinks that John
is ethically obligated
to identify himself?
I do.
Why?
This is supposed to be
a safe space.
What if one of us
admitted to a crime
in the middle of
a discussion?
Well, then,
you'd be stupid.
There are no
truly safe spaces --
I mean, certainly not
in a college classroom.
But believe it or not,
I, uh,
was wrestling with
whether or not to tell you
last night, and...
honestly, I still don't know
what the right decision is.
Okay, well,
let's explore that further.
I want everyone in here
to write a five-page essay.
Tell me why or why not
you think that John had
an ethical obligation
to tell us he's a cop.
There's June's car.
Tracker.
What's the plan?
You go in, find June.
Remember, her undercover name
is Coco.
She's a friend in town.
Buy her a drink,
chat her up.
I will hang back and try
and spot who her tails are.
Okay.
You up for this?
Hell yeah.
Coco?
Hey.
Harper found a tracker outside.
We think they're here.
Yeah, I know.
One's at your 4:00.
Haven't spotted
his backup yet.
♪♪
Hey, honey.
Can I get you something?
Yeah, sure. Uh, I will have
what she's having.
Do you want another one?Sure.
Make it three.
Coco.
Hey, what a coincidence, seeing
you all the way down here.
Like hell.
You followed me.
We got a lot of money
on the line with this deal,
so we need to be
very careful.
A lot of people in
this business, you know...
they don't
have integrity.
Yeah, 'cause you're
just filled with integrity,
aren't you, Sato?
Oh, you say my name in front of
someone that Idon't know?
What is wrong with you?
No, what's wrong
with you?
No one asked you to sit.
Who is this bitch?
Oh, you just
killed yourself.
I'm looking at an empty chair
right there.
Then who's gonna conduct
the hydrogenation process?
Who's gonna perform
the molecular synthesis
to get the acid tables
balanced?
You get that wrong,
you're gonna have
buyers with brain bleed.
You're the chemist.
She's the chemist.
Yeah, she is.
Now back off.
And tell your boss
the price just went up 5%
for the lack of trust.
Oh, I don't think so.
Let's take a walk,
talk about this somewhere
a little more private.
♪♪
Hmm?
We're gonna go
for a little ride.
Think about why, uh, I got
such a bad feeling about you.
Harper:
These guys are cops.
They put a tracker
on your car.
Got a bad feeling
about me,huh?
Hey, we're not cops.
You want me to do 'em here
or take 'em to the farm?
Hey, you gotta
believe me.
Coco, you know me.
Then what's with
the tracker?
Salonga wanted you
surveilled,
in case you guys tried
to rip us off.
I swear.
Look, we want this deal
to happen.
We needthis deal
to happen, okay?
We just wanted to
make sure.
Well, now you are.
But the price
just went up 10%.
Consider it a tax
for pissing me off.
Salonga ain't gonna go
for that.
Hmm, then this is goodbye.
I got plenty of other buyers.
Yeah, okay, okay!
I'll make it happen.
But she comes, too.
At that price, I want her
to test the product
in front of us to make sure
that it's pure.
Forget it. No.
She doesn't go out on buys.
What? N-No.
I'll go.
I've already spent my share
of the money in my head.
I'll call you on this phone
with the new location.
And you better pick up
on the first ring.
Now piss off.
Come on.
♪♪
I can't believe
we just did that.
"You want me to do them here
or take 'em to the farm?"
You are sobadass!
Wait, how much do you know
about opioid chemistry?
I mean, just what they
taught me at the Academy.
But I got straight A's
in high school chemistry, so...
Then you're gonna have
some homework to do.
What time is it?
Hey.
Look, I am sosorry.
It's cool.No, it's not.
Drinks turned into
this undercover thing,
which was super cool --
but not the point.
Look, there's no excuse
for me leaving you hanging.
Can you do the interview now?
Or tonight?
When is your paper due?
It's fine.
The drunk lady
across the hall
used to be
a luchadora.
I'll just ask her.
What?
Mexican wrestler.
No. No.
Look, give me
another chance.
Okay? Tonight.
I promise
I'll be there.
Okay. Sure.
Now I gotta
get to school.
Okay.
♪♪
You get my report
on Mack Daniels?
Yeah, I did.
Are you sure this is the way
you want things to go?
He'll get fired,
might do jail time.
Mack didn't get hurt
a month ago.
He got hurt
six months ago.
He's deep
into an addiction,
and he's walking around
with a loaded gun.
And, sir,
i-it's not just that.
I-I went back
to his hotel room.
There were
prescription bottles
with other people's names
on 'em.
And he could be doing anything
to get those pills.
Cops have to be held to
a higher standard.
Anything less,
all hell breaks loose.
I agree.
I just wanted to make sure
you saw the repercussions.
He's going to
lose his pension.
Yeah.
I-I struggled with that.
But it's what I should have
done with Isabel.
Alright.
So, one more thing.
Chen's going on
a special assignment today.
She'll be joining Harper
on an undercover operation.
This is Sergeant June Zhang
of Fresno PD.
We are gonna help out
on her op today.
Appreciate
the assistance, guys.
I'm June, the UC.
My case officer,
Lieutenant Balasco,
who is not nearly as mean
and awful as he looks.
For the last eight months,
I have been up on a crew
out of San Jose who made bank
selling precursors of
liquid Fentanyl.
But they got greedy, tried to go
from selling the parts
to making and selling
the finished product.
But their lab blew up,
killing their chemist
and destroying
their entire supply,
leaving them with no product
and a lot of pissed-off buyers.
Which is when I swooped in,
promising enough product
to satisfy all their customers
and then some.
But last night, all our
hard work almost fell apart,
until the quick thinking
of Officer Chen saved my ass.
Chen, stand up so they can
see what you're wearing.
Yeah.The op today is simple.
Trade drugs for cash,
then arrest everybody
and try to get them to flip on
Aldo Salonga, their boss.
Alright.
You have your assignment.
Everyone in position
by 10:00 a.m.
What the hell
are you doing?
You can't pit an
untrained probationary officer
against one of
the most dangerous
crime syndicates
in California.
I don't want to hear it, Tim.
She volunteered.
Plus, Grey authorized it,
and we have some of
the best operational expertise
she could ask for.
They know the gladiator cage
you're walking into.
You don't.
That's not volunteering.
That's being used.
Hey, don't let Bradford
kill your confidence, okay?
His...hang-ups about UC work
are his to deal with, not yours.
I kinda hoped that
he would be proud of me.
Wow. That sounds stupid
when I say it out loud.
No, it doesn't.
He's your training officer.
He's gotten you this far.
There's nothing wrong
with wanting his approval.
And for what it's worth,
you've got mine.
You handled yourself
like a pro last night.
Those instincts
can't be taught.
Thanks.
Hey!
I need your help!
Somebody hurt Silas!
Come on!
♪♪
I came by this morning,
found him like this.
He won't say
what happened.
Silas.
Look, Officer West is here.
Hey, Silas.
Looks like it hurts.
Did you, uh,
crash your bike?
Someone hurt you?
Where is your bike?It's okay.
You can talk to us.
If anything happened,
let us help.
I called his mother.
She's -- She's on her way
back from work now.
Okay, well,
in the meantime, Silas,
come back
to the Center,
and we'll get those wounds
cleaned up, alright?
I'm never
going back there.
What? Why?
Look, uh,
I'm sorry to hear that.
Do you mind if I borrow
your notebook?
Finish up
your patrol for you?
Look, I'll, uh,
bring it back.
Promise.
Hey, can you, uh --
can you stay with him?
Yeah.
Hey. Yeah, it's, uh,
Jackson West.
Are you still working
in the area?
♪♪
Control, 7-Adam-07,
show us Code 6.
Silas' last entry was a broken
street light at this address.
Something happened.Check it out.
♪♪
The bike.
Police!
What?Sir, we need to
talk to you
about this bike over here
and what happened
to the young man
who was riding it.
Bobby: ...Madness,"
the show where
everyone's a winner.
Sir, open the door
right now.
He's running!
...and win the gold.
Now here he is.
Nothing.
with the gift of gab,
your "Money Madness" host,
Sam Lovejoy.
Show yourself now!
Lovejoy: Thank you, Bobby,
and hello, everybody.
This is "Money Madness."
I'm Sam Lovejoy,
and I just can't wait
to give away all this cash.
Just look at my suit pocket.
It's bursting at the seams
with cash.
Now, Bobby, who's tonight's
first soon-to-be winner?
Bobby: Sam, this is
Miss Donna McGee
from Akron, Ohio.McGee: Hello.
Lovejoy: Now, Bobby, who do we
have playing on the phone?
Bobby: Just darling Donna.
Earl:
Get out of my house!
This is my house!
Get out of it, I said!
Hey, hey!
Come on. Come on.
Come on!
Ow!
He was spying on me!
I saw him, outside,
writing things about me,
saying I'm crazy.
I'm not crazy!
He's just a kid.
He was staring at
a broken street light.
You didn't have to
hurt him.
Liar.
Liar!
I taught him.
I taught him!
♪♪
I know you're worried
about Lucy.
Who said I was worried?
I'm just saying,
she can handle herself.
I knowshe can.
I trained her.
Eagle One in place.
Alright, uh, let's go over this
one more time.
Salonga's crew arrives,
you test the Fentanyl,
give them a show,
we get the money,
they get this van,
and then, boom,
strike team takes them down.
Walk in the park.
And if not...
...we make some noise until
the cavalry arrives.
You want to go over
the signals again?
Yeah. "Workhorse" means
we're in trouble.
And "Beautiful day,"
we're all good.
Lucy.
Mm-hmm?
Are youall good?Yeah. Yes.
You know, if you're not nervous,
you're not human.
Okay? So, use this
to your advantage.
Be scared. Be wild.
Be unpredictable.
Be a cobra.
Can I ask you
a question?
No.
What's your formula
for when you tell people
you're a police officer
in off-duty life?
I try not to put myself
in social situations
where I need to.
Right.
It's just that I got outed as
a cop in my Criminal Law class,
and there's some
pretty strong feelings
that I should've been
upfront about it.
You did the right thing
keeping it a secret.
Now you gotta
sit in the back row,
always have your eyes
on the door.
Why?
Because they know
you're a cop now,
which means they know you carry
an off-duty weapon.
Somebody may try
to take it from you,
or maybe just attack you
because they hate cops.
All due respect, I can't live
my life like that --
with being suspicious
of people,
seeing the world
as dangerous.
The world isdangerous.
Being vigilant is
the price of admission.
♪♪
It's go time.
Let's do this!Where's the money?
First things first.
I wanna test
the shipment.
♪♪
Hard positives
on every scale.
When's the last time
you saw that?
Never.
There's nothing available
this pure.
Now let's see
the cash.
We're in business.
♪♪
Nolan:
Who the hell is that?
We've got another guest
at the party.
Standby for rescue.
If this is a set-up,
you're the first to go.
Relax.
It's just my boss.
And he wants
to talk...to you.
Me?
Good morning.
My apologies
for last night.
Sato overstepped.
It won't happen again.
Come in and talk to me.
Why?
A monkey can be taught
to test for drugs...
or a cop.
I need to see that
you really know the science.
Why aren't we going in there
and arresting everybody?
We need to see
the money first.
What the hell.
It's a beautiful day.
Nothing's gonna go wrong.
♪♪
Don't concern yourself
with him.
It's a little hard
not to.
Okay, stop trying
to scare me
and just tell me
what we're doing here.
Simple.
I know
a little chemistry.
The hydromorphone hydrochloride
you're selling --
remind me
of the formula.
You speak Tagalog.
My best friend in elementary
school grew up in Quezon City.
I...basically
lived at her house.
I picked up a little bit.
Problem?
Nope.
I just have a flair
for the dramatic.
Okay.
Are we done?
I like you.
So I have an offer.
I kill Coco
and the other one.
You keep
half the money.
Come work for me.
Betrayal's not really
my style,
but I'm flattered
by the offer.
Can we finish the deal now?
♪♪
Now, that's sexy.
Weapons down!
Weapons down on the ground
right now!
Drop the gun!
Hands above your head!
Interlace your fingers!
Put your hands behind your head!
Interlace your fingers now!
Hands behind your head.
Man: Hands up, weapons down.
Do notmove.
You okay?
Give me your hands.Sato!
You set us up,
you snitch!
You're dead!
You hear me?!
-Eyes on him.
-You're dead!
You watch your back!This brings back
some memories.
First day together.Oh, right.
Watch your head.
♪♪
You did good.
Beth. Hey.
You okay?
Tim Bradford,
my hero and savior.
I didn't
have a choice.
The hell you didn't.
When your coked out ex-wife
was working undercover,
you had all kinds
of options.
Now, all of a sudden,
your hands are tied?
Hypocritical bastard.
I-I can't excuse
the past, okay?
But this is now,
and Mack crossed
too many lines.
I have three young kids
and a husband
who is looking
at yearsin state prison
and no more pension.
How am I supposed to
feed my kids?
I'm sorry this happened.
But I didn't do it to you.
Mack did.
You...are a cop.
You're supposed to
look out for your own.
♪♪
♪ I wasn't the favorite
♪ I wasn't the first one
off the gun ♪
♪ Might have seemed
I was chasing ♪
Hey.
You gotta be kidding me.
What's so funny?
♪ No, never count me out
♪ No, it ain't how you start
Wow.
So, what do we do now?
Let the kid choose.
You know he's gonna
choose mine, right?
You wanna put money on that?
How about dinner?
I don't know,
I heard you had a boyfriend.
Hmm.
The actor?
Doing a little
background on me, huh?
Well, that boyfriend
is no more.
Long story.
I look forward to hearing
about it over dinner.
♪ How you finish,
finish, finish ♪
♪ Ain't saying it's easy
You know we don't have class
tonight, right?
Right. I-I just --
I needed some help.
I'm not gonna write
your paper for you.
No. No. I-I was hoping maybe you
could tell me whatto write.
I've spent the last two days
talking to cops about
whether I should've
identified myself,
and the answers have ranged from
"probably not" to "no way."
But...I am struggling
with how betrayed
my classmates felt.
So, I just...need a little
outside perspective.
You should've
said something.
I'm sure there are
a dozen reasons why cops think
that your job is
a need-to-know thing,
but come on.
It's 2021.
You guys have a hell of a lot
to make up for.
So, you want to
win back trust?
You gotta assume a higher level
of responsibility.
You gotta go the extra mile
every single time.
You think I have a chance
to mend some fences here?
Yeah. I do.
Everyone in this classroom
wants to change the system,
and they're driven by hope
and a ton of anger.
But hope is what keeps them
moving forward.
So if they see that
you're serious
about being part of
the change,
they'll let you back in.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
♪ The beginning
That's so -- I --
I should've
written that down.
What was the part
in the beginning,
when you said that...
You know what?
I -- I got it.
It's -- Thank you very much.
It's good stuff.
Oh, and they always want us
to go undercover as strippers.
Harper: Yes!
As if our bodies are
the only thing we have.
Yes.
Well, actually,
my -- my body does have
magical powers,
butit does,
a lot of the times,
feel like, as a female UC,
that they just want to
get you naked
for the guys in the van.
Mm-hmm, so that they can
drool over you
in a cloud of their own farts.
I don't think I can use
any of this for my paper.
Okay. Alright.
What -- What exactly
do you need to know?
Women have been cops
in the LAPD
over 100 years now,
but does it still feel like
you have to act like a man
to fit in?Good question.
Well, you're the rookie,
the last one in.
What do you think?
Um...
Mm, I think...
I think fitting in
is a trap.
I'm sitting between two of
the best cops in the state...
Mm....who had to navigate
an avalanche of obstacles
just to get to the mountaintop.
They didn't do it
by trying to fit in.
They did it by --
you know, by, um...
being stronger, smarter,
more agile.
They had to to navigate
a system that still believes
being a girl is inherently
soft or weak,
as though empathy
is somehow a liability.
There isn't a guy
in the force
who can do what these guys
can do.
Mm.
And there sure as hell
isn't anyone tougher.
Hoo!
I will drink to that.
Hell yeah.
--Captions by VITAC--
♪♪
Damn it!