Jackson:
Last day of training.
Last day of Tim
barking orders.
Last day that they can fire us
at a moment's notice.
Last day of them recording
every flaw for posterity.
It's kind of
bittersweet.
Nope.
Just sweet.
[ Chuckles ]
Sorry. Sorry.
Guys,
stop apologizing.
You guys have
finally made it,
and I will be
right behind you.
Look, the extra month
will fly by.
You know it.
Now, is Tim gonna do
anything special
to memorialize
your last shift together?
Not knowingly.
You know,
when you move on
from an important
relationship,
there are steps you should take
to ensure a healthy parting.
We are going to work through
every single one of them.
Uh, how, if he doesn't know
you're doing it?
Trickery.
Bye.
That's...
Yeah.
Who are yougonna ride with
today?
No idea.
Grey's busy, and Smitty's
getting a back tattoo.
That's --
Yeah. Don't ask.
So, we are out of TOs,
and I'm guessing
I'm finishing my rookie year
at the front desk.
Huh.
Lopez: Boot.
Where's our gear?
Wait, what?
We started this journey
together.
I think we should end it
that way.
Don't you?
Yeah.
Then let's go.
♪♪
I thought we were tight.
You did?
Um, we are.
That's --
I mean, why? What?
You told
your ethics professor
she should come for
a ride along?
No.
Mm.
We -- No.
We didn't even,
uh, discuss it,
but I-I need to
pass this class,
so it's super important
she doesn't get shot today.
No promises.
You ride with me, you ride
the roller coaster.
Okay, Nyla, I know that --
Hi. Good morning.Good morning.
Uh, Professor Ryan, this is
Detective Nyla Harper,
my training officer.
I'm told
you're gonna be going
on a ride along
with us today.
I hope that's okay.
I didn't want to put you in an
awkward position by asking you,
but your watch commander said
that you'd feel cheated
if I didn't
ride with you, so...
And he was right.
[ Chuckles ]
Uh, shall we?Mm.
Okay.
Harper: So, you, uh,
sign all the paperwork
that says that
we are not liable
if you are maimed
or killed?
I did. It seemed
a bit excessive.
Mm.
No, it's not.
I mean, we will try our best
to protect you,
but we cannot guarantee
your safety.
You will be exposed to all
the same dangers that we are.
Well, more farmers die yearly
than cops do.
I didn't have to sign
a liability waiver
to go apple picking.
That's because you weren't
picking them
out of a wood chipper.
Nolan: Uh, hey,
have you ever seen
a body camera up close?
No.
Well, they're
always running,
uh, until
we actually need them.
We switch them on,
then they start recording,
and they go back
two minutes
so we can catch any of that
last-minute action.
Oh, yet they're
always broken
whenever the cops
cross the line.
You'd be surprised
how many police officers
actually want
a body camera.
Oh.
That way,
it makes it easier to
disprove complaints.
Okay,
then you will not mind
if I record
the ride along myself --
as research tool.
No problem.
[ Chuckles ]
Just as long as you
turn it off
when we hit the strip club
for the lunch buffet.
She's kidding.
That buffet is terrible
at that strip club.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh Ready to go?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
[ Cameras beeping ]
You got yours on?
Yeah.
Alright.
It's our last shift
together.
It's crazy, huh?
Not really.
Come on.
I mean, we've been ridingshoulder to shoulder
for over a year now.[ Engine starts ]
And soon, there'll be a new
rookie sitting in that seat,
annoying the crap out of me
for 12 hours a day.
So, you're not gonna missriding with me at all?
It's a job,
not happy hour.
Mm. Denial. Check.
What?
Hmm?
Nothing.
♪♪
So, you teach
full time?
No. Just nights
and weekends.
My day job is
civil rights litigation.
And then there's lecturing,
the writing,
the cable news hits.
When do you sleep?
Sleep?
What's that?
Oh, is that what you were doing
in my class on Monday?
[ Chuckles ]
What?
No. Uh, no.
Sometimes, I just --
I hold a blink
for a really long time.
You sure lying to your teacher
is the way to go here?
Actually, now that
I hear it out loud,
I'd like to revise my answer.
Yeah. Uh-huh.[ Chuckles ]
So, uh, given how busy
you are,
why take the time
for a ride along?
Well, I'm finishing up a book
on the future of policing.
Hey, what would you say is
the, uh, biggest challenge
you face day to day?
Finding
a safe bathroom.
Uh, that is --
that is true.
I mean, we can't use a stallbathroom for safety reasons.
The door has to go
floor to ceiling.
And the location of thebathroom, also very important,
so that not a lot of peoplecan see us entering and leaving.
[ Radio static crackles ]
Dispatch: 7-Adam-15,
residential burglary alarm,
1330 Monrovia.
Hundred bucks it's
an accidental trigger.
That is a hard pass.
[ Chuckles ]She's -- She's kidding.
No. No way we'd blow off
a service call.
[ Radio beeps ]
Copy. Responding.
[ Static crackles ]
Lucy: Do you see yourself
as my mentor?
No. I'm your TO.
It's my job to make sure you're
not dangerously incompetent
when you hit the streets withoutsupervision tomorrow.
You know,
when I was a rookie,
I couldn't wait
to get off probation.
Oh, I am excited.
Believe me.
But I also know the importanceof acknowledging your loss
when going throughsomething like this.
"Acknowledging
your loss"?
Hmm.
What is this, some
"Intro to Psych" closure BS?
It's not BS.
It's a widely used
psychological model
to help people cope withthe end of a relationship.
Relationship?
Partnership.
Mentorship.
Whatever you want tocall it.
Look, I don't want to
call it anything.
It's not like you won't see me
tomorrow at the station.
You know, what's there
to talk about?
A lot.
I have a list.
So...
A list?
You know, littering isa $250 fine.
Worth it.
What are you smiling
about?
Well, we were at denial,
but now we have movedto anger.
That's more progress.
Thank you.
[ Radio chatter ]
Gets me out of
the office.
I mean,
not just for today.
I mean, you could have
bounced me from the program
after that first day.
I owe you my career.
♪ I confess,
don't hate the playa... ♪
I'd settle for a sandwich.We're near Phillipe's.
But you just
had breakfast.
You questioning
the pregnant lady?
[ Chuckling ] No, ma'am.
No, ma'am.
What?
You're gonna be a mom.
And?
I don't know.
I mean...
a lot's happened since
we started out together.
I knew my TO would be
important to my career,
but...I don't know.
I didn't realize how important
you'd be to my life.
♪ They might shine,but when they lights go out... ♪
Lay off the sappy stuff.I'm nauseous enough as it is.
[ Chuckles ]
Fiona: Have you read
my work?
I have.
I actually follow you
on social media.
Oh. And?
I'd make a lot of the reforms
you're pushing for,
but some just aren't
based in reality.
Well, maybe not
your reality.
Look, either you want
my opinion or you don't.
If you are just here to confirm
your own point of view,
then I-I will stop
engaging.
No, no, no, no.
That's not what I'm looking for.
I-I'm just used to copstaking my head off
any time I suggestchanging the status quo.
So...
Well, you would be
surprised
how many cops actually know
the system has to change,
but just feel powerless
to make it happen.
Hmm.
[ Door closes ]
Homeowner set off the alarm
accidentally.
Hundred bucks.
Just put it on my tab.
So, you two
getting along? Huh?
My two teachers?
Mm.
Yeah.
We're bonding
by making fun of you.
Oh. Outstanding.Let me get in on that.
Have you noticed
how much I've been
saying "like" lately?
[ Alarm beeping ]
Child abduction.
Suspect is drivinga gold Tacoma truck.
Plate number
2-Queen-Robert-Ida-4-4-5.
Victim was kidnapped from...
City of Angels Hospital.
How old?
Uh...five hours.
Here we go.
[ Engine starts ]
[ Rotor blades whirring ]
Air Three
is lifting now.
I'm 10-9-7.
Searching forthe suspect vehicle.
Uh, newborn baby girlwent missing 20 minutes ago.
The hospital is going overthe surveillance footage.
Wait, don't all babies
get LoJack these days?
Yeah, it was found inthe elevator, cut off.
Who owns the Tacoma?
Uh, that would bethe father -- Jared Young.
Looks like they're going through
a messy divorce.
He was visiting the hospitalearlier that day,
but security had him leave.
There may have beensome kind of threat.
So, what, he went back in
and he just took the baby?
Jared's got quite an extensivecriminal history here.
Lot of narcos --uh, narco possession,
possession to sell,under the influence.
Mm, just the guy you want
taking care of your newborn.
Well, we got the whole citylooking for him.
He won't get far.
So, this baby that the, uh,
whole city is mobilized
to find --
is she by any chance white?
We issue plenty of
Amber Alerts
for children of color,
as well.
Do you have a kid?
Daughter.
And, uh, you're sure
your daughter
would get the same attention
as his son?
From the media? No.
But out here, we --
we look just as hard.
Mrs. Young,this is Detective Lopez.
I'm out heresearching for your baby.
Mrs. Young: [ Voice breaking ]
You have to find her.
Yes, ma'am,we're doing everything we can,
but I need your help.
Is there any place your husbandmight take her?
He lives in Bell Gardens.
Yes, ma'am.
We have officers on the wayto his apartment now,
but if he's not there,
where would he be?
Out buying drugs,
if he has any money.
And if he's not?
Jared will do anything
to get a fix,
including selling our baby.
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
Gold pickup,
two blocks up.
[ Tires squealing,
engine revving ]
♪♪
Negative.
Texas plates.
Five hours old.
That poor mother must begoing out of her mind.
Let me guess --
you think if the parents
had properly
worked through
their separation,
this whole thing
could have been avoided?
No. Mom needs to get as far awayfrom him as possible.
But I do think that havingeasier access
to counselingand mental health resources
could preventsituations like this.
Sure. But most guys
still wouldn't go.
Yeah, because we stigmatizemental health,
treat it as less importantthan physical health.
It's ridiculous that they teachsex ed in schools,
but not how to be
in a relationship.
I wish someone taught me
how to be in this one.
Oh, so we are
in a relationship.
So, what's the focusof your book?
Uh, reinventing policing --
with a more limited
mandate.
Amen to that.
You agree with taking resourcesaway from police?
If it lessens our load,
then yes, absolutely.
Yeah, we complain about itall the time.
Police have become the catch-allfor the city's problems.
We're expected to be cops,
uh, psychologists,
social workers, teachers,
mediators.
And they only train us
for one of those jobs.
Gold truck.
Two cars ahead.
That's him.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
We have eyes onthe Amber Alert suspect vehicle.
Heading west on Pico,
passing Westlake.
7-Adam-19, inbound on Olympic,passing Ardmore.
7-Adam-07, coming west fromWilshire and Rimpau --
moving to intercept
from the front.
Air Three responding.Heading west from Bell Gardens.
ETA to your location --
approximately six minutes.
Can you parallel suspect
until I get eyes on?
Affirmative.
Parallel?
Yeah, we follow on side streets
and alleyways.
Oh, so he doesn't spot you
and run?
Exactly.
Last thing we want
is him speeding through trafficwith a baby in the car,
especially since
there's no way
he's got an infant car seatin there.
No, we'll just wait untilwe have enough units,
and then we'll
box him in.
Intersection ahead.
We still have him?
Yeah, he's about half a carlength ahead,
but he's speeding up.
He might've seen usbefore we made our turn.
♪♪
7-Adam-19,
Maxwell and Pico.
West of target --waiting for him to pass.
Suspect just went past.Speed -- 50 miles an hour.
We'll move to parallel
on the north.
Copy that.
Why not just set up
a roadblock?
Roadblocks are considereda lethal measure.
Didn't know that.
Yeah,there's a strong chance
a desperate driverwill ram a roadblock.
Clear!
We don't use them unlesswe have no other choice.
Come on, come on.Watch out, watch out!
[ Tires screech ]
I can't see
around the truck.
Move it!
I got it.
Move! Hey!I got it after this car.
Hold on. There we go.Got it.
Do you see him?No.
Well, maybe -- maybe he turned
around when we got stuck.
7-Adam-19,
we've lost visual.
You got eyes on him?
Negative.We haven't reacquired visual.
Where the hell
is that airship?
Pilot: Air Three is overhead.
Arriving on scene.
What's the suspect's 20?
We lost visual.
Pico, east of Maxwell.
It's possible he turned off andheaded either north or south.
Copy that.
We're gonna orbit.
♪♪
Contact.
Suspect vehicle now heading
north on Livingston.
Repeat,
Copy. On our way.
Speed is
approximately 65.
Looks like he's heading
for the freeway.
[ Tires screech ]
Hold on.
Suspect just sideswiped
another vehicle.
He's lost control.
[ Car crashes ]
Tell me that wasn't
our guy.
He just TC'd into
a telephone pole.
Can you see
inside the truck?
Negative.
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
[ Tires squealing ]
[ Brakes screech ]
Harper: Hands!Nolan: Police!
Show me your hands!
Where is your daughter?
Jared: What?
Nolan: Keep your hands
where we can see them.
No kid.
There's no kid in here!
There's no kid!
Your baby,
where is she?
At the hospital
with her mom.
Lucy:
Then why did you run?
Tim: Gun and drugs.
Fiona: If he doesn't have
the baby, who does?
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
Never thought
I'd be disappointed
a meth-head wasn't
taking care of a newborn.
But I guess there's still
plenty of time
for him to mess up
this kid's childhood,
once we get her back.
Ifwe get her back.
[ Radio chatter ]
You know, whenever you need
Halloween costumes
for Lopez Jr.,
my mom has dozens
in storage.
I'm talking cop uniforms
for every age.
You never really wanted to beanything else?
Astronaut? Ninja?
Ninja astronaut?
[ Chuckles ]
I mean, that'd be cool,
but...mnh-mnh.
No.
I guess I just
wanted to be my dad.
It was like my way of
feeling close to him
when he wasn't around.
Was that a lot?
Yeah.
I mean, he was a detective
when I was born,
trying to make a name
for himself.
Lot of long hours.
But you were close.
Yeah, eventually.
Mom was kind of on her own
until I was 12.
And that's when he moved up,
got more stable hours.
Mm.
I mean,
I always loved him --
don't get me wrong --
even when he wasn't around.
I have a lot of
great memories, you know?
Of course.
You know, you and Wesley are
going to be awesome parents.
I know.
It's just...
We both get so wrapped up
in our cases,
we barely make timeto have dinner together.
How are we supposed tomake time for a kid?
Wesley is loaded.
You get yourself a nanny.
Or three.
So a stranger
can raise my child?
I mean,
it won't be a stranger
when you get to know them,
you know?
Look, you are not
the first detective
to have to balance work
with a kid.
Talk to Harper
about how she did it.
Lopez: Harper, can you ten-three
to a backup channel?
Sure, go to 11.
Don't record this.
[ Camera clicks off ]
I need you to give methe reals on something.
How difficult was it
to go back to work
after Lila was born?
Honestly,
I barely remember.
I almost died
giving birth, so...
But, uh, that's -- that's not
gonna happen to you.
G-Giving birth can be
a wonderful experience,
I've been told.
Definitely get
the epidural.
Don't worry.
I'm not a lunatic.
I'm thinking of scheduling a C,but I'm worried
that the stitches
and everything
will keep me off workeven longer.
I worried about the same thing,but you know what?
I got stitches anyway --
just not in my stomach.
Okay. Change us back
to channel one.
Wh-- I-I-- I thinkI want to hear this.
Tell me the truth --
Am I gonna poop myself?
And I'm out.
Wow.
[ Chuckles ]
I wish I could say no.
Why can't we just do thattwilight sleep thing
they did back in the '50s?
[ Chuckles ]
I asked.
Apparently it is
"grossly unethical."
Sgt. Grey: Detectives,
are you done?
Both: Yes, sir.
We must seem callous,
joking while a kid is missing.
No, I get it.
I'm sure it's hard
to work
these kinds of cases.
Calls involving kidsare the worst.
You can't help but think,what if they were mine?
Mm.
Yeah,
I don't have kids,
but I feel the same way
every time another Black kid
gets shot by police.
[ Computer beeps ]
Oh. Hospital sentthe video of the kidnapping.
You can't see her face.
Lopez:
That is just terrifying.
A stranger
snatching your baby
when you're not thereto protect them.
Don't worry.
I will personally
stand watch over your kid
until you leave
the hospital.
You better.
Do they have an ID
on the kidnapper?
Not yet.
Listen to me.
We're gonna find her,
alright?
And that baby's
gonna be fine.
You'll see.
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
We don't have time
for this.
Every minute we waste waitingfor an ID on this woman
is a minute she could behurting this kid --
or worse.
Look, you need to
get your head right
in case this goes bad.
I'm squared away.
The fact that you just said that
means you're not.
Look, you've been lucky
on the job so far.
No. Alright.
I'm sorry. That --
That came out wrong.
You've been through Hell --
stuff that would've broken
a lot of veteran cops.
But a dead kid
is different.
A dead kid
changes you forever.
[ Sighs ]
I really hopeour last shift together
doesn't end with that.
Yeah. Me too.
[ Radio chatter ]
Okay, so what's next
on your list?
[ Inhales sharply ]
Okay.
"Surround yourself with people
who support, value,
and energize you,"
which...may have to waituntil later.
Then, uh, "Reflect onthe lessons learned --
both the good and the bad --and express gratitude."
Okay.
So, what have I taught you
that you're grateful for?
Um...hmm.
Not to second-guess
myself.
Yeah, early on,
one look from youcould send me into a tailspin.
Plain Clothes Day.
Mm-hmm.
But I've learned to trustmy instincts,
even if they go againstwhat you would do,
which will be crucialfor undercover work.
You serious about
being UC?
Yeah.
Why? Do you not think
I'm tough enough?
No, it's not about
being tough.
I mean, look,
you're as tough as they come.
It's just
you're...sensitive.
[ Scoffs ]
You are!
Look what happened
with Tamara.
You gave her your car,
for crying out loud.
And today --
today, this whole need
to relive the last year,
talk about
our feelings.
I happen to thinkthat caring about people,
connecting with them,is what makes me a good cop.
It does.
Just not a good UC.
Look, to work undercover,
you have to be able to lie
to someone's face --
make them believe
you're their best friend
and then stab them
in the back.
I just don't think you have
that killer instinct.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
But it's better
you hear it now.
[ Radio chatter,
siren wailing in distance ]
You're right.
And I appreciate
your honesty.
You always tell me
the truth,
no matter how painfulit's gonna be,
and you deserve the samefrom me.
I've been struggling withbeing honest with you all day.
I've been hiding behindthis stupid closure checklist,
trying to get up the courageto tell you something.
Okay.
What?
I have feelings
for you.
Uh, like f--Look, we've been througha lot this year.
I mean...
you saved my life.
And I didn't want tosay anything before
because I didn't want toput you in a weird position.
But now, I mean,
I think...
I think the reason why you'reso protective of me and --
and why you don't want meto be an undercover cop
is because...
...because you havefeelings for me, too.
Lucy, I --
No, listen, I-I know
it's complicated.
You're my TO.
You're responsible
for me.
I know that you would nevercross that line, but...
starting tomorrow, I guess...you're not,
and I...
Uh -- Eh --
First of all...
I-I just, like --
Thank you.
Um...you're...
Look, Lucy,
I'm -- I'm flattered.
I am.
You're a great girl.
Woman. Woman.
And I...
Um...
[ Sighs ]
Crap.
Listen.
[ Laughing ]
Are you kidding me?!
I'm sorry!
Are you kidding me?
Wait, I'm sorry.
Oh, you're sorry.
Wait. Just wait.
Lie to your face --
check.
Make you thinkI've fallen for you --
double check.
Oh, and stab you
in the back
when you thinkwe're best friends --
triple check.
Look me in the face...
Nope.
...and tell me
you don't thinkI have the killer instinct
to do undercover work.
Look me in my face.
♪♪
[ Radio chatter ]
It's weird now,
isn't it?
Nope.
I was just
making a point.
And you're undermining it
by feeling guilty.
Harper:
You're out of your mind.
You want to try
the Camden Experiment
in Los Angeles?
I'm sorry. What's
the Camden Experiment?
Uh, fire
all police officers,
make them reapply
for their jobs.
Oh, just that?
[ Chuckles ]
Well, you're both good cops.
You'd be back on the force
in no time.
But running new backgroundchecks on every single officer,
most especially combing through
their social media posts --
that'll get rid of
most of the problem.
We'd be coming back to
a gutted force.
I mean,
you would be down 10%.
Maybe 20%.
But you would be coming back to
a betterforce.
And what about the kid
that goes missing
the day we're all fired?
I mean, it wouldn't happen
overnight.
It would happen gradually,
in stages.
But without major action,
things will neverget better.
Sgt. Grey: 7-Adam-15,
we have a possible suspect ID
on the Amber Alert.
Last name Cissane,
first name Rita.
Suspect's husband called 911.
Make contact
to take his statement.
Address is being sent
to your box.
Copy that. We got it.
On our way.
Ethan: Yeah, if, uh --
i-if she reaches out,
um, please, please,
please, please call me.
Um...okay. Yeah, no.
I-I gotta go.
Mr. Cissane,
I'm Detective Harper.
This is Officer Nolan.
I understand that your wife,
Rita, was here with a baby?
Yeah, I-I don't --
I don't know where she is.
I-I tried calling
everyone that I know.
I-I tried to stop her
from leaving,
but she was holding that baby,
and it was...just so little.
I know. They can look
so fragile at that age.
Uh, tell us about
your wife.
Is there anything that could
have precipitated this?
You don't know?
W-We lost our daughter, Casey,
this morning to SIDS.
Rita went into the nursery
to check on her,
and then I heard screaming,
so I ran in,
and she was so still...
s-so cold.
I am so sorry.
Sir, h-how old was she?
[ Crying ] Two months.
That's why your wife was
at the hospital today?
Yeah, we -- we raced Casey
to the Emergency Room,
hoping that they could do
something, but it was --
it was too late.
And then there was so many, uh,
questions and -- and forms.
It took me a while to realize
that, um, that Rita had left.
She wasn't answering her cell,
so I thought maybe s-she --
she came home,
but she wasn't here,
and then she just showed up
like nothing had happened,
and she was just...
holding this little baby
and calling her Casey
and saying that everything had
been a big mistake.
[ Sniffles ]
Okay, uh, we're gonna
have to initiate
Child Death Protocol.
Treat the place
like a crime scene.
Notify Homicide,
the District Attorney, and CPS.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
We didn't kill our daughter.
It was -- It was --
It was SIDS.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
I'm not saying that we believe
that you harmed your child,
but we do have protocols
we have to follow.
Eh, sir, it's --
the hard fact is
what most people consider
to be SIDS
is actually accidental
suffocation
from soft bedding
or a toy.
Uh, right now, we have to
focus on your wife.
Is there anywhere you think
she might have gone?
I don't know.
I've reached out to everyone
I can think of,
but she's not really
herself right -- right now.
Has she been depressed
lately?
Yeah. I mean, she hasn't been
eating or sleeping.
The doctor said she had,
um...PPD,
but Rita refused any help.
Uh, has she been
drinking a lot?
Any drugsor medication?No.
No, the doctor prescribed
antidepressants,
but Rita wouldn't take them.
I'm just so scared that --
Thank you, sir.Okay, thank you.
Please don't hurt her.
She's not herself right now.[ Car doors open, close ]
You have to promise me that
you won't hurt her, please.
[ Engine starts ]
[ Sobbing ]
♪♪
Updated Amber Alert.
New suspect vehicle isa green Ford Fiesta.
License plate3-Paul-Charles-Ida-0-2-6.
Suspect is Rita Cissane.
31-year-old white femalewho lost her baby to SIDS.
This case is all the nightmaresin my closet combined.
I know. Sorry.
How am I ever gonna let my kid
out of my sight?
With all the things we seeon the job,
the -- the things I knowabout people --
Look, the things we see
are outliers.
Look, every day, we show up
on people's worst day.
We see the exception,
not the rule.
I know that up here,but --
Look, whether the kid is with
you or Wesley or a nanny,
they'll be fine, okay?
It's just so differentfrom the way I grew up.
Wesley was raised
by a nanny.
But when my mom went to work,she put me in the back room,
and the other womenwould check in on me.
Can't exactly drop off Lopez Jr.in Holding every morning.
[ Chuckles ]
I don't know.
Smitty is
surprisingly maternal.
[ Chuckles ]
That is the most horrifying idea
I've ever heard...
and I want it to bea reality show so bad.
Right? I would watch
the hell out of that.
Rita is negativeon any previous 5150 holds,
and there are no registeredfirearms in her name.
If this woman's doctor couldn't
get through to her,
how will you?
I-I mean,
this woman is in crisis.
She needs a psychiatrist.
Yeah, but the baby
needs a cop.
The honest truth is wedon't have enough information
to know what
we're dealing with.
But that's every call.
It's a constant struggleto figure things out
before it's too late.
Uh, 7-Adam-19,
go to channel nine.
Go for 7-Adam-19.
Did you studypostpartum depression
in your psych major?
Yeah. PPD is fairly common,affects 1 in 8 new moms.
In most cases, they feel tired,
alone, guilty.
Some feel a lack of attachmentand then guilt
for not feeling attached.
Some are overwhelmed by paranoia --
visions of horrible thingshappening to their own child.
I see Rita turned downtreatment.
That tells me she's probably  dealing with shame,
trying to cope alone,isolating.
Now add to that
the trauma
of finding her childunresponsive.
That could precipitatea mental break.
If it's an extreme case of PPD,which is rare,
she could be thinking aboutharming herself or her baby.
Tim. Green Fiesta.
Plates match.
That's our car.
Nolan, we found
Rita's car.
21000 block of Manningham.
On our way.
Let's go.
♪♪
Lucy: Control, 7-Adam-19,
we've located the Fiesta from
the revised Amber Alert.
21000 block of Manningham.
[ Pleasant music plays
on stereo]No sign of suspect or child.
It's still hot.
She must have just ditched it.
Man: Hey. You looking
for the driver?
Tim: Yeah, you see
where she went?
Nah. I was walking by
when she parked on the curb.
How long ago?About five minutes.
Enough time for Butch and I
to circle the block.
Did she have
a baby with her?
No idea.
I just watched her
totally demolish
that parking spot.
[ Laughs ] Reminded me
of my ex-wife.
Uh, yes, sir.
Please call us
if you remember
anything else.
Okay.
Control, 7-Adam-19, I got
the vehicle, unoccupied.
Witness says the suspect hereless than five minutes ago.
She's on foot.
We need backup
and an airship
to secure
a 10-block radius
for a grid search.
♪♪
I don't like this.
She wouldn't have abandoned
the car
unless she stopped
for a reason.
Odds are it won't be
a good one.
We gotta find her fast.
This is crazy.
There's no way we find her
and the baby in time.
We've got multiple units
and an airship searching.
We will find them.
How? They could be
anywhere.
No. On foot with a newbornand a five-minute head start,
she's definitely withinour grid.
Someone will have seen her.
Just...pray we find her beforeshe does something rash.
♪♪
Up on the right.
[ Siren chirps ]
Not her.
Can I make a suggestion?
Of course.
Would it be helpful to have
Rita's husband
brought down here
for -- for when she's found?
That could be
dangerous.
We don't know what the situationwas like at the house,
and even if the baby's death
truly was accidental,
there could have been
marital issues
that added to Rita's PPD.
We'd be introducing
a wildcard
to an already tenuoussituation.
Wait, so it's all on you?
I mean, no matter what you find
when you get to her,
you have to be ready to
deal with it?
What -- What if you make
a mistake?
We have to live with it.
If we can.
Pilot: All units, Air Three has
eyes on the suspect.
Fourth Street Bridge.
Repeat --
She has the baby.
She's standing at the railing.
Possible jumper.
Repeat, possible jumper.
Here we go.
Control, advise Fire we have
a possible jumper
on Fourth Street Bridge.
See if they havea crash pad available.
We'll also need RA andbackup units, Code 2 high.
♪♪
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
[ Car doors close ]
Maybe I should
stay back.
Uh, it's up to you,
but a friendly face
not in uniform
might actually calm
the situation.
How do you want to
play this?
You go talk to her.
You sure?
Yeah, I'll step in
if I need to.
W-Why -- Why Nolan?
He has a way of connecting with
people in crisis situations.
Hi, Rita.
I'm John.
[ Baby crying ]
How do you know
my name?
Uh, Ethan told me.
He's very worried
about you.
I'm fine.
Who's that
you got there?
Casey.
This is Casey.
Oh.
Casey looks
a little bit cold.
Why don't we bring her inside,
off the bridge?
No.
She's fine with
her mama.
Do you mind if I just
make sure?
Stay back.
Okay, yeah.
I'll stay back.
We -- We can just talk.
Lucy: How's she doing?
Uh, it's touch and go.
What do you need?Keep them back.
We don't want to
spook her.
Okay.Nolan: No, I know it can
feel isolating,
being a parent to
a newborn...
She's not looking at
the baby.
Nolan:
...so much to learn.
[ Baby fusses ]You never feel like
what you're doing...
She's trying to
convince herself
that it's her baby
she's holding.
Yeah. Deep down inside,
she knows it's not.
What happens when
she figures out the truth?
It's hard to say
for sure.
It could break the spell or it
could send her over the edge,
literally.
Control, what's the ETA
on Fire?
Dispatch: Three minutes.
Might as well be
three hours.
Nolan: Are you thirsty,
Rita?
I can get you
some water.
Nolan.
Can I talk to her?
Hey, Rita, I'm gonna
introduce you
to my friend,
Angela, okay?
Okay.
Hi, Rita.
I'm here to help.
Is this Casey?
Yes.
I love that name.
My fiancé and I can't agree
on a name for our baby.
How did you choose?
I don't know.
When she was born, she just
looked like a Casey.
[ Baby fussing ]
How far along are you?
14 weeks.
I'm already scared
about giving birth.
The pain.
Don't worry about
the pain.
Once they put your baby
in your arms
and you look down into
those beautiful eyes,
it was all worth it.
I heard all newborns
have blue eyes.
Not Casey.
Dark brown,
right from the start.
The most amazing
head of hair.
I hope
if I have a daughter,
she's born with hair.
My cousin's little girl,
she was bald
for like the first
18 months.
Everyone thought
she was a boy.
I love putting
Casey's hair
in little pigtails.
She always fights me,
but she looks so cute.
Rita, can you do something
for me?
Can you look at Casey?
Just look in those pretty,
brown eyes.
[ Baby crying ]
No.
Please, Rita.
I need you to
look in her eyes.
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
[ Crying continues ]
It's not Casey,
is it?
[ Voice breaking ] No.
No.
Here. I got her.
I'll get her back to
her mother, okay?
Tell her [Sniffles]
I'm sorry.
Nolan:
Thank you, Rita.
That was a very brave thingyou did,
and now I need youto come with me, okay?
My baby died.
I know.
I'm so sorry.
[ Sobbing ]
Come on. Come on.
[ Baby cooing ]
♪♪
[ Engine shuts off ]
Well, thank you
for today.
This is an experience
I will not forget.
Well, we should schedule
another one of theselittle ride alongs
so that we can continuethe conversation.
Oh, that won't be
necessary.
[ Camera clicks off ]
The book's already written,
isn't it?
I sent it to my publisher
last week.
Mm.
What?
Then what was today about,
then?
Just an anecdote
for the book tour?
No, I didn't know the day was
gonna end up the way it did.
But how do you write a book
about policing
without having seen it
up close?
Oh, I have seen it.
Believe me.
Today may have been
my first ride along,
but it was not my first time
sitting in the back seat
of a cop car.
I see, but if you're going to
fix an engine,
don't you think it would be
helpful to look under the hood?
That is a flawed analogy,
Officer Nolan,
because a car is not
actively trying to
keep you from fixing it.
Uh, excuse me.
Look, I get that the path
to real change
seems almost impossible.
I mean, police departments are
pros at circling the wagons
when public opinion
turns against them.
But I promise you,
the only way
things really will change
is if cops get on board.
I agree.
But cops only act when activists
make so much noise,
they cannot be ignored.
Like in Camden.
Look, you're talking to
two police officers
who would like to
see things change,
and we're not the only ones at
the station that feels this way.
I just think that...
uh, maybe you could benefit
from some of our insights.
Alright.
You sold me.
Great.
I'll tell Sergeant Grey.
I'm sure he'd love to
be part of the conversation.
Oh, thank you.
And thank you both for
the ride along.
I will see you in class.
Looking forward.
I think that went well,
all things considered.
Oh, yeah. No, she's definitely
gonna give you an "A."
-You think?
-No.
She is gonna make you earn it
in class,
like the rest of
her students.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
You have any plans for
the rest of the night?
Hugging my daughter
until she is sick of it
and then hugging hersome more.
Sounds nice.
Nolan.
I'll see you tomorrow.Alright.
Sir.
Well?
How'd it go
with Professor Ryan?
Good, I think.
She's gonna be calling you to
talk about, uh, police reform --
for her book.
[ Chuckles ]
You point her my way to get back
at me for the ride along?
No, sir. No.
I just know
how committed you are
to making things better.
Even if it does mean having to
admit you're wrong to do it.
Oh. Uh, I'm sorry?
When was I ever wrong?
Well, nothing comes to
mind off hand.
I guess there was that one time
you said if I succeeded,
your house would be
"flooded with middle-aged losers
looking for an 'Eat Pray Love'
path to reinvention."
I wrote it down.
You haven't succeeded yet,
Officer Nolan.
Yes, sir.
Good night, sir.
Good night.
Lopez: Can't wait to get out
of this uniform.
Hey, thanks again for
riding with me.
Are you kidding me?
I wouldn't have missed it
for the world.
And now
it's end of shift,
and you are no longer
a rookie.
[ Exhales deeply ]
How does it feel?
Unreal.
I mean, everything in my life
has been geared towards
getting me to this moment,
and...now it's here.
Kinda can't believe it,
to be honest.
Well, congratulations.
You earned it.
♪ I couldn't see the forest
for the trees ♪
♪ Too many empties on the side
♪ But I kept trading all
my cigarettes for sunsets ♪
♪ Now I'm getting richer
all the time ♪
We did it.
No. Youdid it.
What's this?
It's a copy of
your final evaluation.
I wrote it
before our shift today.
Like Plain Clothes Day.
Only this time,
I didn't have to rewrite it.
Mm.
♪ I'll be young before I die
"Officer Chen impressed me
with every decision she made
today.
I will miss
riding with her."
♪ I'll be wrong before
I'm right ♪
♪ I keep filling up
my crowded heart, yeah ♪
You don't let anyone
ever tell you
you can't do something.
Not even me.
♪ Now all I see is the beauty
of the thunderstorm ♪
Yes, sir.
♪ Let it wash it all away [ Inhales deeply ]
Step five -- acceptance.
Our checklist is complete.
[ Chuckles ]
Um...I have
a gift for you.
It's a thank-you.
For every lesson
I had to learn.
Uh, should I open it now?
Absolutely.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
♪ I'll be dumb before I'm wise
[ Pop ]
♪ I'll be wrong
before I'm right ♪[ Chuckles ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Laughs ]
It's been a blast, sir.
I'll see you tomorrow...Lucy.
See you tomorrow, Tim.[ Door opens ]
♪ I will laugh and I will cry [ Door closes ]
[ Chuckles ]
Ready to celebrate?
You know it.
[ Chuckles ]
So, yeah. It was
the perfect way to end the year.
[ Indistinct conversation ]
Exactly.
Where you going?
Uh, home.
No, you're not.
You are coming to dinner
with Lila and me.
Uh, that's -- that's very nice
of you, but I'm okay.
No, you're not.
You feel like a failure
because they're moving on
and you're not.
But you will.
I appreciate that,
but you, uh,
certainly don't have to take me
to dinner out of pity.
It's not pity
when you're paying.
♪ I'll keep filling up...
W-Well, how can I say no
to that?
You can't.
I'm gonna go pick up
Lila.
Reservation is under my name
at Mercado.
And I expect a skinny margarita
waiting when I get there.
Yes, ma'am.
Mm-hmm.
And, um...
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[ Car door closes ]
-Official Movie downloading site: www.msmoviesbd.com --[Check it out]
♪♪