Previously on "The Rookie"...We're
not picking a name until B-day.
I had no idea you were
this superstitious.
I just wear a talisman
a drug lord gave me
to keep evil spirits away
from my unborn child.
Nice of you to see us off.
Gun!
Killing Cesar
would be unsatisfying.
But if Cesar's child
were to die --
We knew a gang war
was coming, right?
Which presents an opportunity.
You want me to go back in
as the chemist?
- No!
- You abducted me
when you know
what I have been through!
Do you still want this?
Yeah.
♪ Feel me
sneakin' around again ♪
Tell me.
My cover is Nova Lin,
former chemistry major
with a bent moral compass
and a fortune
in student loan debt.
Court records will show
you made bail yesterday,
and your cover
will be fully papered.
So you are back out in the wild
and open for business.
You will make camp at
the Hollywood Premiere Motel.
It is the bottom of the barrel,
the last branch you hit
on your way down,
and it will send the message
that you are desperate
to make money.
♪ My heart lies to you
Tell me the number-one rule
of undercover work.
No case is worth my life.
At any time
before the operation begins,
I have the authority
to pull the plug
and pull out of this op.
Once I'm out there
and things go sideways,
defend myself or run away.
There is no shame
in running away.
♪ I lie
Your mission is
to identify everyone
conspiring to manufacture
and distribute narcotics.
Stick to that objective.
Unless your targets are also
conspiring to commit murder,
make a mental note and move on.
Illegal weapons, stolen
property, cars -- ignore it.
You are not to take action
on misdemeanors
unless it advances this case.
Policy, procedure,
and the law --
those are your guidelines.
You can defend yourself.
You can defend others.
You can even use deadly force
without revealing your identity.
But whenever possible,
talk your way
out of a dangerous situation.
♪ I followed the waves to you
This isn't like
the deal we did with Coco.
This time, you'll be alone.
There is no surveillance van
outside.
There is no rescue team
next door.
Your only contact
will be with me,
making regular reports
at both 9:00 a.m. and midnight.
Now for the hard part.
At least it was for me, anyway.
Let me have it.
♪ Between my fire sighs
and my burning eyes ♪
♪ My heart burns wildly
in his eyes ♪
Final words,
and listen closely --
There is a chance
that nothing will happen,
that Salonga won't make contact,
and that the only thing
you will get
is a paid vacation
to the Hep C Motel.
But you can never...
...let down your guard.
Never relax.
Because if it comes,
when it comes,
you will have to do
everything right.
Because one wrong word,
one wrong move...
...one wrong look,
and you're dead.
Hello!
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm dog-sitting
for your neighbors,
and I kind of locked myself out.
- Here you go.
- Oh, my God. Yes.
Not sure how much time
you've spent in public
wearing only a towel,
but it's terrifying.
Um, did you want to come in?
You're not
a serial killer, are you?
Not that that wouldn't be
the perfect bookend
to this morning from hell.
Well, I'm actually
a police officer,
so the truth is, I'm --
I'm sworn to protect you.
Oh. Me, personally?
You, e-especially.
Uh, s-so, I-I'm imagining
the dog got out
while you were, uh,
getting into the shower?
That little ass
was sitting on the lawn,
staring at me
through the window.
So I threw on a towel,
went out to get him,
and, well, the rest is obvious.
Which house are you staying in?
- The green craftsman.
- Ronnie and Dylan's place.
I think they gave me
a spare key.
My luck is turning around.
I'm Bailey, by the way.
John. Uh, how do you know
Ronnie and Dylan?
I work with Ronnie.
- You're a firefighter.
- Yeah.
But you can't ever
tell Ronnie about this,
'cause the firehouse would never
let me live it down.
No problem.
It'll be our first secret.
I like that.
And I love your place.
Thank you.
I put a lot of work into it.
Well, you got skills.
You live here alone?
I do.
And I-I found it.
So, um, now, do you need
any help, uh, finding the dog?
No. He's back in the house.
I don't know how,
but when I got outside,
he was in the bathroom
staring at me.
And I swear that little bastard
was laughing.
To be honest, I-I've never
really cared for him.
Really?
- Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I mean, he's so cute,
but he so knows it.
I know.
Thank you for saving me.
I will return
the sweatshirt to you.
Uh, well, my shift ends at 8:00.
Maybe I could grab some takeout
on the way home.
We could spend dinner
plotting your revenge
against your canine nemesis.
I'd like that.
Then it's a date.
I'll wear my fancy towel.
Thanks again. Bye.
Your mom sent another stroller.
How many kids
does she think we're having?
Uh... Tim and Jackson are here.
Good morning.
There's bad news. And you think
a riot shield will save you.
Save us? N-No.
Protect us from major
bodily injury? Hopefully.
Must be really bad
if you brought Jackson.
I'm here
for my calming presence.
I mean, who can be angry
looking at that face?
What happened?
I got a call this morning
about Ralph Hall.
No.
Wait, why is that name familiar?
The feds, uh, discovered
that his venue was being used
as a cover for money laundering.
His venue?
Mm-hmm.
My venue.
-Our wedding venue. Yes.
And at 5:04 this morning,
it was...
seized by the FBI.
Angela.
Oh, it's over.
What? No, no, no.
We -- We can find another place.
No. We won't.
I'm done. We're getting married
Saturday at the courthouse.
Okay, we are not getting married
at the courthouse.
Then find someplace, but we're
getting married Saturday,
and I'm done thinking about it.
I don't need fancy.
I-I never needed fancy.
I just want to be married.
We're on it!
- We?
The war is over.
Word is, the last of Cesar's
lieutenants
have kissed La Fiera's ring
and joined Malos Dorados.
In less than two weeks,
Sandra de la Cruz has become
the second-biggest player
in Southern California.
And she is not slowing down.
We are hearing that any crew
that is unaffiliated
is getting pressured
to join her.
So talk to your street contacts
and your C.I.s.
Alert Narcotics
of any intel you collect.
-Where's Cesar? No one knows.
But Sandra's definitely
hunting him.
You know, if we could
get to him first,
we might be able to flip him.
Use his anger against La Fiera
to sabotage his old operation.
You are not the first
to think of that.
In fact, a task force has been
dedicated to finding him.
But if you think you can succeed
where they've failed,
- knock yourself out.
- Yes, sir.
Oh, and Smitty will be
your T.O. today.
Sarge, the kid only has
a few days left as a rookie --
I'm cool with letting him
ride solo today.
You are? Oh, well, I'm not.
- Worth a shot.
- Anything else?
Yes, sir.
Lopez's wedding is now Saturday.
And you are all
officially uninvited
unless you hear otherwise.
Spread the word.
Aw, come on.
Guys, it's a first marriage.
Okay. That's it.
Be safe out there.
Okay, so, the wedding
is now on Saturday,
which means we have two days
to plan and pull off a ceremony
and a reception.
Can you help?
Are you kidding?
I've been preparing for
this moment my whole life.
Y-Yeah, except it's got to be
what Angela wants.
Don't worry. I got that message
loud and clear.
But I could use some help.
Oh, well, we figured that,
so we hired you an elite team.
Powerpuff Girls could totally
take out the Avengers.
No. They don't exist
in the same universe.
That fight could never happen.
But it could, 'cause it's all
just made up anyway, right?
There are rules.
Okay. What's the problem?
Silas is being difficult.
Silas has autism, and rules help
him make sense of the world.
Tamara, Silas,
this is my mother, Patrice.
You'll be helping her today.
Are you okay
with that arrangement?
Oh, of course.
From the outfit,
Tamara clearly has good taste.
And Silas' attention to detail
will be a godsend.
Now, I don't know
about the two of you,
but I do my best work
with a beverage.
Maybe a little food
to go along with it?
Yes, please.
I could eat.
This just might work.
Mm-hmm.
If you were the entitled
but not too bright son
of a dead drug lord,
betrayed by your people
and hunted by apex predators,
where would you go?
Vegas.
Because?
I know I'm gonna die,
and I want to do it in Sin City.
Can't argue with that.
Smitty, can I ask you
a personal question?
I am currently single
and very open to being set up.
That's not -- I --
You must have wanted
more than this
at one point, right?
You had ambition, maybe?
When you were younger?
- You want the truth?
- I do.
Faulkner wrote, "You cannot swim
for new horizons
until you have courage
to lose sight of the shore."
I like the shore.
Look, I get it.
You want the stink of being
held back as a rookie off you.
And finding Cesar and flipping
him is the way to do it.
But how you gonna pull that off
as a rookie
with no street intel?
I'm gonna talk
to Cesar's girlfriend.
Half the department's
already taken a run at her.
Yeah, but I saved her life.
You don't look like
housekeeping.
Nova, right?
Like the star.
Who the hell are you?
Dahrio Salonga.
My brother sends his regards.
Aldo. Yeah,
I met the old man once.
It got me arrested.
Whatever you're here for,
it's a hard pass.
- We need a cook.
- A good one.
Who can make a lot of product.
Good quality product.
I said pass.
Your brother runs a leaky ship.
I'm not getting back on board.
Leak's been plugged.
Permanently.
Yeah, he went down ugly.
We even gave it a name --
The Sato Special.
See, I don't want to know that.
Just like I don't
want to know you.
Yeah, you do.
We've been watching you.
You're not exactly
on an upward trajectory.
Cooking for us
will get you paid.
- You've been watching me?
- Had to make sure
you didn't make a deal
with the cops to get bail.
Now we know.
So we're gonna
take a ride together,
do some business.
Ride to where?
You'll see.
Put down the laundry.
Leave the gun in the basket.
I'm gonna want that back.
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
Uh...
Can I get a jacket?
Sure.
Thank you.
Okay, I'm ready.
Give me your phone.
What? No.
No. You already got my gun. No.
I'm not asking.
Now let's go.
Reyna.
Look, I already spoke to
a bunch of cops.
I don't know where Cesar is.
I'm -- I am sorry.
Who is the happiest baby?
God, those chubby cheeks, too.
I know I owe you
for everything, okay?
For saving us.
But I don't know where Cesar is.
I haven't spoken to him
in over a week.
Then who's paying his paycheck?
Nobody. He's my cousin Hector.
I got two more cousins
even bigger back at the house.
Good. Though you probably
won't need them anymore
once La Fiera murders Cesar.
Which she will 100% do
when she finds him.
He's only got one chance,
and that's to make a deal
with us --
witness protection.
He won't go for it.
He's too proud to be seen
as a rat.
Well, then it's your job
to convince him
it's not snitching
when you torpedo your enemies.
And it's not snitching
to stay alive long enough
to be a father to your child.
Look.
There's no other way out.
Just have him call me.
She gonna call?
She'll call Cesar.
Whether or not he calls me...
I don't know.
Hey, stop! Hey, hey, hey!
Stop! Hey!
Hey, guys! Shoplifter!
Back to work.
♪ Everyday, sitting around
♪ I watch it slowly fade
♪ The images found
♪ Closed eyes, closed eyes,
no, I ♪
♪ Closed eyes,
closed eyes, no, I ♪
Stop! Nowhere to go!
You alright?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just -- Ow!
Just jammed my hand.
I'll call an ambulance.
No, don't bother.
It's just dislocated.
Uh, it's happened before.
One of the occupational hazards
of working construction.
Agh!
Ooh.
I'm good. I'm good.
As the driver,
it would be helpful
to know where we're going.
You seem nervous.
Nah, it's every girl's dream
to drive
to an undisclosed location
with two armed men.
Relax. We just need to pick up
the ingredients for the cook.
"Pick up." You mean steal?
Just keep driving straight.
I'm just asking
for a little help, okay?
It makes my job a lot harder
when the paperwork isn't right.
Nolan!
You okay? So, I heard you got
injured in your foot pursuit.
Oh, I just dislocated my finger.
My non dominant hand.
Uh, be sore for a couple days --
I'll be good to go.
- That guy assaulted you?
- No, I slipped
when we came --
Oh, excuse me for a second.
Hey, Judge, thanks for calling.
Listen, don't worry.
I got your back.
Thanks. Oh, not you.
Make sure you document
the injury.
It might seem like
it's nothing now,
but turn into an issue
down the road,
you need a paper trail.
Yes, sir.
Oh. Um, incidentally,
I spoke to Reyna --
Cesar's girlfriend.
I think there's a chance
he'll reach out.
The optimism of a rookie.
It burns bright,
and then it's gone forever.
Hey, Nolan.
Our guy just peed himself.
Take care of that, will ya?
This place is beautiful.
They really shouldn't
leave standing water like that.
It attracts mosquitoes,
and mosquitoes carry disease.
We'll make sure that's running
before the wedding.
And hire an exterminator.
Sorry,
w-we're closed for repairs.
We saw that on your website.
Which means you have nothing
booked for Saturday.
Right. Because we're closed
for repairs.
A pipe burst.
There was extensive damage.
We know.
We saw it on your website.
So Mr. Nolan reached out
to your contractor
and arranged some friends
to come get this damage fixed
by Saturday.
He -- He what?
Mrs. Evers' son Wesley
is getting married here
on Saturday.
It won't be a big wedding,
'cause it's last-minute
and people won't be able
to travel.
But w-we're closed --
you can't --
Oh, of course we can.
And we did.
And I'm gonna expect a discount,
since you'll be able
to start holding events here
weeks ahead of schedule.
Now, let's you and I discuss
what you'll be able
to provide on short notice
and what I'm gonna
have to bring in.
Look, I don't know
what Aldo told you about me,
but this isn't what I do, okay?
I -- I'm a chemist.
I-I don't know how to pull off
a -- a heist.
A heist?
Oh, that's way fancier
than what we're gonna do.
Nah, this is gonna be a lot of,
"Get on the floor!
This is a robbery!
Don't move, or I'll kill you!"
You're coming to make sure
we steal the right stuff.
Well, look, I have a contact
who can get us what we need.
It'll just take a few days --
We don't have a few days.
If we don't deliver
the product we owe,
things go badly for all of us.
Besides, why pay when we can
steal it for free?
Light 'em up.
Damn it.
It's Lucy.
What do we do?
Treat it like any other stop,
but we do not run anyone
in that car.
Lean back in your seat.
What are you doing?
You're out on bail,
Half-Life's got a warrant,
and this ride is stolen.
There's no way these cops
are gonna let us go.
When I pop this guy,
bail out and cap his partner.
W-Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look, before we start shooting
cops in broad daylight,
can -- just let me
try something, okay?
What?
Flirting.
I haven't gotten a ticket
since I was 16.
I know how to get out of them.
Okay? Just -- Just trust me.
I'm sorry, Officer.
Was I going too fast?
Yes, ma'am.
You almost caused an accident.
We're in a hurry.
It's my brother's birthday,
and I haven't gotten
any party supplies.
License and registration,
please.
C'mon, you don't really
need that, do you?
You should come to the party
after work.
We'd have fun.
Yeah.
I bet we would.
Alright, I'm gonna let you go
with a warning this time.
But slow down. Okay?
Yeah, I promise.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
Have fun at that party.
See?
Cops are easy -- you just got to
know how to play them.
What's up?
- We just pulled over Lucy
in a red SUV, definitely stolen.
She was with
two serious-looking men.
Any idea where they're going?
Negative. But she said
they were picking up supplies
for her brother's party.
Uh, Salonga has a brother --
Dahrio.
Uh, she could mean
he's who's with her.
And party supplies obviously
means ingredients for a cook.
Where are you?
Uh, south of Wilshire Park.
Alright, there are
three chemical storage
supply companies
in that vicinity.
Well, they're gonna rob
one of them.
And we're gonna let it happen.
Alright. Here we go.
Why do I have to go in?
I can just write down
what I need.
I'm a cook, not a crook.
You're whatever I say you are.
Hey, if anybody gets hurt,
I am out.
That's not how it works.
You can't only be in the game
a little.
That's how you get killed.
Now come on.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Don't move!
Everyone down, right now!
Right now!
♪ A new distorted lens
to look through ♪
Oh, oh! Don't. Don't!
Don't do it!
Unless you want
a closed-casket funeral!
Touch that gun and you're dead,
you hear me?
Don't make me kill you!
Come on! Down!
♪ I've never seen a sight
that looked so beautiful ♪
Hey, what are you doing?
Get her.
Don't hurt me. Don't.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Just sit down right here.
Sit down.
Hey, mama.
Hey.
You're a sexy one, aren't you?
Watch them.
Anyone as much as twitches,
blow their brains out.
Let's go.
Nova, let's go!
-Tell me.
A silent alarm
was just triggered
at Sutherland Chemical.
Do you want us
to alert available units?
Yes, but advise them
to keep clear of the area
until further notice.
And get an airship over there
so we can see where they go
when they leave.
I might just take you with us.
Would you like that?
Come on, baby.
That's it?
Uh, yeah. And --
And then we're done.
I'll grab one.
You get the other one.
I got a bad back.
I don't care.
We'll see how scared
you can get.
What are you doing?
Roll it out here. Uh...
Yeah, you take it
the rest of the way.
I'll go get Half-Life.
Hey. We're out of here.
Let's go.
Oh, but we were just
getting friendly.
Yeah, let's go right now.
Don't touch me.
Hey!
Let's move!
See you soon.
It's over.
They stole the precursors
for meth.
No one was hurt.
From the security footage,
Lucy navigated policy
and procedure perfectly.
She avoided crossing the
threshold with stolen property.
Where is she now?
I don't know.
The airship didn't get there
in time,
and Dahrio had
a switch vehicle nearby.
We lost her.
Well, this is where Reyna
said Cesar is hiding out.
I don't even know
why you're still working.
A busted finger gets you
a week off at least.
Cesar.
Don't run.
Reyna told us where to find you.
She shouldn't have done that.
I'm not making a deal.
Sniper!
7-Adam-15, shots fired.
Shooter is on the roof
of a building
one block west of 9731 Hickory.
He's on the run.
Requesting backup and R.A. unit
for a gunshot victim --
Not conscious. Not breathing.
You two alright?
22 years on the job
without incident.
One shift
with the unlucky charm --
a freaking sniper.
I need a moment.
Did you manage to track
the shooter?
No. He even took
his shell casing.
But it's gotta be
La Fiera's doing.
And now that she's gotten
her revenge,
I'll bet she'll head home
to Guatemala,
lay low in friendly territory
until the dust settles.
She was tracing Reyna's calls.
Most likely.
And I led her straight to him.
Don't do that to yourself.
You were trying to do
the right thing.
It's not your fault.
I'm -
I'm sorry, will you excuse me?
I have an ADA problem.
Okay, we should have stopped it.
It was my call.
And Lucy handled herself
like a pro.
She was hot-walking
those guys around
like she had been doing it
for years.
She is clear that
if she is in over her head,
she can pull herself out.
She won't, and you know it.
There's no quit in Chen.
Look, she's due for a check-in
at midnight.
I will take
her temperature then.
If I feel like
she is in too deep,
then we can go get her.
Call me right after.
Alright.
Now I gotta go
to my second job --
planning Lopez's
emergency wedding.
Uh, plates and flatware
are under "food," right?
Yes. Even though we don't eat
the plates,
they still fall under
the food category.
Copy that.
Great. So, that leaves...
Flowers, music, an officiant,
the cake,
and the marriage license.
Nope. Picked up the license
during lunch.
And I got the music.
My performing arts teacher
is a cellist.
I told her to learn
the "Wedding March"
and some Cardi B.
Who? Uh, never mind.
She's -- She's joking.
I -- I feel bad.
W-Why?
Well, this is
for something special.
Tamara and I are doing it
for money.
It doesn't feel right.
Oh, nonsense.
You two are providing a service.
It has value,
and you should get paid for it.
It doesn't make your help
any less special.
Or appreciated. Okay?
Okay.
Seriously, who is Cardi B?
Let me show you a video.
Unh-unh. No.
Ah, Mr. Del Monte.
Uh, y-you have a second?
Ah, Nolan. Uh, not really.
Actually, I'm kind of late
for dinner.
You charged my shoplifter
with felony assault.
Why?
Look at your hand.
I slipped and fell.
While in pursuit of the suspect.
Wouldn't have happened if
he hadn't committed the crime.
He committed a misdemeanor.
We can't up-charge him to
a felony because I was clumsy.
No, relax.
It's not gonna go to trial.
This guy's gonna plead out.
I'll knock it down
to, like, reckless endangerment.
He'll get a couple years'
probation, tops. It's fine.
And a felony on his record,
which will affect
every aspect of his life
from here on out.
How can that be justice?
Okay, look, I know
you're still new to all this,
but that's exactly what it is --
it's justice.
And actually,
last time I checked,
I had a pretty
sterling reputation
with your police union, so...
It's still wrong,
and you know it.
How about this --
I won't tell you
how to arrest them,
and you don't tell me
how to charge them.
Good talk.
You made it! Come in!
Thank you, again. I washed it.
Oh, you didn't have to do that.
Oh, good, 'cause I didn't.
Seconds ago, on your doorstep,
I realized a better person
would've washed it,
so I said I did, but...
now I'm caught
in a tangle of lies.
Bailey, this is Fiona.
Hello.
Hi. I-I didn't realize
it was a party.
-A party? No. Uh, sorry.
I w-would've called you, um,
but I don't know your last name
and I didn't have your number.
Uh, Fiona Ryan is my ethics
and law professor.
She's helping me
with an emergency work issue.
But you're welcome to stay.
I-I want you to stay.
Will there still be food?
Yes. Then I'll stay.
Excellent choice.
So, what's the issue?
John just became aware
of the systemic problem
of overcharging
in the justice system.
Okay, when you say it like that,
you make me sound naive.
I had a wobbler today.
It's a crime
that could be charged
either as a misdemeanor
or a felony.
Yes, and the ADA went ahead
and charged it as a felony
even though it was not one.
Things are so much more simple
in the UCMJ.
Uniform Code
of Military Justice.
I thought
you were a firefighter.
I am. I'm also a reserve
in the Army National Guard.
And a Capoeira instructor,
in case you ever want to
learn dance fighting.
Ooh, I love dance fighting.
Oh, it's the most
excellent workout.
I do it every Thursday night
after I volunteer at the ACLU.
Okay, between the two of you,
I'm officially starting
to feel like a slacker.
Good.
So, why can't you just go
to this D.A. guy
and ask him
not to charge a felony?
Well, cops don't decide
on the charges.
The D.A.'s office does that.
Oh, do not leave out
the department's complicity
in this problem, John.
Police officers are ordered
to write up
almost all wobblers as felonies.
-Mm.
-Not ordered.
Strongly encouraged.
And where we don't,
the D.A. almost always upcharges
to the felony anyway.
So, what are you gonna do?
And don't let the fact
that this decision will tell me
everything I need to know
about you as a person
sway your choice.
Oh, I like her.
I like you. Mm-hmm.
Lucy missed her check-in.
She's cooking.
You don't know that for sure.
She's either cooking
or she's dead.
She's not dead.
Then she's making product.
From the chemicals she stole,
we know it's meth.
Alright, that takes
four to eight hours.
Look, you and I both know
it's against the law
for her to allow product
she cooked to hit the streets.
If we don't find her, she's
gonna stop it by herself...
or die trying.
Are you done?
No. I'm just getting started.
It's gonna take me all night.
Why? You've been at it
for three hours already.
I want it finished
and out the door by sunrise.
Yeah, and I want a mansion
and a yacht,
but I'm dealing
with chemicals that explode
if you look at them funny,
so I'll take the time I need.
It's out by sunrise,
or it's over.
Where's the rest of it?
The lab you built me
was undersized,
so I only had enough time
to make one batch.
Why the hell
are you telling me that now?
'Cause I wasn't in the mood
to have this conversation.
I'm done with your attitude.
I can find another cook.
Wait, wait. Look, I'm sorry.
It's -- It's been a long night.
But I can make some more.
And it'll be quicker this time.
I promise.
Do it.
But I'm not waiting.
Half-Life will stay
while you cook.
I gotta get this
out on the street.
It should all go out together.
Why?
Aah!
Hey. It's me.
La Fiera's here.
Mission Road -- hurry.
Okay, I-I give up, I give up!
iNo más! iNo más!
It's okay. It's okay. Amiga.
Amiga!
Amiga, huh?
Who says I need a friend?
Everybody needs a friend.
Especially one
with certain skills.
You want to come work for me?
It's clearly my best option.
I haven't said
it was an option yet.
I hear you're running
Aldo's operation.
You owe product
to the Madrigal family,
which means
you owe it to me now.
Sure. No problem.
I can give you half right now.
It's already in the truck.
And she can make the rest.
She can?
Then what do I need you for?
Wait.
You can make the rest, right?
Yes, ma'am.
There's enough chemicals here.
I just...
I need my hands free.
You look familiar to me.
I can't imagine why.
We've never met.
I'm not so sure.
I have a very good memory
for faces.
I --
I swear, I'd remember you.
You're unforgettable.
I'm just a nobody.
You're not a nobody, are you?
No, I'm a cop.
And you're under arrest.
You stole my line.
I thought you said
she needed rescuing.
Turn around, Hermana.
Hands behind your back.
I told you it was gonna end
this way.
You okay?
Let's just go with yes.
How'd you guys get here so fast?
Not that I'm complaining.
When you didn't report in
last night,
Sergeant Grey called the chief,
who called
every law enforcement agency
in Southern California.
400 cops just spent
the night looking for you.
Wow.
I told you to leave it alone.
You did. And I didn't.
And now he's got me on his side.
Okay, fine.
I'll -- I'll knock down
the assault charge
on his shoplifter.
Not good enough.
I just got off the phone
with three other
division watch commanders.
As of tomorrow,
we're instructing
all our officers
to treat wobblers
as a misdemeanor,
never a felony,
unless there's
damn good reason to.
And if you keep overcharging,
you're gonna lose
the cooperation
of the arresting officers.
Good luck making a plea deal
after that.
Expect a call from the D.A.
Maybe even the mayor.
They have the number.
And you -- don't ever come
calling for a favor.
You just made an enemy
at the D.A.'s office.
Was it worth it?
Absolutely, sir.
Good.
Get back to work.
I'll be out of here
before you know it.
No, you won't.
You can lie to yourself about it
if you want,
just like you lied to yourself
about Diego.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Cesar might have sent
the shooter who killed him,
but you loaded the gun.
You crossed a line with Diego
you said you never would.
You used him as a cover to talk
to Cesar's father.
You hung the target
around your son's neck.
He's dead because of you,
Hermana.
And deep down, you know it.
This is amazing.
I can't believe you pulled it
together in two days.
No, it was a team effort.
Quarterbacked by Patrice.
Thank you for being there for me
during the craziness.
I know it hasn't been easy.
Oh, you owe me forever.
I mean, you could save my life
like three times
and we still wouldn't be even.
I know.
Is there anything I can do?
Set up chairs? Arrange flowers?
No. You're the bride.
Just relax, enjoy.
I need superglue,
hair pins, and your badge.
Why my badge?
I'll handle this.
You should go get ready.
This wedding
is starting on time.
Yes, sir.
Mom, this is perfect.
You finally used your powers
for good.
Well, it was nice having a
practice run for the real thing.
I'm thinking next June
in Tuscany.
No, Mom, this is our wedding.
The only wedding. We'll see.
So, we just realized
that Lopez doesn't have
her something old,
something new,
something borrowed,
something blue.
Oh. Uh, let's see.
Hmm.
My grandmother wore this
at her wedding.
Should be old enough, I think.
Yes. Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, great, she'll be wearing
my brooch.
Welcome.
Please sit wherever you like.
And the bar is open.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, my friend.
Alright.
And thank you, by the way,
for being my plus-one.
I hope it's not too weird that
our first date is a wedding.
Well, technically,
our first date was a TED Talk
on prosecutorial abuse.
Ah. To be fair, you came
into my life wearing a towel.
I felt compelled
to be unexpected.
Puts a lot of pressure
on our first kiss.
Good. I like a challenge.
I need to borrow something.
Oh, hi. Jackson.
Good to meet you.
Bailey. And you too.
- What do you need?
- Doesn't matter.
Ah, something borrowed. Okay.
Perfect. Henry made me this
when he was in third grade.
It's my good luck charm.
I'm gonna want that back.
Of course. Thank you.
Bye.
Shall we? Yes.
Ooh!
Uh, nice pocket square, sir.
Could I, um, maybe borrow it
for a few hours?
What? No.
It pulls together
the whole outfit.
It's for Lopez, sir.
It better come back spotless.
Thank you.
As I was saying --
first Nolan, now Chen.
Turned out to be
a pretty good teacher.
Forget undercover work -- you
might have found your calling.
Here's the thing, sir --
it's all my calling.
If I were to go into politics
this afternoon,
I would be president
in four years.
I believe it.
Officer Chen.
Look at you!
Triumph suits you.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you both
for believing in me.
Well, the hardest part
is still ahead --
adrenaline crash.
Monday morning,
it is back to transients
-and noise complaints.
-Yeah.
To tell the truth,
I kind of missed it.
Um, will you excuse me?
Yeah.
♪ Mary, she's not weeping
no more, no ♪
Hey.
Nice suit.
Nova would be impressed.
Nova was a little thirsty.
I like to think of her
as assertive.
Mm.
First solo op, and you take down
two major drug traffickers.
Not bad.
Thank you.
Hey, Chen.
Yeah?
Save me a dance.
♪ I'm the sick light
of a hurricane's eye ♪
Come in.
♪ I'm a violent lullaby
Wow.
Stop. I feel enormous.
No, you look amazing.
What have you got for me?
Oh! Yes.
Uh, something old --
Patrice's grandmother wore this
on her wedding day.
Old? That thing looks haunted.
Uh, something borrowed --
Nolan says this is lucky,
so that should cancel out
the brooch.
And something blue --
from the Sarge.
How am I supposed to
wear all this?
Right.
♪ His soul is trapped...
Alright.
♪ I crawled back
in my mother's womb ♪
How's that?
Ridiculous.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're so welcome.
Now get out
of here before I start crying
and ruin my makeup.
Yes, ma'am.
Um, did you need anything else?
Oh, uh, a breath mint?
Fresh pack --
something new.
It's like "Mary Poppins"
in there.
Oh, wedding's in 10.
Have you seen Jackson?
Not recently.
Is that the wedding bouquet?
Yeah. I was supposed to give it
to him to take to Mrs. Lopez.
Well, I can do that.
There you go.
I'll be right back.
Okay. Thanks.
I'm coming!
Angela? It's John.
I got your bouquet.
Angela?
Lopez?