Previously on "The Rookie"...
Officer Stanton
will be taking over
the training
of Officer West. Someone broke
into your home?
So, who are you claiming
these days, D?
He did something
that really bothered me.
The way he treated
this one family. Black family.
It's my job to teach you
the right way
to think on the street.
I hear he's a solid cop.
Learn what's useful
and ignore the rest.
Officer Nolan, you will be held
over the FTO program
for an additional month.
Why didn't you tell me? Why do you think?
Congratulations, Detective.
If I show up pregnant
on day one,
that's all they'll ever
see me as.
♪♪
Hey! Mom!
Actually, I'm so sorry.
I'm just running out the door.
Oh, you're always busy.
You haven't been home
in over a year.
Uh, yes, well, rookies still
don't get vacation time, Mom.
You know this.
How about I come for a visit?
Huh?
Uh, well, that would
be... lovely, Mother.
I really don't think
I have the...
time.
Danny had an affair with his ex,
so I dumped him.
I need emotional
support. Emotional support.
Mom, I am so sorry.
He just proposed to you, though.
I sent flowers.
They're getting delivered today.
Oh, that's so thoughtful of you.
But I should have known
this was not gonna last.
I told him I wanted
three carats, and apparently,
I'm only worth one
and a quarter.
Uh... A quarter!
Mother.
You're supposed to give the ring
back when you break up.
Nonsense! It's damages.
Compensation
for pain and suffering.
And, now, weren't you
in trouble recently?
'Cause Cousin Carol sent me an
article from Facebook or som--
I did not read it.
Your concern is touching.
Um, it's -- Everything's okay.
I am back on track.
At least I think I am.Ohh. Oh.
But to that end, I really --
I can't be late, so I'm --
Okay, go, go, go.
I'll settle myself in.
Okay.
U-Uh, actually,
that's my bedroom.
And I'm sure you want your mama
to have it.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
--Captions by VITAC--
Wanna crash on our couch?
No. Maybe. I ju--
She's such an emotional vampire,
and I've got that 30-day
extension hanging over my head.
I cannot afford to lose focus
right now.
On your six! Oh!
If I'd have been a banger,
you'd be dead.
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm not fond of him.
Yeah. Join the club.
I hate training with the public.
I feel like we're sharing
trade secrets.
Is it possible Tim Bradford
is having performance anxiety?
There are pills for that,
you know.
Look, I've come in second behind
Lopez the last four years.
Now that Annie Oakley's
with the detectives,
I got the patrol crown
in the bag.
Oh, there's only one problem
with that.
Me.
Firearm re-qualification day.
And, yes, I said "day"
because even though
the department allows a month
for you to re-qualify,
I expect every officer here
to leave with a passing score.
As police officers,
we can never lose sight
of the power we carry
on our hip.
There are only three
circumstances where an officer
should discharge
his or her weapon.
What are they? Rookies?
To defend their own life.
To defend another person's life.
To prevent the escape
of an individual
who's committed a felony
involving the use or threat
of deadly force and poses an
imminent danger to the public
if he or she were allowed
to escape.
Very good.
I'm Officer Dixon,
your Range Master.
Each target has two sides --
the civilian and the suspect.
When you see the suspect,
you have three seconds
to get shots off.
If you fire on the civilian
side, it is an automatic fail.
You have 36 shots,
two magazine changes.
30 hits is a pass, 29 a fail.
Whoops.
Almost made somebody an orphan.
Rookies, you're up.
Care to make it interesting?
20 bucks if your Boot makes it out on top?
I'll take that bet.
Me, too.
Officers ready? Begin.
♪♪
Officer Nolan!
So, finishing first with
the most hits, fastest time,
and tightest grouping...
Officer Chen.
Congrats. You are the new
Mid-Wilshire champ.
Thank you! Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Uh, Bradford, Harper,
you both tied for second.
I don't know what I hate more --
tying for second with
you or losing to a rookie.
And in last place,
my only fail in three years --
Uh, sir, when --
Officer Nolan,
if I hear one more word
about a guy in scuba gear...
If you don't pass
re-qualification within 30 days,
you will be put on desk duty
and be given
remedial firearm training.
Is that really the way you want
to end your rookie experience?
No, sir.
Then I suggest
you put in some range time
before your next test.
Alright, see you all
back at the station.
Hey, I need you to sign this.
Tamara.
Good morning.
Can you sign the title
to the car?
Cops keep eyeballing it,
and they're not gonna believe
you gave it to me.
You know, you still haven't confirmed
our Tuesday morning
appointment with the social worker.
We need to find you a real place to live.
I'll be there. I promise.
Alright.
Oh, hey.
I was a psychology major.
Cool, but it's just a class
that I have to take.
Well, you might want to
pay a little extra attention to it.
I found that it really helped me
understand what motivates people.
So does living on the street.
Fair enough.
The car is officially yours.
Drive safe. Thanks.
You're welcome.
How's the puppy? She's doing really great.
Oh, she told me to tell you, uh,
better luck next time
at the range.
♪♪
Get changed. Yes, sir.
7-Adam-07,
attach to event 1426...
...to assist Homicide
on their 187.
Did you take a look at
that gang book I gave you?
Yes, sir. It was very informative.
But I don't want to get to
a place where all I see is gangs.
Who's telling you to do that?
What's the deal? Homicide.
And, guys, I gotta run to court.
Detective's en route.
Yeah, no problem.
We'll take over.
Give me some quality
teaching time with the Boot.
Thanks.
Ooh-ee! A cholo piñata.
Definitely a gang-banger.
Looks like he got dressed using
the thug life handbook.
What do the tats tell us?
Spider web shows us that he was
caught up in the life.
And the three dots by his eye?
Stands for "mi vida loca."
That and the clock tattoo
shows us that he's done time,
and based on the yellow belt
and the bandana,
he probably banged with
Malos Dorados.
Officer West, I taught you well.
Sorry for making you wait.
Nah, that's a first.
Didn't know detectives knew
the word "sorry."
Well, it wasn't too long ago
I was the one
babysitting the crime scene.
So, what do we got?
Hispanic male, tortured,
shot execution-style.
Probably killed
by another gang-banger
whose body we'll find
in an alley next week.
Classic case of No
Victims Involved, if you ask me.
Well, I didn't.
Go start a canvass.
Yes, ma'am.
Mm-hmm.
Jackson.
Don't let that guy turn you into a hater.
It's easy to judge,
but this was someone's kid.
I just really miss
riding with you.
Everything okay?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
Mid-Wilshire shooting champ!
I like the sound of that.
Wait, do I get a trophy?
I love trophies. Relax.
You had a few good shots.
Come on! I rocked it!
Don't be salty just because
you got second place.
Plus, you won 40 bucks.
I should get a cut of that.
Not happening.
But as your T.O., your successes
are my successes.
So you should be thanking me
for training you so well.
Wow.
Isn't that your car?
Yeah, it is.
And he's trying to steal it.
Sir, step away from the vehicle.
It's mine. I just bought it.
But I can't get
this stupid door to open.
What do you mean
you just bought it?
This girl -- she sold it to me
for 4 grand.
$4,000?!
It's worth at least $10,000!
Okay, $8,000.
Am I in trouble? No, sir.
Nope. Sorry to bother you.
♪♪
You -- You have to push all
the way down before pulling up.
Hey! Thanks.
♪♪
I should get a do-over.
I mean, a guy running around
in a scuba suit
and an air tank at a gun range?
That's weird, right?
Have you never been to
a public range in L.A. before?
It's weird when someone
is not cosplaying.
But you shouldn't have let it distract you.
You had a gun in your hand.
N-- I know. It was just --
No, no, no, no! No excuses.
The streets are full
of distractions.
You lose focus,
someone gets killed.
I was really hoping I could
impress Sergeant Grey today.
Yeah, well, you didn't.
"Momster"?
I-I'm sorry.
Do you mind if I...?
Sure. Go ahead.
Hey, Mom, what's up?
I need directions downtown.
Well, didn't Henry download
that driving app on your phone?
Yes, but it has a very weird
robot voice.
And I've got
impatient son voice.
Use the driving app, Mom. Bye.
I'm sorry. That's --
That's all right.
Look, when I first joined,
my mom used to call
all the time during shifts.
But eventually,
I just realized that
that was her way
of making sure I was okay.
That's very nice.
This is not that.
Help! Police! Help! Police!
Police, help!
There's a woman
destroying my house!
♪♪
I ShareBnB the place,
and when I came by to get my
mail, I caught her like this.
You can't make me leave.
Okay, no, w-we're just
checking to make sure
that everything is okay.
Clearly it's not. Do something!
Could you get her out of here,
please?
She's ruining Monica's
birth experience.
Um, ma'am, technically,
the young lady
isn't doing anything illegal.
She's well within her temporary
tenant rights to be here.
And giving birth
really isn't a crime.
It is when it's on my white
European goose downs!
You need to get her out of here, please.
Yep.
- No!
- Ma'am, come with me.
This way. Come on.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Easy. Easy. You okay?
I'm okay.Okay.
I'm okay.
I don't like how high
her blood pressure is.
Okay. Um, uh, Monica,
my name is Nyla.
We need to get you
to a hospital.
No, please.
No, no, I don't want to have
my baby at the hospital,
not after what happened
last time.
Please, I don't want to
have my baby at the hospital.
Okay. It's okay.
Listen, I will be with you
the whole way.
♪♪
Monica?
I'm Dr. Kang.
You brought her in?
Yes, sir.
She passed out earlier,
but she came to
in the ambulance.
Who's her OB?
I'm not using one.
I have a doula.
Well, that's not very smart.
No, it's just that I had
a really bad experience
with my first.
The -- The cord got twisted,
and the doctor --
he wouldn't even check to see --
Would you please calm down?
Your blood pressure's sky-high,
and getting hysterical
just makes things worse.
Hey, Doc, this is your patient.
Don't talk down to her.
Just listen.
Can you calm your partner down?
She's not my partner.
She's my boss.
And she is firing you.
We would like a new doctor,
please.
I'm the head of obstetrics,
and this is not a police matter.
I want a new doctor.
Page me when she
comes to her senses.
I can't do this --
fighting with doctors again.
T-They don't want to listen.
They just don't want to listen.
Hey. We will make them listen.
You got it? Okay?
Me and you. Together.
Who's the doctor she wants?
Sorry I'm running late.
Just think, once you retire,
no more schedules, no more --
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Just keep it down
about those retirement talks.
I haven't told anyone yet.
You having second thoughts?
No. As soon as I send
this rookie class on their way,
I am all yours. Oh, well, I like
the sound of that.
You like that? Alright.
But I-I was hoping that we could
look at these together at lunch.
"Taking Off the Badge:
Retirement Strategies
for Law Enforcement."
Don't laugh.
We both know the statistics.
Most cops die within
seven years of retirement.
That's not gonna happen.
I know it's not because
I'm not gonna let it.
Luna, how are you?
I'm good, Detective Lopez.
How you liking the promotion?
Love it.
Hey, Sarge, I'm working
a weird homicide.
M.E. pulled out silicone-coated,
armor-piercing slugs
out of my vic.
Armor-piercing?
Damn. Who'd he piss off?
I don't know.
But the guy had ties
to Malos Dorados.
You have a C.I. in still
with them?
Felix Minosa.
But I passed him over to Wysocki
when I became Watch Commander.
He'll hook you up. Thanks.
Nice seeing you, Luna.
You, too.
You're gonna have to
tell them soon, Wade.
They love you around here.
They're gonna want a chance
to say goodbye.
Still can't believe
how that doctor talked to her.
Oh, there's plenty more
where he came from.
Sounds like you're talking
from experience.
Well, after Lila was born,
I-I-I knew something was wrong,
but the doctor just said
I was being dramatic.
But honestly, if it wasn't
for that nurse...
I-I will never forget the look
on Donovan's face
when I was being wheeled
into surgery.
He was holding Lila,
and she was just so small and --
and fragile and I just --
I thought I'd never
see them again.
I'm sorry.
You deserved better than that.
Yeah. I did.
Uh, excuse me. Hi. Yes?
Are you Dr. Peterson? Yes.
We have a woman who is in labor,
and she's showing signs
of pre-eclampsia.
I'm sorry. I already have
a patient in labor.
Now you have two.
Dr. Kang is the doctor on call.
Would you let Dr. Kang
deliver your baby?
He's my boss.
What room is she in? She's in 309.
I will introduce you to her.
Ah.
Sorry.
Mom, this isn't a good time.
John, help! Get away from me!
Mom, what's going on?
Who are you speaking to?
I said get away!
Mom?
Something's wrong at my house.
My mom's in trouble.
Take the shop. Radio for backup.
Right.
♪♪
Hey.
What's going on? Is my mom okay?
She's a feisty one.
Knows more curse words
than my old drill instructor.
Uh, who the hell are you?
I'm Danny Hill.
I'm your mom's fiancé.
Ex-fiancé! You cheater!
I'm not a cheater. Evelyn!
Liar! I had coffee with Pamela
to tell her about
our engagement.
We were married 30 years.
It was the decent thing to do.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe
anything you say.
Will you please leave?
Okay.
Can I just, um,
get the ring back?
I don't have it.
Mom, you showed it to me
this morning.
I know, but it -- it --
it was so big
it kept slipping off my finger.
Maybe it's around here
somewhere.
Mom, just give him back
the ring.
I don't have it.
Is that why
you went downtown today,
so you could sell it
in the diamond district?
Of course not.
Mom.
You barely had it 48 hours.
You never actually intended
to marry me, did you?
You scammed me for the ring!
Oh, you gold-digging --
Yeah, d--
Still my mom.
I want to file a police report.
Good luck with that.
That is your right, sir.
W-What?
Why are you taking his side?
I'm not. This is not a costume.
I am a police officer.
Filing a report is his right.
Betrayed by my own son.
I'm beginning to think
I dodged a bullet.
You gotta be kidding me.
Bad puppy.
You sold my car to
buy new clothes?
And earrings.
It's my car. You gave it to me.
To sleep in, not to sell.
Do you have any idea
what it's like to go to school
every day with greasy hair
and dirty clothes?
So, yeah, I sold your
janky-ass ticket magnet
and bought a few nice things.
I just want to feel normal
for once.
And so where's the rest
of the money?
It's in my college fund.
Look, why didn't you say
something earlier?
You came by this morning.
You clearly already had a buyer.
I knew you wouldn't understand.
You would have just said no.
No. Wait.
Where are you staying?
With my cousin. Is it safe?
Well... hell!
All units B.O.L.
211-armed just occurred.
Suspect is male, Black,
6-foot, black pants, blue hoodie.
Weapon a handgun.
Come on. Let's get to work.
Hey. There's our guy.
I don't think so.
Uh, the hoodie's green,
not blue.
The suspect is 6 feet.
That guy's too short.
'Cause some scared RP
with a gun in their face
is gonna tell the difference
between green and blue?
6 feet and 5'6"? Come on.
Control, 7-Adam-07,
8th and Bronson,
got a possible 211 suspect.
Code 6.
Here we go.
Hey. LAPD.
Show me your hands.
I said show me your hands now!
What the hell?! Roll over!
I didn't do anything!
Roll over, dumbass!
On your belly!
Aah! I live right here!
Hands behind your back.
Why are you cuffing me?!
Ow! For your safety and ours.
My -- Your -- My safety?! Aah!
You're hurting me!
Look, sir, please,
it's gonna be okay.
We just have to check you out.
Check me out?!
I live right here!
Okay. What are you doing?!
That's my son!
Ma'am. Ma'am. Mama, I didn't --
It's gonna be okay.
Hey! Back up! I didn't do nothing.
Let my baby go! Get off of me!
Lady, I will knock your ass out!
Get your hands
off my wife! Are you crazy?!
Control, 7-Adam-07, I got a house
emptying out on me. Son, it's okay.
Send backup. Let him
go! It's all right, son.
Everybody on the ground! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Control, 7-Adam-07, we need
a supervisor out here. Code 3.
Everybody,
just stay where you are.
Just -- Just give us
a minute to explain.
Everybody on the ground now!
I know, I know, baby. It's okay.
♪♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Baby, you're okay.
Everyone down on the ground!
Let him go! What do you need?
Help Jackson
hook these idiots up.
We're arresting
the whole family?
What the hell did I just say?
Wait, even the grandmother?
Are you serious?
Alright, West, Chen,
you stay here.
Stanton, come here.
Let's go sort this out.
Hey, I'm recording this.
I see you.
It's always the same
with you guys.
Get those cuffs off my boy!
We can't, ma'am.
Not yet, anyways.
It's protocol. I'm sorry.
Not as sorry as this
fake-ass brother.
Uncle Tom sellout.
We spotted the 211 suspect,
ordered him to stop.
H-Hold up, hold up.
They -- They just
pinched that guy
half a mile from here
two minutes ago.
You didn't hear that
on the radio?
I'm arresting all of them.
Attempted assault
on a police officer,
resisting arrest,
criminal threats.
What are you doing here?
There are cameras all around.
You nabbed an innocent man.
The D.A. won't file.
These people
don't respect authority.
You grabbed the wrong guy.
You're senior officer.
It's your call.
Control, 7-Adam-19, Code 4.
Shut down Code 3 units
and cancel the supervisor.
Jackson, come here.
Uncuff that gentleman
with an apology.
Talk to the family,
explain the situation.
See if you can
dust them off, okay?
Okay. I'll join you in a minute.
And now you're gonna
kiss their ass?
It's called the least we can do.
It's not right.
That's not right.
He should lock him up.Finally.
Uh, sir, I am -- I'm truly sorry
for the, uh, confusion.
Confusion?
You just cuffed my grandbaby
and pointed guns
at my entire family.
And we're very sorry, ma'am.
Look, ma'am,
we were looking for a suspect
that fit the description
of your grandson.
Oh! Yeah. Young and Black.
We need to
speak to your Sergeant. Tim: Of course.
Ma'am, here's my business card
in case you want to
file a complaint.
You bet your ass we do.
Hey. It's a girl.
Mother and daughter
are doing just fine.
That's great. What happened with your mom?
Oh, it's just a hot mess,
which is normal.
Fiancé flew in to win her back.
She'd already
hocked the engagement ring,
so he filed a police report,
with me, which I'll hear about.
I just wish I could say
this was new behavior,
but she's been pulling this
love-'em-and-leave-'em stuff
since my dad split.
Well, not like I'm trying to
defend her or anything,
but a single mom raising a kid
alone in the '60s --
'80s.
Late '70s, early '80s.
Whatever.
Women couldn't even get their
own credit cards back then.
I mean, society was designed to
make them depend on men.
So maybe that made your mom
a little... mercenary.
Your old C.I. came through.
What did Felix tell you? That
my murder victim was recruited
to be local muscle
for a Guatemalan cartel,
specifically for La Fiera.
La Fiera? It's a woman?
Her real name's
Sandra de la Cruz.
She's a big-time drug runner
from Guatemala.
Legend goes that
when she was only 15,
she was walking home
from the hospital
with her newborn son
when she got caught
in the crossfire
between two rival gangs.
To protect her baby,
she picks up a semiautomatic
off a dead narco
and kills everyone.
The cartel was so impressed,
they recruited her
and named her La Fiera.
And you believe that?
There's songs written about it
and a kick-ass telenovela.
So, whether her origin story
is true or not,
La Fiera is very real
and very dangerous.
And you think she's connected
to your homicide?
I don't know.
What are these?
You're putting in your papers?
When?
I don't know.
Were you gonna say something?
Like you share all
your personal decisions?
Eventually.
Exactly.
I'll tell everyone
when I'm ready.
Yes, sir.
I'm happy for you.
I just...
It won't be
the same without you.
Well, I'm either going to the
range or home to my mother.
So, you're going to the range?
100%. Maybe even a late dinner?
You know, you could always
ask her to get a hotel.
You know, you'd think
that'd be the case.
You broke the first rule
of being a cop --
have your fellow officer's back.
I did.
You questioned
every move I made,
all before the suspects
were even in cuffs.
But what really pissed me off --
calling for a supervisor.
The whole city hears that and
thinks we're in over our heads.
We were in over our heads!
No, you were!
Don't let it happen again.
Hey. Was he actually giving you
a hard time
about today? Yeah, it's whatever.
I just have to hold it down
for a few more weeks
then I'll be free of him. What happened?
He jacked up the wrong suspect,
then threatened the family.
A Black family,
and it's not the first time.
You should tell Grey. Or at least
talk to Tim about it.
I did already.
Tim said that he heard Doug
was "a solid cop,"
and that I should,
"learn what's useful from him
and ignore the rest."
He said that? Yeah.
And, look,
as horrible as today was,
technically,
Stanton didn't break any laws.
Plus, he's an 11-year vet
and I'm just a rookie.
No one's gonna listen to me.
We're listening.
And we're here if you ever want
to talk about it.
Thank you.
♪ I see the wrecking
♪ I see the rain
♪ I see the way now
♪ I see the way --
Excuse me. Hate to bother you.
I saw you on the range earlier.
I'm with the LAPD.
♪♪
Hey. I just heard.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
My truck, not so much.
Any idea who the shooter is?
No, not yet.
I did get a look at him, though.
He was at the firing range
during our qualifications,
wearing a full scuba suit.
Who's the
investigating detective?
Uh, actually,
it looks like it's you.
Crime scene techs identified
the shooter's ammunition --
silicone-covered,
armor-piercing.
Same as my homicide.
And then the suspect got away
in a white sedan,
but I only got a partial plate.
Luckily, that was all we needed.
So, we've got five possibles.
Only one was a white sedan.
It's a rental out of Pico-Union.
You get a name?
Yes, they e-mailed us
a copy of his driver's license.
Guillermo Sandoval.
That's him. This is the guy.
He's definitely connected
to my murder.
Victim worked for
a Guatemalan cartel.
Any idea
where this guy is now? Actually, yeah.
We got a hit off
of his credit card
that he used for the rent-a-car.
It's, uh, one of those
no-tell motels on Ventura.
I'll call for a warrant.
I got him! Got him!
Show me your hands.
Out here. Nice and slow.
Out here. On your knees.
Give me that.
Hands on your head.
He just sent a text.
"Policía. Plan B."
♪♪
He's a cop.
At first,
it didn't make sense to me
how a cop with a good reputation
could do this.
Then I did a little research.
You survived
the Massacre of Antiguo Leon.
Your village stood up
to the cartel,
and they were slaughtered.
Men, women, children...
your children.
But this man
that you tortured and killed
had nothing to do with that.
He worked for the one
who ordered it done.
La Fiera.
And you want revenge,
but she's a hard one to catch.
Smart and very cautious.
Rumor is she only travels
by yacht to avoid ambush.
So... that explains
the scuba gear.
You needed to practice shooting
with all that equipment on.
Clearly, that was Plan "A."
But you sent someone a text
ordering Plan "B."
So, what is that?
You'll find out... soon enough.
Yeah, well, thanks for nothing.
My guy at the DEA didn't even
know La Fiera was in town.
That's more than a little scary.
And it's so strange to think
that if I hadn't been distracted
by a guy in a scuba suit
at a gun range,
there would be a bloodbath
on a yacht right now.
Yeah, that was a good spot.
Not what you said yesterday.
But who's keeping score?
Clearly, you. Clearly.
I hope Grey is, too, though.
You think there's any way he
would be so impressed by this,
he might, you know,
let me off the hook
for that 30-day extension?
Officer Nolan,
why were you given
an official letter of reprimand
and extended in the FTO program?
Because I ignored
an LAPD regulation.
Among other things.
And do you feel that that was
a fitting punishment,
considering your violation?
Yes.
And yet you want
special treatment.
When we pinch someone breaking
the law, they are punished.
If those rules apply to them,
then they absolutely
apply to us, as well.
La Fiera's in town with her son
for a college tour.
They're gonna kill her
on campus.
♪ Ice tunnel
when the pressure closes ♪
So, now we have to
protect a drug lord?
Can't we just
take an early lunch
and let nature take its course?
Any real questions?
Anyone have a case on her?
She's on everyone's radars,
but there's no open warrants
in the US.
So as far as we're concerned,
she's clean.
Think she has private security?
Definitely.
And they'll be packing.
Let's pray we get there before
the trouble starts.
♪ Walk out with adrenaline
♪ So cold-blooded
Mom, wait up.
♪ Ah, ah
Can you believe Stanton?
"Can't we just let nature
run its natural course?"
Really? No comment? None at all?
Look, he's not
my favorite cop, either,
especially after
he handled that family.
You mean the way
he terrorized them?
Look, I've been around guys
like Doug my entire career,
military and police.
They're rough around the edges.
"Rough around the edges,"
"old school," "hard-charging."
Come on, man.
Stanton is a racist.
You don't know that for
sure. Uh, yeah, actually, I do.
But you're right.
Let's just make excuses for him.
Phew!
This place is something else.
A lot nicer than where I went.
Chico State. Where'd you go?
Ah!
Too short for basketball.
So football?
Come on, you played, didn't you?
Knew it.
What is that supposed to mean?
I also had a 4.4 GPA, and I was
valedictorian of my class,
if you were wondering
how I got in.
I wasn't.♪ Ah, ah
♪ So cold-blooded
♪ Ah ♪ So cold-blooded
It's the perfect combo
of hard work and fun.
All units. Found them.
Lopez, Humanities building,
east entrance.
This campus is mad lit.
Yes, what can I do for you,
Detective?
You may speak freely in front of
my son. I hide nothing from him.
There's a credible threat
against your life.
I have officers ready to escort
you to a safe location.
It's okay.
♪♪
Just as a precaution.
La Fiera!
Get down!
Go! Run!
Look out!
Go! Go! Run!
All units,
I'm taking rifle rounds.
Humanities building,
third floor.
Diamond formation
when we get inside, got it?
I'll provide cover fire.
Alright, time to run like hell.
Ready? Three, two, one, go.
♪♪
Who is it? Who's after me?
I can't tell you that.
He's arrested, no?
There'll be a record.
I'll find out anyway.
So why not
just give me his name?
'Cause of what you might
do to him.
I thought that you didn't
hide anything from your son,
"La Fiera."
I like you. A strong hermana.
But I am just a businesswoman.
Businesswomen don't have
narcocorridos
written about them. Please.
People in my country,
they like to tell stories,
create legends.
Doesn't make them all true.
Lopez, 7-Adam-15.
Shots fired. West stairwell.
Pursuing suspect towards roof.
Copy that.
It's killing you, eh?
That you can't be out there
in the action?
I'm protecting you. No.
You're protecting your criatura.
You're pregnant, no? I can tell.
Diego gave me
awful heartburn, too.
What? No.Hey, come on, hermana.
We're not sisters.
Do you know why
they call me "La Fiera"?
You were caught in a narco
gunfight with baby Diego.
You grabbed a gun and laid
everyone to waste.
Sounds more legend than truth.
No.
That story is all truth.
We're survivors, Diego and me.
When it comes to your child,
there is nothing you won't do,
nothing you won't become
to protect them.
You'll see.
♪♪
Aah! Ohh! Ohh!
Get down on the ground now!
Ponte en el suelo!
♪♪
The State Department's
satisfied with your statement.
You can go. Ay, muchas gracias,
Detective.
Diego, he likes this school.
So, who knows?
Maybe we'll see you around.
Don't mistake
the professionalism
I showed you today for weakness.
Loving your son
doesn't excuse you
from the crimes
you've committed.
You come back to L.A. when
there's a charge on your head,
I'll put the cuffs on myself.
I would expect nothing less,
hermana.
Officer West. I'm on my way out.
Can this wait till the morning?
Uh, no, sir. This -- This can't.
Alright, come on.
It's, um --
It's Officer Stanton.
He, um -- He's a bad cop, sir.
In what way?
To be honest, every way.
Who he chooses to pull over,
how he -- how he treats suspects
of color,
the things he says.
Give me specifics.
Saying that a crime has
"no victims involved"
just because the deceased
was affiliated.
Look, a lot of cops
feel that way.
It's an attitude
I don't agree with,
but it doesn't violate
any rules.
I-It's not just that, sir.
Y-Yesterday we
felony-stopped a man
who did not fit
the suspect description.
He was outside of his own home.
I know about that.
I read the report.
Did you check the body cams?
Beca--
Stanton wanted to arrest
this guy's entire family, sir.
Last I checked,
it's within cops' discretion
to make arrests.
It was unwarranted, sir!
Look, Stanton escalated
the entire situation
to the point where it became
dangerous for both us
and that man's family.
Bradford, we're in the middle
of something, so --
I-I think I know
what it's about.
Look, whatever Officer West is
telling you, I stand with him.
Fine.
I'll put Stanton on the desk
till we figure it out.
With all due respect, sir,
that is not good enough.
Jackson.
Excuse me, son?
You've been on the job
for five minutes.
I've got 25 years.
You don't know what
I had to put up with,
what your father had to put up
with to get this far.
You stand on our shoulders.
And yet the water is still
above my head.
So, tell me this, sir.
What were
all your sacrifices for?
Get the hell
out of my office, West.
Look, I know you're pissed. Why aren't you?
I am. It's just...
I've been making excuses
for pricks like Stanton
my entire life, figured
there was no changing them,
so I'd let it go,
I gave them a pass.
It wasn't a pass.
You gave them permission.
Silence is complicity, sir.
Yeah.
I get that now.
But Sarge is right.
Benching Stanton is the only
recourse he has.
It's not good enough.
♪ Come back home
♪ Back to these open arms where
you belong ♪Can you page Officer Chen?
Tamara. Hey.
Hey!
♪ Come back home Look.
I don't trust people
who are nice to me.
♪ You know I've been waiting,
waiting for so long ♪Yeah, I get it.
Look, predators are everywhere,
especially on the street.
Trust is something that needs to
be earned, not bought.
So, how can I
earn trust with you?
Well, according
to my psychology textbook,
there are seven different ways
to build trust
in a relationship.
Mm-hmm.
And if memory serves,
I believe they boil down to
doing what you say
you're going to.
Exactly.
Um, I need a safe place
to keep this at night.
It's the first computer
I've ever owned.
♪ Come back home
Uh, I used to do all my school
work on the one at the library,
but it's like
a hundred years old.
And your cousin's
is not a safe place?
It's safe-adjacent.
I mean, I won't get attacked
while I'm asleep,
but this will get pawned
in five seconds.
You can pick this up here
every morning before school.
Uh, excuse me.
Could you leave this
at the desk under
Tamara Colins? Thanks.
Thanks. Yeah.
Hey, have you
ever been to the SCLA campus?
I was there today,
and it is beautiful.
You should check it out. Yeah, right.
I can't afford that.
They have scholarships.
I could help you apply for one.
I don't know. Maybe.
Well,
why don't you grab your stuff,
and we can talk about it
over dinner?
And then after that, I can drop
you at your cousin's house
and see if "safe-adjacent"
is safe enough.
♪ Waiting there for me
♪ To come back home
Hi!
♪ Come back home
Oh! Aww, she's beautiful.
♪ Back to these open arms
where you belong ♪
♪ Come back home
♪ Is that you that I see
walking down the road? ♪
Thanks for the gift.
On the table with the red bow.
Then who did?
I'll call you back.
♪♪
♪ Come back home
"Querida Angela.
In my country,
we tie a red ribbon
around a baby's wrist
to ward off evil.
Thank you for protecting
my child today.
Consider this a gift of
protection for yours.
Con cariño, La Fiera."♪ Come back home
♪ Come back home
♪ Back to these open arms
where you belong ♪
♪ Come back home
Don't worry.
I'm giving you
exactly what you want.
I'm leaving.
If you were leaving,
you'd already be gone.
You're waiting.
Waiting for your audience
to appear
so you can put on another show.
You think that little of me?
After everything I've done
for you, you hate me.
Mom, I don't hate you.
I'm just so tired
of playing the games.
Aren't you?
Yes.
♪♪
Well, then, maybe we could try
not playing them
and just be real
with each other.
I don't know if you could
handle the real me.
But I'll give it a shot.
Okay.
How would you like me
to make a little supper?
Unless you still
want me to leave?
Mom.
Supper would be great.
Okay.
♪♪
And the guest ro-- That's my...
♪ I put a lot on the line
Hey.
You were supposed to meet me
outside 15 minutes ago.
I'm sorry. My bad.
What happened?
Wade. Talk to me.
It's just...
Percy's son came to see me.
His T.O.'s a problem.
What kind of problem?
You know what kind.
♪♪
When I joined the Department,
I told myself,
"Do whatever you need to do
to survive,
get a promotion,
then you can make
some real change."
And now you're about to retire.
And I haven't changed
a damn thing.
Okay.
Well, what you
gonna do about it?
♪ Ooh
♪♪