Previously on "The Rookie"...-Hey, get back!
-Hands!
Jackson: No! Chris!No sign of the suspect?
Harper: No, but we did
recover his weapon.
Wait a minute.
There's supposed to be a gun.
Officer Erin Cole never switched
her camera on during the raid.
Armstrong.
No!
Armstrong.She said his name
before she saw him.
You did good, my friend.
Very good.
Do you realize what
you are accusing him of?
If I'm right, he's betraying
everything we stand for.
So we gather
more evidence.It's not enough.
We got to
trip him up somehow.
get into his head.
Tell me what you know
about Armstrong.
A hidden compartment
in the laundry room wall...
Armstrong: You broke into
my house to kill me
because I found out
you were dirty.
No one's
gonna believe that.
I won't be the only one
saying it.
There's another cop
on the payroll. John Nolan.
Aah!Control,
this is Officer Nolan.
You don't have time
for that, John.
You got to go,
or they're gonna find it.
The evidence
in your house.
[ Sirens wailing ]
♪♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Heart beating rapidly ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Sir, it's a set-up.
Nick Armstrong's on his way
to the hospital.
Says you tried to
kill him.
Says you're on
the Derians' payroll.
It's a lie. Nick's the one
who's the dirty cop.
He murdered Erin Cole.
He's setting me up.
Okay, okay.
Let us inside
so we can take
a look around
and you and I can talk.
Do you have a warrant?
Nolan, you do not want to
play things this way.
Actually, sir, this is exactly
how you want me to play things.
Two cops are dead,
and a third one is a murderer.
We're both gonna be
under the microscope on this.
So we need to play this
exactly by the book,
which is why you need a warrant,
and I need to call a lawyer.
[ Sighs ]
Warrant's in process.
Sit tight.
Do not make this worse
for yourself.
[ Cellphone beeps ][ Exhales sharply ]
[ Ringing]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Cellphone beeps, clicks ]
Hey, Nolan, what's up?
Is Angela okay?
Yeah. No.
I'm not calling about her.
Wesley, I-I, uh,
I need you.
I-I need -- I need your help.
I have to hire you.
Yeah, of course.
Hey, tell me what's happening.
Nick Armstrong
is framing me.
He murdered Erin Cole.
He planted evidence
in my house,
which is now surrounded
by cops.
I told Grey he needs
a warrant to come in.
You were right
to demand a warrant.
My job is to keep them
from getting it.
Judge Paloma is
the on-call judge tonight.
He's 10 minutes
from my house.
Is the evidence
that Nick planted easily found?
Yeah.
He wasn't very subtle.
[ Sighs ] Alright. Look,
this is what I need you to do --
[ Trash can clatters ]
Wesley?
Wesley, are you there?
Uh...yeah.
Yeah, uh...
Listen...
what I need you to do
is bag the evidence.
Hide it somewhere else.
Somewhere it won't
easily be found.
I-I can't tamper
with the evidence.
No, you won't be.
Legally, we'll argue that...
with knowledge of
at least two dirty cops,
you had no choice
but to secure the evidence
until you knew
it was gonna be safe.
Well, that might fly in court,
but I could lose my job.
Forget about your job,
Nolan.
I'm trying to keep you
out of prison.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
♪♪
You here for Nolan?
Yeah.
He called me.
This is just a signatureon a search warrant.
There's nothing for youto do here. Go home.
Clearly, you've never seen me
at a probable cause hearing.
Is, um...
[ Doorbell rings ]
...everything alright?No.
Everything is
a dumpster fire.
Two cops are dead,
and I'm here
to get a warranton a friend of mine.
Is there anything else
bothering you?
Oh, boy.
And I was having
such a lovely dream.
Okay,
let's make this quick.
Raise your right hand
and repeat after me.
-Hey.
-Coming through.
[ Groans ]
You got to get Nolan.
Did you arrest him?
Is he in custody?
Not yet.
We shouldn't talk
about this.
I know you're friends,
but Nolan's a killer.
You can't trust him.
You hear me?
You hear me?!Yes, sir.
I hear you.
Percy: Jackson.
Dad.
How is he?The bullet went
straight through.
Doesn't seem likeit hit anything vital,
but he's definitely
gonna need surgery.
What did he say to you?
Same thing he said
at the scene --
Nolan tried to kill him
after admittingthat there was damning evidence
hidden at his house.
I-I'm sorry.Like, I-I don't believe him.
I mean,Nolan's a great cop,
the best of us,
but so is Armstrong.
Stop. Stop.
Our job is to collect facts
right now, not form opinions.
Understood?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
It's been a horrible few days --Chris' death, and now this.
It's easy to lose focus,
but that's exactly why
it's vital that we don't.
I need you to stay here
and keep an eye on Armstrong
once I'm gone.
Report back
on everything he says.
Yes, sir.I won't let you down.
[ Sighs ] Good.
Commander --We don't have to
talk now,
but when we do,
you have the rightto have a union rep present.
I don't need a rep.
I need protection.
From who?
Harper.
She's in on it, too.
[ "Stay Fuego" plays ]
[ Pounding on door ]
♪♪
[ Light switch clicks ]
[ Pounding on door ]
♪ They not appreciating ya
♪ They don't see how you glow [ Cellphone ringing ]
♪ They keep on underrating ya
Nolan, what the hell
is going on?
Harper, I've really
stepped in it.
Armstrong lured me
to his place,
made me think it was to confess,but it was a set-up.
He planted evidence in my house.
Why the hell didn't you call me
before you went...
Please tell me you at least
taped the conversation.
Yeah,
that would have been smart.
Well, that would
explain why there are
cops at my front door.
Armstrong needs to frame
both of us
in order for this
to work.
He break into your house,
too?
No. My security system
would have nuked him.
I should really invest
in one of those.
Yep. It's a little late
for that.
I am really sorry,
Nyla.
Yeah, and I am really looking
forward to yelling at you
when we are on
the other side of this.
I think you mean "if."
[ Sighs ]
Be smart, Nolan.
It only gets bumpier
from here.[ Cellphone beeps ]
♪ You got somewhere to go Let's go.
Try not to make a mess.
There is a gun safe
in the hall closet.
Keys are here.Lock up when you're done.
We going to
the station?
No.
Internal Affairs.
♪ Stay fuego, stay fuego
Is this right?I'm afraid so.
Your Honor,
may I see the state's
probable cause affidavit?Care to cite?
1538.5 PC, In Theodor.
Your Honor,
I would object
under evidence code 1040
through 1042,
on the grounds that it may
unnecessarily reveal
information, sources,
and investigative tactics.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, given that
the subject of the search
is a police officer familiar
with investigative tactics,
evidence code section 1040
should not apply.
Respectfully.What exactly
are the charges
the state is considering
against Officer Nolan?
Well, for starters,
assault with a deadly weapon,
attempted murder
of a peace officer,
and conspiracy.
Clearly an act
of self-defense.
Detective Armstrong lured
Officer Nolan to his house,
pulled a weapon,
and fired.
Now, Officer Nolan returned fire
in self-defense,
and no physical evidence
listed here asserts otherwise.
Sadly, Your Honor,
an informant has corroborated
Detective Armstrong's
account.
In a sworn statement,
he identified Officer Nolan
as working with
the Derian crime family.
Um, but their informant
has not be certified "tested"
or "reliable."
And with personal jeopardy
as a murder suspect
in this very case,
his account can hardly
be considered credible
without cross-examination.
[ Sighs ]
The state makes the case
corruption exists
within the division.
Officer Nolan
is connected to that,
and there is imminent threat
to the destruction of evidence
without expedient action.
[ Pen scratches ]
Aren't you two married?
Almost.Soon.
[ Chuckles ]
Good luck.
And good night.
[ Sighs ]
You did great back there.
Thanks.
You didn't make it easy.
Wesley...
...tell Nolan
I'm rooting for him.
Sergeant, Judge Paloma signed
the warrant at 0319 hours.
Endorsed for night service.
You're green and go.
Please be careful.
Nolan,
you're out of time.
They're coming in.[ Grunts ]
Don't resist.
Don't say anything.
I'll meet you
at the station.
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Heart beating ]
♪♪
[ Siren chirps ]Put your hands
behind your back.
Yes, sir.
[ Handcuffs clicking ]Am I under arrest?
Not yet.
We got to do everything
by the book.
Let's go.
Please tell me that Armstrong
has got cops all over him.
Yeah, I can't do that.
You know why.
Come on. You cannot believe
that Nolan is dirty.
We don't.Chen.
I got it from here.
Head to Nolan's.
Assist in the search.
Yes, sir.
Sergeant.
Um...
Uh...never mind.
Sir --Save it for upstairs.
Nolan?
Do you understand?
Nolan.
What?
Technically,
you're not under arrest.
You're cooperating.
But once you're not free to
leave beyond a brief detention,
that constitutes an arrest
and starts the clock.
D.A. will have 72 hours to
present their case against you.
Yeah, I-I know --
I know that.
Of course.
But I also know
that you're in shock,
and I need you to focus.
If convicted,
you're looking at 25 years,
which is why you need to
let me do all the talking.
One mistake,
one ill-chosen word,
and you are going
to prison.
But we don't have to
play it like that.
The truth is on my side.
And you think
that means something?
[ Scoffs ] If you were
any other defendant --
[ Sighs ]
What?
Never mind.No, I want to know.
If I was
any other defendant, what?
You are a white man.
A cop.
You have already been treated
with a level of deference
my other clients
would never get.
If you were Black
or Brown,
the police would've created
exigent circumstances
and kicked the door in,
shot you if they thought
you reacted aggressively,
arrested you
if you surrendered,
confident that the D.A.
would bully you
into a plea deal.
That's not fair.
I'm not that kind of cop.
Neither is Grey.You telling me
you've never bent the rules?
Not like that.
Look, you have a chance
to survive this
because of who you are.
But only if you do
exactly what I say.
Can you handle that?
It's been alleged
that the Derian crime family
recruited you during your tenure
as an undercover operative.
In exchange for money
and concealing your identity,
you provided
sensitive police intelligence
which helped them
avoid prosecution.
Now, is there any truth
to this?
Any bit at all?
Absolutely not, sir.
That is Armstrong's truth.
He did those things,
and he is using me and Nolan
to cover his tracks.
Detective Armstrong
has an unblemished record
here in this Department.
So I'm gonna need to see
some pretty serious evidence
to substantiate that.
Yes, sir.
We have body cam
and dash cam video
that shows Armstrong making
a series of texts
at critical moments
during the hunt
for Officer Rios' killer.
It was Armstrong
who redirected Nolan
into booking the murder weapon
into evidence
so that Erin Cole could steal
the gun from Nolan's shop.
Look, you can see here --
Armstrong hands her a note.
Do you have that note?
No, sir.
Then how can you know
what was on it?
I can't know for sure,
but I --
Armstrong says
that you and Nolan
lured him to the oil fields
under false pretenses
planning to kill him
because he was onto you.
That's another lie.
We were trying
to identify
the burner phone number
he was using
in hopes of getting our hands
on his call and text records.
And did you get any?No.
I mean, we did identify
the phone number,
but the phone had just been
activated that morning.
Which is when we decided
that Officer Nolan
should go speak
with Rosalind Dyer in prison.
What? Why?We figured
she would have
some sort of insight
into his criminality.
She also tried to have Armstrong
murdered a few months ago,
which makes it believable
that Nolan went to her
to conspire with her.
No. No.
That is not what happened.
Look,
this is Nolan's body cam
from when Armstrong
shot Erin Cole.
You can clearly see
that she says his name
beforeshe sees him.
Why didn't you come forward
with Officer Nolan's suspicions
prior to taking investigative
action on your own?
Why didn't you instruct your
trainee to trust the system?
I can see now
that I made a mistake.
But at the time,
I did not think
that it was in the department's
best interest
to disparage a fellow officer
without additional evidence --
That is not your damn job!
What does the placard say
on my desk?
Commander.
Internal Affairs.
This office is
the only investigative unit
required by
the California Constitution.
Do you know why?
Because police officers
are infused
with the power
of the state,
the power to take a life
in pursuit of justice,
power that is
all too easily abused.
And yet at every turn,
cops like you
look at us like the enemy --
the rat squad!
How the hell do you expect me
to root out problem cops
when I'm sabotaged
at every turn?!
We are going to tear
your life apart, Detective.
And if we find
as much as a typo
in the statement
you're about to write,
you won't be a cop
anymore.
[ Breathes deeply ]
We should be tearing Armstrong's
house apart, not Nolan's.
Relax, Boot.
We're doing both.
Look, we got a job to do.
We can't play favorites.
There is no way that
Harper and Nolan are dirty.
Three days ago, you'd
have said the same
thing about Erin Cole.
Y-- Sure.
But I know Nolan
a hell of a lot better
than I knew Erin, and so do you.
He's got the strongest
moral compass of us all.
Maybe. Or maybe that's only
who he is when it's easy.
Look,
at the end of the day,
we only think
we know other people.
I learned that
the hard way.
[ Straw slurping ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Slurping continues ]
What time is it?
Time for
another Fresca.
What's going on?
Not much, really.
"General Hospital's" on
in a few.
No. [ Sighs ]
With Nolan.
Oh, he's in custody.
Getting the full cavity search
from I.A.
You know,
I never trusted that guy.
Nobody's that nice.
They find anything
at his house?
W--
You're awake.
You were supposed to
text me.
Well,
he's filling me in.
That's not really
his job.
As long as we're talking,
can I ask you a question?
Yeah, of course.
Look,
you said that Nolan
came to your house
to kill you.Yeah.
But first,
he told you about
a bunch of evidence
hidden at his place?
Why would he waste time
doing that?
Nolan's a talker.
You know him.Yeah. I do.
But he's not a boaster,
and he's definitely
not stupid.
You accusing me
of something, Boot?
No, sir.
Just trying to wrap
my brain around this.
Look.
I get it.
I g-- I get it.
We all feel betrayed.
It's heartbreaking
to find out
that somebody
you cared about
isn't who you think
they are.
I mean...
[ Sighs, chuckles ]
I-I-I'm sorry.
I-I got to close my eyes.
That surgery
took it out of me.
I'm just...Sure thing.
We'll be right outside.Yeah.
Smitty.
[ Monitor beeping ]
♪♪
Tim: Find anything?Not yet.
Maybe there's nothing
to find.
Yeah, or maybe Nolan was trained
to know where cops would look.
Hell, he built this place up
from the studs.
Probably designed a hidey-hole
we'll never find.
Did we do all this?
Grey said the wall was ripped
apart before he came in.
Why would Nolan do that?
Don't know. Don't care.No, think about it.
Armstrong insists
that Nolan tried to kill him.
But then why did Nolan leave
before the job was done?
Why rush back here
and tear the walls up?
I'll tell you why --
it's because he's looking
for the evidence, too.
Woman: Bradford.
[ Sighs ]
You see, now,
that's a proper hidey-hole.
For a civilian.
You just got done saying
Nolan would build something
we'd never find.
Maybe I overestimated
the guy.
Mm, no.
Look, Nolan's a lot of things,
but he's not sloppy.
He comes in here, desperate,
rips open the walls,
ends up in the bedroom,
finds the opening
behind the bed
filled with whatever
Armstrong hid in there --
And then what?
And then...
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
♪♪
[ Police radio chatter ]
You don't think
that's random garbage, do you?
No,
that's Nolan being smart.
He knew we'd find
the goods,
so he chucked them
down the hill.
Our warrant is for Nolan's
property, not the neighbor's.
So, if we open that bag
without a Steagald warrant,
anything we find in there
will be inadmissible.
Exactly.
So let's go get that warrant.
Go for it.
But it's a waste of time.
What?Look, that is not
the evidence.
Nolan wouldn't
jeopardize evidence
by throwing it
down a hill,
where it could be damaged
or destroyed.
If I'm right
and he's innocent,
then that means
the real evidence
is hidden somewhere
in this house.
That bag is just a fake-out
meant to buy him some time.
Time for what?To talk his way
out of this.
Just remember,
don't say a word.
I'll do
all the talking.
Wesley: We'll be making our own
recording of this interview,
as is our right.
Further,
I'm exercising our right
to identify
everyone monitoring.
Very well.
I am Commander Percy West
of the Internal Affairs Unit.
Behind me in Observation
is Sergeant Wade Grey,
and Assistant District Attorney
Luca Bravant.
Thank you.
First of all --
Oh, no.
It doesn't work that way.
Officer Nolan, per government
code 3300 and Lybarger,
I am required to advise
that you do nothave
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you.
Refusal to fully and completely
answer all of my questions
will result in
your immediate termination
and referral
to the District Attorney
for prosecution.
Do you understand?Yes.
Having received
the Lybarger warning,
do you give up your right
to remain silent,
and will you honestly
and without reservation
answer all
of my questions?
Commander, my client has
no intention of answering --
Yes. Yes.
I'll answer
all of your questions.
Honestly, completely,
and without reservation.
No. He won't.
Not another word.
I have to do this.
No matter
the consequences.
If everything
you just said is true,
then why did you flee
the scene?
I object to that
characterization.
Officer Nolan
left Armstrong's house
because he was in fear
for his life.
Is that true?Not completely.
John.I left Armstrong's...
after he told me
he had hidden
incriminating evidence
at my house.
Honestly, I panicked.
Rosalind got into my head
at the prison.
She gave me slim odds
at survival against Armstrong
because he was smarter
than me
and more ruthless.
And she was right.
I never saw
the frame coming.
Where's the evidence
Armstrong planted?
It's in the water heater.
[ Sighs ] Yes.
Told you so.[ Sighs ]
We got police files, a couple
pistols, and a bunch of cash.
Alright.
CSU will process it.
If there's as much
as a single DNA strand
from Armstrong on it,
we'll know he's involved.
You up for
another assignment?
Whatever you need.
Drive up to Chowchilla
and retrieve
the security footage
of Nolan's meeting
with Rosalind Dyer yesterday.
What?
Sir, I'm --
I'm not sure
we're the right team
for that assignment,
given Chen's history
with Rosalind Dyer.
What assignment?
He wants us to get
the surveillance tape
from Nolan's meeting
with Rosalind yesterday.
What the hell was he doing
meeting with Rosalind?
Percy:
It's your call, Bradford.
You're her T.O.
I trust your judgment.
Tim,
it's not a problem.
Okay.
Yeah, we can handle it.
Sir, good intentions aside,
I know I made a mess of this.
You have to let me tryand fix it.You can't.
Even if everything
you told me is true
and Detective Armstrong
is guilty as sin,
your actions might very well
have allowed him
to muddy the waters enough
to escape punishment.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
And that'll be
my burden to bear.
But right now, we have
bigger fish than Armstrong.
Ruben Derian has been laughing
at this department for years.
Because of him,
two cops are dead.
He has to pay for that,
and I can make it happen.
Let me wear a wire.
No.
Look, it's not as crazy
as it sounds.
Yes.Yes, it is.
O-Okay, listen.
Just...
Ruben Derian is used to
playing with loaded dice.
He's always
a step ahead of us
because Armstrong's
been feeding him intel,
but now, for the first time,
he's flying blind.
He's gonna be desperate
to know what's going on,
whether the frame on me
is working,
whether Armstrong
has flipped.
And why would
he listen to you?
I'm the only guy
more desperate than he is.
Look, Armstrong is burned
in this department
no matter what.
But if Ruben can get Serj
to admit to the frame,
I'm redeemed.
I can stay on the job.
Ruben will see
the value in that.
He'll have a new molewith another 20 years
left on the job.
15 maybe.
We're done,
Officer Nolan.
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]He just saved
your life.
The odds of Ruben buying
your act are slim to none.
Well, he wouldn't
have to buy it.
A meeting alone would
constitute cons-- conspiracy.
And if he shoots you
on sight?
Then the D.A. could indict him
for capital murder.
Sir...
Sergeant, I know I can't undo
the mistakes I've made,
but I can help
make things right.
No matter
what it costs me.
♪♪
[ Door opens ]
You are,
without a doubt,
the biggest pain in my ass
I've suffered
in 25 years on the job.
Is that a yes?
Vice has a C.I.
in the Derian organization.
He works at
one of their karaoke bars.
We can use him
to spin Ruben,
giving you a fighting chance
to convince the Derians
that you're desperate
to make a deal.
I quit.
[ Sighs ]
[ Groans, retches ]
Hey.
[ Clears throat ]
How's it going?
Uh, my client
just staged a mutiny.
Now he's trying
to get himself killed.
Can we talk?
I can't.
I'm retracing Armstrong's
movements for I.A. --
Wesley.
You know I peed on that,
right?
Angela.
I'm just saying,
you might want to
wash your hands.
Angela.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why do you think?
I mean, you don't
want to have a kid?
[ Sighs ] This isn't how
it was supposed to go.
I wanted
the storybook wedding
and the honeymoon
that we'd never forget.
I wanted the romance
before the responsibility.
I wanted to be ready.
We can still have
all of that.
No, we can't.
It won't be the same.
No.
Not all of it.
But here's what
will be the same --
You are gonna look beautiful
in your dress.
And I will cry when I see you
walking down the aisle,
and you'll make fun of me for it
for the rest of our lives.
No, I won't.
Yeah, I will.
This is our path,
Angela.
And it is not the one that
we thought we were on yesterday,
but we are still on it
together.
I promise when we look back
at this moment,
it will feel like
the gift that it is.
You say that now,
but once the hormones kick in,
you're in
for a rough ride.
Bring it on.
This is the part
where you kiss me.
I would, but I'm feeling
super pukey right now.
So...rain check?
[ Sighs ]
[ Retching ]
What kind of a prison
doesn't have audio
on their surveillance
cameras?
Sound costs money.
Head back to the shop
while I go get a statement
from Rosalind.
What? No way.
It's for your own good.
You have
a personal connection.
So do you.It's not the same.
If I can't handle
talking to Rosalind
while she's in a cage,
I shouldn't be a cop.
[ Sighs ]
[ Door buzzes ]
Tim: We have a few questions
to ask you.
Shouldn't take long.
Mm. This is about John,
isn't it?
We know you talked to him
about Armstrong yesterday.
Can you describe the content
of that conversation?
You know,
I am so impressed with you.
The way you handled
what was obviously
a very traumatic
experience --
it's inspiring.
Thanks.
That means a lot
coming from you.
Rrow.
So defiant.
Alright,
let's stick to Nolan.
Just like you were when the lid
came down on that barrel.
You know, it must have
driven Caleb crazy --
denying him the fear
he so desperately
wanted to see in you.
How --
Do I know that?
[ Chuckles softly ]
You think the camera
in the barrel was for Caleb?
Don't listen to her, Chen.
She's just playing mind games.
Oh, I am totally
playing mind games.
But I'm not lying.
♪ Stars shining bright
above you ♪
♪ Night breezes seem
to whisper "I love you" ♪♪ Night breezes seem
to whisper "I love you"♪
♪ Birds singing
in the sycamore tree ♪
Knock it off.
Ah.
The fierce protector.
We're done here.
Let's go.
We'll have I.A.
follow up.
[ Door buzzes ]
Armstrong's lasted
this long
because his contingency plans
have contingencies.
Whatever you've already found,
there's more.
What did she mean
by that?
Armstrong's
prepared to run.
He's got a go-bag
hidden somewhere.
Lopez, I got something
for you to chase down.
Sgt. Grey:
So, we have to assume
the Derians are watching
the station,
so you'll be on your own
the second you leave.
I heard a whisper
y'all were up to something.
I want in.Forget it.
You are still under
active investigation.
And before you say
"So's Nolan,"
there's no operation
without him,
which is the onlyreason
why he's involved.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Then take a walk.
We will monitor you
through audio bugs and GPS --
You have to believe the lie
or else you can't sell it.
Ruben needs to feel like
you are desperate enough
to betray everything
you care about.
That shouldn't be
too hard to sell.
Anything else?Be careful.
But not too careful.
Undercover
is all about offense,
even when
you are playing defense.
Are you done?Yes.
No, no.
Don't be afraid to pull
the rip cord, okay?
Arresting Ruben Derian
is not worth your life.
NowI'm done.
[ Door buzzes ]Are you ready
to do this?
Yes, sir.
Woman:
We have some breaking news
in the recent scandal
rocking the LAPD.
A source inside the department
tells KZYO
that Officer John Nolan,
a rookie  in the Mid-Wilshire Division...Check, check.
...has been suspended
without pay,
and it appears
that criminal charges
will be filed at any moment.
♪ And now we're thrivin',
ain't nobody denyin' ♪
♪ This is my squad
[ Cellphone clicks, dials ]
[ Ringing]
Ruben: Who is this?It's John Nolan.
I'm hanging up.Wait.
[ Heart beating rapidly ]
If you don't help me,
I'm a dead man.
I'll do anything.
Keep your phone on.
[ Earpiece beeps ]We're in business.
8500 team,
subject's in play.
[ Cellphone rings, beeps ]
Lopez, what's up?
Just cementing
Armstrong's timeline.
The good news is that
his cellphone GPS
puts him at Nolan's house
for over an hour yesterday.
That's about how long
it would take
to cut a hole in the wall
and plant evidence.
Yes, sir. Good job.
Where you at now?Cemetery.
Armstrong spent 31 minutes here
after he left Nolan's.
Probably saying goodbye
to his wife
just in case
things went sideways.
That's what I thought,
but then Tim called.
Word is that Armstrong has
a go-bag hidden somewhere.
Wait a minute.
You don't think --
That he buried the bag
on top of his wife's coffin?
No. But I'm gonna do
some digging anyway.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Found it.
[ Sighs ]
[ Retches, coughing ]
What the hell was that?
Nothing. [ Sighs ]
It's been three hours.
How long before we give up?
Patience is a virtue,
Officer Nolan.
Yes, sir.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Here we go.
[ Cellphone beeps ]This is Nolan.
[ Distorted ] Hudson Avenue  and Twelfth Street, 10 minutes.
A second late
and we're gone.
[ Engine starts ]We're green and go.
I repeat,
we are green and go.
♪ Then get it all
♪ You want it all?
♪ Fight for it
I just landed.
20 seconds to spare.
No one in sight.
We're in place.
We're watching on the drone.
Get ready, Nolan.
Black SUV coming your way.
I see it.
[ Earpiece beeps ]Going dark.
♪ I'm out of pennies
for that wishing well ♪
♪ So I'm throwing bodies,
and they wish me well ♪
♪ Ride the wave Strip.
What?
Clothes off. Shoes, too.
Let's go.
♪ Caged animals in a cube,
chasing that salary ♪
♪ Into this business like
a knick to your femoral, bam ♪
[ Sighs ] They're stripping him
of all the bugs.
♪ Wanna cross my path,
you gotta pay ♪
♪ Pull on up to the --
♪ Moved from your stomach
up into your veins ♪
Seriously?You wanna roll
in your underwear?
Man: Should we pull the plug,
sir?
Negative.
Hold position.
♪ Others already
on their journey ♪
♪ Fight for it
♪ You want it all?
For your head.
No way.No hood, no go.
♪ You want it all?
♪ Fight for it
Don't suppose you washed this
after the last guy.
Get in the car.
♪ Then get it all
Sgt. Grey:
All units, hold position.
They'll be watching
for movement.
Drone operator,
do not lose him.
Man: Roger that.[ Door buzzes ]
♪ Conquer
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Breathes deeply ][ Ringing]
I have a call for you
at the nurse's station --
Sergeant Grey?
Boss is calling.
Probably to sing
my praises.
[ Telephone ringing ]
♪♪
Hello?
Hello, Nicholas.
How's the gunshot wound?
I'll survive.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm not so sure
about that.
You have made
quite a mess.
You can't really believe
that your slapdash
frame job of Nolan
is going to hold up.
Still got a couple cards
up my sleeve. Not anymore.
You see, I've been turning
those cards over for you.
Who do you think told John
about your little hidey-hole?
And now I've told them
about your go-bag.
You're out of moves, Nick.
Enjoy prison.
Wha--
[ Grunts ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ The Bobby Lees'
"Guttermilk" plays ]
Man: Heads up.
Losing visual.
They're going in a tunnel.
Moving to the other side to intercept.
Let's tighten up.
We need eyes on ASAP.
You sure he said Grey?
Positive.
Smitty.
What are you --
♪ I left that girl dyin'
somewhere down on the way ♪
♪ Stuck on that dead bus
and then left in a desert way ♪
♪ I haven't slept for my
Target reacquired.
Jackson:
Sergeant, Armstrong slipped
his detail at the hospital.
He's gone.All units,
we need to get Nolan out now.
♪ After what I saw
[ Tires screeching ]
♪ I'm just like guttermilk,
yeah ♪
[ Sirens wail ]
Show me your hands!
Roll down your window!
Get your window down.
♪ Somewhere down --
guttermilk ♪
Nolan.
Nolan's out of the pocket.
They must have switched him out
in the tunnel.
[ Smacks table ]
♪♪
[ Tires screech ]
[ Car door closes ]
♪♪
You wanted to talk?
So talk.
But maybe first,
explain to me
the surveillance team
that was following you.
That's your fault.
You didn't give me any time
to lose a tail.
What kind of sloppy protocols
is Armstrong teaching you?
Why don't you ask him
yourself?
[ Groans ]
[ Laughs ]
It was a nice play,
Nolan.
It was a nice play.
And it might've worked,
had I not called Ruben
and told him you were
way too much of a Boy Scout
to ever sell your soul.
You wanna do
the honors?
It'd actually be
my pleasure.
Careful. Last time
you tried this, you missed.
Yeah.
I made it too complicated.
Having to pull the gun,
flip the chair.
This is gonna be
much simpler.
I'd ask for last words, but
I'm sick of hearing your voice.
Wait![ Gun clicks ]
What the...?
♪♪
[ Groans ]
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Footsteps approach ]
[ Sighs ] Is he dead?
Drop the gun!
Now. On the ground.
Right now.
Take out your phone.
Dial 911.
Put it on speaker.
Place it next to your gun.
[ Ringing]
Woman: 911.
What's your emergency?
This is Officer John Nolan,
badge number 25253.
I have multiple suspects
in custody.
Requesting backup
and ambulances, plural.
One victim,
multiple gunshot wounds.
Status unknown.
Now, take off your clothes.
Excuse me?
Not you.
Strip. Now.
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪♪
Gunshot victim unconscious,
not breathing.
[ Door opens ]
So,
I'll make this quick.
N.O.I.D.
What does that stand for,
Officer Nolan?
Notice of Intent
to Discipline.
Why are you smiling?
'Cause it means
I still have a job.
Don't celebrate yet.
You're not gonna like
what's coming.
Neither will you,
Detective Harper.
Sir, can I say something,
please?
As a training officer,
I have one job,
and that is
to teach Officer Nolan
the right way
to be a cop.
And...I failed.
I should bear
all the consequences.
Nyla, no.Yes.
As touching as this is,
Officer Nolan has received
enough instruction
to know
right from wrong.
Clearly, I have given you both
way too much leeway.
That's on me.
What is Noble Cause Corruption,
Officer Nolan?
When an officer justifies
bending or breaking the rules
if they believe that infraction
is being done
in the name of justice.
The ends justify the means.
The mind-set
that bad behavior is okay
as long as
it produces justice
is a cancer.
And it's long past time
we treat it as such.
Big changes are being made
moving forward.
Those changes are starting
right here, right now.
You both will receive
letters of reprimand
in your file.
In addition,
Officer Nolan,
you will be held over
the FTO program
for an additional month,
and you will have to pass
a Review Board Test to advance.
Yes, sir.
To be clear,
receiving a letter of reprimand
as a rookie
is almost certain
to keep you from advancing
in the department.
So any hopes of joining
a specialized unit
or making detective
should be abandoned.
Given those constraints,
you will have to decide
if the life of a patrol officer
is good enough for you.
Alright, go home.
Get some rest.
I am so sorry.[ Scoffs ]
John, I --It's not your fault.
It's kind of a lot
my fault.
Nyla.
What are you gonna do?
Exactly what Grey said.
I'm gonna go home,
I'm gonna go to bed,
and in the morning,
I'm gonna get up and...
...try to earn back
what I've lost.
[ Black Gatsby's "The Price"
plays ]
♪♪
[ Door opens ]
You were wrong earlier.
About anything in particular,
or just in a global sense?
You said
at the end of the day,
we only think we know
other people, but you're wrong.
Okay, Lucy --
No.
When I was
in that barrel,
I knew
you would find me.
No matter what it took.
I found you
because of your ring, okay?
You saved yourself.
And I really hope what happened
with Rosalind today
doesn't screw
with your head.
If it does,
I'll deal with it.
And I know
you'll help me.
Uh, it's not really part
of my job description.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, uh,
I was wondering, um,
well, Chris' funeral
is tomorrow, and...
Look, is it okay
if I go home with you
and we can just go together
in the morning?
Of course.
We could talk about
you joining I.A.
on the way home.
Dad.
Look, I'm not saying
you have to decide now,
but if you really want to
make a difference
in this department,
you should think about it.
I will.
I promise.
Good.
I'll ask you again
next week.
I have no doubt.
I'm taking a long bath
when we get home.
I'm going
straight to bed.
No, you're not.
These dogs aren't gonna
rub themselves.
Pregnant women
are very needy.
I don't think
you're fully prepared.Uh-huh.
Lopez,
I have some good news.
Me, too.Can I go first?
It's the only
bright spot in my day.
Sure.
What's up?
It's been an honor
having you under my watch.
What?You will be reporting to
Detective Sergeant Caradine
from now on.
Your promotion
is official.
Congratulations,
Detective.
♪ This is the end
Thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
So what's your good news?
Uh, she's --Um, going to take a bath
and get my feet rubbed.
Okay.
Mine was definitely better,
but okay.
Thank you, sir.
It wouldn't have happened
without you.
Have a great night,
you two.
♪ Put the cash
right in my hand ♪
Why didn't you want me
to tell him?
I've been trying to
make detective for years.
If I show up pregnant
on day one,
that's all they'll ever
see me as.
They'll treat me as fragile,
and I'll never get a real shot.
Okay, so we keep it
a secret for now.
For now.
♪ On my way now,
on my way ♪
[ Lock clicks, keys jingle ]
[ Light switch clicks ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Cork pops ]
[ Liquid pouring ]
[ Bottle thuds ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Cellphone beeps, clicks ]Hello?
Congratulations.
I underestimated you.
Rosalind.
You won.
I didn't win.
People died.
People I care about.
I know.
But there is a bright side.
At least for me.
Armstrong's criminality puts
all of his cases in jeopardy.
Including mine.
Rosalind, you are never
going to walk free.
We both know that.
Now, I'm hanging up,
I'm calling the prison,
and they're gonna come
confiscate that phone you're on.
I know.
But it was worth it
to hear your voice.
I'll be dreaming abou--[ Cellphone beeps, clicks ]
[ Cellphone thuds ]
[ Sighs ]
--Captions by VITAC--
Download Movies from - www.msmoviesbd.com
♪♪