♪ Everybody gather 'round
♪ It's time to break through
the ups and downs ♪
♪ Lift your spirits...
- Professor Ryan.
- Oh, Officer Nolan.
Little late for class,
don't you think?
My apologies
for missing the exam.
I got, uh, stuck at work,
last-minute call.
- Armed robbery.
- Is everyone alright?
Yes, thank you,
but about the exam,
is there any way
I could make that up?
I made my policy clear
on the first day --
a missed test
is a failed test.
Yes.
You also said in your
first lecture that, uh,
"Strict law is often
great injustice." Cicero.
Oh, okay.
Well, if you want an exception,
you'll need to earn it.
Tell me what I have to do.
You have to answer
one legal question.
Okay, that's easy.
Um...
A woman witnesses
a stabbing in a nightclub.
She's pretty sure
the assailant is Black
and that he has a scar
on his right arm.
Wait. She's sure that he has
a scar on his right arm
but not sure that
he's African-American?
Did I say African-American?
Right. Black. Sorry. Mm-hmm.
Uh, there are
over 400 club-goers,
so it's going to take a while
to interview them all.
And the longer you wait...
The more their memories
will have a chance to degrade,
and it would give the assailant a chance to
destroy any evidence.
And if you do not find
the culprit tonight,
you probably never will.
So who do you round up
to question?
"A," all the Black men,
"B," all the men,
regardless of color,
or, "C," everyone?
Are there any more facts?
This isn't really easy to answer
based on what you've given me.
Well, this is not an easy class.
Get me the right answer
by end of day tomorrow,
and I will let you
make up the exam.
Right. Thank you. I will.
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
"Hey, sorry to do this by text,
but it's just
not working with us."
Yeah. What's going on?
Well, I set up a-a lunch for you
with the head of
the Mayor's security detail.
There's a driver position
opening.
Higher profile, better pay,
and it'll get you
to I.A. faster.
Look, thank you, but, um...
I'm just not sure that's where I
want to end up, you know?
Well, I thought after
the Doug Stanton situation,
you'd be motivated to
clean up the Department.
You want to be where you can do
the most good, right?
Yeah, yeah, of course, but --
Well, then it's settled.
I can't believe him.
- I know.
Maneuvering me to
I.A.like I have no say in it.
No, not your dad. Emmett
breaking up with me by text?
What is he, 14? He doesn't have
the guts to do it in person?
Most guys don't. Look, just
be happy he didn't ghost you.
Okay. Can we get to work now?
Did Emmett talk to you
about this?
No. Why would he?
Because you're friends.
We don't talk feelings.
We drink and watch sports together.
That's guy for "friends."
Well, straight guy
for "friends."
- Look, you want my advice?
- Walk it off.
He's clearly not the right guy for you.
That is the same advice he
would give me if I got hit by a pitch.
What is wrong with men?
So much. Look, I
am really sorry to hear that.
But I will pick up some tequila and
ice cream on the way home,
and we can listen to my
breakup playlist on repeat
and maybe throw a few
little shady prank calls at Emmett.
- Thanks.
- Here. Here you go.
Change of clothes,
prenatal vitamins,
antacid, anti-gas, ginger chews,
and magnesium supplements.
I have never loved you more.
Have, uh, you heard anything
from the kidnappers?
Not since the last ransom demand.
But I'm waiting on DNA
results from the crime scene.
Hopefully they come in before I
get back to the Abassi house.
Mm. How's Judge Abassi
holding up?
As well as can be, I suppose,
considering his son
was abducted.
You've argued in front of him.
You know anyone
who'd want revenge?
Every criminal who ever
stepped foot in his court.
Half the lawyers.
I'm gonna need more clothes.
DNA results?
No, it's your mom,
texting me again.
Yeah, sorry. She wants to talk
about the baby's trust fund.
Whatever the question is, my answer is yes.
That has been well established.
But, believe me, there are
complications to having money.
Like always being able to
pay the rent or buy food?
Like having your child
kidnapped for ransom.
Finally, my DNA results.
Um ...gotta get changed.
You can, um, handle your mom, right?
"Uh, yeah, Mom?
You're breaking up.
I'm gonna have to
call you back."
Perfect. Love you.
I love you, too.
I need a couple unis
on my kidnapping case.
Can you spare
Harper and Nolan?
Sure thing.
- What do you need them for?
- I'm running down a lead.
I have a conflict of interest.
Something I should know about?
Not yet. Okay.
I'll call Harper and Nolan
back in.
Actually, have them meet me
at the Abassi house.
Will do. Appreciate it.
Looking good, Officer West.
Don't I always, Detective Lopez?
So, Officer West,
I've decided who it is
you'll be riding with today.
Great. Who's the lucky officer?
Me. Sir?
Considering your upcoming
graduation from the FTO program,
I thought it'd be a good idea
if we talked about your future
in the department.
Funny. Just had a similar
conversation with my dad.
Did he enlist you
to help steer me to I.A.?
No. I.A. is not
the right path for you.
But you know what is.
Yes, I do.
Now go set up our shop.
If you were to single out all
the Black men for questioning,
it wouldn't be,
technically, profiling
because the added element that
they were all in the building
when the crime was committed
makes it legally okay, right?
I-It's a dark, crowded bar.
Are we sure the witness
even saw a Black guy?
No, the witness
wasn't definitive.
So what's the answer?
Well, you're going about this
all wrong.
It's not about finding
the right answer.
It's about finding the answer
that she wants.
Or the one
that she doesn't want.
Can't imagine she'd think
me worthy of retesting
if all I said was
"Question all the Black men."
Why? 'Cause she's Black?
Well, yeah. Right?
What?
She could just be testing you --
to see if you'd censor yourself
with her to curry favor.
Hey. Let me bring you
up to speed.
This is Austin Abassi, age 20,
son of Judge William Abassi.
Three days ago,
Austin was kidnapped
from his apartment in Hollywood.
The kidnappers sent
an untraceable e-mail
demanding 100 grand in ransom.
On Thursday night,
a backpack full of cash
was left at the designated
drop-off spot,
but Austin wasn't returned.
Let me guess -- they came up
-with the 100
-K so fast,
the kidnappers wanted more?
A million. That's when the Judge
finally called the police.
We processed the crime scene.
A female DNA sample was found
on an empty beer bottle.
- Did you get a match?
- She's not in our system,
but a familial DNA test
determined the sample
comes from the offspring
of someone we currently
have behind bars.
Someone I can't interview
because of
a conflict of interest.
- Oscar?
- You have got to be kidding me.
I'm guessing
your conflict of interest
is that he stabbed your fiancé.
Technically, my conflict is
the desire to kill him for that.
But you wouldn't really.
I'm pregnant. Don't try me.
O-Okay. So, wait.
Oscar has a daughter?
Not according
to any official records.
In fact, I can't find any
records of a relationship.
That doesn't surprise me.
Oscar's too much of a narcissist
to keep a girlfriend.
- What's going on?
- Did something happen?
Judge Abassi, Mrs. Abassi,
this is Detective Harper
and Officer Nolan.
They're going to be running down
a lead regarding this man --
Oscar Hutchinson.
He's currently serving
40 years at Cal Correctional
for multiple violent felonies.
Harper and Nolan will be going
to the prison to question him.
Whatever resources you need,
you'll have them.
Yes, and if there's a deal
to be made, please, make it.
We need Austin back safely.
Well, the good news is,
uh, with Oscar,
there's always
a deal to be made.
Sir, feel free to call us if
his stereo gets that loud again.
Have you ever been dumped
out of the blue before?
Let me think.
One time, my wife left the house
in the middle of the night,
and I didn't see her again
for two years.
Okay, I get it.
In the grand scheme of things,
this isn't that bad.
I just wanna know why.
Can you please ask?
Somebody tagged our shop?
It can't be.
It's been almost a decade.
Since what?
No, it's definitely him.
The color palette,
the angle of the letters.
What is happening right now?
♪ Get back up, get up,
go get it ♪
Control to 7-Adam-19,
I've got an on view felony
five-ninety-four.
I'm setting the Command Post
at Pico and La Brea.
Start me enough units
for a six-block perimeter,
a canvass team,
a forensic team, air support,
notify the Press
Information Officer.
♪ Let's go ♪ Let's go
Oscar has to be behind this
kidnapping somehow, right?
No record of
any female visitors,
and none of his mail has
ever referenced a daughter.
So either Oscar's been keeping
her a secret from us...
And why do that?...or he's unaware
that she even exists.
Which presents a clear argument
for nature over nurture
as a predicate
for criminal behavior.
If she's involved
in the kidnapping at all
and not just some kid who had
a beer at Austin's apartment
and went home
before he got grabbed.
There are so many unknowns,
and I, for one, am confident
that Oscar's gonna
answer all of them.
I'm kidding.
He's gonna be a giant
pain in the ass.
Hey, it's my two
favorite police officers.
As you can see, we've mostly
cleaned up the place
after the riot.
It's really hard to get brains
out of cinder block.
I guess you'd know.
You don't get a lot
of visitors, do you?
I'm not sure what the point
would be.
I'm not going out of here
on my feet --
unless you come
bearing a pardon.
No such luck. Mm.
Then what are you doing here
asking questions about visitors?
DNA turned up at a crime scene
that links directly to you.
But you have been in here, so...
What are the matches
in the polymorphic markers?
You learn a lot about DNA
in my line of work.
6 out of 13.
That's a first-degree relative.
Since both my folks are dead
and I'm an only child...
...I got a kid.
What'd he do?
She is connected
to a kidnapping.
Oh, way to go!
You really had no idea
you were a father?
No.
Wow. It's a lot to process.
Well, all this time, I had
an organ donor on the outside.
I'm gonna really hit that
prison hooch harder now.
Okay. I'm gonna need you
to make a list
of every woman
that could be the mother.
Yeah.
That's not gonna be that easy.
I don't like to brag, but I was
quite popular back in the day.
Alright. On to the next lead.
Uh, uh, now, hold up, now. Hold.
Um, a drive around my old haunts
might really jog the memory.
- Forget it.
- You gotta give to get,
Detective.
You want help?
I want a day pass.
You're gonna do it,
because we both know
you wouldn't have driven all the way
out here if you had any other leads.
Road trip.
Judge Abassi must have
friends in high places
- to get this approved so fast.
- You know Oscar's gonna
try to rabbit the first
chance he gets, right?
We're not gonna
give him that chance.
♪ Slam, da duh-duh, da duh-duh ♪
♪ Let the boys be boys
They say fashion is cyclical.
Think this is coming back in?
Yeah. That's gonna take
a few more cycles.
Hey, I'm happy to see
they updated your look
with some modern jewelry.
Alright. So, here's how
this is gonna work.
You stop cooperating,
it's back to prison.
You mislead us,
You say a joke that
I don't really think is funny,
it's back to prison.
I'm sensing a pattern.
You try to escape --
"It's back to prison."
Maybe by way of
the emergency room.
No. That's not how we roll.
But Judge Abassi might not be
as dispassionate.
And I bet he can get you
transferred to a Super Max
just as easily as he
got you out on furlough.
There's no reason to be
like that. We're a team.
So where's my stuff?
All the names and numbers of
my conquests are right on here.
♪ Let the boys be boys
♪ Slam, da duh-duh...
You got a charger?
When was the last time
someone went through this?
Can probably get a few bucks
for this on eBay.
Keep looking.
♪ Da duh-duh,
let the boys be boys ♪
For Lila. Ah!
This is the charger.
We can juice this baby up
in the car
while we're getting
an early lunch.
It's cruel and unusual
punishment
to deprive a prisoner
of nourishment.
Start moving.
-Look, 3
-Eyez was active
from 2006 to 2010.
Victims all over the city.
Just when I thought I got close
to catching him, he stopped.
I thought maybe he died or
got arrested on other charges.
I still check VICAP
every three months to see
if he pops up in another city.
Must've been a seriously
hard-core guy
for you to obsess like that.
What was his main crime?
This. He's a tagger.
Cost the city hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
In property damage.
It doesn't explain why you
were so obsessed with --
- Wait.
- Hold on.
3Eyez tagged your shop?
Back when you were a rookie?
My T.O. was chasing a suspect.
I was guarding a vehicle
full of evidence.
A vehicle that was 10 feet away
from your shop?
It was right under your nose.
I was ordered to keep my eyes on the car.
I had just left the Army, where
you follow orders to a "T."
Oh, man, I could just imagine
the relentless teasing.
Did they give you a nickname?
Please say yes.
No.
That's why you're so intent
on catching this guy.
It's personal.
He's a criminal,
and it's our job to stop him.
I mean, the statute of
limitations on these crimes
ran out years ago.
Even if we were
to track him down
for tagging our shop,
it's a misdemeanor.
Is that really
the best use of our time?
I will get us a fresh shop.
Colleen, this is Oscar. Hey.
Listen. Is there any chance
I knocked you up in the late '90s?
Hello?
-Sasha. Baby, it's Oscar.
You ever call me again,
I'll come down there
and rip your throat out!
Okay. I'm gonna
take that one as a no.
Hello?
- Betty.
You know, I was just
thinking of you, too.
Okay. Put it on speaker.
...much fun.
We always tore it up, didn't we?
We sure as hell did.
Listen. Um, is there any chance
you and I had a kid together?
No, but I'm down to try.
I still have a few eggs
left in me.
Well, listen, they give me
conjugal visits --
Okay! You know what? That's it.
Are you there?
This is not a dating service.
If you are not helping,
you are going back.
Baby, I'll call you back.
Look, if it's not Betty,
it's probably Margaret.
She works at a diner,
like -- I don't know --
10 blocks or so from here.
Worth a shot, right?
Fine.
I think you should teach
at the Academy.
I mean, yeah, sure, when I'm Nolan's age.
They need you now.
The good you can do as a teacher
is exponential.
I know it's not what
you were picturing,
but keep an open mind.
Once you hit P2, I can steer you
to assignments that will
help prepare you to teach.
Look, I'm... obviously grateful
for your faith in me -- Great.
I'll set up a lunch with
a few instructors on Tuesday.
Um, I'm actually
supposed to be meeting
with the Mayor's team
on Tuesday.
But I'm sure I could do both.
Control, 7-Adam-07, I have
an on view five-ninety-four,
tagging in progress, at
South Rimpau and Olympic.
♪ A good man know a bad man ♪
♪ ...know a good man
Aah!
Sir, are you okay?
Aah! I'm good! Go!
Aah!
Damn it!
Officer down,
South Rimpau and Olympic!
Are you having
a heart attack, sir?
No! No, it's my back.
Are you sure? Yeah, I'm sure!
- Is he having a heart attack?
- No! It's just my back.
- Where is the tagger?
- He went left around the corner.
Stay here and call an ambulance.
- Okay.
- Aah!
Look, don't move.
Sir, don't get up.
♪ A little bit
of bad, bad, bad, bad ♪
♪ A little bit of
♪ A little bit
of bad, bad, bad, bad ♪
♪ A little bit of
Son of a...
Questioning every man
at the nightclub
would be more palatable.
That's not racial profiling.
But it would take forever.
What I should do is take a photo
of everybody holding their IDs
as they leave the club.
That way, I can circle back.
Yeah, but that's not one of the options.
I know.
Whren vs. US Supreme Court
says you can profile
as much as you want, as long as
there's at least some pretense.
I don't think
that's what they meant.
It is what they meant.
I got my law degree online
two years ago.
You know I'm licensed
to practice in five states
and the unincorporated territory
of Guam?
Okay. What's your take on this?
There's a stabbing
at a nightclub.
The victim says she's pretty
sure the suspect is Black
and he has a scar
on his right arm.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
She's sure about the scar
but only "pretty sure"
that he's Black?
- That's what I said.
- Something's off.
Obviously, she's creating
a diversion
while he's probably in the back,
robbing the place.
That's what you get
for asking a sociopath.
Mmm, I love the smell
of a greasy spoon.
Sit wherever you want.
Oscar? I thought you were in
prison for the next 40 years.
Early release. Good behavior.
-Seriously? No.
He's helping us with a case, and
then he's going straight back.
Okay. You're no fun.
Can I have some pie?
Did you and Oscar have a kid?
Oscar?
I am sorry. Do I know you?
You lousy little --
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Ma'am, ma'am, ma'am. Easy.
- What is all this about?
You knock me up and disappear,
and then I find out
you're in jail for murder?
Wait. Ashley is Oscar's kid?
You cheated on me with Cindy?!
Hold on. I think
it's coming back to me.
You son of a --Ladies, ladies! L-Ladies!
Please, I appreciate
how difficult
this must be for you,
but right now
we need to speak
with your daughter.
- Is she in trouble?
- I hope not.
But the sooner we find her,
the sooner this guy
gets back behind bars.
Let me get a pen.
Sir, don't get up.
Officer Chen, remind me.
Which one of us
gives the orders?
You do, sir.
Yeah.
Dave? Oh, you work
with Emmett, right?
Yes and yes.
Did you lose consciousness
at any point?
- No.
- Any pain in your chest?
No, I threw my back out.
It happens two times a year
like clockwork.
Well, I still gotta take you in,
make sure there's nothing else.
So, you're going out
with Emmett, right?
Was. Oh. Sorry.
Why the hell would he break up
with you? You're gorgeous.
Uh, do I really need
to be here for this?
No, sir.
I, uh, finished canvassing.
No one got a good look
at the tagger.
We're ready to transport him.
You'll follow?
No, I have to wait for my T.O.
Officer West
will take over from here.
Too bad.
Do you want to go out later?
Tonight? God, yes.
Okay. Great.
Uh, Jackson will
give you my number.
Bye.
What are you doing?
What? A girl can ask a guy out.
Yeah, a guy that works
with your ex?
- That is not why I did that.
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh --
- No comment.
Boot, let's go.
Not a word about the shop.
- Give him my number.
- I see you.
So, you're my dad, huh?
Mom told me you were
a roadie for Matchbox 20.
Better than
telling you I was serving 20.
It's more like 40.
How do you know Austin Abassi?
Uh, we were dating a little.
When was the last time
you saw him?
I don't know.
A week ago, maybe two.
Is he okay?
He's been kidnapped.
And you're lying to us.
I-I'm not.
Crime-scene techs found your DNA
on a beer bottle
in Austin's apartment.
That DNA wouldn't have
survived a week.
You need to come clean.
Right now.
As Ashley's lawyer,
I'm going to advise her
not to talk to you
until we've conferred.
Okay, that's not gonna
happen, because you're
not a real lawyer,
and even if you were,
there are rules against
family representing family.
Wrong. I passed the bar.
And as far as that being rules,
it's more like guidelines.
And even if they were rules,
we're family by blood only.
You do not want him
as your lawyer.
- He's a nine-time loser.
- If you tell them anything
without first getting
advice of counsel,
you're guaranteed
to do jail time.
Okay. He's my lawyer.
Could I have a moment alone
with my client, please?
So, you're in on it.
Maybe. Come on, kid.
Sniffing out cons
is on the family crest.
Okay.
Austin's parents cut him off,
so we figured,
if he was kidnapped,
his parents would
have to pay up.
Okay. That's not the most
original idea, but still,
if you execute it properly,
I guess...
Where is he now?
A friend's apartment
in Culver City.
Okay. I'm gonna
see you through this.
But you have to insist that I'm
with you every step of the way.
They're going to try
and separate us.
Okay.
You know, I really
can't picture
you and Mom together.
You kidding me?
She was the love of my life.
Officers?
Yeah, what we have here
is a victimless crime.
Austin was having a disagreement
with his parents about money --
So he faked his own kidnapping?
Not the most original idea.
And not victimless, either.
Austin's parents have been
going through hell with worry.
Whatever.
- Uh, they're loaded.
- Not a million dollars loaded.
They have been frantically
trying to pull money together.
Who said anything
about a million?
Austin sent an e-mail
asking for 100K.
That was delivered yesterday.
And he didn't tell you.
That snake's trying
to cut me out.
I'm gonna kill him.
That's my girl.
And a-as your lawyer,
I recommend that you refrain
from making any kind of
threats -- even in jest.
Do you know where Austin is now?
Yeah.
I-I don't want
to be in handcuffs.
Oh, no one does.
You get used to it.
Austin?
That bastard. He must have
taken the money and split.
Everybody freeze.
Control, 7-Adam-15,
update my call
to a suspicious circumstance.
I have blood at the location,
and the occupant is missing.
Possible two-oh-seven.
And I need a unit
to escort a prisoner
- back to Cal Correctional.
- Uh, wait a minute.
Who else did you tell about
your fake kidnapping plan?
-Don't answer that.
Your so-called lawyer
does not have your best interest
at heart.
He is only looking to extend
his time out of prison.
If you actually care about
Austin, you'll help us find him.
The only way you're
gonna stay out of prison
is by moving your way
up the food chain.
Take us to your boss.
You order takeout?
No.
W-Whoa! Don't hurt me. I'm --
Police. What's in the bag?
I don't know.
It's a TaskFast gig.
Pick it up from "A,"
drop it off at "B."
And where was Point "A"?
Car wash on Melrose.
"I'll drain a pint
of blood every two hours
until I get my million bucks."
Oh, my God.
Angela.
Don't know what to
congratulate you on first --
detective or baby.
Long as your presence
is letting me keep this case,
- it doesn't matter.
- Ooh, sorry.
Judge Abassi already reached out
to the SAC personally.
My guys are en route.
We'll take it from here.
You should, uh --
You should go home.
Get some rest, put your feet up.
Angela, you're gonna be a mom.
Congratulations.
You know, I recently
became a parent myself
- if you want any tips.
- Oscar Hutchinson.
And you must be the daughter,
girlfriend, co-conspirator?
And my client. You can't speak
to her alone without me present.
You're a felon
and a family member.
Well, we can stand here
arguing about my standing,
or we can say goodbye to LAPD,
go in, make a deal,
catch the kidnapper,
and have you home by dinner.
Alright. Let's go. Both of you.
Sir, you can't trust him.
This is not my first day...
Officer.
Listen, it was really nice
seeing you two again.
And, Nolan, because you're
such a Good Samaritan,
I'm gonna help you answer
that law-class question.
The answer is, "A,"
detain all the Black guys.
Because, well,
that's what cops do.
And -- And, A-Angela, listen,
if -- if you need a birth coach,
I just got
my Doula certification,
and, you know, we can negotiate
a really good nice price.
Alright, let's go, smart guy.
- Good job not killing him.
- Thanks.
I'm gonna go pack up my stuff.
Mm.
Yes?
Professor Ryan,
it's, uh, John Nolan.
Do you have an answer for me? N-Not yet.
Um, am I limited to the answers
that you gave me?
- Yes.
- The thing is, that
description isn't reliable,
so as an officer,
I'd have to hone in
on the other witnesses -
She hung up on me.
This isn't funny. I'm sorry.
- I need this make-up test.
- I know.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Where should we go tonight?
- Do you think he likes sushi?
- Everybody likes sushi, right?
- What?
You disapprove?
You think I'm just dating him
to make Emmett jealous?
And, yeah, maybe I am,
but he deserves it, and it's --
Will you say something, please?
Look, today's the first time
you've talked about Emmett
in weeks.
Well, you hate it when I talk
about personal stuff.
And yet you still do.
But in all those conversations,
you haven't said one word
about your boyfriend.
What are you saying?
Look, maybe Emmett
treated the relationship
like it didn't matter because
you treated it
like it didn't matter.
Alright, focus up.
You read the file.
-You think 3
-Eyez
is done for the day?
Um... no.
He tagged two police cars, but
they're already being repainted,
and he got interrupted
when he tagged that building.
He'll want to throw up
a full tag.
Somewhere that makes
a statement.
Exactly. And we'll be there
to catch him.
"Eagle Eye."
What? The nickname I got.
Uh, after the shop
got tagged under my nose.
But it wasn't my T.O.
who came up with it.
It was Isabel. Kind of
became her pet name for me.
Aww. That's sweet.
Yeah.
7-Adam-19.
Falling accident,
8950 South Ridgley Drive.
Injuries unknown.
7-Adam-19, responding.
Where's Jackson? The CAD report
said officer down.
He's not answering his cell --
Percy. Jackson's fine.
I got hurt.
He's just getting us
a cup of coffee.
What happened?
Tried to chase down the tagger.
I threw my back out.
You know you're
too old for that.
Follow my lead, take a desk job.
Pay's better.
I hear you've been pushing
Jackson toward I.A.
We need him. There's
a lot more Dougs to weed out.
That's true.
But Jackson's in a unique
position to make a difference.
So I think he'd have more of an
impact at the Academy than I.A.
Well, he's my son.
You don't think I know
what's best for him?
I know he's your son.
I'm not trying --
You can, uh, have mine, Dad.
I'll come back once you guys
are finished planning my career.
Ma'am, don't move.
Alright? An ambulance
is on its way.
I think it's broken.
- Uh, Tim?
- Just one second.
Ma'am, can you tell me
exactly what happened?
Eagle Eyes, you should look up.
-You're 3 -Eyez?
W-W-What? N-No.
You tagged my shop. Twice.
Technically, three times.
Shutting up.
It's not as easy
as it used to be.
I'm exhausted.
So I get to participate
in the prison garden program.
It's three times a week.
Practically smell the fresh air.
And a case of ginger ale a week.
Name brand.
Not the discount crap.
Fine. Just tell me
who's got Austin.
Where was the proof-of-life
photo taken?
You know, speaking of
ginger ale, I'm super dry.
And I have an awful lot
to tell you.
Fine. But you're giving it
all up when I get back.
You know what we love
about you, Oscar?
It's that you're
so damn predictable.
Well, you can't blame
a lifer for trying.
- Shouldn't we have told the FBI?
- I texted Lopez.
She said we'd fill them in
once Oscar took us
to the kidnappers
and we made the arrest.
I told you before, I can't
betray my client's trust.
Unless we get something
in return.
You've got no leverage here.
The FBI is not
gonna deal with you now.
And if we charge you with
obstruction of justice,
the warden's gonna take away
all of your privileges.
Fine. But I want a cupcake.
After. A cupcake?
I heard they've gotten fancy
since I went in.
- Deal.
- Now what do you know?
Well, according to my daughter,
the only other person
that knew about the scam
was Austin's drug dealer,
Malcolm Green.
He works out of a chop shop
in Sylmar.
Alright,
we're gonna do some recon,
see if you're telling the truth.
No problem. I'll just
hang out here by myself.
- Maybe I'll take a nap.
- Oh, come on, Oscar.
We've been through far too much
for you to pretend like you're
not just trying to escape
the second we turn our back.
So we got you a babysitter.
That's the guy
you want me to watch?
Yep. Give me your handcuff keys.
What?
So he doesn't trick you
into letting him go.
Oh. Like that could happen.
Fine.
If you hear gunshots,
call in the cavalry.
But do not leave him.
You should tell Oscar about
your plans to become a DJ.
Happy to!
Too harsh?
For Oscar? No.
It's time to send
the judge another package.
Go get a pint of blood
from the kid.
That's the same
as a liter, right?
How should I know?
I don't speak metric.
But a pint's definitely
less than a quart --
-Dude. Same amount as last time!
-Come on!
Alright.
I don't see Austin, but I think
we're running out of time.
These two idiots are gonna
kill him without meaning to.
Control, 7-Adam-15, we have
the two-oh-seven suspects.
We have exigent circumstances.
We are making entry.
I need Code 3 backup.
And notify the supervisor.
♪ I got it, I got it, I'm good
♪ I get it
♪ I bought it, I bought it,
I get it, I get it ♪
♪ I got it, I got it, I'm good
♪ I'm wit' it, I'm wit' it,
I get it, I get it ♪
♪ I got it, I got it, I'm good
♪ You dig it?
Squad hustle like a relay ♪
♪ On his back like a...
Whoa.
I've only seen that in movies.
I'm gonna buy a Porsche.
And a stripper -- two strippers.
What are you gonna do
with your money?
Dude! Quit it!
He doesn't look so good.
Looks better than you.
He's fine.
He doesn't look fine.
Must have been a ghost
or something.
My grandma told me
this story about this, uh,
ghost that was haunting toilets.
Grandma?
Really creepy stuff, man,
like out-there type stuff.
- Police!
- Down!
Get down on the ground.
Get on the ground.
Drop it right now.
Right now! Drop it!
-Get down on the ground!
-Down on your knees.
Down on your knees!
Interlace your fingers.
- You got them?
- Got 'em.
7-Adam-15, we got a Code 4.
Scene's clear for EMTs.
25-year-old male,
unconscious but breathing.
Heavy blood loss.
Okay, Austin, you're
gonna be alright, buddy.
We got help on the way.
You said
you were gonna make a deal,
that I wouldn't see the inside
of a jail cell.
Yeah, I might've lied
about that.
You're the worst father ever.
Is there a mug for that?
Oh, hello!
I love a man of his word.
It's gonna take a little while
to process you.
You're gonna want to
keep your blood sugar up.
Ah, a cupcake.
Thanks.
I didn't know you had
that kind of cruelty in you.
Oh, it's not about that.
See, as parents,
that's what we do.
We sacrifice for our children.
Sheriff's Department will
be here shortly,
take you back to prison.
I do feel something, you know.
About having a kid,
knowing the old
Hutchinson bloodline
isn't gonna die with me.
And yet you still put yourself
first every step of the way.
It's all I know.
I know I'm wasting my breath
on this, but...
if you really want to
improve yourself in prison,
stop taking random degrees and
just take a hard look inside.
If you want to be more than just
a cautionary tale to that girl,
you got a lot of work to do.
So, I gotta know --
why'd you start up again
after all these years?
My husband dumped me
for his massage therapist.
And I realized I wasted
the last seven years of my life.
So what? You wanted to get back
at him for leaving you?
No.
I just... wanted to
feel young again.
You're being charged with
a misdemeanor.
You'll have to pay a fine.
Otherwise, you're free to go.
And for what it's worth...
♪ I've known you
my whole life ♪...you're still young.
♪ Still can't figure you out ♪
And your husband's an idiot.
♪ What makes me wanna cry
is what makes you wanna shout ♪Thanks.
♪ I used to get so mad,
now I can't live without ♪
- Hey.
- Oh, hi.
♪ You don't care about
money We still on for tonight?
♪ No, we didn't have a cent Um...
♪ Couple of nobodies I didn't have
the purest motives
when I asked you out earlier.
You're trying to get back
at Emmett. I get it.
W-- Why did you say yes?
Dude keeps beating me
at Pictionary.
I could use a win.
S-So, we're being equally petty.
Great.
Look, the guy broke up with you
over text.
He has this coming.♪ Oh, my, my
But if you've changed
your mind...
Yeah, I have.
I want to go out
for the right reasons,
not because I'm hurt and angry.
I respect that.♪ I knew you were crazy
But mark your calendar.
I'm gonna ask you out again
in two weeks.
Deal.
♪ I knew when I let you go,
I'd be back again ♪
Mm.
What? What?
Well, you called me down here.
No, I didn't.
I did.
Uh, look, I really appreciate
you both for, um,
having such an interest
in my future.
And I know I wouldn't have
these career options
if you hadn't opened the door.
Look, I-I have to
find my own path.
And it's way too soon
to know what that is.
♪ I knew when I let you go,
I'd be back again ♪
I just hope that you both
are okay with me
coming to you for advice
as I figure things out.
Of course.
♪ You don't get pushed around,
you always defend ♪Yeah.
But you better come to me first.
I am your father.
He's right.
But he is a little close
to the situation,
so you better check in
with me after,
for a more balanced opinion.
R-Right, yeah.
♪ So I'm bleeding for you Yes, sirs.
Kidnapping yourself
to get your parent's money?
That is messed up.
Sadly, I knew more than a few
Austin Abassis growing up.
You know, I always heard
money could ruin a kid.
I just thought that was
something rich people said
to keep poor people
in our place.
I'm gonna call Patrice tomorrow,
discuss how we structure
the trust
so our kid doesn't grow up
to be an entitled jerk.
That sounds like a plan.
♪ ...some way, some day,
somehow ♪
So, are we gonna talk
about Oscar?
When I found out
Oscar was connected,
I fantasized about tearing him
apart with bearcats
and then peeing on
what was left.
Then I realized that
saving that kid's life
was the only thing
that mattered.
Oscar just wasn't
worth the effort.
Amen to that.
You know, your fantasies
are a little gruesome.
That's not what you said
last night.
♪ ...told me I could fly
♪ Convinced me there has never
been a better time to be alive ♪
Professor Ryan.
Oh, you almost missed
your deadline.
Almost.
So, do you have an answer
to my question?
Yes. Uh, no, actually.
Um, I spent the day trying to
figure out the answer
you were looking for.
Clearly, the racial element to
the question wasn't accidental,
so was it all just a test
to see what I would do
to avoid a failing grade?
And then I realized something
that gave me
the clarity that I needed --
the consequences of doing
my job wrong are too extreme
to just pick an answer
to curry favor with you.
I can't pick "A,"
question all the Black men,
because that would
just be wrong.
I can't pick "B" or "C"
'cause there's not enough
information.
We both know what damage
a false arrest can do
to a person's reputation,
to their psyche.
So if failing the answer
to the question means
I don't make up my exam
and get an "F,"
so be it.
Hmm.
Okay.
♪ Oh, somewhere, oh, somehow
You have 45 minutes.
Yes!
Thank you.
Oh, do you mean right now,
to be --
Mm-hmm.
That --
Yeah, okay, that's fair.
Unexpected.
Didn't think that would work.
"John Nolan."
--Captions by VITAC--
Damn it.