There they are.
Ooh.
Bright-eyed and bushy-tailed.
They got no idea
what's coming for them.
Please tell me we did not
look that nervous
our first day as rookies.
Alright. Let's go give them
a warm Mid-Wilshire welcome.
Hey. New recruits?
Welcome, guys. My name is --
John Nolan. Yeah. Hi.
Wow. It is such a pleasure
- to meet you.
- Wow.
You were my inspiration for
coming into the department.
And when I think about
six months ago,
I-I was data auditing
the AP matrix
in the IT department.
Well, thank you for saying that.
We're very happy to have you.
Uh, I'm Lucy,
and this is Jackson.
Hey.
Welcome to Mid-Wilshire.
Are you rookies, too?
- Not anymore.
- We're --
W-Well,  we're actually P2s.
While I selflessly
held myself back
so that you guys could
get your bearings.
Come on.
Do you know
who your T.O. is yet?
I think his name is Bradford.
Oh, he was my T.O. He's great.
You will learn so much.
But?
He can be intense.
But don't worry.
If you find yourself
in a self-doubt spiral,
I'm always around. Thank you.
Rookies sit in front row.
This way.
Right here? Yeah. Plant her.
Thank you. You betcha.
Sorry about that.
How much did you
have to bribe Grey
to not give you
Bizarro World Nolan?
As a training officer
in the LAPD,
it is my duty to train
any and all recruits
assigned to me.
Two pairs
-of Lakers tickets.
-Mm-hmm.
Alright. Settle in.
We got some new blood today.
Stand up
so everyone can see you.
You earned the right
to be in this room,
but you have to prove
yourselves to stay.
The way we do things matters.
Tradition and protocol
are the metal
from which every cop
in this city is forged.
That being said,
it's my pleasure
to welcome you
to the FTO program.
State your name
and badge numbers.
Barnes, Katie.
Badge number 44313.
Uh, hi. I'm Larry Macer.
Uh, everybody calls me
"The Badger" --
- Oh!
- Oh, geez.
- Come on.
- Oh, my gosh.
Badger.
My office. Now.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Washing out at roll call
on your first day?
That has gotta be a record.
I heard about a recruit who
ran over his captain
driving into the parking lot.
But I'm sure it's an urban myth.
Watch your head.
Dad!
Henry! I had no i--
This is amazing.
This is --
This -- This is awesome.
Hey, buddy! I didn't know
I was gonna see you today.
Oh, that's why we're here.
We just wanted to say hello.
Oh, that's great.
Uh, you remember my son, Henry,
his lovely fiancée, Abigail. Hi.
It's good to see you.
You guys just flew in
this morning?
We drove, actually.
From my mom's new place
in Arizona.
We helped her get moved in.
Yeah, the road trip was
a little us time
before Henry starts the new job.
Oh, that's right.
Congratulations.
What exactly will you
be doing again?
Uh, Henry is
the new youth liaison
for, uh, Ben's new nonprofit,
uh, clean water foundation.
You don't know
what that means, do you?
Not really, no.
I'll be traveling the world,
connecting with youth activists
to build partnerships
between the nonprofit
and the communities
they serve. That --
And promoting it all
on social media.
That's why Ben needed to hire
somebody young and hip.
That's right.
- Yeah.
So when am I gonna
see you guys tonight?
You won't.
We're staying in Malibu.
Oh.
Henry has an early session
tomorrow,
so the company got us
a hotel room.
I totally get it.
L.A. traffic, all that.
Don't worry.
Text me if anything changes.
Will do. Have a safe shift.
You bet.
Have a great first day training.
- Thank you.
- Bye, guys.
Later, guys. Bye.
Knock 'em dead.
Oh, it's killing him
to be so supportive.
It's killing me
Think he can tell?
Not at all.
I will. I will.
Bye.
That was my mother.
Is she still mad about the cake?
Patrice doesn't do mad,
she does disappointed.
- Fewer wrinkles.
- So, what did she say?
I had told her that we were
having a hard time
finding a venue,
so she called her country club.
That club where that asshat
asked me for a clean fork?
That's the one.
And they had an opening,
so she booked it.
Without asking us?
Why would she?
It's only our wedding.
I'm not getting married
at that country club.
Agreed.
So, which one of us
is gonna tell her?
Um...
Tim.
Hey. You got a minute?
Professor Ryan. Come in.
Isn't our sit-down scheduled
for next week?
This is about
something different.
What's going on?
For over a week now,
somebody has been
leaving notes on my car.
At home, at work,
the market, dry cleaners.
Now, the notes are creepy,
but they are not threatening,
which is smart, because --
Because without
credible threats,
there's no crime. Exactly.
It's just enough
to send a message --
"I'm watching you."
But this morning,
I found my car window smashed,
and, uh, this was inside.
Whoever is behind this,
he or she is escalating.
Is there anyone you can think of
that could do
something like this?
I'm one of the faces
behind a loud
criminal justice
reform movement.
I'm all over social media,
cable news.
And a lot of people do not like
what I have to say.
Does anyone know what you drive,
where you live?
No, no.
I've worked very hard
to make sure
that that is not
public information.
What's your schedule today?
Uh, well, I have yoga at 11:00,
and then, uh...
teaching tonight.
Let's get a report written up,
and I will assign
Nolan and Harper
to patrol the areas
you'll be in today.
Thank you, Sergeant.
After you.
This is a shop.
It's not a cop car, squad car,
or black-and-white.
It's a shop.
It's where you work.
First, we examine
the exterior for damage.
Any nicks, scratches,
dents, or dings,
you write 'em up.
Got it? Sir.
Load the war bags, Boot.
Shotgun safety check.
Verify it's empty, safety on,
load it, close the action.
Remington 870.
Three-inch magnum,
ghost-ring sights,
six-round magazine tube,
steel receiver
with a polymer over-mold.
Sir, if it's all right with you,
I prefer to keep
one in the chamber.
That extra half-second counts.
There's only three reasons
a person would be
that familiar with this weapon.
You a big-game hunter, Boot?
Negative, sir.
Don't destroy anything unless
it needs to be destroyed.
Relatives in law enforcement?
Negative, sir.
First in my family.
Former military, then.
Hm.
But standard issue is
an M4 carbine.
If you were in country,
using a shotgun --
I was a breacher.
82nd Airborne,
2nd Brigade Combat Team.
Advance team and combat patrol.
80-deuce. "All the way"...
sir.
Alright.
Some new ground rules, then.
You don't have to call me "sir."
It'll be an adjustment,
but you're gonna be fine.
Wanna get a coffee?
Stop. It's not a big deal.
Yes, it is. You're turning 18.
You're finally getting
your own place.
Come on. This is exciting.
Yeah, my first solo apartment,
you could literally
reach the stove
without getting out of bed.
In my first place,
I eventually stopped
fighting with the cockroaches,
and I just treated them as pets.
But I'm sure yours will be
much nicer than that.
I lived under a bridge.
Bugs don't bother me.
♪ We're just living in
the moment, just do you ♪
Thanks again for helping me with
the transitional housing
paperwork.
I wouldn't have found out
about the program
if it wasn't for you.
I'm happy to.
♪ I wanna get to know you
better ♪
Who's that girl
with Officer Zaddy?
That's, uh, Tim's new rookie.
Yeah, she just started.
How's it feel to be replaced?
Uh, great.
I am happy for somebody else
to be tormented by Tim
for a change.
♪ Never wanna stop
Whoa.
Sorry, is he paying
for her coffee?
♪ Let's go through a phase
together ♪
♪ We'll be gone for days,
whatever ♪
And he's letting her drive?
So much for torment.
Oh, he is evil.
He's luring her into
a false sense of security,
and then -- bam!
"I've been shot.
Where are we, Boot?"
Man, she's gonna be
wearing that coffee
by the end of her shift.
Are you smiling?
I'm sorry, all you did
for the last year was
complain about
how Tim treats you,
and now you're happy
that he's doing
the same thing to her?
That's a little messed up.
Hey.
What are you doing
in my neck of the woods?
James!
Uh, just a little covert
undercover police work.
Ohhh, staking out
the yoga studio, huh?
Always had a bad feeling
about that place.
No one should be that happy
after exercise.
How's the Community Center
going?
Swimming upstream every day.
I'm trying to get this
self-defense class going,
but I just lost my instructor.
Well, Detective Harper
is an expert
at hand-to-hand combat,
and a phenomenal teacher.
Really?
Ah, but I-I'm -- I'm sure
you have plans tonight.
Uh, I-I could probably swing by
for an hour or so.
That'd be awesome. Thank you.
Harper.
I'm gonna hold you to that.
Looks like we're on.
What are you doing?
Uh, just taking some pictures.
I'm on public property.
Pictures of what?
Birds.
What's going on?
This gentleman was
taking photos of you.
Is that true?
Wait a minute. I know you.
You were in one of my classes.
Your Torts class, two years ago.
I-I sat in the front row.
I came to all your office hours.
So you just happened to be
photographing birds
in front of her yoga class?
Wild, right? It feels like fate.
No, it feels like stalking.
Did you break into
Professor Ryan's car
this morning? No.
Give me your camera.
- Don't.
Why?
It's an unreasonable search.
Uh, no.
This is evidence
that can be easily deleted.
So we have the right
to examine it.
I disagree. You need a warrant.
He has rights.
Thank you, Fiona.
Well, don't take it personally.
- The law is the law.
- Alright, fine.
We will get a warrant.
But we have the right
to detain him
while we are waiting for it.
So I'm gonna do that.
Put your camera in your bag
and your hands behind your back.
So, he's been stalking you?
Somebody has.
Oh, sorry.
James, this is Fiona --
Ryan. Yeah, I know.
I follow you on social media.
Yes, I follow you, too.
You're doing some
really important work
in this neighborhood.
Thank you.
Hey, if you ever need
a civil rights litigator,
please give me a call.
Wow. I hope you mean that,
because I will.
Anytime.
Tell Nyla I'll text her
the details for tonight.
Will do.
You're all right following us
to the station?
Yeah. And...
you're okay, right?
Of course. Okay.
I heard you were
a real hard-ass.
Random tests,
getting into people's heads.
Why not with me?
Or is this part of it?
You're messing with me
right now, aren't you?
Well, yes and no. Okay, then.
How am I doing?
Fine so far.
You'll have some challenges,
but you'll push through 'em.
What kinds of challenges?
People with strong
military backgrounds
can struggle with
the transition to being a cop.
That won't be me.
I've been on combat patrol,
doing exactly this.
Wrong.
There are three major
differences between
police and military,
and if you want to be a cop
instead of a soldier,
you'll have to conquer
all of them.
Tell me.
One, cops are expected
to be proactive.
You don't wait for orders.
Two, you are no longer bound
by military objectives.
The actions you take are
up to your discretion.
And, three, the people
we come up against on the street
aren't enemy combatants.
They're our fellow citizens.
7-Adam-19, clear for traffic?
7-Adam-19, go ahead.
Silent alarm, 4-5-9 type with
multiple motion activations.
755 Bollinger Road. 7-Adam-19?
4-5-9 with a silent alarm?
Burglary.
Most likely second degree,
entering a commercial structure
with the intent to commit theft,
grand theft, petty theft,
or any felony.
Good.
7-Adam-19, copy.
Negative on lookouts.
Want me to post
on the side door,
and you can recon the front?
Sounds good.
Just stay to the left of --
The door. Visible hinges.
Outward-opening door puts
the kill zone on the right.
Okay. If I see suspects inside,
what do we do?
Call for reinforcements.
You mean, call for backup.
Yes, sir. I meant backup.
Then we can surround
and call out,
or make entry and engage.
What would you do?
Uh...
Why force confrontation?
Get air support on the roof,
and surround and call out.
Perfect.
Gun!
7-Adam-19. Shots fired.
Two armed suspects.
Requesting backup and airship.
Sir, I've got a shot. How?
Little ricochet trick
I picked up in Fallujah.
Ugh! Aah!
Lay on your stomach.
Hands behind your back.
Are they gonna find anyone else
in the building?
No. Don't lie to me.
Barnes, suspect's secured.
Our job is now
to render first aid.
Sorry.
Sorry, right.
- You trained for this?
- Yes, sir.
-What the hell is that? What?
Tim put his hand
on her shoulder.
Man, I saved his life
on my first day.
I didn't even get a fist bump.
So, it seems Andy Becker
got fixated on you
when you gave him an F
in your class.
He thought it was
to get his attention.
Everything since
has been the long game
to get you to fall in love
with him.
I know.
Did you find any evidence that
he broke into my car?
No. He didn't take
-any pictures of that.
-Oh.
So he's a creep,
but there's no evidence
that he actually
committed any crimes?
Right.
You think that I'm an idiot
for keeping you
from doing that search without
the warrant.
No.
Y-You've dedicated your life
to protecting civil liberties.
If anything,
I-I respect you more
for sticking to it
when it's this personal.
Now, I did put an emergency
restraining order on him.
Hopefully,
he'll get the message.
Thank you.
- See you in class?
- I'll be there.
What are we doing here?
You'll see.
You were right.
About earlier.
That was different
than the Army.
One second,
a guy's trying to kill us.
The next, we're saving his life.
You're still in
the headspace where
everyone is either a friendly
or an enemy combatant.
It's my job to help you change
that mind-set.
These people are all
your neighbors.
Now, some are neighbors
with problems
who do stupid things,
crazy things, selfish things,
but they're just people.
I want you
to take a look around.
What do you see?
Ah. Finally getting a Tim Test?
We passed six people
on our way in.
Four males, two females.
There's one ingress
and egress road.
The hillside to our back
gives us a tactical advantage.
That's well-spotted.
But I want you to be
in the present,
not thinking about
potential threats.
What do you see here?
Uh...
A ladybug.
It's... very cute, sir.
No.
It's adorable.
You see the tiny spots?
Focus on them.
I want you to take
a deep breath.
Feel the sun.
Go ahead. Close your eyes.
I'll cover you.
This is your present.
You made it home.
Life is good.
You're safe.
When you're in country,
everything's hostile.
You never turn it off,
you only turn it down.
Cops who are fearful,
they use officer safety
as a way of treating everyone
like the enemy.
But they're not.
In fact, you're doing the job
wrong if you are.
I don't know how to live
like that anymore.
You'll remember.
Just give it time.
Be in the moment.
That's it?
It's harder than you think.
At least it was for me.
But it's only way I could
leave the war behind.
You don't have to wait for me.
I know.
So, you ready for the exam
next week?
Uh, I will be ready.
Sorry. Hold on a second.
Hello?
What -- Who is this?
How dare you say that to me!
Who was that?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
Someone just posted
my home address,
my phone number,
and my license plate
to the Internet,
with a message reading,
"Come teach this bitch
a lesson."
Okay. Thank you.
I'll let her know.
That was the Assaults Unit.
They handle the criminal threats
like this.
Along with
the Cyber Crimes Division,
they're gonna track down
the original post.
Well, thank you,
but my information's
all out there now forever,
so there's no putting that horse
back in the barn.
Well, my gut tells me
it's your stalker, Andy.
He got pissed about
that restraining order
and put your address online
in hopes that some hate group
will try to do you harm
while he sits safely
on the sidelines watching.
Well, thank you
for walking with me.
Uh, knowing how this sounds,
how about I just
follow you home,
just to make sure it's safe?
I don't need a bodyguard.
All due respect, that's exactly
what you need right now.
No. That is exactly
what they want --
for me to be afraid.
I am not going
to give that to them.
But thank you for your help.
Good night.
Tamara, what's up?
Lucy, can you come get me?
Yeah. Where are you?
My cousin's.
He's been drinking.
Tamara!
Hey, I'll be right there.
Get the hell out now.
Just let me get my stuff.
Consider it back rent.
Where the hell
am I supposed to go?
Who cares?
Been freeloading off me
long enough.
Okay, everyone take a breath.
Go get her stuff.
I said, go get her stuff!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't come back.
Wow.
What happened?
My place isn't ready yet.
A plumber found black mold,
and now they're saying
it could be two months.
Oof.
And when I told Scott
I needed to stay longer,
he lost it.
His skanky girlfriend doesn't
like me being there.
I'm so sorry.
It's whatever.
I'll figure something out.
No. You will... stay with me
until your place is ready.
You don't have to.
Yes, I do.
You're family.
Thank you.
Mm.
You want to, uh, go to 7-Eleven,
buy way too much candy,
and watch some horror movies?
Okay. "Okay"?
That's a -- That's a good idea.
Sure. Why not.
Okay, okay.
♪ By my side, next to me
Oh! Hello.
Hi.
- Am I at the wrong house?
No. Lopez and Wesley are
right through here.
Ah. I'm Tim.
Oh, you're one of Angela's,
uh, police friends, aren't you?
For now.
I thought we were
talking wedding plans.
We are.
Tim is here
as a neutral third party.
Wasn't aware that we needed one.
This is a little unusual,
isn't it?
Agreed.
Oh, you know, weddings can be
a stressful time.
We just figured
this... would help.
Okay.
What's first on the agenda?
♪ We can work it all out,
work it all out, you'll see ♪
Ceremony locations --
Episcopal church
or Catholic church?
Oh, good.
We're starting small.
♪ Although we fight,
I still love you hopelessly ♪
I am so sorry.
Everyone seems
to be running late.
I-I don't get it.
I mean, there was
so much interest in
a self-defense class.
Even had to reprint the flyer
four times.
You got the day wrong.
What? No, I didn't.
It's the 10th.
Right, but this says Friday.
Today's Tuesday.
Oh, my God.
Uh, I-I can't believe
I just wasted your time
like this.
Well, it's not a total waste.
I can still train you.
Oh, I-I-I wasn't gonna
take the class.
Well, I'm loose and ready to go,
so I'm fighting somebody.
♪ Hard to know
♪ Somehow
Don't look at me.
♪ We can work it all out,
you'll see ♪
This is Henry.
Leave a message,
and I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Hey, buddy. Just me checking in.
Uh, just calling to see how
your first day went.
Give me a ring. I'll be up late.
Hey, y'all.
To be honest, I wasn't sure
that I was up to making
my weekly livestream.
As you may have heard,
my privacy was attacked today
in an attempt to silence me.
I was not intimidated then,
and I sure as hell
am not intimidated now.
So listen very carefully.
I am not afraid,
and I will never stop fighting
for what is right.
And if you have a problem
with that,
you know where to find me.
Professor, it's, uh, John Nolan.
Disarmed. Ready to arm.
What are you doing here?
I was just, uh, checking on you.
I-I caught your video.
I told you I don't need
a bodyguard.
Right. Did you happen to look
at the comments?
All the references to "100%"?
As in "100% white America,"
with associations with
the Southern Front
and, uh, Patriots for Purity --
serious white supremacy groups.
These are dangerous people.
Like I don't know that?
But if I succumb to
their threats, they win.
I understand,
but it's an irrefutable fact
you can effect
a heck of a lot more change
if you're alive.
- Good night, Officer Nolan.
- Good night, Professor.
Don't forget to re-arm
your security system.
I am. Now go away.
Best and final.
Okay.
She's agreeing to
limit her invitations to 125
if you agree to add cousin
Jessica to your wedding party.
The one with the teeth?
Fine.
Make it 100, and we have a deal.
Okay, Jessica's in
if you go down to 100.
Oh, come on. This is silly.
Just tell me what you want.
This is your wedding.
I'll go along with anything.
Oh, come on, Mom. I know you.
You don't go along
with anything.
Well, I may have been
a little forceful
with my opinion,
but I thought I was helping.
I mean, you're both so busy
with your jobs
and the baby coming,
and I've got nothing but time.
Can you get me some water?
Sure. Maybe Tim can help.
Thank God.
We haven't had much time
to visit you lately.
No, I understand.
I mean, you're a detective now.
You're probably exhausted.
I am.
But this wedding should be
a chance for us to bond.
I'm sorry it's been
so contentious.
Well, I'm sorry
I didn't ask
about the country club.
It just -- It seemed like
something I could do
to show you how happy I am
you're joining the family.
If you don't want
to get married there...
I really don't. Well...
But I would like
your opinion on things.
When you ask for it.
Is that so awful?
No. No.
I just want you and Wesley
to be happy.
Thank you.
But if you serve a buffet,
I will die of shame.
Seated dinner it is.
Oof!
Ow.
Come on.
You can do better than that.
He really can't.
Uh, I really can't.
You okay?
Yeah.
I still can't believe
I messed up those fliers.
Hey, let me buy you dinner
this weekend.
You know,
to -- to make up for it.
Uh... that is sweet,
but I actually --
I-I just started
dating someone, so...
Define "just started."
One date? Five?
One.
Okay, so, let me
take you out on one date.
Then you can see how you feel.
That seems like
a reasonable proposal.
He's a good wingman.
Is that a yes?
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I could
make that happen.
Great.
♪ Sucker
You planning to be out here
all night?
Yeah. You gonna yell
at me some more?
No. I brought you coffee.
Thank you.
Listen, I'm sorry
I snapped at you earlier.
It's not a problem.
Very stressful situation.
Thank you.
And thank you for staying.
It does make me feel better
knowing that you're here.
You're welcome, Professor.
Oh, please.
Considering what you're doing,
call me Fiona.
Oh, sorry.
That's my son.
Everything okay?
It's the last thing
you need to be hearing about
right now.
Actually, I could use
a distraction.
Okay. Um...
Uh, my son got a job
and dropped out of college.
But you wanted him to graduate
because you didn't?
I made a nice life for myself
and my family,
but not finishing...
it just always left a hole
in my confidence.
Well, you know,
college isn't for everybody,
and there are many ways
to get an education.
This job of his,
is it a good one?
Oh, crazy good.
Well, there you go, then.
I mean, college will
always be there.
Maybe this is the education
he needs right now.
Wow.
Look at you.
Teaching me
outside of class too.
I'll shadow you to school
and then head home,
get some shut-eye.
Yeah, my publisher's
bringing in...
...a private security company
for the next few weeks.
Good.
Oh! Henry's coming to dinner.
Oh.
That's a powerful piece.
Oh, yeah.
My grandmother made that.
She was a sculptor.
Is it supposed to be
melted like that?
No. It was damaged during
the MOVE bombing.
Wait, I remember that.
Oh.
Most people don't.
Yeah. I'm -- I-I grew up
outside Philly.
That was, what, 1984?
It was May 13, 1985.
Yeah.
The cops were trying to get
a group of Black activists
out of their house,
and when they couldn't
get them out,
they fired 10,000 rounds
of ammunition
into a house
with children in it.
Then they dropped a bomb
on the roof --
killed 11 people,
including 5 kids.
I remember there was
a-a huge fire.
Did your grandmother's
house burn?
Mm. Yeah. Along with 60 others.
Two whole blocks.
And the cops just watched.
That sculpture was the only
thing we could salvage.
I'm so sorry.
I was 10 years old.
Playing in her front room
when people started coming,
banging on the door,
telling us we had to get out.
There were embers falling
from the sky,
burning our skin.
Nana grabbed my hand
and we ran, but...
we couldn't get away.
No wonder you became
an activist yourself.
Exactly.
Now you understand why I'm not
backing down from these
Southern Front jackasses.
- Armed. Away. Exit now.
- Alright. Ready to go.
Okay. Give me one second.
Okay.
How'd you sleep?
Good.
Not good.
Don't tell me --
you've got some sure-fire
REM-sleep technique I can try.
Actually, I do.
Man, I heard you were
such a hard-ass,
and here you are,
showing me ladybugs
and teaching me
how to be all zen.
What can I say?
I'm a complicated guy.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
♪ Watch what I can do
♪ ...I can do
♪ I got that feeling
♪ ...what I can do Oh, no.
Hello?
Listen to me very carefully.
The white supremacists
we were talking about --
the Southern Front --
they just pulled in behind you.
What do I do?  Stay calm.
I'm right behind them.
We don't want them to know
you've seen them yet.
Oh, my God, John --
Don't worry, okay?
Just keep driving,
keep your speed even.
I'm gonna call in
for a little help.
Why are they following me?
Why don't they just kill me?
The Southern Front
likes to make statements.
They kidnap high-profile targets
and then put them on trial
to answer for their crimes.
And everyone's found guilty.
Give me a sec.
Control, this is
off-duty Officer John Nolan,
badge number 2-5-2-5-3.
I have a possible 2-0-7
in progress.
Victim is headed west on 11th
in a silver late-model Sentra,
being pursued
by two pickup trucks --
one brown, one blue,
both lifted.
Three occupants, presumed armed.
I'm following in my P.O.V.,
a black Tundra.
7-Adam-19 responding.
What do I do?
Do I run the light? No.
Uh, stop, but be ready to bolt.
I'm gonna try something.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Are you hurt? Are you okay?
'Cause --
Oh, that's some damage.
Oh, I don't think
this is gonna buff out.
Did you have that damage before?
Police. Get down. Get down.
Get on the ground.
Here.
Cuff yourself to that,
right there.
Cuff yourself -- fast.
You're making a big mistake.
Well, they tell me that
all the time.
Out of the car! Now!
7-Adam-07, shots fired.
Multiple armed suspects
with assault rifles.
Need backup and airship.
What are you doing?
Firefight is one block north.
If we take the alley,
we'll come up on them
from the side
so we can box in the enemy.
The suspects, not enemy.
Right, suspects.
Grab her! We gotta go!
She's running!
Fiona's on the move!
Headed south down the alley,
one armed suspect in pursuit.
We gotta even the odds here.
I'm runnin' on empty.
One odds-evener coming up.
Be ready.
Down on the ground! Don't move!
- You got him?
- Yeah. Got him.
Roll over!
Oh!
Don't move! You're under arrest!
You okay?
No! I'm not okay.
They tried to kill me.
Day two and you're filling out
the paperwork?
You got something to say, Chen?
Uh, yeah, I do. I...
Why are you being
so nice to her?
My first few days on the job,
you kicked me out of the car,
tormented me.
A month later, you -- you -- you
stole my duty belt
while I had to go pee.
You called me "Boot"
so many times,
I get triggered
when I go shoe shopping.
Look, Officer Barnes
has other issues.
Like what?
Like, she's fit and beautiful
and smart --
She won't wear perfume.
W-What does that have to do
with anything?
What?
Look, I teach my recruits
according to what they need.
Officer Barnes
won't wear perfume
because she's still worried
it'll give away her position.
A part of her is still
waging a war in Afghanistan,
and if she's gonna be a cop,
that has to go.
You are a kind
and insightful person.
You see the good in people.
So much so
that I had to show you
the world can be a scary place.
Officer Barnes only sees
a scary place,
and she needs to know that
not everyone's out to hurt her.
Is she gonna be okay?
I think so.
And who knows --
one day...
she might even be
as good as you.
There.
Grey said your security team
is top-notch,
so they will make sure
you're safe.
Was Computer Crimes able
to figure out
if Andy was the one
who doxxed me?
Unfortunately, no.
If it was him, he covered
his tracks very well.
Can the student offer
the teacher some advice?
Sure.
You're not gonna sleep well.
For a while.
You're gonna be jumpy
and irritable and on edge.
Is this experience talking?
It's the downside
of having a job
filled with trauma and tragedy.
Yeah, I'm all too familiar
with the toll it can take
on the mind and body.
Just take your feelings
seriously,
and get help if you need it.
It'll only get worse
if you don't.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
See you in class?
Unless you wanna pass me
right now.
Mm, I'll see you in class. Okay.
♪ Like the world's never known
♪ Whoo
How's your report coming?
Just finished.
I, uh... need to talk to you
about something.
Transitioning from
military to police
has been harder than I expected.
And you're handling it.
In two shifts, you turned
your past into an asset.
I mean, you switched
from warrior to caregiver.
Yeah, but it's what's
still down the road
that has me worried.
What do you mean?
Looking out over the city
yesterday,
feeling the sun on my face --
that's the first time
I've felt at peace
in a long time.
And that feeling will grow.
You just need to give yourself
a little more time to adjust.
No, I don't know that I can --
at least not while
wearing a uniform.
I need to see what life is like
when I'm not in survival mode
all the time.
And that's not gonna happen
if I'm a cop.
So, with my report,
I am also submitting
my resignation memo.
No. I don't accept that.
You're gonna be a great cop,
and I know it.
And I can help you transition.
From warrior to peacekeeper...
to peace.
I really appreciate it, sir.
But this might be
the last chance I have
to change my course,
leave the violence behind.
And I need to take it.
Thank you for everything.
Barnes.
I'm gonna check in on you.
And your POST certificate's good
for three years.
You change your mind,
you will always have
a home here.
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm
Okay. Just about ready.
So, how is the job going?
Any new adventures planned?
Dad, you don't have to pretend
to be happy about it.
I'm not pretending.
I dropped out of college.
I know you're not okay
with this.
I-I wasn't at first.
O-Or second.
I just had to get past myself
a little bit.
Henry, this is your life,
and I know this is going to be
an incredible experience
for you.
Thanks.
♪ Like the world's never known ♪
- Feeling okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, just tired.
Guess this new lifestyle's
doing a number on me.
Well, get used to it.
Ben said you're gonna be
jetting around the world --
Europe, Asia.
Yeah. South America. Seriously?
Do you wanna land that salad
on the table for me?
Did you guys know
that "arrabbiata"
is actually Italian for "angry"?
Are you making us
angry pasta, Mr. Nolan?
You okay, babe?
Yeah, I just --
I don't feel so good.
Henry! Call 9-1-1.
Hey! Hey!
Take a deep breath.
Come on. Wake up.
We got help coming.
You're gonna be fine.
Henry, you're gonna
be fine, okay?