1
00:00:02,611 --> 00:00:04,004
♪ Everybody gather 'round ♪

2
00:00:04,047 --> 00:00:05,744
♪ It's time to break through
the ups and downs ♪

3
00:00:05,788 --> 00:00:08,095
♪ Lift your spirits… ♪

4
00:00:08,138 --> 00:00:10,445
-Professor Ryan.
-Oh, Officer Nolan.

5
00:00:10,488 --> 00:00:12,273
Little late for class,
don't you think?

6
00:00:12,316 --> 00:00:14,057
My apologies
for missing the exam.

7
00:00:14,101 --> 00:00:15,972
I got, uh, stuck at work,
last-minute call.

8
00:00:16,016 --> 00:00:17,495
-Armed robbery.
-Is everyone alright?

9
00:00:17,539 --> 00:00:19,323
Yes, thank you,
but about the exam,

10
00:00:19,367 --> 00:00:21,369
is there any way
I could make that up?

11
00:00:21,412 --> 00:00:23,849
I made my policy clear
on the first day --

12
00:00:23,893 --> 00:00:26,635
a missed test
is a failed test.
Yes.

13
00:00:26,678 --> 00:00:29,464
You also said in your
first lecture that, uh,

14
00:00:29,507 --> 00:00:32,641
"Strict law is often
great injustice." Cicero.

15
00:00:32,684 --> 00:00:34,904
Oh, okay.

16
00:00:34,947 --> 00:00:36,862
Well, if you want an exception,
you'll need to earn it.

17
00:00:36,906 --> 00:00:38,299
Tell me what I have to do.

18
00:00:38,342 --> 00:00:39,865
You have to answer
one legal question.

19
00:00:39,909 --> 00:00:41,084
Okay, that's easy.

20
00:00:41,128 --> 00:00:44,827
Um...

21
00:00:44,870 --> 00:00:47,047
A woman witnesses
a stabbing in a nightclub.

22
00:00:47,090 --> 00:00:49,092
She's pretty sure
the assailant is Black

23
00:00:49,136 --> 00:00:52,095
and that he has a scar
on his right arm.

24
00:00:52,139 --> 00:00:53,836
Wait. She's sure that he has
a scar on his right arm

25
00:00:53,879 --> 00:00:55,446
but not sure that
he's African-American?

26
00:00:55,490 --> 00:00:57,100
Did I say
African-American?

27
00:00:57,144 --> 00:00:59,668
Right. Black. Sorry.
Mm-hmm.

28
00:00:59,711 --> 00:01:03,672
Uh, there are
over 400 club-goers,

29
00:01:03,715 --> 00:01:05,587
so it's going to take a while
to interview them all.

30
00:01:05,630 --> 00:01:07,328
And the longer you wait...

31
00:01:07,371 --> 00:01:09,156
The more their memories
will have a chance to degrade,

32
00:01:09,199 --> 00:01:11,549
and it would give the
assailant a chance to
destroy any evidence.

33
00:01:11,593 --> 00:01:13,508
And if you do not find
the culprit tonight,

34
00:01:13,551 --> 00:01:14,900
you probably never will.

35
00:01:14,944 --> 00:01:17,773
So who do you round up
to question?

36
00:01:17,816 --> 00:01:20,341
"A," all the Black men,

37
00:01:20,384 --> 00:01:22,908
"B," all the men,
regardless of color,

38
00:01:22,952 --> 00:01:25,259
or, "C," everyone?

39
00:01:25,302 --> 00:01:27,130
Are there
any more facts?

40
00:01:27,174 --> 00:01:30,220
This isn't really easy to answer
based on what you've given me.

41
00:01:30,264 --> 00:01:32,527
Well, this is not
an easy class.

42
00:01:32,570 --> 00:01:35,356
Get me the right answer
by end of day tomorrow,

43
00:01:35,399 --> 00:01:37,314
and I will let you
make up the exam.

44
00:01:37,358 --> 00:01:40,796
Right. Thank you.
I will.

45
00:01:42,841 --> 00:01:47,585
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪

46
00:02:02,252 --> 00:02:05,037
"Hey, sorry to do this by text,

47
00:02:05,081 --> 00:02:08,519
but it's just
not working with us."

48
00:02:11,870 --> 00:02:13,655
Yeah.
What's going on?

49
00:02:13,698 --> 00:02:15,787
Well, I set up
a-a lunch for you

50
00:02:15,831 --> 00:02:17,615
with the head of
the Mayor's security detail.

51
00:02:17,659 --> 00:02:19,226
There's a driver position
opening.

52
00:02:19,269 --> 00:02:20,705
Higher profile, better pay,

53
00:02:20,749 --> 00:02:22,925
and it'll get you
to I.A. faster.

54
00:02:22,968 --> 00:02:26,015
Look, thank you, but, um...

55
00:02:26,058 --> 00:02:28,452
I'm just not sure that's where
I want to end up, you know?

56
00:02:28,496 --> 00:02:30,454
Well, I thought after
the Doug Stanton situation,

57
00:02:30,498 --> 00:02:32,674
you'd be motivated to
clean up the Department.

58
00:02:32,717 --> 00:02:34,589
You want to be where you can do
the most good, right?

59
00:02:34,632 --> 00:02:36,417
Yeah, yeah, of course, but --
Well, then it's settled.

60
00:02:39,246 --> 00:02:41,073
-I can't believe him.
-I know.

61
00:02:41,117 --> 00:02:43,511
Maneuvering me to I.A.
like I have no say in it.

62
00:02:43,554 --> 00:02:46,122
No, not your dad. Emmett
breaking up with me by text?

63
00:02:46,166 --> 00:02:48,777
What is he, 14? He doesn't have
the guts to do it in person?

64
00:02:48,820 --> 00:02:51,171
Most guys don't. Look, just
be happy he didn't ghost you.

65
00:02:51,214 --> 00:02:52,607
Okay.
Can we get to work now?

66
00:02:52,650 --> 00:02:53,782
Did Emmett talk to you
about this?

67
00:02:53,825 --> 00:02:55,087
No. Why would he?

68
00:02:55,131 --> 00:02:56,393
Because you're friends.

69
00:02:56,437 --> 00:02:57,786
We don't talk feelings.

70
00:02:57,829 --> 00:02:59,222
We drink and watch sports
together.

71
00:02:59,266 --> 00:03:00,876
That's guy for "friends."

72
00:03:00,919 --> 00:03:02,791
Well, <i>straight</i> guy
for "friends."

73
00:03:02,834 --> 00:03:05,359
-Look, you want my advice?
-Walk it off.

74
00:03:05,402 --> 00:03:06,925
He's clearly not
the right guy for you.

75
00:03:08,449 --> 00:03:10,929
That is the same advice he would
give me if I got hit by a pitch.

76
00:03:10,973 --> 00:03:12,496
What is wrong with men?

77
00:03:12,540 --> 00:03:16,457
So much. Look, I am
really sorry to hear that.

78
00:03:16,500 --> 00:03:19,590
But I will pick up some tequila
and ice cream on the way home,

79
00:03:19,634 --> 00:03:22,202
and we can listen to
my breakup playlist on repeat

80
00:03:22,245 --> 00:03:24,465
and maybe throw a few little
shady prank calls at Emmett.

81
00:03:24,508 --> 00:03:26,380
-Thanks.
-Here. Here you go.

82
00:03:26,423 --> 00:03:28,686
Change of clothes,
prenatal vitamins,

83
00:03:28,730 --> 00:03:32,386
antacid, anti-gas, ginger chews,
and magnesium supplements.

84
00:03:32,429 --> 00:03:34,736
I have never
loved you more.

85
00:03:34,779 --> 00:03:36,520
Have, uh, you heard anything
from the kidnappers?

86
00:03:36,564 --> 00:03:38,740
Not since
the last ransom demand.

87
00:03:38,783 --> 00:03:40,916
But I'm waiting on DNA results
from the crime scene.

88
00:03:40,959 --> 00:03:43,266
Hopefully they come in before
I get back to the Abassi house.

89
00:03:43,310 --> 00:03:45,355
Mm. How's Judge Abassi
holding up?

90
00:03:45,399 --> 00:03:47,270
As well as can be,
I suppose,

91
00:03:47,314 --> 00:03:49,403
considering his son
was abducted.

92
00:03:49,446 --> 00:03:51,448
You've argued
in front of him.

93
00:03:51,492 --> 00:03:52,971
You know anyone
who'd want revenge?

94
00:03:53,015 --> 00:03:54,930
Every criminal who ever
stepped foot in his court.

95
00:03:54,973 --> 00:03:56,061
Half the lawyers.

96
00:03:56,105 --> 00:03:57,933
I'm gonna need more clothes.

97
00:03:59,369 --> 00:04:01,458
DNA results?

98
00:04:01,502 --> 00:04:03,852
No, it's your mom,
texting me again.

99
00:04:03,895 --> 00:04:06,942
Yeah, sorry. She wants to talk
about the baby's trust fund.

100
00:04:06,985 --> 00:04:08,422
Whatever the question is,
my answer is yes.

101
00:04:08,465 --> 00:04:10,380
That has been
well established.

102
00:04:10,424 --> 00:04:13,862
But, believe me, there are
complications to having money.

103
00:04:13,905 --> 00:04:17,387
Like always being able
to pay the rent or buy food?

104
00:04:17,431 --> 00:04:19,650
Like having your child
kidnapped for ransom.

105
00:04:22,000 --> 00:04:24,220
Finally, my DNA results.

106
00:04:26,004 --> 00:04:27,963
Um ...gotta get changed.

107
00:04:28,006 --> 00:04:30,052
You can, um,
handle your mom, right?

108
00:04:30,095 --> 00:04:31,619
"Uh, yeah, Mom?
You're breaking up.

109
00:04:31,662 --> 00:04:33,621
I'm gonna have to
call you back."

110
00:04:33,664 --> 00:04:35,187
Perfect. Love you.

111
00:04:35,231 --> 00:04:36,972
I love you, too.

112
00:04:39,366 --> 00:04:41,411
I need a couple unis
on my kidnapping case.

113
00:04:41,455 --> 00:04:43,065
Can you spare
Harper and Nolan?
Sure thing.

114
00:04:43,108 --> 00:04:44,849
-What do you need them for?
-I'm running down a lead.

115
00:04:44,893 --> 00:04:46,808
I have a conflict
of interest.

116
00:04:46,851 --> 00:04:48,157
Something I should know about?

117
00:04:48,200 --> 00:04:49,593
Not yet.
Okay.

118
00:04:49,637 --> 00:04:51,552
I'll call Harper and Nolan
back in.

119
00:04:51,595 --> 00:04:53,380
Actually, have them meet me
at the Abassi house.

120
00:04:53,423 --> 00:04:54,555
Will do.
Appreciate it.

121
00:04:56,296 --> 00:04:57,993
Looking good,
Officer West.

122
00:04:58,036 --> 00:05:00,256
Don't I always,
Detective Lopez?

123
00:05:00,300 --> 00:05:01,866
So, Officer West,

124
00:05:01,910 --> 00:05:04,260
I've decided who it is
you'll be riding with today.

125
00:05:04,304 --> 00:05:05,653
Great.
Who's the lucky officer?

126
00:05:05,696 --> 00:05:07,829
Me.
Sir?

127
00:05:07,872 --> 00:05:11,093
Considering your upcoming
graduation from the FTO program,

128
00:05:11,136 --> 00:05:12,399
I thought
it'd be a good idea

129
00:05:12,442 --> 00:05:14,749
if we talked about your future
in the department.

130
00:05:14,792 --> 00:05:17,099
Funny. Just had a similar
conversation with my dad.

131
00:05:17,142 --> 00:05:19,449
Did he enlist you
to help steer me to I.A.?

132
00:05:19,493 --> 00:05:21,843
No. I.A. is not
the right path for you.

133
00:05:21,886 --> 00:05:23,410
But you know what is.

134
00:05:23,453 --> 00:05:26,369
Yes, I do.
Now go set up our shop.

135
00:05:31,374 --> 00:05:34,246
If you were to single out all
the Black men for questioning,

136
00:05:34,290 --> 00:05:37,119
it wouldn't be,
technically, profiling

137
00:05:37,162 --> 00:05:39,556
because the added element that
they were all in the building

138
00:05:39,600 --> 00:05:42,211
when the crime was committed
makes it legally okay, right?

139
00:05:42,254 --> 00:05:43,908
I-It's a dark, crowded bar.

140
00:05:43,952 --> 00:05:45,823
Are we sure the witness
even saw a Black guy?

141
00:05:45,867 --> 00:05:47,738
No, the witness
wasn't definitive.

142
00:05:47,782 --> 00:05:49,653
So what's the answer?

143
00:05:49,697 --> 00:05:51,394
Well, you're going about this
all wrong.

144
00:05:51,438 --> 00:05:52,874
It's not about finding
the right answer.

145
00:05:52,917 --> 00:05:55,267
It's about finding the answer
that she wants.

146
00:05:55,311 --> 00:05:57,008
Or the one
that she <i>doesn't</i> want.

147
00:05:57,052 --> 00:05:59,533
Can't imagine she'd think
me worthy of retesting

148
00:05:59,576 --> 00:06:01,709
if all I said was
"Question all the Black men."

149
00:06:01,752 --> 00:06:03,101
Why? 'Cause she's Black?

150
00:06:03,145 --> 00:06:05,365
Well, yeah. Right?

151
00:06:05,408 --> 00:06:07,018
What?

152
00:06:07,062 --> 00:06:09,107
She could
just be testing you --

153
00:06:09,151 --> 00:06:12,720
to see if you'd censor yourself
with her to curry favor.

154
00:06:12,763 --> 00:06:16,245
Hey. Let me bring you
up to speed.

155
00:06:16,288 --> 00:06:19,074
This is Austin Abassi,
age 20,

156
00:06:19,117 --> 00:06:20,815
son of Judge William Abassi.

157
00:06:20,858 --> 00:06:22,382
Three days ago,
Austin was kidnapped

158
00:06:22,425 --> 00:06:23,948
from his apartment
in Hollywood.

159
00:06:23,992 --> 00:06:26,124
The kidnappers sent
an untraceable e-mail

160
00:06:26,168 --> 00:06:27,996
demanding 100 grand
in ransom.

161
00:06:28,039 --> 00:06:29,824
On Thursday night,
a backpack full of cash

162
00:06:29,867 --> 00:06:31,608
was left at the designated
drop-off spot,

163
00:06:31,652 --> 00:06:33,218
but Austin wasn't returned.

164
00:06:33,262 --> 00:06:35,046
Let me guess -- they came up
-with the 100
-K so fast,

165
00:06:35,090 --> 00:06:36,918
the kidnappers
wanted more?

166
00:06:36,961 --> 00:06:39,268
A million. That's when the Judge
finally called the police.

167
00:06:39,311 --> 00:06:41,009
We processed
the crime scene.

168
00:06:41,052 --> 00:06:43,228
A female DNA sample was found
on an empty beer bottle.

169
00:06:43,272 --> 00:06:45,927
-Did you get a match?
-She's not in our system,

170
00:06:45,970 --> 00:06:48,103
but a familial DNA test
determined the sample

171
00:06:48,146 --> 00:06:50,932
comes from the offspring
of someone we currently
have behind bars.

172
00:06:50,975 --> 00:06:53,543
Someone I can't interview

173
00:06:53,587 --> 00:06:55,632
because of
a conflict of interest.

174
00:06:58,026 --> 00:06:59,810
-Oscar?
-You have got to be kidding me.

175
00:06:59,854 --> 00:07:01,725
I'm guessing
your conflict of interest

176
00:07:01,769 --> 00:07:03,727
is that he stabbed
your fiancé.

177
00:07:03,771 --> 00:07:05,990
Technically, my conflict is
the desire to kill him for that.

178
00:07:06,034 --> 00:07:06,991
But you wouldn't really.

179
00:07:07,035 --> 00:07:08,471
I'm pregnant.
Don't try me.

180
00:07:08,515 --> 00:07:10,908
O-Okay. So, wait.
Oscar has a daughter?

181
00:07:10,952 --> 00:07:12,780
Not according
to any official records.

182
00:07:12,823 --> 00:07:15,043
In fact, I can't find any
records of a relationship.

183
00:07:15,086 --> 00:07:16,784
That doesn't surprise me.

184
00:07:16,827 --> 00:07:19,439
Oscar's too much of a narcissist
to keep a girlfriend.

185
00:07:19,482 --> 00:07:22,267
-What's going on?
-Did something happen?

186
00:07:22,311 --> 00:07:24,356
Judge Abassi, Mrs. Abassi,

187
00:07:24,400 --> 00:07:26,663
this is Detective Harper
and Officer Nolan.

188
00:07:26,707 --> 00:07:28,839
They're going to be running down
a lead regarding this man --

189
00:07:28,883 --> 00:07:30,450
Oscar Hutchinson.

190
00:07:30,493 --> 00:07:32,234
He's currently serving
40 years at Cal Correctional

191
00:07:32,277 --> 00:07:33,801
for multiple
violent felonies.

192
00:07:33,844 --> 00:07:36,847
Harper and Nolan will be going
to the prison to question him.

193
00:07:36,891 --> 00:07:39,894
Whatever resources you need,
you'll have them.

194
00:07:39,937 --> 00:07:43,680
Yes, and if there's a deal
to be made, please, make it.

195
00:07:43,724 --> 00:07:45,334
We need Austin
back safely.

196
00:07:45,377 --> 00:07:47,554
Well, the good news is,
uh, with Oscar,

197
00:07:47,597 --> 00:07:49,469
there's <i>always
a deal to be made.</i>

198
00:07:51,253 --> 00:07:54,996
Sir, feel free to call us if
his stereo gets that loud again.

199
00:07:55,039 --> 00:07:58,173
Have you ever been dumped
out of the blue before?

200
00:07:58,216 --> 00:08:00,305
Let me think.

201
00:08:00,349 --> 00:08:03,047
One time, my wife left the house
in the middle of the night,

202
00:08:03,091 --> 00:08:05,093
and I didn't see her again
for two years.

203
00:08:05,136 --> 00:08:07,051
Okay, I get it.
In the grand scheme of things,

204
00:08:07,095 --> 00:08:08,923
this isn't that bad.
I just wanna know why.

205
00:08:08,966 --> 00:08:10,664
Can you please ask?

206
00:08:13,493 --> 00:08:16,408
Somebody tagged our shop?

207
00:08:16,452 --> 00:08:19,934
It can't be.
It's been almost a decade.

208
00:08:19,977 --> 00:08:22,153
Since what?

209
00:08:22,197 --> 00:08:23,981
No, it's definitely him.

210
00:08:24,025 --> 00:08:27,289
The color palette,
the angle of the letters.

211
00:08:27,332 --> 00:08:28,595
What is happening
right now?

212
00:08:34,514 --> 00:08:36,341
♪ Get back up, get up, go get it ♪

213
00:08:36,385 --> 00:08:37,952
Control to 7-Adam-19,

214
00:08:37,995 --> 00:08:39,910
I've got an on view felony
five-ninety-four.

215
00:08:39,954 --> 00:08:42,043
I'm setting the Command Post
at Pico and La Brea.

216
00:08:42,086 --> 00:08:44,045
Start me enough units
for a six-block perimeter,

217
00:08:44,088 --> 00:08:45,873
a canvass team,
a forensic team, air support,

218
00:08:45,916 --> 00:08:47,352
notify the Press
Information Officer.

219
00:08:47,396 --> 00:08:49,529
♪ Let's go ♪ Let's go ♪

220
00:08:49,572 --> 00:08:52,096
Oscar has to be behind this
kidnapping somehow, right?

221
00:08:52,140 --> 00:08:53,620
No record of
any female visitors,

222
00:08:53,663 --> 00:08:55,839
and none of his mail has
ever referenced a daughter.

223
00:08:55,883 --> 00:08:58,146
So either Oscar's been keeping
her a secret from us...

224
00:08:58,189 --> 00:09:00,801
And why do that?...or he's unaware
that she even exists.

225
00:09:00,844 --> 00:09:03,064
Which presents a clear argument
for nature over nurture

226
00:09:03,107 --> 00:09:04,718
as a predicate
for criminal behavior.

227
00:09:04,761 --> 00:09:06,850
If she's involved
in the kidnapping at all

228
00:09:06,894 --> 00:09:09,592
and not just some kid who had
a beer at Austin's apartment

229
00:09:09,636 --> 00:09:11,463
and went home
before he got grabbed.

230
00:09:11,507 --> 00:09:14,075
There are so many unknowns,
and I, for one, am confident

231
00:09:14,118 --> 00:09:16,120
that Oscar's gonna
answer <i>all</i> of them.

232
00:09:16,164 --> 00:09:18,035
I'm kidding.

233
00:09:18,079 --> 00:09:19,559
He's gonna be a giant
pain in the ass.

234
00:09:20,995 --> 00:09:23,693
Hey, it's my two
favorite police officers.

235
00:09:23,737 --> 00:09:25,216
As you can see,
we've mostly

236
00:09:25,260 --> 00:09:27,479
cleaned up the place
after the riot.

237
00:09:27,523 --> 00:09:29,438
It's really hard to get brains
out of cinder block.

238
00:09:29,481 --> 00:09:30,831
I guess you'd know.

239
00:09:30,874 --> 00:09:32,702
You don't get a lot
of visitors, do you?

240
00:09:32,746 --> 00:09:34,399
I'm not sure what the point
would be.

241
00:09:34,443 --> 00:09:36,401
I'm not going out of here
on my feet --

242
00:09:36,445 --> 00:09:38,229
unless you come
bearing a pardon.

243
00:09:38,273 --> 00:09:40,057
No such luck.
Mm.

244
00:09:40,101 --> 00:09:42,930
Then what are you doing here
asking questions about visitors?

245
00:09:42,973 --> 00:09:46,150
DNA turned up at a crime scene
that links directly to you.

246
00:09:46,194 --> 00:09:48,588
But you have been
in here, so...

247
00:09:48,631 --> 00:09:51,155
What are the matches
in the polymorphic markers?

248
00:09:51,199 --> 00:09:52,983
You learn a lot about DNA
in my line of work.

249
00:09:53,027 --> 00:09:54,376
6 out of 13.

250
00:09:54,419 --> 00:09:57,466
That's a first-degree
relative.

251
00:09:57,509 --> 00:10:00,817
Since both my folks are dead
and I'm an only child...

252
00:10:02,950 --> 00:10:04,821
...I got a kid.

253
00:10:05,735 --> 00:10:07,258
What'd he do?

254
00:10:07,302 --> 00:10:08,912
<i>She</i> is connected
to a kidnapping.

255
00:10:08,956 --> 00:10:10,522
Oh, way to go!

256
00:10:10,566 --> 00:10:12,437
You really had no idea
you were a father?

257
00:10:12,481 --> 00:10:15,353
No.

258
00:10:15,397 --> 00:10:18,182
Wow.
It's a lot to process.

259
00:10:18,226 --> 00:10:20,445
Well, all this time, I had
an organ donor on the outside.

260
00:10:20,489 --> 00:10:22,534
I'm gonna really hit that
prison hooch harder now.

261
00:10:22,578 --> 00:10:24,406
Okay. I'm gonna need you
to make a list

262
00:10:24,449 --> 00:10:26,495
of every woman
that could be the mother.

263
00:10:26,538 --> 00:10:28,366
Yeah.

264
00:10:28,410 --> 00:10:30,673
That's not gonna be
that easy.

265
00:10:30,717 --> 00:10:34,764
I don't like to brag, but I was
quite popular back in the day.

266
00:10:34,808 --> 00:10:36,070
Alright.
On to the next lead.

267
00:10:36,113 --> 00:10:37,854
Uh, uh, now, hold up, now.
Hold.

268
00:10:40,074 --> 00:10:44,469
Um, a drive around my old haunts
might really jog the memory.

269
00:10:44,513 --> 00:10:46,384
-Forget it.
-You gotta give to get,
Detective.

270
00:10:46,428 --> 00:10:48,560
You want help?
I want a day pass.

271
00:10:48,604 --> 00:10:50,780
You're gonna do it,
because we both know

272
00:10:50,824 --> 00:10:52,913
you wouldn't have driven
all the way out here if you
had any other leads.

273
00:10:56,830 --> 00:10:58,135
Road trip.

274
00:11:02,183 --> 00:11:05,099
Judge Abassi must have
friends in high places

275
00:11:05,142 --> 00:11:06,535
-to get this approved so fast.
-You know Oscar's gonna

276
00:11:06,578 --> 00:11:07,884
try to rabbit the first
chance he gets, right?

277
00:11:07,928 --> 00:11:09,669
We're not gonna
give him that chance.

278
00:11:09,712 --> 00:11:12,846
♪ Slam, da duh-duh, da duh-duh ♪

279
00:11:12,889 --> 00:11:14,804
♪ Let the boys be boys ♪

280
00:11:14,848 --> 00:11:17,285
They say fashion
is cyclical.

281
00:11:17,328 --> 00:11:19,069
Think this is coming back in?

282
00:11:19,113 --> 00:11:21,332
Yeah. That's gonna take
a few more cycles.

283
00:11:21,376 --> 00:11:23,595
Hey, I'm happy to see
they updated your look
with some modern jewelry.

284
00:11:23,639 --> 00:11:26,511
Alright. So, here's how
this is gonna work.

285
00:11:26,555 --> 00:11:28,600
You stop cooperating,
it's back to prison.

286
00:11:28,644 --> 00:11:30,646
You mislead us,
it's back to prison.

287
00:11:30,690 --> 00:11:32,822
You say a joke that
I don't really think is funny,

288
00:11:32,866 --> 00:11:33,954
it's back to prison.

289
00:11:33,997 --> 00:11:35,433
I'm sensing a pattern.

290
00:11:35,477 --> 00:11:37,305
You try to escape --
"It's back to prison."

291
00:11:37,348 --> 00:11:39,176
Maybe by way of
the emergency room.

292
00:11:39,220 --> 00:11:40,874
No.
That's not how we roll.

293
00:11:40,917 --> 00:11:43,006
But Judge Abassi might not be
as dispassionate.

294
00:11:43,050 --> 00:11:45,400
And I bet he can get you
transferred to a Super Max

295
00:11:45,443 --> 00:11:48,142
just as easily as he
got you out on furlough.

296
00:11:48,185 --> 00:11:50,753
There's no reason to be
like that. We're a team.

297
00:11:50,797 --> 00:11:52,494
So where's my stuff?

298
00:11:56,803 --> 00:12:01,721
All the names and numbers of
my conquests are right on here.

299
00:12:01,764 --> 00:12:02,983
♪ Let the boys be boys ♪

300
00:12:03,026 --> 00:12:04,724
♪ Slam, da duh-duh… ♪

301
00:12:04,767 --> 00:12:06,421
You got a charger?

302
00:12:06,464 --> 00:12:10,207
When was the last time
someone went through this?

303
00:12:11,556 --> 00:12:13,558
Can probably get a few bucks
for this on eBay.

304
00:12:13,602 --> 00:12:15,125
Keep looking.

305
00:12:15,169 --> 00:12:17,867
♪ Da duh-duh, let the boys be boys ♪

306
00:12:17,911 --> 00:12:20,043
For Lila.
Ah!

307
00:12:20,087 --> 00:12:21,392
This is the charger.

308
00:12:21,436 --> 00:12:23,003
We can juice this baby up
in the car

309
00:12:23,046 --> 00:12:24,178
while we're getting
an early lunch.

310
00:12:25,657 --> 00:12:27,398
It's cruel and unusual
punishment

311
00:12:27,442 --> 00:12:28,791
to deprive a prisoner
of nourishment.

312
00:12:28,835 --> 00:12:30,401
Start moving.

313
00:12:30,445 --> 00:12:32,839
Look, 3 Eyez was active
from 2006 to 2010.

314
00:12:32,882 --> 00:12:34,710
Victims all over the city.

315
00:12:34,754 --> 00:12:37,539
Just when I thought I got close
to catching him, he stopped.

316
00:12:37,582 --> 00:12:40,455
I thought maybe he died or
got arrested on other charges.

317
00:12:40,498 --> 00:12:43,110
I still check VICAP
every three months to see
if he pops up in another city.

318
00:12:43,153 --> 00:12:44,633
Must've been a seriously
hard-core guy

319
00:12:44,676 --> 00:12:46,635
for you to obsess like that.
What was his main crime?

320
00:12:48,724 --> 00:12:52,075
This. He's a tagger.

321
00:12:52,119 --> 00:12:54,034
Cost the city hundreds
of thousands of dollars.

322
00:12:54,077 --> 00:12:55,731
In property damage.

323
00:12:55,775 --> 00:12:57,951
It doesn't explain why you
were so obsessed with --

324
00:12:57,994 --> 00:13:00,388
Wait.
Hold on.

325
00:13:00,431 --> 00:13:03,043
3Eyez tagged your shop?

326
00:13:03,086 --> 00:13:04,218
Back when you were a rookie?

327
00:13:04,261 --> 00:13:06,176
My T.O. was chasing
a suspect.

328
00:13:06,220 --> 00:13:08,222
I was guarding a vehicle
full of evidence.

329
00:13:08,265 --> 00:13:11,965
A vehicle that was 10 feet away
from your shop?

330
00:13:12,008 --> 00:13:13,880
It was right under
your nose.

331
00:13:13,923 --> 00:13:16,056
I was ordered to keep
my eyes on the car.

332
00:13:16,099 --> 00:13:18,058
I had just left the Army, where
you follow orders to a "T."

333
00:13:18,101 --> 00:13:20,408
Oh, man, I could just imagine
the relentless teasing.

334
00:13:20,451 --> 00:13:21,801
Did they give you a nickname?
Please say yes.

335
00:13:21,844 --> 00:13:23,585
No.

336
00:13:23,628 --> 00:13:25,239
That's why you're so intent
on catching this guy.

337
00:13:25,282 --> 00:13:26,849
It's personal.

338
00:13:26,893 --> 00:13:29,025
He's a criminal,
and it's our job to stop him.

339
00:13:29,069 --> 00:13:30,766
I mean, the statute of
limitations on these crimes

340
00:13:30,810 --> 00:13:32,463
ran out years ago.

341
00:13:32,507 --> 00:13:34,030
Even if we were
to track him down

342
00:13:34,074 --> 00:13:37,033
for tagging our shop,
it's a misdemeanor.

343
00:13:37,077 --> 00:13:39,383
Is that really
the best use of our time?

344
00:13:41,472 --> 00:13:43,387
I will get us
a fresh shop.

345
00:13:45,520 --> 00:13:47,957
Colleen, this is Oscar.
Hey.

346
00:13:48,001 --> 00:13:50,786
Listen. Is there any chance I
knocked you up in the late '90s?

347
00:13:50,830 --> 00:13:53,093
Hello?

348
00:13:58,359 --> 00:14:02,754
-Sasha. Baby, it's Oscar.
-<i>You ever call me again,</i>

349
00:14:02,798 --> 00:14:04,844
<i>I'll come down there
and rip your throat out!</i>

350
00:14:04,887 --> 00:14:06,280
Okay. I'm gonna
take that one as a no.

351
00:14:07,977 --> 00:14:09,979
-<i>Hello?
-Betty.</i>

352
00:14:10,023 --> 00:14:11,459
You know, I was just
thinking of you, too.

353
00:14:11,502 --> 00:14:13,504
Okay. Put it on speaker.

354
00:14:13,548 --> 00:14:15,028
<i>...much fun.</i>

355
00:14:15,071 --> 00:14:16,072
<i>We always tore it up,
didn't we?</i>

356
00:14:16,116 --> 00:14:18,683
We sure as hell did.

357
00:14:18,727 --> 00:14:22,731
Listen. Um, is there any chance
you and I had a kid together?

358
00:14:22,774 --> 00:14:24,472
<i> No,
but I'm down to try.</i>

359
00:14:24,515 --> 00:14:26,430
<i>I still have a few eggs
left in me.</i>

360
00:14:26,474 --> 00:14:28,215
Well, listen, they give me
conjugal visits --

361
00:14:28,258 --> 00:14:29,781
Okay! You know what?
That's it.

362
00:14:29,825 --> 00:14:31,348
<i>Are you there?</i>

363
00:14:31,392 --> 00:14:33,524
This is not
a dating service.

364
00:14:33,568 --> 00:14:36,571
If you are not helping,
you are going back.

365
00:14:38,703 --> 00:14:40,140
Baby, I'll call you back.

366
00:14:41,968 --> 00:14:44,927
Look, if it's not Betty,
it's probably Margaret.

367
00:14:44,971 --> 00:14:46,886
She works at a diner,
like -- I don't know --

368
00:14:46,929 --> 00:14:48,539
10 blocks or so from here.

369
00:14:48,583 --> 00:14:50,019
Worth a shot, right?

370
00:14:50,063 --> 00:14:52,543
Fine.

371
00:14:57,679 --> 00:15:01,378
I think you should teach
at the Academy.

372
00:15:01,422 --> 00:15:04,773
I mean, yeah, sure,
when I'm Nolan's age.

373
00:15:04,816 --> 00:15:06,557
They need you now.

374
00:15:06,601 --> 00:15:10,126
The good you can do as a teacher
is exponential.

375
00:15:10,170 --> 00:15:12,955
I know it's not what
you were picturing,
but keep an open mind.

376
00:15:12,999 --> 00:15:15,044
Once you hit P2,
I can steer you

377
00:15:15,088 --> 00:15:17,786
to assignments that will
help prepare you to teach.

378
00:15:17,829 --> 00:15:20,745
Look, I'm...
obviously grateful

379
00:15:20,789 --> 00:15:22,486
for your faith in me --
Great.

380
00:15:22,530 --> 00:15:25,228
I'll set up a lunch with
a few instructors on Tuesday.

381
00:15:25,272 --> 00:15:27,187
Um, I'm actually
supposed to be meeting

382
00:15:27,230 --> 00:15:28,666
with the Mayor's team
on Tuesday.

383
00:15:30,016 --> 00:15:31,843
But I'm sure
I could do both.

384
00:15:38,633 --> 00:15:41,679
Control, 7-Adam-07, I have
an on view five-ninety-four,

385
00:15:41,723 --> 00:15:43,986
<i>tagging in progress, at
South Rimpau and Olympic.</i>

386
00:15:45,596 --> 00:15:47,947
♪ A good man know a bad man ♪

387
00:15:52,342 --> 00:15:53,953
♪ ...know a good man ♪

388
00:15:55,563 --> 00:15:57,347
Aah!

389
00:15:57,391 --> 00:15:58,653
Sir, are you okay?

390
00:15:58,696 --> 00:16:00,394
Aah! I'm good! Go!

391
00:16:00,437 --> 00:16:02,439
Aah!

392
00:16:02,483 --> 00:16:04,964
Damn it!

393
00:16:05,007 --> 00:16:06,443
Officer down,
South Rimpau and Olympic!

394
00:16:06,487 --> 00:16:07,967
Are you having
a heart attack, sir?

395
00:16:08,010 --> 00:16:09,098
No! No, it's my back.

396
00:16:09,142 --> 00:16:10,752
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure!

397
00:16:10,795 --> 00:16:12,841
-Is he having a heart attack?
-No! It's just my back.

398
00:16:12,884 --> 00:16:14,843
-Where is the tagger?
-He went left around the corner.

399
00:16:14,886 --> 00:16:15,844
Stay here
and call an ambulance.

400
00:16:15,887 --> 00:16:17,367
-Okay.
-Aah!

401
00:16:17,411 --> 00:16:18,890
Look, don't move.

402
00:16:18,934 --> 00:16:21,023
Sir, don't get up.

403
00:16:21,067 --> 00:16:23,504
♪ A little bit of bad, bad, bad, bad ♪

404
00:16:23,547 --> 00:16:26,637
♪ A little bit of ♪

405
00:16:26,681 --> 00:16:29,205
♪ A little bit of bad, bad, bad, bad ♪

406
00:16:29,249 --> 00:16:30,859
♪ A little bit of ♪

407
00:17:28,351 --> 00:17:31,354
Son of a...

408
00:17:37,621 --> 00:17:40,537
Questioning <i>every</i> man
at the nightclub

409
00:17:40,581 --> 00:17:41,930
would be more palatable.
That's not racial profiling.

410
00:17:41,973 --> 00:17:43,236
But it would take forever.

411
00:17:43,279 --> 00:17:45,281
What I should do
is take a photo

412
00:17:45,325 --> 00:17:47,022
of everybody holding their IDs
as they leave the club.

413
00:17:47,066 --> 00:17:48,502
That way,
I can circle back.

414
00:17:48,545 --> 00:17:50,156
Yeah, but that's not
one of the options.
I know.

415
00:17:50,199 --> 00:17:52,854
Whren vs. US Supreme Court
says you can profile

416
00:17:52,897 --> 00:17:55,204
as much as you want, as long as
there's at least some pretense.

417
00:17:55,248 --> 00:17:56,727
I don't think
that's what they meant.

418
00:17:56,771 --> 00:17:58,207
It <i>is</i> what they meant.

419
00:17:58,251 --> 00:18:00,122
I got my law degree online
two years ago.

420
00:18:00,166 --> 00:18:02,298
You know I'm licensed
to practice in five states

421
00:18:02,342 --> 00:18:04,257
and the unincorporated territory
of Guam?

422
00:18:04,300 --> 00:18:05,867
Okay. What's your take
on this?

423
00:18:05,910 --> 00:18:07,564
There's a stabbing
at a nightclub.

424
00:18:07,608 --> 00:18:10,263
The victim says she's pretty
sure the suspect is Black

425
00:18:10,306 --> 00:18:12,743
and he has a scar
on his right arm.

426
00:18:12,787 --> 00:18:14,658
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
She's sure about the scar

427
00:18:14,702 --> 00:18:16,399
but only "pretty sure"
that he's Black?

428
00:18:16,443 --> 00:18:18,358
-That's what I said.
-Something's off.

429
00:18:18,401 --> 00:18:20,490
Obviously, she's creating
a diversion

430
00:18:20,534 --> 00:18:22,666
while he's probably in the back,
robbing the place.

431
00:18:22,710 --> 00:18:25,800
That's what you get
for asking a sociopath.

432
00:18:30,674 --> 00:18:33,590
Mmm, I love the smell
of a greasy spoon.

433
00:18:33,634 --> 00:18:35,418
Sit wherever you want.

434
00:18:35,462 --> 00:18:40,162
Oscar? I thought you were in
prison for the next 40 years.

435
00:18:40,206 --> 00:18:41,946
Early release.
Good behavior.

436
00:18:41,990 --> 00:18:43,818
-Seriously?
-No.

437
00:18:43,861 --> 00:18:45,602
He's helping us with a case, and
then he's going straight back.

438
00:18:45,646 --> 00:18:48,083
Okay. You're no fun.
Can I have some pie?

439
00:18:48,127 --> 00:18:50,172
Did you and Oscar
have a kid?

440
00:18:50,216 --> 00:18:51,869
God, no.

441
00:18:51,913 --> 00:18:54,263
Oscar?

442
00:18:54,307 --> 00:18:56,265
I am sorry.
Do I know you?

443
00:18:56,309 --> 00:18:58,049
You lousy little --

444
00:18:58,093 --> 00:18:59,703
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!

445
00:18:59,747 --> 00:19:00,704
-Ma'am, ma'am, ma'am. Easy.
-What is all this about?

446
00:19:00,748 --> 00:19:02,706
You knock me up
and disappear,

447
00:19:02,750 --> 00:19:04,882
and then I find out
you're in jail for murder?

448
00:19:04,926 --> 00:19:06,667
Wait.
Ashley is Oscar's kid?

449
00:19:06,710 --> 00:19:08,886
You cheated on me
with Cindy?!

450
00:19:08,930 --> 00:19:10,453
Hold on. I think
it's coming back to me.

451
00:19:10,497 --> 00:19:11,933
You son of a --
Ladies, ladies! L-Ladies!

452
00:19:11,976 --> 00:19:13,891
Please, I appreciate
how difficult

453
00:19:13,935 --> 00:19:15,328
this must be for you,
but right now

454
00:19:15,371 --> 00:19:17,156
we need to speak
with your daughter.

455
00:19:17,199 --> 00:19:18,200
-Is she in trouble?
-I hope not.

456
00:19:18,244 --> 00:19:19,680
But the sooner we find her,

457
00:19:19,723 --> 00:19:21,725
the sooner this guy
gets back behind bars.

458
00:19:21,769 --> 00:19:23,205
Let me get a pen.

459
00:19:25,033 --> 00:19:26,904
Sir, don't get up.

460
00:19:26,948 --> 00:19:29,472
Officer Chen, remind me.

461
00:19:29,516 --> 00:19:31,300
Which one of us
gives the orders?

462
00:19:31,344 --> 00:19:32,780
You do, sir.

463
00:19:32,823 --> 00:19:34,651
Yeah.

464
00:19:37,393 --> 00:19:40,222
Dave? Oh, you work
with Emmett, right?

465
00:19:40,266 --> 00:19:41,919
Yes and yes.

466
00:19:44,748 --> 00:19:46,663
Did you lose consciousness
at any point?

467
00:19:46,707 --> 00:19:48,883
-No.
-Any pain in your chest?

468
00:19:48,926 --> 00:19:51,190
No, I threw my back out.

469
00:19:51,233 --> 00:19:53,496
It happens two times a year
like clockwork.

470
00:19:53,540 --> 00:19:55,498
Well, I still gotta take you in,
make sure there's nothing else.

471
00:19:55,542 --> 00:19:57,065
So, you're going out
with Emmett, right?

472
00:19:57,108 --> 00:19:59,937
Was.
Oh. Sorry.

473
00:19:59,981 --> 00:20:02,201
Why the hell would he break up
with <i>you?</i> You're gorgeous.

474
00:20:02,244 --> 00:20:03,941
Uh, do I really need
to be here for this?

475
00:20:03,985 --> 00:20:05,291
No, sir.

476
00:20:05,334 --> 00:20:06,944
I, uh,
finished canvassing.

477
00:20:06,988 --> 00:20:08,903
No one got a good look
at the tagger.

478
00:20:08,946 --> 00:20:11,253
We're ready to transport him.
You'll follow?

479
00:20:11,297 --> 00:20:13,081
No, I have to wait
for my T.O.

480
00:20:13,124 --> 00:20:14,691
Officer West
will take over from here.

481
00:20:14,735 --> 00:20:17,303
Too bad.

482
00:20:17,346 --> 00:20:18,956
Do you want
to go out later?

483
00:20:19,000 --> 00:20:20,871
Tonight?
God, yes.

484
00:20:20,915 --> 00:20:22,786
Okay. Great.

485
00:20:22,830 --> 00:20:24,962
Uh, Jackson will
give you my number.

486
00:20:26,137 --> 00:20:27,095
Bye.

487
00:20:28,444 --> 00:20:29,489
What are you doing?

488
00:20:29,532 --> 00:20:32,100
What?
A girl can ask a guy out.

489
00:20:32,143 --> 00:20:33,232
Yeah, a guy that works
with your ex?

490
00:20:33,275 --> 00:20:35,234
-That is not why I did that.
-Mm-hmm.

491
00:20:35,277 --> 00:20:36,887
-Uh --
-No comment.

492
00:20:36,931 --> 00:20:38,846
Boot, let's go.

493
00:20:38,889 --> 00:20:40,195
Not a word about the shop.

494
00:20:40,239 --> 00:20:42,415
-Give him my number.
-I see you.

495
00:20:45,940 --> 00:20:48,072
So, you're my dad, huh?

496
00:20:48,116 --> 00:20:50,945
Mom told me you were
a roadie for Matchbox 20.

497
00:20:50,988 --> 00:20:53,904
Better than
telling you I was <i>serving</i> 20.

498
00:20:53,948 --> 00:20:55,254
It's more like 40.

499
00:20:55,297 --> 00:20:57,299
How do you know
Austin Abassi?

500
00:20:57,343 --> 00:20:59,301
Uh, we were dating
a little.

501
00:20:59,345 --> 00:21:01,129
When was the last time
you saw him?

502
00:21:01,172 --> 00:21:03,262
I don't know.
A week ago, maybe two.

503
00:21:03,305 --> 00:21:04,654
Is he okay?

504
00:21:04,698 --> 00:21:07,309
He's been kidnapped.
And you're lying to us.

505
00:21:07,353 --> 00:21:08,615
I-I'm not.

506
00:21:08,658 --> 00:21:10,312
Crime-scene techs
found your DNA

507
00:21:10,356 --> 00:21:12,271
on a beer bottle
in Austin's apartment.

508
00:21:12,314 --> 00:21:13,924
That DNA wouldn't have
survived a week.

509
00:21:13,968 --> 00:21:15,709
You need to come clean.
Right now.

510
00:21:15,752 --> 00:21:18,189
As Ashley's lawyer,
I'm going to advise her

511
00:21:18,233 --> 00:21:20,366
not to talk to you
until we've conferred.

512
00:21:20,409 --> 00:21:22,629
Okay, that's not gonna
happen, because you're
not a real lawyer,

513
00:21:22,672 --> 00:21:24,718
and even if you were,
there are rules against

514
00:21:24,761 --> 00:21:26,328
family representing family.

515
00:21:26,372 --> 00:21:28,765
Wrong.
I passed the bar.

516
00:21:28,809 --> 00:21:31,638
And as far as that being rules,
it's more like guidelines.

517
00:21:31,681 --> 00:21:34,597
And even if they were rules,
we're family by blood only.

518
00:21:34,641 --> 00:21:37,600
You do <i>not</i> want him
as your lawyer.

519
00:21:37,644 --> 00:21:39,776
-He's a nine-time loser.
-If you tell them anything

520
00:21:39,820 --> 00:21:41,822
without first getting
advice of counsel,

521
00:21:41,865 --> 00:21:44,172
you're guaranteed
to do jail time.

522
00:21:44,215 --> 00:21:47,306
Okay.
He's my lawyer.

523
00:21:48,655 --> 00:21:50,570
Could I have a moment alone
with my client, please?

524
00:21:59,927 --> 00:22:02,059
So, you're in on it.

525
00:22:02,103 --> 00:22:04,366
Maybe.
Come on, kid.

526
00:22:04,410 --> 00:22:06,673
Sniffing out cons
is on the family crest.

527
00:22:06,716 --> 00:22:08,805
Okay.

528
00:22:08,849 --> 00:22:10,633
Austin's parents
cut him off,

529
00:22:10,677 --> 00:22:13,419
so we figured,
if he was kidnapped,

530
00:22:13,462 --> 00:22:15,508
his parents would
have to pay up.

531
00:22:15,551 --> 00:22:18,119
Okay. That's not the most
original idea, but still,

532
00:22:18,162 --> 00:22:20,600
if you execute it properly,
I guess...

533
00:22:20,643 --> 00:22:21,905
Where is he now?

534
00:22:21,949 --> 00:22:23,907
A friend's apartment
in Culver City.

535
00:22:23,951 --> 00:22:26,432
Okay. I'm gonna
see you through this.

536
00:22:26,475 --> 00:22:29,173
But you have to insist that I'm
with you every step of the way.

537
00:22:29,217 --> 00:22:30,871
They're going to try
and separate us.

538
00:22:30,914 --> 00:22:32,176
Okay.

539
00:22:32,220 --> 00:22:34,440
You know, I really

540
00:22:34,483 --> 00:22:37,225
can't picture
you and Mom together.

541
00:22:37,268 --> 00:22:39,619
You kidding me?
She was the love of my life.

542
00:22:41,447 --> 00:22:43,405
Officers?

543
00:22:48,454 --> 00:22:51,674
Yeah, what we have here
is a victimless crime.

544
00:22:51,718 --> 00:22:55,156
Austin was having a disagreement
with his parents about money --

545
00:22:55,199 --> 00:22:56,418
So he faked
his own kidnapping?

546
00:22:56,462 --> 00:22:58,115
Not the most
original idea.

547
00:22:58,159 --> 00:23:00,030
And not victimless, either.

548
00:23:00,074 --> 00:23:02,642
Austin's parents have been
going through hell with worry.

549
00:23:02,685 --> 00:23:03,817
Whatever.

550
00:23:05,035 --> 00:23:07,821
-Uh, they're loaded.
-Not a million dollars loaded.

551
00:23:07,864 --> 00:23:10,998
They have been frantically
trying to pull money together.

552
00:23:11,041 --> 00:23:13,000
Who said anything
about a million?

553
00:23:13,043 --> 00:23:15,481
Austin sent an e-mail
asking for 100K.

554
00:23:15,524 --> 00:23:16,960
That was delivered
yesterday.

555
00:23:18,571 --> 00:23:20,137
And he didn't tell you.

556
00:23:20,181 --> 00:23:22,749
That snake's trying
to cut me out.

557
00:23:22,792 --> 00:23:24,098
I'm gonna kill him.

558
00:23:24,141 --> 00:23:26,013
That's my girl.

559
00:23:26,056 --> 00:23:28,537
And a-as your lawyer,
I recommend that you refrain

560
00:23:28,581 --> 00:23:31,410
from making any kind of
threats -- even in jest.

561
00:23:31,453 --> 00:23:32,672
Do you know
where Austin is now?

562
00:23:32,715 --> 00:23:35,457
Yeah.

563
00:23:35,501 --> 00:23:38,155
I-I don't want
to be in handcuffs.

564
00:23:38,199 --> 00:23:40,201
Oh, no one does.
You get used to it.

565
00:23:44,814 --> 00:23:46,555
Austin?

566
00:23:48,078 --> 00:23:50,820
That bastard. He must have
taken the money and split.

567
00:23:50,864 --> 00:23:52,256
Everybody freeze.

568
00:23:54,215 --> 00:23:56,173
Control, 7-Adam-15,

569
00:23:56,217 --> 00:23:58,349
update my call
to a suspicious circumstance.

570
00:23:58,393 --> 00:24:01,309
I have blood at the location,
and the occupant is missing.

571
00:24:01,352 --> 00:24:02,876
Possible two-oh-seven.

572
00:24:02,919 --> 00:24:04,443
And I need a unit
to escort a prisoner

573
00:24:04,486 --> 00:24:06,793
-back to Cal Correctional.
-Uh, wait a minute.

574
00:24:06,836 --> 00:24:08,664
Who else did you tell about
your fake kidnapping plan?

575
00:24:08,708 --> 00:24:11,406
-Don't answer that.
-Your so-called lawyer

576
00:24:11,450 --> 00:24:13,060
does not have your best interest
at heart.

577
00:24:13,103 --> 00:24:15,671
He is only looking to extend
his time out of prison.

578
00:24:15,715 --> 00:24:18,848
If you actually care about
Austin, you'll help us find him.

579
00:24:18,892 --> 00:24:20,981
The only way you're
gonna stay out of prison

580
00:24:21,024 --> 00:24:22,809
is by moving your way
up the food chain.

581
00:24:24,680 --> 00:24:26,029
Take us to your boss.

582
00:24:31,818 --> 00:24:33,559
You order takeout?

583
00:24:33,602 --> 00:24:35,256
No.

584
00:24:43,046 --> 00:24:45,048
W-Whoa!
Don't hurt me. I'm --

585
00:24:45,092 --> 00:24:46,223
Police.
What's in the bag?

586
00:24:46,267 --> 00:24:48,051
I don't know.
It's a TaskFast gig.

587
00:24:48,095 --> 00:24:49,836
Pick it up from "A,"
drop it off at "B."

588
00:24:49,879 --> 00:24:51,359
And where was Point "A"?

589
00:24:51,402 --> 00:24:52,926
Car wash on Melrose.

590
00:25:01,717 --> 00:25:03,980
"I'll drain a pint
of blood every two hours

591
00:25:04,024 --> 00:25:05,547
until I get my million bucks."

592
00:25:05,591 --> 00:25:06,983
Oh, my God.

593
00:25:19,474 --> 00:25:21,476
Angela.

594
00:25:21,520 --> 00:25:22,999
Don't know what to
congratulate you on first --

595
00:25:23,043 --> 00:25:25,741
detective or baby.

596
00:25:25,785 --> 00:25:27,700
Long as your presence
is letting me keep this case,

597
00:25:27,743 --> 00:25:29,745
-it doesn't matter.
-Ooh, sorry.

598
00:25:29,789 --> 00:25:32,835
Judge Abassi already reached out
to the SAC personally.

599
00:25:32,879 --> 00:25:35,403
My guys are en route.
We'll take it from here.

600
00:25:35,446 --> 00:25:37,144
You should, uh --
You should go home.

601
00:25:37,187 --> 00:25:39,102
Get some rest,
put your feet up.

602
00:25:40,756 --> 00:25:43,150
Angela, you're gonna be a mom.
Congratulations.

603
00:25:43,193 --> 00:25:45,369
You know, I recently
became a parent myself

604
00:25:45,413 --> 00:25:48,111
-if you want any tips.
-Oscar Hutchinson.

605
00:25:48,155 --> 00:25:52,507
And you must be the daughter,
girlfriend, co-conspirator?

606
00:25:52,551 --> 00:25:54,857
And my client. You can't speak
to her alone without me present.

607
00:25:54,901 --> 00:25:57,730
You're a felon
and a family member.

608
00:25:57,773 --> 00:26:00,907
Well, we can stand here
arguing about my standing,

609
00:26:00,950 --> 00:26:03,823
or we can say goodbye to LAPD,
go in, make a deal,

610
00:26:03,866 --> 00:26:05,651
catch the kidnapper,
and have you home by dinner.

611
00:26:07,653 --> 00:26:09,524
Alright. Let's go.
Both of you.

612
00:26:09,568 --> 00:26:12,222
Sir, you can't trust him.

613
00:26:12,266 --> 00:26:14,573
This is not my first day...
Officer.

614
00:26:14,616 --> 00:26:17,184
Listen, it was really nice
seeing you two again.

615
00:26:17,227 --> 00:26:19,273
And, Nolan, because you're
such a Good Samaritan,

616
00:26:19,316 --> 00:26:21,580
I'm gonna help you answer
that law-class question.

617
00:26:21,623 --> 00:26:23,799
The answer is, "A,"
detain all the Black guys.

618
00:26:23,843 --> 00:26:26,062
Because, well,
that's what cops do.

619
00:26:27,977 --> 00:26:31,024
And -- And, A-Angela, listen,
if -- if you need a birth coach,

620
00:26:31,067 --> 00:26:32,939
I just got
my Doula certification,

621
00:26:32,982 --> 00:26:35,637
and, you know, we can negotiate
a really good nice price.

622
00:26:35,681 --> 00:26:37,813
Alright, let's go,
smart guy.

623
00:26:37,857 --> 00:26:40,381
-Good job not killing him.
-Thanks.

624
00:26:40,424 --> 00:26:42,426
I'm gonna go pack up my stuff.
Mm.

625
00:26:44,254 --> 00:26:46,953
Yes?

626
00:26:46,996 --> 00:26:49,129
Professor Ryan,
it's, uh, John Nolan.

627
00:26:49,172 --> 00:26:51,174
Do you have an answer for me?
<i>N-Not yet.</i>

628
00:26:51,218 --> 00:26:53,176
Um, am I limited to the answers
that you gave me?

629
00:26:53,220 --> 00:26:56,266
-Yes.
-The thing is, that
description isn't reliable,

630
00:26:56,310 --> 00:26:58,138
so as an officer,
I'd have to hone in

631
00:26:58,181 --> 00:27:00,662
on the other witnesses --

632
00:27:00,706 --> 00:27:02,055
She hung up on me.

633
00:27:02,098 --> 00:27:04,144
This isn't funny.
I'm sorry.

634
00:27:04,187 --> 00:27:05,928
-I need this make-up test.
-I know.

635
00:27:05,972 --> 00:27:07,669
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.

636
00:27:07,713 --> 00:27:10,237
-Where should we go tonight?
-Do you think he likes sushi?

637
00:27:10,280 --> 00:27:12,674
-Everybody likes sushi, right?
-What?

638
00:27:12,718 --> 00:27:14,328
You disapprove?

639
00:27:14,371 --> 00:27:16,635
You think I'm just dating him
to make Emmett jealous?

640
00:27:16,678 --> 00:27:21,074
And, yeah, maybe I am,
but he deserves it, and it's --

641
00:27:21,117 --> 00:27:23,250
Will you say something,
please?

642
00:27:23,293 --> 00:27:24,686
Look, today's
the first time

643
00:27:24,730 --> 00:27:26,296
you've talked about Emmett
in weeks.

644
00:27:26,340 --> 00:27:27,689
Well, you hate it when I talk
about personal stuff.

645
00:27:27,733 --> 00:27:29,256
And yet you still do.

646
00:27:29,299 --> 00:27:31,084
But in all
those conversations,

647
00:27:31,127 --> 00:27:33,869
you haven't said one word
about your boyfriend.

648
00:27:33,913 --> 00:27:35,523
What are you saying?

649
00:27:35,566 --> 00:27:37,177
Look, maybe Emmett
treated the relationship

650
00:27:37,220 --> 00:27:38,918
like it didn't matter
because

651
00:27:38,961 --> 00:27:40,876
<i>you</i> treated it
like it didn't matter.

652
00:27:46,360 --> 00:27:48,318
Alright, focus up.
You read the file.

653
00:27:48,362 --> 00:27:49,972
You think 3 Eyez
is done for the day?

654
00:27:50,016 --> 00:27:54,150
Um...no.

655
00:27:54,194 --> 00:27:57,240
He tagged two police cars, but
they're already being repainted,

656
00:27:57,284 --> 00:27:59,721
and he got interrupted
when he tagged that building.

657
00:27:59,765 --> 00:28:01,897
He'll want to throw up
a full tag.

658
00:28:01,941 --> 00:28:03,725
Somewhere that makes
a statement.

659
00:28:03,769 --> 00:28:06,119
Exactly. And we'll be there
to catch him.

660
00:28:09,557 --> 00:28:12,255
"Eagle Eye."

661
00:28:12,299 --> 00:28:14,475
What?
The nickname I got.

662
00:28:14,518 --> 00:28:16,912
Uh, after the shop
got tagged under my nose.

663
00:28:18,435 --> 00:28:20,176
But it wasn't my T.O.
who came up with it.

664
00:28:20,220 --> 00:28:23,919
It was Isabel. Kind of
became her pet name for me.

665
00:28:23,963 --> 00:28:26,052
Aww. That's sweet.

666
00:28:26,095 --> 00:28:28,489
Yeah.

667
00:28:28,532 --> 00:28:30,404
<i>7-Adam-19.</i>

668
00:28:30,447 --> 00:28:32,885
<i>Falling accident,
8950 South Ridgley Drive.</i>

669
00:28:32,928 --> 00:28:34,974
<i>Injuries unknown.</i>

670
00:28:35,017 --> 00:28:37,150
7-Adam-19, responding.

671
00:28:41,371 --> 00:28:43,765
Where's Jackson? The CAD report
said officer down.

672
00:28:43,809 --> 00:28:45,114
He's not answering
his cell --

673
00:28:45,158 --> 00:28:47,334
Percy. Jackson's fine.
I got hurt.

674
00:28:47,377 --> 00:28:48,944
He's just getting us
a cup of coffee.

675
00:28:48,988 --> 00:28:50,859
What happened?

676
00:28:50,903 --> 00:28:53,775
Tried to chase down the tagger.
I threw my back out.

677
00:28:53,819 --> 00:28:55,298
You know you're
too old for that.

678
00:28:55,342 --> 00:28:57,605
Follow my lead, take a desk job.
Pay's better.

679
00:28:57,648 --> 00:29:01,130
I hear you've been pushing
Jackson toward I.A.

680
00:29:01,174 --> 00:29:02,958
We need him. There's
a lot more Dougs to weed out.

681
00:29:03,002 --> 00:29:04,873
That's true.

682
00:29:04,917 --> 00:29:08,311
But Jackson's in a unique
position to make a difference.

683
00:29:08,355 --> 00:29:11,271
So I think he'd have more of an
impact at the Academy than I.A.

684
00:29:11,314 --> 00:29:13,795
Well, he's my son.
You don't think I know
what's best for him?

685
00:29:13,839 --> 00:29:15,449
I know he's your son.
I'm not trying --

686
00:29:15,492 --> 00:29:18,408
You can, uh, have mine, Dad.

687
00:29:18,452 --> 00:29:21,150
I'll come back once you guys
are finished planning my career.

688
00:29:32,901 --> 00:29:34,773
Ma'am, don't move.

689
00:29:34,816 --> 00:29:35,774
Alright? An ambulance
is on its way.

690
00:29:35,817 --> 00:29:37,558
I think it's broken.

691
00:29:37,601 --> 00:29:39,255
-Uh, Tim?
-Just one second.

692
00:29:39,299 --> 00:29:40,779
Ma'am, can you tell me
exactly what happened?

693
00:29:40,822 --> 00:29:43,172
Eagle Eyes,
you should look up.

694
00:29:49,831 --> 00:29:51,441
-You're 3
-Eyez?

695
00:29:51,485 --> 00:29:52,660
W-W-What? N-No.

696
00:29:52,703 --> 00:29:55,358
You tagged my shop.
Twice.

697
00:29:55,402 --> 00:29:58,361
Technically, three times.
Shutting up.

698
00:29:58,405 --> 00:30:01,364
It's not as easy
as it used to be.

699
00:30:01,408 --> 00:30:03,627
I'm exhausted.

700
00:30:06,065 --> 00:30:09,024
So I get to participate
in the prison garden program.

701
00:30:09,068 --> 00:30:10,765
It's three times a week.

702
00:30:10,809 --> 00:30:13,159
Practically smell
the fresh air.

703
00:30:13,202 --> 00:30:16,249
And a case of ginger ale a week.
Name brand.

704
00:30:16,292 --> 00:30:17,859
Not the discount crap.

705
00:30:17,903 --> 00:30:21,167
Fine. Just tell me
who's got Austin.

706
00:30:21,210 --> 00:30:23,169
Where was the proof-of-life
photo taken?

707
00:30:23,212 --> 00:30:25,780
You know, speaking of
ginger ale, I'm super dry.

708
00:30:25,824 --> 00:30:27,564
And I have an awful lot
to tell you.

709
00:30:27,608 --> 00:30:31,394
Fine. But you're giving it
all up when I get back.

710
00:30:52,285 --> 00:30:55,766
You know what we love
about you, Oscar?

711
00:30:55,810 --> 00:30:58,334
It's that you're
so damn predictable.

712
00:31:06,386 --> 00:31:09,302
Well, you can't blame
a lifer for trying.

713
00:31:09,345 --> 00:31:10,694
-Shouldn't we have told the FBI?
-I texted Lopez.

714
00:31:10,738 --> 00:31:12,261
She said we'd fill them in
once Oscar took us

715
00:31:12,305 --> 00:31:13,741
to the kidnappers
and we made the arrest.

716
00:31:13,784 --> 00:31:15,090
I told you before, I can't
betray my client's trust.

717
00:31:15,134 --> 00:31:16,222
Unless we get something
in return.

718
00:31:16,265 --> 00:31:18,528
You've got
no leverage here.

719
00:31:18,572 --> 00:31:20,879
The FBI is not
gonna deal with you now.

720
00:31:20,922 --> 00:31:23,142
And if we charge you with
obstruction of justice,

721
00:31:23,185 --> 00:31:26,580
the warden's gonna take away
all of your privileges.

722
00:31:26,623 --> 00:31:29,365
Fine.
But I want a cupcake.

723
00:31:29,409 --> 00:31:32,151
After.
A cupcake?

724
00:31:32,194 --> 00:31:34,066
I heard they've gotten fancy
since I went in.

725
00:31:34,109 --> 00:31:35,937
-Deal.
-Now what do you know?

726
00:31:35,981 --> 00:31:37,634
Well, according to my daughter,
the only other person

727
00:31:37,678 --> 00:31:39,332
that knew about the scam

728
00:31:39,375 --> 00:31:41,508
was Austin's drug dealer,
Malcolm Green.

729
00:31:41,551 --> 00:31:43,162
He works out of a chop shop
in Sylmar.

730
00:31:53,302 --> 00:31:55,130
Alright,
we're gonna do some recon,

731
00:31:55,174 --> 00:31:56,523
see if you're
telling the truth.

732
00:31:56,566 --> 00:31:59,265
No problem. I'll just
hang out here by myself.

733
00:31:59,308 --> 00:32:01,832
-Maybe I'll take a nap.
-Oh, come on, Oscar.

734
00:32:01,876 --> 00:32:03,878
We've been through far too much
for you to pretend like you're

735
00:32:03,922 --> 00:32:06,402
not just trying to escape
the second we turn our back.

736
00:32:09,057 --> 00:32:10,624
So we got you
a babysitter.

737
00:32:12,408 --> 00:32:13,757
That's the guy
you want me to watch?

738
00:32:13,801 --> 00:32:15,759
Yep. Give me
your handcuff keys.

739
00:32:15,803 --> 00:32:18,197
What?
So he doesn't trick you
into letting him go.

740
00:32:18,240 --> 00:32:21,026
Oh.
Like that could happen.

741
00:32:22,549 --> 00:32:23,767
Fine.

742
00:32:25,813 --> 00:32:27,946
If you hear gunshots,
call in the cavalry.

743
00:32:27,989 --> 00:32:30,122
But do not leave him.

744
00:32:30,165 --> 00:32:32,559
You should tell Oscar about
your plans to become a DJ.

745
00:32:32,602 --> 00:32:34,517
Happy to!

746
00:32:34,561 --> 00:32:36,389
Too harsh?

747
00:32:36,432 --> 00:32:38,347
For Oscar? No.

748
00:32:51,839 --> 00:32:54,189
It's time to send
the judge another package.

749
00:32:54,233 --> 00:32:56,191
Go get a pint of blood
from the kid.

750
00:32:56,235 --> 00:32:57,976
That's the same
as a liter, right?

751
00:32:58,019 --> 00:33:00,587
How should I know?
I don't speak metric.

752
00:33:00,630 --> 00:33:02,806
But a pint's definitely
less than a quart --

753
00:33:02,850 --> 00:33:05,853
-Dude. Same amount as last time!
-Come on!
Alright.

754
00:33:07,898 --> 00:33:09,813
I don't see Austin, but I think
we're running out of time.

755
00:33:09,857 --> 00:33:11,728
These two idiots are gonna
kill him without meaning to.

756
00:33:11,772 --> 00:33:14,818
Control, 7-Adam-15, we have
the two-oh-seven suspects.

757
00:33:14,862 --> 00:33:18,518
We have exigent circumstances.
We are making entry.

758
00:33:18,561 --> 00:33:21,303
I need Code 3 backup.
And notify the supervisor.

759
00:33:21,347 --> 00:33:23,697
♪ I got it, I got it, I'm good ♪

760
00:33:23,740 --> 00:33:25,742
 I get it

761
00:33:25,786 --> 00:33:27,657
♪ I got it, I got it, I'm good ♪

762
00:33:27,701 --> 00:33:29,833
♪ I bought it, I bought it,
I get it, I get it ♪

763
00:33:29,877 --> 00:33:31,705
♪ I got it, I got it, I'm good ♪

764
00:33:31,748 --> 00:33:33,446
♪ I'm wit' it, I'm wit' it,
I get it, I get it ♪

765
00:33:33,489 --> 00:33:35,274
 I got it, I got it, I'm good

766
00:33:35,317 --> 00:33:38,016
♪ You dig it? Squad hustle like a relay ♪

767
00:33:38,059 --> 00:33:39,452
♪ On his back like a… ♪

768
00:33:56,991 --> 00:33:59,776
Whoa.
I've only seen that in movies.

769
00:34:01,778 --> 00:34:06,566
I'm gonna buy a Porsche.
And a stripper -- two strippers.

770
00:34:06,609 --> 00:34:08,046
What are you gonna do
with <i>your</i> money?

771
00:34:08,089 --> 00:34:10,352
Dude! Quit it!

772
00:34:10,396 --> 00:34:12,746
He doesn't look so good.

773
00:34:12,789 --> 00:34:16,228
Looks better than you.
He's fine.

774
00:34:16,271 --> 00:34:18,534
He doesn't look fine.

775
00:34:53,047 --> 00:34:55,310
Must have been a ghost
or something.

776
00:34:55,354 --> 00:34:57,573
My grandma told me
this story about this, uh,

777
00:34:57,617 --> 00:34:59,662
ghost that was
haunting toilets.

778
00:34:59,706 --> 00:35:01,273
Grandma?

779
00:35:01,316 --> 00:35:04,841
Really creepy stuff, man,
like out-there type stuff.

780
00:35:04,885 --> 00:35:06,278
-Police!
-Down!

781
00:35:06,321 --> 00:35:07,540
Get down on the ground.
Get on the ground.

782
00:35:07,583 --> 00:35:09,890
Drop it right now.
Right now! Drop it!

783
00:35:09,933 --> 00:35:12,022
-Get down on the ground!
-Down on your knees.
Down on your knees!

784
00:35:12,066 --> 00:35:13,328
Interlace your fingers.

785
00:35:15,809 --> 00:35:17,941
-You got them?
-Got 'em.

786
00:35:21,075 --> 00:35:25,384
7-Adam-15, we got a Code 4.
Scene's clear for EMTs.

787
00:35:25,427 --> 00:35:29,431
25-year-old male,
unconscious but breathing.

788
00:35:29,475 --> 00:35:30,911
Heavy blood loss.

789
00:35:30,954 --> 00:35:33,566
Okay, Austin, you're
gonna be alright, buddy.

790
00:35:33,609 --> 00:35:34,784
We got help on the way.

791
00:35:40,181 --> 00:35:44,098
You said
you were gonna make a deal,

792
00:35:44,142 --> 00:35:47,057
that I wouldn't see the inside
of a jail cell.

793
00:35:47,101 --> 00:35:50,148
Yeah, I might've lied
about that.

794
00:35:51,497 --> 00:35:53,760
You're the worst father ever.

795
00:35:53,803 --> 00:35:56,980
Is there a mug for that?

796
00:35:57,024 --> 00:35:58,460
Oh, hello!

797
00:35:58,504 --> 00:36:00,070
I love
a man of his word.

798
00:36:00,114 --> 00:36:02,116
It's gonna take a little while
to process you.

799
00:36:02,160 --> 00:36:03,552
You're gonna want to
keep your blood sugar up.

800
00:36:03,596 --> 00:36:05,598
Ah, a cupcake.

801
00:36:05,641 --> 00:36:07,077
Thanks.

802
00:36:10,124 --> 00:36:12,039
I didn't know you had
that kind of cruelty in you.

803
00:36:12,082 --> 00:36:13,997
Oh, it's not about that.

804
00:36:14,041 --> 00:36:15,173
See, as parents,
that's what we do.

805
00:36:15,216 --> 00:36:17,305
We sacrifice
for our children.

806
00:36:17,349 --> 00:36:18,959
Sheriff's Department will
be here shortly,

807
00:36:19,002 --> 00:36:21,048
take you back to prison.

808
00:36:21,091 --> 00:36:23,485
I do feel something,
you know.

809
00:36:23,529 --> 00:36:25,226
About having a kid,

810
00:36:25,270 --> 00:36:26,662
knowing the old
Hutchinson bloodline

811
00:36:26,706 --> 00:36:28,447
isn't gonna die with me.

812
00:36:28,490 --> 00:36:30,840
And yet you still put yourself
first every step of the way.

813
00:36:30,884 --> 00:36:32,364
It's all I know.

814
00:36:32,407 --> 00:36:35,497
I know I'm wasting my breath
on this, but...

815
00:36:35,541 --> 00:36:38,108
if you really want to
improve yourself in prison,

816
00:36:38,152 --> 00:36:41,982
stop taking random degrees and
just take a hard look inside.

817
00:36:42,025 --> 00:36:44,724
If you want to be more than just
a cautionary tale to that girl,

818
00:36:44,767 --> 00:36:46,769
you got a lot of work to do.

819
00:36:58,999 --> 00:37:00,740
So, I gotta know --

820
00:37:00,783 --> 00:37:03,482
why'd you start up again
after all these years?

821
00:37:03,525 --> 00:37:07,616
My husband dumped me
for his massage therapist.

822
00:37:07,660 --> 00:37:10,880
And I realized I wasted
the last seven years of my life.

823
00:37:10,924 --> 00:37:13,448
So what? You wanted to get back
at him for leaving you?

824
00:37:13,492 --> 00:37:15,363
No.

825
00:37:17,322 --> 00:37:21,456
I just...wanted to
feel young again.

826
00:37:35,688 --> 00:37:39,039
You're being charged with
a misdemeanor.

827
00:37:39,082 --> 00:37:42,172
You'll have to pay a fine.
Otherwise, you're free to go.

828
00:37:42,216 --> 00:37:44,262
And for what it's worth...

829
00:37:44,305 --> 00:37:45,915
♪ I've known you my whole life ♪...
you're still young.

830
00:37:45,959 --> 00:37:47,569
♪ Still can't figure you out ♪

831
00:37:47,613 --> 00:37:49,876
And your husband's
an idiot.

832
00:37:49,919 --> 00:37:53,575
♪ What makes me wanna cry
is what makes you wanna shout ♪
Thanks.

833
00:37:53,619 --> 00:37:58,101
♪ I used to get so mad,
now I can't live without ♪

834
00:38:00,800 --> 00:38:03,063
-Hey.
-Oh, hi.

835
00:38:03,106 --> 00:38:04,673
♪ You don't care about money ♪
We still on for tonight?

836
00:38:04,717 --> 00:38:07,676
♪ No, we didn't have a cent ♪
Um...

837
00:38:07,720 --> 00:38:10,026
♪ Couple of nobodies ♪
I didn't have the purest motives

838
00:38:10,070 --> 00:38:11,854
when I asked you out
earlier.

839
00:38:11,898 --> 00:38:14,335
You're trying to get back at Emmett.
I get it.

840
00:38:14,379 --> 00:38:16,685
W--
Why did you say yes?

841
00:38:16,729 --> 00:38:18,383
Dude keeps beating me
at Pictionary.

842
00:38:18,426 --> 00:38:19,732
I could use a win.

843
00:38:19,775 --> 00:38:22,082
S-So, we're being
equally petty.

844
00:38:22,125 --> 00:38:24,127
Great.

845
00:38:25,607 --> 00:38:28,393
Look, the guy broke up with you
over text.

846
00:38:28,436 --> 00:38:30,482
He has this coming.
♪ Oh, my, my ♪

847
00:38:30,525 --> 00:38:32,788
But if you've changed
your mind...

848
00:38:32,832 --> 00:38:35,269
Yeah, I have.

849
00:38:35,313 --> 00:38:37,097
I want to go out
for the right reasons,

850
00:38:37,140 --> 00:38:39,491
not because
I'm hurt and angry.

851
00:38:39,534 --> 00:38:41,710
I respect that.
I knew you were crazy

852
00:38:41,754 --> 00:38:43,146
But mark your calendar.

853
00:38:43,190 --> 00:38:45,540
I'm gonna ask you out again
in two weeks.

854
00:38:45,584 --> 00:38:48,456
Deal.

855
00:38:48,500 --> 00:38:53,548
♪ I knew when I let you go,
I'd be back again ♪

856
00:38:53,592 --> 00:38:55,594
Mm.

857
00:38:57,639 --> 00:39:00,468
What?
What?

858
00:39:00,512 --> 00:39:02,688
Well, you called me
down here.

859
00:39:02,731 --> 00:39:03,993
No, I didn't.

860
00:39:04,037 --> 00:39:06,518
I did.

861
00:39:06,561 --> 00:39:09,738
Uh, look, I really appreciate
you both for, um,

862
00:39:09,782 --> 00:39:11,653
having such an interest
in my future.

863
00:39:11,697 --> 00:39:13,786
And I know I wouldn't have
these career options

864
00:39:13,829 --> 00:39:15,918
if you hadn't
opened the door.

865
00:39:15,962 --> 00:39:18,356
Look, I-I have to
find my own path.

866
00:39:18,399 --> 00:39:22,142
And it's way too soon
to know what that is.

867
00:39:22,185 --> 00:39:23,926
♪ I knew when I let you go,
I'd be back again ♪

868
00:39:23,970 --> 00:39:25,798
I just hope that you both
are okay with me

869
00:39:25,841 --> 00:39:30,280
coming to you for advice
as I figure things out.

870
00:39:30,324 --> 00:39:32,544
Of course.

871
00:39:32,587 --> 00:39:36,243
♪ You don't get pushed around,
you always defend ♪
Yeah.

872
00:39:36,286 --> 00:39:37,418
But you better come
to me first.

873
00:39:37,462 --> 00:39:38,767
I <i>am</i> your father.

874
00:39:38,811 --> 00:39:40,334
He's right.

875
00:39:40,378 --> 00:39:42,467
But he is a little close
to the situation,

876
00:39:42,510 --> 00:39:44,294
so you better check in
with me after,

877
00:39:44,338 --> 00:39:45,948
for a more balanced
opinion.

878
00:39:45,992 --> 00:39:47,559
R-Right, yeah.

879
00:39:47,602 --> 00:39:50,083
♪ So I'm bleeding for you ♪
Yes, sirs.

880
00:39:50,126 --> 00:39:53,347
Kidnapping yourself
to get your parent's money?

881
00:39:53,391 --> 00:39:55,305
That is messed up.

882
00:39:55,349 --> 00:39:59,092
Sadly, I knew more than a few
Austin Abassis growing up.

883
00:39:59,135 --> 00:40:01,573
You know, I always heard
money could ruin a kid.

884
00:40:01,616 --> 00:40:03,966
I just thought that was
something rich people said

885
00:40:04,010 --> 00:40:06,142
to keep poor people
in our place.

886
00:40:08,362 --> 00:40:10,320
I'm gonna call Patrice
tomorrow,

887
00:40:10,364 --> 00:40:11,887
discuss how we structure
the trust

888
00:40:11,931 --> 00:40:15,500
so our kid doesn't grow up
to be an entitled jerk.

889
00:40:15,543 --> 00:40:17,415
That sounds like a plan.

890
00:40:17,458 --> 00:40:20,243
♪ ...some way, some day, somehow ♪

891
00:40:20,287 --> 00:40:24,117
So, are we gonna talk
about Oscar?

892
00:40:24,160 --> 00:40:26,946
When I found out
Oscar was connected,

893
00:40:26,989 --> 00:40:30,166
I fantasized about tearing him
apart with bearcats

894
00:40:30,210 --> 00:40:32,081
and then peeing on
what was left.

895
00:40:32,125 --> 00:40:34,214
Then I realized that
saving that kid's life

896
00:40:34,257 --> 00:40:36,782
was the only thing
that mattered.

897
00:40:36,825 --> 00:40:38,653
Oscar just wasn't
worth the effort.

898
00:40:38,697 --> 00:40:41,351
Amen to that.

899
00:40:41,395 --> 00:40:43,179
You know, your fantasies
are a little gruesome.

900
00:40:43,223 --> 00:40:44,703
That's not what you said
last night.

901
00:40:44,746 --> 00:40:47,096
♪ ...told me I could fly ♪

902
00:40:47,140 --> 00:40:51,884
♪ Convinced me there has never
been a better time to be alive ♪

903
00:40:51,927 --> 00:40:53,320
Professor Ryan.

904
00:40:53,363 --> 00:40:54,626
Oh, you almost missed
your deadline.

905
00:40:54,669 --> 00:40:56,454
Almost.

906
00:40:56,497 --> 00:40:57,933
So, do you have an answer
to my question?

907
00:40:57,977 --> 00:41:00,196
Yes.
Uh, no, actually.

908
00:41:00,240 --> 00:41:02,764
Um, I spent the day trying to
figure out the answer

909
00:41:02,808 --> 00:41:04,853
you were looking for.

910
00:41:04,897 --> 00:41:06,725
Clearly, the racial element to
the question wasn't accidental,

911
00:41:06,768 --> 00:41:10,990
so was it all just a test
to see what <i>I</i> would do

912
00:41:11,033 --> 00:41:12,992
to avoid a failing grade?

913
00:41:13,035 --> 00:41:14,384
And then I realized something
that gave me

914
00:41:14,428 --> 00:41:16,299
the clarity that I needed --

915
00:41:16,343 --> 00:41:19,955
the consequences of doing
my job wrong are too extreme

916
00:41:19,999 --> 00:41:23,393
to just pick an answer
to curry favor with you.

917
00:41:23,437 --> 00:41:25,395
I can't pick "A,"
question all the Black men,

918
00:41:25,439 --> 00:41:27,049
because that would
just be wrong.

919
00:41:27,093 --> 00:41:28,442
I can't pick "B" or "C"

920
00:41:28,486 --> 00:41:31,314
'cause there's not enough
information.

921
00:41:31,358 --> 00:41:34,448
We both know what damage
a false arrest can do

922
00:41:34,492 --> 00:41:37,320
to a person's reputation,
to their psyche.

923
00:41:37,364 --> 00:41:41,324
So if failing the answer
to the question means

924
00:41:41,368 --> 00:41:45,764
I don't make up my exam
and get an "F,"

925
00:41:45,807 --> 00:41:47,243
so be it.

926
00:41:49,245 --> 00:41:52,074
Hmm.

927
00:41:52,118 --> 00:41:53,859
Okay.

928
00:41:53,902 --> 00:41:56,775
♪ Oh, somewhere, oh, somehow ♪

929
00:41:56,818 --> 00:41:58,385
You have 45 minutes.

930
00:41:58,428 --> 00:42:00,039
Yes!

931
00:42:00,082 --> 00:42:01,649
Thank you.

932
00:42:01,693 --> 00:42:04,565
Oh, do you mean right now,
to be --

933
00:42:04,609 --> 00:42:06,175
Mm-hmm.
That --
Yeah, okay, that's fair.

934
00:42:08,351 --> 00:42:10,136
Unexpected.

935
00:42:10,179 --> 00:42:12,268
Didn't think
that would work.

936
00:42:12,312 --> 00:42:15,358
"John Nolan."

937
00:42:17,000 --> 00:42:19,000
<font color="#D81D1D">Corrected by</font>
<font color="#138CE9">== Flatto (subscene.com) ==</font>

