♪ Buh buh buh-buh buh-duh-duh
♪ Green light
Finally finished!
Good as new.
Hope it'll stay that way
this time.
What smells like smoke?
Oh, Lucy. She's, uh,
smoke-cleansing your house.
Okay, all done.
Armstrong's energy is no longer
welcome in this home.
But if you feel it coming back,
just call me.
There's a more intensive
treatment I can do.
Ah, that sounds awesome,
but no, actually, this is --
this is good. You know what?
We should really
cleanse the station.
Oh, trust me, that process
is already under way.
They've reassigned
about a third of our officers
to other divisions, bringing in
a bunch of new blood.
Word is, my new T.O.
is from Valley Bureau.
Man, it sucks that Lopez
couldn't finish your training.
Yeah, but I'm psyched for her.
I mean, being a detective
is all she ever wanted.
On the bright side -- even if
your new T.O. is a nightmare,
you've only got 25 days
till you graduate.
You should be moving up with us.
It is not fair
that Grey's holding you back.
That letter of reprimand
was severe enough.
I screwed up.
Actions have consequences.
But when you graduate,
you have to celebrate.
No more Tim Tests? Come on.
He's been quiet lately.
Too quiet.
He's planning something.
Definitely.
Where's the paint?
In the car.
Where's your car? Where's my car?
Someone stole my car.
Who hikes halfway up
to the Hollywood sign
to steal someone's car?
I'm surprised
they got it to start.
Do not speak ill of my baby.
Did you lock it?
Wow. Way to blame the victim.
That's...
So you locked it?
It doesn't actually lock.
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Ugh!
Mnh!
I understand there's a lot
of pressure to look good
on your first day
as a detective,
but we've already
had five housekeepers quit,
and I really like this one.
This is your fault.
You got me pregnant.
I went up a cup size.
Now none of my tops fit.
Right.
I, uh, had noticed a... change.
You did?
Will everyone else?
Oh, I -- I certainly
hope that your co-workers
aren't as focused on your breasts as I am.
My co-workers are 60% men.
Well, they will find out
eventually.
Yeah, but I have to make my mark
as detective before they do.
Once they know I'm pregnant,
they're gonna treat me
different, like I'm delicate,
so I have until I start showing
to prove myself.
Hey. You will.
You got this.
I'm just gonna have to
buy a new wardrobe
on my way to work.
Why is there a pizza box
in here?
Why is roll call
in the parking lot?
It was all
in the departmental e-mail.
You actually read those?
Chen does. Oh.
Turns out, that room needs
some serious earthquake retrofitting.
And we've just been sitting
in it day after day?
Listen up.
In the wake of recent events,
several changes have been
instituted department-wide.
Officer Bradford, you want
to read the top line change?
Yes, sir.
"Any officer requesting
a copy of a police report
must get written approval
by a sergeant.
After use, all copies
must be destroyed.
Failure to do so
will result in discipline."
Officer West?
"Every recruit in the
academy must now report all contact
with active-duty officers,
no matter how small."
And, Officer Nolan?
"No officer shall buy,
own, or possess a phone,
even for personal use,
without also providing the
department with the number."
Do I have to tell my girlfriend
about it, too?
These changes are necessary.
What Nick Armstrong did
has tarnished the badge
and made all of our jobs harder.
We have to prove
to the community
that we are still
worthy of their trust.
And I know
each and every one of you
will go the extra mile
to do that.
To business.
Among our new faces is
Officer Doug Stanton.
Where you at? Here, sir.
Officer Stanton
will be taking over
the training of Officer West.
And finally,
we've been asked to man
the Fourth Street
Community Center this week.
Harper, Nolan, you're up.
And the punishment continues.
Be safe out there.
U-Uh, sir, real quick.
Um, my car was stolen yesterday.
It's in the SVS,
but I took the liberty
of making some fliers.
So if you happen to see it
on patrol,
I would really be grateful
if you could just text.
Is this the car
you left unlocked?
Well, technically, I-I mean,
it's the door mechanism.
Dismissed.
Chen, let's go.
Yeah, coming. Thank you.
Ohh, good. Thanks, Smitty.
♪ Let me know why you had to
lead me on all year ♪
♪ Following the road,
yellow brick, with no fear ♪
♪ No cheap thrill
when we linkin' up to chill ♪
♪ No, I can't cuff,
gotta go and make appeal ♪
Lopez, right?
Yes, sir. Angela Lopez
reporting for duty.
Not like that, you're not.
What?
Duty manual prohibits detectives
from displaying equipment --
Equipment in public,
unless in use.
I know. My gun is
under my jacket.
But I can still see your cuffs
and your pepper spray.
I can't let you
go out like that.
And are you wearing a vest?
Detectives don't wear vests.
Change and get back here quick.
Newbies make the coffee run
every day.
Uh... yes, sir.
Lopez?
You missed a tag.
Hey. Let me give you a hand.
Thanks.
Technically, I'm your
T.O., but I read your file.
If it were up to me,
you'd already be riding solo.
So let's just drop the whole T.O./Boot B.S.
and just be partners.
Yeah. I'd love that.
You think this is a test.
No.
A lot of T.O.S out there
play mind games,
try to make up silly tests,
but, uh, I'm not one of 'em.
Let's go.
♪ Ah ah-ah ah
Grey's right.
We need to rededicate ourselves
to doing this job the right way,
which means the last 25 days
of your training
are gonna be even more intense.
We should check the chop shops,
see if anyone brought my car in.
That's what you're focused on?
Even as parts,
your car is worthless.
Not to me.
Let the hunk of junk go
and focus on
the end of your training.
Is that what you would do?
Let someone get away
with stealing the thing
that means the most to you?
The only constant in your life
for the last 10 years?
It's a car.
It's the only place --
Never mind.
The only place what?
Where I felt safe...
after Caleb.
There's a chop shop on Melrose.
We'll start there.
Not what I pictured.
They're all like this.
Bottom of
the funding food chain.
Well, there goes
the neighborhood.
Policía.
I'm Officer Nolan.
This is Detective Harper.
Don't bother. You won't be here
long enough for me to remember.
Okay. Well, if you change
your mind, uh, drop on by.
We'd love to hear any
concerns you have about what's
going on in the community.
You're my concern
about what's going on
in this community.
They only staff this place
when the department's
doing damage control.
Well, that way, the higher-ups
can congratulate themselves
on how much they care,
without actually doing anything.
Well, if that's your take,
what are you doing here?
Just trying to make
a difference. We're being punished.
I like her.
Okay. Well,
you know where we'll be.
So far, so good.
That was not
the warmest of welcomes.
You expected otherwise?
Look, I know you think all this
is just Grey twisting the knife,
but I honestly believe
he wants us
to use our newfound perspective
to engage with the neighbors.
Sure. You go with that. I will.
Is that your lunch?
Uh, no, it's enough jollof rice
to feed about 30 kids,
as well as some egusi
and some moin moin.
Nigerian food.
It's, uh, Heritage Day
at Lila's school,
and I am supposed to bring
a traditional dish.
A dish?
I may have gone
a little overboard.
But I just --
I want Lila to see
that I am here for her now.
When did you sleep? I didn't.
Listen, you do not know
these moms. They go all out.
I swear, I --
Not one of them has a job.
Judging other moms.
Now you're getting
the hang of parenting.
I got a lot of time
to make up for.
I just -- I want Lila to see
that I am invested.
Try this.
Wow. Too spicy?
For children? Mm.
Sure. It's good.
Oh, good.
Whew! You scared me.
Nice speech
by the Watch Commander.
Oh, it wasn't just a speech.
Grey means it.
Sure. I get it.
A few bad apples taint us all.
These personnel shifts
and rule changes
make it harder
for good cops to do the job.
Well, I'm not afraid
of a little hard work, sir.
Whatever it takes
to do things right.
Spoken like a true rookie.
So, tell me about you.
Married? Kids?
Married, yep, 13 years,
two kids.
Nice. Nice.
What's the wife do?
Giselle's a teacher.
Hopefully, she turns my kids
into doctors.
So no more cops in the family?
Nah.
Job's changed.
People used to respect us,
look to us for help.
Nah. These days, I wouldn't wish
being a cop on anybody.
Not the words of encouragement
you were hoping for.
Hey, I am always happy
to hear another point of view.
Oh. You, uh, mind if I get this?
Partner, not T.O., remember?
Yo.
How's, uh, community policing?
Room for improvement.
Hey, do you have any interest
in tutoring
for a couple hours this week
after shift?
Just wanted to offer some perks
here at the CPC, you know,
draw in some of the neighbors.
Lucy said she's on board. What's the pay?
A sense of accomplishment.
Sign me up.
You're the best. Thank you.
Now, should a copier
be making this noise?
No calls pending. Might as well
see if we can help.
What's the problem?
Hell if I know.
It's like a spaceship in here.
It's all computers these days.
Let me take a look.
Took you long enough.
Almost had to give away
your first case.
There was a line,
but I'm good to go.
It's a burglary report
from a funeral parlor overnight.
Could be addicts
looking for embalming fluid.
Or weirdo sex stuff.
Either way, check it out.
Call me when you get back.
Newbies pick up lunch, too.
LAPD Community Center, right
across the street, over there.
We have ticket sign-offs,
crime-stat updates,
after-school tutoring.
Just want to come in and talk,
say hi, just come on in,
drop in, say hi.
♪ Yeah, be the last time
you wrong ♪
♪ 'Cause it's hard to swim
with those concrete shoes on ♪
♪ Skinny jeans and some chucks
Hey!
Really?!
7-Adam-15 foot pursuit.
Northbound on Alvarado at 8th.
Male, Hispanic.
Control, 7-Adam-07,
attach us to that.
Code 3.
That should get you
to the garage.
Take it easy.
7-Adam-15-A also responding.
Blue jacket, green pants.
Want is 4-5 --
Look out!
Suspect headed west on 5th.
♪ But now it's far too late
to get myself correction ♪
♪ I blame the school,
they shoulda shown me
some attention ♪
♪ I got a chip on my shoulder
♪ And everybody knows it
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, come, on.
No -- God!
Oh, no.
Whew! Something die in there?
You check
embalming-fluid levels?
Last night.
But they haven't been touched.
And nothing else
seems to be missing.
Why would someone break in
and not take anything?
Could be a weird sex thing.
You okay?
Uh, yeah. It's just --
Did you cremate someone
this morning?
No. Not for a few days.
♪♪
So, who's that?
Got him.
Hey, come on! Take it easy!
It's okay, we're just
arresting him for burglary
for stealing this backpack.
What, you need four cops
for a kid stealing a bag?
Yo, my man, back off.
It's -- It's okay. It's okay.
Look, calling for backup is
simply protocol.
We don't know
if the suspect is armed.
Better safe than sorry. Safe for who?
Not for people
who look like him. Or me.
You want us to stick around?
No, uh, we're cool.
I'm not cool.
Are you?
Look, this guy just made
one of your neighbors a victim.
Okay? He's going in. Simple.
It's never that simple. Alright?
If the city wasn't spending
50% of its budget on cops,
then maybe he would
have gotten a leg up
instead of the short end
of the stick.
Look, I hear you.
Trust me, I do.
But I don't have
a time machine, okay?
So right here, right now,
this guy just broke
someone's window,
which is not cheap to fix, and
he took their property.
So if you want to help him,
help him get a good lawyer.
I will.
Are we just supposed to
ignore crime, in his eyes?
It's not that easy.
I mean, he's fighting
against a rigged system,
and he is not winning.
Wears you down.
Uh, you mind taking a walk
back to the center?
I, uh, can still make it
to Lila's school on time.
No. Yeah, of course. What are
you gonna do about the food?
Improvise.
Good luck.
Dispatch, can you connect me
to City Services?
City Services. This is Mike.
Hey, Mike.
Uh, this is Officer John Nolan.
I'm standing at a park gate
on the 500 block of West Elm,
with a bike lock on the gate.
Is that you guys?
A bike lock? No way.
So you wouldn't have an issue
if I took it down?
No, sir.
Excuse me.
Hi. Me again.
I don't suppose you have
a pair of cable cutters
I could borrow?
Sure. You're trustworthy enough,
I guess.
Oh, I don't know if
James would agree with
you, but yes, I am.
You been working
with this crew long?
No. James just throws me jobs
when he can.
Most days, I just line up
at the local Home Depot,
take whatever work drives up.
Used to own
my own construction company,
but that went belly up
when the economy tanked.
I was in construction
in Pennsylvania
before I became a cop.
Yeah, I had...
more than a few very lean years.
Oh, "lean's" being kind.
I almost lost my house.
Something to be said
for day work, though.
Doesn't pay great, but it also
doesn't keep me up at night
worrying about
how I'm gonna make payroll.
You know what? Um...
Write your name and number on
the back of one of those for me.
I have cops coming to me
asking me to do jobs
for them all the time.
I would be happy
to throw them your way.
That'd be great. Thanks. Yeah, no problem.
Uh, I'll be right back
with these.
Write down that number. Yeah.
Park's open.
What the hell is wrong with you?
It was a simple burglary call.
You could have closed out
the case as a non-worker.
Instead, I'm hearing
that you have the coroner
and a full CSU team on site.
Yes, sir.
It's a possible homicide.
No. It's an albatross
around your neck.
Those ovens burn
at 1,800 degrees.
The DNA is most likely cooked.
And unless you have a victim,
the lab moves you
to the end of the line,
so they won't even get
to those fragments for months.
No victim, no cause of death
means no homicide.
All you have is a Health
and Safety Code violation
for improperly
disposing of a body.
I'm impressed.
The way you made it
over that fence --
couldn't do that
even back when I was your age.
You ever think about a career
in SWAT or Metro?
Only all the time.
Buddy of mine's
a commander over at SWAT.
I can put in a good word.
Yeah, that would be amazing.
Alright.
7-Adam-19,
show us Code 6 Get out of my car.
for an on-view 415.Get out!
This is your house.
Get out -- now!
What seems to be the problem?
The problem is
the drunk giant in my back seat.
We landed here 20 minutes ago,
and he refuses to get out!
Sir, get out of the car. Tim: Can
you please stand on the sidewalk?
Don't hurt the car.
It's my only source of income.
What is the goal of this call,
Officer Chen?
To get the Mountain's
ugly cousin out of the car.
Wrong. It is to get him
out of the car
without making things worse.
Now, do you think you can get him
out without relying on your weapons?
Really? A Tim Test right now?
Our goal as police officers
should be to de-escalate
whenever possible.
This from the guy
who set me up to fight
a suspect on day one?
Does this mean
you're not up to the challenge?
No, sir. I am game for whatever
you want to throw at me.
Great. So, here's the deal.
You start with 100 points.
Reach for anything on your belt,
and you lose points.
Baton is 10. Taser equals 15.
If you take out your gun,
that's 50.
Leave this call
with 85 points or less,
and you lose and I write up
a blue page on you.
Getting one of those at this stage of
your training would be a real problem.
Can I earn points? Absolutely.
You get him calm, 5 points.
He agrees
to get out of the car, 10.
You get him to apologize
to the driver, 20 points.
But if you use
any of your weapons,
game over -- you lose.
Back up. I got this.
Excuse me. Hi.
I'm Officer Chen.
What's your name?
I want the pretty girl.
Where'd the pretty girl go?
Well, she's right out here.
Why don't you come out
and see her?
You're trying to trick me.
They told me all about that
in the Marines.
You're a Marine?
Two tours in country. Oorah.
Thank you for your service.
Why don't you get on out
and let the pretty girl
have her car back?
Don't tell me what to do.
Ooh! That's 15, Officer Chen.
You're already
in the loss column.
Let's go out.
Eat a bag of d--Not helping.
I'm not a bad guy. Sir, look --
Back off! Okay. Okay.
Look, I get it.
It's been hard being home,
back in your life,
where nothing feels normal.
But she's just trying
to do her job.
And I know your mother didn't
teach you to disrespect women --
Don't talk about my mom.
She died when I was over there.
I'm so sorry.
You know she would tell you
that you're better than this.
You fought for freedom,
and that includes
this girl's freedom
from you harassing her 'cause...
'cause you got drunk and lonely.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
Bite me.
Fine.
Thanks.
Do you live here, sir?
Yeah, upstairs.
Alright. Head on up,
straight to bed.
And just take it easy
next time you're at the bar.
Yeah.
Calm, plus leaving,
plus an apology.
I crushed this test.
Nice recovery.
Mm-hmm. Have a great day, ma'am.
Oh! Uh, just wait one second.
Have you seen this car while
you've been driving around?
Mm. Super cute. Yeah, thanks.
You know what?
I did see it.
Where?
There it is.
Somebody's inside.
Control 7-Adam-19,
occupied 10-8-5-1,
Wilshire Normandy Station.
Stop right there! Put your hands
on top of your head.
Fingers interlaced.
You are under arrest
for auto theft.
No. You don't understand.
I didn't steal the car.
The guy who owns it lent it
to me, but he lost the keys.
I'm the guy who owns the car.
You didn't even lock it.
What did you expect?
Yeah, well, it doesn't lock.
It does now.
What? How did you fix it?
It was easy.
Just popped off the door panel.
Took like two minutes.
Wait, are you living in here?
How old are you?
17.
Where are your parents?
Dead.
Alright, anything in here that's
gonna stick me? Needles, knives?
No.How long have you been
living on the street?
A year.
Careful with that!
Oh.
Sorry.
Must be hard living like this.
What do you care?
Uh... I-I'm not
gonna press charges.
Here, stand up.
Seriously?
Yeah, it's my car,
my prerogative.
Boot --We'll get you set up
over at a children's shelter,
alright?
Oh, you don't have to.
I got someplace else I can go.
Does it have doors that lock
and people that care about you?
Does the children's shelter?
You know how many times I got
my stuff stolen from there?
And it's too far from school.
You still go to school?
Yeah. I do.
And I get good grades.
Any more dumb questions?
Look, I don't want to make
getting to school hard for you,
but I don't have a choice here,
so it's either jail
or the shelter.
But I won't just
dump you there, okay?
I'll -- I'll help you find
a permanent place.
Is she for real?
Officer Chen, a word.
You, stand here,
hands on the car.
Congratulations. On what?
On your first puppy. What?
Every rookie adopts a puppy
at some point --
someone they think
they can save.
Honestly, I'm surprised
it took you this long.
Did you have a puppy?
That's... not relevant here.Mm-hmm.
What is
is that it never goes well.
Okay, well, she's not a puppy.
She's a girl in trouble,
and I'm gonna help her. Okay?
7-Adam-07, show us Code 6
on the burglary call
at 1119 Brower.
7-Adam-07, copy.
Hey. Um, I'm D'Andre,
and these are my folks.
They don't really speak
much English.
West African?
Uh, Somalia, actually.
I was born in Long Beach.
So, uh, someone
broke into your home?
Yeah. We -- We spent the night
in Bakersfield
for my basketball tournament.
Just got home a few hours ago,
and door was busted open.
TVs, computers,
and my mom's jewelry.
Sorry to hear that.
Used to play a little ball
back in high school.
Used to call me the Dougernaut.
You got a nickname?
Not... really.
Uh, "D" sometimes.
"D," huh? "D-Ball."
Nice. I like it.
So, did anyone know
you'd be gone?
Did you post on social
or anything like that?
Got any tattoos, D-Ball?
I mean... one.
A little, tiny dot
I gave myself when I was 13.
See?
So, who are you claiming
these days, D?
What?
Uh, I'm not claiming anybody.
I'm not in a gang.
So, you're not
Murder East Nation?
State Line Crew?
No, dude,  we got robbed.
You owe anybody money, D-Ball?
What --
Sometimes burglaries
will have personal motives.
My partner is just trying
to narrow the suspect field.
Look, sir, could I ask you
a favor, partner to partner?
What is it?
Officer Lopez never let me do
any interviews alone,
and I could use the practice
over the next three weeks
before I end up riding solo.
You'd be doing me
a real solid, sir.
Alright.
I'll be back in the shop.
But your report
better be bulletproof.
If I find as much as a typo,
it's a blue page.
Understood.
Look, I, um -- I got to
apologize about my partner.
He's done
a lot of work with gangs,
and it gets kind of stuck
in his head.
Would you please show me
the point of entry, sir?
Yeah.
Round of applause
for the conquering hero.
What happened?
I snagged a deep-dish pizza
on the way there,
'cause Donovan is from Chicago,
so, you know, heritage.
And kids love pizza. Only thing they ate.
One mom -- she brought
this jellied fish thing.
One kid cried when he saw it.
Looks like I win at momming.
Not sure that's exactly
how you're supposed to see it.
Shh! Ba-- Shh!
I'm enjoying my triumph.
Anyway, how are things
going here?
Great. I signed off
on a couple fix-it tickets.
Came up with some ideas for
reaching out to the community.
Would you like to hear them?
Sure.
All set.
Thanks for
letting me do that.
Mm-hmm.
Get to work on that report.
Did one of you clip
the bike lock in the park?
I did. Yeah.
Are the kids using it?
Yeah, luckily, my oldest
found the dirty needles
in the sandbox
before little kids played in it.
I had no idea.
Did you at any point
stop to wonder
why the lock was even there?
Those lights have been busted
for a year.
Do you know what happens
in a dark public park?
Yes, drug dealers.
And junkies and who the hell
knows what else.
We lock the park
to keep them out.
We could have helped.
You should have called 911.
To do what?
Clear them out for the night?
Maybe kill someone
in the process?
We're not all trigger-happy.
I mean, most of us want to help.
I don't know about "most."
But I can't roll the dice that
a good cop is gonna show up.
So we found our own solution.
The lock was there
to protect us,
to protect our kids.
Look, you shouldn't have to
trade a place to play
for safety.
No.
We shouldn't.
But we do.
♪♪
City gave you permission
to work on this yourself?
Uh, yeah.
Took some convincing, and I
got to do it on my own time.
All the city has to do now
is come and inspect.
Until then, lights are working.
Hey, that's just great.
You must feel real good
about yourself.
Actually,
my shoulders and my back
are a little angry with me.
And what about tonight?
When they break the lights
again? What then?
Uh, cameras are on the way,
and the Watch Commander
has approved more patrols
in the area,
so if anybody's caught
messing with the lights,
they'll be arrested.
So, more Black and Brown people
in prison.
And then you'll be gone,
and it'll just go back
to the way it was.
I'm just trying to help.
You ever wonder
why cops spend so much time
in neighborhoods like this?
It's 'cause
the arrests are easy.
Hell, I've lost count
of the amount of times
I've seen rookies brought here
and taught,
"This is what a junkie
looks like,
and this is
what a dealer looks like."
And from that moment on,
that's how cops see us.
Okay, look, I wasn't
trained like that.
Well, that's because your
training officer looks like us.
Look, the only person
you helped this morning is you.
Made yourself feel good
while you put a Band-Aid
on a systemic wound.
You want to make
a real difference?
Stop picking on us
and attack crime at the source.
Keep meth
out of this neighborhood.
Anything less,
you're just wasting
both our time.
Morning.
You okay?
Uh... Tamara left the shelter
during the night.
The girl who stole my car.
Right. Sorry.
I'm, like, wrapped up
in my own little drama.
Mm.
I talked to her caseworker.
Tamara's had it rough.
Both of her parents O.D.'d.
She got taken in by relatives,
but there was violence
in the house, so she split.
What are you gonna do?
Try and find her,
even though
Tim's giving me a hard time.
He calls her my puppy.
Says that every rookie gets one.
He's just being judgy.
You know how he is.
Uh, all due respect, screw Tim.
Yeah, and all the other T.O.S.
You know, I am so sick
of being at the bottom
of the food chain,
like, constantly jumping
through somebody else's hoops.
Are you all right?
What is up with all this drama?
Doug.
Like
He did something yesterday
that really bothered me.
The way he treated
this one family.
Black family.
Did he put hands on them?
No, no, it's just the way
he -- he talked to them.
Like, the -- the disrespect
was, like...
24 more days.
Yeah.
No.
It's super healthy.
Then you eat it.
I have too much work to do to
spend the next half-hour puking.
Can I help?
I'm dead in the water.
Our unknown suspect forced entry
into a funeral crematorium
and disposed of a body.
No prints, no DNA,
no gender, age, or race.
All we got is a sneaker print
from the most popular brand
on Earth.
There has to be something.
Suspect approaches,
forces entry.
Alarm goes off.
According to the alarm company,
he enters a code.
Enters it again.
Alarm is still going off,
so he cuts the wires.
He didn't try
two different codes.
He tried the same code twice.
Got to go.
♪♪
Now she's got me doing it.
We got to
get something straight.
Okay.
I was super pissed
when I went home last night,
the way you pushed me yesterday.
Then, I realized
you just don't know any better.
So it's my job
to teach you the right way
to think on the street.
Officer Lopez did that already.
Yeah. Sure.
But I got
a very different perspective
than your former T.O.
I've seen a ton
of gang activity in my time.
And that experience
has taught me
that crooks and dirtbags
always try to hide who they are.
D'Andre didn't seem like
a crook or a dirtbag.
They never do.
Do you know the significance of
that dot tattoo, Officer West?
You see, he has three more
on his chest,
so when he puts his hand
over his heart
and holds up two fingers,
it makes the area code 213.
Birthplace of Crips.
That kid, D-Ball,
is a straight-up gangster.
Maybe I'm wrong.
If so, that's on me.
But I've seen
far too many good cops
get caught flat-footed
making the wrong assumption.
We must remain ever-vigilant
on this job.
Otherwise, we end our shift
in a body bag.
Morning.
You are... six minutes late.
Sorry. I was putting up
lights in the park.
You know they're just gonna
smash those out again.
That's what James said.
But the lights are up,
which means crime will be down,
and the patrols and cameras
will keep the lights working.
That's got to be
value-add, right?
Look, I know you.
I know your heart
is in the right place, but...
...you can't come at this
like you are some kind of...
...savior.
You mean White savior.
Look, that's the last thing
I'm trying to be.
But what am I supposed to do?
How can I be an ally
to the people who live here?
Stop pretending like you know
what they need
and just ask.
Mr. Moore, thanks for coming by.
Y'all paintin' in here?
Something like that.
Have a seat.
Would you like
some coffee or water?
I could use a beer.
You used to work
at Saint Dubois Funeral Home.
Is that correct?
Barely.
I mean, it's been so long.
Your pay stubs show that you worked there
up until two months ago.
Feels longer.
Records also indicate
that you had
your own access code
for the security system.
It was your code
that was entered
during a recent break-in.
Anybody could have seen
that code, tried to use it.
True, but the wear on shoes
is as unique as a fingerprint.
No two people walk
exactly the same way.
This, you may remember,
is your shoe.
And this is
from the crime scene.
♪♪
Okay, yeah, I broke in.
But I didn't kill anyone.
I swear.
I just burned the body,
like all the others.
Others?
Like in more than one dead body?
Yeah.
Okay. I'm going to stop you
and read you your rights.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you cannot afford
an attorney,
one will be provided for you.
Do you understand the rights
I've just told to you?
Yeah. I'm not stupid.
Of course not.
And with these rights in mind,
do you wish to speak to me?
Okay.
Mind if I invite in a friend?
Is she cute?
How many bodies
did you dispose of
while you worked there?
Not many.
7... 12.
I don't know. It was, like,
once every couple months.
But then I got fired,
and I was really scared
to tell the guys, so...
when they brought me
another body, I just broke in.
And who are the guys?
They'll kill me!
You can be a good witness
or an accessory to murder.
Up to you.
Okay, fine.
K-Town Mafia --
Brian Simuro's crew.
But he's crazy. I need
Secret Service protection.
You mean  witness protection.
That, too. Give me all of it.
Pretty sure
that albatross just flew away.
Nice work, Detective.
I'll finish up here
with Mr. Moore.
Go coordinate with Ezra
in the gang unit.
This is gonna be
a front-page arrest.
♪♪
What's an albatross?
Okay, and you've reattached
your front license plate,
which means I can sign off
on this fix-it ticket
as prepared.
There you go.
Thank you so much for coming in.
As you can see,
it's been just a little slow.
Still getting up to speed.
Don't forget to send in the $10
as the...
...processing fee.
Another satisfied customer.
Oh.
Go for John Nolan.
Hey. It's Hugo.
I lent you bolt cutters
yesterday.
Right! Yes. Hey, how are you?
Uh... I'm on a job right now.
We're doing
a commercial kitchen.
They want vinyl composition
tiles in the food-prep area.
Harper.
So we're going through
lots of denatured alcohol...
...paint thinner, drain cleaner.
Building codes forbid
vinyl composition tiles
in food-prep areas.
He knows that.
He knows I know that.
The pay is great,
but the coffee is terrible.
All the filters I found
are stained red.
Plus, no A.C.
until we get the Freon.
And don't even get me started
on the propane.
All the brass on the tanks
turned blue.
Red phosphorus gets
run through coffee filters.
Freon, denatured alcohol --
these are all ingredients
that produce
anhydrous ammonia gas.
Gas that turns brass fittings
on propane tanks blue.
Where are you?
Can't say, but you keep
those jobs open for me.
Of course I will.
Red phosphorous,
ammonia gas? I don't --
It means that Hugo has been
roped into building a meth lab.
Probably a super-lab.
We got to go save him.
Alright, I will call Metro.
I'll tell them to get
a SWAT team together.
No, we have to go.
SWAT doesn't know
what Hugo looks like.
What if they lump him in
with the narcos?
♪♪
This is it.
This is where Hugo's phone was
when we last hit that signal,
but there's nothing here.
Nolan, look over there.
Gases from a meth lab
kill any vegetation
near the vent ports.
It's somewhere over there.
Okay, listen to me.
Some gases
from a ruptured meth cook
can kill you instantly.
So, even with this on,
it can give you
about 30 seconds, tops.
♪♪
We hear a boom, we get
out of there immediately.
Do you copy that?
Copy.
♪♪
Ready.
Oh! Thank God you found us.
They weren't gonna let us go.
Where are the keys?
Up on the wall!
Hurry. We got to
get out of here.
Come on!
Thanks. Oh, my God.
Oh!
That's gas. Nolan, we have
got to get out of here!
Okay, go!
We got to go!
Nolan, come on! We got to go!
I'm not leaving him behind!
We got to get out of here!
Come on. Go, go, go, go!
Come on!
♪♪
...29...28...27...26...
...24...23...22...
21... 20...
♪♪
Ohh, you okay?
You good? Yeah.
Don't watch.
Trust me. There's nothing
we can do for him.
Tamara.
How did you find me?
I checked
all the local high schools
to see where you were
registered, and they told me
that you're usually
hanging out at the library
until closing time.
You can take me back
to the shelter,
but we both know I won't stay.
I know, but living on the street
isn't any better.
You know, you deserve more.
There isn't more.
There's just this.
You don't believe that.
Otherwise, you would have
given up, dropped out.
I think you believe that there's
something better out there.
You just need someone
to help you find it.
So, look, um...
I'm gonna give you my car.
What?
Just until
you get back on your feet.
You know, I know
it doesn't run great,
but it took me to college,
it saw me through
three really bad relationships,
and it kept me sane after --
well, after I almost died.
What's the catch?
You got to let Social Services
help you find a place to live --
one that I'll make sure
is safe --
and you have to keep
checking in with me regularly
until that happens
so I know you're okay.
Like, once a week?
Like, once a day.
It's a free car.
That barely runs!
Once a day
until you're off the street,
or no deal.
♪♪
Thanks.
How's life without Lopez?
Definitely not the same.
Hey, have you ever seen anyone
with one of those
2-1-3 dot tattoos?
Not in like a decade.
That's some
old-school gang stuff.
Stanton tell you about that?
Yeah, right after he told me
that I should listen to him
because he has a different
perspective than Lopez.
Look, Stanton was originally
an L.A. County sheriff.
Rookies in
the Sheriff's Department,
they don't start out
on the streets.
They do two years as guards,
mostly at the Twin Towers.
That sounds like a nightmare.
Nothing like having inmates
pelting you with bags of feces
on the regular
to give you
a jaded view of humanity.
Or a certain color of humanity.
♪♪
Look.
I hear he's a solid cop.
Learn what's useful
and ignore the rest.
Alright?
If you quote me on that to Chen,
I'll deny it.
♪♪
You all done?
I got to pick up the kids
from my mom.
Hmm. How old?
70.
You were talking
about Moms, right?
Mm.
12 and 14.
Mm!
You got any? I do.
Uh, her name is Lila. She's 7.
Right on. Right on.
You grow up around here?
Inglewood.
You still live there?
Is this a side door
into a conversation
about cops living in
the communities they serve?
Busted. Mm.
But you got to admit,
it would make a difference.
Yeah, sure,
but it would also mean
that anyone who was angry
at the police could take it out
on me, my family, my home...
my little girl.
And don't act like you don't
know nobody who wouldn't do it.
I mean...
we're not tight, but...
I get it. I get it.
It's complicated.
Yeah.
For both of us.
But I appreciate you're
willing to talk about it.
Thanks for looking out for Hugo.
He said you straight-up
saved his life.
Well, that wasn't just me.
I mean, Nolan insisted
that we both go personally
so that SWAT would not see Hugo
as a criminal.
Don't write Nolan off.
He is more of a guardian
than any other cop
I have ever worked with.
I mean, right now,
his shift is over,
and yet he's still inside,
waiting for kids
to come by for tutoring.
Anyway, have a good night.
♪ Directions mean nothing
in the dark ♪
♪ When you don't know
where you stand ♪
Whoa. Hold on. No, no.
Whoa, whoa.
You -- You gave her your car?
Listen, I can't deal
with any more judgment.
No. No.
I was gonna say
that's very generous.
Thanks.
Hey!
Uh, hi. Come on in.
Oh, thanks.
These are my boys,
Aaron and Michael.
Uh, hi. I'm John.Hi. I'm Lucy.
Nice to meet you.
Look, I -- I know I've been
giving you a tough time,
but I really do appreciate
what you were trying to do
this morning.
Even though it was misguided.
Yeah.
Plus, they've changed
the way they teach math again,
so I'm a little lost.
Well, you came
to the right place.
Lucy is excellent at math.
Jackson is excellent at math.
Yes, and he will be here soon.
Why don't we,
uh, get you guys settled?
Right this way, gents.
Look, I don't take handouts,
so if you're gonna tutor
my boys, I am gonna pay.
Well, how about this?
Uh, we'll tutor
Michael and Aaron,
and you sit down
and talk to us a little more
about what this neighborhood
really needs.
I can do that.
Perfect timing.
Jackson, this is James.
You met him outside the park.
Yes.
Right this way. These are
the guys that need your help.
♪ I'll be coming back
This is the numbers guy.
Why don't you grab that chair.
How old are you?
12. 13.
--Captions by VITAC--
♪♪