Alright, you guys!
- Whoo!
You just finished your first day
of Police Academy.
How do you feel?
Uh, like it might've been
a bad idea.
Look, I personally don't mind
doing it again tomorrow.
How about you?
Still feel like puking?
Uh, no. I did that
when you were taking
your extra lap, so now,
I just feel
a sense of achievement
and an even greater sense
that sticking, uh, close
to you two is what's gonna
get me across the finish line.
Well, how about this --
we will all get through
together.
All for one, one for all.
Oh! Pinkies!
Hey, well, I personally
want to celebrate
by doing another lap.
That guy serious? Mm-hmm.
- Okay, ready?
- Yep.
Go for it.
What? D-Did you say go?
Three, two, one, go. Wait --
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
No one's saying I got my lights
punched out, but --
Whoo!...I'm just saying...
maybe think twice before you
take on Recruit Chen.
Do it! Go!
Go! Make it!
I'm on your side!
Boom. Oh!
Ohh! No!
Your flashlight's not on!
Your flashlight is not on!
The winner. The loser.
His flashlight wasn't on.
We can do it again.
A-ha. What?
Calm down.
Okay, first of all,
just hold the mitts up.
Geez.
Alright.
Disassemble. Ready?
Three, two, one, go.
Once I catch my breath,
I'm gonna come back in,
and it's gonna be round two.
I'm -- I'm gonna take
a shot at the title.
And I'm arranging it nice, too.
Oh. Oh!
Another winner! Fudge!
How does it feel to be
so defeated?
I...
Man, I gotta practice.
Stop it. Yeah.
Someone gotta practice.
Ooh! Cut. Cut.
Okay.
Alright, you guys, we ready?
What?
First time in uniform.
Everything except the badge.
So, tell me, uh,
why do you want to be
a police officer, Recruit Chen?
Oh, good question,
Recruit Nolan.
- That's me.
- Um...
I guess I want to do
something that matters.
Aw. That was a cute answer,
but everyone will say that.
So, can you do me a favor
and dig deeper, please?
Okay.
Um, I guess -- I guess
I've been adrift since college,
trying on different hats
and different personalities,
and nothing's felt right,
until -- until this.
But I don't think the time spent
trying to find myself
was wasted.
You know,
everything I've done so far,
the profound and the foolish,
has prepared me to become
a police officer
so that I can protect
those who need it the most
and from those
who would do them harm.
Uh, that's... unexpected
and actually amazing.
That was really well said.
Thank you. That was -
I hope they don't ask me.
Now, make no mistake --
you will be tested.
You will see things no one
should have to see,
do things a person
should never be asked to do.
But what will get you
through it all is character.
When faced with
the worst of humanity,
you will need to be your best.
Aww, I love that.
Especially the Captain's speech.
I miss her.
Yeah, me, too.
She would be so proud
of you two.
Of all of us.
Look, just 30 more days and
you'll be a P2, too.
Also? As well?
Okay, until then,
don't speak to us
when we're on duty.
Whoa.
Seriously, we can't be
caught dead socializing
with a lowly P1.
Somehow, I always knew this
about you two.
Ben! Guys, it's Ben!
Hey! Hi!
Oh! Ben!
Oh, congratulations, buddy.
Oh, come, come.
Come in, come in, come in.
God, where have you been?
Where haven't I been?
I mean, other than here.
I spent six months traveling
the world,
meeting fascinating people.
And by fascinating people,
you mean attractive women?
Who you dated?
No, not this time,
Officer Chen and Officer West.
And congrats to you two,
by the way.
No, I started my own global
charitable foundation.
- Wow.
- But even saving the world
couldn't keep me from
coming home and celebrating
my best friend
becoming a glorious P2,
whatever that is.
Anyway, way to go, buddy.
Uh, stop. Actually, I haven't,
um, moved on.
Uh, since you've been gone,
there's been a little...
shifting.
Wait, so you three
are still rookies?
Oh, not those two.
They're good. Just me.
Um, I, uh, have
a 30-day extension
for breaking the rules.
Well, in my business,
breaking the rules is how you
make your first million.
Uh, if only.
But, I-I-I'm flattered.
I'm so glad you're here.
It's so great to see you.
I just feel terrible that
you came all the way to
L.A. for me.
Oh, relax.
You know the foundation is
centered here.
I got plenty of work to do,
including getting Henry
squared away.
For what?
His -- His new gig.
I-I-I thought he told you.
No, and he's already got a gig
called being
a college student, so...
Well, you know what?
You should probably, uh,
talk to him about that.
Now, until then,
I don't think there's any point
in letting this go to waste.
Whoa!
Congratulations, pal.
There's got to be
a ceremony or something
to mark the rite of passage
into P2, right?
When my dad moved up,
he said the Watch Commander called him
to the front of roll call and gave him
a bottle of 30-year-old scotch.
Ah. I'm not really
a whiskey girl.
Oh, God, I hope
Sgt. Grey hasn't heard
the stories about
me and tequila.
Honestly, I hope they give us
something besides alcohol.
Wait, they're gonna give us
separate things, right?
'Cause I --Okay, just slow down, okay?
Don't ruin it by overthinking
everything, okay?
Just relax. Go with the flow.
Right. Go with the flow.
Mm-hmm. Because we are P2s now.
Hey.
Ooh.
And we get to sit with
the cool kids.
Oh, hell no. Keep moving.
Okay.
Man, that hurt in high school,
and it still hurts now. Yeah.
Well, we can't sit in
the front row,
'cause the front row's
for rookies.
So... boom.
Second row, baby.
That's right. What-what.
Hey, nice.
Hey.
Hey, sorry I missed your call.
Oh, no problem. Um...
Why are we whispering?
Uh, I'm in Roll Call right now,
but don't worry.
- I think I have a second.
- So, uh, tell me what's going on.
Ben said he gave you a job,
but he wouldn't give me any details.
Yeah. Uh, I've been meaning to
talk to you about that.
Is it like a summer internship
or something?
No, it's a full-time job.
I, uh, start next week.
How are you gonna manage that
with college?
I'm not. I'm dropping out.
You're dropping out?
Officer Nolan,
you better be taking
a 911 overflow call
from Dispatch.
Y-Y-- Uh, yes, sir. Sorry, sir.
Uh, Henry, we'll talk
about this later.
Do you want to add another week
to your 30-day extension?
You're already
the oldest rookie.
Wanna become
the longest-serving one?
No, sir. It won't happen again.
Good. Now, to the business
of the day.
Officer Chen, Officer West,
you'll --
Where the hell are y'all going?
Oh. Uh, sir,
we thought that maybe --
Sir, it's our first day as P2s.
So, what? You want me to
throw you a party, huh?
Give you a gift?
Give you flowers? What?
What is the reward
for moving up, Office Chen?
Getting to do the job another day, sir?
Are you asking me or
are you telling me?
Doing the job, sir.
That's right.
And today, you'll be
riding together.
I don't usually pair new P2s,
but I thought you two
could handle it.
Don't make me regret it.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
Sit down.
Moving on.
All PAS devices need
software updates.
Be sure to swap out
your old ones ...m guessing your dad lied.
Yeah, no kidding.
...before your shift.
Hey. Henry. Me again.
Uh, call me, buddy.
We need to talk.
Okay. Talk to you soon.
I can't believe he's doing this.
I ju-- He loves school.
He tells me that all the time.
And he knows how I feel
about having to drop out at his age.
Go easy on him.
I-It could be a great job.
How would you feel
if Lila dropped out
of second grade?
Oh, my baby girl would never
disappoint me like that.
Hey, do you have
any camping gear?
Yeah. Enough to take a two-week excursion
down the Amazon. Why?
I'm chaperoning
an overnight camping trip
for Lila's Girl Scout troop.
Wait, you don't like camping?
No one does.
But I have bigger problems.
Alonzo is gonna be there.
The music class guy.
What's the problem?
I thought the two of you hit it off.
We did. And he asked me out.
But I had to cancel,
and then we re-scheduled,
but then he cancelled
at the last minute.
- And you think it was a revenge cancel?
- Feels like it.
But the bottom line is
I need to look good
the next time I see him,
and that is not gonna happen
if I am covered in bug spray
trying to set up a tent.
So, do you want to borrow the
camping equipment or not?
Yes.
Another congratulations text?
Uh, from my cousin. Cop family.
They're all taking me to dinner
at Pacific Dining Car
for baseball steaks tonight.
Hmm. Family tradition.
Wanna come? My treat.
Oh. Thanks. Um... actually,
my parents are coming over
for dinner tonight.
I think they're coming around
to me being a cop.
Uh, that's great.
Yeah.
I'm hot. I'm sorry.
Are you not hot?
Yeah, but we can't
turn on the A/C
until after lunch, so...
Why not?
Oh, my gosh, you're right.
That's a Tim rule,
and he's not here.
It's just us...
and we call the shots.
- Ha.
- Ooh!
Ooh!
The sweet, sweet chill
of independence.
Ooh. You know
something Lopez never let me do?
Hmm?
Yes!
Bumping that bass
of freedom, baby.
Okay.
Ooh, ooh.
Get up, Boot!
"Quit" is a four-letter word.
Do you hear me?
Failure is not an option.
Oh, come on, man.
We're almost home.
Who wants a steak? Huh?
Come.
Can I help you?
Is Angela Lopez here?
In the changing suite.
She's gone through half
of our tissue supply.
Thanks.
You okay? What happened?
This.
- You're going into labor?
- No, the baby's fine.
I just -- Oh, I never imagined
I'd have to pick a wedding dress
based on its ability
to hide my belly.
Who said you have to
hide your belly?
My bridesmaids.
They said this is the one
that camouflages it best.
So, I kicked them all out
and texted you.
You text me "911" on my day off
to ask me if a dress
makes you look fat?
Does it? Yes.
Because you're pregnant.
Are you ashamed of
your baby?
Of course not.
Okay, then who cares what
your stupid friends think?
Show off that baby belly.
Wear what you feel confident in.
Hell, wear a white half-tee
and let your gut hang out
like my Uncle Elliot
at my niece's christening.
He didn't.
Oh, yeah. He even managed to get
his gut in
the holy water somehow.
Anyway, what does your dream
wedding dress look like?
A V-neck dress with
bell sleeves.
Okay. So, we'll start there.
I'll go talk to the lady and
have her pull a few choices.
Okay.
It's our first call as P2s.
There you are.
We got a triple homicide on
the second floor.
Sir, what do you need
us to do? Canvass the area?
Track down potential witnesses?
No, I got a special job
for you two.
Guarding evidence. Follow me.
This is the evidence?
Our suspect may have
helped himself
to some snacks
before taking off.
We think this chocolate bar
might be one of them.
TID's stuck in traffic.
Just keep it safe
'til they get here, Boots.
Uh, with all due respect, sir,
we're no longer Boots.
We're P2s. Don't let it melt.
7-Adam-15, silent
alarm, manually activated,
2-11 type at
Copley Bank & Trust,
28700 Wilshire.
Control, we're on site
at that possible 2-11.
Hold for confirmation.
Control, we have a confirmed
2-11 in progress.
Send additional units
and airship.
Have them shut down about
a block before they get here.
Send a supervisor.
Harper, I think
I can get in close.
Do it. I'll post up here.
Stay behind cover.
Let me know what you see.
Don't make a move
until I tell you.
Come on, come on,
come on, move it!
Put the money in the bag!
Fill it up! Faster! Come on!
Control, suspect is male,
six-foot, black leather jacket,
beige shirt, blue jeans,
wearing a mask,
armed with a handgun.
I'm counting seven hostages,
including two tellers
and a guard.
Come on!
Move! Move!
Keeps your hands up high!
Do not fire. Two coming out.
We got two hostages coming out.
Police! Drop that gun!
Leave or I'll shoot her!
No. No, you won't!
You're not gonna do that.
We're gonna work this out
right now.
No, we can't!
But you gotta let me leave
with this bag or she dies!
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
Okay, look, clearly,
everything's gotten
out of control, so, uh,
I find it's best
in these situations to just
slow everything down,
so let's start with
an introduction.
I'm John Nolan.
What's your name?
Yeah. You're on camera
right now.
They are comparing your face to
DMV records as we speak.
It's Cooper.
Cooper. Okay, good.
Cooper, first thing
we need to deal with
is the young woman you're
terrorizing with that gun.
Look, I let her go
and you kill me.
No. No, not true.
Right now, you have cover
and concealment.
So long as you stay behind
that pillar,
you're gonna be fine.
Cooper, funny story -- this is
not my first bank robbery.
First one was before
I was a cop, and that day,
I had a whole bunch of
problems on my mind,
but as soon as
the guns came out,
I only cared about one thing,
and that was making sure
everybody got out of there
alive, and I think, deep down,
you want the same thing, Cooper.
Look, I don't want to
hurt anyone.
But I don't have a choice, okay?
My family -- I understand.
I know your family would want
you to survive this, too.
So... let the girl go.
Look, if I do, you gotta
let me walk out of here.
Cooper, there's another dozen
officers outside
and more on the way.
Look, none of this
was supposed to happen.
I know. Yet here we are.
Look, you just let her go,
put the gun down,
and it'll all be over.
Go.
Good. Good, good, good, good.
We're almost home.
Now you just gotta
put that gun down.
Nice and easy.
Great. Right there.
Just put your gun down
right there.
No, don't!
Drop it! Drop your gun!
Drop it!
He had a gun!
He was gonna shoot us!
He was giving up!
One Code 4 in the bank.
Suspect is down.
Gunshot wound to the chest.
Unconscious, not breathing.
You okay?
His gun was empty.
To the left.
No, no. Too much, too much.
Back to the right.
Just a hair to your left.
Come on, it's turning into
chocolate sauce.
Yeah, look, we can't have
our first day
as full-fledged cops
end in failure
because we could not preserve
crucial evidence.
Well, unless you can get the sun
to crank the temperature down,
we're screwed.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, sir, uh, these are
the cooling aids
to help protect the evidence.
I like the dedication,
but we just found our suspect
walking down La Brea,
covered in the victims' blood.
He immediately confessed.
Wait, so, this is just...
Garbage.
Uh, do the city a favor and
clean it up before you go.
7-Adam-07,
disturbance at 25616 Wilshire.
Are you free to respond?
Control, that's an affirmative.
Show us responding.
Alright. Let's just, uh,
shake this off
and rock the rest of the day.
Can you grab the chocolate?
Ew. Oh, my -- Ugh.
You doing okay in there?
You ever tried zipping up
a dress
with a bowling ball
on your belly?
It takes time,
so quit rushing me.
I am not rushing you.
I'm prepared to stay here
until you've tried on
every single dress.
Whoa.
Really? Oh, yeah.
I know. It's perfect.
Thank you so much
for doing this with me.
Of course.
Get your claws off my dress!
"My dress?!"
You put it back on the rack!
It's okay.
Everything's gonna be fine.
The police are on their way.
Let go now!
Oh, we're not getting involved
unless someone loses a limb.
Though I should probably
film it for evidence.
Police.
Lopez? What are you doing here?
I'll give you three guesses.
Are you helping her find
a wedding dress?
Well, right now,
I'm watching you
not do your job.
Look, ladies, you just need to
settle down.
Ma'am, you gotta let go of
the dress right now, okay?
They grow up so fast,
don't they?
...my dress!
I'm not leaving without
this dress!
Aah!
Stay there.
Ooh, looking good, Officer Chen.
Looking good.
♪ If you don't think...
It always feels
a little callous to me --
using a death notification
to question a loved one.
It's actually when people tend
to be the most forthcoming.
And for all we know,
Cooper's wife
was supposed to be
the getaway driver.
Well, the car's here.
Man, a house like this.
Why rob a bank?
Why not just take out
a second mortgage?
Maybe he did and he just needed
the cash right away.
For what? Property taxes?
I'm serious.
This whole case is weird.
Cooper said he didn't have
a choice.
What's that supposed to mean?
Looks can be deceiving.
I mean, people in this town
drive around
in cars they can't afford,
flaunting wealth
that they don't have.
Maybe Cooper was just
one of those people
and he got desperate.
What's the wife's name?
Alice Hicks.
You hear that?
Yeah.
Open the door, please.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
No one is coming to the door.
We are making entry to
welfare check Cooper's wife.
Police! Anyone home?
House is clear.
Ice cream's been left out
awhile.
That phone alarm's been
going off since 7:00 a.m.
Any sign of the wife or
daughter?
Nothing.
They might have gone voluntarily
and left the phone behind
to avoid being tracked.
Or they got caught up in
whatever Cooper was doing,
and they're in danger.
Control, notify detectives.
Our bank robber's wife
and daughter are missing.
This is a possible crime scene.
Thanks. We'll take it from here.
Hey. Any updates?
Uh, just that Alice
sent an e-mail
to her daughter's school
this morning
excusing her from class.
Well, we need to know when
that e-mail was sent,
because if it went before
the phone alarm went off --
Nolan, I need you
to take a breath.
Okay, I know this case has
gotten under your skin,
but we've done our jobs.
It's the detectives' case
now, okay?
We are end of shift.
It just feels weird going home
not knowing what happened.
I know. I get it, but trust me,
being able to clock out
at the end of shift,
it is a gift.
Caradine, he will --
he will work this case hard,
and we get to go home.
Uh, more accurately,
you get to go to my house
- to pick up the camping gear.
- Mm.
So that you can spend
the night in the great outdoors
with a bunch of second graders.
And a man who may
or may not hate you
'cause you blew him off.
You know, I feel like you
enjoyed saying that
- just a little too much.
- Did I smile?
I was trying not to smile.
I saw it. Sorry. Guilty.
Ooh. Someone looks handsome.
Thank you. Figured I better be
photo-ready
in case this makes
the Christmas card.
Yeah. What you, uh...
cooking for
your own celebration?
Yeah, it's a special occasion.
I'm making lotus root soup.
It's my mom's favorite.
Okay. Mmm.
Oh, my gosh. It's perfect.
Jackson. Hi.
You still listening to that
mindfulness podcast I sent you?
Every day, Mrs. Chen.
Thanks for recommending it.
Oh, are you leaving?
Uh, Jackson's family is
taking him out to dinner
to celebrate.
Oh. How lovely.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Bye, guys. Bye-bye!
Where's -- Where's Dad?
Oh, he's got his book club
tonight.
Well, that's fine.
We can just have
a girls' night celebrating.
Actually, I'm not here
to celebrate.
We need to talk about
this whole police officer thing.
What? Mom...
Look, you gave it a year,
proved you could do it.
Brava.
It's time for you to do
something meaningful
with your life. "Something meaningful"?
Yeah.
Go back to school.
Get your master's.
Have a profession.
Being a cop is my profession.
As a paid bully for the city?
Is that how you see me?
It's how a lot of people
see you.
Especially now.
I want to be proud of you,
instead of hoping people
don't ask me
what you do for a living.
Mom, can you just support me?
You know, you seem happy enough
for Jackson.
- I-I don't get it.
- Jackson is not my child.
You are. Your father and I
have been very patient,
supporting you
as you quit grad school,
followed your passions,
but now, it is time to
get serious about your future.
Being a police officer
is my future.
I love this job. I love it.
I get to help people.
You want to help people?
Become a doctor. Wow.
Sorry to be so blunt,
but it needed to be said.
Right. Lucy.
What?
Your father and I
will always love you.
Mm-hmm.
But you are risking
your life
for a thankless job,
and we cannot be supportive of
this any longer. Okay. Okay!
Okay. I heard you
the first time.
If you're done expressing
your disappointment,
I would -- I would like
some space, please.
Can you just go?!
♪ ...this love to be at ease
Come on.
Hey. You need help with that?
Alonzo. Hi.
No. No, I'm fine. I got it.
Where are Lila
and the other girls?
Moonlight hike.
I fake-pulled a hamstring
so I could stay behind,
man the fort.
Maybe I should join them.
You wanna wander around
in the woods at night?
You're braver than me. Yeah.
Uh, you know what?
Maybe I will --
I will just make camp.
Okay, you know what?
I have no idea what I'm doing.
Neither did I.
This is all my gear.
Look, I understand if
you changed your mind
about wanting to go out with me.
I just don't want it
to be weird between us.
Wait. I didn't change my mind.
You changed your mind.
You cancelled on me.
Yeah, but then you
revenge cancelled on me.
No. That was a regular cancel.
And after that,
you cancelled on me again.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I-I was stuck
at a crime scene.
I was sure you hated me.
No. No. I don't hate you at all.
Good. I don't hate you, either.
Good.
So, you still owe me
a date, though.
S'mores and a beer work?
Wow. Okay. Yeah. For now.
But if this goes well,
I require someplace with
a wine list and indoor plumbing.
I can make that happen.
Drink fast. Drink fast.
You know,
if we're not there in 15,
they're gonna give away
our table.
Oh, I'm sure once the Maitre d'
sees that it's you,
he'll just move us to
the front of the line.
Listen, look, I never would have
offered Henry a job
if I knew you'd be this upset.
Well, of course I'm upset, Ben.
He's throwing away
his education.
A college degree isn't
the silver bullet
that it used to be. I mean...
this is a phenomenal job
for a kid his age.
He's gonna get to travel
the world, alright?
Make connections,
gain life experience.
Okay, how much is he gonna make?
Low six figures.
That's... more than I make.
I don't want Henry
just thinking that
things in life are just
gonna be handed to him.
Oh, like they were to me?
This is a real job, John,
and I didn't
just give it to him.
He had to come in and sell me
on why he was
the best candidate.
And like it or not,
that's the way the world works.
People are given opportunities
all the time
- because of who they know.
- I wasn't.
Well, you say the word,
and I'll set you up as head of
my security right now.
You'll be making triple
what you do in LAPD.
Trip--
No. Ben, it's -- it's --
it's not about the money.
No. It's about you.
I mean,
you dropped out of school
because Sarah got pregnant,
and there's a part of you
that resents it, right?
This is just opening up
old wounds.
You think I'm jealous of my kid
because he's succeeding
where I --
Failed?
Let's take a rain check
for dinner.
Um -- I don't -- I'm just --
I think I've lost my appetite.
This is stupid.
No matter what I pick,
Patrice will overrule me.
So don't let her.
Look, my dad got drunk at
my wedding and made Isabel cry,
and then my uncle lost
his dentures
in the chocolate fountain.
Same uncle as the baby tee?
Yeah, although he wore
a purple suit to the wedding.
Look, my point is,
there are a million things
you can't control,
so pick what you want.
I want tres leches.
But Patrice will blow a gasket
if I pick an "ethnic" cake.
You know what? Screw Patrice.
Alright, if she's got
a problem with tres leches
or anything else for that
matter, she can answer to me.
Really?
Hell yeah.
Tim Bradford --
What are you doing?
Sit back down.
Will you be my Man of Honor?
Your what? That's not a thing.
Yes, it is.
You're the only person who's
made me feel like
I can get through this wedding
without losing my mind.
Please? I need you.
Fine. I will be
your Man of Honor.
Thank God.
Your first official duty
is to fire
-my old Maid of Honor,
-Gretchen.
What?
Good morning! No. Don't.
- Don't what?
- Don't say words to me.
Beds were invented for a reason.
How awkward was it with Alonzo?
Smiles? Do tell.
We are going on a date tonight.
So, until then, you and I
are gonna find
a nice, quiet spot
to spend our shift,
preferably behind a coffee shop
with a clean bathroom.
No problem. Consider it done.
First, though, we should
probably stop
at the Diamond District.
Why would we do that?
Nolan. What did you do?
I came into work early
because I couldn't sleep.
I just kept thinking about
our bank robber's family --
his wife and daughter just
disappearing like that.
And I know we're supposed to
end the shift
and just move on,
but I couldn't.
So, I spoke to
Sergeant Caradine --
I'm sorry. You did what?
And you were right.
Cooper and his wife
were beyond broke --
two mortgages, tens of thousands
in credit card debt.
Alice had recently took a job
at a jewelry store.
In the Diamond District.
Caradine said it would be okay
if we just dropped by there,
talked to her boss, see if
she tried to contact him,
maybe asked for a loan.
And good news --
right down the street,
they set up
the best coffee truck in town.
It's a win-win.
Is that a yes?
Hey. You were up and out early.
And you were home late.
- How was the celebration?
- Awesome.
Great food, good company,
and a few too many shots.
Mm.
Oh, check out
what my folks gave me.
Saint Michael,
patron saint of cops.
Mm. Is it too late for
your parents to adopt me?
What? Trouble with the folks?
No. They're just not
as fun as yours.
You ready to go? Yes, ma'am.
Day two on our own. Let's roll.
Are you gonna say that
every day?
What? "Let's roll"?
You don't like it?
Eh, you can do better.
Hmm.
Hey, hey,
I've been looking for you.
So, listen, about last night --
Don't you dare back out on me.
Relax. I never go
back on my word.
Good. Because Gretchen
will be here any second.
And you don't think you should
be the one to fire her?
I would, but I'm working a case
and I gotta get to the morgue.
I'm here to see Angela Lopez.
Coward.
Gretchen?
Tim Bradford.
We met before at Angela's
niece's quinceañera.
Right. Hi.
Hey. So, Angela asked me
to meet with you.
Oh.
We were supposed to talk about
the strippers
for the bachelorette party.
Do you have a connection
or something?
Or, hear me out,
you interested in making
a little extra cash?
What? No. No.
Look, I-I'm sorry to be the one
to have to tell you this --
Ugh. Ignore.
You were saying?
You're fired.
It's not you, it's Lopez.
She's -- Wait.
Are you firing me from being
my best friend's Maid of Honor?
Yes. She wants me to take over,
be her Man of Honor.
Thank God.
This whole thing's been
a nightmare.
These... are "Patrice's Picks."
Do not deviate from
the approved list of vendors
without Patrice's consent.
There's a little
anti-anxiety medication
in the front pocket --
you're gonna need it.
This is the Patrice phone.
She gave it to me so I can
always be on call.
There's about a half a dozen
messages
that I haven't had the strength
to listen to yet.
Good luck.
Alright. If you need me,
I'll be just down the block.
All I need is a quart of coffee
and a glazed donut.
Hey. Hey, are you seeing this?
There's a van -- just pulled
up outside Alice's building.
It says "Nonna Primo's Pizza"
on the side.
That same van was parked outside
the bank yesterday.
Yeah, I remember.
That cannot be a coincidence.
What if Cooper was forced
to rob that bank?
Tell me if this tracks -- home
invasion right after dinner.
Cooper is getting his daughter
some ice cream,
bad guys break in
looking for money.
Only despite the McMansion,
Cooper's beyond broke,
but the bad guys
have his wife and kid.
So he tells them he'll rob
a bank for them.
They hold the wife and kid
as collateral,
and then they drive Cooper to
the bank in the pizza van.
To make sure he goes through
with it.
Only Cooper gets killed.
That's Alice.
Cooper couldn't make good
on the money.
They're gonna force her
to steal from her job.
You think the kid's in the van?
Possibly. I'll call Grey,
tell him what's going on
and have additional units
hold a perimeter.
Right.
No. Good.
Come to me. My name's John.
We know you're in trouble.
- We're here to help you.
- They have my daughter.
I know. Is she in the van?
No. They left her behind.
And if I don't walk out of here
in five minutes
with a quarter million
in diamonds,
they're going to kill her.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, Lucy, I need you to
help me find
a little girl being
held hostage.
The mother is here with me now.
The men that took them
are forcing her
to steal from her employer.
She was blindfolded
on the drive here,
but she said the ride
to the Diamond District
- took about 15 minutes.
- Closer to 10, I think.
Well, that's still
a big search grid.
I-I-I know we took a freeway.
I could hear it.
Uh, what direction was
the sun coming from?
I felt the sun on my face,
so, um, ahead of us.
10 eastbound. We're en route.
How long were you driving
before you got on the freeway?
Not long. Maybe a minute.
So nine minutes on the
freeway, driving the speed limit.
'Cause they couldn't risk
being pulled over.
Right. So, at 65 miles per hour,
going backwards from
Spring Street,
11:00 in the morning,
during moderate traffic.
I'd say they got on at Crenshaw.
Can you remember
any other details?
Anything will help them
find her.
Potholes -- there were two
back to back
right after the first turn.
Uh, they shook the car. The driver cursed.
When you took your first turn,
was it a right or a left?
A right. Uh -- uh, no.
My body leaned right, so left.
- It's them.
- Lucy, I need you to find
that little girl fast, alright?
We're on it.  Alright.
I need you to answer that.
Everything is going to be okay.
Just be calm.
How? They're gonna kill my baby.
I can't be calm.
Then be angry.
What?
What's taking so long?
I had to go to the bathroom
and throw up
because you terrified me.
Get it together.
If you're not back here
in three minutes,
I tell Charles to break
your daughter's neck.
They're not gonna find her
in three minutes.
What are we gonna do?
We'll get my partner to
stall them for us.
Hey, Harper, you wanna
have some fun?
There's a cop out here.
Stay inside until she's gone.
Okay.
Okay. Thanks.
Dispatch put out an alert to all units.
We've got two candidates on
the twin potholes.
Closest one is right up hereon Oakmont.
- Right there.
- Two big-ass potholes.
Mom said they took a left
onto this road
just before
they drove over them.
Which means we take
the next right.
Slow down.
This is a dead-end street.
We don't want to spook them
by rolling in.
Let's pull over
and park somewhere.
7-Adam-07, Code 6
at Oakmont and Arbor.
She could be in
any one of these houses.
Or none of them.
Let's think positive.
How do we find the right house
without spooking them?
Use what we learned about
criminal behavior.
Number one -- they're secretive.
Look, all the curtains are down
on that gray house.
The first thing you'd do if you
were holding a hostage.
Number two --
they're often messy.
Number three -- they don't
spend their money wisely.
Control, run the plate
2-David-David-Tom-4-5-6
and run out the RO.
Vehicle is registered
to Charles Lindsey Snealing.
He comes back clear and valid
with a restraining order and
a history of armed robbery.
Damn, we're good.
...careful
he doesn't draw a card.
Where's the girl?
It's okay. You're safe now.
Harper, we got her.
You have a nice day.
Show me your hands!
Hands! Show me those hands!
Right now! Out of the van!
- Open that door slow.
- Out of the van now!
Stop right here by the front.
Close the door!
Sweetheart.
Oh.
Are you okay?
They didn't hurt you?
Chen. West.
Look, I know the transition
from rookie to P2
isn't always... as satisfying as
officers think it's going to be.
No parties, no cupcakes, no
30-year-old bottles of scotch.
Dad told you, huh?
I can't believe you fell for it.
Me either, sir.
Did you become a cop for
the attaboys, Officer West?
No, sir.
How about you, Chen?
Why did you become
a police officer?
Because I wanted to do something
meaningful with my life, sir.
And are you?
Yeah. Absolutely.
That girl wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for the work
you did today.
I'm putting you both up for
the Distinguished Service Medal.
♪ They live in Wonder...
What are you doing?
Being your Man of Honor.
♪ ...beneath the peak of
a mountain ♪
♪ With a fountain made of snow ♪
Are those ...e Patrice files?
Yep.
Look, the way I see it,
I've got one job --
give you the wedding
that you want.
No more interlopers.
No more drama.
No more files and lists.
Care to do the honors?
Anyone tell you
you're kind of amazing?
All the time.♪ Floating castles in the air
Oh. I forgot this.
Oh.
You know the lithium battery
in that thing
is gonna explode, right?
Where are you and Alonzo
going for dinner?
Uh, an Italian place
on the Westside.
You don't sound
very excited about it.
N-No. I am. I just...
It's my first date
since Donovan...
Oh! I remember my first date
after the big divorce.
It was kind of a nightmare.
What? Did you talk about
your ex the whole time?
No. No. I fell asleep at
the table before she arrived.
It was the end of my first week
at the Police Academy.
When did you wake up?
Uh, after she'd eaten three
courses and left me with the bill.
Good for her.
I don't know.
Should I just cancel?
What? No. Come on. Don't --
You're putting way too much
pressure on it.
Look, it's just food
with a fellow human.
If you don't like it, you never
have to see him again.
If you do like it, I'm gonna
want all the details tomorrow.
♪ Every daughter...
Hey, what's up?
I could tell you were hiding
something about last night,
so I called your mom, and she
told me what she said to you.
And I told her that
if she didn't apologize,
she's never stepping foot in
this apartment again.
Jackson --
And this is from
the West family,
to remind you that there are
people who are proud
of what you've accomplished.
Of who you are.
Saint Michael.
Hey, it's no Distinguished
Service Medal, but --
No, it's -- it's better.
Thank you so much. Of course.
Yeah. Will you, um, help me?
I've never been good
at these things.
Let's see.
Alright.
As soon as I am done with this,
I need you to pop on your shoes,
because I am taking you
for baseball steaks.
What?!
Wait, wait, can we have sushi?
Deal. Yeah.
♪ Another one
Hey. Hey.
Wow. Nice digs.
Thanks.
Is this what Henry's office
is gonna look like?
Eh, it'll be a little smaller.
Gotta give him something
to work towards.
Right.
Listen, I want to apologize
for last night.
Don't worry about it.
Eh, hear me out.
Ben, you're my best friend,
and you're the most generous
person I know.
You helped me get on my feet
when I moved out here,
and now you're helping my son
figure out
what he's gonna do
with his life.
And you've worked really hard
to build your foundation.
I know that. And I'm sorry
I was dismissive.
Well, there's nothing
to apologize for.
Henry's your son.
You want what's best for him.
I just don't know how to
reconcile my desire
for him to have a better life
than I did
and wanting him to understand
the sacrifices I made
to get him here.
Does that make sense?
It does.
Hmm. He's a grown-up now.
He's gonna make his own choices,
even if I don't like
what those choices are.
John, I'm gonna watch out
for him, okay?
I know you will.
To college dropouts.
Actually, I went back to school
to get my degree.
Mm?
Good for you.
- Is your professor hot?
- No comment.
Oh, that's a yes.
Oh, come sit down.
We need to talk.
What are you studying?
Ethics.
Mm. Indeed. Was she ethical?
Yes.