will be taking over
the training of Officer West.
Someone broke into
your home.
So, who are you claiming
these days, D?
He did something
that really bothered me,
the way he treated
this one family -- Black family.
Hey!
[ Grunting ]
I am hereby placing you
under administrative leave.
Gun and badge.
I think I could be really good
at undercover work.
June: The op today is simple --
trade drugs for cash,
then arrest everybody
and try to get them to flip
on Aldo Salonga.
Salonga: I need to see that you
really know the science.
Are we done?When it comes to your child,
there is nothing you won't do
to protect them.
Diego![ Gunfire ]
Harper:
Her son was her humanity.
With him gone...War is coming.
[ Mid-tempo hip-hop plays ]♪ Then I'm back on the come-up
♪ Back on the -- Back on the --
Back on the come-up ♪
How's Henry?
Well, he's good.
Thanks.
Sarah and Abigail
have him set up in Arizona.
He'll do his rehab there.
I'll join them
once I graduate to P2.
Ten more days.
Harper says your focus
is on becoming a T.O.
I think that's where I can do
the most good.
Any advice?
Think how hard it is
doing this job.
Now think about doing it while
babysitting an armed toddler.
Got it.
But seriously,
if you have any more wisdom
on how to be better prepared,
I would appreciate it.
Sure.
[ Gunfire ]Automatic weapons.
A lot of them.7-Adam-19, shots fired.
Multiple shooters.[ Siren wailing ]
Crestview Cemetery.
Requesting airship and backup.
And mobilize SWAT.
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
[ Gunfire ]
Where arethese guys?
♪♪
Come on!
Let's go!
[ Gunfire ]
♪♪
Up here.
Police!
Don't move!
♪♪
Got him?
Yeah.
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
How did he make it this far
in this condition?
Heat of battle.
7-Adam-19, one in custody,
not conscious, not breathing.
Let's go find out
where he was coming from.
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Sirens wailing in distance ]
♪♪
[ Sirens approaching ]
--Captions by VITAC--
Look, I don't want to
alarm you,
but our guest list
is out of control.
What are you talking about?
I mean we're almost
at maximum capacity
and half your cop friends
haven't even responded yet.
Yeah, cops don't really respect
RSVPs, especially for --
Especially for what?
First marriages.
Uh-huh.
So they just think
that I'm your starter husband?
Yes, but if it makes you feel
any better,
I'm 72% certain
you're my forever husband.
Only 72%?
It goes up to 81%
if you make me breakfast.
[ Cellphone buzzing ]
Lopez.[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Yes, sir.
Text me the address.
[ Cellphone beeps ]What?
The war just started.
[ Sirens wailing,
helicopter blades whirring ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
♪♪
Hey. Looks like Cesar Madrigal's
been using the cemetery
as a supply depot.
Guys were loading a car
with narcotics, got ambushed.
La Fiera?
Definitely her
Malos Dorados.
All sporting
the yellow sneakers.
Looks like she sent
five shooters,
including the one
that was shooting at us.
They came in on foot
and opened up on Cesar's guys.
Unfortunately for yellow kicks,
they miscounted the enemy.
Got caught in a crossfire of two
of Cesar's crew they didn't see.
In less than a minute,
there's a baker's dozen of DBs.
You up to speed?Getting there.
Where's Sergeant Caradine?Sweating the cemetery owner.
She's clearly
on Cesar's payroll.
This is only gonna get worse.
La Fiera's out for blood.
And Cesar is just strong enough
to put up a decent fight.
You don't think
he can win?
No.
La Fiera has a lot more
resources than Cesar
and, honestly,
a level of brutality
that his crew's never seen
before.We can't just stand by
and watch them
shoot up the city.
I mean,
we got lucky this time.
No innocents were hurt,
but that can't last.
Word is Sandra flew back from
Guatemala after burying Diego.
She's bunkered down
at Hotel Mathilde.
Rented out
the whole ninth floor.
Good to be queen.What about Cesar?
According to Narcotics,
he's in the wind.
I know someone
who might have some insight
on where to find him --
Mack Daniels.
He was working for Cesar's dad
after getting fired by LAPD.
Will he talk to you?Got him into rehab.
I can give him a call,
see if he has any idea
where Cesar might hole up.
Do it.
And you -- go talk to La Fiera.
Impress on her
the need to stand down.
Cesar killed her son.
I don't think
there's anything I can say
that'll get through to her.
But I'll try.
Thank you.
Alright.
And Ithought my day was gonna
be chasing down cop RSVPs
for the wedding.
It'll only take
like two minutes
for La Fiera to tell you
to go screw yourself, so...
We should split the RSVP list.
It'll get done faster.
Yeah.
I'm not doing that.
Fine.
E-mail me the list.
Thank you.
Should've read
the fine print
on that whole man-of-honor
thing.
No kidding.
I'm just saying,
the cop who tackles the perp
should be the one
to do the paperwork.
What? No.
The cop who didn't risk life
and limb
running down a methed-out
sous-chef should have to do it.
Otherwise, you are
disincentivising
hands-on policing.Ooh.
You could just let me go.
Then there's no paperwork.[ Knock on glass ]
Oh. What's that, Sarge?
You need me?
Sorry, partner.
Paperwork's all yours.
Fine, but you are
tackling the next three guys.
Uh-huh.Let's go.
You can teach me
what the hell sous vide is.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Yes, sir?
You heard about the mass
casualty event this morning?
Uh, yes, sir, but we knew
a gang war was coming, right?
Yes.
And it's far from over.
Which, Detective Harper tells
me, presents an opportunity.
In times of chaos like this,
it's not just
the criminal pecking order
that gets shaken up.
Undercover operations
get upended.
Long-term UCs and CIs
are neutered
when their bosses get killed
or caught.
But the upheaval
also gives us a chance
to put new UCs
in the field.
I got a call from June Zhang
this morning.
Aldo Salonga
is out of prison,
and he is desperate
to cook product to move.
So he called her cover identity
and asked about you.
You want me to go back in
as the chemist?
June is already up
on another operation,
so she told Salonga
that you might be available.
[ Exhales sharply ]
I'm ready.
Not so fast.
This wouldn't be a sting
operation like the last time.
This would probably be
a long-term placement.
Which means you'll be
on your own,
without a surveillance team
or access to immediate backup.
It normally takes months
to properly train an officer
to go deep undercover
like this.
Hundreds of hours of classroom
and field training.
I told Detective Harper
she has today
to evaluate your readiness.
If she doesn't sign off
with confidence
that you can handle it,
I will not approve
the assignment.
Yes, sir.
I won't let you down.
It's not about letting me down,
Officer Chen.
There is no failure
for finding yourself unprepared
for a job
you did not prepare for.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
Go get changed.
I'm throwing you
in the deep end.
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
[ Door closes ]
♪ Come slay
♪ We do what we say
♪ Run daily, easy money
♪ 'Cause we slay
♪ Shout out what we a prey
♪ So we slay
[ Siren chirps ]
♪ ...slay
♪ Them a run from me
♪ 'Cause me slay
♪ Bad gyal come inna ya day
♪ Make way
♪ ...dead...ago pay
♪ Come slay
♪♪
Nice hideout.
It's not a hideout.
It's a base of operations.
I know you.
You were at my dad's hospital.
That's right. The day
you tried to kill La Fiera.
Allegedly.Nothing alleged about
what happened this morning.
You lost a lot of men.Tim: And product.
I don't know
what you're talking about.Sure, you do.
You started a war
you can't win.
Says who?
Everybody.
You're a minor league ball club
next to Fiera.
Even if you couldcompete,
you killed her son.
She's out for blood.
Your blood.
Tim:
But she's also a businesswoman.
Wars are expensive.
Unpredictable.
Word is she made a deal
with your father to take over.
Now, if you offered
to honor that deal,
she might let you walk away
with your life.
What belonged to the father
will be inherited by the son.
That's in the Bible.
So this bitch can run around
all she wants
claiming she made
some sort of deal with my dad,
but no one's gonna believe it.You better hope not.
If you lose the support
of your father's lieutenants,
they'll jump ship and you'll be
all by your lonesome.
Hey, you guys wouldn't happen to
know where La Fiera is, right?
In case I want to pay
my respects.
Sorry. You'll have to figure
that one out on your own.
Yeah.
I'm working on it.
So, what now?
Hope Lopez is doing better
with La Fiera.
[ Bell chimes ]
Police.
I'm here to talk
to Sandra de la Cruz.
Detective Lopez.
We haven't met yet.
No, but you match
the description
of the man who threatened
my fiancé.
That doesn't sound like me.
I get along with everyone.
And yet I can tell you're not
gonna get along with me.
My heart breaks.
Is Sandra inside?
Do you have a warrant?Not yet.
Is that a problem?
Not yet.
[ Door opens ]
Hermana.
Thank you for the flowers
you sent for Diego's funeral.
They were lovely.
We held the service
at Casa de Dios.
Thousand attended
and walked with me
as we buried him
in Chichicastenango --
in a bright yellow tomb
to honor the sunshine
he brought into my life.
You should've stayed
in Guatemala.
No.
I have unfinished business
here.
Listen to me.
Up until this point,
you've managed to fly
mostly under the radar,
away from the eyes
of federal law enforcement.
But you announced yourself
in a big way this morning.
A dozen dead bodies elevates you
to the top of the watchlist.
I have nothing left to lose,
hermana.
But there is a very simple thing
you can do to end this war
before it goes any farther.
And what's that?
We both know
you were wiretapping
a dying man's
hospital room.
You heard him promise
to give me control,
but he slipped into a coma
before he could tell his people.
You want this war to end?
Give me that recording.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
You were offered
aplus-one.
You -- You crossed that out
and wrote "plus four."
N-- Emotional support animals
are not wedding guests.
Hey, Mildred.
John Nolan here.
Yeah. Uh, so, listen.
Here's the thing.
What Tim is too embarrassed
to say is that he screwed up.
He told Angela
the wrong venue cap.
Now they have too many guests.
We just need a few people t--
You will?
Thank you so much.
I know the couple will be
so pleased.
Alright.
Bye.
Are you proud
of yourself?
Throwing a fellow officer
under the bus?
I think Detective Lopez
would approve of my methods.
Mm.
[ Engine revving ]
Control, 7-Adam-19.
Run a plate --
3-John-Robert-Queen-1-5-8.
Send details to our box.
[ Computer beeps ]
His name is
Miguel Offer.
He's got quite a list
of priors.
We're getting
a very good picture
of Cesar's operation here.
Yeah. Too bad none of this intel
will be relevant
once La Fiera wipes him off
the map.
[ "Bridal Chorus" ringtone
plays ]
Hey.
How'd it go?
The good news is I can stop
the war.
How?
By giving La Fiera
the wire-tap recording
of her and Madrigal
making their deal.
Well, let's do it.
We'll stop the body count.
Not all of it.
She's gonna kill Cesar
no matter what.
Better one homicide
than a second massacre.
Can we do that, though,
ethically speaking --
pick the winner
of a drug war?
What's our
number-one mandate?
Protect the lives
of the people of Los Angeles.
So we end the violence today.
We go after La Fiera tomorrow.
Exactly.
I'll run it up the flagpole.
Any luck finding Cesar?
He's up in Acton,
holed up in a cabin.
We're documenting the comings
and goings of his crew,
keeping an eye out
for trouble.I got to go.
Looks like the feds have joined
the party.
I'm headed
to my lady doctor next.
Want to come to that, too?
Special Agent Taggart, DEA.
We need to talk.
Fiona: Well, thanks for agreeing
to talk to me.
Of course. Yeah.
Nolan said
you were interviewing cops
for your book
on police reform.
I'd talk about that
all day.
John mentioned that you come
from a police family.
Yep.
Dad, my uncles, two aunts,
half a dozen cousins.
Yeah, the Wests are blue
through and through.
And Black.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
Um, you want to know
if being Black
affects my stance
on police reform.
Does it?
Hell yeah.
I've seen firsthand
how the right kind of policing
can serve our communities
and make people's lives better.
So when an officer abuses their
power in those communities,
I take it personally.That's interesting.
Given your family,
I might've expected
a blue-wall-of-silence answer
from you.
There definitely was a time when
I had more faith in the system,
but recently I've seen firsthand
how broken it is.
How so?
It needs to be a lot easier
to fire bad cops.
[ Down-tempo music plays ]I almost died trying.
♪♪
[ Car door opens, closes ]
Why the cloak and dagger?
You were in La Fiera's hotel
suite for 17 minutes, 9 seconds.
What'd you talk about?
Makeup tips,
cutest members of BTS --
Be careful, Detective.
You just got
to the big kids' table.
I can easily have you
put back in uniform.
No, you can't.
You know what else
you apparently can't do?
Wiretap La Fiera.
Because if you could,
you wouldn't be asking me
what we talked about
for 17 minutes and 9 seconds.
Now, why am I here?
I'm running a multiagency
task force -- DEA, FBI, BNE.
Why not LAPD?
We're on the front lines
of this.
You should be
bringing us in.
I have over 25 years' experience
dealing with cartels.
I say when it's time
to bring in local PD.
So, here's the carrot.
You tell me
what you know,
and I'll consider inviting you
into the inner sanctum.
We have a recording
of Tomás Madrigal
giving La Fiera control
of his drug operation.
I want a copy of that tape.That's funny. So does she.
To cement her control, which is
why you can't give it to her.
We need time to analyze that,
go over the angles.
Do you even speak Spanish?
What does that have to do
with anything?
Veinticino años de experiencia
con los carteles.
¿Hablas el idioma?
¿Conoces la cultura?
Vez como la política
de los Estados Unidos
ha creado mas caos y crimen
en América Latina?
No wonder we're losing.
Look, I'll take your request
under advisement,
but it's LAPD's recording.
We'll decide
what we do with it.
Now, you see,
you played that all wrong,
because unlike you, your boss
knows that the best path
to putting La Fiera behind bars
is through a federal court.
So I'm just gonna go
over your head,
take that tape, and leave you
watching from the sidelines.
[ Engine starts ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
So, what's my first test?
Buying drugs
without getting ID'd or...
Are you going undercover
as a tweaker?
No.
So that wouldn't be
a very useful test.
I can't cram 100 hours' worth
of training into one shift,
so I have to get
to the heart
of what you need to know
in order to survive.
When you are a UC,
you have to be on triple duty.
So what does that mean?
It means I need to keep three
things in my head at all times.
Yes.
What are they?
First I always have to be aware
of the law
and proper procedure.
There are certain actions
I can take as a UC --
I can be the lookout
for a burglary.
I can drive
the getaway car --
and a lot of actions
that I can't take.
I can't get high.
I can't assault
or victimize someone.
Second?I always have to be
my character,
spend every moment channeling
Nova Lin and not Lucy Chen.
Third?
Um...
Oh, shoot.
You have to not get caught
or killed.
Right.
If you really were
a drug cook,
the only thing
that you would be worried about
is whether you are getting paid
or popped
at the end of your cook.
But as a UC, you have to have
three complicated streams
of consciousness going through
your mind at all times.
How much time have you spent
on your backstory?
I've filled
four journals.
What?
It's -- It's just
gonna be interesting
to see what you thought
was important about Nova
and what was not.
Anyway, I'mma step out.
I'm gonna give you five minutes
to get into character,
and then we are going
to a party.
[ Car door closes ]
Sgt. Grey:
Officer West,
we just received
an anonymous tip
on one of La Fiera's
strongholds.
Units from Hollywood Division
are on their way.
Meet them there
and keep me in the loop.
Yes, sir.
You think Cesar Madrigal
called it in
so we'd do his dirty work
for him?
I do, which makes him smarter
than I thought.
Yes, sir.
Still, we'd rather arrest
these guys quietly
than have a repeat
of this morning's bloodshed.
I'm on my way.
[ Indistinct talking on radio ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪♪
Hey.
Officer West, Mid-Wilshire.
Came by to see
if you guys needed a hand.
Thanks. We're just bringing
the rest of the guys out now.
Found enough long guns
to arm a small battalion.
Well, well, well.
Look who it is.
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
You were fired.Was.
Turns out being saddled
with an incompetent rookie
isn't grounds
for termination,
even if that rookie's daddy
does run IA.
This is the rookie
you were telling us about?
Yep.
Officer Jackson West.
The kid who stabbed me
in the back.
Let's go.
[ Indistinct talking on radio ]
♪♪
[ Mid-tempo hip-hop playing ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Sniper.
Where you been?
I had some trouble.
Nothing I couldn't handle.
This -- This is Nova.
I don't think
you two have met yet.
I'd remember.
Likewise.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Careful.
You're about to burn
that burger.
You know your way
around a grill?
I usually cook in
a more controlled environment.
That so?
What do you cook?
All sorts.
Mainly catering.
Big orders.
Nova came through for me
recently.
Uh, I'mma go grab a beer.
You two talk.
Where'd you learn to cook?
Here and there.
But every top chef
needs formal training.
Sure,
but I only just met you.
You don't see me asking
where you did time.
What makes you think
I did time?
Nature of the beast.
Well, if you're friends
with Sniper,
that means
you're in the business,
and if you're
in the business,
eventually you catch
a charge.
♪♪
I might be able to use someone
with your background.
Yeah, I'll need to do
my due diligence first.
I only work
with professionals.
Well, by all means,
ask around.
Tamara: Why do you have to be
so complicated?
I'm not being ridiculous.
Something wrong?No.
Man: Just get in the car.
Get in the freakin' car.
Get your hands
off of me!
Do you know them?
No.
Man: Let's go.
I just don't like seeing a girl
being mistreated.
I can fix that.
Watch the grill.[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Hey!
Yeah, you! Boy!
Come here!
What's the problem?This kid put his hands
on the girl.
Nova didn't like it.
Yeah. She's, uh,
she's sensitive that way.
Me, I think a girl could use
a little more focus.
What?
Go on.
Tell him.
You should treat that girl
better.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Kiss my ass.
What did you say to me?
Nothin'. Sorry.
Won't happen again.
See that it doesn't.
Now piss off.
♪♪
Nice gun.
It's all right.
It's a cop gun.
♪♪
Yeah.
They use 'em 'cause they're
reliable when things get real.
It's good enough for me.
♪♪
Well, let's eat.
Let's eat!
Took you long enough.
L.A. traffic.
What do you want from me?
Got one unmarked car,
two sets of civvies
fresh from lost-and-found.
You were supposed to
pull clothes from our lockers.
We texted you
our combinations.
Oh, I didn't do that.
Why do we rely on you
for anything?
I've been wondering that
myself.
Oh, um, Smitty, one more thing.
Um, about Lopez's wedding.
Yeah.
She got my RSVP, right?Yeah, that's just it.
You can't send an RSVP card to a
wedding you weren't invited to.
Oh, of course I'm invited.
I'm the deejay.
[ Engine starts ]
He's not the deejay.
You're not the deejay!
It's not right.
Those bodies
are on ourmurder board.
The DEA can't just force us
to follow their command.
That tape could end
the bloodshed right now.
Angela, stop. The Chief already
sent the recording to the feds.
You have to let this go.
He's back.
Who?Doug Stanton.
He was dispoed on our pinch.
He's back on the job.
He's in the Hollywood Division.Damn it.
I'm so sorry.
Looks like Stanton appealed
his termination and won.
What, and --
and no one cared to tell me?
The brass is under
no obligation
to notify you or me
of their rulings.
After everything he did,
not a single repercussion?!
That's not entirely true.
He lost his seniority
and got demoted to P2,
where he'll be
for the rest of his career.
He'll never be
a training officer again.
But he still wears
the badge.
The Police Commissioner
and the Board of Rights
ended up seeing things
his way.
Because they were
more interested
in avoiding
a wrongful-termination suit
than punishing
a corrupt cop.
Look, Sarge.
This man left me there
to die.
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
This isn't over.
I'm gonna bring it up
at the Sergeants Staff meeting.
I am not done fighting
for you.
Yeah. Don't bother.
We both know
it won't do any good.
Stanton won.
Thank you very much.
And now we have cut the list
by 27 guests.
That's not bad.
You told them
I was so guilt-ridden
I've been crying in bed
all day.
It really helped paint
the picture.
You do remember I hold your fate
in my hands?
Duly noted.[ Vehicles approaching ]
Control, 7-Adam-19,
be advised.
Cesar is on the move
with his crew.
Requesting airship
to aid in our surveillance.
[ Vehicles passing ]
I did good, right?Harper: You did great.
I knew it was a setup.No, you didn't.No, you didn't.
Okay.
I couldn't know for sure, but --
You should be in school.
Relax.
Nyla wrote me a note.
See you tonight?Yeah.
Uh, hey,
who was that boy?
Do youknow?
They're not dating, right?
Because I did notlike
that kid.
Never mind.
So, what's next?
You never know what comes next
when you're undercover,
so why would I
tell you now?
[ Seat belt clicks,
engine starts ]
[ Muffled heartbeat ]
[ High-pitched ringing ]
[ Fist thudding ]
[ Voices echoing ]
[ Laughter ]
[ Ringing continues ]
Get your ass off my desk.
Are you not
housebroken yet?
We decided that Sandra de la
Cruz can have the recording.
You could have called
to tell me that.
So why are you here?
We installed malware
on this drive.
She plugs this into
her computer,
snakes its way
throughout her entire network --
tablets, phones, routers.
In one fell swoop, we get
evidence on the whole operation.
But you need someone she trusts
to deliver it to her.
Is this really the best idea
you've got --
a glorified spam link?
Will you give it to her
or not?
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Car doors closing ]
Tim:
A booty call?
He's in the middle of a gang war
and that's his priority?
That's how his father knew
he would just run the business
into the ground.
That's why he sold out
to La Fiera.
Let's find out
who this girlfriend is.
I'll run her plates.
Control?
[ Knocks on glass ]
Officer West.
Professor Ryan.
What can I do for you?
Well, Jackson called
to tell me
about Officer Stanton
being reinstated.
He asked for my help.
What kind of help?Exposure.
A Black rookie officer
being abused and left to die
by his white T.O.,
and the guy keeps his job?
If it were up to me,
we'd be on CNN right now.
So what's stopping you?
I felt like I owed you
a heads-up, sir.
Son, you don't
owe me anything.
I understand your anger,
just like I understand
your instinct to go public.
But I believe you'll be making
a mistake.
Jackson: The Department has
left me with no other option.
If my life is worth less
to the Department
than the cost of a lawsuit,
why should I protect them?
You shouldn't.
You should protect yourself.
And I'm telling you, going
on TV, putting Doug on blast
will just cause the Department
to circle their wagons.
They will shield Doug
to defend their own reputation.
You'll be inadvertently
making a martyr out of him
and isolating yourself.
And that right there
is why things will never change.
Until cops speak up
about what is really happening,
change will never come.I hear you.
But at what cost?
This young man's career?
Sarge,
I have to do something.
Jackson is willing to step up
and risk losing everything.
But you insist
it won't work.
So tell me.
What will?
You've been a cop
for a long time.
Tell me what we can do
to make the department turn
against Doug Stanton.
Or we'll be
on the 6:00 news.
Lucy Chen,
meet Sergeant Mark Murray --
aka Shea.
Uh...
[ Chuckles ]
It's a pleasure, sir.
And that burger
was truly delicious.
Thank you. You made
a nice save with the kid.
Besides being
a grill master,
Shea is a court-certified expert
in clandestine narcotics labs.
Manufacturing dope
is part of my official duties.
Now, Detective Harper
informs me
that you're gonna be posing
as a chemist.
Yes, sir.Okay. Come on.
So, Dilaudid,
meth, heroin, fentanyl.
Chemically speaking,
what's the difference
between nasal decongestant
and meth?
One oxygen molecule.
Just one.
And to add that molecule?
You have to break
the pseudoephedrine down,
then add methyl alcohol
and evaporate it
so that the oxygen can --
Boom! Half your chemicals
just burned up.
Improvise. Where do you get
the methyl alcohol?
Um...
Where?
Windshield washer fluid,
then fertilizer
with anhydrous ammonia.
Sodium metal
or lithium metal.
You can get that
from batteries.
Yes, you can.
Good.
We're gonna spend
the afternoon cooking.
Knowing what to do
is one thing.
when everything goes wrong --
That's what's gonna
keep you alive.
Alright.
Show me what you got.
[ Knock on door ]
Where's your doorman?
Running an errand.
[ Door closes ]
Cafecito?
You must have some.
I have it shipped in daily
from my country.
We have
the best in the world.
Guatemalan style.
Very sweet.
But don't worry --
the beans
are called Huehuetenango.
Low on acid.
Easy on the tummy.
Your baby won't mind.
Now, you have something
for me, no?
There's a condition.
The war stops today.
You declare
an immediate cease-fire
and a guaranteed protection
of Cesar Madrigal.
You ask a lot
of grieving mother.
You chose
this line of work.
This is the price
of doing business.
Say it.
No harm will come
to Cesar Madrigal.
You have my word.
[ Items shuffling ]
[ Sighs ]
The Federalesput a Trojan horse
in here, yes?
Brand new
and air-gapped
so it can't connect
to your network.
Of course.
You watch us,
hermana.
We watch you.
Tell the DEA
better luck next time.
[ Scoffs ]
Gueroslike that always
underestimate chicaslike us.
♪♪
[ Music playing faintly
over speakers ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Engine starts ]
[ Vehicle door closes ]
Control, be advised,
Cesar is on the move.
Have the nearest unit
pick up the tail.
We're gonna question
the girlfriend.
Tomás: My son --
He's foolhardy and rash,
but he's still
my blood.
Sandra:
Cesar will be provided for.
You have my word.
Then you,
Ms. De la Cruz --
I want you
to continue my legacy.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
And just like that,
there is peace in Los Angeles.
Felicidades,Angela.
Cafecitois good,
verdad?
Quesadilla de Arroz?
My abuelita's
is better.
You want the recipe?
No.
Stop acting like
we're friends.
For the moment,
our interests align,
and it'll stay
that way
if the violence stops
and Cesar stays alive.
I told you.
Killing Cesar
would be unsatisfying.
He must suffer
like I suffer.
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Can I use
your bathroom?
This baby's bouncing
on my bladder like a trampoline.
♪♪
Tim:
Police, open up.
We have some questions for you
regarding Cesar Madrigal.
Don't know him.That's weird.
We just saw him leave.
May we come in?
I'm calling my lawyer.
Good.
You really should.
We're in the process
of getting a warrant.
[ Baby crying ]
Look,
it's criminal 101
for suspects
to hide illicit items
in their
girlfriends' homes.
Cash, contraband,
you name it.
That gets you arrested.
That gets you put in prison.
That gets your baby
put in foster care.
That is not the outcome
we're hoping for.
So,
let's sit down,
have a talk about this
taking a different path.
[ Cellphone plays
"Bridal Chorus" ringtone ]Hey.
Lopez: I think Cesar
might have a kid somewhere,
and La Fiera's
going to kill him.
Yeah,
a little ahead of you, there.
Do me a favor --
call in back-up. Code 3 high.
5917 Sycamore Court.
Five shooters on site.
You have a cast-iron tub
in your home?Yes, upstairs.
Get your baby.
Get inside. Lock the door.
Hide in the tub.
It's bulletproof.
♪♪
Call it off.
Murdering Cesar's baby
is twisted, even for you.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
But if Cesar's child
were to die,
well, that's just karma
balancing the scales.
It doesn't bother you?
Making another mother
grieve the way you do?
Like I said --
I cannot stop
what I did not order.
Nolan:
What's the plan?
They came here expecting to find
a helpless woman and child.
Let's show them how steep
the price of admission is.
Galeno, right?
You work with La Fiera.
I met you at the hospital
last week, remember?
You were
dressed different.
Yeah,
I was in uniform.
Easy, gentlemen.
If I see a weapon,
we're gonna have
a real problem.
Look, I appreciate the position
that you're in, officers,
but you need
to try to understand mine.
We have
a job to do,
and the price of failure
is death.
So there is nothing
for us to lose.
You, on the other hand --
you have options.
I think
he wants us to walk away.
How much?How much do you want?
Oh, I want to be
Batman rich.
What's that take?
Like, a billion?
Way more.
Yeah, like 10 or 20.
Since I don't think you have
that kind of cash on you,
it looks like
we're sticking around
and I don't get to be Batman.
Then I guess
we're done talking.
[ Gunshot ]Rgh!
[ Rock music plays ]
[ Doors slam, guns cocking ]Ow.
[ Bullet casing clinks ]
[ Baby crying ]
♪♪
Fall back upstairs?
Negative. They'll just
light the house on fire
and shoot us
when we come out.
Our only option
is to take the fight to them.
Well, it looks like
we're done talking, too.
♪♪
♪ Don't tell me
how to do my job ♪
♪ You carry on like
a son of a bitch ♪
Whoa!
♪ They got a name
for people like you ♪
♪ Ahhh
♪ But I didn't take the time
to write it down, though ♪
[ Gunshots ]
♪♪
♪ You have a lot of fun
playing grab-ass with the boys ♪
[ Baby crying ]♪ Which one's going to give you
a ride home? ♪
♪ Which one's gonna
walk you to the door? ♪
[ Gunfire ]
[ Gunshot ]
Ow!
Don't even breathe.
♪ Maybe the sun waits for you
to be shown what to do ♪
[ Baby wailing ]
♪♪
[ Grunts ]
This is gonna hurt.
But I owe you for shooting me.
You know what they taught
us at the Academy about
fighting a guy with a knife?
No, tell me.Says if you hold it
the wrong way,
you got a chance.
If they hold it
the right way, run.
♪♪
How am I holding it?
The right way.
You gonna run?
No.
♪♪
[ Spits ]
[ Knife slices ]
That the best you got?
♪♪
[ Baby crying ]
[ Handcuffs click ]
First knife fight?Yeah.
He hold it
the right way?
Yeah.
♪♪
Control, 7-Adam-19.
Five in custody.
Code 4.
[ Knock on window ]Stella?
Wade.
Come on in.
Appreciate you
taking the time.
This is
Officer Jackson West.
Pleasure to meet you,
ma'am.
You, too.
But, listen,
I read the report
on your attack
in Doug Stanton's file.
It's unconscionable,
but your Sergeant here
knows as well as I do
that when an officer
is reinstated by the Department,
there's literally nothing
their Watch Commander
can do about it.
With all due respect,
ma'am,
that's, uh --
that's not true.
Stella,
we go way back.
You know firsthand
how hard it is
to make meaningful changes
inside the Department.
So all I'm asking is
that you hear Officer West out.
Alright.
You have my attention.
As you all know,
I have instituted
new training protocols
with the goal of moving us
towards a more modern approach
on policing.
We're gonna watch and discuss
a new training video
about ensuring
your partner's safety.
Officer: Control, 7-Adam-7.
A to B. I'm out with three.
Doug: Copy,
right behind you.
Jackson:
Stop where you are.
Look, you guys
do not want to do this.
Look --
Stop where you are![ Gunshot]
Hey! Oh!
[ Groaning]
[ All murmuring ]
♪♪
Officer: Whoa!Officer #2:
Is that Stanton?
Officer #3:
That's Stanton.
Lucy: He's still breathing.
He's still breathing.
Tim: 7-Adam-19, we need
an ambulance to our location.
Officer down,
24-year-old male,
full body trauma.
What happened, partner?
Who did this to you?
[ Murmuring continues ]
♪♪
This is not
what it looks like.Yes, it is.
This is the truth
about Doug Stanton --
what kind of cop
he is.
One who won't have your back
when you need it the most.
Come on, guys.
Come on,
you -- you know me.
They do now.
♪♪
Hey, Lucy.
So, I just got off the phone
with Shea.
You rocked the cook.
He said
you're more knowledgeable
than half the guys
that work for him.
What? Wow.
So, what does that mean?
Well,
I spoke to Grey,
and I told him you are
as ready as you could be,
considering
the circumstances,
and he approved
the operation.
[ Chuckles ]
There is no telling
how long you will be
off the grid,
so you need to get your
personal life squared away.
Yes, ma'am.
This assignment,
it will be hard.
It will be lonely,
and at times,
it might even be boring.
But you can never
let your guard down.
If you do,
you are dead.
You got it?Yes.
Alright.
Go home.
The real work
starts tomorrow.
♪ Come with us, don't stay
♪ In the midst of your mind...
Paperwork on this one
is gonna take forever.
I was gonna order
some food.
How about Thai?
You're a good cop,
Nolan.
I'll grant you that.
Thank you,
sir.
I appreciate it.
Is that a yes to Thai?
♪♪
How serious are you about
becoming a training officer?
Very serious.
Training our next generation
is the most sacred position
an officer can hold.
It's not
a consolation prize
or a rung on the ladder
to your next promotion.
I know that.
No,
I don't think you do.
Because last month,
you wanted to be a detective.
Then you found out
that couldn't happen,
and now
you want to be a T.O.
Sir, I don't want
to be a T.O.
I'm going tobe a T.O.
If you want to doubt
my convictions,
that's fine.
You don't want to help me?
That's fine, too.
But you're not
going to deter me.
♪ ...or feel
♪♪
Let's get Mexican.
Love it.
♪ ...beyond the pale
Hey.
I left messages
for you.
Lying in wait for
the pregnant woman to walk out?
Way to be creepy.
How'd it go?
La Fiera saw
right through your play.
Made an audio recording
and ditched the thumb drive.
That's my fault.
Shouldn't have
sent in a novice.
♪♪
When you look at her,
all you see
is a woman
from a third-world country
with
a fourth-grade education.
But she's smarter
than you.
Oh, really?
But not you?
No,
she probably is.
But I'm humble enough
to know that,
which is why I'm going to be
the one who takes her down.
♪♪
[ Tires screech ]
[ Grunts ][ Screams ]
No! No!
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Muffled shouting ]
No!
[ Van door closes ]
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
[ Panting ]
You screwed up
betraying Mr. Salonga like that.
[ Scoffs ] I don't know
what you're talking about.
We grabbed up
your friend Coco.
It took
a little cutting,
but she told us
that she was a cop --
that you were all cops.
You're lying.
Coco would never say that,
because it's not true.
W-Wait, wait.
[ Muffled ]
No! No! No!
[ Muffled shouting ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Man: Look,
I'm not asking you.
I already know.
My question is,
what else do the cops know
about Mr. Salonga's operation?
We have certain
upcoming transactions.
I need to know
if they've been compromised.
I have no idea.
[ Lighter clicking,
muffled moaning ]
Last chance.
[ Moaning ]
Listen to me.
Whatever Coco said to you,
she's lying.
That's what people do
when they're being tortured.
She would have admitted
to being an elephant
if you
had asked her.
You set that fire,
and Salonga
is as good as dead.
Word on the street is
he's in debt
to some really bad people,
and I am the only one
who can get him out of it
by cooking him up
a fortune.
But I am not gonna do that
if you hurt her.
So pull your head
out of your ass and let us go.
[ Muffled groaning ]
[ Lighter clicks ]
[ Sniffs ]
She's pretty good.
Of course she is.
[ Clears throat ]
I taught her
everything she knows.
Pass me a towel?
Wow!
You're a full-service asshat!
You'll thank me
for it later.
And you!
You abducted me
when you know
what I have been through!
That is exactly
why I did it.
[ Scoffs, groans ]And if you're looking
for an apology,
you're not
gonna get it.
I needed to see
how you would react.
And honestly, youneeded to see
That was
your last test.
Really?
'Cause that's what you said
after the lastlast test.
Which is why you didn't
see this one coming.
[ Exhales sharply ]Look at me.
[ Sniffles ]
This is your final chance
to back out.
Do you still want this
after what you just experienced?
[ Scoffs ]
♪♪
Yeah.
[ Scoffs ]
Yeah, I do.
♪♪