- [SIREN CHIRPS]
- NOLAN: Control, 7-Adam-15.
Show us on a vehicle stop,
Sherman Grove and Wyngate.
Clear for plate.
- DISPATCH: Go ahead.
- 2 Frank Adam Nora 3-2-1
- MAN: Let's book it!
- HARPER: They're bailing.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Control, we got multiple runners.
East and Westbound.
Need Code 3 units and an airship.
[SEATBELTS CLICK]
[CAR DOORS OPEN, CLOSE]
MAN: Move! Get out of here!
Driver's heading East. Nolan, with me.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[TRUNK POPS]
[LID CREAKS]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[PLAYS THEME SONG ON UKULELE]
♪ I'm gonna win for you ♪
♪ Like I know you want me to do ♪
[TATTOO NEEDLE BUZZES]
So, um... How is she?
She made me run out to buy
her concealer at 6:00 a.m.
To cover the tattoo.
She does it every morning.
Well, wouldn't you?
I mean, can you imagine
walking around with
a serial killer's brand on you?
When can she have it removed?
Four weeks, two days, nine hours.
Hey, for your first day back,
I thought you could use
some sugar and some carbs.
Oh, that's sweet.
- Literally.
- [CHUCKLES]
So, are you... ready?
Absolutely, um.
Doctor signed off on physical,
department shrink signed off on mental.
- Oh, uh, but could you do me a favor?
- Anything.
I just don't want everybody
clapping during roll call, so...
Well, that's tradition, though.
You know, I mean, you survive
something like that,
they're gonna want to
show you some respect.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Thank you.
Hey, did Henry and Abigail
make it in last night?
Yes. Boy, they have
a whole long list of...
Wedding venues they need to investigate.
Oh, fun.
- No?
- No, yes.
No, yeah... I mean, yes.
It's just...
It's a lot to take in, you know?
It seems like only yesterday
Henry was a toddler on my shoulders,
just holding on to my hair,
his little feet in my hands.
Aww, that's sweet.
He was a bit of a puker.
So hard to get that
smell out of your hair.
Ew.
♪ ♪
Hey, so, what's your plan?
- For what?
- Officer Chen.
I'm sure you've got
some Alpha strategy,
to get her "back on the horse."
- So, what is it?
- Your standard input overload.
Force her to push through
dynamic engagements.
Hone in her fight-or-flight response.
So basically get her into
as many fights as possible.
I'm gonna remind her that
she's a cop, not a victim.
[SCOFFS] She knows she's not a victim.
Look, Chen doesn't need to fight,
she needs to make peace with
the voice inside of her head
telling her she's never
gonna be safe again.
Okay, I've been training rookies
a lot longer than you.
- I know what she needs.
- That's ego talking.
[SIGHS]
What happened to Chen,
is every woman's worst fear.
- I'm aware of that.
- But you have never lived that fear.
It's clear that you have
her best interests at heart.
I'm just asking you to consider,
whether she might
be better served by...
Someone who has been through
what she has been through.
And that someone's you.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
I'll tell Grey to make the switch.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Hey!
What are you guys doing here?
Oh, the wedding venue
we were gonna look at,
got shut down by the health department.
Oh! I guess you're crossing
that one off your list.
Are you kidding?
It'll be super cheap now...
- Which is our price point.
- [LAUGHS]
Well, I am just starting my shift,
so I-I really can't hang out with you.
Actually, I was hoping
I could hang out with you.
I've done a lot of self-reflection,
since I dropped out of school,
and meeting you, seeing how
you reinvented your life,
has been really inspiring.
Wow, Abigail. Thank you.
That's a very nice thing to say.
It's made me want to become a cop.
So I was hoping I could
do a ride-along today.
Ha!
You almost had me.
This is another, "I'm pregnant..."
"Psych, I'm not pregnant" bit.
Yeah, I'm not falling for it.
No, no, she's... She's serious, Dad.
- Totally.
- I'm... Oh, okay, sorry.
Uh... Oh.
Well, given your history, Abigail,
with the arson, I don't know
that that's possible.
She was 17 when that happened.
And... And I was never convicted.
- Right.
- The DA cut me a deal.
I realize it won't be easy,
but I really want to try.
Well, I'd have to ask
the watch commander.
But, you know, he's always saying
recruit the brightest
and the best, so...
Great. I'll just grab
my jacket from the car.
Okay.
You can't let her become a cop.
What?
Yeah, she's been talking
about this for weeks.
And I'm trying to be encouraging,
but... I'm barely okay
worrying if you're gonna
make it home every night.
I-I can't do that with her.
Well, this sounds like something
you should discuss with her.
Dad, please,
can you just make sure she has a-a,
- a bad time?
- Henry, I can't do that.
- Please.
- I-I...
- I can lean into the bad parts.
- Great.
- Okay. Uh...
- T-Thank you. That's wonderful.
- Reporting for duty, sir!
- [CHUCKLES]
This is gonna be great.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[APPLAUSE]
[SCATTERED CHEERS]
Sorry, I tried.
Yeah, you're dead to me.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Welcome back, Officer Chen.
How're you feeling?
Can't wait to get on the streets, sir.
Just get back to normal.
So glad to hear that.
We're gonna mix things up a bit.
You're gonna be riding
with Harper this week.
Which means, Nolan, you and your
ride-along are with Bradford.
Sorry, wait. What? Ride-along?
Which brings us to Officer West.
Tell me, son, you enjoy
the red carpet last night?
What? H-How did you know
- I was at a red carpet...
- LAPD Media Relations sent me a link.
MAN: And now some hot goss
from "Hot Suspect" star
Sterling Freeman.
TV's favorite cop has
been hitting the town
with real-life LAPD Officer
Jackson West.
Looks like these cops
- [LAUGHTER]
- should call the fire department,
'cause it's getting hot in here.
- [SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
- Okay.
Yeah, no, no, no, keep laughing.
I also gained 10,000
new Instagram followers
- overnight, so...
- West,
the only followers
you should worry about
are your superiors.
Think about us next time
you're out on the town.
- Yes, sir.
- Alright. That's it.
Stay safe out there.
Nolan, you scheduled a ride-along
without clearing it with your TO first?
No, sir. I cleared it
with Detective Harper.
She said it was alright.
'Cause she knew she wasn't
riding with you today.
Alright, so who am I saddled up with?
Uh, it's my future daughter-in-law,
Abigail, over there.
She's considering signing up
to the Academy.
She's like nine pounds.
And I'm not interested in
chasing tame calls today.
Uh, no need to.
I think Abigail would benefit
from seeing the harsh side
of police work.
You don't want her to be a cop.
I'm... merely concerned
about her suitability.
So perhaps we should show her
what she'd be signing up for?
No problem.
Scaring rookies off the job
is my specialty.
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Hi, I'm Abigail.
My name is Officer Bradford.
You'll address me only
as Officer Bradford.
Do you understand?
- You sign the liability waiver?
- Yes, sir.
- Officer Bradford.
- Good.
Then you understand
you could be injured,
maimed, paralyzed, burned, or killed
- during this ride-along.
- I mean, yeah, sure.
We're not tour guides...
We're the police.
We drive towards the sound of gunshots.
So, if that's gonna be a problem,
you should bail out now.
No problem at all.
Let's go find some gunshots.
♪ ♪
So, why the switch?
Tim felt you'd be better served
riding with me.
[SCOFFS] Yeah, right.
This has to be some kind of elaborate
Tim Test that he roped you into.
Do I strike you as someone
who could get roped into anything?
Especially by Bradford.
Fair enough.
So, I'll ask you again...
Why the switch?
I convinced him,
that I would have more insight
into what you were going through.
And could therefore be more helpful
to your re-integration onto the street.
Did you go on a date
with a serial killer, too?
- Uh, no.
- Well, then I'm not sure,
how much help you'd be.
But it's fine, 'cause
I don't need any help.
I've already worked through the trauma
using both cognitive
and exposure therapy,
combined with mindful breathing,
and Eye Movement Desensitization
and Reprocessing,
so it's... it's fine.
LOPEZ: You don't get it...
Grey didn't show that red-carpet stuff
just to tell you how to act
appropriately off-duty.
He's sending you a message...
Fame and police work don't mix.
Come on. Look,
it was just my fifteen minutes.
That's not a thing you should want.
Unless you want to say goodbye
to doing undercover.
Or joining SWAT.
Or Robbery/Homicide.
Nobody's gonna wanna
ride with a "celebrity."
Okay, look, you're blowing this
way out of proportion.
Okay? It was just a red carpet.
I have it under control.
[DOOR OPENS IN DISTANCE]
Does that guy look familiar?
You mean Captain Suspicious? Yeah.
I think I saw him on a BOLO
back at the station.
Run his plate.
I'm guessing we're looking
at our first arrest of the day.
[SIREN CHIRPS, RADIO CHATTER,
CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
TIM: If you really want to be a cop,
first thing you need to
come to terms with is death...
In all its forms.
Stay here.
NOLAN: I'll never get used
to the smell of death.
ABIGAIL: It's actually not that bad.
But I kind of got a thing for armpits.
- The funkier the better.
- I don't need to know that.
[SIREN WAILS IN DISTANCE]
We got a jumper.
Did a header from the roof.
You really don't want to see this.
No, I kinda do.
If you're gonna hurl, kid,
do it over there.
Huh.
I'm not even sure what I'm looking at.
Impact velocity tends to
turn people into piñatas.
Five stories onto asphalt,
and it's limbs akimbo.
That's his left leg.
- That's his spine.
- Oh, okay.
Yeah, I see now.
- We got an I.D.?
- Yeah.
Heston Dayton, 22.
You thinking homicide? Suicide?
I won't know until I do an autopsy.
And even then, it might not be clear,
given the state of the body.
Have you notified next of kin?
Not yet.
Okay, let detectives know
that we'll take care of it.
C'mon.
Thank you.
That was cool.
That was a human being.
We're about to go tell his family,
they'll never see him again.
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-07, be advised,
vehicle is registered to a felon
with outstanding warrants.
I love being right.
First name Jedi, last name Monet,
sending details to your box.
Whoa.
Seems Mr. Monet has
an affinity for armed robbery
and assault with a deadly weapon.
- Light him up?
- No, get backup going first.
Better safe than sorry with this clown.
7-Adam-07, headed south
on Hauser near 9th.
Need backup for a felony car stop.
- You sure?
- Hell, yeah.
7-Adam-19, responding.
We're approximately 30 seconds
out, heading Northbound.
[SIRENS WAILING]
♪ He-e-e-y ♪
Five bucks he rabbits.
♪ I fight fire with fire ♪
You can pay me after.
You never accepted the bet, so...
♪ A fever spreading like wild ♪
- [SIRENS WAILING]
- ♪ Gonna kill like Abel and Cain ♪
♪ Nobody to see, ♪
♪ nobody to lose ♪
Driver, turn off the vehicle
and place both hands
outside the window.
♪ Get ready for me, ♪
♪ I'm ready for you ♪
- Oh, my God, you're that cop!
- Aah!
- Sterling's boyfriend!
- Oh, my God!
- Are you shooting a scene?
- Jackson,
get them the hell out of here!
- Hey, ladies, you need to step back!
- Aah!
- He's gonna arrest me!
- Ladies. Ladies, ladies.
- You need to get back.
- LOPEZ: Jackson!
- ♪ Aw, yeah! ♪
- You need to get back.
- Ladies, stay back.
- LUCY: He's running. He's running!
- [SCREAMS]
- Lady, stay back.
[OBJECTS CRASHING]
LUCY: Get out of the store,
get out of the store.
- [LAUGHING]
- Back!
Move! Move, move!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE REVS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
LOPEZ: He's empty!
Hey!
Stop where you are!
- Police!
- Stop right there!
Hands behind your head, fingers laced.
Down on your knees.
Control, show us
one in custody. Code 4.
[HANDCUFFS RATTLE, CLICK]
♪ Play your favorite song ♪
♪ Get your armor ready ♪
♪ Take two deep breaths ♪
♪ As your hands get steady ♪
- [ENGINE REVS]
- ♪ Is your game face on? ♪
♪ Are you suited up tight? ♪
♪ Call your warcry ♪
♪ Getting ready for the night ♪
Hey, I-I just wanted to say
I'm sorry about before...
At the crime scene.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- I wasn't thinking about the family.
I get it, but listen...
What we're here to do, is awful.
Death notifications always are.
You spend the drive over dreading it.
Trying to come up with words
that will somehow... soften the blow.
Knowing that there aren't any.
This boy lived here
with his mother and his sister,
and what we're about to tell them
has the potential to destroy lives.
There's no shame in waiting in the shop
if you're not up for it.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Police!
What? What'd he do this time?
Ma'am, I'm Officer Bradford.
This is Officer Nolan.
- Can we come in?
- No.
- Ma'am, I think it's best if you let...
- Just tell me,
what Heston did.
We regret to inform you
that your son was killed this morning.
- What?
- What's going on?
Mom?
Your brother's dead.
- No.
- I'm afraid so.
What happened?
He fell from a building in downtown.
It's possible he jumped.
No, he would never do that.
N-N-Never.
Do you know what he was doing downtown?
No.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [LIQUID POURS]
I hadn't seen him in a couple of days.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Who are you?
I'm Abigail.
I'm... I'm doing a ridealong.
It doesn't matter.
Did you see him...
His body?
No.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Like what?
Make him alive again? Can you do that?
No.
TIM: You asked what Heston
had "done now"?
What kind of trouble was your son into?
Just hanging around with idiots.
Anybody we should talk to?
[ENGINE REVS, HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYS]
- What did you do?!
- Guys!
- What the hell did you do?!
- What?
It's your fault he's dead!
What the hell are you squawking about?
- Hey, leave her alone!
- Hey.
- [GROANS]
- Here. Ma'am...
Ma'am, calm down.
Who is this guy?
He's the reason Heston's dead!
What are you talking about?
I just talked to him this morning.
- NOLAN: Get up.
- [GROANS]
7-Adam-15, can you run a name for me?
Everest Jones, born 02/01/96.
Wait,
he... he's not really dead, is he?
Yes, he is,
if you know anything about it,
you need to tell us right now.
- Dude, I don't know anything.
- Liar!
- Hey, hey.
- Do you have a specific accusation?
No.
But ever since Heston's been
hanging out with this loser,
he's been getting himself in trouble.
DISPATCH: 7-Adam-15, first name
Everest, last name Jones.
Priors for criminal threats
and brandishing a firearm.
You're under arrest for
assault and battery.
They attacked me.
Detectives will come by later
to talk to you and your mom.
If you have any questions,
give me a call.
[DOG BARKS]
[CAR DOORS OPEN, CLOSE]
Thanks for jumping in the fight.
- No problem.
- [SIGHS]
And sorry for biting your head off.
It's okay. I can't even imagine
what you must be feeling right now.
Take care of yourself.
♪ ♪
You okay?
Better than her.
Come on.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- Turn to the right.
- Okay,
and that concludes today's festivities.
Transport'll be here soon.
- You want me to do the paperwork?
- Oh, nope.
That was a nice job out there.
Thanks.
So, you're just not gonna
let me help you at all.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- I don't need any help.
I already told you, I'm fine.
We'll see.
Abigail?
- Hey.
- Hi.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Did you get the flowers we sent?
And the basket. Thank you.
So, you're Nolan's ride-along.
- How's it going?
- It's, uh, a lot.
- Mm-hmm.
- What the hell is this?
I let you run around with Harper
for half a day
and you start hugging people on duty?
Don't listen to him. He's all bark.
I gotta pee.
All bark?
She is not buying what you're selling.
That's because I don't hold
her fate in my hands.
Heard you dodged some bullets.
Yeah, a few.
What, are you keeping tabs on me?
Look, if you need anything,
you let me know.
You got a time machine?
I wish I did.
NOLAN: Alright, Everest,
time to come clean.
You need to tell us what
you know about Heston.
Maybe he did really jump.
How the hell should I know?
His sister tried to
scratch your eyes out.
She thinks you're responsible.
Well, I was at the DMV
in Culver City all morning,
clearing up tickets, so...
They got cameras there,
so if you're lying...
I'm not! And I know my rights.
I don't have to talk
to you two anymore, so...
Get him processed.
I'll get the detectives
table up to speed.
Right.
You warned me, and I didn't listen.
Like it or not, I'm a celebrity now.
- Celebrity-adjacent.
- Hey, whatever.
Look, e-either way,
somebody almost got
hurt today because of me...
because I thought it'd be cool
to walk down the actual red carpet,
have people take my picture.
- It made me feel important.
- You're young.
You still think popularity matters.
So, what do I do?
I can't answer that.
Wait, you think I should...
break things off with Sterling?
Unless you got another way
to stay under the radar...
Yeah.
[CHOMPING]
A little hungry?
No.
I get it.
This job isn't how you
imagined it would be.
What's gonna happen with Everest?
Well, he's got an alibi.
Detectives will run it down.
If it's real, he'll get "cited out,"
be home before dark.
It's still possible Heston's
death was an accident...
Or a suicide.
An autopsy's gonna
shed some light on that.
Look, it's good that you see now,
how rough this job can be,
before you sign on.
Now you can move on, and...
Figure out what it is
you really want to do.
But I really want to do this.
Now more than ever.
Your job affects people...
makes a difference in their lives.
If there had been a cop
like you around,
back when I needed help...
Things would've been different.
Thanks for making today happen.
And for believing in me.
♪ ♪
Hey. Where's your ride-along?
Oh, Henry came to pick her up.
They're crashing a wedding in Malibu
to see if they like the place.
Well, let her know I thought she showed
some solid instincts today.
And she's clearly
got some fight in her.
So, I'd be happy to put in
a word when she turns 21.
That's very nice of you.
You should know she's got
a little trouble in her past, you know.
She knows that's gonna make the road
a little harder for her,
but she's committed.
Okay, what kind of trouble?
Ex-boyfriend put some revenge porn
on the Internet when she was 17.
She kind of torched his car...
[SIGHS] She'll never be a cop.
She knows she handled it the wrong way.
- She did a ton of community service...
- Doesn't matter.
The law sees it as an incident
of domestic violence...
That's a hard pass at the Academy.
There's gotta be something
she can do...
There isn't.
It's a shame.
She seems like a good kid.
- [SHOWER RUNNING]
- Oh!
[DOOR OPENS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
You're not gonna shower?
Uh, I'm gonna do it at home.
Oh, but you're not going home.
- What?
- Ready?
- Almost.
- I'm... I'm sorry, ready...
Ready for what?
We have plans.
- Girls night.
- Oh, I get it.
You've seen that I'm fine on the job,
but you're still not convinced?
No, that's not it.
We just thought it would be fun.
But if you're not up for it...
Oh, wait, no, I am. It's...
You guys have just never
asked me out before.
But that's great. Uh, cool.
So, where are we going? A bar?
Club? [CHUCKLES]
[THE BLUE STONES']
["SHAKIN' OFF THE RUST" PLAYS]
- ♪ Bang my head against the wall ♪
- Oh.
Uh, this is a joke, right?
- I...
- You were right.
I have never gone on a date
with a serial killer, and you have.
And that would make anyone
question their judgment.
- Yeah, sure, but, uh, this is...
- But nothing.
Look, you can never truly know
that you are fine until you know
that you can trust your judgment again.
- [SIGHS]
- So, we're here,
in this controlled environment
with zero stakes,
so you can meet and evaluate
a succession of men.
- If you can call them "men."
- Look, I appreciate,
what you're trying to do here.
And actually, it's fairly
psychologically sound,
but this... This is... unnecessary.
Well, it'll just be
a great story for tomorrow.
You are not gonna take "no"
for an answer, are you?
I am just real committed to
getting you to say "yes."
♪ So I'm shaking off the rust ♪
♪ And you've got no trust ♪
Okay. Fine.
- Yes.
- Great.
We will be sitting over there...
- Y...
- ...having just some BYO.
Uh, oh, no. If I'm doing this,
so are you guys.
Can't have a control study
without independent data.
Otherwise how will I know
that my judgment is sound?
She's got a point.
Don't make me pull
the buried alive card.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Screw it, I'm in.
- [CHUCKLES]
[TV PLAYS INDISTINCTLY]
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
- Hey.
- Hey. [CHUCKLES]
Well, at the risk of sounding
like my mother,
is that what you're wearing tonight?
- [SCOFFS]
- We got that restaurant opening,
the vodka launch, the runway show.
I just thought we could
stay in tonight.
I ordered a pizza.
Extra large with all the toppings.
See, my... my... my PR rep
had to pull massive strings,
to get us into that vodka launch.
Well, I'm not dating your PR rep,
and I don't care about vodka launches,
and runway shows.
Well, that's not true. You're right.
I would love to go to
a runway show, just...
Not tonight.
Okay, hey, hey.
What is going on with you?
Okay, um...
I got recognized at work.
From the red carpet last night.
- That is so cute.
- No, it... it's not.
It was a real problem.
Look, Sterling, I have to be anonymous,
for my job.
What are you saying?
I don't know.
Look, man, if we could
just stay in tonight,
it would really mean
a lot to me, please.
Look, this PR stuff,
it's part of my job.
It's how I make connections,
stay relevant.
[SIGHS]
Jackson...
Don't make me go without you.
- We'll have fun.
- Yeah.
But we can have fun here.
I can't.
I have to go.
Okay. Yeah.
♪ ♪
Thanks.
For nothing.
- [HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYS]
- [INHALES DEEPLY]
You ready?
Uh...
- Can I...?
- Mm.
Thanks.
♪ What's up, what's up. ♪
♪ What's up, what's up? ♪
♪ Unh, it's the young ♪
♪ Paul Bunyan in this bitch ♪
- [SIGHS]
- ♪ Whoo! I got babes
Okay, let's do this.
Do you ever have
any intrusive thoughts?
I mean, I know it's not "PC" to say,
but women are paid less
because they just naturally
take fewer risks.
♪ Come to gettin'... ♪
♪ I'm a lifer ♪
So there I was,
wandering the crash site,
carrying this guy's leg...
Mm-hmm.
Did you have any early
behavioral issues?
How would you describe your
relationship with your mom?
And would you submit yourself
to a full background check?
If not, um, why?
♪ Would you like some popcorn ♪
♪ along with that butter? ♪
Ah, ah, ah, ah. Don't say anything.
Let's just sit here,
until the timer goes off.
Anyway, I learned my lesson.
Don't wear open-toed shoes
to a crime scene.
- [BUZZER]
- Okay.
- She did good.
- Yeah.
This has actually been...
really interesting.
I feel like I learned
something about myself.
That's great. [CHUCKLES]
Oh, you have a string coming...
[TATTOO NEEDLE BUZZING]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- Hey, hey.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- [GROANING]
[CROWD MURMURING]
You know, you really shouldn't
touch a woman without asking,
but, you know,
we don't need to make a thing of it,
right?
Are you okay? What happened?
♪ ♪
Good morning.
How are you feeling?
Just gearing up for a day of
country clubs and wedding halls.
I mean, how are you feeling
about the "not becoming a cop"
situation?
I'm fine.
It's not the first time
I lost out on something
because of what happened.
- And it won't be the last.
- Abigail...
I'm gonna take a shower.
Hey. Good morning.
Morning.
She's heartbroken, you know.
Yeah, I know, but, uh,
I think it's for the best.
Henry, I-I'm disappointed
you feel that way.
You love her,
but you're rooting against her?
All because you can't handle
the idea of her being in danger.
Okay, Dad, that's not fair.
I'm trying to protect her.
Deciding what's best for
her is not protecting her...
That's controlling her.
And you're better than that.
I shouldn't have
played along yesterday,
and that's on me,
but I would be a failure
as a father, if I didn't tell you,
you're falling down as a fiancé.
- [SIGHS]
- Abigail deserves your empathy,
and your honesty.
You can't give her that,
you should tell her it's over.
[KEYS RATTLE]
[BRONZE RADIO RETURN'S
"THERE WILL BE ANOTHER" PLAYS]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Uh, yeah?
I don't feel so good.
Aw.
Did you eat that whole pizza?
I went for a slice when I got home,
but the box was empty.
Worse.
I spent the whole night in bed,
shame-eating,
while I refreshed
Sterling's Instagram feed.
Oh, no.
- FOMO overload?
- Oh, yeah.
You have no idea.
Red carpets, gift bags,
and guess who Sterling sat
next to at the fashion show...
- Hmm?
- Lady Gaga.
Oh, my God. And you missed her?
- I know.
- Ohh.
That's when I ordered another pizza.
I'm sorry, what? You...
You ate two pizzas?
Mm, it sounds so bad
when you say it out loud.
And completely unsustainable
as a coping mechanism.
Aw.
What are you gonna do?
I think I have to break up with him.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, me too.
Just, I like him.
Like, a lot.
Well, on the bright side,
you won't be alone in being alone.
You know, we can FOMO together.
Okay.
♪ There will be a better one ♪
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hey.
You seen Nolan?
Not yet, hey,
Lucy had a bit of a moment
last night when we were out.
It's... It's not a big deal.
- She's fine.
- What the hell is Harper doing?
Helping, don't get all "Tim" on me.
I just thought you should know.
Lucy's okay?
- She will be.
- Alright.
Thanks for letting me know.
Nolan, I got something.
Me too. Who goes first?
I do.
Listen, Medical Examiner called.
Heston Dayton wasn't a jumper.
- Pushed?
- More like tossed.
He was dead before he left the roof.
Strangled.
Weirdly, he also had acid burns
on his forearms, less than a week old.
Well, funny you should say that.
I looked up the arrest records
for Everest Jones.
His burglary charge was
for stealing drain cleaner,
which contains sulfuric acid.
Which is used to cook meth.
You think they were cooking it
in the trailer park?
No, we'd have smelled it.
So, what now? We bring
the detectives up to speed?
Not yet.
Let's go to Everest first.
I know what you're thinking,
but I'm fine.
You nearly broke that guy's arm.
I was just doing what they
taught us in the Academy.
React quickly.
Subdue the threat.
He was picking a piece of
thread off of your shirt.
And you got triggered.
Yeah, well, what do you know about it?
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
Come on.
When you're undercover,
you can't let go for even a second.
You have to maintain
complete control over your responses,
read between every glance.
It is physically, mentally,
and emotionally exhausting.
Okay, and, what, you slipped up,
and one of them figured out
you were a cop?
What?
[SIGHS]
I always met my case officer at a bar.
It was the one place,
that I could go where I could...
Drop the character, and I could
stop strategizing and just have a beer,
and be myself.
So, one night,
one beer turned into two,
which turned into...
Well, I lost count.
And if it were any... other scenario,
I would have sobered up,
I would've cut myself off,
but...
I wasn't with the crooks.
I was with another cop.
And I trusted him.
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, it was a long time ago, but...
My point is...
I shut down.
I didn't even tell my husband.
I just, I kept telling
myself that I would...
Deal with it when I was ready.
But with every passing week,
it just got worse.
Maybe I pushed you too hard,
last night.
But I know what it is like
when you do not face things head-on.
- Hey.
- [BREATHES SHAKILY]
Yeah?
You're gonna get through this.
I promise.
♪ ♪
What... What happened to him?
Your case officer.
He fell down a flight
of stairs, a few times,
had to take a disability pension.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[RADIO CHATTER]
You and Chen are close, right?
Yeah, I'd say so.
How's she doing?
I mean, really doing?
She's good.
Really.
I think she'll be better,
once she gets that tattoo removed.
Can you imagine that...
Walking around every day,
branded by the worst thing
that's ever happened to you?
You think because
it's physical, it's worse?
Tragedies always leave scars...
Only some of them you can see.
[RADIO CHATTER]
[MOTORCYCLES PASSING]
♪ ♪
Well, that can't be good.
We saw two Dead Bastards
leaving the park
when we pulled in there yesterday.
- Can't be a coincidence.
- Let me guess...
- They sell a little meth?
- A lot of meth.
And they wouldn't take
kindly to a couple of idiots,
trying to cook and
sell in their territory.
So, they chuck Heston off of a roof,
come back by the park
to do the same to Everest,
but leave when they see us.
Yeah, but now they came back
to finish the job.
Confiscate any product
or cash they find on site.
- So, what's our next move?
- We call in the cavalry
and hope nobody gets killed
while we're waiting.
7-Adam-15, in position for recon.
- Stand by for tactical assessment.
- Roger that.
We just landed at the staging
area around the corner...
SWAT's mobilizing,
but I'm not sure we can
wait around for them to land.
Set up an OP and then report
back to me.
[RADIO BEEPS]
Okay,
Bradford and Nolan are hopping the wall,
to give us eyes inside.
Get ready to move out.
[TRAILER DOOR SLAMS OPEN]
[RIFLE COCKS]
[DOG BARKING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINES RUMBLE]
♪ ♪
Oh!
- [GROANS]
- Get back here.
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
MAN: Get him up. Get him back inside.
- [RADIO BEEPS]
- Sarge,
this thing is going south fast.
I definitely don't think
we can wait for SWAT.
SGT. GREY: Copy that.
You two proceed to target.
[RADIO BEEPS]
That's my truck.
What?
I lent it to Abigail and Henry,
to go take a look at wedding venues.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
They must've come here to see Ellen.
Abigail was talking
about her last night.
- [RADIO BEEPS]
- Sarge, we got a new situation.
Where'd he cook?
I don't know.
- Try again.
- [YELPS]
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Sit down!
Stop, stop! She doesn't know anything.
Okay, how about you?
You know where the kid cooked?
Where he kept the cash?
No.
Man, we don't know anything.
We're just... We're
just in the wrong place,
at the wrong time.
Lot of that going around.
People wandering into territory
they got no business in.
Messages got to get sent.
You killed my brother.
Nah, he killed himself, really,
by being stupid enough,
to wander into the middle
of a criminal enterprise,
like a turkey, staring up at the rain,
and then drowning.
That's a myth, actually.
- What's that?
- Turkeys don't actually do that...
- Look up at the rain and drown.
- Okay, okay.
Well, if somebody
don't start telling me
what it is I need to know right now,
then Big Death is gonna
drown you in the toilet.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
We're in position.
All units... Green Light.
I repeat, Green Light.
♪ ♪
Drop your guns now!
Get on your stomach!
- Arms out, palms up!
- Now!
Get down, get down.
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[FLOOR CREAKS]
I thought you checked the place.
- I did.
- Check it again.
[BEADS CLACK]
- [TASER CRACKLES]
- [GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
What the hell are you doing back there?
[ALL SCREAM]
[GUNSHOT]
Go, go, go, go, go!
Get on the ground now!
- Get on the ground!
- Get down!
- Right now!
- Get on the ground!
- [GRUNTS]
- Clear?
All clear.
- You got him?
- Got him.
- Hey, you okay?
- What?
- He asked if we were okay.
- What?!
- [HANDCUFFS CLICK]
- Come here.
Come here.
Police!
Stop where you are!
- Down on your knees.
- Hands behind your head,
fingers laced. Don't move.
7-Adam-19, two suspects in custody.
Code 4.
♪ ♪
[SIREN WAILS]
What? It's totally your fault.
What? This is my fault?
How is this my fault?
- This is all your fault!
- Because I like going out?
Are you crazy?
You're the one that's putting
your job ahead of our relationship.
Because it is not a relationship!
I'm just arm candy to you
to all your celebrity responsibilities.
- How can you say that?
- Because it's true.
Well, if you're so unhappy,
then walk away, okay?
- I'm not gonna stop you.
- I know you won't.
- That's why it's over.
- Fine.
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
[SIGHS]
[VAN DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
You okay?
Yeah. That was hard.
[VAN DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Ah!
- That was awesome!
- [BOTH LAUGH]
Honestly, I'm glad we didn't get
a chance to rehearse,
'cause the first take, always the best.
I know, right? I mean,
you were such a good actor,
I totally believed you
were breaking up with me.
Dude, you were incredible.
In fact, you were so good,
I could probably get you
a guest role on the show.
Aww. That's so sweet.
- Yeah.
- Focus!
The public breakup was meant
to get you out of the spotlight.
And as long as you guys
stay off the radar,
Jackson's choices in
the department stay open.
Right. Sorry. Uh, got carried away.
Well, that's 'cause you're passionate.
- That's what I dig about you.
- Aww.
Hey, uh, you got any of that
pizza left at your place?
I'm starving.
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS] What's so funny?
Can we go?
I finally found the one thing
that makes me not want to be a cop.
Yes. The paperwork is a bitch.
- Who's a bitch?
- Oh, you're my bitch.
Okay. Can we go home now?
Uh, I have another 30 minutes here,
but you guys should take off.
- I'll meet you at home.
- Sure.
Today was scary.
Yes, it was.
Yeah, you're used to it, though, right?
Used to it? No, no, no.
Especially not with you two in danger.
But we're trained to
deal with our fear.
You know, most people operate
in fairly conflict-free environments.
So, when something... shocking, happens,
they're, overwhelmed,
and they panic or freeze.
Everyone has a plan until
they get punched in the mouth.
Exactly. And cops are
a little used to getting
punched in the mouth.
Conflict is literally in
the job description, so...
We try to recognize fear,
and not let it paralyze us.
I never thought about it that way.
My man didn't freeze when
the bullets started flying.
He jumped on top of me. My hero.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm not a hero.
Um, I have to tell you something.
I wasn't supportive,
of you wanting to be a cop.
I asked my dad if he could
scare you straight.
And he called me out
for being selfish...
And he was right.
- Oh.
- Look.
You deserve, so much better,
and, uh, I'll understand if you,
don't want to marry me anymore.
♪ ♪
That escalated quickly.
You're not... Not upset?
A little.
I don't know why you didn't
just say something.
But... I get it.
- I'm a bit of a wildcard.
- [CHUCKLES]
You grew up in a stable home,
with parents who believed in you.
I'm used to people underestimating me.
I just didn't think
you were one of them.
♪ You... ♪
But we'll work through it.
You're not getting
rid of me that easily.
Thank God.
[CHUCKLES]
Proud of you. Proud of both of you.
And I think we should celebrate
Henry's newfound maturity...
With pie.
- Now you're talking.
- Wait, wait.
Don't you have to
finish your paperwork?
I'll come in early tomorrow.
[CHAIN RATTLING]
[SNIFFLES, SIGHS]
Hey. Hi.
You got no quit in you, do you, Boot?
No, sir. I get that from you.
I don't think so.
You walked in the door this way.
It's what makes you so aggravating.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm taking that as a compliment.
It was meant to be.
- You have a good night.
- Yeah, you too.
[PUNCHING BAG THUDDING]
You know... [SIGHS]
I got half a dozen scars.
Bullet wounds, knife wounds,
broken bottle.
Then there's the ones you can't see...
Isabel's addiction,
a dad, who would tune me up
on the regular.
And whether I like it or not,
they're a part of me.
I-I know what you're trying to do,
and I appreciate it, but...
This is different.
I was tattooed by a sadist
who etched my day of death,
- into my skin.
- Okay, but you didn't die. Okay?
You lived.
And now he's the one in the ground.
But... [SCOFFS]
I'm not trying to tell you
what to do with it.
Okay? Burn it off,
keep it, whatever gives you peace.
All I'm trying to do,
is give you some hard-won perspective.
You can choose to see that tattoo
as your greatest failure.
But I see it as proof
that you're a survivor.
It wasn't your day of death,
Officer Chen.
It was the first day,
of the rest of your life.
And no one can take that away from you.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
You're welcome.
You riding with me tomorrow?
[CHUCKLES]
Yes, sir.
Good. Get in early.
War bags need restocking.
Okay.
♪ ♪
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com