John.
- Hey.
- How are you?
Great. I was just, um...
- I haven't seen you.
- Yeah, I know.
I just was swamped with work
and, uh, the kitchen renovation.
How was your vacation with Oliver?
Great! You know, we went to Utah,
- we hit all the state parks.
- Oh, it's so beautiful up there.
Seriously. I mean, stunning.
I've been thinking about you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Eh, would you be interested
in coming over
and helping me test out
the new kitchen?
You want me to cook for you?
I would cook.
- I wouldn't say no to a-a co-pilot.
- Mm.
My use of vegetables has been described
as a crime against humanity.
Kids can be so cruel.
Sure. I mean, I'd love to.
Why are you holding a towel?
40-year-old male,
traumatic amputation of right hand
in construction accident.
BP 100/70, heart rate 110.
Get him into Trauma Two,
page Ortho, and order an x-ray.
Start an IV with two liters of saline.
John, is that the...
Yes. Yeah, that's his.
Hey, um, what time?
- Uh, 7:00?
- It's a date.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com
So, what are you gonna cook her?
Couple of big-ass steaks
and a lovely baked potato.
- What?
- You know we're in L.A.?
She's at least a pescatarian.
And she definitely doesn't eat carbs.
- So, no potato?
- Your safest bet
is a kale salad with
a nice piece of salmon.
Man, food used to be so easy.
There was only two kinds...
Fried and other.
- Okay, Grandpa.
- Nolan.
There's a lawyer looking
for you at the front desk.
Uh-oh. What'd you do?
- Are you John Nolan?
- That depends on...
Are you here to
serve me with a subpoena?
No. I'm a trust and estates lawyer.
Susan Banker, I'm here to inform you
about what your
father left you in his will.
What... Wait.
- My father's dead?
- Yes.
I'm sorry. Did no one tell you that?
I haven't spoken to
my father in 35 years.
He left me something in his will?
Was it a lot of something?
$14 and his 1971 Chevelle.
- You're kidding.
- No. There's the check.
The car will be delivered later today.
And what if I don't want the car?
Then get rid of it.
Just sign the bottom...
...confirming your
receipt of the check.
Eh, how did he die?
Heart attack. Or drowning.
He was in the pool at his house
in Tempe when it hit.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
We're celebrating Smitty's last day
as Mr. Irrelevant.
The sergeants exam happens
once every two years.
Whoever scores the lowest gets called
Mr. Irrelevant
'cause they got no chance
- at getting promoted.
- Hey!
So, if this is Smitty's swan song,
that means the new scores
are gonna be posted soon.
- Tonight.
- That's exciting.
- You're gonna do great.
- No doubt.
Hey.
You alright?
My dad died.
I'm so sorry. Are... Are you okay?
Yeah, I honestly
never knew the man.
It's just a little unexpected.
Alright. Well, if you need anything...
Nah. I'm fine.
Honestly. I'm good. Thank you.
Alright. Party's over.
So, Officer Smitty...
These past two years,
you have handled your irrelevance
with the poise and dignity
I expect from a man of...
Of little ambition.
Thank you, sir.
To business.
Today is Follow-Up Day.
Detectives have several cases
that are on the edge
of being back-burnered.
You're gonna take the day
to see if you can breathe
new life into them.
So, Bradford and Chen,
you have a three-day-old home invasion.
The victim is a former
gang member, Nevin Cooper.
No forensics, no suspects.
We're on it, sir.
Lopez and West,
you're going to Hancock Park.
A statue was stolen from
a homeowner's front yard.
It looks like a giant turd.
Well, that "turd" is worth
a half a million,
- so track it down.
- Yes, sir.
Which brings me to Harper and Nolan.
Actually, sir,
Robbery Homicide requested
that Officer Nolan and I
follow up on one of their cases.
And how much did you pay
for them to request that?
That's a very cynical question, sir.
- Seems fair to me.
- Yeah.
What do you think, Officer Nolan?
What?
On it. Yes, sir.
Hey, you sure you're alright?
There's no shame in
taking a personal day.
Oh. Yeah, I know.
Uh, just seemed so disingenuous,
you know?
Last time I saw my dad, I was ten.
He was driving away in that Chevelle.
The car he left me.
Sounds like the plot of
a bad first novel.
- No offense.
- No. No, you're not wrong.
Hey, listen.
It's one thing to lose focus
during roll call,
but out here, you get
distracted, you get killed.
So I need you sharp.
I am.
I will be.
We're closed.
Police.
Uh, we're following up
for Detective Calderon.
We're just checking in to see if
you've thought of anything new
that might help us catch the guy
who robbed you and killed your wife.
No. He came inside
and hit me right away.
Uh, I couldn't do anything to stop him.
To save her.
Sir, we're very sorry for your loss.
You told detectives the man
was wearing a mask?
Yes.
And he took several hundred dollars
from the register
and a case of whiskey?
Well, another thing.
I didn't notice it until this morning
when I started to clean,
but there was a new roll of scratchers
under the counter.
They're not there now.
He must have taken them.
Scratch-off lottery tickets?
Yes. Um... like these.
High value. 500 tickets a roll.
- Did you report those as stolen?
- An hour ago.
That's how we're gonna catch this guy.
Uh, sir, the lottery office
will flag all the serial numbers
and cancel the tickets.
If he tries to redeem a winner,
it'll get flagged.
Good. I hope you catch him.
And I hope he gives you
a good reason to kill him.
Sir.
We will keep you posted.
Uh, if anything else occurs to you,
just give us a call.
Why did you stop me?
It is not our job to police his grief.
Good morning, officers.
What can I get you?
We're looking for Nevin Cooper.
Oh. He's a little busy right now.
Can I help you with something?
Hey, everything okay?
Yeah.
It's just some confusion in our order.
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
Marquel, right?
I know you?
I'm the guy who put
Keon in Pelican Bay.
Heard you filled the void.
Ah, what can I say?
"Some are born great,"
"some achieve greatness,"
"and some have
greatness thrust upon them."
- Shakespeare.
- Play?
"Twelfth Night."
Smart for a cop.
I read you weren't running
with these guys anymore, Nevin.
Found a different path in prison.
Bitch binge-watched
too much British baking.
Got himself rehabilitated.
It's not every day that you see a gang
be so forgiving to someone
who's left the flock.
That's inspiring.
Unless you're here to sweat him.
You guys wouldn't happen to know
who broke into Nevin's
house a couple nights ago,
- tied him up?
- I sure don't.
But I tell you what, I hear anything,
you will be my first call.
I'll see you around, Nevin.
- You alright?
- Fine.
Got a lot of work to do
and it's tight in here,
so, Sasha'll give you
some donuts on your way out.
I know you're scared, but we can help.
I'm not scared. I'm busy.
I got things handled.
Okay, so, why call the cops
if you got it handled?
- I didn't.
- Let me guess. Sasha did.
Before you could tell her not to?
I appreciate what you're trying to do...
Turn your life around.
- I know it isn't easy.
- It is what it is, man.
You can't handle Marquel
and his crew on your own.
I don't know what you're talking about.
They just came to buy some pastries.
Now I gotta get back to work.
Sure.
You change your mind,
you know where to find us.
Looks like that's where the statue was.
You're gonna make a great detective.
Why haven't you guys
found my statue yet?
That's why we're here, sir...
To see if you have any new information.
If have any new information?
This is your job.
I've been calling you every day.
Yes, sir, we're aware.
That's why we're here.
Did they find it?
No.
Ma'am,
I read over the initial police report.
What exactly did you mean when you said
that whoever took it
should get a reward?
- What the hell?
- I did not say that.
- Did I?
- Mrs. Nithercott,
did you have anything to do
with the disappearance of the statue?
Of course not.
No, uh, just I'm not as sad
as Roger is that it's gone.
What are you saying?
I thought you loved that piece.
It looks like a dinosaur
copped a squat on our front yard.
I bought it, because it
reminded me of our honeymoon.
How does that remind you
of your honeymoon?
Maybe I don't want to know.
Look, you wanna find the thief?
Talk to the members of
the homeowners association.
They hated that thing as much as I did.
You ever play the lottery?
Only when the
jackpot goes to a billion.
- You?
- Every week for 20 years,
when I lived back in Foxburg.
Buy a ticket at the gas station
on the way home on a Friday night,
spend the time it took me
to fill my tank
just fantasizing what I
would do with the money.
And?
Mostly I would just think about
what life would be like
if I never had to worry
about money again.
Oh, yeah. That would be nice.
I can barely see the edge
of the hole I'm in.
7-Adam-15, give the bridge a call.
Yeah, this is Officer Nolan.
I was asked to call.
Right. Thank you.
My inheritance has arrived.
- Hey.
Nice car. It's a classic.
Yeah. It has a matching 350 four-barrel
with an original turbo trans.
You drive it all the way
in from Arizona?
No.
No, I,
uh... I actually drove it to New York
and then I got on a cargo ship
and then we went
through the Panama Canal.
No need to be an ass about it.
What do you think I could get for it?
I don't know, man.
W-What, you want to sell it?
I don't know. The guy who
left it to me was bad news.
Real piece of crap.
- Hey!
- Don't talk about my dad!
Hands behind your back!
Ow!
Your dad?
That would make him...
- My brother.
- Half-brother.
Wait. Just wait. Just... Just stop.
- What is your name?
- Pete. Nolan.
- And your father was?
- Charles.
He had a beer belly,
he had blue eyes,
a Marine Corps tattoo.
I don't know, he liked to take
his teeth out at parties.
He was quite a character!
You got me on that last one.
He was 35 when he abandoned
my mom and me.
Alright, what do you want to do here?
Take off the cuffs.
- You're gonna let me go?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
'Cause the last cop I punched
was not that cool about it.
How many cops have you punched?
Like, today, or, like, ever?
I'm kidding. One.
Five. I've punched five cops.
Look...
Before today,
I didn't even know I had a brother.
Half-brother, alright?
And I was just as surprised
when the chick read the will
and said that you were getting the car.
I don't know why he did that.
Yeah. I don't know
why he did that, either.
Now, if I'm free to go,
uh, I'm gonna go.
Back to Arizona, alright?
Um... look, this has all
been a bit of a shock,
but if you'd like to... wait
around till after my shift,
- I don't know, maybe we could...
- What?
Hang out and get to know each other
and become best friends?
No.
I'll pass, enjoy the car.
Nice meeting you.
It's a push.
Lunch?
So, how does it work?
The sergeants exam?
Do you get the stripe right away?
No. Passing the test is the first step.
You only get promoted
when a spot opens up.
If you're at the top of the
list, might take a month or two.
The lower you are,
the longer it's gonna take.
And for some, they'll never get a shot.
Be taking the test again in two years.
Hey.
Your home invasion
victim was just assaulted.
He's on his way to the ER.
Nevin? We just saw him.
Yeah, Marquel must have
doubled back after we left.
Is he hurt bad?
Fractured right arm, bruised ribs,
couple of loose teeth.
He's gonna be in pain for a few weeks.
Do you guys know who did it?
Yeah, but we can't do anything about it
unless Nevin makes an official ID.
Which he's not going to do.
But maybe his girlfriend will.
Good luck.
How is he?
He's tough.
Didn't want me to call 911,
even though the bone was sticking out.
I'm sorry.
That sounds upsetting.
He's trying so hard to make up
for the things he did.
Why can't they just leave him alone?
Because they're predators.
- But, we can help.
- How?
He's here because you
came around this morning.
Marquel had to make sure that
Nevin wasn't snitching.
Snitching about what?
No way.
Sasha, you walk away,
he ends up back in prison or dead.
Look, without us,
Nevin either gives in,
gives Marquel what he wants,
or he doesn't and Marquel kills him.
We're his only hope
at a different outcome.
You promise you can protect him?
I'd be lying if I said yes,
but he's got no chance without us.
Marquel wants Nevin
to launder drug money
through the bakery.
Said he had 24 hours to decide.
Now you know.
So, what's the play?
Arrest Marquel for assault?
No.
We do that, and Marquel's guys
will kill Sasha and Nevin.
Then what?
I don't know.
Neighbor says
she didn't witness the theft,
but, quote, "That statue
was the real crime."
And the woman I talked to
said that she wished
she had the balls to steal
that thing years ago,
and whoever took it should have
a statue erected in their honor.
Alright. One more house
and I'm calling it.
Police!
There's a car in the driveway.
LAPD!
We just have a few questions for you.
I guess we can follow up tomorrow.
Help!
Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
- Help!
Help!
Oh.
- Oh, God.
- Oh! God!
Think how I feel.
I've been lying in it.
I have a brother.
My father is dead,
and I have a brother.
Yeah, we've been through
all of this at some length.
I mean, yesterday,
I didn't have a brother,
and today, I have a brother.
That is a serious shift
in the universe.
Is it?
Look, I mean, real siblings are
people that you share
your childhood with.
That guy shares some DNA.
Doesn't make him your brother.
Got your suspect in interrogation.
Northeast Division caught her
trying to cash in
one of the stolen scratchers
at a 7-Eleven in Los Feliz.
Her?
Smitty, our killer is a six foot,
200-pound male.
Well, she's none of those things.
I didn't know the scratcher
was stolen, okay?
I swear.
Where'd you get the ticket?
- Work.
- And work is?
The Red Angel.
Strip club.
You know, I've had some
pretty pathetic tips before,
but this is the first one
that's landed me in jail.
Relax. You're not under arrest.
We just need the name of the guy
who gave you the ticket.
I don't know.
From the stage,
it's just a sea of losers.
- No offense.
- None taken.
I don't really frequent those.
I mean, I've been.
I just don't make a habit of...
Does the club have cameras?
- Not officially.
- That's a yes.
I'll call the club and get
the footage sent over,
and then you and Chastity
can go through every frame,
and find the guy that
tipped her the ticket.
Together?
As in she'll be watching me
as I watch her...
As in... you're solving a murder.
Right.
Stealing that statue
was a public service.
That almost got you killed.
Still worth it.
Angela. Excuse me. Angela.
Oh.
Is this your station?
What a funny little world.
Who's that?
Wesley's mom.
What's she in for?
They found an unlicensed gun in
her car during a traffic stop.
Oh, wait. Here.
I'm about to do one of
my signature moves.
How is that even possible?
Uh, the key is core strength,
and pride in my downstairs area.
Well, it's well-earned.
Thanks.
Got somewhere else to be?
No. I... Kind of.
It's... I-I have a date.
It's not for a few hours.
Oh, good for you.
Dating is challenging,
especially towards the beginning.
Well, this is, uh, an old
girlfriend, actually.
Oh.
Making what's old new again.
Yeah.
Seem a little nervous, though.
Well, when... when we
were together before,
it was, you know, magical.
It just...
That was a long time ago.
Have you talked to her
about your fears?
- No.
- Men.
You are incapable of communicating
with someone you care about,
but have no problem
being explicit with some
stranger in a thong.
Oh. Oh, there he is.
Scratch-off guy.
Right before we went
upstairs for a private.
That is a nice, clear image.
We should be able to get a match
off facial recognition.
So, I, like... cracked the case?
Yes, you did.
Cool.
I'll walk you out.
Well, if you ever
wanna come by the club,
I'll give you a free lap dance.
Oh, thanks. That's very sweet.
We should probably just keep
this professional, though.
Okay.
Hey, man.
- Hey.
- Hey, I, uh...
I just want to say sorry for earlier.
I-I know things got a little
out of hand, you know?
It's pretty normal for me, but, uh,
I know you don't know me
that well, so...
You were going through
some stuff, so it's okay.
Like I said, I just, uh...
I just wanted to say sorry, and, uh...
And I did, so...
Alright.
Hey. Where are you staying?
I'm renovating a house on Beechwood.
You're welcome to use the guest room.
Oh, it's okay, man. I'm staying
at the Starlight Motel.
Plus, I gotta catch this bus to
Tempe in the morning, so...
Oh. I love Tempe. I did the, uh...
The Ironman competition there twice.
Oh, cool.
I've never been to the gym.
Uh, Pete, this is Chastity.
Chastity, Pete.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Um... do you wanna, like,
go get, uh, sushi or something?
Yeah. Okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Sick. Alright.
Hey, man, uh... you think
I could have some money
for that sushi date?
Yeah.
Thank you, man.
It's... It's L.A. sushi.
Don't worry about paying me back.
I won't. Have a good one.
That was weird. Me and him. Huh?
Stay out of trouble. If you can.
This is serious.
They found a gun in your car.
Well, you know how dangerous
this city can be.
A woman has to be able
to protect herself.
Mom, where did you even get the gun?
Christian.
The... The tennis instructor?
Well, we're dating now.
Don't say it.
I know what you're gonna say.
He likes me for me.
- It's not my money.
- Mom, come on.
Don't tell Angela
about Christian, please.
I don't want him to get in trouble.
Promise me, now.
Yes. I promise.
Lawrence. Oh, how nice to see you.
Patrice. Wesley.
- It's been far too long.
- Uh-huh.
You called the family lawyer?
I thought I was gonna handle this.
Oh. Oh, sweetie, I love you,
but, you work above
an Ethiopian restaurant.
And... you need a "real" lawyer.
I knew you'd understand.
Well?
My mom fired me.
- Ouch.
- Mm.
Did she say where she got the gun?
Yeah, but it's privileged.
I can't tell you.
Well, she's got to give the guy up.
Ballistics came back.
The gun in her car was used in
an armed robbery six months ago.
Homeowner was shot.
She's looking at accessory
after the fact.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
Hi.
Coat.
Something to drink?
Sure.
Your place looks great.
Oh, thank you.
Hope you like white.
Did someone punch you?
Yes. Um... I have had a day.
Do you want to talk about it?
If I start talking about it,
the whole night's gonna be about that,
and I want tonight to be about us.
So, what do I do?
The smart thing would be to get
Nevin to launder the money.
Use him as a CI to roll up
Marquel and his whole crew.
Um, Nevin's trying to go straight.
We'd be destroying that.
Yes, in order to put some
pretty bad people behind bars.
Look, it's a tough call, but...
You're gonna have to get used to
making those as a sergeant.
- The scores are in?
- The list just arrived.
You're number 8 out of 140.
Yes! I knew it.
Congratulations... Sergeant Bradford.
Not a sergeant yet.
At eight on the list,
it'll probably take six months or so.
Actually, there's a position
opening in North Hollywood.
The captain there owes me a big favor.
If you want, I can make it happen.
You'd start in two weeks.
T-Two weeks?
Uh... Uh, can I think
about this overnight?
Yeah, of course.
But there's no guarantee
you'll get a better opportunity,
if you pass this up.
Uh, more wine?
No, I am... good.
And the food was to your satisfaction?
- It was great.
- Excellent.
This is weird, isn't it?
No.
- Yes.
Yes, it's weird.
You know what? I-I
got some advice today,
from a...
Sort of a relationship expert,
and I think we should try it.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I'm gonna tell you
- exactly what I'm thinking.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Is that even possible?
- I'm...
W-Well, here it goes.
I'm gonna give it a try.
Okay.
When we were together...
It was so...
Easy.
It was so good.
And now, here we are, 20 years later,
and I'm...
Worried that maybe I'm trying to
recapture something that
could potentially
already be gone forever.
Does that sound crazy?
No. I mean, I-I...
- Feel the same way.
- Okay.
Because I really like you, Grace.
I like having you as my friend.
I really like having you in my life,
and I am terrified of
screwing that up again.
Is this...
A mistake, trying to open this door?
I don't know.
I mean, maybe.
But, um...
But what?
I really...
Want you to kiss me right now.
What was that?
Someone just stole my inheritance.
Shouldn't you call it in or something?
No.
Pretty sure I know who did it.
Yeah, I've been here all night.
What a completely natural way
to answer a door.
Oh. Hey, John.
Hi, Chastity.
- You know her?
- Yeah. Long story.
Chastity, have you been
with Pete all night?
- Yes.
- Did you at any point in time
- witness him stealing a car?
- Oh, yeah.
- I for sure saw him do that.
- Mm.
I don't lie to a cop for a guy
until at least the third date.
Why don't you and I go for a walk?
O... kay. Yeah.
Thank you.
So, you gonna arrest me now?
No. We have to talk.
- What? There's nothing to talk about.
- Our dad is dead,
and I don't know what to do with that,
and I got a feeling you don't either,
but maybe together,
we could figure something out.
Alright, maybe that could help.
- You know?
- Yes.
- My head is spinning around right now.
- Exactly.
And if you're anything like me,
you've got to be wondering,
why would he leave this car to me?
Yeah, I mean, you know...
We did work on it every day
after school, you know?
He would save up money
and try and get all the parts,
slowly build it up.
I mean, it took four years
to build the whole car
and then two to get it
to look like this.
At least you had those moments
with him, you know?
It's more than I got.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about that. I, um...
I think maybe he was
a little over-the-top
and overcompensated with me
because of how he bolted out on you.
It wasn't all good, though, you know?
Like, he came to my games,
but, like, he drank a lot,
and by the seventh inning,
he was, like, trashed
and embarrassed me
in front of my friends.
- You know?
- Doesn't sound very fun.
He gave me my first beer when I was 13
and then my first joint when I was 15.
So, I turned out great.
I grew up thinking
I did something wrong.
You know, if he loved me,
he wouldn't have left, right?
I'd stay up late at night,
listening to my mom,
cry herself to sleep,
coming up with crazy plans
how I was gonna track him down
and, I guess, win him back?
But now I'm thinking...
I dodged a bullet.
You dodged a huge bullet.
Yeah.
Still love him, though.
- Is that weird?
- No, that's not weird.
It's human.
You know what? You should have the car.
- What?
- Yeah, man, it's what he wants.
We should honor it, right?
- Are you sure about this?
- Plus,
I know I'm nuts and everything,
but I'll figure it out you know,
maybe me giving you this is, uh...
My closure, or whatever they call it.
I don't know if it's what Dad intended,
but by leaving me the car,
he actually connected me to you,
- so...
- Oh.
- Stay in touch, Pete.
- Yeah.
Just come... come visit.
You can make sure she's running right.
Deal.
Oh.
I have something for you.
Come on. I...
Come on.
That's not...
I figured, you know, maybe...
Pop the lid.
I figured, maybe, you know...
- Oh, you really don't have to...
- Hey, man.
It's our dad.
You deserve to have half, right?
Uh...
Look at that. He's a chunky guy.
- Yeah.
- Get a lot of that.
Alright.
- Got some more beer.
- Oh, that's right.
Hey, do you, uh...
Do you wanna come in for a-a nightcap?
I'm gonna braid her hair
and watch a-a fight.
Very sweet. We really do have to go.
- I have to be at the hospital early.
- So early.
- Oh.
- Cool, cool.
Okay, well, it was
very nice meeting you.
And, uh...
- Cheers.
- Do we... Do we hug?
- Yeah. Hell yeah.
- Alright.
Thanks for not arresting me.
Yeah. Stay out of trouble.
I will.
Aww. I like him.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I just can't believe I have a brother.
Half!
We're half-brothers.
Sorry, the walls are thin.
Brother.
So, um... I guess...
We're driving ourselves home.
- Yeah.
Not exactly how I pictured the evening.
I'm sorry for spoiling our date.
You kidding me?
I mean, this goes down in
the unforgettable column.
Well, um...
Lest we forget,
before all this happened...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...I think we were interrupted.
I think we were right about...
- Mm.
- ...here.
- What's in the bucket?
- Half my dad.
Oh.
Like I said... unforgettable.
See you soon.
Yes, you will.
Bye.
Hey, Marquel.
Can we talk for a minute?
Unless you gotta get permission first.
Nah, man. I'm good.
You here to threaten me,
Officer Bradford?
"Stay away from Nevin or else"?
No. We both know you don't scare.
So, what? You here to play
to my better angel?
Yeah, something like that.
See, here I thought
you were a hard case,
the man who put Keon in Pelican Bay.
Nevin did his time.
He gave your crew a decade of his life.
Took the fall like a good soldier.
Let him walk away.
And what's that do for my rep?
Lettin' people slide?
"Reputation is an idle
and most false imposition,"
"oft got without merit,"
"and lost without deserving."
You have lost no reputation at all
"unless you repute yourself
such a loser."
"Othello."
That was a nice pull,
but Shakespeare didn't know nothing
about running a gang
in the 21st century.
You don't want to go down this road.
Trust me.
Ain't no off-ramp here, Bradford.
See, I got plans for Nevin.
There's nothing you can do to stop 'em.
- What do we do now?
- I don't know.
We made our play, and we failed.
Wow, I never thought I'd
see you give up that easily.
You got a path to victory, Boot,
I'm all ears.
No, I don't, but you're the king
of subversive tests and tricks.
There's got to be some way to win
by coming at this sideways.
Harper, Nolan.
So,
Rampart picked up that scratch-off guy,
from the strip club video.
Tucker Novak?
Is that the guy you put a BOLO out on?
- Yes, sir.
- Then, yes.
He's in Cell 3.
- I'm innocent.
- Of what?
Of whatever y'all
about to accuse me of.
You went to the Red Angel
strip club two nights ago.
Nope.
- Can I have that?
- No.
You stole those tickets
from the liquor store on Pico,
and then you killed the owner.
Whoa! I had nothing to do with that.
And I sure as hell didn't kill anybody.
Then who did?
I want diplomatic immunity.
Yeah, see, my father...
He was born in Spain,
and they're members of NATO... I think.
So... Yeah. I want diplomatic immunity.
Okay. You got it.
- Wait. Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Spanish father means you are solid.
Awesome. Alright, check this out.
My boy Colt gave me
a call the other day,
said he needed help scratching
off 500 lottery tickets.
But, hey, he didn't mention
no murdered woman.
And he just let you keep the winners?
I mean, only the small ones,
like I gave that stripper.
No, he kept the big one.
The big Kahuna, worth 250 grand.
- And where can we find Colt?
- I don't know.
He told his roommates he was moving out
once he scratched off the big winner,
and last I heard of him,
he was still trying
to cash in the ticket.
Lottery doesn't pay out prizes
that size at convenience stores.
Either you have to mail it in
or go up to Sacramento.
I'll call Sacramento PD, have
them sit on the lottery office.
Uh, what about me?
Uh, you're under arrest for
accessory after the fact.
But what about my immunity?
So, bad news.
Wesley.
You'll never believe...
I met the most fascinating
people in here last night.
Uh-huh.
Lawrence, give us a minute.
Well, we're discussing
my legal strategy, dear.
He does DUIs for rich kids,
which is why you spent
the night in jail.
This is a criminal matter.
You need a criminal lawyer.
Okay, thanks, Lawrence.
I know why you want
to protect Christian,
but you do not understand
who he really is.
I ran a background search.
He's been to prison for armed robbery,
and the gun he gave you...
He used it in a crime after he got out.
He shot someone.
They almost died.
God, I had no idea.
He took advantage of you,
but you will be charged in his crime
unless you tell Angela
that he gave you the gun,
so that she can go arrest him.
Christian Roberts,
we need to talk to you.
Damn. I was really hoping
he wouldn't run.
Told you not to eat that meatball sub.
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
Why are you wet?
I don't want to talk about it.
7-Adam-07, send additional
units to our location.
- Foot pursuit... lost visual.
- Wait! Wait, wait!
- Get on your stomach.
- Dispatch, cancel request.
- Suspect in custody, Code 4.
- Hands behind your back.
Nolan.
Colt Henry,
he just tried to cash
in a stolen scratch-off
at a store across from Union Station.
He must be trying to grab
a train to Sacramento.
- Feel like some overtime?
- Hell yeah.
- Check the board. Where is it?
- There.
Train to Sacramento, platform three.
Okay, that is in 20 minutes.
- Let's split up.
- Hey, hey, listen.
So far, this case has been
strippers and idiots,
but this guy...
He killed a woman in cold blood.
- Don't lose sight of that.
- I won't.
Attention, please.
This is the last call for
Amtrak Pacific Surfliner,
train number 579,
en route to San Diego.
I went to the far end of the concourse.
No sign of Colt.
Passengers for Amtrak
Pacific Surfliner number 579,
please proceed to track one.
Police. Turn around very slowly.
- Move, move, move.
- He's got a gun!
He's got a gun!
Move.
Where is he?
- I don't know. Did you see him?
- No.
Someone help me!
Go. Go.
Back up.
Don't do this.
- Get back, lady.
- Not gonna happen.
Show me your hands,
and they better be empty.
I didn't mean to kill that woman.
She grabbed for my gun.
Why'd she do that?
There was only a few hundred
in the register.
There's nothing we can do
about that now,
but you can control, what happens next.
My whole life, I never won anything.
But I got that big ticket now,
and I want to cash it in.
It's worthless, Colt.
Just like the one you tried
to cash in across the street.
They were all cancelled,
the moment they were reported stolen.
This is... It's not fair.
I never won anything in my life.
But I won that.
You... You can't take
that away from me.
The only thing you
are winning is a body bag
if you don't give up right now.
You think I care?
I'm looking at life in prison.
So...
I'm calling the shots here.
So, turn around and walk away.
Right now.
- Or else...
- Or else what?!
Your last act in life is
gonna be murdering a child?
The world doesn't
owe you anything, Colt.
Not a winning lottery ticket,
not a happy childhood.
Nothing.
We all got to do the best
with what we got,
and for you, right now,
that means giving up
and getting on the ground.
O-Okay.
I'm pulling my hand out.
I let go of the gun.
It's...
D-Don't shoot me.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Oh.
Suspect in custody. Code 4.
Thank you.
I handled your father's
leaving very badly,
and his death,
and I've spent the past few years
just feeling sorry for myself.
I'm...
Look, it's my fault, too,
for not being around more.
- I've been a little selfish.
- A little?
Sorry.
Look, I promise to try harder to...
Get over myself,
be there for you.
And the good news is
the DA's not pressing charges
against you,
so we can all use this as, um...
A learning experience.
Genius move, making Nevin's
the go-to donut shop for the LAPD.
Yeah, Marquel wouldn't dare
launder money here now.
North Hollywood's lucky to have
a sergeant like you coming in.
Actually, I, uh...
I told Grey that I'm not
interested in moving up,
just yet.
What, are you holding out for Malibu?
Tim Bradford finishes what he starts.
I haven't finished training you yet.
No. You haven't.
You are gonna move up at
some point, though, right?
Because I put a lot of time
into those books on tape.
Yeah.
♪ -
"I had a great time last night!"
No exclamation point.
"Great time last night."
"Let's do it again... soon."
"Let's do it again soon?"
"Let's do it again soon."
Why don't people just call anymore?
Hey. I was...
I-I was just trying to text you.
Trying?
Well, uh, there's an art to it.
I'm just messing with you.
I just spent the last half-hour
rewriting a text to you,
and then I just...
You know, I, um...
I figured that I'd just call.
Well, I'm glad you did.
What was that?
Uh, that was the sound
of my inheritance, being stolen again.
- Can I call you right back?
- Sure.
Tell Pete I said hi.
Will do.
Yo.
I thought you said you
needed me to have the car
so you could have closure.
Yeah, no, I-I don't really
believe in closure.
Plus, Chastity loves the car.
- Hi, John.
- Hi, Chastity.
So, Pete, listen,
I-I know you don't believe in closure,
but I do, and you've given me some...
Closure I never thought I would have.
So thank you.
Anytime, man.
Hey, you think you could do me a favor
and maybe mail me the keys?
'Cause I had to hot-wire
this in your driveway.
Sure thing.
Stay safe, Pete. Keep in touch.
You got it.
Hey, man,
having a brother cop is pretty sick.
That means a-a lot to me, Pete.
Even from you.