♪ I put on my shoes
Just a minute.
- ♪ 'Cause I'm comin' for you
- HENRY: Dad!
Henry!
Dad.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Abigail had a buttload of flyer miles,
so we, uh, flew out to surprise you.
Oh, my God.
Abigail,
it's so nice to finally meet you.
It's great to meet you, too.
The videos didn't do it justice.
This place is a wreck.
I think it's awesome.
It's like a faded beauty queen
that you're bringing back to life.
Oh, wow. You are quickly
becoming my favorite.
Mine, too.
Uh, we have some good news.
Exciting. Lay it on me.
I'm pregnant.
Kidding. I'm... I'm kidding.
We're engaged.
Sorry about the pregnant thing.
I-I thought it would soften the blow.
Abigail, uh, that is, um, is beautiful.
That's a beautiful ri...
I hope you didn't, uh,
spend your tuition money.
I used the money that I
was saving to go to Europe,
because Abigail's the journey
I want to spend the rest of my life on.
- Aww.
That's so... That is...
That's so...
Does your mom know?
She thought it would be best
if I told you in person.
Uh, yeah. She also recommended
that we quickly follow the news
- with some electrolytes.
- That is...
hilarious and entirely unnecessary.
Have you set a date?
Not yet, but we're, uh,
we're talking about June.
Isn't it exciting?
It's so exciting.
Crap!
I feel like Goldilocks,
except instead of "too hot"
or "too cold,"
every guy I date is either,
you know, "too frat-bro,"
or "too stick me with the check"
because you are never going
to finish that screenplay
"working on your abs."
Let's face it,
I am never going to find someone.
Yeah, not if you keep looking
in hipster clubs and hot yoga studios.
- Ah.
- What you need is a grown man.
I would just settle for
a decent pickup line.
Oh, thank God, okay.
Wow. We gotta go.
Thank you.
Mom.
What are you doing here?
Your father and I are getting divorced.
Hi, Mrs. Chen. I'm so sorry.
Oh, Jackson, sweetheart, thank you.
What happened?
I don't want to talk about it.
Okay, is this like the time
that you didn't talk to Dad for a week
because he forgot your birthday?
I said I don't want to talk about it.
Oh. I'm sure my back will be fine.
I assume you have extra bedding.
Oh. Mom, you're not
sleeping on the couch.
I'll get you a hotel.
Nonsense. No, I'll take the couch.
Mrs. Chen, you can take my room.
Such a sweet boy.
Would you mind putting this in my room?
I have to get ready for work.
Is that really what you're wearing?
Nice groupings.
Thanks.
So, I need yesterday's
after-action reports.
I will have them for you
at the end of shift.
You mean when today's are due?
I know you're used to being
out on the edge, all alone,
but paperwork's part of the gig here.
Copy that. I will get caught up quick.
Officer Nolan's not the only one
being evaluated, Detective.
I know you got the golden ticket,
but you got to do the work.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Henry got engaged.
Yeah, he just turned 20.
I know. It's too young.
Didn't you get married around then?
That's not the point.
So, I just talked to my dad.
Apparently, he only brought home
a bagel for himself.
- He did not bring one for my mom.
- That's why she left?
Bagel that broke the camel's back.
- Maybe it's for the best.
- Oh, God, no.
Separately, they will make
my life twice as miserable.
I have to get them back together.
- Just...
- Morning.
She is definitely warming up to me.
So, Officer West,
- can you tell us what a "friendly" is?
- Yes, sir.
A "friendly" is another term
for a Confidential Informant.
Correct. And Confidential Informants
can be an incredibly useful tool.
They're definitely tools.
Are you saying you don't
use them, Officer Bradford?
No, sir. Just saying
that they're lying liars
who lie and they need to be dominated,
never allowed to think
they're in control.
- Officer Lopez, you agree?
- No, sir.
C.I.s are most useful when they think
they're part of the team.
You're both wrong.
Please, school us, Detective.
C.I.s are just people trying to get by.
Some are psychopaths who play ball
because it's the best available option,
some are people in over their heads
who cling to you desperately
as a way out of trouble.
Treating them all the same
is a mistake.
Well, it's time to put
these theories to the test.
Nolan, Chen, part of the second
phase of your training
is developing your first C.I.
See, you've known this day was coming,
so I'm confident that you have
a plan of action in place.
But be forewarned...
you will be evaluated on the arrests,
generated by your C.I.,
as well as their long-term viability.
So, choose wisely.
Alright, that's it.
Be safe.
Sir, you have to let West participate.
- Do I?
- You've read my daily evals.
His work is as strong
as it's ever been,
and this is an opportunity to prove
that he's ready to move on.
It's a big swing, Officer West.
Screw it up...
it's likely to be the last nail.
You sure you want to take that chance?
Yes, sir.
Alright. You're in.
- Good?
- Thank you, sir.
You are the greatest T.O.
in the history of T.O.s.
- Here you go.
- You got a choice to make...
be conservative or be bold.
Tim's gonna make sure
Lucy bags a workhorse
for her first C.I.
- Nothing flashy.
- And Harper?
My guess is she'll
let Nolan drive it...
sink or swim on his own.
You think we should go big.
It's the riskiest move,
but the one that will get you
into short sleeves quicker.
But a big fish takes time,
and if you fail to recruit him,
you run the real risk of hitting
the week's end without someone.
And Grey'll bounce me for sure.
Screw it.
- Let's go for it.
- That's the spirit.
- You got a candidate?
- Yeah.
A guy the Feds use,
but you should hit an ATM
on the way over.
This guy's not cheap.
Hey, Nick. Heading home?
My bed awaits.
I just had an armed robbery suspect
in the box all night, I'm fried.
- How're you?
- I just found out
my son got engaged.
Whoa. I-Isn't he, like, 12?
- 20.
- Right.
- You like the girl?
- Abigail.
She seems very sweet.
Just met her for the first time
this morning.
Also 20.
You run her through the system?
A background check?
No, it's against the rules,
and it's just...
- wrong.
- If it were me,
I'd want to know.
See you tomorrow, well...
Technically tonight.
- Right.
- Here you go.
Oh.
What are we doing here, Boot?
As you're aware,
pawn shops are required by law
to notify law enforcement
if they believe someone
is trying to pawn off stolen property.
I pulled city records.
This shop has never called us.
Either the owner is a saint, or...
Or he's dealing with
a lot of stolen goods.
Exactly. Making them the perfect
candidate for my first C.I.
Don't get too cocky, Officer Chen.
Recruiting a reliable C.I.
is hard work.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, my parents are...
Uh, never mind.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- What can I do for you?
- We're doing interviews
for the detectives in Robbery-Homicide.
Has anyone tried to pass off
stolen items recently?
No, absolutely not.
How do you know they're not
stolen before you buy them?
'Cause I'm a very good judge of people.
What's your impression of me?
That you're a very distrustful woman.
Detective Harrison, it's Officer Chen.
Yeah, we're gonna need you
to send Code Enforcement
down to High-Life...
- That's not necessary.
- Hold on, Craig.
If you're aboveboard,
there shouldn't be a problem, right?
Okay.
There may be a few things
that are from questionable sources.
Nice job.
Great, let's see it,
and don't give me any of that
low-end misdemeanor crap.
Woman brought this in yesterday,
and it's not the first designer bag
she's brought me.
Mm. Retails for what?
- Five grand?
- Six.
What are you looking for?
These high-end bags
have serial numbers sewn in.
They're registered
to the original buyer.
Yeah.
Bingo.
Hey, there.
Bianca, right?
Do I know you?
No, I have this acquaintance
in narcotics.
He, uh... Well, actually,
I installed a new
kitchen island for him.
Anyway, I was telling him
I need a low-level drug mule
that I can flip into a C.I.,
and he mentioned you.
Bianca!
Why are you running?
We know where you live.
- She got drugs in her bag.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
- Bianca, is that right?
Easy.
Okay. Easy. I got you.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Relax, okay?
- Heroin?
- Yep.
Enough to put Bianca in prison
for the rest of
her child-bearing years.
Do you want to go to prison, Bianca?
No.
Then you're gonna
have to flip on your boss,
and depending on how that goes,
you're gonna become an informant...
my informant...
pointing us to more drug dealers
and suppliers.
I can't do that. They'll kill me.
And we'll protect you.
He can't promise you that.
You need to be clear with a C.I.
You'll do your best
to treat them right,
look out for them, but you're not God,
and you're not with them 24/7.
Understood.
And thank you.
So, those are your choices, Bianca.
You can go to jail or you can help us.
What's it gonna be?
You're gonna get me killed.
Hey, if anything happens,
we'll be just across the courtyard.
Your boss usually punctual?
For a drug dealer.
Look, don't be a hero.
Just give him the bag,
you take your fee, you walk away,
just like you've done
hundreds of times.
All done.
Talk in a normal voice.
Tell the man at the funeral home
that I want to be turned into a tree.
Make sure they don't put me in a box.
I get claustrophobic.
Bianca, I promise...
...if anything goes wrong,
we will be there.
Can I go to the bathroom
with this stuff?
Sure.
And don't listen.
Hey, girl.
I thought...
Yeah, don't do that.
He'll be here in a minute.
Let's get set.
Damn it.
So, I was thinking
we could start small,
see what type of intel you have.
Hold your roll, Officer.
The only reason I'm talking to you
is 'cause you paid my greens' fee.
Truth is, I work exclusively
with the Feds.
They pay way better than the LAPD.
100 grand last year,
for intel on nine high-profile felonies.
Now, you gonna match that?
While the LAPD can't beat
that kind of number,
your FBI handler isn't gonna give you
the kind of personal attention
that I will.
He offering massages?
There's got to be something or someone
that's bothering you.
My ex-wife is screwing
this Pakistani guy.
Owns a used car dealership
on Van Nuys...
definitely moving stolen cars.
And why do you care?
My ex torched all my Armani
suits on the way out.
So... you take something
she cares about away from her...
I'll play ball.
He's here.
He went into the room.
She's going in.
What's going on?
It's fine.
Let it play out.
See?
All good.
Arms up.
- Hey, I don't get to keep that?
- Sorry.
Alright, well, let's go get this guy.
Okay, just sit here, relax.
The hard part's done. Great job.
Freeze.
- Police!
- Hands up.
Drop the bag.
Interlace your fingers
behind your head.
Don't move.
Decent bust, rookie.
Bianca?
Hey.
Harper, I need Narcan
in the room right now.
Bianca. Hey.
Stay with me, alright?
Where'd she get the drugs?
Must have had a leftover from the deal.
- Easy, easy, easy. I got you.
- Control, 7-Adam-15...
We need an ambulance
at the Dollar Motel on Olympic.
Female, 25, head injury and overdose.
Mrs.?
Uh, these officers
want to speak with you.
Cool.
What's up?
We're here about some stolen property.
Do you recognize this bag?
Yeah, I've got one just like it.
We believe this one is yours.
It was at a pawn shop.
We matched the serial number
to your credit card purchase.
Hilda!
- Yes, Missus?
- You're fired.
- What?
- Please, don't make a scene.
It'll just upset me.
Uh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey.
What's going on? What'd you do?
Hilda's been robbing us.
I have not.
Who are you?
This is my daughter, Olivia.
Stepdaughter.
You were 9 when I was born.
Olivia, do you know anything
about a stolen handbag?
The description
the pawn shop owner gave us
fits you more than your housekeeper.
Yeah.
Yeah, I took it.
But she has so many,
she didn't even notice.
You are such a brat.
You're such a parasite.
Don't talk to your mother that way.
- You are not my mother!
- Okay, calm down.
Calm down. Both of you, okay?
I want her arrested.
It's the only way she'll learn.
Are you sure that's what
her father would want?
Her father wants whatever I tell him.
Six stolen cars.
Grey's gonna be impressed,
but we still need to get Hickey
officially signed up.
On it.
- Yo.
- Mr. Hickey,
it's Officer West.
Your intel was spot-on.
We've impounded six stolen vehicles
and arrested Mr. Fawad Chandio.
That's awesome.
Nicky's gonna cry for a week.
So, it means you're on board?
- I'm a man of my word.
- Great.
We'll just need you to come into
the station and
fill out some paperwork.
Yeah, you got it.
She'll be okay.
We're gonna keep her overnight
and monitor her for a concussion.
Thanks.
You know, I still don't understand,
how she overdosed while in custody.
I left her alone
while we made the bust.
I just... I feel terrible.
You two used to date.
- What?
- No... What?
No. Ye... Well, yes, but...
I'm not judging. You're very pretty.
Thank you.
Well, I'm not uncomfortable at all,
and I think we should
probably go, right?
- Nice meeting you.
- You, too.
So, are you counting Bianca
as your first C.I.?
Shouldn't I?
Got a solid arrest off her intel.
Yeah, but Grey's also evaluating
long-term prospects and
she doesn't have any.
Right.
Ever bother you
- using people like that?
- Nope.
The drugs she's moving
kill people every day.
She's not a saint.
- She's a criminal.
- Right.
You didn't answer my question.
You checking that box and moving on?
No. I need to find a real C.I.
Good answer.
So, where's your mom?
Uh...
she died last year.
Cervical cancer.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Thanks.
So, I left school to be with my dad,
only to find out
that he'd been hooking up
with that trophy skank
while my mom was in hospice.
Yeah, well, you shouldn't
go home tonight,
once you process out.
I don't have a choice.
Daisy convinced my dad
to hold on to the money my mom left me
until after I graduate from college.
Can he do that?
I don't know.
I can't really afford a lawyer
to find out.
Look, you are in a bad situation,
but stealing, it's...
it's not gonna make it better.
What will?
Am I crazy, or was that way too easy?
It was a little easy.
On the other hand, you showed Hickey
that you can get things done.
Lopez, West, my office.
I'm gonna call you back.
So, this is Special Agent
Wyck Bird from the FBI.
He says you're trying
to poach his informant.
Wait, sir, I-I can explain.
Save your breath.
Hickey's mine.
Guy's a clearinghouse
of high-value intel.
Bureau doesn't need the LAPD
messing with our meal ticket.
I didn't know informants
came with exclusive rights.
Now you do.
He called you to get us to back off.
And he used us to do him a solid.
Now he's kicking us to the curb.
He said you were hassling him.
Stop hassling him.
Or else.
Sergeant.
Special Agent.
- Sir...
- Save it.
I told you what would happen
if you swung and missed.
You're dismissed.
So, you got a game plan
for running down a new C.I.?
Not yet. Any suggestions?
Oh, that's right.
You're not here to teach me.
Ms. Harper?
Hi.
Uh... um, what are you doing here?
You didn't sign your petition.
Right. I'm sorry.
- I, um...
- Excuse me. Hi. John Nolan.
Hi. Good to meet you. My name's...
None of his business.
Um... I'm gonna take 10,
you figure out a next step.
Come on.
This is bleak.
There's nowhere else we can meet?
It's private.
I don't want anyone here
knowing my business.
Okay.
We got lucky with the judge.
He believes whenever possible,
it's important for the mother
to be part of the child's life.
Okay.
That's... That's great.
How's it going here?
Uh, it's fine.
It's a lot harder than
I thought it would be.
What is?
Being normal.
You're doing great.
The better hours, the new apartment...
the judge will be impressed.
I hope so.
'Cause if I don't see my daughter soon,
I am gonna lose my mind.
Hey.
- Hey, back at it already?
- Yeah, couldn't sleep.
Just laid there,
staring at the ceiling.
Figured screw it...
I'll clock in early.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yeah, sure.
I need to recruit a C.I.
My first one... she O.D.'d on me.
Oh.
You know what? You need a forger.
They're at the hub of
all criminal activity.
Tell Logan in Commercial Crimes
I asked him to throw
some names your way.
You are a life-saver. Thank you.
- Hey, John?
- Yeah?
I ran a background check
on Henry's girlfriend.
Don't worry, I tied it
to an open investigation.
No one will ever know.
- I-I didn't ask...
- I know.
I know.
But if I were you...
I'd want to take a look
at what's inside.
What's that?
Nothing, what was your thing about?
- Nothing.
- Great. Lunch?
Great.
So, what do I do?
Open it.
It's about Henry's safety.
You should see what it says.
- Dad.
- Hey!
Oh, my God, you guys are all
about the surprises this week.
Hi, I'm Abigail... Henry's fiancée.
Yeah, I know.
I just really love saying that, so...
- Congratulations.
- Yeah, that's awesome.
What do you want to eat?
- I'll come with you.
- Okay. Good.
- We'll be back.
- Right.
May I take your order?
They look so happy. I want that.
- Baby steps.
- Right.
Well, first, I have to get
my mother out of our apartment.
- Yes.
- They really do seem happy.
Would I be sabotaging that
by reading what's in this envelope,
or is that the illusion,
and Abigail's just a time bomb
waiting to go off?
So, what's the next step
on the C.I. front?
Forger.
- Who'd you get that from?
- No one.
Detective Armstrong.
Cheating on me with another detective?
I had no idea we were exclusive.
Okay, we got too much,
but everything looked so good.
Perfect timing, uh, uh,
Henry, Abigail,
this is Nyla Harper,
my training officer.
Nyla Harper, Henry is my son.
And I know what you're thinking...
far too young to have a 20-year-old.
Nope. Nice to meet you both.
- Let's get to work.
- Right.
Um, that's all you.
See you guys at home.
So, you got a place to start,
or are we Googling "forger"?
- Ooh, I got a list.
- Mm.
What did you think of Abigail?
She seemed nice. Why?
No reason.
They just got engaged.
Oh, good for them.
Yeah.
- No?
- Yeah.
No, I'm...
- Yeah, it's great.
- Oh.
No, eh, eh...
- Drunk driving...
- Knock, knock.
Officers.
Can I help you?
Beat it.
This is your place?
Yes, sir.
- You do head shots?
- We sure do.
What about fake IDs?
No, sir.
Lying to a police officer...
that's a crime, isn't it?
Not as big a one as forgery
and counterfeiting
government documents.
Just trying to make a living.
These cellphone cameras
have killed my business.
- Am I going to jail?
- Well, that depends.
Maybe I can help you if you help me.
I don't know what that means.
Do you want me to bribe you?
- How much...
- No. No. No.
That's not... Okay. How do I...
I need someone with their ear
to the street...
- You're gonna be his snitch.
- My snitch.
We're gonna take all this
stolen property as evidence.
We're gonna book it and tie it
to an unknown suspect.
If you screw us,
we will suddenly know
who the suspect is,
get a warrant, and come arrest you.
We are looking for leads
on serious felons here, okay?
Not teenagers trying to buy alcohol.
You making papers for anyone
like that right now?
I did get a heads-up
about a big job that might come my way.
Fake identities, driver's licenses,
passports, the works.
As soon as you get details,
you call me.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Congrats.
You have a real C.I.
I'm on my way home now, Mom.
Yes, I got the shopping list
you texted.
There's no milk because
I'm lactose intolerant,
remember?
Mom, I gotta go.
Opal, what's up?
Thank you.
- Tim.
- Yo?
Olivia showed up at Opal's pawn shop
with more of her stepmom's stuff,
but she didn't want money this time.
She wanted a gun.
Police!
7-Adam-19... shots fired
at our location, send backup.
I hate you!
Drop the gun!
You turned my dad against me!
Olivia, drop the gun!
- She ruined everything!
- Now!
Stand up. Keep your hands up.
Do not move.
You've made this so much worse.
Come on.
You are gonna pay for those bags.
Ma'am, stay right there.
What's going on?
What the hell are you doing here?
I came to get the rest of my things.
Wh... Are you okay?
Officers, would you like to see
where Mrs. hides all her drugs?
Yes.
Yes, we would.
I'm home!
About time.
It's way past your curfew.
Oh, very funny.
You have a lot of tattoos.
Oh, yeah. You like 'em?
Each one signifies
a meaningful moment of my life.
I'm trying to talk Henry
into getting one.
I have no idea what I would get.
Yeah, well, that's a decision
that will last you a lifetime.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I see what you did there,
Is anyone hungry?
I can tell you're freaked out.
Don't be, okay?
- Okay.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's John.
I really hope I'm not, um...
stepping over the line here,
but I really have no one
to talk to about... anything
parenting-oriented.
Never mind. You know what?
I'll take care of this.
- Just forget I called.
- John, how can I help?
I'm having a parenting emergency.
Good thing I specialize
in emergency medicine.
Are you still at the hospital?
Yeah, for a couple more hours.
Could I come buy you a cup of coffee,
- ask you some questions?
- Of course.
Thank you.
I'm just gonna head right
back out for a little while.
- Okay.
- Oh, could you pick up some pie?
- Yeah, she loves pie.
- I love pie.
Sure.
I feel like a monster.
You're not a monster.
I mean, you're a father.
So, I should just open this up
right now and read it?
Absolutely not.
But it's my job to protect him.
It is your job to respect him,
and running secret
background check on the girl
he's in love with is not doing that.
Okay, but I didn't run this.
- Doesn't matter.
- No, no.
Of course not.
And yet I still can't
bring myself to throw it away.
What if you read it?
And then that way,
you could just tell me,
if she's a serial killer
or a mime.
No, but I will throw it out for you.
But...
It's the right thing.
Hey, if you want to know
something about Abigail,
you should just ask her.
You're right.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I messed up.
I tried to regain
all the ground I lost,
but it might have just cost me my job.
You know, Lucy would tell me about you,
at the academy,
how far ahead you were
from all your classmates.
Seems so long ago.
What happened to that Jackson?
What happened to that young man
I met at graduation?
So full of confidence.
A lifetime of expectations
crashed headlong into reality.
Well, "Sometimes you win,
sometimes you learn."
Freud?
Cat poster Lucy used
to have in her room.
You need to get back to the time
when you knew who you were,
not who you were trying to be.
Oh, my gosh.
You're absolutely right.
I can't start counting
up wins and losses
when the season's just begun.
Morning.
Where did the coffee cups go?
Oh, I moved them
next to the coffee maker.
I liked them by the dishwasher.
That's ridiculous.
It is more convenient.
Did... Did...
Did you rearrange the furniture?
Yes.
There's a better flow
in the room this way.
That's...
That's great.
You know what? Screw the FBI.
I'm gonna flip Hickey,
take him away from the Feds,
and show Grey that he's wrong about me.
That's a really bad idea...
but I love it.
- Yes.
- How you gonna pull it off?
Okay, I-I stopped by the men's
detention center on the way in,
spoke to Chandio, and it turns out,
he's not sleeping
with Hickey's ex-wife.
He's never even met her.
So, Hickey had another reason
to torpedo the stolen car ring.
Exactly. So, we find out what that is,
and we can use it to leverage Hickey.
They made contact last night.
Ordered, um, five full sets
of fake documents.
All young women?
Yeah.
- Human trafficking?
- Yeah.
Who's the buyer?
Cartel.
Not sure which one.
But they'll kill me if they
find out I'm talking to you.
Where's the exchange taking place?
Uh, Whiteman Airfield.
In two hours.
You sure he said noon?
Yeah, I wrote it down.
7-Adam-15...
all units stand by off-site.
Target is running late.
Hold position until further notice.
You think he's gonna show?
If there's one thing you can count on,
it's that criminals are always late.
What?
- Nothing.
- What?
Trent Silver.
Name of the lawyer,
you were talking to
at the precinct yesterday.
I checked the sign-in
sheet at the front desk.
Why would you do that?
I'm a cop.
Curiosity's part of
the job description.
So, he does family law?
He's none of your business.
My personal life is
none of your business.
Why you're back in uniform?
None of your business. Are we clear?
For now.
Son of a...
Didn't someone from the FBI
call and talk to you guys?
- I'm already taken.
- Yeah, about that.
After we swept up those stolen cars
and shut down that dealership...
And learned that you were lying
about the owner
sleeping with your ex...
It got us thinking.
So we did some digging,
and it seems that you paid
a visit to a few businesses
in that neighborhood yesterday evening.
Tried to use our show
of force as a means
to extort some
hardworking men and women.
We've got you on extortion.
We own you.
So, call the FBI and let them know
that you are booked
for the foreseeable future.
Okay.
Alright, sure.
But I need to know how much
you're gonna pay for tips.
- That's a fair question.
- Totally.
The answer is...
- Zero.
Hello?
- I read it.
- Read what?
Wait... the background check?
No. You threw that away. I saw you.
I couldn't help myself.
I mean, I dug it out of
the trash after you left.
No. Why?
You're supposed to be
the angel on my shoulder.
But I started thinking.
I mean, if this was my son,
what would I do?
And then the next thing I knew,
I was tearing it open
and reading what was inside.
I-Is it bad? What does it say?
Two years ago,
Abigail was charged with arson
and use of a caustic substance
against a former boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
Nolan. Heads up.
I have to go.
7-Adam-15... target has arrived.
Single black SUV. Wait for our signal.
Nice and easy.
Just go give them the documents.
Police! Hands where I can see them!
Get out of the car! Do it now!
No, please. You're making a mistake.
- Are you being held against your will?
- Not by him.
He's helping us escape.
Wait. Escape from who?
El Leon.
- Head of the Aquino Cartel?
- He's my husband,
and these woman "belong" to his men,
but we're finished,
putting up with the abuse.
You have to let us go.
Ugh.
- Who is that?
- It's my husband.
He keeps calling,
telling me to go back.
You brought your phone?
Guaranteed he's tracking that.
We gotta get out of here.
Get behind us.
7-Adam-15, converge on me. Code 3.
Anybody raises the gun
above their waist
gets a hollow point in the eye.
There's no need for that.
We're simply here to give
the ladies a ride home.
- You the husband?
- Nah.
I'm his attack dog.
Elena, why do you do this?
You know there's no place to go.
Get in the car. All of you.
- We won't.
- Oh, yes, you will.
No, they won't.
Huh. There's eight of us...
...and two of you.
Actually, there's
a whole lot more than two.
So, here's the new plan...
You, your boys
are gonna get back in your cars
and you're gonna drive away,
empty-handed.
I'd say you got about 20 seconds
before the cavalry arrives.
This isn't over, Elena.
We'll get to you soon enough.
Well, that was exciting.
I guess not for you.
That's probably
a regular Tuesday for you.
Oh, no, the pucker factor
was definitely at 11.
West!
Nolan, Chen, don't wander off.
- Special Agent Bird just called me...
- Look, Sergeant,
it was my decision to pursue Hickey
and try and steal him away
from the Feds.
Seems like you succeeded
from the way Bird was yelling.
Yes, sir.
Officer Lopez, is this
how you train your rookies?
To ignore the orders of federal agents?
Pretty much, sir.
Any day we can remind
our federal brethren
that we are their equals...
is a day worth living.
It appears you three successfully
recruited your first C.I.s,
and I'm impressed.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, Officer West?
Short sleeves, please.
Yes, sir.
Hey, why's your bag by the door?
Your father is on his way
to pick me up.
He apologized.
He just needed to miss me.
Oh.
He's downstairs.
Alright, sweetheart,
it's been a lovely visit.
Come by the office.
We can talk about why
you're not dating anyone.
Thank you, Jackson.
Bye, Mrs. Chen.
No wonder I can't find
a healthy relationship.
My dysfunctional parents are why
I am 28 and still single.
Are you sure that's why?
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I'm just saying
that your only real relationship
was with Nolan.
- Yep. I've known the whole time.
- Wait...
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- What? You think I'm stupid?
- No.
- Listen, you fell for a divorced guy
coming out of a 20-year marriage.
Okay? I-It was safe.
Never meant to last.
Come on. Let's go celebrate.
Tomorrow, my forearms
will be liberated.
It is pretty glorious.
Yeah, actually, how did you
get your parents to make up?
Oh. I got Wesley to call each of them
pretending to be a divorce lawyer,
telling them the costs of a divorce,
and that snapped them out of it
pretty quick.
- Well played.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
Will you please, please help me
get the furniture back to where it was.
- But it's better this way.
- I know.
But will you help me get it
back to the way it was?
Yes.
Oh.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Guys, there's something I need to say.
I know about the arson.
You ran a background check?
You knew she had a record?
Yeah, she told me on our third date.
I... can't believe you did that.
It's okay.
He... He did it to protect you.
No, I don't need protecting,
especially from you.
Do you want to know what happened?
If you want to tell me.
An ex-boyfriend posted
some videos on the Internet...
after we broke up.
Personal videos of us...
together.
He did it to get revenge,
and it worked.
He took something from me
I'll never get back.
I'm so sorry.
So, I went to his house...
and I... torched his car.
And I got arrested and he didn't.
Happy now?
Not in the least.
Abigail...
...I'm sorry my fear
overcame my judgement.
I, uh...
I can't take that back,
but I can promise you
it won't happen again.
That's good enough for me.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's great that that's behind us now,
because I really am pregnant.
I'm kidding. Again.
- Oh, my...
- Joke.
Geez.
Okay, we're gonna have
to work on the jokes, though.
'Cause I already have
a high-stress job,
and, uh... I think you're gonna
give me a heart attack.
Understood.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.MY-SUBS.com