WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Okay, here we are.
Thank you for being
our designated driver.
Oh, I figured you needed
to blow off a little steam
after the week you had.
Forget about being left back.
You just need to make
peace with being back
in long sleeves, I have.
No, you haven't.
No, I haven't.
Oh, guys.
911, what is your emergency?
This if off-duty officer
Jackson West, badge 33356.
I need a unit to my home
for an on-view suspect
dealing eleven-three.
I'm gonna cut around
the back side, cut 'em off.
Police. Get down on the ground,
keep your hands where I can see them.
Foot pursuit! Westbound in the alley!
Suspect's a male, white,
5'10", 200 pounds.
Suspect in custody.
Yo, you slinging dope
in my neighborhood?
Mr. Wilson?
Oh, hey, Jackson.
You know this guy?
Yeah, he's my landlord.
You ever heard of a Night General?
No, sir.
Night General Detectives.
They respond to any major crime scene
after normal business hours.
They work the case until it's assigned.
They have to be a master in everything
because they see everything.
- Sounds impressive.
- It is.
And most of them got
the attitude to go with it.
This my tour guide?
I thought you were
assigning me a rookie.
I am a rookie, sir. John Nolan.
Nick Armstrong.
Detective Armstrong
is our new Night Detective.
He asked for a patrol officer
to show him around,
help him get familiar
with our division.
Yeah, I just did a ten spot
up in the seven-seven,
so I don't know none of the
players in this part of town.
Hell, I don't know where
to get a decent cup of coffee.
Well, I got you covered on the coffee.
I'll do my best on the rest.
Fair enough.
Alright, it's roll call time.
You want to come?
Yeah. First day of school,
might as well meet the other kids.
Were you Night General
back at the seven-seven?
Yeah. Last five years.
After my wife died,
I found the nights the hardest,
- so I filled 'em.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Married?
- Divorced.
- Before or after you signed up?
- Before.
Part of the catalyst
to make the change.
Change is hard. I hate it, man.
- But here I am.
- Life is contradictory.
- Tell me about it.
- Settle down. Find a seat.
First up,
I'd like to congratulate
Officer Jackson West
on the fine pinch last night.
No crook is safe from Officer West,
not even his landlord.
- Letter of commendation?
- Change of address form.
Your apartment is now considered
a "house of ill repute."..
...and under asset seizure.
We need your new address by tomorrow,
even if it's Mama's house.
Alright.
This sharp-dressed man in the doorway
is Detective Nick Armstrong.
He'll be in the field after hours
for your detecting needs.
Yes, Officer Lopez?
Detective Armstrong,
on a scale of 1 to 10,
where 1 is "patrol friendly"
and 10 is "making us guard a cleared
crime scene"
in the pouring rain 'cause you get
"a power trip off of it,"
where do you stand?
- Lopez.
- No, it's alright, Sarge.
I appreciate a direct question.
A lot of cops take off the uniform,
they put on the suit.
Suddenly, they think they're better
than the officers in this room.
I'm not one of them.
Patrol is where it all happens.
It's fast, honest, pure, raw.
85% of all crimes are solved
at the patrol level.
So, the way I see it,
I am here to help you,
not the other way around.
And if that doesn't win you over,
I have five dozen of the finest
donuts in the break room.
That's all I'm saying.
Detective, you think you can
buy us with donuts?
Absolutely not.
Maybe rent you, though.
Okay, are we done?
Good, 'cause we're done.
Be safe out there.
Bradford, let me see you a sec.
Chief Williams added another book
to your Sergeants Exam reading list.
"Split Second Leadership:"
"Leading Men In The Line Of Duty."
- Men?
- It's from the '60s.
How is this relevant
to 21st-century policing?
Ours is not to reason why,
Officer Bradford.
Read the book.
Yes, sir.
Sergeant Grey is setting me up to fail.
- You see that, right?
- No. I really don't.
Come on, there's no way I'm gonna find
someplace to live in one day.
Not with that attitude.
7 to 10 days would be
a reasonable amount of time.
It's at the sergeant's discretion.
Just like sticking me
back in long sleeves
was at his discretion.
You know, I know two guys
from the academy
who both got 80s,
and they're both in short sleeves.
Why's he penalizing me?
You know, I think I liked you better,
when you were a coward.
You complained less.
If I have to suffer, so do you.
So, you're gonna read this
out loud to me between calls.
Only way I'm gonna get it
memorized in time.
Or I could drive
and you could read it to yourself.
Nice try. Start reading.
Okay.
"Chapter One."
"True leadership generates
respect, not fear."
"It elevates people,
rather than diminishing them."
I like this book.
You would.
Keep reading.
"The number-one mistake
new leaders make"
"is to think themselves
suddenly infallible."
"The best leaders understand that
even the lowliest patrol officer"
"has something valuable to teach them."
Repeat that last part back to me.
Memorizing is all about repetition.
Trust me. I'm a psych major.
I-I know this stuff.
The best leaders understand that
even the lowliest patrol officer
has something valuable to teach them.
Again.
7-Adam-19,
family disturbance at 217 Evergreen.
Thank God.
7-Adam-19, copy. En route.
Okay, ETA three minutes.
Time to read some more.
"An open mind and an open door."..
And that's why phase three recruits
all have tan left arms.
I am not gonna lie,
the change to short sleeves
has been life-altering.
I remember it well.
Then I quickly, uh, moved into suits.
I mean, it's not as hot as wool,
but it's not cool, either.
How long did it take you
to make the move?
What? Uh, detective? Four years.
I didn't think that was possible.
Yeah, well, I'm still
the only cop who's done it.
But I still wonder if I...
if I moved too quickly.
Well, speaking as someone
who wants to move up rapidly,
I am officially your number-one fan.
If there's any hints you can dispense,
I am all ears.
You hook me up on the local 411,
and I'll dispense a little knowledge.
Deal.
All units, incoming four-fifteen.
Shaw Memorial.
Security fighting with unknown male.
I haven't been in a fight in a while.
Buy that call.
Let's go get in some trouble.
- Sure.
- Here we go.
They're gonna kill each other!
My boys... they bought
these military vests
off the Internet,
and they wanna try them out!
- Bulletproof vests?
- Oh, I hope so.
They won't listen to me.
- Maybe you'll listen to them.
- Ma'am, get in the house.
- I called the cops.
- Put the guns down!
- Put them down!
- 3, 2, 1.
Drop your weapons!
Oh, my God!
- Stay in the house.
- See, I told you they'd work.
- Drop the guns right now!
- Drop your weapon now!
- Relax.
- We were just messing around.
J-Bag bet me the vests wouldn't work.
You been drinking,
or are you normally this stupid?
Get up.
I-I don't feel so good.
Tim.
- Tim.
- Look at you!
You guys never listen
to what I'm saying.
- I won the bet.
- What bet? He's dying!
It doesn't matter!
It was his idea to buy the vests!
7-Adam-19. I need an ambulance.
- Gunshot wound to the upper torso.
- Mom, go back in the house!
He's bleeding. What are you doing here?
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Just came in on a 5150 hold.
He got loose. He's high on something.
Whoa.
Hey, big guy. Hey.
We don't want anybody
hurting you, okay?
Tase him, tase him, tase him!
Come on, big guy. Come on.
- Grace?
- John?
I'm open to ideas.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Yeah, I probably should
have... stretched before that.
How long have you been a cop?
- Six months.
- You're kidding me.
I mean, they didn't let me
touch a patient for three years.
Oh, well, I think LAPD puts value on
"on the job" training.
I thought you were gonna be a painter.
I mean, things happened, so...
What did you give him,
and can I get some?
Detective Armstrong, this is Grace.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- How do you know Nolan?
- We went to college together.
Briefly.
Gunshot victim coming in!
Good seeing you again, John.
Nice to meet you, Detective.
Nice to meet you.
This the first time
you've seen her since?
Yeah.
She looks good.
Come on. Yep.
Come on.
No.
Come on. Come on.
Hey, West.
What's up?
You find a place to live yet?
Smitty, it's only been,
like, two hours.
After you book your DUI,
meet me at the west gate.
Ohh.
Smitty?
Jackson. Welcome home.
- Home?
- That's right.
You have a chance to stay
at the best-kept secret
in the LAPD...
Shangri-La Westgate.
Low maintenance, zero commute,
and a vacation is easy as
"Gentlemen, start your engines."
Smitty, you live in
the police station parking lot.
I even have the password
to the coffee shop WiFi.
Baller, isn't it?
"Baller" is not the first word
that comes to mind,
and not one that sounds good
coming out of your mouth.
But... you know what?
This actually is
something that might...
Boot!
I told you to meet me at the shop!
$400 a month, zero security deposit.
- We got a deal?
- Let's go!
Let me get back to you.
Alright, so, what's the deal
with Dr. Grace?
What do you mean?
Mm, noticed a little
something-something,
under the surface.
You didn't catch it?
No, but I was, uh,
a little preoccupied.
You know, surprise,
adrenaline, head trauma.
Okay.
What... What do you think it was?
Hey, I... No idea. No idea.
7-Adam-15,
manually activated panic alarm.
Multiple distress activations.
7-Adam-15, responding.
Code 2 High.
Is it locked?
Let's try the side of the house first.
Hey.
Look.
Police! Come on out!
Show me your hands!
I got you. I got you.
It's okay. Oh, oh, oh.
- Alright.
- They have Jeff.
They have our son.
- There's... There's two of them.
- Shh. It's okay.
- They're upstairs.
- How long ago?
Uh, 20 minutes, half hour.
Home invasion, possible 207.
We're clearing the house now.
- Stay here.
- Okay. Okay.
Clear!
Jeff?
- No.
- I'm sorry.
No! Jeff!
- God...
- I'm sorry.
So, what do we've got?
Our victim's name is Jeff Christian,
17 years old.
Apparent gunshot wound to the back.
- Any others?
- Yeah.
Matt and Marilyn Christian. Parents.
Both assaulted,
described two masked assailants.
Males, white, maybe Hispanic.
5'9 " to 5'11", medium build.
Uh, the primary wore white
sneakers with a red triangle.
I already put out a BOLO citywide.
Can I tell you,
it's nice to have a detective here,
- from the get-go.
- Yeah.
Now, you want the on-call
homicide dicks to respond?
Nah, I'll take this one.
Anything special you want
them to pay attention to?
Uh, there was a piece
of electrical tape
covering the doorbell camera.
Hey.
75% of cops would have
missed that tape.
That's a nice spot, Officer Nolan.
You want to work with me on this one?
Yes, sir, I do.
Good. Come on.
Mr. and Mrs. Christian, I...
I am, uh...
I'm sorry.
All I can offer is a promise.
I will hunt the men who did this.
I will hunt them
to the ends of the Earth,
and I will not stop until I find them.
If there's anything you need,
the LAPD is here for you.
Thank you.
Would you excuse us?
What do we got?
Is that a puncture wound on the elbow?
Yeah. Entry wound.
The bullet entered the elbow,
probably bounced off the humerus bone,
severed the brachial,
and then came out of the back.
What's this fluid in his mouth?
Pulmonary edema, but let's
let the coroner handle that.
Any sign of struggle?
Uh...
Not really, but...
how does someone get shot in the elbow?
Reaching for a loaded gun.
But what does lunging
for a gun suggest?
- He was fighting back.
- Eventually,
but why wait so long?
- Was he trying to reason with them?
- Maybe.
But maybe shooting the kid
wasn't the original plan,
but once he grabbed the gun...
Bang. No choice.
But why are they in this room?
The master bedroom,
the parents' room...
that's where all the expensive stuff is.
But here...
Wait a minute.
Cubby hole.
Prescription pills.
Yeah.
I'm gonna have to let the lab confirm,
but I'm saying that's Oxycontin.
You think maybe this
was the real target?
See that piece of plastic on that nail?
The baggie probably ripped
when they pulled it out,
and they lost a few pills.
So that explains what
they were doing up here.
So, what do we do next?
Uh... we dig into Jeff's past,
find out everybody he knew.
Two of those people either
killed him or know who did.
Perfect.
The suspect pool just shrunk
from the whole world to about 200 now.
Eliminate women, the very tall,
short, young, old...
we're talking maybe 50 names.
We could have these guys
ID'd before dinner.
Good move, pulling me
away from Smitty's RV.
He just dropped the rent
a hundred bucks.
Yeah, my dad always said
the only true negotiating power
is the ability to walk away.
Smitty's Shangri-La
is where cops go to die.
That's one way of looking at it.
And the other is that it's freedom,
model of efficiency.
No commute, cheap rent.
You can spin it all you want.
Doesn't change the fact that it's
another step in the wrong direction.
Why not just move back in
with your folks
while you look for a place?
Talk about the wrong direction.
'Cause you haven't told your
dad about your test score?
No.
Alright, fine. Fine.
I'll stay at home tonight,
but only 'cause it'll get Smitty
to knock down the rent even more.
Just like that,
we're back where we started.
"Chapter Three."
"The healthy habits of command."
"Delegation is the key"
"to leading men in times of stress."
"Don't ever think you can carry
the load all by yourself."
That is so true. Don't you think?
It's hard enough to listen to it
without you editorializing.
Hey, I'm happy to stop reading
and catch up on paperwork.
You're gonna have to
re-read all of this anyway
- to really memorize it.
- No.
I memorize best when I hear it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Huh.
- Why?
- Nothing. I...
Boot.
You might have a learning difference.
A what?
Technically, it's classified
as a disability,
but it really just means that you're
wired to process
information differently.
In your case, through... through
hearing rather than reading.
I don't have a learning disability.
A lot of people have them.
I bet Isabel helped you in the Academy,
read through the materials
with you and stuff.
We're not talking about this.
7-Adam-19, suspicious person.
Unknown male sitting in a red minivan.
Possibly casing at 1966 Keegan Street.
7-Adam-19, show us responding.
All I'm saying is...
Never mind.
Let's talk on the sidewalk.
Rex?
You're still chasing bounty?
I thought you moved to Reno.
All my bail jumpers come to L.A.
I got a tip one of 'em's
down the street
staying at his aunt's place.
We got three 911 calls
about a weirdo in a minivan.
- Casing.
- Watch your tone, Boot.
Oh, you don't get to
call her "Boot," Rex.
You're retired.
She's the police now.
Let's see your bail bonds license
and the warrant on your jumper.
You let her talk to you like that?
Nico Sandoval. Attempted murder?
Okay, you need to call dispatch
and let us know when you're out here.
- This guy sounds dangerous.
- Uh, I've been Code 5
on dangerous men since
before you were born, little lady.
Well, in this century,
you notify local law enforcement
so when you get in the weeds,
we know who's out here.
I don't call for help.
Help calls for me.
Maybe you need to let this guy
read your book.
Rex, if you're gonna be out here,
you gotta play by the rules.
Ah, come on, Tim.
I call this in,
someone's gonna snatch my bounty.
I need that money.
Nico shows, you give us a call.
No one's gonna "snatch your bounty."
Alright.
It's good to see you, Rex.
It's good seeing you, too, Tim.
Detective Armstrong.
I spoke to some of Jeff's friends.
Turns out he did a stint
in rehab three months ago.
Wow.
Funny how his family
failed to mention that,
and that explains the fluid
you saw coming out of his mouth.
The only cause for that
to happen in a dead body
is a bad chest cold
or an opioid addiction.
That's good to know.
We need to get a warrant
for Jeff's rehab records,
see if he made any friends in there.
Actually, I spoke to an ex-girlfriend.
She told me while Jeff was in rehab,
he connected with a man who was, quote,
"ass cancer in a skin suit."
Got Jeff to deal some drugs for him
while he was in his fancy prep school.
This skin suit have a name?
Bruno Winch.
He lives over in Highland Park.
LAPD! Probation search!
Open up!
- Bruno Winch! LAPD!
- Clear!
- Clear.
Clear!
Clear.
Baseball bat. Tough way to go.
White shoes, red triangles.
I don't see you in 20 years,
now I see you twice in one day.
I still cannot believe you're a cop.
How long have you been in L.A.?
Uh, less than a year.
Moved out after Sarah and I got divorced
and Henry went off to college.
That's right.
Yeah, Henry would be, um, 20 now.
20.
That's so weird. We're so old.
Right. And yet,
you look exactly the same.
How is that even possible?
Grace. Did Bruno make it?
He's critical, but I think he'll live.
- He's in ICU.
- Any chance for an interview?
No, we had to induce a coma.
There's a lot of pressure on his brain.
- Couple days, maybe?
- Most likely, it's gonna be a week.
But we bagged his clothing for you.
Excuse me.
Yeah, see, I didn't feel anything then.
Yeah, maybe I'm just making it up.
Now I think you're just
giving me a hard time.
Absolutely possible.
So, what are we thinking with Bruno?
He and his partner
pull a home invasion to get to Jeff.
Jeff probably stole
something from him...
maybe owed him drugs, money.
But then how does Bruno
end up beaten half to death?
Don't do that... speculate.
Making up stories is how
innocent men go to jail
and guilty men go free.
- Thus endeth the tip.
- Understood.
- Alright. End of shift.
- Uh, you riding back to the station?
Oh, no, I don't have
to clock out like you do.
I'm gonna stay here, have some
questionable hospital food,
see if a miracle happens
and Bruno wakes up.
Okay. Later.
Later.
Armstrong?
I'm doing a huge renovation
on a house I just bought.
I could really use
an extra set of hands.
Pizza and beer on me.
Pizza and beer?
- This place is a wreck.
- Yes.
But it's my wreck.
So, hey, tell me about Grace.
Uh... we dated.
Yeah, I knew it.
She had that "bad breakup" energy.
It was 20 years ago,
and she's wearing a ring,
probably has a kid.
I'm sure she barely remembers me.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Just tell me what happened.
We met my junior year.
I was... dating my ex-wife,
Sarah, since high school,
and, uh, we hit a bad spell
and broke up.
And that's when Grace happened.
Yeah, we'd been friends
for a few months,
and there had always been a spark,
but it just...
went off like a bomb.
Crawled all over each other
for two weeks.
It was zero to 160 in
the span of a heartbeat.
And then?
Then Sarah showed up at my dorm
eight weeks' pregnant.
Damn. Damn.
And you did the right thing?
There was really no other choice.
I still loved her, and that was my kid.
So, I, uh, dropped out of school,
packed up my things,
moved back to Foxburg.
I was married in a month,
a dad within six,
got a job in construction,
never looked back.
Never?
Well... I mean, not never.
Now your paths have crossed again, so...
So, nothing. I'm seeing someone,
and she's married.
Married women are the best.
You find yourself
a sexually frustrated, hot little mama
whose husband isn't doing it right...
I can't do that, I mean,
just thinking about
that stresses me out.
That's... That's how lives are ruined.
That... is the right answer.
Hey, you can't be faithful to a girl,
you can't be faithful
to an oath or a badge.
- I'll drink to that.
- Yes.
- Running late?
- Yeah, had to commute
from my folks' place in Simi Valley.
Half the LAPD lives in Ventura County,
but they all seem to
make it to work on time.
Yeah, well, my dad was getting all up
in my business about getting extended.
Literally had to stop him from coming
down here and lighting up Lopez.
Look, the hole you're in
has nothing to do with Lopez.
But she's gonna pay the price
when the commander's son
goes belly-up halfway through training.
I told him it's not her fault.
Yeah, so, tell him again.
Lopez bent over backwards for you.
She protected your ass
when any other T.O.
would've sent you packing.
You owe her your career.
I know.
Hey.
You're the cop who wrestled
the guy in the kilt.
Yes. Actually, I'm here
checking on another patient.
Bruno Winch?
- We're trying to I.D. his p...
- Bruno's still in a coma.
Right. I figured... as much.
I just thought I'd come and check.
You could have done that by phone.
See ya.
I officially feel like
you're stalking me.
That is as ridiculous
as it is accurate.
We really just didn't get a
chance to catch up yesterday.
Like, how long have
you been working here?
And, uh, do you have any kids?
I've been here three weeks,
I'm the new head of emergency medicine,
and I have an 8-year-old.
Oh, 8's such a great age,
I mean, obviously,
they're all great, but 8 is...
John, listen...
I don't mean to be rude.
I can't do this with you.
Grace, it's been 20 years.
You left a note on my door.
I mean, I never heard from you again.
Sarah was pregnant.
You broke my heart.
I mean, I thought that
we were both in love,
and then you just disappeared.
I can't believe that I am still
this angry with you.
- Grace...
- You know, I'll have them call you
when your suspect wakes up.
Mr. Christian?
Can I help you with something?
Uh, Detective Armstrong
asked me to come in
so he could re-interview me after,
you know, the initial shock's passed.
But I'm not sure it has.
I can only imagine what you're
going through right now.
Hell, if somebody hurt my Henry,
I'd be out for blood.
I'll go let Detective Armstrong
know that you're here.
- Armstrong.
- Yeah. What's up, buddy?
I was just talking
to Matt Christian in the lobby.
- Mm-hmm?
- I told him,
if anything happened to my son,
I'd be out for blood,
and he just got this look.
I mean, I-I could be
misinterpreting it.
Our job as investigators
is not to speculate.
It's to think about what we've seen,
what we've heard,
and articulate the facts.
What are those facts?
Matt paid for Jeff to go to rehab.
Uh, that's where Jeff met Bruno.
Yep.
It's definitely possible
that Matt met Bruno there
when he was visiting his son.
Maybe Matt recognized Bruno's voice
during the home invasion?
Let's go talk to Matt.
Alright. Thanks for coming by, Matt.
- How's Marilyn today?
- We didn't sleep.
She, uh... She can't stop crying.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I only have a few follow-up questions,
and then we'll get you
back to her, okay?
- Yeah.
- Alright,
Was Jeff on pain medication?
We found oxy in his room.
He tore his knee last year.
Eh... Doctor gave him
a couple of pills.
He was hooked for a little while,
but... I got him clean.
- Re-birth Malibu.
- That's right.
They straightened him right out.
- Did you ever visit him there?
- Of course.
You know, when they let me.
Did you meet a patient
named Bruno Winch?
Doesn't ring a bell.
But what's this got to do
with the home invasion?
That... wasn't about Jeff.
Well... actually, we think
he was the real target.
What are you talking about?
Bruno Winch is one of the men
that entered your home,
bound and beat you,
and killed your son.
I have a photo of him.
Maybe you recognize him.
- Oops.
- Uh, that's the wrong photo.
That's what he looked like
yesterday when we found him, so...
- Is he dead?
- No.
He's just in the hospital.
We're waiting for him to wake up
so he can tell us who did that to him.
I don't actually
have the photo with me.
Uh... let me go get it.
Uh, Matt, why didn't you mention
that Jeff had a drug problem?
Wasn't a problem anymore.
And I didn't want his
whole memory to be that.
- Of course.
- Well, that's a father's job...
protect his kids.
He was the best part of me.
I failed him.
Matt, I know you feel guilty.
Put him in rehab to straighten him out,
watch him get connected with bad people
who just pulled him deeper down,
but that is not your fault.
If you know anything
that can lead us to Bruno's partner,
you need to tell me.
Just let us do our job.
Sorry. Printer's broken.
Uh, I can e-mail you the photo.
Sure.
Uh... I really have
to get back to my wife.
O-Of course. Of... Of course. Come...
Uh, we'll be in touch. Soon.
Thank you.
- So, what do you think?
- He's out for revenge.
We get a surveillance team on him?
If he knows who Bruno is,
it's likely he knows
who Bruno's partner is,
and he'll go after him next.
Which is why when I stepped out,
I had SIS put a tracker on Matt's car.
Airship will follow.
While we hunt down the partner.
- You doing okay?
- Fine.
I know what's bothering you.
Seven Year Glitch.
- Sorry. Seven Year what?
- Glitch.
The most dangerous time for a cop
happens every seven years,
like clockwork.
It's when most of us lose the passion,
grow complacent, disillusioned.
I went through it myself.
Okay, well... I mean,
I've only been on for six months.
You're not a regular rookie.
You've been gung-ho
since you were a kid.
And now you're glitching early.
Okay, well, h-how do I fix my glitch?
How'd you fix yours?
I became a T.O.
Changed my routine. Challenged myself.
Well, I am challenging myself.
Me not being all in, all the time,
is me changing my routine.
But... you know, I can...
I can put all that on hold
for six more months,
embrace my inner slacker
after you're free of me.
- I'm not asking you that...
- I know.
But it's the right thing.
Do you want me to read to you?
- No.
- Come on.
- You have to learn it.
- I can do that on my own.
- What are we doing back here?
- I checked the computer.
Rex didn't bring in
his bounty last night,
which means he's been
out here this whole time.
So this is a welfare check?
Oh, don't put it to him like that.
7-Adam-19,
got a broken car window,
missing driver.
Send backup to my location.
Rex.
Eh, that little punk
- hit me with a cheap shot.
- 7-Adam-19, we need
an RA to 1966 Keegan.
Assault victim. Broken arm,
- possible concussion.
- Where'd he go?
- His aunt's house.
- He's long gone by now, though.
We need a warrant, or backup.
- Sit down.
- No, go...
Go, go! Go with him. I'm fine. Go!
Tony Craig! That's Bruno's partner.
He's all over Bruno's cellphone.
They even texted about
the home invasion.
Apartment's in Century City.
Matt Christian's in the wind.
I thought there was a tracker
on his car.
He ditched it at the mall. Disappeared.
- Which mall?
- Century City.
He's going after Tony.
Whoa, Nico, where is he?
He, I don't know.
- He isn't here.
- There's blood on your front door.
That's exigent circumstances,
so I'm not leaving till
you tell me where he is.
He isn't here!
So, you're gonna call him.
Otherwise we're gonna book you
for aiding and abetting a fugitive.
Do it now.
Hey. What's up?
Cops are here. Where are you?
I'm in Florida.
Nico Sandoval!
You got five seconds to surrender!
I'm in Florida, yo.
You guys want some of this?
Michelle! Bail me out, okay?
You're coming, too. Let's go.
- What?!
- Right now.
Tony's gate is open.
Clear.
Matt got here before us.
He must have knew
we were right behind him,
took Tony someplace to finish him off.
Yeah. But where?
Mrs. Christian,
I know you think you're protecting him,
but what your husband
is doing is wrong.
Look, m-ma'am,
right now, you can't see
beyond this moment.
Neither can your husband.
Making those men pay for what they did
is all he cares about.
I, uh...
I know just... a little
about what it's like
to be obsessed with something
at the expense of everything else.
And trust me, it will not
change the way you feel.
Look, your son is gone,
and what your husband is doing
will destroy both of you.
I know it's too late to save Jeff,
but if you can tell us where Matt is...
...you might not lose your husband.
Matt!
What did you do with Tony?
What he deserved.
And now it's over...
or it's gonna be soon.
The cement.
Matt put Tony in the cement.
That criminal killed my boy.
I know, and he's gonna pay, okay?
So, you don't have to do this.
You can just come on down.
You don't get it.
I died in that bedroom
alongside my son.
The only thing keeping me alive
was killing them.
And now that's over.
Hey, Nolan!
Look, I found him,
but I can't get him up.
Help me!
We can only save one guy,
and right now, Tony is the victim!
Matt, I know this seems
hopeless right now,
but don't make your wife
bury two bodies.
It will destroy her.
Nolan! Help me!
Come here.
Come on!
Watch yourself.
ABCs. Go.
There we go.
We saved him.
Training for the rematch with Nico?
Ah, we got him in the end.
Here.
- What's this?
- It is...
"Split Second Leadership:"
"Leading Men In The Line of Duty,"
the audio book.
This book's out of print.
There's no audio book.
Yeah, which is why
I recorded one for you.
Uh, listen,
I-I talked to Isabel,
and from what she said,
it's clear you're
a kinesthetic learner,
which just means that
you need to listen
while you're being active
in order to absorb things.
There's no shame in it. Really.
Honestly, it's probably why
you excel at being a cop.
Uh... I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Thanks.
"Split Second Leadership"
by Curtis Philbrick,
read by the best rookie
you've ever trained.
- Hey, headed home?
- Yeah.
You live alone, right?
Yeah. First time ever. No roommates.
It's heaven. Why?
Well, welcome aboard.
Women's softball's on ESPN,
and I just made a pitcher of mojitos.
Come on in.
Yeah, nice!
Nope.
Hey.
I talked to Lopez, and she said
you needed a place to live
and a kickass roommate
to help you find some balance.
Thank God. Thank you.
Aww. Yeah. Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Hey.
Good Lord, don't you have
someplace better to be?
It's nice to see you, too.
Hey... thanks.
Look, I put the paperwork
through under your name.
So, you're gonna get
the bounty on Nico.
Thank you.
Look, Rex,
I... I know you're not the
kind of guy that asks for help,
but if you ever find yourself
out here again,
just give me a heads up.
Little professional courtesy, right?
Exactly. Alright.
Thanks, brother. Alright.
You take care.
Hey.
It's been a long day, John.
No, I know. Of course.
And I'll only take
a moment of your time.
Look, I left you a note
because I wouldn't have been
able to go through with it
if I saw you in person.
And I don't regret marrying Sarah,
and I have loved every minute
of being Henry's dad.
But what I did to you was selfish,
and you deserve better, and I'm sorry.
Thank you.
So... now that we're friends again,
it hurts when I do this.
- Good night, John.
- Good night, Grace.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.MY-SUBS.com