♪ Got so much back ♪
♪ That you could call me J‐Lo ♪
Ow!
♪ Call me J‐Lo ♪
♪ Building so fast
that I ran out of LEGOs ♪
♪ Out of LEGOs ♪
♪ Just bought a runway ♪
♪ For my new tornado ♪
♪ New tornado ♪
♪ The game is mine,
I can't let go my Eggo ♪
♪ I told my mama ♪
Hello?
Officer Nolan,
this is Detective Nyla Harper.
I'm your new
training officer.
My ‐‐ Great!
Um, I'm sorry,
did you say "detective"?
Yeah.
Isn't that
a little unusual for ‐‐
I thought
we should get a drink,
size each other up a bit
before shift tomorrow.
Meet me at Third Strike.
20 minutes.
Third Strike.
Okay, got it.
I'm gonna ‐‐
I'm gonna need like 30.
20, or I'm gone.
Oh, uh, okay.
Um...
♪ It's perfect ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Say it again ♪
♪ I'm cavin' in ♪
♪ Come back one more time ♪
♪ I live with a troubled mind ♪
Uh, excuse me.
I'm meeting someone here,
a Nyla Harper.
Um...
I'll grab a draft
when you got a minute.
♪ Come back one more time ♪
♪ Much too proud to question why ♪
♪ After all these years ♪
♪ I'm cavin' in ♪
Let me guess.
First date?
Worried
she's not gonna show?
Oh, no, no. I wouldn't bring
a first date here.
No offense.
Oh, none taken.
I am meeting someone,
though.
My, um ‐‐ My TO.
My training officer.
I'm a rookie. LAPD.
You're a rookie?
Yeah.
Mid‐life career change.
Oh. Good for you.
Thanks.
You wouldn't happen to see her,
did you,
someone probably just
checking her watch,
looking annoyed?
Maybe.
I‐I don't really
pay attention
to people
sitting at the bar.
So, why the change?
Hmm.
Uh, you know, uh,
sometimes life
just gives you a nudge.
For me,
it was a divorce,
my son moving
off to college,
and an ill‐timed trip
to the bank.
Makes sense.
Wife left you,
kid left you.
Nothing like
a gun in hand
to make you
feel powerful again.
No, that's not why
at all.
Are there maybe
some other customers
that could use your help?
You're her.
You're my TO.
Took you long enough.
Wow. Okay.
Why the game?
Wanted to see
if you could play.
So, if it wasn't
about your gun,
why do you want
the badge?
Well, because when people
are having their worst day,
I want to be there,
try to help make it right.
Oh, God,
you're one of those.
One of what?
A guardian.
There are two kinds of cops,
Officer Nolan ‐‐
there are Warriors
and Guardians.
One's a hunter,
the other's a nurturer.
One is only alive
when they're in the fight.
The other is happy
to clock out after 12.
One is worth my time.
The other is not.
♪ Come back one more time ♪
♪ In this cold, empty home ♪
That went well.
I don't understand.
So, she's a detective,
but she's coming back
to patrol?
Is that allowed?
Well,
it's not unheard of.
Actually,
I've never heard of it.
Lucky me.
Well, I've been through
a lot of TO mind games,
and it's really
not that bad.
All you need
to remember is
be absolutely perfect
at all times.
Thanks.
Look, seriously,
you are a great cop.
You just need to keep
being a great cop,
and she'll see that.
Oh, Rachel.
Uh, I'll see you guys
in there.
Hey!
Hi!
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
It's ‐‐
It's your birthday?
Yeah!
And I am spending it
doing what I love ‐‐
picking up
juvenile contact reports.
I got your gift.
How do you always find
the perfect thing?
Mm, just six months
of scouring
every used book store
in Los Angeles.
I tracked down a copy of
"Aeronautics Through the Ages."
Sounds like
a page turner.
Well, my grandfather
did the illustrations.
He was obsessed
with planes.
When I was a kid,
we spent every weekend
at local airfields.
Well,
until security crackdowns.
Anyway, um,
I should get to work.
We still on for Friday?
Yeah.
I'll pick you up at 8:00.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Whatever you're about
to say, don't.
We have a new Training Officer
joining us this morning,
Detective Nyla Harper.
Nyla?
What's up?
You're late for roll call.
Oh, that's still a thing?
Take a seat.
As I was saying,
Detective Harper just completed
four years of undercover work.
She has volunteered to bring
her wealth of experience
to the FTO program.
Officer Nolan,
I'm sure you'll learn a lot.
Looking forward to it,
sir.
If you need anything,
ask Lopez and Bradford.
They'll bring you
up to speed.
Yes, sir.
Alright, that's it.
Be safe out there.
Hey. Angela Lopez.
Hi.
He's Bradford.
Surprised to see a detective
volunteer as a TO.
Most would see it
as a step backward.
While clearly,
you've never moved forward.
I get the appeal, though ‐‐
surround yourself with kids
who don't know enough
to see through your bull.
Look, solid policing
is anything but bull.
Whereas cops like you spend
so much time over the edge
you don't even know
where the line is.
Don't get your panties
in a bunch, handsome.
I'm not saying
you're not tough.
I'm just saying
you're not me.
I love her so much.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's all this?
Our gear.
Ticket book?
You're not gonna need that.
Or that. Or this.
Okay, well, Sergeant Grey likes
to see two citations a week.
Grey's not your TO.
Give me an AR‐15
with PVS‐14 night vision
and a laser sight.
You're AR certified?
Card's on file.
Coming up.
You really think
we're gonna need an AR‐15?
Sure hope so.
L‐Look, um,
about last night.
I‐I really
don't understand the ruse.
If you wanted to know
why I wanted to be a cop,
you could have just asked me,
and I would have told you.
I wanted to see who you were
when you weren't kissing
your new TO's ass.
And I found out
you can't be trusted.
Because
I want to help people?
Because you started
spilling secrets
to a complete stranger.
What if that waitress had
a brother in the Rolling 60s
who would just love to smoke
an off‐duty cop?
I didn't think of that.
Clearly.
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
That won't happen again.
You obviously have
a wealth of experience.
And I'm looking forward
to learning everything
you have to teach.
Oh,
I won't be teaching you.
You're my training officer.
Which earns me
a 5% pay bump.
Whether you learn
or not.
I know you're probably
worrying about
what to get Rachel.
Don't.
You are riding with
the world's best gift‐giver.
So let's start
brainstorming.
What are you thinking about
getting her?
Nothing.
It's her birthday.
We've been dating
for two weeks.
If I get her something,
it'd be weird.
So, you just wished her
happy birthday,
and now you're done?
Yep.
Okay.
Maybe I should get her
something small.
Broken taillight.
Which he clearly
can't afford to fix.
Ah, look,
she barely stopped.
She could have caused
an accident.
But she didn't.
Is this why you became a cop,
Five Percent?
To harass hard‐working people
just trying to get by?
Doesn't sound
very guardian‐like to me.
No, ma'am, but Sergeant Grey
likes to see 2, 2, and 2 ‐‐
two citations, two misdemeanors,
and two felony arrests a week.
Yeah,
we won't be doing that.
And if he fires us?
I can't get fired.
I have a golden ticket.
Like in "Willy Wonka"?
Like in the LAPD.
It's a reward for policing
above and beyond.
I had my choice ‐‐
any station, any detail.
And you picked this?
Mm‐hmm.
Well, you must have taken down
some heavy hitters.
It's what warriors do,
Officer Nolan.
Which is why we don't
get out of this car
for anything
less than a felony.
And when we do step out,
we step out hard and fast.
Strike before they can.
And if you slow me down,
you are done.
Aah!
Are you kidding me?!
Please stop.
Drop the guns now!
Show us your hands!
Okay, okay.
You got 'em?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Police.
Is someone in there?
I‐I don't want trouble.
Are you okay?
I'll move.
I just need my cart.
We're not clearing you out.
We're here to help.
We'll take you to a hospital.
You've been hurt.
I'm fine.
I'm fine. Just lea‐‐
Leave me alone.
Okay, um, no problem.
I just need some information
for the report.
No, I got‐‐
I have to go.
At least tell me your name.
Alice.
Sheldon.
Alice Sheldon.
Thank you, Alice.
I'll make sure those boys
never hurt you again.
If you need anything...
We were just protecting
our neighborhood.
My ‐‐ My dad said they're
tanking the property values.
She's a human being.
I'm not so sure
about you two.
Maserati. No plates.
Let me guess.
Not worth
getting out of the shop for.
No, this one,
we stop.
A rag around
the steering column
to hide
the broken ignition.
That car is stolen.
Driver in the Maserati,
pull over.
Driver.
Step out of the car.
You're hot for a cop.
I know.
Everybody out. Now.
Hands where
I can see them.
Nolan. VIN.
Control, 7‐Adam‐15.
Need you to run
a VIN for me.
Number's 7‐1‐8.
Hey, stay where you are.
Stay where you are!
You're under arrest.
Hey, stop!
Get up.
7‐Adam‐15.
In foot pursuit of suspect.
7th and Figueroa.
Hispanic male, 5'7",
gray shirt, gray jeans.
Requesting backup
and airship.
Aah!
Aaaah!
7‐Adam‐15.
Start an RA to 7th and Figueroa.
Suspect down. Broken leg.
Conscious and breathing.
Just stay still.
Help is on the way.
She pushed me.
That bitch pushed me.
Come on.
Okay, ready.
So, what happened?
Gravity.
He says you pushed him.
I know I said I wasn't
gonna teach you anything,
Five Percent,
but, um
here's a lesson.
Criminals lie.
She's right.
You really think
she could've pushed him?
I don't know.
With Talia, I never would've...
I never would have
considered it,
but Harper has this real
"ends justifies the means" vibe.
Still. Throwing somebody
off a roof
in broad daylight
is hardcore.
But she has
a golden ticket.
Maybe she thinks
that'll protect her.
Wait, a golden ticket
is rarified air.
My dad caught a serial killer
and a bank crew
in the same shift
and never got
a golden ticket.
Okay.
If you were me,
would you go to Grey?
Look, Harper might have
a ticket, but you don't.
You have the responsibility
to inform the watch commander
of any potential issues
on the job.
And an allegation
of police brutality
would definitely be one.
Excuse me.
May I have a word?
Oh, right on time.
I'll come back later.
No. Stay.
This concerns you, too.
See, Detective Harper
asked me to review
her body‐cam footage.
Hey! Stop!
Stop! Hey!
Aaaaah!
I told you to stop!
Looks conclusive to me.
Yes, sir.
So I'll forward it
to Internal Affairs with a memo.
Hopefully it'll head off
any civil lawsuits
that might be
coming your way.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
And thank you
for the trust.
I'm sorry, sir.
No, you did the right thing
coming to me.
I‐I‐It's not
that I don't trust her.
No, you shouldn't
trust her.
So, word is Detective Harper
spent the last four years
doing "controlled deliveries"
in the LAPD‐DEA task force.
I'm not familiar
with the term.
An undercover agent
poses as a drug smuggler.
Goes into Mexico,
negotiates with the cartel.
Guarantees delivery of dope
into the U. S.
with their own lives.
And then they actually smuggle
the dope over the border,
planting micro trackers
in it.
See, and then
once it's distributed,
SWAT moves in,
arrests everyone
that touched it.
And then
she goes back to Mexico
and starts the whole thing
over again.
But only now,
the cartel is looking for
someone to blame,
with blow torches,
power tools, you know.
Explains the attitude.
She spent
the last four years
neck‐deep in paranoia
and adrenaline,
lying every time
she opened her mouth,
striking out
at any sign of aggression.
Now, don't get me wrong ‐‐
I have the utmost respect
for her service,
but transitioning
back into a uniform?
That's gonna be a bitch.
So, you made her my TO?
I didn't have much say
in that matter.
She would eat
a 25‐year‐old recruit alive.
At least
you stand a chance.
Thank you,
but I‐I think I would stand
a much better chance
if I knew why she wanted
to be here in the first place.
When you find out,
let me know.
What are you doing?
Raiding
the lost and found.
Why?
For Alice.
The transient those kids
were paintballing.
I ran her name.
10 years ago, she was on
the tenure track at UCLA,
teaching chemistry.
Had a house,
a couple dogs,
then everything
fell apart.
That's awful.
But, I mean, we interact
with homeless every day.
You don't bring them
care packages.
Those kids
took away her dignity,
tortured her for fun.
She deserves
a little compassion.
Look, I, uh, have a couple
sweatshirts in my car.
We can grab them
on the way out.
Sounds good.
Look, it's a bad idea.
No, it's not.
Do you even know
if Rachel likes baseball?
Who doesn't like
baseball?
It's America's pastime.
In the '30s.
Rachel is not into sports.
Try to think of something
that's for her.
Smile!
Thank God.
Uh, we got a call
about an assault?
They just barged in
and started taking pictures.
My son is very sick.
Good! Yay!
...what you're doing.
Oh, that's awesome!
Ready?
Hey,
what's going on in here?
Just a second.
Step out in the hallway
right now.
Both of you.
What's the problem,
Officer?
They broke into my son's room
and started posing.
"Broke in"
is an exaggeration.
You told the nurse
you were his sister.
I didn't say
I was his sister.
I said I was a sister.
We're just trying to help.
Bella saw a Facebook post
about little Cody
and his fight against cancer.
She has a half a million
followers on social media.
I was just trying to draw
attention to his plight.
Doesn't that count
for something?
Not without permission.
You're under arrest
for trespassing
and photographing a minor
without a parent's consent.
I told you this was a bad idea.
You need more empathy posts.
Your follows are stagnant.
The consultant told us
to find a sick kid ‐‐
He's not a consultant.
He's your cousin,
and he still lives with his mom!
He's got his finger
on the pulse.
Okay, enough.
Alright, I am really sorry
that this happened.
We will come back
and get your statement.
Honey,
get back in bed.
Can't we get in there?
Just one picture.
No!
Looks like she moved on.
She left
some stuff behind.
Hey, you know where
the woman who was attacked went?
Have you seen her?
Whose stuff
is this here?
What's that?
I don't know, but Alice
was trying to protect it.
Could it be her daughter?
No, she didn't have kids.
Control,
I need you to run a name.
Katrin Arnoux.
I show a Katrin Arnoux
as the victim of
a hit‐and‐run in 2009.
Homicide?
Negative.
Victim was left paralyzed.
Any suspects?
Negative.
Would you like
contact information
on the investigating
detective?
Yeah.
Send it to the box.
Wait,
you don't think that...
10 years ago,
this girl was paralyzed
by a hit‐and‐run driver.
And right after,
Alice fell apart,
ended up here.
Sure sounds like guilt
to me.
We gotta find her.
She's a fugitive.
Look, I only went to Grey
because you refused
to deal with me.
You could have shown me
your body‐cam footage on scene.
I don't answer to you,
Five Percent.
No, you don't.
But if you are committed
to making this
an antagonistic relationship,
don't expect me
to roll over and take it.
Where ‐‐
Where is it?!
Looking for this?
That's mine!
Give it!
Who is she?
She's, um...
It's no one.
I j‐‐
It's not anyone.
It just ‐‐ I like it.
Her name
is Katrin Arnoux.
N‐N‐No.
No. No.
But I think
you know that.
What happened 10 years ago,
Alice?
Nothing. Nothing.
Nothing. I have to go.
I think something did.
Something that
destroyed your life.
N‐N‐No.
N‐No, no, no.
It was late.
Maybe you were tired.
You never saw her.
You tried to convince yourself
it was an animal,
but then you saw
the news.
And you tried to move on,
but it haunted you.
Poisoned every part of your life
until you ended up here.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You do.
And I think some part of you
is relieved it's finally out.
I never meant
to hurt anybody.
I'm sorry,
but you're under arrest.
Okay. Okay.
Son of a bitch.
What?
Who is he?
Corkscrew.
I knew him in Arizona.
If he's in LA,
something's up.
You met him
when you were undercover?
What are you do‐‐
What are you...?
What are you doing?
Um...
You know,
you're not supposed to
take off your uniform
on shift.
You gonna
run and tell Grey?
Just forget Grey.
Just tell me
what's going on.
I'm your only backup
out here.
Corkscrew knew me as a tweaker
named Crystal.
If I play it right,
he'll tell me why he's in town.
Only come in
if I need you.
How will I know?
You'll know.
Crystal?
These are my clothes.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's me.
Dude. Corkscrew.
Dude,
what are you doing here?!
Can we get hi‐res copies
of these?
No.
How about I take Rachel
to the shooting range?
Again, that is something
you would like.
You got to get something
for her.
I see couples at
the shooting range all the time.
All the time?
Okay, some of the time.
I think
it's a great idea.
You could do
a whole Insta story.
We can help.
An un‐boxing video
for the gun.
You posing
in the outfits.
There are no outfits.
It's Nolan.
So, answer it.
Why, 'cause you want intel
on the new TO?
Or don't answer it.
Suit yourself.
Hey, you're on speaker.
What's up?
Hypothetically, is it worse
to disobey a direct order
from your TO
or to stand by
and watch while they're killed?
Depends on the TO.
Look, disobeying a direct order
is a serious offense.
So really think about it
before you do it.
What's going on?
I'll let you know
when I figure it out.
Okay, so, look.
I‐I need cash.
You know, times is hard.
A guy like you's
in town.
Something big
must be going on.
I want in.
Forget it.
No, hey, look!
I'm a great lookout.
I‐It'd be like
old times!
Hey, the last time
you were supposed to help out,
you flaked!
I almost got pinched.
A buddy of mine's
doing five years.
O‐Okay, but that ‐‐ b‐but that's
not my fault, though.
Are you saying
it's mine?
You junkie bitch!
Hands where
I can see them!
Uh, uh, this crazy bitch
attacked me.
Turn around.
Put your hands on the wall.
Spread your feet.
Ma'am, I need you
to do the same thing.
Let him go. Arrest me.
Ma'am,
you're under arrest.
Come on.
Give me your hand.
I'm telling you,
she started it.
Oh, you can tell
just by looking at her,
that lady is trouble.
How long
have you known her?
I never seen her before.
Why? What did she say?
Nothing.
Just a routine question.
I just need your ID
and your mobile number,
and I can get
out of your hair.
Yeah, it's, uh ‐‐
It's 480 ‐‐
Sorry, I need to get it
off your actual phone.
Procedure.
Okay.
Perfect.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Alright,
we're far enough away.
Pull over and let me out.
Not until you answer
a couple of questions.
What did Corkscrew say?
Pull over!
What's he doing in LA?
I am your TO.
Pull over now!
Yeah, you know what?
You really
don't act like it.
You know,
I'd tell you what he said,
but you'd probably just blab it
to some random waitress.
Okay, how am I
the untrustworthy one here?
Everything you have
said to me so far
is either a lie
or an evasion.
Not lying
when I say I hate you.
You know, I don't even think
you can help it anymore.
I don't think lying
is second nature to you.
I think it's first.
It's who you are.
Pull over right now,
Five Percent,
or I will have your badge.
Pretty sure
I'm getting fired.
You're pretty sure?
Dude, you are
100% getting fired.
But you got
to let her out.
I can't stand down now.
I've gone too far.
You can't keep her
in there forever.
What's your plan?
Dessert.
How did you do that?
The shop only opens
from the outside.
Enjoy your cupcake
'cause it's the last thing
you'll eat as a cop.
I got Corkscrew's
mobile number.
We can track his contacts
and his movements.
Still fired?
Not today.
Definitely tomorrow.
Control, I need
to monitor a cellphone.
What is she wearing?
More importantly,
what's she doing in our house?
Detectives don't go back
to patrol.
It's got to be a demotion.
Jackson heard
she has a golden ticket.
She had her pick of assignments,
and she chose this?
Nah. Something wonky's
going on.
That's really her?
We think so.
She looks so...
so pathetic.
As far as we can tell,
her life fell apart
after she hit you.
It's almost impossible
for a transient
to hang on
to anything.
Belongings are stolen,
confiscated by the city.
But she held on
to your picture for 10 years
in conditions
worse than prison.
She never
let herself forget.
Even for a moment.
What are you saying?
She's suffered enough?
Back in the day,
if she was arrested,
she would have gotten
three years in prison.
Maybe five.
Instead,
she's been punishing herself
for the last decade.
She ran
but didn't escape.
I'll never run again,
Officer Lopez.
Yes, ma'am.
I apologize.
I wasn't trying to excuse
what she did to you.
Only ‐‐
Only what?
She destroyed
a part of me.
And you have the nerve
to plead her case?
She was out of line.
No, she's right.
I overstepped.
This is Ross Tegan,
AKA Corkscrew.
He operates as a straw buyer
out of Arizona,
transporting unlicensed weapons
into California
where they end up
on our streets.
Thanks to Detective Harper,
we now know the location
of his next sale.
Detective?
He may not look like much,
but Corkscrew
is putting guns in the hands
of the most dangerous gangs
in the city.
Cut off his pipeline,
our streets get safer,
and our jobs get easier.
So we'll observe
the exchange
from a van
across the street.
As soon as the buy
takes place,
SWAT will move in
to make the arrest.
What about me?
So, you and Nolan
will secure the perimeter
with Bradford and Chen.
Make sure we don't get
any nasty surprises.
So, it's my bust,
but you want me
to wait outside?
That's exactly what I want,
Detective Harper.
Is that gonna be a problem?
No, sir.
Good.
Gear up.
Hang back, Nolan.
You need to watch
your back.
Oh, I'll be miles
from the action.
I mean with Harper.
Now, Grey's put you
in a bad position.
She's a land mine
waiting to go off.
So if you find yourself
in a jam, text Officer Chen.
We'll be there.
Thank you.
Don't go
all emotional on me.
Training rookies
is a sacred duty,
and it bothers me when cops
don't treat it that way.
Just be safe.
Let's go, Chen.
Nice.
No serial numbers?
Yeah.
And they're $250 apiece?
That's the deal.
Can you get 100 more?
Sure.
I got 'em close by,
as long as you got the cash.
I'll text my guy.
They're upping the buy.
Hold position.
Who's the buyer?
Most likely, it's one of
two local arms dealers ‐‐
Osito or Brooker.
Osito.
The Teddy Bear?
It's his nickname.
I assume
it's meant to be ironic.
Between those two guys,
they provide 60% of the guns
from here to Fresno.
Sounds like
firsthand knowledge.
You work undercover on that
before the task force?
You've been doing
your homework.
Need to know
who I'm riding with.
Hmm.
And...?
Don't you think
you know me now?
Oh, I don't think
even you know you.
Whatever.
That's a bunch of crap.
Ever considered therapy?
What makes you think
I'm not already in therapy?
You ever thought about
more therapy?
You hate every gift idea
I pitch.
Because they're all
things you want.
It's not just guy stuff.
Isabel loved going
to the shooting range.
Isabel was a cop.
You're basically
the same person.
Rachel
has different interests.
So, what you're saying is
I should stop coming up
with my own ideas
and just listen to you?
Basically.
Look, man,
is the money coming or not?
He'll be here.
This is taking too long.
If Osito wants more,
set up another buy.
Alright, deal is done.
Moving in.
Perimeter units,
lock down all traffic.
What? No. No.
Hold that order.
Stay in position.
Who the hell is this?!
Harper.
Osito is a must‐catch.
If we roll up on these guys now,
we will spook him,
He's not coming, and we can't
risk losing these two.
Yeah, but ‐‐
Detective Harper,
this is not your call.
Respect the chain of command
and your fellow officers,
or I will fire you,
golden ticket or not.
Team one, move in.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're on perimeter.
I am not gonna let these guys
blow my operation.
It is blown!
The only thing you're gonna
accomplish charging in there
is having Grey fire you.
And while I would love
to be rid of you,
I am positive
you are here for a reason.
That golden ticket could have
gotten you any detail anywhere.
You picked this.
So I have to believe
that reason is important ‐‐
too important to blow it
because of a bruised ego.
Man #1: Hands up!
Don't move! Don't move!
Do not move!
Man #2: Put your hands
behind your back.
Hold on.
Keep still, keep still,
keep still.
Look, if you're expecting
a thank you ‐‐
Oh, I know
better than that.
Man #1: Hands on the car!
Man #2: Keep your hands up.
This one's clean.
Did you see that?
What?
That blue Mustang
just made a U‐turn.
That driver looked scared.
That could be
Osito bringing the money.
Or it could be
some random guy
that realized he left his phone
at the store.
No, the look
on that driver's face,
when he saw the cops ‐‐
that's our guy.
What did he look like?
Hispanic, mid‐30s,
full face, brown hair,
scar over his left eye.
That's Osito.
Don't call it in.
SWAT already has their bust.
This guy is mine.
They're on Osito, but Harper's
enforcing radio silence.
Tell me he invited you
to track his phone.
Yep.
7‐Adam‐19.
We're Code 4 on the scene.
Breaking down
the perimeter.
Where is he headed?
He can't live here.
With any luck, he's leading us
to his home base.
I'd feel a lot better
with backup.
Nah,
that's too conspicuous.
Long as he doesn't know
we're following him,
there's no telling
where he might lead us.
You are aware
we're in a black and white?
I know.
So, what now?
It's perfect.
There's only one way in...
or out.
7‐Adam‐15.
We got a 417
at Diamond Lock Storage.
19901 Jefferson Boulevard.
Requesting backup and airship.
Code 2 High.
Feel better?
No.
Let's go.
Don't move.
Lay down
flat on your stomach.
Hands out to your sides,
palms up.
Ready?
LAPD!
Malfunction!
Get covered.
Covering! Covering!
Moving in.
Get up! Get up!
Hey, let's go! Let's go!
Are you okay?
The vest caught it.
Looks like you've got a little
warrior in you, after all.
And you've got
a little guardian.
Hey, watch your mouth.
Osito!
It's over!
Put your weapons down
and come out
with your hands high.
Hands on the car!
Turn around!
Get down on your knees!
Hands behind your head!
Got him.
Now, doesn't that
make it all worthwhile?
No.
But it helps.
Protect and serve.
You can't throw a dead cat
around you without...
What do you think?
That I'm glad he's not
yelling at me like that?
Say it.
I'm sorry that my recklessness
put you in jeopardy.
My job is to train you,
not to chase after
my own windmills.
And?
If you would like
to file a formal complaint,
I will not hold it against you
in any way.
No, I'm good.
But when you're ready,
I'd like you to tell me
why you're here.
I wouldn't
hold your breath.
And for the record,
technically, Five Percent
should be your nickname.
Is that it?
Yes. No.
Have a nice evening.
You always
have to push it.
Ms. Arnoux.
Thank you for coming in.
I didn't like
the way we left it.
I shouldn't have
unloaded on you like that.
I was completely
in the wrong.
I made your situation about me,
my own issues.
It was insensitive,
and I'm sorry.
If there's
anything I can do
to help you through
this process, I'm here.
Your own issues?
I got into a fight with
a boyfriend in high school.
We were at a party.
I left.
He got drunk
and flipped his car.
It was a closed casket.
After that,
I went into a dark place,
and I guess Alice's guilt
just triggered something in me.
Really, if you need anything,
here's my card.
Wait.
When it happened,
I thought she had taken
everything from me.
But the truth is
my life is amazing.
I have a husband who I met
at physical therapy
and two kids
who are my whole world.
I've gained so much more
than I've lost.
Can I tell them that ‐‐
the DA?
Will it help?
Yeah.
A statement from you
could mean the difference
between hard time
and treatment.
That's very generous
of you.
No.
It costs me nothing.
♪ Your heart is pure ♪
♪ Of this ♪
Hey.
Hey!
♪ I am sure ♪
It's your birthday.
Yes, it is.
But I'm heading to dinner
with my family.
That's okay.
I just came by
to give you this.
You wrap that yourself?
Is it that obvious?
No, it's not.
Should I open it now?
Sure.
♪ Let's build a bridge ♪
♪ And meet somewhere in the middle ♪
It's a, um ‐‐
Chuck Yeager's Bell X‐1.
First plane
to break the sound barrier.
Yeah.
I just thought maybe
we could put it together
Friday night
instead of going out.
I'd love that.
Good.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
And thanks
for the present.
Yeah.
♪ We made promises ♪
♪ We said we'd keep ♪
Okay.
Have fun
with your parents.
Thanks.
♪ Let's build a bridge and
meet somewhere in the middle ♪
♪ We'll put it together
little by little ♪
♪ Things will get better ♪
♪ And our love ♪
♪ Our love will last for ♪
Have a good day at school.
Bye!
♪ In the middle ♪
♪ Put it together little by little ♪
What are you doing here?
You can't see her
without supervision.
I know. I know.
Look, my lawyer's
filing a petition.
You're late on child support
and you can afford a lawyer?
Here's half.
I‐I was gonna mail it
to you this morning, but...
I'm getting a pay bump
at work.
So I should be able to get it
squared in a few weeks.
Whatever.
I'm also petitioning
for joint custody.
♪ Let's build a bridge
and meet somewhere ♪
50‐50.
♪ In the middle ♪
And who will
look after her
when you disappear
for months at a time?
That's over.
I'm back working patrol.
Regular hours.
Right here in the neighborhood.
♪ Things will get better ♪
Are you okay?
♪ And our love ♪
I'm getting there.
♪ Our love will last forever ♪
And then I'm getting her back.
Corrected by
Flatto (subscene.com)