- Previously on "The Rookie"...
- Nick Armstrong.
You can't be faithful to a girl,
you can't be faithful
to an oath or a badge.
I'll drink to that.
I interviewed for my
dream job. I got it.
- That's great!
- It's in New York.
Rosalind Dyer,
the most rare of unicorns...
a female serial killer.
I led the task force
that caught Rosalind.
Don't let me off that easy!
My wife was dying! I wasn't there!
I do know one last secret.
- I don't care.
- It's about Armstrong. And it is bad.
Name names, okay? Just testify.
Armstrong.
She said his name before she saw him.
_
Hollywood division is in pursuit
after a shots fired call.
Uh, gr... gray Maserati, no plates.
Suspect vehicle is picking up speed.
He's... He's blowing lights.
Sidewalk! Sidewalk!
He's on the sidewalk!
- Wait. That voice.
- We are lead car.
- That's Chris.
- I'm gonna need backup, guys!
We went to the Academy together.
- Hey, get back! Get back!
- Hands! Hands on the window!
Okay, keep breathing.
7-Adam-07, shots fired.
Officer down. Repeat, officer down.
Hey. Not a good time right now.
Serj just shot a cop.
That was him?
If he can escape...
Escape? Ruben, come on.
Even if he gets clear,
10,000 cops are hunting him.
Attention all units,
Air-12 spotted a gray Maserati
matching suspect's vehicle
entering covered parking
structure at 6th and Grand.
They just spotted his
car, man. He's cooked.
Well, if he's cooked, then so are you.
- You understand?
- Ruben!
Damn it!
There.
Got a gun.
You need to secure it while
I go after the suspect.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Suspect vehicle located
in a parking structure on 6th and Grand.
Gun on scene. Need backup. Code 3.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Shut down all Code 3 units.
Suspect is G.O.A.
Hey. I don't know how,
but Serj got away.
'Cause I'm a slippery bitch.
Serj, don't be smug.
You left the damn gun in the car.
It must've slipped out.
Yeah, and when ballistics matches it
to the wounded officer,
you're gonna spend the rest
of your life in Pelican Bay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Screw that.
Ruben said you were gonna fix it.
So fix it. We own you.
Okay, if I can make the gun go away,
it'll cripple any case against you.
- What do you think I should do?
- Go to ground.
And don't call me no more. You hear me?
Everything goes through Ruben.
No sign of the suspect?
No, he got away clean. But
we did recover his weapon.
Nine-mil. Recently fired.
Good work. Anything else?
Uh, yes. Car is registered
to a dealership...
International Luxury Auto.
- Stolen?
- Not reported.
We need to run background checks
on the dealership employees.
Already happening, but we
would get a much faster ID
from the mobile fingerprint
unit inside your car.
We pulled a clean print from
the driver's side window.
Uh, yeah. Great.
And just like that,
our suspect has a name.
Serj Derian.
Control, suspect is Serj Derian.
Run a full background check
and alert the Watch Commander.
_
LAPD! Serj Derian,
come out with your hands up!
- Clear!
- You got something?
- Police report.
"Suspect... Serj Derian".
His name is all over these.
Someone inside the department
has been feeding intel
to the Armenian mob.
And by someone, you mean...
A dirty cop.
Still thinking about Grace?
You're a good detective.
You're an easy case.
You know what?
When we get back to the station,
I'm gonna book the evidence,
I'm gonna call her.
Call her?
You better get your ass over there
and tell her in person.
They're putting together a
raid at Ruben Derian's house.
- Is Serj there?
- Only one way to find out.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Attach us to that ATL.
_
- Any eye on Serj?
- Not yet,
but there's at least a
handful of unknowns inside.
I would put Stapleton, Cole,
and Brady on the 3/4 corner.
Jennings and Sanchez,
they can take the 2 side,
and we'll join in on the stack.
Sorry. Second nature.
All good, sir. You're the
senior detective on site.
Operation is yours.
Okay.
You're acting detective?
- For the day.
- Doing great.
Okay. Stack, fall in.
Suit up.
Redcon 1, let's go. Let's move.
Stand up!
Hands on your head! Turn around!
What can I do for you?
We have a warrant to search
the premises for Serj Derian.
You could have just called.
So much banging and
crashing just to discover
that my brother didn't randomly drop by.
All clear. No sign of Serj.
Mr. Derian, we'd like you to come
with us to the station voluntarily.
Yeah, you bet.
Uh, look, why don't I meet
you guys down there, huh?
There's only a half-hour left.
_
- Best game of the season. Good series.
- _
Tactical master class.
What the hell's going on?
Why was I called to your
station, Code 2 High?
Because they know a cop took Serj's gun
from Nolan's shop during the raid.
They're checking body cameras.
I'm dead. Mine wasn't on.
T-They're gonna know the second
that they check that video.
- Hold it together, Erin.
- Screw that!
I'm the one exposed here.
You have to do something.
I am! And if you do exactly what I say,
you've got a shot at getting away clean.
Ruben's got a half a million
for you, to help you disappear.
You're lying.
No, I'm not.
And with me on the inside
making sure the case
against Serj falls apart,
you just might be able to survive this,
but only if you play it cool, okay?
I'm scared.
I know.
Turn in your body camera
and then get out of here.
But first, leave your cellphone
and anything else they
can use to track you.
You got someplace to go where
you can get off the grid?
Yeah. I do.
Okay. Good.
Don't screw me here, Detective.
I won't.
You told her I'd give
her a half a million?
- Are you crazy?
- Hey, hey,
hey, don't cheap out on me now, Ruben.
- Erin's lost everything.
- Not yet.
Listen to me.
- You don't have to kill her.
- She's weak.
She'll flip the second they catch her,
and she won't just give me up.
She'll give you up, too.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do. And so do you.
Which is why you're gonna
make sure she stays silent.
Forever.
No. I won't.
I've done a lot of bad things for you,
but I ain't doing that.
Yes, you will, my friend.
Because when you sell me your soul,
you don't get to choose how I use it.
Hey, you... Ruben!
Hey! You...
Alright.
7-William-10, are you clear for a 10-21?
- Code 3.
- 7-William-10.
Clear.
Hey, Nolan. What's up?
We have a possible
location for Erin Cole.
You want in?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I want in.
_
- Clear!
- What do we got?
She's on foot. A few steps ahead.
Alright, everybody head inside.
Split up. She could be anywhere.
You know me. Come on.
We've been through a lot together.
You can talk to me. Just talk to me.
I never wanted this.
I had problems. You know?
Debts.
They paid them, and then...
then they owned me.
Who did? The Derians?
Yeah.
And I told Serj I was done,
but he... he pulled a gun
and he tried to kill me
when I wouldn't scare and...
The shots fired call.
Chris is dead because of me.
No, no, no! Wait! No, don't.
It doesn't have to all be for nothing.
Okay, you can start to make this right.
Just...
name names.
Okay? Just testify.
Armstrong.
25-year-old female,
multiple gunshot wounds to the chest.
Not conscious, not breathing.
You did good, my friend.
Very good.
I'm out.
There is no out.
You know this.
Shut up! Shut up!
I said I'm out.
I've paid my debt off five times over.
I can't do this anymore.
You can't make me.
There... is... no... out.
I s-s...
Your work isn't done.
The cops don't have
any evidence on Serj.
But you need to make
sure it stays that way.
And if anyone gets close to the truth...
you need to take care of them.
I promise it'll be
easier the second time.
Armstrong.
No!
- You think I'm crazy.
- _
No. It's just been a traumatic 24 hours,
and I think you're fried.
It's clear...
she says "Armstrong"
before he steps out.
She was trying to tell
me something about him.
Maybe, but it could have been anything.
I mean, look, we know
that Erin was a dirty cop,
but we have seen nothing to suggest
that she was working with
anyone else on the job.
How did she get into my shop, then?
I locked it.
And as a detective,
Armstrong would have a very easy time
getting his hands on those files
without leaving a paper trail.
So, what, Armstrong murdered
Erin to shut her up?
Do you realize what
you are accusing him of?
Yes, I do. He's my friend...
and a mentor, and this is killing me.
But if I'm right,
he's betraying everything we stand for.
It's not enough.
So we gather more evidence.
Armstrong was with me
nearly all day yesterday.
It was a fast-moving situation,
but he had to have contacted
both Ruben and Erin,
contact that could have
been caught on body cam,
on shop cam or dash cam.
Which you need me
to authorize access to.
Alright.
I'm in.
But don't tell anyone else about this.
If this gets out,
it will ruin Armstrong's life...
and your career.
And if I'm right?
Then it will tear the department apart.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Thanks for being positive about my move.
Well, you haven't moved until
you get on that flight tonight.
And we still have one last dinner.
You'll come visit, right?
I mean, once Lucy's
Thirty Day Push is over?
Hey. You're here early.
That would imply I left.
Any movement?
There's still no evidence
that puts Serj in that car.
And they checked every traffic
camera on the chase route?
Yeah. All the way to the parking garage
where the Maserati was abandoned.
And without the murder weapon,
I have to put Serj in that
car during the shooting
or he's gonna get away
with killing a cop.
How you holding up?
I watched him die.
It's, um...
It's tearing me up.
I've been where you are.
I'm gonna help you get through it.
Thank you.
Alright.
We're gonna have to recanvass,
starting with the original 911 call.
L.A. is the most self-obsessed
city on the planet.
Someone has a photo that
puts Serj behind the wheel.
Just watch.
Every time there's a break in the case,
Armstrong sends a text.
_
Okay, right here. Outside Ruben's house.
When he crosses past Erin,
you can see him slip her something.
That's a stretch. You
can't see their hands.
True, but after this, inside the house,
Armstrong is checking
his phone during the raid
to see when Erin has got
the gun from my shop,
and I swear to God,
you can see the exact
moment he finds out she did.
Well, this is all still circumstantial.
I mean, Armstrong could
be texting his mother
or his girlfriend.
I'm not saying that I believe that,
but this is still not
enough to take to IA.
What if we can tell what
he was texting and to who?
Could we get a warrant?
Search his phone records?
If Armstrong really is dirty,
do you believe that he is dumb enough
to crime on his own personal cellphone?
No.
I can't get a warrant for a burner
unless we know the number.
So how do we get that number?
Isolate the signal somehow.
Get him out in the middle of nowhere,
where there's only a few active phones,
and then we pull the records
from the nearest cell tower.
So how do we get him out there?
I have an idea.
How did the shooting inquiry go?
Smooth so far.
They said they might reach
out for some follow-up,
but given what's at stake,
they're keeping me active duty.
That's good news.
We need you out there
turning over rocks,
- avenging Officer Rios.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Yes?
I might have a way to run down Serj.
You got my attention.
There's a former contact of
mine from way back in the day.
He runs in the same
circles as Serj and Ruben.
He might talk to me.
Well, run it down.
You don't need my permission.
I do if I want to go
plainclothes and unmarked.
I'll spook him if I show
up in blues and a shop.
Do it.
Good having you back out there, Nick.
Hey!
You, uh, mind if I tag along?
Better than finding my own clues.
Sure. The more, the merrier.
Great. Uh, let me grab my keys.
I'll meet you in the parking lot.
What I'm about to tell
you stays between us.
Okay.
For the last nine months,
Vice has had an active informant
inside Ruben Derian's operation.
Cisco Fane.
Third-generation bottom-feeder.
He's helped generate
three search warrants
netting over $2 million in narcotics.
He could give us Serj.
That's the hope.
But Cisco's been radio silent
since he was sent a request
for a meet yesterday.
And you're worried
he's been compromised?
I'm worried he's been
dumped in a shallow grave.
You think Erin's the only
dirty cop on Derian's payroll?
I think you always plan for the worst,
which is why we're
keeping this op quiet.
Any idea where Cisco
could be? If he's not dead.
Well, the Derians have been muscling in
on the east side sex trade.
They've taken over
SROs, massage parlors,
and a karaoke bar where Cisco works.
I-I still can't believe karaoke bars
are covers for brothels.
Everywhere is a cover for a brothel.
That's depressing.
I should ride with Armstrong.
We need eyes on him at all times.
Alright, but be very
careful what you say.
If you are right about him,
he's basically been operating undercover
inside the police department.
- His radar is gonna be hypersensitive.
- Got it.
- And make him drive.
- Okay.
Why?
Behind the wheel, you're
at a tactical disadvantage.
If anything goes south,
you'll need both hands
to defend yourself.
So, who's your contact?
Just some overachieving
dirtbag I used to hang with.
He got a name?
Yep.
Ah, okay. Okay.
I'm piggybacking on your play. I get it.
You at least gonna tell me where
we're meeting Mr. Nameless?
Uh, Baldwin Hills.
Cool if I ride with you?
Sure thing.
You mind driving, though?
I didn't get much sleep last night.
- Sure.
- Great.
This is where the
high-speed chase began.
9:15 yesterday morning, a local
calls in shots fired to 911.
Based on Erin's confession,
we know that she was meeting
Serj here to pass along intel.
Things got heated, and they
started firing at each other.
Chris and his T.O. arrive on
the scene two minutes later,
in time to see the Maserati
haul ass out of here.
Eight minutes later,
Chris is fatally wounded.
You sure you're up for this?
- You could still take the day, if you need it.
- No way.
I want to see this guy in
handcuffs just as badly as you.
On the bright side, it sure does
put my wedding drama in perspective.
Does that mean you're letting
the two moms plan the festivities?
Hell no. But I will work a little harder
to listen to their advice.
Uh, excuse me, sir?
Were you here yesterday morning?
No, they chased me out.
- Who chased you out?
- The bride and groom.
- What were they doing?
- Who?
- The bride and groom.
- Posing.
For what? Photos?
Wait, why would someone
take wedding pictures here?
Who cares why? Were they
taking pictures of themselves?
No, they had an angry camera lady.
She's the one that chased me away.
- That's something.
- Yeah.
Do you know who Harper's contact is?
To be honest, no.
She's always been very
protective of her sources.
Smart.
Gotta keep sensitive
information need-to-know.
Officer Cole proved that.
How you coping after the shooting?
Yeah, it's been rough.
I keep replaying it over
and over in my head,
wondering what I could
have done different.
She pointed her gun at you.
You had to take the shot.
Yeah, but you said you thought
you were getting through to her.
If I just hadn't
surprised her like that,
who knows what would have happened?
She might have flipped.
Given us Serj and Ruben.
And anyone else in the
department who might be dirty.
You think there's another
rat in the department?
God, I hope not.
It's Rachel's last night.
You doing anything special?
Dinner, take her to the airport.
Wow.
You always said it would
be a cold day in Hell
before you drove anyone to LAX.
So... are you really gonna
visit Rachel in New York?
No.
I'm gonna rip the Band-Aid
off at dinner tonight.
Long distance never works.
You don't know that.
Yeah. I do.
I'm really gonna miss her.
Me too.
So, what's the plan?
We're gonna go practice our ABCs.
What if we find Cisco?
- Improvise.
- Thank you.
Why does God hate me?
Good morning.
We're here conducting
an Alcohol Beverage
Control compliance check.
Kiss my ass. We don't serve minors here.
I follow the laws, even the dumb ones.
Convincing argument,
yet we're gonna need to
put eyes on everyone here.
It's the Police Department.
I need everyone to step
out into the hall now.
- Come on.
- Let's go. Come out.
IDs out.
Step outside.
- Let's go.
- Tim.
Don't you shoot up my club.
I just had it painted.
Get everyone back.
This is the police.
Need you to step out into the hall now.
Aw. Whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa.
What's going on?
What the hell'd you say to me?
- What?
- Get up against the wall.
Put your hand up.
What?
LAPD's been looking for you.
Look, after the shooting,
Ruben locked everything down,
made everyone give up their phones.
Here's a new one.
I need you to find out
where Serj is and text me.
They'll cut me into
pieces if they catch me.
Tough, alright?
You do it, or I violate
you and send you to Lompoc.
- You got that?
- Yeah.
He's clean.
Watch your attitude next time.
I told you, we don't serve minors.
Yeah, you did.
But I noticed a half-dozen
other infractions.
I'd get those fixed
before Code Enforcement
shows up in the morning.
Have a nice day.
I checked every event space
within a mile of the warehouse.
None of them had weddings yesterday.
Where'd this bride and groom come from?
No idea. And without
a venue to question,
we're left calling up every
photographer in Los Angeles.
Well, social media to the rescue.
#Wedding.
That's a lot.
Try #WreckTheDress.
- Okay.
- It's the new thing.
Destroy your dress after the wedding.
Wait, don't dresses cost a fortune?
Why in the hell would people do that?
To spite their mother-in-laws.
- Wait.
- Whoa.
That's the Maserati.
We gotta get that photographer in here.
Stay here. I won't be long.
Excuse me. With all due respect,
we should be in there with you,
in case things go sideways.
Negative. My guy is skittish.
If I need you, I will signal.
She go rogue like this all the time?
Not all the time.
Why are you so worried?
I'm not.
I just want to do this by the book.
The last thing we need
is another officer down.
Ah. That's Henry.
Do you mind if I take this?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey.
How's he doing?
Uh, definitely anxious.
- He text anyone?
- No, not yet.
Alright. I'll stay inside
another 10 minutes,
make him sweat.
_
Hey, Grace.
Hey. You answered.
Yeah. Sorry. A lot's been going on.
I know. I...
I wasn't thinking.
I just, um...
We need to talk.
I gotta go.
Wha... You... You were
supposed to stay outside.
Where's your guy?
He went out back.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah. Thought I heard something.
Did your guy give up Serj?
No. Man, he was... he
was just playing me.
He... He just wanted reward money.
That's aggravating.
But that's the job, right?
90% failure, 5% victory.
What's the other 5%?
Fear.
You mind driving back
with Detective Harper?
I've intruded on your time long enough.
- You got it.
- Alright.
See you later.
You think he knows?
I think we better pray
bringing him out here
was worth the risk.
Alright, I got the cell records
from the nearest tower.
Four cellphones were pinged
during the 15 minutes we've been here.
Mine, yours,
Armstrong's official cell...
hmm... and this.
His burner. We got it.
Can you pull up his
call and text records?
- Damn it.
- What?
That number was first
activated this morning.
He hasn't made a single call or text.
He's using a fresh burner phone today?
That is smart.
Cops make the best criminals.
We got to be smarter.
We got to trip him up somehow.
We got to get into his head.
What?
Told you you'd be back.
You told me not to trust Armstrong.
Oh, John.
I get so few visitors.
Let's catch up first.
There's no time.
Maybe for you.
I've got nothing but time.
So, are you seeing anyone?
We're not talking about that.
Protective.
Which means that you are.
Okay, fine. Yes, I'm seeing someone.
She's an amateur astronomer
and professional luge polisher.
We met at a Lizzo concert.
We're gonna raise ocelots
together. It's very exciting.
Now, let's get back to Armstrong.
- You're no fun at all.
- Two cops are dead,
and the guy I thought was
my friend is responsible.
Now help me...
Kill him?
Catch him.
Mm. Less interesting.
And help will cost you.
Cost me what?
The truth. About that girlfriend.
- Forget it.
- Okay.
She's thinking about
going back to her husband.
She's been trying to call me all day.
Well, call her back.
Right now.
Hey.
You've been trying to call me
to tell me you're getting
back together with Simon.
I'm sorry.
Do you love him?
No.
But I have to do this for Oliver.
I know you think you do,
- but you're wrong.
- John...
I've been going back and
forth in my head for days.
Do I give you your space
or do I tell you how I feel?
I know how much you love your son.
I know you'd do anything
to make him happy.
But I've been down this road.
I've stayed together for
the kid, and it's a mistake.
Please don't.
I mean, this is so hard for me to do.
Grace, I love you.
That has to matter.
I have to go.
- Grace...
- I'm sorry.
How are you feeling?
Don't push it, Rosalind.
Now tell me what you
know about Armstrong.
Before my arrest, he broke into my house
without a warrant.
Yeah, he told me about that.
Well, I broke into his.
Afterwards.
And you found something.
A hidden compartment in
the laundry room wall...
filled with all kinds of goodies.
Like what?
Money. Guns. Evidence.
The sort of thing a crooked
cop keeps for insurance.
Sadly, nothing I could use
to keep me out of prison.
Unfortunately for you...
they're not gonna take
the word of a serial killer
- to give you a search warrant.
- No, they're not.
I'm gonna have to do
what you did... break in.
Hope that I can find something
that will lead me to
evidence I can actually use.
I don't think your T.O.
is gonna approve of that.
You'd be surprised.
But this is a one-man operation.
I owe Harper too much to
put her career in jeopardy.
So noble.
I give you 6-to-1 odds against, though.
Odds of what?
Surviving.
Armstrong is much
smarter than you, John.
Twice as ruthless. Hell, he caught me.
So, if this is the last time I see you,
you will live on in my fantasies.
Well, that makes one of us.
I told you I'd keep you posted.
I'm taking care of it.
You don't have to know how.
I gotta go.
- Hey.
- Are you still at the prison?
I'm on my way back.
Rosalind give you anything useful?
Nah. It was a dead end.
Uh, I think it's time to
bring Grey into the loop.
How far away are you?
20 minutes.
Rachel.
Hi. I'm at the front desk.
- Where are you?
- Oh.
I am... I'm sorry.
The day just got away from me.
I can be back in 20 minutes.
Uh, Tim. It's Cisco.
He got a location on Serj.
- Rach...
- I heard.
Go get him.
I am so sorry.
It's okay. I-I understand.
Guess I'll, uh, call you when I land.
- In New York.
- Yeah.
Uh, please do that, okay?
And again, I'm... I'm sorry.
Better this way.
Wait, go back.
We got him. Thank you.
Sir, we found photos that put Serj
in the Maserati during the pursuit.
Great job. Gear up.
We just got a location.
SWAT's mobilizing.
Harper, grab Nolan, get
ready for a tactical assault.
- Wheels up in two minutes.
- Sir, Nolan is currently unavailable,
- but if I could talk to you in private for a second...
- No time.
We got a cop killer to catch.
All available units respond
to the command post
at Wilshire and Devonshire.
Special operations has
located suspect Serj Derian
and is requesting marked units
for additional perimeter
and traffic control.
Attach over the box and
respond to the command post.
_
What?
They know where you are.
You gotta get out of there. Now.
You screwed me. You're a dead man.
Go!
Stop! Get your hands
in the air! Drop the gun!
Turn around! Get down on your knees!
One down! Two steps back!
On your knees!
Don't move.
- Police! Don't move!
- Drop the gun!
You're under arrest for
the murder of Chris Rios.
Okay. Which terminal?
Uh, four.
Thanks.
Now what?
Passenger, please exit the vehicle.
I... I'm sorry I missed dinner.
It's okay.
I probably would have
spent the entire time
thinking about the end.
Is this the end?
Yeah.
I d... I don't know.
I... I spent the day
planning to say goodbye...
Yet, here you are.
And yet, here I am.
Look, Rach, I don't know
what happens next...
but I think we should find out.
_
Nick?
It's over, John.
- What is?
- All of it.
They caught Serj,
and I'm dead if I don't make a deal.
- Why did you do it?
- Not like this.
I owe you the truth, but face to face.
I'll be sitting in my living room.
The back door's still open
from when you broke in.
I'll be there in 10 minutes.
Right here, John.
Don't do anything stupid.
Little late for that. Where's Harper?
She's not along for this ride.
Get on your knees,
hands behind your head.
Sure, sure.
I got some things I want
to get off my chest.
Save it for IA.
Well, it's not for IA. It's for you.
Look, I can't make
this right. I know that.
But I have to at least try
to make you understand.
You don't think I understand?
You sold us out,
and you murdered Erin Cole.
She pointed a gun at me.
Look, I-I-I didn't want that to happen.
I got caught up in a rip
current five years ago
that I can't get out of.
When Rebecca died,
I was a quarter million
dollars in the hole.
Insurance covered a fraction
of what it cost to take care of her.
I had debt collectors calling me up
when I was out in the
street chasing criminals,
holding grieving victims in my arms.
And that makes everything you did okay?
- Of course not, but...
- No.
You once told me not
to let you off the hook.
"Confessed" to me that
Rosalind Dyer's case
stopped you from being there
for your wife when she was dying.
Now I know that was a lie,
a lie you told yourself
because the truth was too painful.
- What's the truth?
- You're a coward.
You weren't there for Rebecca
because you were too
weak to watch her suffer,
so you blamed the job, same
way you blame your debts
for becoming a criminal and a murderer.
It doesn't matter that you fell down.
Everybody falls down.
What matters is what comes next.
Do you make it right, or
do you just make it worse?
You know your problem, John?
You think you're better than people.
No. Just you.
Now get on the floor, arms out.
Here's the thing.
I-I knew you were
onto me this morning...
that whole wild goose chase.
So...
I spent the day preparing for the worst.
Last time I ask.
Get on the damn ground.
You were friends with Erin.
Hell, I found video of the two of you
conspiring outside a
bar the other night.
Turns out, Serj recruited
you the same time as Erin,
paid you serious money to
funnel police files to him.
- No one's gonna believe that.
- Yeah, they will.
'Cause I won't be the
only one saying it.
There's another cop on the payroll.
John Nolan.
Which bring us to this moment.
You broke into my house to kill me
because I found out you were dirty.
But I killed you in self-defense.
Aah!
Oh!
Ohh!
Ahh.
I wouldn't do that.
Control, this is Officer Nolan.
You don't have time for that, John.
You got to go, or they're gonna find it.
Find what?
The evidence in your house.
Hurry, John!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -