♪ The beat is on,
I'm on a roll ♪
♪ I put on my shoes ♪
♪ Stand and watch
as I tear it up ♪
Just a minute.
♪ 'Cause I'm comin'
for you ♪
Dad!
♪ And I got something,
all the loving ♪
Henry!
♪ Everything you need ♪
Dad.
Hey,
what are you doing here?
Abigail had a buttload
of flyer miles,
so we, uh, flew out
to surprise you.
Oh, my God.
Abigail, it's so nice
to finally meet you.
It's great
to meet you, too.
The videos
didn't do it justice.
This place is a wreck.
I think it's awesome.
It's like
a faded beauty queen
that you're bringing
back to life.
Oh, wow. You are quickly
becoming my favorite.
Mine, too.
Uh, we have
some good news.
Exciting.
Lay it on me.
I'm pregnant.
Kidding.
I'm -- I'm kidding.
We're engaged.
Sorry about
the pregnant thing.
I-I thought
it would soften the blow.
Abigail, uh, that is, um,
is beautiful.
That is a beautiful ri--
I hope you didn't, uh,
spend your tuition money.
I used the money that I was
saving to go to Europe,
because Abigail's the journey
I want to spend
the rest of my life on.
Aww.
That's so --
That is --
That's so...
Does your mom know?
She thought it would be best
if I told you in person.
Uh, yeah.
She also recommended
that we quickly follow the news
with some electrolytes.
That is...hilarious
and entirely unnecessary.
Have you set a date?
Not yet, but we're, uh,
we're talking about June.
Isn't it exciting?
It's so exciting.
Crap!
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
I feel like Goldilocks,
except instead of "too hot"
or "too cold,"
every guy I date is either,
you know, "too frat-bro,"
or "too stick me
with the check
because you are never going
to finish that screenplay
working on your abs."
Let's face it,
I am never going
to find someone.
Yeah,
not if you keep looking
in hipster clubs
and hot yoga studios.
Ah.
What you need
is a grown man.
I would just settle for
a decent pickup line.
Oh, thank God.
Okay. Wow.
We gotta go.
Thank you.
Mom.
What are you doing here?
Your father and I
are getting divorced.
Hi, Mrs. Chen.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, Jackson, sweetheart,
thank you.
What happened?
I don't want
to talk about it.
Okay, is this like the time
that you didn't
talk to Dad for a week
because he forgot
your birthday?
I said I don't want
to talk about it.
Oh. I'm sure my back
will be fine.
I assume
you have extra bedding.
Oh. Mom, you're not
sleeping on the couch.
I'll get you a hotel.
Nonsense.
No, I'll take the couch.
Mrs. Chen,
you can take my room.
Such a sweet boy.
Would you mind putting this
in my room?
I have to get ready
for work.
Is that really
what you're wearing?
Nice groupings.
Thanks.
So, I need yesterday's
after-action reports.
I will have them for you
at the end of shift.
You mean
when today's are due?
I know you're used to being
out on the edge, all alone,
but paperwork's
part of the gig here.
Copy that.
I will get caught up quick.
Officer Nolan's
not the only one
being evaluated,
Detective.
I know you got
the golden ticket,
but you got to do the work.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Henry got engaged.
Yeah,
he just turned 20.
I know.
It's too young.
Didn't you get married
around then?
That's not the point.
So, I just talked
to my dad.
Apparently, he only brought home
a bagel for himself.
He did not bring one
for my mom.
That's why she left?
Bagel that broke
the camel's back.
Maybe it's for the best.
Oh, God, no.
Separately, they will make
my life twice as miserable.
I have to get them
back together.
Just...
Morning.
She is definitely
warming up to me.
So, Officer West,
can you tell us
what a "friendly" is?
Yes, sir.
A "friendly" is another term
for a Confidential Informant.
Correct.
And Confidential Informants
can be an incredibly
useful tool.
They're definitely tools.
Are you saying you don't
use them, Officer Bradford?
No, sir.
Just saying that
they're lying liars who lie
and they need
to be dominated,
never allowed to think
they're in control.
Officer Lopez,
you agree?
No, sir.
C.I.s are most useful
when they think
they're part of the team.
You're both wrong.
Please, school us, Detective.
C.I.s are just people
trying to get by.
Some are psychopaths
who play ball
because it's
the best available option,
some are people
in over their heads
who cling to you desperately
as a way out of trouble.
Treating them all the same
is a mistake.
Well, it's time to put
these theories to the test.
Nolan, Chen, part of the second
phase of your training
is developing
your first C.I.
See, you've known
this day was coming,
so I'm confident that you have
a plan of action in place.
But be forewarned --
you will be evaluated on
the arrests
generated by your C. I.,
as well as
their long-term viability.
So, choose wisely.
Alright, that's it.
Be safe.
Sir, you have to let West
participate.
Do I?
You've read
my daily evals.
His work is as strong
as it's ever been,
and this is
an opportunity to prove
that he's ready
to move on.
It's a big swing,
Officer West.
Screw it up,
it's likely to be
the last nail.
You sure you want
to take that chance?
Yes, sir.
Alright. You're in.
Good?
Thank you, sir.
You are the greatest T. O.
in the history of T. O. s.
Here you go.
You got a choice
to make --
be conservative
or be bold.
Tim's gonna make sure
Lucy bags a work horse
for her first C.I.
Nothing flashy.
And Harper?
My guess is
she'll let Nolan drive it --
sink or swim on his own.
You think
we should go big.
It's the riskiest move,
but the one that will get you
into short sleeves quicker.
But a big fish takes time,
and if you fail
to recruit him,
you run the real risk
of hitting the week's end
without someone.
And Grey'll bounce me
for sure.
Screw it.
Let's go for it.
That's the spirit.
You got a candidate?
Yeah.
A guy the Feds use,
but you should hit an ATM
on the way over.
This guy's not cheap.
Hey, Nick. Heading home?
My bed awaits.
I just had
an armed robbery suspect
in the box all night.
I'm fried.
How're you?
I just found out
my son got engaged.
Whoa.
I-Isn't he, like, 12?
20.
Right.
You like the girl?
Abigail.
She seems very sweet.
Just met her for the first time
this morning.
Also 20.
You run her
through the system?
A background check?
No, it's against the rules,
and it's just...wrong.
If it were me,
I'd want to know.
See you tomorrow.
Well,
technically tonight.
-Right.
-Here you go.
Oh.
What are
we doing here, Boot?
As you're aware,
pawn shops are required by law
to notify law enforcement
if they believe someone
is trying to pawn off
stolen property.
I pulled city records.
This shop
has never called us.
Either the owner is a saint,
or --
Or he's dealing
with a lot of stolen goods.
Exactly.
Making them the perfect
candidate for my first C.I.
Don't get too cocky,
Officer Chen.
Recruiting a reliable C.I.
is hard work.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, my parents are...
Uh, never mind.
Morning.
Good morning.
What can I do for you?
We're doing interviews
for the detectives
in Robbery-Homicide.
Has anyone tried to pass off
stolen items recently?
No, absolutely not.
How do you know
they're not stolen
before you buy them?
'Cause I'm a very good judge
of people.
What's your impression
of me?
That you're
a very distrustful woman.
Detective Harrison,
it's Officer Chen.
Yeah, we're gonna need you
to send Code Enforcement
down to High-Life --
That's not necessary.
Hold on, Craig.
If you're above board,
there shouldn't be
a problem, right?
Okay.
There may be a few things
that are from
questionable sources.
Nice job.
Great, let's see it,
and don't give me any of that
low-end misdemeanor crap.
Woman brought this in
yesterday,
and it's not
the first designer bag
she's brought me.
Mm.
Retails for what?
Five grand?
Six.
What are you looking for?
These high-end bags
have serial numbers sewn in.
They're registered
to the original buyer.
Yeah.
Bingo.
Hey, there.
Bianca, right?
Do I know you?
No, I have this acquaintance
in narcotics.
He, uh --
Well, actually, I installed
a new kitchen island for him.
Anyway, I was telling him
I need a low-level drug mule
that I can flip into a C. I.,
and he mentioned you.
Bianca!
Why are you running?
We know where you live.
She's got drugs
in her bag.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Bianca, is that right?
Easy.
Okay. Easy. I got you.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Relax, okay?
Heroin?
Yep.
Enough to put Bianca
in prison
for the rest of
her child-bearing years.
Do you want to go
to prison, Bianca?
No.
Then you're gonna
have to flip on your boss,
and depending on
how that goes,
you're gonna become
an informant -- my informant --
pointing us to more drug dealers
and suppliers.
I can't do that.
They'll kill me.
And we'll protect you.
He can't promise you that.
You need to be clear
with a C.I.
You'll do your best
to treat them right,
look out for them,
but you're not God,
and you're not
with them 24/7.
Understood.
And thank you.
So, those are your choices,
Bianca.
You can go to jail
or you can help us.
What's it gonna be?
You're gonna get me killed.
Hey, if anything happens,
we'll be just
across the courtyard.
Your boss usually punctual?
For a drug dealer.
Look, don't be a hero.
Just give him the bag,
you take your fee,
you walk away,
just like you've done
hundreds of times.
All done.
Talk in a normal voice.
Tell the man
at the funeral home
that I want to be
turned into a tree.
Make sure they don't
put me in a box.
I get claustrophobic.
Bianca, I promise...
...if anything goes wrong,
we will be there.
Can I go to the bathroom
with this stuff?
Sure.
And don't listen.
Hey, girl.
I thought --
Yeah, don't do that.
He'll be here in a minute.
Let's get set.
Damn it.
So, I was thinking
we could start small,
see what type of intel
you have.
Hold your roll, Officer.
The only reason
I'm talking to you
is because you paid
my greens' fee.
Truth is, I work exclusively
with the Feds.
They pay way better
than the LAPD.
100 grand last year
for intel on
nine high-profile felonies.
Now,
you gonna match that?
While the LAPD can't beat
that kind of number,
your FBI handler
isn't gonna give you
the kind of personal attention
that I will.
He offering massages?
There's got to be
something or someone
that's bothering you.
My ex-wife is screwing
this Pakistani guy.
Owns a used car dealership
on Van Nuys --
definitely moving
stolen cars.
And why do you care?
My ex torched all
my Armani suits on the way out.
So, you take something
she cares about
away from her...
I'll play ball.
He's here.
He went into the room.
She's going in.
What's going on?
It's fine.
Let it play out.
See?
All good.
Arms up.
Hey, I don't get
to keep that?
Sorry.
Alright, well,
let's go get this guy.
Okay, just sit here,
relax.
The hard part's done.
Great job.
Freeze.
Police!
Hands up.
Drop the bag.
Interlace your fingers
behind your head.
Don't move.
Decent bust, rookie.
Bianca?
Hey.
Harper, I need Narcan
in the room right now.
Bianca. Hey.
Stay with me, alright?
Where'd she get the drugs?
Must have had a leftover
from the deal.
Easy, easy, easy.
I got you. I got you.
Control, 7-Adam-15 --
We need an ambulance
at the Dollar Motel on Olympic.
Female, 25,
head injury and overdose.
♪ If the squad ain't with me,
then it ain't right ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Ay-ay-ay-whoa ♪
♪ Yeah, ay ♪
Mrs?
Uh, these officers
want to speak with you.
Cool.
What's up?
We're here about
some stolen property.
Do you recognize
this bag?
Yeah, I've got one
just like it.
We believe this one is yours.
It was at a pawn shop.
We matched the serial number
to your credit card purchase.
Hilda!
Yes, Mrs?
You're fired.
What?
Please,
don't make a scene.
It'll just upset me.
Uh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, hey.
What's going on?
What did you do?
Hilda's been robbing us.
I have not.
Who are you?
This is my daughter,
Olivia.
Step-daughter.
You were 9 when I was born.
Olivia, do you know anything
about a stolen handbag?
The description
the pawn shop owner gave us
fits you more than
your housekeeper.
Yeah.
Yeah, I took it.
But she has so many,
she didn't even notice.
You are such a brat.
You're such a parasite.
Don't talk to your mother
that way.
You are not my mother!
Okay, calm down.
Calm down.
Both of you, okay?
I want her arrested.
It's the only way
she'll learn.
Are you sure that's what
her father would want?
Her father wants
whatever I tell him.
♪ Then it ain't right ♪
♪ Ay, ay, ay, ay ♪
Six stolen cars.
Grey's gonna be impressed,
but we still need to get Hickey
officially signed up.
On it.
Yo.
Mr. Hickey,
it's Officer West.
Your intel was spot-on.
We've impounded
six stolen vehicles
and arrested
Mr. Fawad Chandio.
That's awesome.
Nicky's gonna cry
for a week.
So, it means
you're on board?
I'm a man of my word.
Great.
We'll just need you
to come into the station
and fill out
some paperwork.
Yeah, you got it.
She'll be okay.
We're gonna
keep her overnight
and monitor her
for a concussion.
Thanks.
You know,
I still don't understand
how she overdosed
while in custody.
I left her alone
while we made the bust.
I just --
I feel terrible.
You two used to date.
What?
No -- What?
No.
Ye-- Well, yes, but --
I'm not judging.
You're very pretty.
Thank you.
Well, I'm not
uncomfortable at all,
and I think we should
probably go, right?
Nice meeting you.
You, too.
So, are you counting Bianca
as your first C. I.?
Shouldn't I?
Got a solid arrest
off her intel.
Yeah, but Grey's also evaluating
long-term prospects
and she doesn't have any.
Right.
Ever bother you
using people like that?
Nope. The drugs she's moving
kill people every day.
She's not a saint.
She's a criminal.
Right.
You didn't answer
my question.
You checking that box
and moving on?
No.
I need to find a real C.I.
Good answer.
So, where's your mom?
Uh...
She died last year.
Cervical cancer.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Thanks.
So, I left school
to be with my dad,
only to find out
that he'd been hooking up
with that trophy skank
while my mom
was in hospice.
Yeah, well, you shouldn't
go home tonight,
once you process out.
I don't have a choice.
Daisy convinced my dad
to hold on
to the money my mom left me
until after
I graduate from college.
Can he do that?
I don't know.
I can't really afford a lawyer
to find out.
Look, you are
in a bad situation,
but stealing, it's...
it's not gonna
make it better.
What will?
Am I crazy,
or was that way too easy?
It was a little easy.
On the other hand,
you showed Hickey
that you can get things done.
Lopez, West, my office.
I'm gonna call you back.
So, this is Special Agent
Wyck Bird from the FBI.
He says you're trying
to poach his informant.
Wait, sir,
I-I can explain.
Save your breath.
Hickey's mine.
Guy's a clearing house
of high-value intel.
Bureau doesn't need the LAPD
messing with our meal ticket.
I didn't know informants
came with exclusive rights.
Now you do.
He called you
to get us to back off.
And he used us
to do him a solid.
Now he's kicking us
to the curb.
He said
you were hassling him.
Stop hassling him.
Or else.
Sergeant.
Special Agent.
Sir --
Save it.
I told you what would happen
if you swung and missed.
You're dismissed.
So, you got a game plan
for running down a new C. I.?
Not yet.
Any suggestions?
Oh, that's right.
You're not here
to teach me.
Ms. Harper?
Hi.
Uh...um,
what are you doing here?
You didn't sign
your petition.
Right. I'm sorry.
I, um...
Excuse me. Hi.
John Nolan.
Hi. Good to meet you.
My name's --
None of his business.
Um...I'm gonna take 10,
you figure out a next step.
Come on.
This is bleak.
There's nowhere else
we can meet?
It's private.
I don't want anyone here
knowing my business.
Okay.
We got lucky
with the judge.
He believes
whenever possible,
it's important for the mother
to be part of the child's life.
Okay.
That's -- That's great.
How's it going here?
Uh, it's fine.
It's a lot harder than
I thought it would be.
What is?
Being normal.
You're doing great.
The better hours,
the new apartment --
the judge will be impressed.
I hope so.
'Cause if I don't
see my daughter soon,
I am gonna lose my mind.
Hey.
Hey, back at it already?
Yeah, couldn't sleep.
Just laid there,
staring at the ceiling.
Figured screw it --
I'll clock in early.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah, sure.
I need to recruit a C.I.
My first one --
she O. D.'d on me.
Oh.
You know what?
You need a forger.
They're at the hub of
all criminal activity.
Tell Logan
in Commercial Crimes
I asked him
to throw some names your way.
You are a life-saver.
Thank you.
Hey, John?
Yeah?
I ran a background check
on Henry's girlfriend.
Don't worry, I tied it
to an open investigation.
No one will ever know.
I-I didn't ask --
I know.
But if I were you,
I'd want to take a look
at what's inside.
What's that?
Nothing.
What was your thing about?
Great. Lunch?
Great.
So, what do I do?
Open it.
It's about
Henry's safety.
You should see
what it says.
Dad.
Hey!
Oh, my God.
You guys are all about
the surprises this week.
Hi, I'm Abigail --
Henry's fiancée.
Yeah, I know.
I just really love
saying that, so...
Congratulations.
Yeah, that's awesome.
What do you want to eat?
I'll come with you.
Okay. Good.
We'll be back.
Right.
May I take your order?
They look so happy.
I want that.
Baby steps.
Right.
Well, first, I have to get
my mother out of our apartment.
Yes.
They really do
seem happy.
Would I be sabotaging that
by reading
what's in this envelope,
or is that the illusion
and Abigail's just a time bomb
waiting to go off?
So, what's the next step
on the C.I. front?
Forger.
Who'd you get that from?
No one.
Detective Armstrong.
Cheating on me
with another detective?
I had no idea
we were exclusive.
Okay, we got too much,
but everything looked so good.
Perfect timing.
Uh, uh, Henry, Abigail,
this is Nyla Harper,
my training officer.
Nyla Harper,
Henry is my son.
And I know
what you're thinking --
far too young
to have a 20-year-old.
Nope.
Nice to meet you both.
Let's get to work.
Right.
Um, that's all you.
See you guys at home.
So, you got
a place to start,
or are we Googling
"forger"?
Ooh, I got a list.
Mm.
What did you think
of Abigail?
She seemed nice.
Why?
No reason.
They just got engaged.
Oh, good for them.
Yeah.
No?
No, I'm...
Yeah.
Oh.
It's great.
No, eh, eh...
Drunk driving --
Knock, knock.
Officers.
Can I help you?
Beat it.
This is your place?
Yes, sir.
You do head shots?
We sure do.
What about fake IDs?
No, sir.
Lying to a police officer --
that's a crime, isn't it?
Not as big a one
as forgery
and counterfeiting
government documents.
Just trying
to make a living.
These cellphone cameras
have killed my business.
Am I going to jail?
Well, that depends.
Maybe I can help you
if you help me.
I don't know
what that means.
Do you want me
to bribe you?
How much --
No. No. No.
That's not -- Okay.
How do I...
I need someone with their ear
to the street --
You're gonna be
his snitch.
My snitch.
We're gonna take all
this stolen property
as evidence.
We're gonna book it and tie it
to an unknown suspect.
If you screw us,
we will suddenly know
who the suspect is,
get a warrant,
and come arrest you.
We are looking for leads
on serious felons here, okay?
Not teenagers
trying to buy alcohol.
You making papers for anyone
like that right now?
I did get a head's up
about a big job
that might come my way.
Fake identities,
driver's licenses,
passports,
the works.
As soon as you get details,
you call me.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Congrats.
You have a real C.I.
I'm on my way home now, Mom.
Yes, I got the shopping list
you texted.
There's no milk because I'm
lactose intolerant, remember?
Mom, I gotta go.
Opal, what's up?
Thank you.
Tim.
Yo?
Olivia showed up
at Opal's pawn shop
with more of
her step-mom's stuff,
but she didn't want money
this time.
She wanted a gun.
Police!
7-Adam-19 --
shots fired at our location.
Send back-up.
I hate you!
Drop the gun!
You turned my dad
against me!
Olivia, drop the gun!
She ruined everything!
Now!
Stand up.
Keep your hands up.
Do not move.
You've made this
so much worse.
Come on.
You are gonna pay
for those bags.
Ma'am, stay right there.
What's going on?
What the hell
are you doing here?
I came to get
the rest of my things.
Wh-- Are you okay?
Officers,
would you like to see
where Mrs.
hides all her drugs?
Yes.
Yes, we would.
♪ They say Rocky
sold his soul ♪
♪ Tomorrow swerves
into yesterday ♪
I'm home!
♪ Well, he dove headfirst
into the deep ♪
About time.
It's way past your curfew.
Oh, very funny.
You have a lot of tattoos.
Oh, yeah. You like 'em?
Each one signifies
a meaningful moment of my life.
I'm trying to talk Henry
into getting one.
I have no idea
what I would get.
Yeah, well,
that's a decision
that will last you
a lifetime.
Yeah.
Oh, I see
what you did there,
Is anyone hungry?
I can tell
you're freaked out.
Don't be, okay?
Okay.
♪ Well, the neon lights
are on the red ♪
Hello?
Hey, it's John.
I really hope
I'm not, um...
stepping over the line here,
but I really have no one
to talk to about...anything
parenting oriented.
Never mind.
You know what?
I'll take care of this.
Just forget I called.
John, how can I help?
I'm having
a parenting emergency.
Good thing I specialize
in emergency medicine.
Are you
still at the hospital?
Yeah,
for a couple more hours.
Could I come
buy you a cup of coffee,
ask you some questions?
Of course.
Thank you.
I'm just gonna head right
back out for a little while.
Okay.
Oh, could you
pick up some pie?
Yeah, she loves pie.
I love pie.
Sure.
I feel like a monster.
You're not a monster.
I mean, you're a father.
So, I should just open this up
right now and read it?
Absolutely not.
But it's my job
to protect him.
It is your job
to respect him,
and running
secret background check
on the girl
he's in love with
is not doing that.
Okay,
but I didn't run this.
Doesn't matter.
No, no.
Of course not.
And yet, I still can't
bring myself to throw it away.
What if you read it?
And then that way,
you could just tell me
if she's a serial killer
or a mime.
No, but I will
throw it out for you.
But --
It's the right thing.
Hey, if you want to know
something about Abigail,
you should just ask her.
You're right.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I messed up.
I tried to regain
all the ground I lost,
but it might have
just cost me my job.
You know, Lucy would tell me
about you at the academy,
how far ahead you were
from all your classmates.
Seems so long ago.
What happened
to that Jackson?
What happened to that young man
I met at graduation?
So full of confidence.
A lifetime of expectations
crashed headlong into reality.
Well, "Sometimes you win,
sometimes you learn."
Freud?
Cat poster Lucy
used to have in her room.
You need to get back
to the time
when you knew
who you were,
not who you were
trying to be.
Oh, my gosh.
You're absolutely right.
I can't start
counting up wins and losses
when the season's
just begun.
Morning.
Where did
the coffee cups go?
Oh, I moved them
next to the coffee maker.
I liked them
by the dishwasher.
That's ridiculous.
It is more convenient.
Did -- Did...
Did you rearrange
the furniture?
Yes.
There's a better flow
in the room this way.
That's...
That's great.
You know what?
Screw the FBI.
I'm gonna flip Hickey,
take him away from the Feds,
and show Grey that he's wrong
about me.
That's
a really bad idea...
but I love it.
Yes.
How you gonna
pull it off?
Okay, I-I stopped by
the men's detention center
on the way in,
spoke to Chandio,
and it turns out
he's not sleeping
with Hickey's ex-wife.
He's never even met her.
So, Hickey had another reason
to torpedo
the stolen car ring.
Exactly.
So, we find out
what that is,
and we can use it
to leverage Hickey.
They made contact last night.
Ordered, um, five full sets
of fake documents.
All young women?
Yeah.
Human trafficking?
Who's the buyer?
Cartel.
Not sure which one.
But they'll kill me
if they find out
I'm talking to you.
Where's the exchange
taking place?
Uh, Whiteman Airfield.
In two hours.
You sure he said noon?
Yeah, I wrote it down.
7-Adam-15 --
all units stand by off-site.
Target is running late.
Hold position
until further notice.
You think
he's gonna show?
If there's one thing
you can count on,
it's that criminals
are always late.
What?
Nothing.
Trent Silver.
Name of the lawyer
you were talking to
at the precinct
yesterday.
I checked the sign-in sheet
at the front desk.
Why would you do that?
I'm a cop.
Curiosity's part of
the job description.
So, he does family law?
He's none of your business.
My personal life
is none of your business.
Why you're back
in uniform?
None of your business.
Are we clear?
For now.
Son of a...
Didn't someone from the FBI
call and talk to you guys?
I'm already taken.
Yeah, about that.
After we swept up
those stolen cars
and shut down
that dealership...
And learned
that you were lying
about the owner
sleeping with your ex...
It got us thinking.
So we did some digging,
and it seems that you paid
a visit to a few businesses
in that neighborhood
yesterday evening.
Tried to use
our show of force
as a means to extort
some hardworking men and women.
We've got you
on extortion.
We own you.
So, call the FBI
and let them know
that you are booked
for the foreseeable future.
Okay.
Alright, sure.
But I need to know how much
you're gonna pay for tips.
That's a fair question.
Totally.
The answer is...
Zero.
Hello?
I read it.
Read what?
Wait...
the background check?
No. You threw that away.
I saw you.
I couldn't help myself.
I mean, I dug it
out of the trash
after you left.
No. Why?
You're supposed to be
the angel on my shoulder.
But I started thinking.
I mean, if this was my son,
what would I do?
And then the next thing
I knew,
I was tearing it open
and reading what was inside.
I-Is it bad?
What does it say?
Two years ago,
Abigail was charged with arson
and use of
a caustic substance
against
a former boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
Nolan. Heads up.
I have to go.
7-Adam-15 --
target has arrived.
Single black SUV.
Wait for our signal.
Nice and easy.
Just go give them
the documents.
Police!
Hands where I can see them!
Get out of the car!
Do it now!
No, please.
You're making a mistake.
Are you being held
against your will?
Not by him.
He's helping us escape.
Wait.
Escape from who?
El Leon.
Head of
the Aquino Cartel?
He's my husband,
and these woman
"belong" to his men,
but we're finished
putting up with the abuse.
You have to let us go.
Ugh.
Who is that?
It's my husband.
He keeps calling,
telling me to go back.
You brought your phone?
Guaranteed
he's tracking that.
We gotta get out of here.
Get behind us.
7-Adam-15, converge on me.
Code 3.
Anybody raises the gun
above their waist
gets a hollow point
in the eye.
There's no need for that.
We're simply here to give
the ladies a ride home.
You the husband?
Nah.
I'm his attack dog.
Elena,
why do you do this?
You know
there's no place to go.
Get in the car.
All of you.
We won't.
Oh, yes, you will.
No, they won't.
Huh.
There's eight of us...
...and two of you.
Actually, there's
a whole lot more than two.
So, here's the new plan --
You, your boys
are gonna get
back in your cars
and you're gonna drive away,
empty-handed.
I'd say you got about 20 seconds
before the cavalry arrives.
This isn't over, Elena.
We'll get to you
soon enough.
Well, that was exciting.
I guess not for you.
That's probably
a regular Tuesday for you.
Oh, no.
The pucker factor
was definitely at 11.
West.
Nolan, Chen,
don't wander off.
Special Agent Bird
just called me --
Look, Sergeant,
it was my decision
to pursue Hickey
and try and steal him away
from the Feds.
Seems like you succeeded
from the way Bird was yelling.
Yes, sir.
Officer Lopez, is this
how you train your rookies?
To ignore the orders
of federal agents?
Pretty much, sir.
Any day we can remind
our federal brethren
that we are their equals...
is a day worth living.
It appears you three
successfully recruited
your first C. I. s,
and I'm impressed.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, Officer West?
Short sleeves, please.
Yes, sir.
♪ Oh, when I got you
by my side ♪
♪ Everything's alright ♪
Hey, why's your bag
by the door?
Your father is on his way
to pick me up.
He apologized.
He just needed
to miss me.
Oh.
He's downstairs.
Alright, sweetheart,
it's been a lovely visit.
Come by the office.
We can talk about
why you're not dating anyone.
Thank you, Jackson.
Bye, Mrs. Chen.
No wonder I can't find
a healthy relationship.
My dysfunctional parents are why
I am 28 and still single.
Are you sure that's why?
What's that
supposed to mean?
Look, I'm just saying
that your only real relationship
was with Nolan.
Yep.
I've known the whole time.
Wait --
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
You think I'm stupid?
No.
Listen -- You fell
for a divorced guy
coming out of
a 20-year marriage, okay?
I-It was safe.
Never meant to last.
Come on.
Let's go celebrate.
Tomorrow, my forearms
will be liberated.
It is pretty glorious.
Yeah, actually, how did you
get your parents to make up?
Oh. I got Wesley
to call each of them
pretending to be
a divorce lawyer,
telling them the costs
of a divorce,
and that snapped them out of it
pretty quick.
Well played.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Wait. Will you please,
please help me
get the furniture
back to where it was.
But it's better this way.
I know.
But will you help me get it
back to the way it was?
Yes.
Oh.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Guys, there's something
I need to say.
I know about the arson.
You ran
a background check?
You knew
she had a record?
Yeah, she told me
on our third date.
I...can't believe
you did that.
It's okay.
He -- He did it to protect you.
No, I don't need protecting,
especially from you.
Do you want to know
what happened?
If you want to tell me.
An ex-boyfriend posted
some videos on the Internet...
after we broke up.
Personal videos of us...
together.
He did it to get revenge,
and it worked.
He took something from me
I'll never get back.
I'm so sorry.
So, I went to his house...
and I torched his car.
And I got arrested
and he didn't.
Happy now?
Not in the least.
Abigail...
...I'm sorry my fear
overcame my judgement.
I, uh...
I can't take that back,
but I can promise you
it won't happen again.
That's good enough for me.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's great that
that's behind us now,
because I really am
pregnant.
I'm kidding. Again.
Oh, my --
Joke.
Geez.
Okay, we're gonna have
to work on the jokes, though.
'Cause I already have
a high-stress job,
and, uh...I think you're gonna
give me a heart attack.
Understood.
Corrected & synced by
Flatto (subscene.com)