Control 7-Adam-07.
Show us at a vehicle stop
on Olympic and Avon.
You got this.
Sir, driver's license
and registration, please.
What's the problem?
You were doing 50 in a school zone.
What's that sound?
My bees.
Your what?
Bees. I'm a beekeeper.
I don't know
if I'll be able to control them
if you give me a ticket.
Sir, threatening an officer is a crime.
Alright, step out of the car.
You okay?
Yeah. You?
I sure am missing my long sleeves.
Do we go after him?
Uh, all units, be on the lookout
for a blue minivan.
Look out, it's...
...full of bees!
- ♪ There it is
- Well, hello!
Well, hello to you, too.
Mm. I was talking to the coffee.
Mm.
It's too early for dad jokes.
I woke up this morning
with an amazing idea...
- Hmm?
- ...for the layout,
of the master closet.
Tell me what you think.
Mm.
- What?
- Nothing.
I-I mean, I was...
I was married for 20 years.
"Nothing" usually means
a whole lot of something.
Well, I mean...
you don't even have, like,
a-a built-in shoe rack.
Oh, well, I got, what,
two pairs of shoes?
Yeah, but I have a lot more.
O-Oh. Yeah. Uh, right.
Uh, I-I mean, obviously, yeah.
I mean, we haven't
even talked about the...
Relax!
It's fine. It's good.
I'm... I'm... I'm kidding.
- Right.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna, um... I'm gonna get dressed.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Crap.
I'm gonna lose it.
Ah, you're back...
You forget something?
My car won't start. Again.
You need a new one.
I need a healthier bank account.
Uh, I can get you to work,
but you're on your own to get home.
Why? What are you doing tonight?
Nothing.
I mean, t-that thing. I told you.
- What thing?
- At my mother's.
Remember?
The mother I haven't met yet?
No, you definitely didn't
tell me about that.
Well, you probably had
a lot on your mind.
Do you want to go?
Do you want me to go?
Of course.
- Great!
- Awesome.
Today is problem day.
So you know what that means.
Actually, sir, I-I don't.
Problem spots on your patrol route.
Locations that attract crime
like a felonious magnet.
Businesses used as a cover
for criminal activity.
No-tell motels,
massage parlors, dive bars.
Or anywhere that ex-cons gather
to plan their next adventure.
The spots you see every day
and you vow to take them down
if you have the time,
but we never have the time.
So... today we make some.
Is there a problem, Smitty?
Oh, no, sir.
I love playing whack-a-mole.
Knock down a problem spot,
it can pop back up anywhere.
But that's the job, right?
And since you're so excited
about doing it,
I think you should share
your excitement
with Officer West out there today.
- Seriously?
Yeah, seriously.
That means, Lopez, you're with Nolan.
Okay. Happy hunting out there.
Look, I know you're probably still mad
about me not rooming with you, but...
Don't flatter yourself, sunshine.
So, uh, what's our problem spot?
You'll see when we get there.
So...
what'd you do last night?
Gym. Dinner. Study.
Rinse, wash, repeat.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
You know, it...
it's just been a while
since the divorce.
You wanna jog behind the shop
all day, Boot?
No. No.
No, sir. Shutting up.
It's just a big step,
and it's never come up.
I wasn't prepared, and now she's mad.
Why do relationships
have to be so complicated?
Some things, you just shouldn't
spring on someone
before they've even had
their morning coffee.
If you can't be honest with each
other, then why even be together?
- And now
- Just, some things
- I'm sitting here wondering why Wesley
- shouldn't be rushed, and I don't know
- doesn't want me to meet his mom.
- if I'm ready to take it to that level.
- Wait, what?
- I thought we were talking about my thing.
I thought we were talking
about my thing.
Wesley said he didn't want you
to meet his mom?
- He actually said that?
- He didn't have to.
"Problem spots," my ass.
What is that smell?
Like sweat socks and licorice.
This whole city's a problem spot.
Sean John cologne and desperation.
- Pull over at that burger joint.
Seriously? You just ate a burrito.
That's the problem spot.
Place has been a haven,
to shady ex-cons since I was a Boot.
Ain't never gonna change.
So, what do we do?
We sit here. Wait.
- For what?
- End of shift.
Problem spot. Check.
So, you want us to chill here
in your rank-ass shop?
Rookies. Ohh.
You all think you can change the world.
This is our problem spot?
What do you see?
Guy waiting for the bus.
Drug dealer.
This corner's a mecca
for upper-class dopers.
Oxy, Molly, Benzos, Vikes...
anything a well-off suburbanite
can choke down
with a Kombucha spritzer.
And right on cue.
Gonna bust that dealer?
Buyer. Dealers are a dime a dozen.
We want to scare the clients away
so business takes a big hit.
Take the lead on this one.
Okay.
Morning, sir.
What is the problem, officer?
Is it illegal
to ask for directions now?
Well, you better lock me up.
License and registration, please.
My partner and I witnessed you
exchange money for a baggie.
Wanna show us what you bought?
No idea what you're talking about.
What's this?
Oops. How'd that get there?
You work for Councilwoman Langston?
I'm her right hand.
Sometimes her left, if you feel me.
Look, Officer, uh... Nolan...
you got a job to do.
I get it. Believe me.
Nobody appreciates the boys...
and girls...
in blue more than me.
It's just, you see, Langston...
she needed me to find her
some, uh, sleep aids.
- Oh. Yeah.
- Just hand over the baggie.
No big deal.
Now you, uh, let me off with a warning,
win yourself
some pretty powerful friends
down at City Hall.
Oh. Sounds like quite an offer.
Councilwoman Langston's office.
But I'm doing okay
in the friend department.
- No, no, no. No, no, no. Uh, um...
- Hello?
I'm sorry.
T-The pills... t-t-they're mine.
- Hello?
- P-P-Please hang up. Please?
I just needed something
to take the edge off.
You can't imagine
what I go through every day.
The wife, boss, the constant
pressure. It's just...
Jump out of the car.
We're locking you up.
Come over here,
- put your hands on the car.
- Yes, sir.
- We gonna be here a while?
- Yep.
Then I need to arrange childcare.
Yeah, sure. You get one call
once we're done processing you.
Thanks.
Hey. I know you're gonna say no,
but...
- ...I think I can help.
- With what?
Well, you know, I know how hard
it is to meet people in L.A.
It's what keeps them in business.
Wait.
You wanna set me up?
Forget it.
Even if this wasn't
your dumbest idea yet,
there is no way you'd be able
to pick someone right for me.
Um, I bet I can.
I'm serious.
If I can fix you up
on one good date, just one,
I get to, uh...
I get to wear short sleeves.
Okay.
- But you're paying.
- Whatever.
And if you lose,
- you're gonna do 50 push-ups
after every call we take.
Okay. New plan.
You drink your soda, and I'm
gonna go do some policing.
Here they come.
Keep cool.
- Morning, officers.
- Boys.
My partner here is a newbie
who wants to learn about
problem spots in town.
So here we are.
- I'm just eating.
- Sure you are.
Danny Dozier.
You just did four years in Chino.
Armed robbery, was it?
And you.
Weren't you the wheelman
for Larry Marks?
Think of this as a
lowlife employment agency.
Each of these dirtbags has
a set of illicit skills,
and they are just itching
for a chance to use 'em.
Hmm. Last time I checked,
associating with felons was
a no-no for parolees.
Raise your hand if you're on parole.
Look, don't make me
run you through the system.
It'll just piss me off.
There we go. That's more like it.
Everybody grab some wall.
Come on. Right this way.
Speed it up.
What are you doing?
Just kick 'em loose with a warning.
Tell them not to come back.
Problem spot handled.
They break the law, they go in.
Go, kid.
Foot pursuit.
White male, gray shirt and blue jeans,
headed north on Fillmore.
Why'd you run, huh?
Stand up.
Spread your feet.
- Where's the gun?
- I don't got one.
I just like bullets.
That ain't a crime, is it?
He must have dumped the gun somewhere
between here and the burger joint.
Help!
Somebody please help me!
I need help! Please, somebody!
Calvin, g...
Calvin! Give me the gun, baby.
Baby, please. Give me the gun.
Calvin!
Hey, Calvin?
Hey, buddy. It's not a toy, okay?
Please put the gun down.
Calvin, give me the gun!
Hey, buddy, please put the gun down.
- Calvin, give me the gun!
- It's not a toy! Put the gun...
Gunshot wound to the upper-right chest!
You did this.
- I didn't do nothin'.
- It was your gun!
Prove it.
Thank you anyway.
Rachel?
Look at you!
- Oh, my G...
- All official!
- Mm!
You were the talk
of the reunion, you know.
I was bummed I couldn't go.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh,
just trying to cut
through some red tape.
But so far, my scissors
haven't been sharp enough.
Oh, problems in Child Services?
Yeah, civil standbys.
LAPD needs a faster response time.
I've had four go sideways
in the last month.
Mm.
Hey. Maybe you can help me.
I-I wish I could,
but I am below
bottom of the food chain here.
- It's...
- Boot!
Get a move on.
No lunch till you finish those reports.
Who's that?
That is my training officer.
I should probably go.
Hey, uh, you're single,
- right?
- Mm-hmm.
Would you want to go out with him?
Uh, he's hot...
but I-I made a vow.
- No more jerks.
- Let's go, Boot!
Okay, so, you don't date jerks.
But how would you like to
help me win a bet against one?
Let's go.
We gotta take this dirtbag
back to the station,
get him processed.
You alright?
No.
I...
I should have tackled the kid.
Taken the bullet myself.
That's a no-win situation.
Had you reacted differently,
maybe the kid would have
shot himself instead.
Hey.
You did the right thing.
Yeah, it was... it wasn't enough.
Hey, Jess.
It's me. Just trying you... again.
Call me back.
Okay.
She is definitely mad at me
and ducking my calls.
What time is dinner with Mom?
- Huh?
- Dinner.
Oh. Um...
At 8:00, I think.
You know, there is no world
in which Wesley is embarrassed by you.
If that was what you were worried about.
It's not.
I'm not charging him.
You're kidding me. Why not?
You never saw the gun
in his possession,
and his prints weren't on it.
All you got was a
pocket full of bullets.
There's no crime in that.
Bullets are the same caliber
as the gun.
It's a 9-millimeter.
Most common handgun there is.
He tossed the gun
while I was chasing him,
and a child picked it up.
- But you didn't see it.
- That kid could've killed himself.
As it is, his mother almost died.
The kid is traumatized.
So how in the hell
can you kick this guy loose?
It's not a case that we can win.
I'm sorry.
I have to get back to court.
Don't call her again.
When she's ready, she'll call you.
You're right.
- Turn around.
- What?
There's a guy back there being chased.
Control 7-Adam-15,
suspicious circs on 5th and Beaudry,
requesting backup.
Back up!
Back up! Move your vehicle!
Come on! Come on, damn it!
- You see them?
- There.
Back seat clear.
Front seat clear.
So, where'd they go?
Head upstai...
Coming through. Out of the way!
What do we have?
Patient suffered
a fractured left femur,
possible internal bleeding,
and head trauma.
- BP?
- Stable.
They gave him two liters
of saline on the way over.
- Hi.
- Hey.
What happened to him? Car accident?
No, no. He, uh, got
dropped off a footbridge.
Landed on top of a car
right in front of us.
- Do you know his name?
- Uh, yeah,
driver's license says he's Cesar Ojeda.
Okay. We need a CT scan. Alert the OR.
- He's jumping the line.
- Not before I talk to him.
- Jessica Russo. DHS.
- Hey.
That's not possible.
Well, make it possible.
He's unconscious and probably
bleeding internally.
If we delay surgery, he could die.
- Is that what you want?
- Nobody wants that, right?
N-No. I... Fine. Fine.
I just need to talk to him
as soon as he wakes up.
Of course. Let's move.
So, who was that guy,
and why did you have to
talk to him so badly?
I can't really tell you that.
Can't or won't?
I ran the plates
on the car that chased him.
It was reported stolen last week.
What about the guys inside?
They were gone by the time
backup cleared the building.
What's your interest?
His real name is Alejandro Mejia.
He's undercover DHS.
He disappeared about six weeks
ago during an infiltration,
and I was alerted,
when you ran his cover
ID through the system.
Wow. So, what was he into?
I-I'm not cleared to tell you that.
So, DHS is taking this over?
Yes, but I would really appreciate it
if you could provide
some extra security
until my guys got here.
Of course.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir?
Yeah, she's definitely mad at you.
Yes, he's, um...
he's unconscious and...
She's a social worker?
You say that like it's equivalent
to being a serial killer.
No. Social workers do valuable work...
coddling criminals.
- Look, if you're not even gonna try...
- Hold your water, Boot.
I'm just getting the lay
of the land on my "date."
- So, where are you taking her?
- Ravenna.
That... sounds expensive.
Oh. It is.
They've got a $100 filet,
just melts in your mouth.
And their wine list... ohh!
It's exceptional.
Well, good.
It seems like a really romantic place.
- Hmm.
- What?
You're gonna have to do
so many push-ups.
Anyway, this... is Rachel.
Pretty.
West, where's Smitty?
Probably watching "Judge Judy"
in the break room.
Sir, was pairing us up
meant to be added punishment?
Think of it more as a kick in the pants.
No way you're advancing
back to short sleeves
until I see the fire back in your eyes.
You collared a guy named
Gleason Dunn earlier, right?
Yeah.
You ship him downtown yet?
No, he's, uh, being processed out.
ADA told me to kick him. Why?
Ballistics came back
on the gun the kid fired.
It was used in
- an unsolved murder last year.
What?
They pulled a DNA sample
from the scene,
but there was no match in the system.
Dunn's DNA isn't in the system.
We don't have it.
Well, we need to get a sample.
Excuse me.
Gleason Dunn.
- Where is he?
- Released.
About 10 minutes ago.
Okay. I'm... I'm on my way in.
Hey.
- Hey.
- So, about this morning...
Oh. This is not the right time.
- Right.
- Yeah.
And also, I mean, it's not a big deal.
So we're good?
Yeah. Uh,
- why wouldn't we be?
- Right.
I brought Grey up to speed.
He said he'd give you
whatever you need.
- Oh, great.
- Any chance you got more clearance
- to tell us about Mejia?
- Yes.
He's a forensic accountant,
an expert in cryptocurrency.
We put him inside
an illegal arms operation,
where he was supposed to
target their financials
and then neutralize their access.
By what? Changing all their passwords?
Basically, yeah.
The downside of digital money.
Then Mejia went silent, what'd you say,
- about six weeks ago?
- Mm-hmm.
So we presumed
- he was either dead or...
- Compromised.
No wonder you need to talk to him.
Look, um, I've got to go brief my boss.
DHS is gonna be mobilizing
some agents to come stand watch.
Are you good until they arrive?
Like Grey said, anything you need.
Hmm.
Alright, I'm gonna take the shop.
Dispatch will arrange pickup
once you're replaced.
- You're leaving?
- I gotta get dressed for dinner.
The great thing about you
being a phase three now
is I don't have to supervise you 24/7.
So have fun on guard duty.
Good luck with Mommie Dearest.
I briefed my buddies
on Midnight shift about Gleason.
They'll get him.
You know, it's not too late.
- For what?
- Scale of 1 to 10,
how sure are you the
gun belonged to Gleason?
10.
Then maybe you need to revise
your statement to the ADA.
You're a rookie whose vision
got blurry in the fog of war,
but now you're clear,
and you did see him toss the weapon.
Write it up like that,
and I'll back you.
I'd be lying.
Kid, you're in the honeymoon
period of being a cop.
Full of piss and righteous vinegar.
But it's not a black-and-white world.
Never has been.
Look, right and wrong matter.
Otherwise, why bother
pinning on the badge?
It's not about right and wrong.
It's about getting the bad guys
off the street.
How you gonna feel
- if we can't pin Gleason down
and he hurts more people?
Or worse.
It can't be worse than today.
Oh, it can always get worse.
Yeah?
Okay, thanks.
The mom died on the operating table.
I'm sorry.
Yes!
I'm so glad she wore that dress.
She didn't want to look too sexy,
but, uh, Mama needs to get
into some short sleeves.
Yo. Where did you go?
Sorry. Uh...
I can't stop thinking about my guy.
He killed someone,
and I just let him walk.
Dude, you did what the
ADA told you to do,
and now you're trying to fix it.
Night shift is on the hunt.
- Yeah.
- Head in the game.
Let's go.
- This is so weird.
- Uh-huh.
Yep, yep, yep.
So, you've, uh...
you've known Chen since...
I mean, Lucy,
since college?
Yeah, we were in psych class together.
Hmm.
Bet she hasn't changed a bit.
No. Always playing matchmaker.
Well, this is my favorite place.
Best filet in town.
Oh, I don't eat red meat.
Sea bass is great, too.
Nothing that had a face.
I'm on a raw-food diet, actually.
You know, reduce my imprint.
Oh, wait. What happened?
They stopped talking.
This is like watching
a nature documentary.
You're just waiting for the
gazelle to get eaten by the jaguar.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna lose this bet.
Pbht.
Look, you seem nice and all,
so I probably should just
tell you the truth.
I let Lucy set us up tonight
because she made me a bet.
And, um, you want her to lose.
No, I want me to win.
Being here with me isn't a win?
Maybe a little.
Mm-hmm.
You know what would be a win for me?
If you could get me...
...a direct line
to your watch commander
so I could talk to him
about civil standbys.
I could do that.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And what would you want in return?
I'm gonna be in long sleeves forever.
Where am I?
You're in the hospital, Mr. Mejia.
You just underwent surgery.
- You know my name?
- Yes, I do.
I'm working with DHS... Jessica Russo.
She told us about your undercover op.
Looks like you have
quite a tale to tell.
- I need to get outta here.
- Not just yet.
You've been through a great deal.
Um, the men who were chasing you...
can you ID them?
No.
Why did they throw you off the bridge?
They didn't. I jumped.
- Why?
- Seemed necessary at the time.
Were they trying to kill you?
Worse.
What do you mean by that?
Mr. Mejia?
Come on. We got to
get to my mom's party.
No.
Not until you admit,
you never mentioned this
thing with your mom before.
I-I thought I did.
Okay, fine. I didn't.
I knew it.
You didn't want her to meet me.
Angela.
Is it because I'm...
- spirited?
- No.
You got us a chess clock
to mediate our arguments.
- I know, but that's not what this...
- And I can be a little feral
- when I eat sometimes, but...
- Angela.
This wasn't about you.
What does that mean?
Look, I have to tell you something...
but I don't want you to freak out.
You're rich.
Well, wealth is relative.
Yeah. Super rich.
Oh, look who decided
to grace us with his presence.
Hello, darling.
- Hello, my dear!
- Hi.
Oh, it's so nice to finally meet you.
You are simply stunning.
Thank you. You are, too, Mrs. Evers.
And... And this beautiful house.
Come on. Let's get you a drink.
So, what made you decide
to become a police officer?
Well, I love my city
and wanted to give back.
- Mm.
- Getting to kick ass helped, too.
Well, I, for one,
thank you for your service.
You know, you put 'em in jail,
and my son tries to get 'em out.
Mother.
Why do you keep calling me "Mother,"
like... like this is "Downton Abbey"?
Insufferable, isn't he?
Definitely, but he's cute.
You know, his grandfather founded
the biggest law firm in Beverly Hills,
but Wesley insists on working pro bono,
over a restaurant that
serves $5.99 buffets.
Mother... Mom.
Well, I just want to give you
a helping hand
from time to time,
but you slap it away.
Well, I do fine on my own.
But you could do so much more.
Okay, can we not talk about this
right now, in front of Angela?
But you're living together.
She's family.
And, you know,
there's never really a
good time to talk with you.
I-I know you want to
do it all on your own
and not touch your trust fund...
- Trust fund?
- ...but
the fact that you seem
mad at me about it,
that is just messed up.
How's your wine?
Amazing.
Yeah, I picked it up
at a spa retreat in Tuscany.
I'm going again in March.
You should come.
Wesley, you two should come.
- 100% yes.
- Yes.
Mm. You know what?
I'm gonna take an Uber home.
The two of you, just...
enjoy each other.
Come on, Wesley.
Always with the drama.
I should go after him.
Oh, nonsense. He's a grown man.
Besides, I want you to taste the stew.
It's my own recipe.
- It does smell good.
- Mm-hmm.
Hi.
I'm here to transfer
the patient to the ICU
for some serial exams,
check for any internal bleeding.
- Sure. Uh, do you mind if I...?
- Sure.
Susan Taylor. How long
have you worked here, Susan?
A lot of fives.
Five months in the ICU,
five years at the hospital,
and, uh, since 5:00 this morning...
5:30, actually...
Okay, well, I'm gonna need
to accompany you.
No problem.
- Why do I do this?
- Do what?
Infiltrate myself into everything.
- I'm like a virus.
- You're not a virus.
Yes. I am.
Why do I care if Tim dates?
Why do I care why
- anyone does anything?
- Okay, you just
want everyone to be happy.
- That's a good quality.
- No, you know what I want?
To get drunk.
Let's get a butt load of tequila,
get up on the roof of our building,
and listen to music
from the Hollywood Bowl.
That's what I want.
Hello?
Yeah.
Thank you for letting me know.
What was that?
Night shift still hasn't found Gleason.
Bastard's still walking
around out there.
Just give 'em time.
- What are you doing?
- Getting my car.
I'm going for a ride.
Going for a ride up the PCH
with a little bit of sad music
or a little off-duty action?
Okay. I'll drive.
Hey, Jess.
Oh, yeah, well, no,
he was a-awake for a minute,
and now he's unconscious again.
They're just transferring him to ICU.
Right. Okay. I'll see you in a few.
How's it going?
Good. Yeah, good.
Uh, Jessica's on her way here
to question him.
It... seems like you
know her pretty well.
Yeah. Well, we're dating.
Really?
- What?
- Nothing.
She's j... She's a little intense.
Oh, that's... just "work Jessica."
Yeah, she's... she's different at home.
Sure.
- What?
- Nothing. Um...
She just... She doesn't
really seem like your type.
- My type?
- Never mind.
You know what? I'm gonna shut up.
People can change a lot in 20 years.
W-What are you doing outside the ICU?
Oh, uh, the nurse transferred
Mejia here from post-op.
They needed to run some tests.
But I just... I spoke with the surgeon.
He didn't want to move Mejia yet.
He was gonna do the exams in post-op.
I need this hospital put
on immediate lockdown!
Nobody in or out.
7-Adam-15, 207 at Shaw Memorial.
I need backup,
unknown number of suspects,
possibly armed, Code 3.
Remember me?
Smitty's rookie?
Had you dead to rights
on a parole violation?
Yeah. What do you want?
Your boy. Gleason Dunn.
Tell me where he is,
and these officers
might just let you go.
- He's not my boy.
- He destroyed a family today,
dumped a gun for a child to find.
Life's full of tragedy.
You want your life to become one?
'Cause I'm hoping for a couple
more decades on the job,
years I will spend making
your life a living hell
if you don't come clean.
Is that really something
you want to sign up for?
'Cause it seems smarter to just
give the guy up and go home.
Police!
Passwords, or I start taking off ears.
I don't... I don't...
I don't know them
- off the top of my head, man.
I got them stored back at my place!
Nice try.
Guess I'm taking some pieces off
to get the truth.
I'm telling you the truth!
I swear! Come on!
Police! Drop the saw!
Stand up right now,
or I will shoot you.
Do not test me.
Okay. Okay, you got me.
Back up. Hands behind your head.
Interlace your fingers.
No problem, officer,
but I got a bad shoulder.
Shut up. Turn around.
I don't know if I can...
Stay right there.
You see where he went?
No, I didn't see where he went.
Can you get this damn saw away from me?
- Can you walk?
- I don't think so.
- Stay right there.
- I don't think I have a choice.
Give me your backup.
Come on, man. I need a weapon.
Got it?
You're under arrest.
Well done, Officer West.
Hi.
Look, I'm sorry.
Just, every time I go
to my mother's house,
I turn into this person
I don't want to be.
Why? Your mom is great.
And don't give me the "You don't
really know her" spiel.
She has nothing but a deep
and genuine love for you.
So why do you keep
turning your back on her?
It's just all that excess.
I always hated that.
I need to make it on my own.
What?
Only a rich person would think
turning down money is a noble idea.
I wore my brother's
hand-me-downs until I was 15.
My mom worked two jobs,
and so did we once we
reached high school.
So... you think less of me?
Are you kidding?
Your mom and I already started
planning the wedding.
California's a no-fault divorce state,
so if you ever felt like
doing me a solid...
Mm-hmm.
Love your mom while you have her.
Take that money
- and do something good with it.
Like fix your car, maybe?
I was thinking more like
feed the homeless,
but I wouldn't say no to a Porsche.
Oh, really?
Or we could just get a chauffeur.
Come on, trust fund.
Mm!
Two hours till we're back on shift.
It's gonna be a long day.
Think you can get a power nap in?
Nah.
I'm just gonna "Clockwork Orange" it.
Hey, come on. Gleason's behind bars.
You gotta feel good about that, right?
Yeah.
But if I wouldn't have pushed
things with my problem spot,
if I would have just sat
in the car, like Smitty said,
or... or let the ex-cons go
with a warning,
then Gleason wouldn't have run
and he wouldn't have...
he wouldn't have dumped the gun,
and that kid would still have a mom.
Stop.
What happened was not your fault.
It was Gleason's, and now he's
on the hook for two murders.
He's gonna be locked up forever.
That's all you need
to take away from this.
You got me?
Yeah.
And don't start listening to Smitty.
You're not that kind of cop.
Yeah, I'm the kind who'll never
get out of long sleeves.
Mm! Excuse me?
Sorry. Your bet.
Clearly, you won't, either.
Do you really think Tim's
gonna make me do push-ups
after every call?
You know what? On the bright side,
when it's over, I'm gonna have
mad upper-body strength.
Come on.
I'll drop you off at your car.
We still got time to shower
and change before roll call.
Let's go.
How's Mejia?
They took him back into surgery,
but, um, I think he's gonna be okay.
And did you get a chance
to talk to him?
I got the passwords,
and we seized $22 million
in assets from the arms dealer.
And you helped take down
a pretty big operation, John.
Despite the fact
I almost screwed it up.
Well, everyone makes a mistake
now and then.
Like the one I made yesterday with you?
Look, um...
I-I wasn't asking to live with you.
I was, uh...
I was just testing the waters.
And I capsized the boat.
Look, Jess...
I am still just figuring out
who I am in this new life.
It hasn't even been a year
since I got divorced,
and I got a brand-new job,
entirely new city.
The only thing I know for sure is...
I love spending time with you.
And a shoe rack
will add value to my home,
and if you have any more...
great ideas, I'd love to hear them.
Deal.
I gotta go.
Look at you, saving the world,
getting the girl.
Far cry from college,
when all you wanted
was a fake ID and to pass organic chem.
Well, it wasn't all I wanted.
You had your charms.
Hey, um, I wanted to apologize
about that crack about Agent Russo
and for assuming
that I know your taste.
I mean, 20 years is a long time.
And yet you are exactly
how I remember you.
I'm not sure if that's
a positive or a negative.
Positive, for sure. And this has...
This has been great seeing you again
and catching up
and being friends again.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I would love to go
on a double date, meet your husband.
I'm not really married.
- Oh, I-I...
- I mean, technically, I am,
but Simon and I...
we separated over a year ago.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah,
I guess that I keep wearing the ring
so I don't have to have
uncomfortable conversations.
Right. I get it. Um...
And I know the drill.
So if you ever want to just talk, I'm...
I'm around.
I might just take you up on that.
Lucy! What are you doing here?
Uh, sorry. I know it's early.
Um, I just wanted to thank you
for going out with Tim last night.
Uh, Bordeaux, your favorite wine, right?
That wasn't necessary.
I hope it wasn't too unbearable.
It was fine. He was... fine.
I know he can come off
like this smug hard-ass,
but, you know, deep down, he...
he has a really good heart.
Anyway, I'll go.
But I owe you one. Big time.
Hey, can I borrow your, uh...
Short sleeves.
Yes!
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.MY-SUBS.com