♪ Okay, everybody, let's go ♪
Alright. Last one.
As much as I like
watching you load the truck,
I've got some studying
I got to do.
And by studying,
you mean...?
Mm, watching "Lady
and the Tramp" with Abigail.
Oh!
We do the, uh, whole
spaghetti thing along with it.
Cute.
So, what are you doing
for your birthday tomorrow?
I'm tiling the bathroom.
Mm. That sounds sad.
No, it doesn't.
Besides, when you're
the oldest rookie,
you really don't
want anyone knowing
you're the older
oldest rookie.
I mean, you just broke up
with Jessica,
and nobody knows that
it's your birthday tomorrow?
Yes, and that's the way
I like it,
so do not tell
Jackson and Lucy.
Promise me.
You're a grown man.
You want to spend
your birthday grouting,
that's, uh,
your prerogative.
Yes, it is.
Oh. That's the boss.
I got to go.
Alright. Love you.
Love you, too. Bye.
Yes, sir.
How can I help you?
♪ All eyes right here ♪
Thanks for coming in
on your day off.
No problem.
I'm excited to get started
on my special assignment.
It's not a special assignment.
It's a mandatory callback.
Oh. I may have renamed that
in my head.
What happened here?
It's a homicide --
and a brutal one.
At least two assailants,
and the victim was a lawyer.
So lots of suspects.
One for now --
building's security guard.
He's in the wind.
Maynard Goetz.
Want me to put out an APB?
It's already done.
Just sit here and guard.
Any detectives come back,
make them sign in.
Keep one boot
in the tape.
Dispatch will call you
as soon as detectives say
you can release
the scene.
And when will that be?
Hour, two.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Coffee?
I haven't had a chance
to make it.
So, no coffee?
Not yet. Sorry.
You know, Nolan kept me up
all night
from this crime scene
he was babysitting.
Look at this.
Look.
Yeah, he was texting me, too.
We'll get
stuck on one soon enough.
Class A's?
Yeah. Tim and I get
our commendation today.
Oh, right, for helping
that family last week.
Mm-hmm.
You know,
it's -- it's crazy.
Like, a few weeks ago,
I thought I was gonna get
bounced from the program,
and now I'm getting an award
from the Deputy Chief.
It's pretty cool
how quickly things can change.
I'm really happy
for you, man.
Aww. Thanks.
Plus, Tim is gonna be
in a really good mood today.
I know.
I'm really happy for me, too.
Sorry.
Let me get this straight.
You're coming to me
for an annual evaluation
that's not due
until December?
I just wanted to get
a jump on it.
Reason?
It's personal.
I figured
I'd spare you the details.
Detective, I hear you.
I really do.
But it's called a yearly review
for a reason --
because that's when
the Paperwork Gods expect it.
So, if you want me to file
this thing ahead of schedule,
I need to know why.
Okay. Okay.
It's...for the judge.
I have a hearing next week
for custody of Lila,
and a strong evaluation
would go a long way.
Look, you came here
untouchable.
Let me level with you.
While I'd fast-track reviews
for most of my officers...
I'm not ready
to do that for you.
Okay.
Wait.
I know you're trying hard
with your daughter.
At the same time,
I can't ignore
that you're still
a wildcard on patrol.
So, if you want this eval,
you got to show me
something different.
What do you mean?
Meaning...
we ride together.
You and me.
And I evaluate you firsthand.
But know this --
I'm writing this evaluation
no matter what happens
out there.
So, if you fall down today,
the world will know.
It is a big deal.
"Light of the City" award?
I thought
you'd be happier.
I planned my emotional day
around it.
I don't do this for the medals
and plaques, Boot.
Yes, only lesser cops
enjoy recognition.
Exactly.
Well, if it doesn't matter,
turn it down.
It doesn't matter to me, but it
does matter to the higher-ups.
Look, a good score
on the sergeant's exam,
this award could help me rise
through the list of candidates.
Fair enough.
Jackson's dedicated
an entire shelf to his award?
He's building a cabinet
from scratch.
He knows how to do that?
Nolan's helping him.
Oh.
Grace.
What's up?
You know, the usual.
Snatching life
from the jaws of death?
Close. I just pulled four Legos
out of a kid's nose.
Four? Amateur.
No commitment
to the craft.
I mean, not like
when we were kids.
Right.
I never went to the hospital
for anything less than seven.
Man on P.A.:
Dr. Sawyer to ER.
Shoot. You know what?
I got to go.
Dr. Sawyer to ER.
I-I just --
I wanted to wish you
a happy birthday.
Oh. Thank you.
Ga-- Uh, wait.
You remembered
my birthday?
I got a Facebook alert.
My birthday's
not on Facebook.
Huh.
That's weird.
Anyway, uh, lives, important
things. I-I got to go.
Grace.
Yeah?
Thanks for calling.
You're welcome.
Right.
Oh, damn it.
Sorry.
This is a crime scene.
Better be.
Uh, bioremediation.
Beg your pardon?
Crime scene cleaner.
Right.
You the log officer?
Yeah.
Officer Nolan.
Um...crime scene's been
processed,
but they haven't
cleared it just yet.
I can have someone call you
when they're ready.
I'll wait.
90% of the job's
planning anyway.
You --
Thanks.
I would've thought 90%
of the job would be scrubbing.
No.
You go in
with the wrong chemicals,
you can make things
a hundred times worse.
The mix of body fluids
and the -- the fabrics,
even the ambient humidity,
it all makes a huge difference.
Oh.
Every job requires
a slightly different
set of tools.
Very impressive.
And how does one
get into bioremediation?
Always liked
setting things right, I guess.
I walk into a tragedy.
When I walk out,
everything is as it should be.
I-I know people think
it's a weird job for weirdos.
No, no, no.
I get it.
Your name again was...?
Ellroy.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too,
Officer Nolan.
Hmm.
You hungry?
Starving.
Half a sandwich?
Whew.
Well, it's a little early
to become my first DUI,
but it's Hollywood.
Everyone's trying
to be someone.
It's not a DUI yet.
Nope. But it will be
in three, two...
one.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Show us on a possible DUI,
6th and Beverly.
Morning, Miss.
Can I speak to you
over on the sidewalk, please?
What? Why?
Uh, you just don't look like
you should be driving.
Have you, uh, been drinking
a little bit?
Got me there,
but I-I wasn't gonna drive.
Oh, so you were just getting
into your car because...?
Just grabbing my purse.
Mm-hmm. Your purse
that's on your shoulder?
Ah!
It is!
Yeah.
Uh, uh, I'm just gonna
run a few tests
to make sure you are
actually okay to drive.
I'm kind of sick of tests,
to be honest with you.
I know.
This will only take a second.
So,
hold your head still.
Follow my finger
with just your eyes.
Horizontal nystagmus.
Okay. Hey, hey!
My dad's coming down
for the ceremony.
It's not a ceremony. It's a
photo op with the Deputy Chief.
Okay, still,
it's a big deal to me.
I'm proud of this.
You should be.
You know you were texting
while driving, sir?
Oh, I just looked down
at my map for a second
while I was stopped
at a red light.
"Yo, running late.
Smiley face, smiley face,
boat."
Yeah, okay,
the boat was a typo.
Yeah, it's so hard to focus
on texting while you're driving.
License and registration,
please.
Hey, what's, uh, what's going on
with your dashboard, there?
Nothing.
Came that way.
I doubt it.
♪ I know that someday
you'll be a friend to me ♪
Looks like Trevor's on
searchable probation for 11-300.
Narcotics.
♪ Boom, yeah,
we'll fight together ♪
Sir, step out
of the vehicle.
Today.
♪ We're wakin' up now,
we mobilizin' ♪
Step to the back
of the vehicle.
♪ Here come a better
solution now, we risin' ♪
Arms on the trunk lid.
Spread your legs.
♪ Straight out the compound,
we startin' the countdown ♪
♪ Okay, ha, finger on
the trigger, and we roll ♪
♪ Burnin' all the bridges
as we go ♪
♪ Nobody lookin' back
no more ♪
There's a packaged powder
in here.
♪ No livin' in the past
no more ♪
♪ No more ♪
It's wedged up in there,
though.
At least a kilo.
Surprise, surprise.
Sir, give me your hands.
Can't get it out.
Relax. They'll tear it apart,
find out whatever it is.
Uh...
You okay?
♪ Hey ay ay, if we just
a dog in the fight ♪
You got a little something
on your shirt.
Thanks.
♪ Hey, now
we gon' take it higher ♪
♪ Hey ay ay, we all just
a dog in the fight ♪
Did you invite Rachel?
To the "Light of the City"
thing?
No. I told you,
it's not a big deal.
You invited her
and she's busy?
Out of town.
Oh. Well,
I'll send her pictures.
Oh, hey, 3:00.
Skateboarder's about to grab
that woman's bag.
Swing and a miss.
Tim!
Whoa,
you're bleeding.
I'll be fine.
You okay?
Yeah.
Get the flares out.
Seal off
the whole street.
Ma'am, are you hurt?
No. I'm fine.
Control, 7-Adam-19.
Show me at a traffic collision
at Melrose and Gardner.
Be advised,
it's a city vehicle.
Coming up with a plan of action?
Deciding what to clean first?
No. I'm grading
the forensic team's work.
Looks like
Tip Johnson's guys.
I give them a B-plus.
How can you tell that?
They swab for DNA
and then lift prints,
which is the correct way
to do it.
Gil River's team
always prints first.
And they work outside in.
That is incredible.
You know the habits
of all the FSU teams?
Most of them.
Oh, look at this.
Yeah.
Yeah, uh,
fingerprint powder here
means someone was trying
to hold the door shut
while someone was trying
to push their way in.
So, this is
where it started.
And obviously,
they got in.
See the blood drops?
If the blood drops
are circular,
that means the victim
was standing still.
Wait, you can...
tell if the person
was moving or not
based on the shape of the drops?
Exactly.
The faster they move,
the more elongated the drops.
So, the narrow part of the drop
will indicate
the direction
the person ran.
You are a natural!
So, um,
it started here.
He's bleeding,
he's running,
he's...bleeding.
A stu-- stutter step.
"Am I gonna get away?"
They caught him.
He went down, and they beat him
something terrible.
Looks like
they dragged him.
He probably grabbed
ahold of the bookshelf
and pulled it down.
And then...
Wow.
That's a $20,000
bottle of tequila.
That's worth more than
all the low-rent furniture
in this place.
Maybe it was a gift.
You know, when I worked
in construction,
I never drove a nice truck
to go bid on a job.
Made the client think
you were charging too much.
Maybe he's just trying
to hide his money.
Tequila will get grass stains
out of white jeans.
Oh.
That's not good.
Sorry, the gruesome murder scene
just got not good?
There's blood
on the windows,
but there's not much
on the desktop.
So, there was something
Uh-huh.
The victim
was on the desktop.
You know what makes holes
like that?
Those are nail holes.
They nailed him
to the desk.
And they tortured him.
There's only two reasons
to torture someone.
You hate their guts.
Or you want them
to tell you something.
Or it's a sex thing.
So, three things.
I'm super uncomfortable.
We're handling it, Sarge.
That's a lot of cops
for a fender bender.
Officer-involved accidents
are very serious.
Someone's getting
a day at the beach.
Day at the beach?
Suspension
without pay.
One of the many possible
discipline options.
I could be demoted,
kicked out of field training.
No point in taking
the sergeant's exam.
Things just keep
getting better.
♪ 'Round and 'round ♪
♪ The wheels on the bus
go 'round and 'round ♪
You two okay?
Yeah. Fine.
Shop's not.
What happened?
I lost focus.
The car just
suddenly stopped.
And the other driver?
Uh, taken to the hospital.
Might have whiplash.
Possible concussion.
It's probably best
you sit out the ceremony today.
Of course.
Can't have the Deputy Chief
handing a plaque
to an officer
facing demotion.
I'll need a collision memo
on this by end of shift.
Given the liability
implications,
you should go to the hospital,
in order to head off
any questions
about your fitness to drive.
Have them do
a full work-up
and prove
that you weren't impaired.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry, Tim.
Follow our shop
back to the garage.
Transfer our gear to a new one,
pick me up at the hospital.
Okay.
Arrest report done.
Eager to get
back out there?
Oh, I do have to add
the CHP 180.
180.
That is so weird.
It's like a full turn.
He did a 180.
Wow.
I wonder if that was a
coincidence or something that --
Jackson?
Yeah?
What are you
talking about?
Paperwork.
Like, uh, formats.
The data, you know?
Have you ever really sat
and thought about
how much data
we actually collect?
Like, terabytes and terabytes
of data our whole lives.
Actually, we carry
more data on our phone
than they ever processed
on Apollo 11.
Fact.
Why don't you
come with me?
Where?
Come on.
Why are you so rough?
Occupied.
It's like
an airplane bathroom.
Let's go in here.
Hey, what are you doing?
Look to the left.
Okay, look,
you don't understand.
That kind of computing power
and all our data,
we are just
a few years away
from being able
to predict crime.
Look to the left.
Okay.
Now.
Now right.
It's like a couple
flying saucers in there.
What?
Oh, my gosh.
I'm high.
On drugs.
I did drugs.
Not on purpose.
No, no, I-I don't do drugs.
I've never done drugs before.
Shocker.
7-Adam-07, go to Channel 2.
Oh, God.
Grey knows. He knows.
No, he doesn't, but he will
if you don't play it cool.
What is it, Sarge?
You got Officer West
with you?
Yes, sir.
I'm here.
Sorry.
You'll be receiving
the special commendation alone.
Uh, from the Deputy Chief.
Right.
Why?
What happened with Tim?
He's been involved
in an incident.
He won't be attending.
Copy that.
I'm dead.
It's over. I --
Is this what it feels like
to be dead?
It's not --
It's not bad.
Look. Don't panic.
We'll get through this.
Look, my dad will be there,
with the Deputy Chief.
Give me your weapon.
What? Why?
Because you can't have a gun
if you're high.
We're going to the hospital,
get your blood tested.
Keep your eyes forward
as we leave the station,
and don't talk to anyone.
You can talk to me.
Copy that.
Come on.
So, that was
a nice gesture,
giving Tim advice
after the accident.
"Team player" is a big part
of the evaluation.
It is.
But I have a feeling
you would've did the same thing
whether I was watching
or not.
Excuse me.
That's my daughter.
Hey, honey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Slow down.
What? You got --
You got in where?
Oh. No, no,
of course I'm excited.
It's a great school.
Yeah, call your mom,
and I will talk to you later.
Hey, congratulations.
Yeah.
She got into Cornell.
And you don't
want her to go.
We settled on UCSB.
Ah, that's close by.
I went to Cornell.
Or was it Colgate?
Whee!
7-Adam-15.
We have a 415.
Shirtless man with a bat.
Drop the bat.
I can't.
I need to protect myself.
From who?
Zombies!
It's starting!
They're everywhere!
Drop the bat,
or we will shoot you.
I'm not gonna
let them bite me!
Hey. I get it.
Infection moves fast.
But we can protect you.
Okay? Our car
is armor-plated.
They won't be able
to get in.
Hey, it's a hell of a lot safer
than being on the street.
But first, you have to
put down the bat.
Put your hands
behind your back.
Palms together.
Spread your feet.
Nice work.
And what's that one do?
Uh, the three B's --
blood, bile, and barf.
Nice.
And this one?
Oh, that's a proprietary blend
from Japan.
It's the only thing that will
get brains out of a jute rug.
I had to sneak it out
through Guam
'cause it's pretty much
straight-up cancer.
Any guess as to when they're
gonna release the scene?
No. It's getting
kind of ridiculous.
I mean, you got a job to do.
I got a birthday to salvage.
It's your birthday?
Yeah.
Control, this is 7-L-9
at the Grand Avenue homicide.
Any word when they're gonna
clear this crime scene?
Sorry.
Homicide's all backed up.
Oh, I...I --
Can I...?
Nell, it's Ellroy.
Hi, Ellroy!
Glad you're on this one.
Sounds like a real doozy.
Oh, yeah!
This guy evacuated
out of every orifice.
Uh, so, are you still planning
that trip to Borneo --
Hey, h-hold on.
Nell, I'm looking at some blood
outside the warranted area,
leading to another part
of the building.
Do you want me to alert
homicide detectives?
Yeah.
And forensics, too.
And let Sgt. Grey know
the security guard
they were thinking was in on it?
They can cancel
the APB.
We found him.
What this place
really needs --
it needs...some calming music,
you know?
Like, uh, monks chanting
or, uh, those whale songs.
That would be nice.
Um, he got some powder
on his face --
Mm-hmm.
white powder, and --
You need to find out
what drug he was exposed to.
The guy we stopped
had priors for PCP.
PCP is fat-soluble.
I mean, that stays
in your system for a lifetime.
Exactly. And if you can
hallucinate at any time,
you can't carry a gun.
It's an automatic retirement.
He'll be off the force.
I'll rush the tests.
Wait, you don't have to
report this, right?
I'm precluded
by HIPAA laws
from discussing this
with anyone.
Good.
If the test comes back positive,
I'll fill out an exposure form.
But if it's nothing serious,
I want to keep it quiet.
Imagine being able to stop crime
before it happens.
Mind-blowing concept
that I've actually sat with
for a few days.
I pitched it --
Hey!
What are you
doing here?
Nothing.
I'm not following.
What were you saying?
Nothing. Just some sci-fi movie
he won't stop talking about.
Go wait by the elevator.
Are you okay?
What happened?
I rear-ended a citizen.
Bad?
She's in the ER.
I don't know
how it happened.
Just --
I got to go.
Everything looks normal.
Great.
People get in accidents.
Even cops.
What do they call it
when a doctor has an accident?
Malpractice.
Well, we're both held
to a higher standard --
for good reason.
How is she?
The CT scan came back negative
for internal bleeding.
We'll keep her overnight
to make sure she's okay.
She asked for you
when they first brought her in.
She doesn't blame you.
Go talk to her.
Thanks.
How are you doing?
I'm okay.
No.
No, you're not.
Do you know how much
this is all gonna cost?
The hospital bills
will be covered by the city.
So will the repairs
to your vehicle.
You just think
that makes everything alright?
Mike, stop.
No, i-it's okay.
He has a right to be angry.
And I have a right
to sue.
We're not gonna sue.
You -- He didn't mean to hit me,
did you?
No, ma'am.
I hope
you feel better soon.
You got business here,
little lady?
My T.O. and I were the ones
involved in this accident.
Oh, right.
The beach boy.
He's screwed.
Have you...looked
at the other car yet?
Not yet.
There's something
I can't get out of my head.
I-I don't remember
seeing brake lights.
Uh-huh.
Can you take a look?
Yeah, when I have time.
You've got time now.
This is important.
Officer Bradford
is a 12-year veteran.
He's been wounded five times
in the line of duty.
He deserves your respect,
not whatever macho crap
this...is...
sir.
Okay.
Let's take a look.
Oh.
Taillights weren't on.
How can you tell?
The brake lights
didn't work
because someone
pulled out the contacts.
Could that have happened
during the accident?
No.
These were pulled
on purpose.
Why would they do that?
Insurance scams.
See it all the time.
Get someone to rear-end you
and collect the settlement.
Maybe your T.O.
isn't screwed after all.
What's that?
The powder?
Ah. Looks like your victim's
into all kinds of scams.
What do you mean?
Powder's, uh,
red phosphorous.
You know, the stuff
on the tip of matches?
Why would they have that?
Well, if they're not
cooking meth,
arsonists use it
to set fires.
Harder to trace
than gasoline,
and you can make a fuse
with it.
Hey.
You switch out
the shops?
Uh, yeah,
but there's something else.
The car was rigged.
What?
The brake lights
weren't connected.
This accident
wasn't your fault.
No wonder
I reacted so slowly.
The leads were
purposefully disconnected?
Yeah.
And there's more.
Sarah had arson materials
in the back of her car.
Clearly, she's a bit
of a renaissance scam artist.
Let's go talk to her.
You rigged the car.
What?
No. I didn't.
Dash cam says different.
So does a physical inspection
of your vehicle.
You searched my car?
I didn't give you permission.
We don't need permission
once it's been involved
in an accident.
I don't think you were
trying to get rear-ended
by a police car.
Bad luck, honestly.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Sarah, this is serious.
Your vehicle's full of evidence,
all admissible against you.
It's not mine.
Then whose is it?
Your boyfriend? The guy who was
threatening to sue me earlier?
No.
What's his name?
I'm not gonna
tell you that.
Emergency contact --
Mike Garvey.
And a phone number.
Just what we need
for a background check.
So you don't go anywhere
while we're running it.
Stay here
until I come back.
If I could just talk
to the IT guys --
No.
No talking to anyone.
Well, look, maybe I am high,
but these are still solid ideas.
Okay.
I'm cool.
I will stay here,
and I will not talk to anyone.
Great.
Get it together.
You're gonna be okay.
Just slow down...
and, uh...
take a breath.
What if the copier
could copy your thoughts?
I think you should
interview him alone.
Why?
Because he knows
I'm the one that hit her.
He doesn't know
you were in the car with me.
His guard won't be up.
I need to be
at the hospital.
Yes, sir.
We'll get you out of here
as quickly as we can.
And I wasn't even
in the car.
I don't understand
why you have to talk to me.
It's...standard procedure.
You can imagine
the paperwork
when an officer gets involved
in an accident.
That cop should be fired.
That is up to
the department.
Do you and Sarah
live together?
Yeah. Why?
Do you ever use her car?
What difference
does it make?!
She was rear-ended.
Yes, sir. If you could
just answer the question.
Do you ever use her car?
No.
Never?
Never.
So, you didn't
disconnect her taillights
to commit insurance fraud?
Nope.
But you have
committed fraud before.
Isn't that true?
Arrested three times,
convicted once.
I'm out of here.
I know
what's going on here.
You're trying to intimidate me.
But it's not gonna work.
'Cause I'm gonna get a lawyer,
I'm gonna come back here,
I'm gonna sue you
and the entire department.
Little advice -- if you can
only afford one retainer,
I'd start
with a criminal lawyer.
You're gonna need
that one first.
Sorry I didn't
get more out of him.
Don't be. The point
was to wind him up.
First thing he's gonna do
is call Sarah
and wind her up
even more.
And then
we see who breaks first.
I've decided.
Dominique can go to Cornell.
We'll just move there.
Ithaca's a nice town.
It's 3,000 miles away.
That's a hell of a commute
to downtown L.A.
I can get a gig there.
Luna's been begging me
to retire from the LAPD anyway.
So, you're gonna follow
your daughter to college?
That's not crazy at all.
This way, I am close by
if she needs me.
Don't do it.
My parents barely let me
out of their sight.
Drove me crazy.
You got to let her
spread her wings.
Fly!
Disagree. Got to
keep your family close.
Zombies take over the city,
you got to be able
to grab them and go.
The man with the nail bat
agrees with you.
Just, uh, you know,
take that in for a minute.
Don't forget, I'm evaluating you
today, Detective.
Yes, sir.
Ithaca is lovely
this time of year.
Jackson?
And you'd be at the nexus
of it all --
dispatching units
to pre-crimes,
and you'd use the copier
to help you.
Hmm.
Jackson!
We're supposed to be
handling calls.
Okay. Yeah. We were just --
Well, we're just --
Let's go now.
Um, Officer Lopez?
Just one quick thing?
Sure. What's up?
It's about Officer West.
Yeah?
I just wanted to say
that he is...
...such an insightful
thinker.
I mean, did you know
he was full of ideas?
I did not.
He's usually much...
quieter.
Hmm.
Nice to see you, Nell.
Mm-hmm.
Only one of you
is getting a deal.
And you want it
to be you.
I was about to leave him.
I went over to borrow
some suitcases from my sister.
I-I didn't know that
he messed with my brake lights.
I swear.
Why were you
leaving him?
He's gone over the edge.
At first, it was
just staged accidents.
We'd shake down
some rich losers for cash
or set a few fires for a cut
of the insurance money,
but now --
But now what?
He's agreed to kill
some guy's wife
for a cut
of the life-insurance policy.
And when is this murder
supposed to happen?
Later today.
Homicide is sending
another forensics team.
This place isn't gonna be
cleared for hours at this point.
You might as well
go home.
I'm good.
Um, hey...
I was wondering...
what is Nell like?
Nell?
She's lovely.
I mean, I-I've talked to her
a lot, you know,
when dispatch calls me,
but I've never met her
in person.
Is she pretty?
Yes.
You know, you could
come down to the station,
meet her face-to-face.
No. I couldn't.
Uh...
Um...
she's busy.
I -- Um, I'm busy.
We're busy.
I couldn't.
Listen -- Nah.
Ta-da.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
That is...
extremely thoughtful.
It's nothing.
Birthdays are important.
This is a treat.
It really is.
You okay?
Yeah.
I missed one.
My sister's.
Her last.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
She killed herself
that year.
Um, at my parents' house.
Ellroy, was that
your first crime scene?
I put everything
the way it was,
but nothing
has been right since.
Ellroy, I don't even know
what to say.
I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
It was a long time ago.
Anyway...
I think
I am gonna take off.
Uh, just...
give me a heads-up whenever
they finally clear the scene.
Of course.
Yeah.
Alright.
Hey, Ellroy,
did you see this?
What's that?
This vent.
The screws have been practically
pulled out of the wall.
What if the bookcase didn't
fall down in the struggle?
What if they moved it so they
could look inside the vent?
Lawyers like this guy,
they deal in a lot of cash.
Maybe they knew
he kept it hidden here,
and they tortured him
to find it.
Well, it wasn't hidden
in the vent.
This thing's coated with dust.
Hasn't been touched in years.
Must have kept looking,
moved next door
into the raw space.
I don't think
they ever found it.
How do you know?
Because they're back.
LAPD!
Drop your weapons!
7-Adam-9 --
Oh, no.
Okay, Ellroy, you're gonna move
to the raw space behind me.
As soon as I say "Move."
Ready?
Move!
Help me!
Oh, God.
That's not gonna hold them
for long.
Alright. Alright.
Okay, um...come on.
Give me your phone.
Mine's dead.
Oh.
I have a pager.
Seriously?
He probably surprised them when
they were searching in here.
Okay.
Now we just have to
find a place to hide
till the cavalry arrives.
Come on.
Over here.
Right.
You stay right here.
By myself?
I'm bringing a pipe
to a gunfight?
It's better
than bare hands.
Stay down! Do not move.
Stay down! Facedown!
Hands!
Good work, Ellroy.
I'm glad I know how to clean
the stains out of trousers.
Freeze!
LAPD!
Turn around!
Drop your weapon!
Keep your hands up!
Sidestep to the right!
Keep going!
Get down on the ground!
On your stomach!
Hands out to the side!
Now, don't move!
Mike Garvey, you're under arrest
for attempted murder.
Nice wig, Boot.
♪ What are you doing here? ♪
It took long enough
to get this going.
You might be
under the limit by now.
Yeah.
Feeling pretty sober.
Look, I know it's a lot.
Let it be a wake-up call.
Getting arrested
might be the best thing
that ever happened to you.
♪ We were lovers, sure ♪
♪ But that's not
what I came here for ♪
♪ I came because... ♪
I'm not an alcoholic.
You were stumbling drunk
at 10:00 a.m.
I had a doctor's appointment
at 9:00.
Bad news?
♪ You say love is hardly... ♪
Not a good day for tests.
My biopsy came back.
Stage 3 breast cancer.
The bar
was across the street.
I just wanted
to feel...less.
I wasn't gonna drive.
I would never hurt anybody.
♪ I am a cold wind ♪
.07.
Just under the limit.
♪ And the hands of Satan ♪
We're gonna release you,
pending D.A. review.
Really?
Yeah.
You deserve
a little good news today.
Thank you.
♪ I've still got daylight
in my heart ♪
How are you feeling?
My head is pounding,
and my throat's on fire.
Sounds like you're coming down
off whatever it was.
Hey.
I was, uh,
looking for Nolan.
Since I'm
running into you...
Not PCP.
Please not PCP.
It wasn't PCP.
Yes!
Or much of anything,
really.
It was horse vitamins
and caffeine.
It was bunk?
But he's been high as a kite
all day.
An allergic reaction can mimic
some of those symptoms.
And from there,
the power of suggestion
did the rest.
♪ ...restart one day ♪
Dress blues?
Bradford and West
are getting their commendations
in a half-hour.
Oh. Right.
I didn't have a chance
to write up your evaluation,
but you'll have it
tomorrow.
And it will be positive.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You know,
I wanted to say...
you did a great job
with your daughter.
Yeah.
The fact she wants to move
across country speaks volumes.
It does.
It says that she's brave
and confident.
You gave her a home --
a safe place to launch from
and retreat to.
Same way you do for us.
I hope I can become
half the parent you are.
♪ Banging on my eardrums
till my... ♪
Laying it on pretty thick,
aren't you?
Yes, sir.
Have fun at the ceremony.
Will do.
♪ Why don't I listen
to myself? ♪
Get it.
Alright. Okay. Yeah.
That's enough.
I told you,
I need to get pics for Rachel.
Come on, Boot.
Buy me a beer.
You make that your home screen,
you're gonna be running
the Academy training course
in a bomb disposal suit.
I would never do that.
It is now...
my lock screen.
Listen...
I wouldn't have gotten
this stupid plaque
if you didn't
have my back today.
So...
you know...
thanks.
For what?
Doing my job?
Today was fun.
I mean, not fun,
but fun...fun.
Well, the fun
hasn't stopped yet.
I'm gonna introduce you
to Nell.
What? W-When?
What?
Don't tell me
you don't want to meet her.
I'd rather face off
against another shotgun.
That's the spirit.
Hey, there, Nell.
Oh! Hi. I'm so happy
to see that you're okay.
Thank you for everything.
Uh, Nell...
this is Ellroy.
Ellroy?
Hi.
Oh, I'm so happy
to finally meet you in person.
I'm good to meet you, too.
I'm glad.
Ellroy saved my life today.
Tell her that story.
Wow.
Is this for me?
Did I miss it?
Miss what?
What is that?
What is this?
Surprise.
Happy birthday!
You know, um...
a year ago, I never would have
believed this would be my life.
I mean,
new beginnings are rare,
and rewarding ones,
even more so.
And here I am,
surrounded by the best people
I've ever known.
And Lopez.
Just --
That's just jokes.
To us.
Cheers!
Cheers.
You want
to cheer somebody?
Alright.
What did you get me?
Take a guess.
A steamer.
Exactly.
Corrected by
Flatto (subscene.com)