Swear to God, now
he has this woman tied up,
his own aunt.
He has a shotgun rigged
with duct tape and a string
so he can shoot her from the fireplace.
Yeah, while Chen's across town
going toe-to-toe with the 5-4.
Yeah, thirty gang members
against me and my T.O.
Oh, my God, that's hardcore.
How the hell'd you get out of that?
No joke, my T.O. goes,
"When you're in the LAPD"...
"You're never alone".
And right on cue,
an airship arrives with a SWAT team.
Damn, there's me thinking
discharging my weapon
this year was a big deal.
Aw, don't beat yourself up, Chris.
I'm sure someday you'll catch up.
Oh, it's like that?
Oh, yeah. It's like that.
Come on, you guys. We're
not in the Academy anymore.
We don't have to be
competitive about everything.
Well, it's not a competition
when I always win.
Ooh, that's a deep cut!
But he does have a point.
- That's it, West.
- Hmm?
You and me, right now...
We're gonna settle this
thing once and for all.
Mm.
Drink up. Drink up.
I can't believe they still
can't let go of their rivalry.
Can't you? They were first
and second at the Academy.
Their dads were first and second.
- Oh! Sorry! Sorry!
- Oh, ho, ho!
- You okay?
- Yep.
Nope.
I was just gonna get some
air. How about you join me?
- Sorry.
- No, no, no. Don't.
So, I'm actually fine.
Just... a little worried about Chris.
I mean, you always gave the
best advice at the Academy.
Thank you. Uh, what's going on?
At first, I thought it was
just a rocky transition.
You know, going from
being top of the class
to being just another Boot.
But... he never really evened out.
Did you know he barely
passed our six-month exam?
- Can you believe that?
- Actually, I can.
If he came in expecting it to be easy,
I mean, it is not.
I'm worried. What if he's
really not ready?
Should I say something?
I can't answer that for you.
I can tell you that this year has
been tough for all of us.
I mean, no vacation, no sick days,
constantly under a microscope.
We've all stumbled.
Yeah.
If I were you, I would just...
tell Chris you're there for him.
And if he can bear down
for one more month,
then he can take some time off
and just clear his head,
you know, reset.
I've been trying to convince
him to go on the road with me,
take an RV and camp, hike,
just disconnect from all the noise
before we come back as P2s.
See, that would be perfect.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I knew I'd feel better talking to you.
50 bucks.
Nolan! I need your help.
I'm sorry. How is this helping?
- Jackson and I are tied.
- One more event will settle this.
If you hit Nolan, you lose.
Wait, what game is this?
- Suicide darts.
Ow!
I do not wanna go to work today.
Mm, you can be a few minutes late.
Yeah, and do push-ups
in between every call
and jog behind the shop?
No, thanks.
Mm.
- Oh, come on!
- Mnh-mnh!
Bradford's chill.
I mean, maybe if you're
playing pick-up with him,
but not when he's your T.O.
He once designed an IED
to blow up baby powder in my face
just to make a point.
Is he allowed to do that?
I just need to get through
the next thirty days,
and then I will be free.
No more mind games. No more Tim Tests.
No more chewing me out in public.
Okay, so you're saying thirty days,
and then I can make you late?
- Mm.
- Hm?
Mm.
Um... listen.
If we bump into each other at work,
can we please just play it cool?
I'm not cool?
No! You know what I mean!
Like, on the... D.L.
The D.L.?
Yep, I said that. I'm sorry.
Don't laugh!
Don't you work with your roommate?
Oh, Jackson's got my back.
He would never talk.
Well, I can't promise I'll be
able to keep my eyes off of you,
but otherwise, deal.
- Thank you.
- Mm.
Aah!
But, wait, Grace might actually
let her ex-husband come back home?
For the sake of her son.
Look, I-I get where she's coming from.
I mean, I did something
similar with my ex.
Staying together for the kid,
even when you knew
the relationship was doomed.
Did that actually make
things better for Henry?
No. But what am I gonna do?
Mansplain to her she's making a mistake?
How well is that gonna go over?
Yeah, not well.
But if you leave her alone,
you risk giving the ex an opening.
Tough one.
I'm looking for some sage advice here.
If you haven't noticed, my
personal life's a dumpster fire.
All I can say is...
I'm rooting for you two.
Good luck, buddy.
You can do it.
I'm telling you.
Today is our rookies' one-year
mark in the F.T.O. program.
Congratulations on not washing out.
Yet.
We'll see.
There's still time.
That also means today is the start
of your Thirty Day Push.
Why is that important, Officer Nolan?
Because in one month,
we will no longer be
probationary employees,
but fully fledged patrol
officers of the LAPD?
- No.
- Damn it.
Because, as your T.O.s have pointed out,
you are not there yet.
The end of the race
is always the hardest.
The Push is to remind
you not to celebrate
until you cross the finish line.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Good.
And... that's all I got.
For the first time in history,
the night shift did their jobs...
left no open cases
that require follow-up.
So, go on, find some crime.
And be safe out there.
It's weird we haven't had any calls yet.
Crime doesn't run on a schedule, Boot.
What are you so happy about?
What? Nothing.
Can't I smile?
You've just been doing it a lot lately.
I didn't realize happiness
was an impediment
to being a good cop.
I'm just surprised you haven't tried
to talk my ear off about whatever it is.
So, what? Did you rescue a kitten?
Adopt a star?
My personal life is
none of your business.
Finally. There's hope for you yet.
My mom is driving me crazy.
She's teamed up with Wesley's mom,
so every time I try to make a decision
about the wedding, I'm outnumbered.
You're the bride.
Shouldn't you get final say?
I'm the only girl in either family,
so they're living vicariously.
And I don't have the
bandwidth to push back
because I'm so focused
on making detective.
If I don't make the next
round of promotions,
I'll have to take the
detective's exam again.
But while I'm distracted,
those viejas are hijacking my wedding.
Come on. I'm pretty
sure it's not that bad.
They decided the color scheme
should be pink and peach.
Oh, no.
Do I look like a woman
who's ever worn peach?
No. You're definitely an autumn.
Is that... ?
No.
Wait a second.
No. Forget it.
Okay, so, how about you
make visual confirmation
before you speak?
Roger that.
You a little nervous about court today?
My lawyer says,
with all of my positive
changes that I've made
and my improved relationship
with Donovan, there's no reason
the judge shouldn't
grant me shared custody.
That's great!
Yeah, except the judge
is a real hard-ass
and has a reputation for being
unorthodox in his rulings.
I'm sure you have
nothing to worry about.
Man! I don't know that I've
ever had a shift this quiet.
Did you really just say
the "Q" word in my shop?
What? Quie...
Na-na-ah-ah-ah-ah! Stop!
You do not, under any circumstance,
ever use the "Q" word while on duty.
That is like saying "Macbeth" in theater
or talking about a
no-hitter in the dugout.
O... kay. I had no idea
you were superstitious.
That is not superstition. That's fact.
Where are you going?
I am going to get the
trauma plate for my vest,
'cause I have a feeling
I'm gonna need it.
You and your big mouth probably
just cost me custody of my kid.
Wilshire units, information only.
Hollywood division is in pursuit
after a shots fired call.
Event 8-0-5 working on channel 4.
Information only.
Turn that on. I wanna hear.
Uh, gr-gray Maserati, no plates.
Suspect vehicle is picking up speed.
Uh, we are southbound on
Normandie, 50 miles an hour.
We got moderate traffic.
Wait. That voice.
That's Chris.
Rios.
We went to the Academy together.
His dad worked Narcotics with
my old man back in the day.
Well, at least Hollywood's
getting a little action today.
O-O-O-Okay, wait.
I'm... J-Just stand by.
Something's going down.
Okay, he's left on Wilshire.
E-Eastbound on Wilshire. Speed is 70.
This is heavy traffic. He's...
He's blowing lights.
- Sidewalk! He's on the sidewalk!
- He's too amped up.
Copy, eastbound Wilshire,
speed 70, blowing lights call.
6-Mary-100, copy?
Copy. Advise Mid-Wilshire.
Want is 245 with a handgun.
Control, 7-Adam-15,
attach us to the pursuit.
Event 8-0-5 and switching to channel 4.
"Quiet", he says.
6-Adam-41, just T.C.'d,
Wilshire at Virgil.
We are lead car. I-I'm
gonna need backup, guys.
I need... I-I need help!
Copy, 6-Mary-47 help call.
Hollywood and Mid-Wilshire
units responding.
Control, 7-Adam-19, attach. Code 3.
Copy, 6-Mary-47 eastbound on Wilshire,
approaching MacArthur Park.
That's right around the corner.
Control, 7-Adam-07,
we're two blocks from there.
Suspect vehicle has crashed!
- Hey, get back! Get back!
- Hands! Hands!
Show me your hands! Hands on the window!
- Chris, get back!
- Hands! Hands!
- Show me your hands!
- No! No!
No! Chris!
Son of a bitch!
Rios!
Control, 7-15, we have the Maserati,
northbound Park View.
In pursuit. Speed's 60. Occupied once.
7-Adam-07, shots fired.
Officer down. Repeat, officer down.
Requesting R.A. for a 25-year-old male,
gunshot wound to the chest.
- Come on, come on, come on!
- Conscious and breathing.
Park View at 7th.
All units, be advised,
7-Adam-15 in pursuit
of gray Maserati heading
south on Alvarado.
- Do you see him?
- Negative. I lost him at the last intersection.
Damn it.
Attention, all units.
Air-12 spotted a gray Maserati
matching suspect's vehicle
entering covered parking
structure at 6th and Grand.
7-Adam-15 responding. Code 3.
Just keep breathing, buddy, alright?
- Martinez.
- Alright. Huh?
Sarge is gonna want to talk
to you. You're a witness.
- I'm not leaving this kid alone.
- I'll go.
One, two, three! Lift!
This shouldn't have happened.
I made a felony stop.
Rios just charged.
I mean, he's made mistakes
before, but never like this.
He knows...
stop at a safe distance,
wait for backup,
- approach with caution, but...
- It hap... It happens.
Rookies aren't used to the adrenaline.
They get amped up. It's
lights and sirens syndrome.
I told him on day one. I told him.
It's the hardest part
about being a T.O. Okay?
We drill it into their head,
but at the end of the day,
they make their own calls.
Still feels like my fault.
No. Come on.
You hurt?
Nah, I just... just tweaked
it pulling him out of danger.
- I'm alright.
- 7-Adam-19,
send an additional R.A. to my location.
You're gonna be okay.
Look at me. Look at me. Alright?
Remember the obstacle
course at the Academy?
First time through,
you had a torn hamstring
and still beat me.
Yeah, and I practiced
every single day after that,
knowing that you'd be coming for me.
I was only number one because
you were there pushing me.
And now I'm gonna be here pushing you,
getting you back to your feet.
Alright?
Okay, and I expect your
"A" game, man, alright?
None of that "I got shot" B.S.
You hear me?
Chris, you hear me, man?
He's losing too much blood!
- How much further?!
- Three minutes out.
Chris. Come on, Chris.
Stay with me, man! Come on!
Chris!
There.
Nolan. Door.
Got a gun.
You need to secure it while
I go after the suspect.
I'll go with you.
No, that gun is a crucial
piece of evidence,
and TID has their hands full
processing the shooting scene,
so I am designating you the finder.
Photograph everything.
Make sure you get that gun
exactly how it was found.
Glove up, collect it, and
store it in our shop's lock box.
- You got it?
- Yes, ma'am.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Suspect vehicle located
in a parking structure on 6th and Grand.
Gun on scene. My T.O.
is in pursuit of suspect
through a maintenance door
on the northeast corner.
Need backup. Code 3.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Shut down all code 3 units.
Suspect is G.O.A.
Damn it.
25-year-old male,
single gunshot wound to the chest.
Possible lung collapse. He's
down two liters of blood.
Aren't you taking him to surgery?
If I don't stop the bleeding,
he won't make it to the OR.
Three, two, one.
Get a gurney. Clear Trauma 1.
Get him on the monitor.
Jackson, I hear... I heard
what happened. Is he... ?
They're, um... They're
trying to stabilize him.
He lost a lot of blood.
- Oh, my God.
- No.
Get it out.
I have to go back to the station, okay?
I got a mandatory callback, but...
will you call me with any news?
Of course. I'm... I'm
not going anywhere.
Okay, scene's secure.
What the hell are you doing?
You holding something
in your right hand?
Your gun hand?
How many times I gotta tell you
to keep your gun hand free at all times?
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
You've been on this job a whole
year, and you're still making
the same dumb mistakes you've
been making since day one.
You want to end up like Rios?
Whoa, Tim.
That's enough, man.
Excuse me?
You don't have to talk to her like that.
She's my Boot.
I'll talk to her however
the hell I want to
so she doesn't end up eating
through a tube the rest of her life.
You got that?
Let's go, Boot.
I did not need saving.
I kind of went overboard
with the crime scene photos.
Better safe than sorry.
No sign of the suspect?
No, he got away clean. But
we did recover his weapon.
Nine-mil. Recently fired.
Good work. Anything else?
Uh, yes. The car is
registered to a dealership...
International Luxury Auto.
- Stolen?
- Not reported.
We need to run background checks
on the dealership employees.
Already happening. But
we would get a much faster ID
from the mobile fingerprint
unit inside your car.
We pulled a clean print from
the driver's side window.
Uh, yeah. Great.
Any update on Chris?
- Nothing yet.
- How is it out there?
Controlled chaos.
We're spread thin through two divisions.
And just like that,
our suspect has a name.
Serj Derian. Number one on
Robbery-Homicide's hit list.
Younger brother of Ruben,
the head of the Derian crime family.
Linked to drug trafficking, extortion,
kidnapping, and murder.
But so far, none of
the charges have stuck.
Now, remember, this guy has
already shot one cop today.
I need you focused, not angry.
LAPD!
Serj Derian, come out
with your hands up!
- Clear!
Clear!
He's not here.
Hey, you gotta go.
I know, but how can I?
Serj wasn't home.
Bradford and Chen are
searching his stuff right now.
What'd I miss?
Harper has a custody
hearing in about an hour,
and she's conflicted about leaving,
but I say number-one priority
has to be getting Lila back.
Tell me I'm right.
100%.
Look, take it from me.
Nothing is more important than family.
Alright, fine.
But I will be back right after.
Hey.
Take my unmarked. I'll
ride back with Nolan.
- Thanks.
- Give Lila a hug for me.
What are we looking for?
Anything that could lead us to Serj.
- What the hell?
- You got something?
Yeah, a police report.
There's more.
"Suspect... Serj Derian".
His name's all over these.
Someone inside the department
has been feeding intel
to the Armenian mob.
And by someone, you mean...
A dirty cop.
Come in.
Close the door.
So, Bradford and Chen just found
confidential police documents
in Serj's home.
Case files for LAPD
investigations into the Derians.
You saying there's a mole
inside the department?
It'd explain why these
guys have been so slippery.
So, we haven't been able to
make a single case against them.
What does internal affairs say?
They're mobilizing.
Commander West was keeping
it close to the vest,
but I got a sense they already
have a few cops in mind.
So, what do we do in the meantime?
Serj's older brother... Ruben.
He runs things from
his house in Glendale.
There's a chance Serj is holed up there.
If not, Ruben's the first
person we should be questioning.
Why are you only telling me all this?
I know I can trust you.
So I'm making you acting detective
until this calms down.
You already passed the
exam, so I might as well
take advantage of you
until the brass realizes
- what they're missing out on.
- Copy that.
So, round up as many units as you need,
call a judge for a
telephonic search warrant.
Yes, sir.
I've wanted this for
so long, so thank you.
Just wish a cop didn't have
to get shot for it to happen.
We answer the call when we get it.
Still thinking about Grace?
You're a good detective.
You're an easy case.
Days like today just make you realize
how little time you could have.
Time I want to spend with her.
That's the kind of thing you
might regret not telling someone.
You know what? When
we get back to the station,
I'm gonna book the evidence
and I'm gonna call her.
Call her?
You better get your ass over there
and tell her in person.
They're putting together a
raid at Ruben Derian's house.
Is Serj there?
Only one way to find out.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Attach us to that ATL.
Lock and load.
Any eye on Serj?
Not yet, but there's at least
a handful of unknowns inside.
- What's the game plan?
- House is around the corner.
I'll have officers cover the perimeter
while the rest of us breach.
I would put Stapleton, Cole,
and Brady on the 3/4 corner.
Jennings and Sanchez,
they can take the 2 side.
We'll join you in the stack.
- Sorry. Second nature.
- All good, sir.
You're the senior detective
on site. Operation is yours.
Okay.
Uh...
You're acting detective?
- For the day.
- Doing great.
- Hey.
Wish I was breaching with you guys.
It'd feel good to subdue a
felon with force right now.
Only temporarily.
- Be safe.
- You too.
Police! Open up!
Hands up! Turn around!
- Clear!
Stand up!
Hands on your head! Turn around!
What can I do for you?
We have a warrant to search
the premises for Serj Derian.
You could have just called.
So much banging and
crashing just to discover
that my brother didn't randomly drop by.
All clear. No sign of Serj.
Mr. Derian, we'd like you to come
with us to the station voluntarily.
Yeah, you bet.
Uh, look, why don't I meet
you guys down there, huh?
There's only a half-hour left
in what has been the
best game of the season.
- It's zero-zero.
- A tactical master class.
Your brother shot a cop.
You're coming with us now.
On what charge?
You're a material witness
to your brother's actions,
and refusing to help could be construed
- as aiding and abetting.
- Let's move.
Clear.
Negative. No response.
Alright, book the evidence.
I'm gonna check and see what's next.
Right.
Auto registration.
And could I get a firearm tag?
Wait a minute.
W-Wait.
Uh...
Th... Uh, there was
a gun. There was, um...
There's supposed to be a gun.
Sorry.
Yeah, I understand. Thank you.
Sir, the weapon we
recovered from the Maserati,
the gun that was used
to shoot Officer Rios.
I secured it, and now it's missing.
That call was from the hospital.
Chris Rios just died.
That gun is now a murder weapon.
And you lost it.
Can we talk about what happened earlier?
When earlier?
With Emmett.
There's nothing to say.
The guy tried to tell
me how to do my job.
On today of all days.
I don't care if he's your boyfriend...
He's not.
Actually, he's a little
dead to me right now.
You may be 30 days from
crossing the finish line,
but the only thing that
happens when you cross it
is that I won't be there to
keep you from washing out.
Or worse.
So you better believe
this next month is gonna be tough.
'Cause I know you can handle it.
That's oddly sweet.
But you're not the one
I'm mad at right now.
I'm used to you. I...
Okay, look.
You are only gonna
hear me say this once.
Emmett's a fireman.
They're idiots.
But they mean well.
And Emmett...
... he's a not-bad fireman.
Don't write him off.
I thought we weren't going
to discuss my personal life.
We're friends.
Hmm.
Hey.
Chris died.
Oh, no.
I can't leave you alone for a second.
Hey. How was court? Did the judge...
He's gonna make his
decision tomorrow morning.
But how about we focus
on the murder weapon
that went missing from the shop?
Okay, you saw me bag it...
and put it in the lock box.
The only time we stopped
between the scene and the station
was at Serj's house, for the raid.
Could one of his guys have taken it?
No, not possible.
We had the perimeter completely
contained, and I locked the car.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Mostly sure. Almost mostly sure.
Even if I didn't, it was
secured in the lock box.
And there's no sign of forced entry.
- None.
- You find the gun?
No, and I don't think he's going to.
Why?
The lock box in the
shop wasn't broken into,
but the key for the boxes
is universal across the LAPD.
You think a cop took the gun?
It's the only logical explanation.
We know there's a dirty
cop connected to Serj.
They must have heard on the
radio I'd secured the weapon.
How long were you away from
the shop during the raid?
Uh, we were, what, 20 minutes?
More than enough time for
one of the officers involved
to take the gun.
It makes sense, but it's cold comfort.
Even if we get the weapon back,
the chain of custody has been destroyed.
The D.A. can't use it to convict Serj
for the murder of Officer Rios.
If we ever find the guy.
Oh, we'll find him.
I'm calling all the
officers from the raid
back to the station.
Officer Lopez will be in charge
of going through all
the body cam footage.
What can we do?
You and Armstrong can
take a run at Ruben Derian.
See if we can sweat
something out of him.
It'd be my pleasure.
Alright. That's all.
Hey, Sarge?
Look, Officer Nolan
conducted himself admirably
throughout the raid.
I don't think he's to
blame for what happened.
That'll be my call, Detective.
I'll deal with it
when the time is right.
Sir...
Nolan.
You do not want to have this
conversation with me right now.
Tell us about your brother.
Serj? He's a nice guy.
A bit of a free spirit.
You two close?
Sure.
But I haven't seen him in a couple days.
He takes off sometimes.
Hm.
Wanderlust.
Those Germans.
They really have a word
for everything, don't they?
But you reported his
car stolen this morning.
An hour after it was used in an incident
that ended with a dead police officer.
The Maserati belongs to
the Derians' dealership.
It was found missing during inventory.
How convenient.
Dozens of people have driven
that car in the past week.
Now, my client has
been very cooperative,
so if you don't have
any more questions...
Alright, if you hear from
your brother, give us a call.
He killed a cop.
He is going to prison.
It is up to you to decide
whether or not you are going with him.
I'll keep that in mind.
Now what?
We find a new way to flush
Serj out into the open.
What the hell do you need
our body cams for, Sarge?
Above your pay grade.
Come on.
Oh, hey, Cole.
How you holding up?
Not well.
I should have said something.
Hey, no. This... This is not your fault.
House is around the corner.
I'll have officers cover the perimeter
while the rest of us breach.
Okay, I would put Shelton,
Cole, and Boyd on the...
We have a warrant to search
the premises for Serj Derian.
Double-O-Smitty. At your service.
That man clearly does not know
the "on" button from the "off".
Officer Erin Cole never switched
her camera on during the raid.
She's a rookie, so it could
just be a mental error.
Or she did it on purpose
to cover up taking the gun.
Either way, we need to talk to her.
I can reach out to her T.O.,
call her back to the station.
No need. Cole's ID badge
shows she's still here...
in the locker room.
She dumped everything that
we could use to trace her.
She's running.
How was Officer Cole at the Academy?
Solid.
Yeah, she was a go-getter.
I mean, she wasn't the
strongest or the fastest,
but she made up for it with passion.
I certainly wouldn't have flagged her
as someone who'd betray the badge.
- And as a rookie?
- Maybe she didn't turn.
Maybe she was rotten from the onset.
Meaning what?
She was put into the
department by the Derian family
as a mole?
- Anything?
- No.
No sign of Cole yet.
An S.I.S. team conducted
a raid on her home
and searched the home
of two family members.
- Nothing.
- Forensic Accounting says there's been
no financial activity
on any of her accounts.
Well, she's a cop.
Smart enough to know how
we're gonna try and catch her.
And to know that every available
uniform will be looking for her.
She'll probably flee to somewhere
that's familiar to her.
The question is, how will she get there?
We put a BOLO out county-wide.
The Sheriff's Department, Metro Transit,
Port Police all been notified.
- Eyes are open.
- John.
Uh... excuse me.
I'm so sorry about Officer Rios.
Thank you.
I know that you guys are
working through the night.
I wasn't sure what to get...
I mean, dinner, breakfast?
No, uh, no, pizza always plays.
You guys want to grab this for the... ?
Yeah.
Anyway, I mean, I-I know you're busy.
I just want you to know
that I'm thinking about you.
I'm thinking about you, too.
Um...
thank you so much for the food.
Uh...
talk soon?
Yeah.
Bye.
Hey. Everything okay?
Um, no. But that's a
problem for another day.
Right now, we need to find Erin.
What are you looking at?
I'm just going over all
her social media accounts.
I'm just hoping to
find something in here
that'll give us a clue
as to where she went.
I just don't get it.
She's so happy and carefree.
W-What could happen to make her do this?
Yeah, I mean, social media
shows the side of us
that we want people to see.
"#RVlife".
The other night at the bar,
Erin said she wanted to
go on a road trip in an RV
just as soon as the
Thirty Day Push was over.
You think that's her escape plan?
It would give her mobility.
It would give her a place
to hide off the grid.
The house the RV is registered to
is at the end of this street.
On our go.
I hope she surrenders without a fight.
I wouldn't count on it.
If she's in deep with the Derians,
she knows they'll kill her
to keep her from talking.
She's on the move!
Watch out. Watch out!
Control, 7-Adam-15.
We just got 245'd by
suspect Cole in an RV.
Beige RV, Arizona plates.
Alpha-Bravo-7-9, heading north
on Mission Road towards 1st.
Look out.
Whoa!
Look out!
She's gonna go through.
She's not gonna stop.
Attention, all units.
Air-16 tracking suspect vehicle
heading east on Colorado
towards Pasadena.
- Clear.
- What do we got?
- She's on foot.
- Couple minutes ahead.
- Alright, head inside.
Split up. She could be anywhere.
Control, suspect is on foot.
Rose Bowl Stadium.
Requesting backup and airship.
Erin!
Drop that gun right now!
I can't.
Come on, Erin.
It's me. You know me.
We've been through a lot
together. You can talk to me.
Just talk to me.
I never wanted this.
I know.
I had problems.
Debts, and... they paid them.
And and then they owned me.
Who did?
The Derians?
I finally paid them back,
and I told Serj I was done,
but he... he pulled a gun
and he tried to kill me
when I wouldn't scare and...
The shots fired call.
Serj, he... he got caught flat-footed,
and he... he jumped
in the Maserati, and...
Chris is dead because of me.
No, no, no! Wait, no! Don't! Just...
It doesn't have to all be for nothing.
Okay, you can start to make this right.
Just...
... name names.
Okay? Just testify.
- Armstrong.
- No!
Control, uh, requesting an R.A. unit.
25-year-old female,
multiple gunshot wounds to the chest.
Not conscious, not breathing.
I know you're all exhausted.
The past twenty-four hours have
brought a... lot of heartache.
You did great work out there.
Remember that.
I was notified that
Rios's memorial service
is Saturday afternoon.
Go home, get some rest.
Nolan.
I'm gonna need you to stay behind.
IA is requesting your statement
while it's still fresh in your mind.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
You okay?
I thought I had a chance
at getting through to her.
I had no choice.
Oh, I...
I know.
Just such a waste.
You want me to make you some tea?
I'm okay.
Come here.
Doesn't feel real, you know?
I know.
It's Emmett.
Yeah, uh, you two should talk.
Hey.
I screwed up.
Yeah. You did.
Come in.
Uh...
You're one of the toughest
women I've ever met.
The last thing you need is a protector,
and I didn't mean to imply that you did.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
I accept your apology.
Really?
Yes.
You gotta get out of here.
Alright.
Whatever you say, boss.
Will I see you tomorrow?
Yeah. Yeah.
Cool.
How'd it go?
Oh. Like opening a vein.
You want to hear some good news?
God, yes.
My lawyer just called.
I got my kid back.
Shared custody. No conditions.
That's everything you wanted.
Nyla, congratulations!
You helped me get here, John.
Just... know that.
Thank you.
And thanks for telling me.
Uh... I needed some good news today.
Hey.
Don't beat yourself up.
You did everything you were supposed to.
I just wish Erin would have given us
something more concrete before she died,
because Serj is gonna
walk for Chris's murder.
... is dead because of me.
No, no, no! Wait, no! Don't!
It doesn't have to all be for nothing.
Okay, you can start to make this right.
Name names, okay? Just testify.
- Armstrong.
- No!
Armstrong.
She said his name before she saw him.
You did good, my friend.
Very good.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -