7-Adam-15, show us
Code 6 at Shaw Memorial.
What's going on?
A guy came into the ER intoxicated,
complaining of stomach pain.
He's clearly been shot
but insisting he's not.
Sir. I hear you're
having a little trouble.
Uh, no, just, um, ate some bad sushi.
- What's your name?
- Arnold.
Arnold what?
I-I don't have to tell you that.
Hey, why... why'd you call them?
Sir, she's required by law
to call us when a patient's been shot.
I told you, I ain't been shot.
Just too much gas station sushi.
Well, unless the wasabi
burned a hole straight
through your stomach,
I'm forced to assume you're lying to us.
So, how about you tell
us what really happened?
Um...
Uh...
He did it!
That's my husband. What... Excuse me.
What's going on? Why are you here?
Nolan! Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Aah! Hey! Careful, man.
I been shot!
You gonna run away again?
- No.
- You got him?
Aah!
Get him an IV antibiotic,
and add 5 milligrams of lorazepam.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, no, yeah, fine.
No, I just... I was...
I got, uh, distracted.
Oh, by what?
Simon, this is Nyla Harper
and... John Nolan.
Uh, nice to meet you, Officers.
You must spend a lot of time here.
Oh, he's here all the time.
Get... Got... Well, the criminals
and the injury... it's constant stuff.
Oh. W-Well, it's nice to meet you both.
Hey.
Dispatch said you got a gunshot victim.
Yeah, he belong to you?
Unfortunately, yeah.
Guy ate all the sushi
at a gas station on Melrose and Fairfax
and refused to pay.
Things got heated. The owner shot him.
Who's the dude close-talking with Grace?
That's her husband.
I thought she was divorced.
Not technically.
What?
- Nothing.
I forgot my deodorant again.
Here. Use mine.
Oh.
I do love a manly musk.
Just not on me.
You're gonna have to start
leaving some things here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What?
Nothing.
You know it's illegal to lie to a cop.
Last week,
I interviewed for my dream job and...
I got it.
Hey, hey! That's great!
It's in New York.
Oh.
Yeah.
Well, I s... I mean,
y-you have to take it.
Dream jobs only come around once.
Yeah, I know.
When do you start?
Next month.
They have cops in New York.
Yeah.
Do you know where you're gonna live?
Not yet.
Maybe you could, um,
help me target some
neighborhoods tonight.
Yeah.
Sure.
We're skipping roll call today.
Grey's got us on special assignment.
- Sounds cool and mysterious.
- Negative.
We will be escorting
some juvenile felons
through a Scared Straight
program at Cal Correctional.
Oh, and let me guess...
you'd rather be on the streets
- chasing real criminals.
- Yep.
I've been to these things before.
It's a lot of chaos and noise...
and the jury's still out
as to whether it actually
makes a difference.
Well, if it helps even one
kid, it's made a difference.
This is... I...
Meet me at the Sally Port.
Thank you.
Hey, you. How you doing?
Not great.
Oliver is in some trouble at school.
That's why Simon was here yesterday.
Sorry to hear that.
- ICU Nurse Adams to recovery.
- Thanks.
You know, and I'm sorry
that it was awkward meeting my ex.
You know, it just didn't feel
like the right time or place
to introduce you as my boyfriend.
- I understand.
- I knew you would.
Like I know you'll understand
that I need to reschedule
dinner tonight.
I think Simon and I have got
to get on the same page
about how to handle Oliver.
Over dinner?
I mean, it's the only
time he can get off work.
Yeah, right. Of... Of course, yeah.
And family comes first.
Um, I have to go right now,
but I will talk to you later.
You got a problem.
- Both of us?
- No, just you.
In the attempt to combat
the high cost of civil litigation,
the LAPD has adopted a pilot program
which uses an algorithm
to target officers who are
most likely to get sued.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
They hired a tech company
run by a supposed genius...
Elvis Grimaldi.
All due respect, why do we
care what this dude thinks?
Because he flagged you
as the most problematic
officer in this station,
and he's got the Chief's ear.
Come on, Sarge. I just
got the tap for detective.
I'll get passed over
if this guy dings me.
Which is why I got him to
agree to spend a day with you,
collect more data for his "algorithm".
So you are going to show him
you are a by-the-book cop
with love in her heart.
Take only the tame calls,
and give him the answers
he wants to hear.
You might just skate through this thing.
Alright, line up. Against the van.
Marco Leland... assault and battery.
Tyson Renner...
Hey, unh-unh.
Up. Off the van. Stand up straight.
Tyson Renner... vandalism.
Fletcher Perry... auto...
Auto theft. That turn you on, baby?
Nothing like getting hit on
by a 12-year-old delinquent
to get your day started.
Hey, yo, I'm 15.
Not better.
What about you? What's your story?
Okay, good talk.
Hector Duran, 17.
Spent three months in juvie
for theft and drug possession.
Okay. I'm Officer Nolan.
This is Detective Harper.
Together, we're gonna be
taking a little field trip
down to the California
Correctional Facility.
For those of you who
complete today's program,
the rest of your sentences
will be commuted.
But this is your last chance.
Get busted again, and
the prison we are going to
will become your new home.
Fine by me.
Really? You ever been there?
Hell yeah.
My brother's doing a bid up there.
Not something to be proud of.
Alright. Road trip time.
So, I made some calls.
This Grimaldi guy made a fortune
on a dating app that he sold to Google.
Claims his algorithm is so good
that it can predict compatibility
with a 90% success rate.
Bull.
Maybe. But rumor is Bieber
used it to land Hailey.
I don't know who those people are.
You the brain messing
with my livelihood?
Mr. Grimaldi, I am Officer West.
This is my training
officer, Officer Lopez.
Call me Elvis. Mr. Grimaldi are my dads.
You don't look as
dangerous as I anticipated.
And you don't look as smart.
Yeah, think I'm gonna go.
You, um... You'll lose out
on gathering more data
points for your algorithm,
and that'll delay exiting
the beta phase by weeks.
You understand about beta phases.
Yes, sir.
Officer Lopez taught me.
Okay, I'm back in. Data uber alles.
But, Officer Lopez, you should know
that negativity towards me
will only strengthen the core data draw
that landed you the top
spot on the naughty list.
I'll take that under advisement.
Excellent. Shall we?
Rachel told me about New York.
I'm happy for her.
What are you guys gonna do?
There's not much to do.
You know, it's... it's not
like it's a semester abroad.
It's permanent.
Long-distance relationships never work.
Thanks for coming.
Of course. What do you got?
Uh, Social Services has
been here a few times
on truancy calls.
Paul hasn't been to
school in the last month
due to an undefined illness,
and the mom recently started a GoFundMe
to cover the medical bills.
Right. You think she's running a scam?
Well, scams are your jurisdiction.
I'm just here to make
sure the kid's okay.
Hello, Ms. Mint?
Hi, I'm Rachel Hall
with the Department
of Child and Family Services.
Uh, is this about the truancy?
Yes. We just have a few
questions for you and your son.
Uh, I'm... I'm sorry.
It's not really a good
time. Paul's asleep.
I understand, but my job
is to make sure he's okay.
And I'm not leaving until I see him.
I-I...
Step aside, ma'am.
I have a radio interview in 20 minutes.
We'll be out of your way in 10.
Paul? Honey?
This is Rachel.
She needs to talk to you, okay?
Hi, Paul.
Have you been to the doctor?
He's been in and out of the hospital
for the last three months.
What's the diagnosis?
"Results inconclusive",
which is doctor for "We have no idea".
Pulse is racing.
Hey, Paul, can you squeeze my hand?
They released him like this?
No, he was better.
It's always the same.
He improves at the hospital,
but after a couple days
at home, he's back to this.
How am I supposed to send him to school?
He can't even sit up.
I understand.
We'll be out of your
hair in just a minute.
So, what do you think?
It's Munchausen by proxy?
She meets the criteria.
Attention-seeking, undiagnosable illness
that gets better when
he's under observation.
It's just so wrong
that a parent would poison
their own child for attention.
Alright, what do you want to do?
$80,742,000.
That how much you made
off your dating app?
Oh, God, no. I made 10 times that.
The $80 million is
how much the LAPD paid
in legal settlements this year.
That's up 3.25%,
which is why they hired me
to target officers like you.
You can't predict behavior with math.
It's literally what I do.
Policing is different.
- I disagree.
- Of course you do.
I find the whole subject fascinating.
Uh, love to pick your brain.
If you're such an expert
on human behavior,
tell me how today's going to go.
Easy. We're gonna drive
around for a few hours,
taking only the tamest calls in town
while your partner attempts
to smooth over your rough edges
and convince me that, deep down,
you really are a sweetheart.
Wrong.
Today, I attached us
to a high-risk warrant
service in Highland Park.
Got you a bulletproof
vest in extra small.
Only way to show you I'm a good cop
is to show you I'm a good cop.
Why does motor pool always
give us vehicles with no gas?
Payback.
Before you were my T.O.,
I had an unintentional propensity
for crashing police cars.
Who needs the restroom?
Come on.
Alright, you guys. Who
wants some snacks? My treat.
Yeah. Beer?
That's a no. Hector?
Another no. Here, guys.
Grab whatever you need.
You two, over there. Now!
You, over here.
What are you doing?
I'm buying them snacks.
But you're about to tell
me I'm being too nice?
They're not Boy Scouts.
They're criminals.
I know you like to think I'm naive
because I tend to see
the good in people,
but that's just laziness on your part.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
And I think you'd be surprised
to see the difference it makes
when you show kids a
little bit of respect.
You were saying?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa! Hector, let him go.
Nah, I'm not adding time to my sentence
because this fool decided
to boost his street cred
by stealing a police ride.
- No!
- Relax. You did good.
Let him go.
Easy. Fletcher! Hey, hey, hey!
Knock it off. Come on, Fletcher.
- What?
- Hands against the side of the car.
Let's go.
You dummy.
Wasn't very smart.
Now you're going back to juvie.
It was worth it.
- Everything Code 4?
- Yeah.
Hector here stepped up
and did the right thing.
- I didn't do it for you.
- Doesn't matter, Hector.
The right thing is the right thing.
- Is he for real?
- Yep.
Control, 7-Adam-15 requesting
juvenile transportation.
Think there's any chance
Tim would come to New York?
I don't know.
I mean, he's L.A. pride born and bred,
but he is crazy about you, so...
You have no clue.
The man's a mystery.
What are they doing here?
They're here to take
Paul back to the hospital.
So the doctors can shrug
and say "Sorry, ma'am"
to the tune of $10,000 a day?
I'm afraid this is not a discussion.
To hell it's not. I am his mother.
Look, I believe you are
a danger to your child.
Therefore, I'm removing
him from your care,
pending a full investigation.
No, you can't do that!
- Ma'am, ma'am.
- You can't do that! No!
- Ma'am, come over here, please.
- You can't do that.
No, please. What are you doing?
I just want to put it out there
that you're completely disobeying
a direct order from the Watch Commander.
Grey just wants me to play nice,
but how I act isn't going to matter
to a geek who only looks at numbers.
I need to convince him that there's data
that he's not factoring
into his algorithm.
And if he gets caught in the crossfire?
Problem solved.
Do exactly as I and the other
officers say at all times.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Morning. Who's this?
Uh, Elvis.
I run a risk evaluation
program for the LAPD.
Huh. Well, you in the right place.
Serving a warrant on the Jacobs Brothers
is like playing chicken
with a runaway train.
That's on fire.
And filled with zombies.
Steagald warrant?
Even better... "no knock".
That's why Detective
Armstrong's my favorite.
- Nick Armstrong?
- Yeah. Why?
My algorithm has you pinpointed
as the highest-performing
detective in the station.
An exemplary officer.
"Exemplary".
Let's catch some bad guys.
Get on your knees! Hands up!
LAPD! On the ground now!
- On your knees!
- Now! Hands on your head!
Hands behind your back now!
This ain't right! You surprised us!
- Code 4. Suspects in custody.
- Sit down.
Want to hear some real
predictive analysis, Elvis?
Ok... Yeah, okay.
The suspect has begun to
show pre-assault indicators.
Hey, nobody told you to stand up.
Sit your ass back down. Now.
Bladed stance. Rocking and bobbing.
It means adrenaline
and oxygen are pumping.
So you watch his eyes.
Once they lock, it's go time.
- Aah!
- Hyah!
And that is why Officer
Lopez is my favorite.
Get up, dummy.
And that was a completely
justified use of force,
by the way.
The law says she doesn't have to wait
for the suspect to
attack to defend herself.
Okay. Uh, tell me more about that.
It's natural to feel nervous.
This ain't nothing.
Welcome to Cal Correctional, Officers.
Please hand over your duty
belts and backup pieces.
They'll be secured in a locker here.
Thought you were bringing
me four young men.
Uh, one of them flamed
out before we got here.
Sounds like I'll be meeting
him soon enough.
You three, face the fence.
You are now in my custody.
You will obey every order I give,
or I will put hands on you
and I will make you obey.
You ball up your fist, I'll take
that as a sign of aggression
and I will put you on the
ground and I will handcuff you.
Is that clear?
Is that clear?!
Yes, sir.
Let's move.
Detective Harper, Officer Nolan.
I'm Warden Miller.
Have you been through
this program before?
I haven't, no.
Well, it can be intense.
Do you have children of your own?
I have a son who's 19.
Then this is gonna be hard to watch.
Take a seat.
Are you deaf?
- I gave you an order.
- Man, get off of me.
I told you... you don't
listen, I make you listen.
Now sit your ass down.
Okay, bring 'em in.
Hey! I know you.
You've got to be kidding me.
You know Oscar?
I apprehended him twice during
multiple escape attempts.
On one of those attempts,
he stabbed my friend.
I can't imagine he has anything
useful to say to these kids.
Yeah, well, he's not here
to say anything useful.
He's here because he's the monster
that they'll be locked up with.
And Mr. Caine here
joined us 11 years ago,
after he was convicted
of a double homicide.
Oh, come on, Warden.
Give him some credit.
Caine tore the arm off of a guy
that he caught his wife
cheating on him with.
He beat them both to death with it.
Not sure it's a good idea
to remind him of that.
No, but it sure is fun.
Mm.
Yeah.
I know what you're thinking...
you're better than me, right?
Yeah, 'cause you on the outside,
'cause you got options.
You just roll your eyes at me?
What you got, a death wish?
You think these guards gonna save you?
I'm in here 40 years.
You think I'm scared of
a few weeks in the hole,
five more on my sentence?
Step back, Caine.
Now.
Caine's passionate.
He's got what
psychological professionals
would describe as "anger issues".
Say something wrong to him,
he'll turn your bones to dust.
But deep down, the real reason
that he's here with you
is because he wishes that someone
had diverted him from this place.
Not me.
I'm here because
it got me out of my cell.
Plus, it gives me a
glimpse of future prey.
I want you guys to end up here.
I'm gonna be behind bars until I'm 90...
long as I don't get caught
blinding another inmate.
Which I will never do again, ma'am.
I have learned my lesson.
Don't talk to me, Oscar. Talk to them.
Yes, ma'am.
So, you're the future
inmates of America.
Trust me, stay on this path, do that,
so you can end up in here with me.
How many criminals get away
with their crimes, Officer Nolan?
- Not many.
- Why is that?
Because they're dumb.
Oh, I'm not dumb.
No, but you lack impulse control.
Yes!
I do!
What's your name?
Hector.
Do you think that you're
a tough guy, Hector?
- I know I am.
- You're not.
Uh, maybe you are.
Doesn't really matter.
There's always gonna be
somebody tougher than you,
somebody willing to
do what you won't do.
Do you know that tough guys
get shanked to death in here every day?
Not me, though.
'Cause I'm not a tough guy.
I'm a cockroach.
I'll do whatever it takes
to come out on top.
This is not how to reach Hector.
It is not your job
to tell her how to do hers.
It's okay, Detective.
I'm willing to listen.
Hector's brother, Thomas,
is incarcerated here.
So you think that a family
reunion is more effective?
I read both their files.
Hector was a model citizen
before his brother got arrested.
He idolized him.
But he hasn't visited in almost a year
because Thomas refuses to see him.
Maybe it's time for Hector
to see how far his brother has fallen.
Hey, you got a minute?
Oh, yeah, of course.
I just spoke to Paul's doctors.
Tox labs came back clean.
They ran every commonly
available poison... nothing.
Wait, so how is his mom making him sick?
I don't know, but this
whole thing is not adding up.
Hmm.
I'm gonna reach out to a co-worker
who had a case on the same block.
Maybe she heard something.
- That's great. Keep me posted?
- Will do.
Down. Up.
Don't... Don't you dare stop.
Give it a rest, Caine.
Boy's with me.
Get up.
On your feet, on your feet!
Let's go!
Thomas?
You on the phone every week,
telling me how great you're doing,
and this is how I see you?
Hector's been getting into
a lot of trouble lately.
Spent the last few months
in juvie for theft and drugs.
He wants to follow in his
big brother's footsteps.
Why the hell you want to do that?
Because he doesn't know any better.
He thinks you're a role model.
Hey, don't talk to him like that.
No, lady cop's right.
I'm no one to be proud of.
How can you say that?
You run things in here.
People respect you.
No, they're afraid of me.
That ain't the same thing.
When you're in here, you can't
afford to be a human being.
And once you lose that,
you can never get it back.
Don't be me.
What's that?
Just a little bit of trouble.
It's a daily occurrence around here,
but I do need to go see to it.
Sharp, put the three of
them on a short leash.
Warden's lying.
Two short bursts mean
there's a riot going on.
About to get crazy up in here.
Sir, do you have a second?
Sure. What's up?
Hypothetically,
what's involved in a lateral move?
Well, I hate to lose you,
but the truth is,
it'd be pretty seamless.
What about NYPD?
That's a whole other beast.
You would have to go
to the NYPD Academy,
complete the FTO program
before you'd even be
allowed back on the streets.
You would basically be
starting from square one.
In fact
you would be the John Nolan of the NYPD.
No, you see that's not funny.
That's hilarious.
It'd be a big sacrifice.
But if Rachel's the
one, it'd be worth it.
Who said this was about Rachel?
Just be sure.
Moving in together is tough enough.
Plus new jobs, new city, no
social network to lean on...
You don't want to end
up resenting each other.
Thanks.
Anytime, "Boot".
Why'd he call you "Boot"?
Nothing. Inside joke.
Hey. What's up?
My co-worker heard that a few other kids
in the neighborhood got sick recently.
Turns out, the city started maintenance
on the main water line four months ago,
so they switched to well water.
And Paul got sick three months ago.
Five years ago, Seaver
Chemical was accused
of dumping heavy metals
from their refinery.
They paid a small fine and
got a high-priced consultant
to certify that the environmental
impact was negligible.
Well, clearly, that
might not be the case.
Yes, but that does not help Iris.
I got her son taken away from her,
and reversing that is not gonna be easy.
Can't you just tell the
judge you made a mistake?
Not without definitive proof.
Iris could lose her son
all because I pulled
the trigger too quickly.
It's okay.
Better hope that the
Warden squashes this riot.
Cops and kids are about the best
hostages inmates could dream of.
Oscar, shut up.
Shouldn't you take these
guys back to their cells?
I mean, Harper and I can guard the kids.
I don't make a move without orders.
I'm guessing three bursts
is worse than two?
It's just a call to prayer.
As in... pray they kill you quick.
Wait. So, uh, you called them
"pre-assault indicators", right?
- Right.
- I got a question.
Did you use your dating algorithm
as a base for the LAPD one?
'Course not.
That's a yes.
Hold on just a second. Sally.
- Elvis, Elvis, where are you?
- Wh...
- He's got a gun.
- Wait, wait, wait. C-Calm down, calm down.
- What's going on?
- One of our clients, I think.
- Uh, who?
- What's happening?
- He's got a gun. He said it's our fault.
- Uh, uh, one of our clients
blames us for his breakup, and
he just showed up with a gun.
Oh, my God. Help!
Uh, wait, Sally, are you still there?
- Sally?
- 7-Adam-07.
7-Adam-07.
We're on scene and have
a possible active shooter
at 2100 Knoll Road. Shots fired.
Wait here behind our car.
When officers arrive, show
them what door we went in
and do exactly as they tell you.
7-Adam-07. We're making entry
now through the north door.
Repeat, two officers
making entry, north door.
All responding units, Code 3.
- Copy. 7-Adam-07 making entry on an active shooter.
- You're not waiting for backup?
Not on an active shooter. We go in.
But you don't. No matter
what you see or hear,
you stay outside, stay behind cover!
If you follow us in, the
coroner can carry you out.
Understand?
- Help us! He's got a gun!
- Go! Go!
How many shooters? How many shooters?
How many shooters? Go!
- Go!
- Go, go!
Go! Get out!
- Go, go, go!
- Get out! Go, go!
- Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go, go, go!
7-Adam-07, units are landing.
Can you give us an update?
7-Adam-07, security check.
7-Adam-100, be advised
7-Adam-07 not responding.
We have more...
Shh.
Oh!
Get on your stomach!
Control, 7-Adam-07. Shooter in custody.
Code 4 in the Bullpen.
Copy, shooter in custody. Code 4.
Hey. How bad is it out there?
Several casualties.
Mostly inmates, one guard.
60% of the prison is
under inmate control,
which means you've got to go.
Lock them in cells in B Wing
and then fold in with the CERT team.
C.O. Sharp is going to
escort you and the kids
to the nearest exit.
At this moment, the coast is clear.
Be safe.
Officers, take care of my brother.
I won't let anything happen to him.
You have my word.
You listen to this man.
Do what he says.
And stay the hell away from here.
You're better than me. Act like it.
Okay, let's go.
See you later, John.
Alright. Time to move.
Not yet. We need weapons.
In case the way is not clear.
Come on, boys.
You never wanted to smash
up a classroom before?
Now's your chance.
Hey. Are you scared?
You want the truth?
No.
I'm not scared at all.
- Right.
- Let's go.
Is there a way out of here that
doesn't go through a cell block?
No.
I knew he was gonna say that.
Let's go, boys. Thank you.
Come on.
Alright, well, we're gonna
get a paramedic to look at you.
Six victims. So far, no fatalities.
Oh, th... thank God.
I never saw this coming.
Why did I not see this coming?
Because you trusted the
data, but people lie.
No guy is gonna reveal a
history of domestic violence
in his dating profile.
But I thought that I-I
had factored in firewalls
for erroneous data.
Not enough.
He's dead.
Just keep walking.
Keep moving, boys. Come on.
Let's go.
Keep walking. Come on, boys.
Hector. Hey, Hector.
No!
Just...
Hey, J.J., I got those
Scared Straight kids.
Hell yeah. On our way.
You don't have to do this, you guys.
Yeah, we do.
Then we're done talking.
Boys, get behind us.
Nolan! We got to go!
- Move! Move!
- Go! Go!
Get up, get up, get up!
- It's locked.
- Keys.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hey. Have you heard from Rachel?
No. Why?
She blames herself
for yanking Iris's son
before the tests were run.
Look, I've been calling, texting.
She's not getting back to me.
What do you think, she's
gonna do something stupid?
You know her better than
I do. What do you think?
Listen up. We got ourselves a VIP.
Get your hands off me!
- That's the Warden.
- You try and take the prison back,
we'll rip her to pieces.
A list of demands will be forthwith.
Until then, have a great day.
Any chance that CERT team is nearby?
No, they're clear on the
other side of the prison.
There's no way they'll
get to her in time.
But we can.
Why? You don't owe her nothing.
'Cause it's the right thing to do.
You remember that.
You practiced it back
at the gas station.
Why does everything have to be
a teachable moment with you?
Because he knows it's annoying.
8977.
You ready?
Yeah.
Why're we going this way?
The Warden's in the opposite direction.
I know, but we need a little help.
From who?
Hey, guys.
Why aren't you out there running
wild, like the rest of them?
I was, then I got tired.
All I really wanted to do
was beat the hell out of
this one guy, Kevin Medved.
And did you?
No, somebody beat me to it.
I know, right? Just my luck.
But I did get to laugh in
his face, which was nice.
I'm surprised to see
you two in one piece.
Where's the kids?
Did you trade them for safe passage?
No, we got them out.
And then you came back.
For the Warden.
Mm. Why you coming to me?
'Cause you're gonna help us get her out.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
If I've learned anything about
you these last few months,
it's that you are the
ultimate opportunist.
You find yourself in a situation
where there's a chance to
escape, you try to escape.
But there's no escaping today,
which is why you're
still here in your cell.
So I'm here to offer
you the next best thing.
To escape? There is no such thing.
Sure there is. Privileges.
You help us rescue the Warden,
you can ask for anything.
You help us, we help you.
Are you in, or are you out?
Have a seat on the bench.
Whoa. What's going on?
She assaulted some corporate
guy outside his office.
I did not. I threw water in his face.
Contaminated water?
No.
But he thought it was.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Let me take her off
your hands, cite her out.
She's all yours.
Thanks.
What the hell were you thinking?
He didn't even
care... that kids are sick.
And he's got kids of his own.
And you were surprised by that?
What do I do now?
How do I make everything right?
I don't know that you can.
But I've... I've called in some favors,
and I got the Deputy
Chief to call the judge.
And based on my personal assurances,
he's reversing the order
removing Paul from his home.
You... You did that for me?
Even though I'm leaving?
Duh.
Tim, I...
I know, I know.
Look, do... do you want to cry about it,
or do you want to go get Iris
and... and bring her to her son?
Both.
Yeah, I can work with that.
Hey. Don't screw us.
Relax.
Hey, guys.
Oscar, get your crazy ass out of here
before I slice you open.
Okay. I guess I'll, uh, trade
these two cops I caught
to the Mexicans.
You got those cops?
Where?
Just outside here. I tied 'em up.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Hi. We'll get you out of here now.
Thank goodness.
What the hell is he doing here with you?
Saving you.
And my services don't come cheap.
We're gonna start the bidding
with a plasma television screen,
followed by biweekly conjugal visits.
We told him you'd make a deal.
I will not.
Then I'll see you later.
Fine.
- Fine.
- Let's go.
Get behind me.
Thank the good Lord.
I just found these two
trying to steal the
Warden from you guys.
Where's Hector?
We got him out.
For real?
For real.
Back off, Thomas.
This ain't got nothing to do with you.
They walk.
Like hell they do.
Thank you.
So I'm gonna make sure these
guys find their way out.
Sit here. I'll change, and
then I'll take you to juvie
to process out with
the rest of the boys.
Cool. Thanks.
Paperwork can wait till tomorrow.
I hear that.
- See you in a minute.
- See you.
Hey, trouble kind of
finds you, doesn't it?
They told us to scare the kids.
We scared those kids.
How are things going with Grace?
Ah, I'm not sure.
She's having dinner
with her ex as we speak.
That a problem?
I don't know. I guess that's up to her.
She knows how I feel.
And how do you feel?
I'm a little in love with her.
You tell her that?
Well, I...
implied it, you know, with my actions.
- It's not the same, is it?
- Nope.
Okay, so, you guys want
to hear something funny?
- It's not that funny.
- No, it definitely is.
- Just not to you.
- I'm losing interest.
Okay, so, Elvis's algorithm
flagged Lopez
- as being most likely to get sued, right?
- Okay?
- He got the wrong Lopez.
- What?
He mixed up two lines
on his spreadsheet,
confused me with another A. Lopez.
Albert Lopez from Property Crimes?
No, Angelo Lopez in Vice.
Oh, in Vice.
Funny, right?
Hey. Harper will be
out in just a minute.
Can I get you some food
for the road or something?
No, I'm... I'm good.
Tell me, have I earned the right
to give you a little advice?
Another teachable moment? Really?
Only if you'd care to hear it.
Fair enough. Hit me.
Alright.
It's okay to put yourself
second once in a while.
Those men today at the prison,
they all had one thing in common...
they were selfish.
They put their own petty,
reckless needs above all else.
When my dad abandoned us, I acted out.
I got into fights. I...
I made bad choices.
And I drove my mom crazy with worry,
and I didn't like how that felt.
She needed me to be better.
So that's what I did.
You make it sound so easy.
It's really not easy,
but it was worth it.
You ready?
Uh, yeah.
Thanks.
Anytime.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I hope that it's okay
that I just came by.
Yeah, of course, of course.
You're... You finished
your dinner with, uh...
- Simon.
Yeah.
- Been an interesting day.
- It certainly has.
Yeah.
- I need to tell you something.
I need to go first.
Okay.
The reason that Oliver has
been having trouble at school
is because of the divorce.
The separation.
Right.
Simon...
He wants to give it another try.
For Oliver.
What do you want?
I don't know.
You and I have such a great thing.
But if getting back together with Simon
is the best thing for Oliver,
how can I dismiss that?
I just need to take some time.
I'm so sorry.