Previously, on 'The Rookie'.
- No sign of infection.
- Infection?
You're murder-victim is part
of a homegrown terrorist cell.
What type of Virus are we talking about?
A weaponized strain
of hemorrhagic fever.
- It's gonna be okay.
- I'm not going out
the way my man Pete here just did.
- I'm coming out.
- Show me those hands!
Don't shoot.
- What the hell?
- He was reaching.
I don't think he was
reaching for a weapon.
So either she doesn't trust me
or she's a liar.
He's back.
Tim!
7-Adam-15 escorting
CDC ambulance to Shaw Memorial.
Heading east on South Grand.
I need a clear path.
Copy that, 7-Adam-15.
CHP is en route to assist.
- Tim better make it.
- He will.
Is it the virus?
There's no bleeding, looks like
he's having a severe reaction
to the shot we gave him.
He's going into anaphylactic shock.
Get me epinephrine!
So, the CDC finally gave the all-clear
to search Jimmy Roskin's body.
We found a burner phone.
I'm not gonna like where
this is going, am I?
He made a call before
I shot him, to another burner.
You think there's a third
terrorist out there?
And we just killed his friends.
Hey! Can we get some help
over here, please?
Right now!
Gun!
7-Adam-15! Shots fired! Shaw Memorial!
Flanking right!
- Covering!
- Moving!
Covering!
Right behind you, right behind you.
Right behind you.
Suspect in custody!
Doctor!
I need some help over here!
I got it!
Are you okay?
I should've... reloaded on the move.
You?
I should've taken yesterday off.
When you said date night,
I thought you meant wine and romance.
Oh, there's wine,
and there's the romance.
I have processed crime scenes
that felt more romantic.
What? Come on. That's...
- Well, that's accurate.
- Okay, look,
I... your new place,
it's gonna be great when you're done,
and, uh, you definitely...
- you seem happy working on it.
- Right?
I haven't felt
this much like me since...
well, since I loaded up a U-Haul,
drove across the country,
and became a cop.
And, uh, tomorrow,
you are back at work being a cop.
Administrative leave is over.
Yeah, you didn't take one, though.
No. No, no, no. No, DHS is different.
With a clean shoot,
it's just right back at work.
Are you sure you're ready
to hit the streets?
Yes! Yes. I just...
well, it's not gonna be
quite the same without Talia.
Taking that job over at ATF was smart.
You know, she was never gonna have
the career that she wanted
over at the LAPD, I mean...
- not after she lied about her brother.
- Yeah.
At least she waited until
after I took the exam.
And if I passed,
six more months of training,
I'm no longer the oldest rookie.
Well, you will always be
the oldest rookie to me.
- Oh.
- Mm.
- Wait, what?
- Okay, yeah. I'm gonna go.
- Jess?
- Yeah?
Did it bother you at all?
Shooting Roskin like that?
Sure.
H-Have you been wondering this
for the last two weeks?
Well, you just never said anything,
and then I didn't...
see anything, so I...
Right. Um...
The truth is...
things like that
affect you a lot less...
the longer that you're on the job.
It's just human nature.
Mnh.
Mm.
Morning.
Oh, hey.
Sorry, um... I can't find my shirt.
You want me to help?
Nope. I have a system.
Uh-huh.
Don't say anything.
I wasn't going to.
- Ooh! Found it!
- Mm.
Ha-ha!
Huh.
What?
Nothing. Just...
it's a little messier...
since I moved in.
Uh, we were dating before,
so I spent two hours cleaning up
every time you came over.
Now you're moved in,
so you get to see the real me.
Is that a problem?
No, I wouldn't want it any other way.
Uh... when did you make
a grilled cheese?
Uh... last night after my shift.
You were sleeping.
Mmm! Mmm.
How are you feeling?
Ready to get back to it.
Did you get the food I sent over?
I did.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- Well, I wanted to,
and eating well is crucial
for a fast recovery.
Alright.
Shake off the rust and grab a seat.
Anyone want to guess
what these numbers represent?
Nolan.
Those are the scores
to our six-month exams.
That is correct, Officer Nolan.
Oh! We all passed.
Technically, yes, but that 81 is ugly,
given that an 80 is basically an F.
- Who got the low mark?
- Clearly not West.
I could tell you,
but self-reflection is necessary
for your success as a patrol officer.
So I want your guesses,
as to which score is
yours by end of shift.
Understood?
Why not give them now?
To mess with our heads.
Are you saying you're so
easily sabotaged, Officer Nolan?
No, sir, I was speaking
for Officer Chen.
Sir, will there be consequences
for the officer with the low score?
Officer Lopez, you want to take that?
At a minimum, a low score means
merciless taunting for months.
- Great.
- But you three did pass,
so there's good news...
you can now wear short sleeves.
Congratulations.
Nolan.
Sir, who will I be riding with today?
I was thinking...
me.
How's that sound?
Alright.
I know I did better
than an 81, didn't I?
- Yeah, the oral exam is the X-Factor.
- He's right.
Chief Williams could ding us
on the tiniest of mistakes,
which I'm sure he did with me,
and Grey knows that,
so he's gonna spend the day
torturing me.
Or he knows you pulled the high score
and plans to torture you anyway.
You're lucky you don't have to worry.
Who says I'm not worried?
You look worried.
I have never had a rookie score
that low on the exam.
- There's a first time for everything.
- No.
Officer Chen is
a naturalborn test-taker.
Nolan didn't even finish college.
Plus, Chen had me for her T.O.
- Nolan had Bishop.
- Really?
You're gonna smack-talk her when
she's not here to defend herself.
You're right. It's not the same.
Even if she was here, you'd still
be fighting for second place.
- What are you doing?
- What?
My rookies wear long sleeves and ties
until the last day of probation.
Yeah, but Sergeant Grey said...
Grey is not your training officer.
I have complete discretion
of the training of my boot,
and that includes uniform.
Okay? So go change back
into your long sleeves.
And don't forget the tie.
Now, Boot.
- Where you going?
- To change back.
Can I ask you a personal question?
If you think it's wise.
Do things bother you less now?
No, you're just as annoying
as you were before.
Very funny. I mean the job.
My first six months have been...
a lot to process.
It's like a raw nerve.
"All the feelings,"
as my son's fond of saying.
Does that... get easier?
Look, a cop has a decision
to make in the first few years.
"How much can I handle?"
How much I'm gonna
let the job affect me.
"If I had an input control,
where would I set it to?"
Some cops set it to 7.
They take a lot in.
Some... set it to 3.
Hell, some set it to zero.
Anybody keep it at 10?
Can't be done.
Let me see your hand.
You've been demoing your house
for about a week,
and you already got calluses growing.
Your body does that to protect itself.
Your mind does the same thing,
whether you want it to or not.
7-Adam-15,
507 at Sunset Plaza, Code 2.
7-Adam-15, copy.
Look, I'm with Wesley on this.
The shower is definitely
a beverage-only zone,
and a soap dish is not a plate.
- Says who?
- Common decency, actually.
- Give me a break.
- He's right.
I live under an overpass,
and even I think it's gross.
Hey, nobody asked you.
Stop pouting.
I'm not pouting.
What are we doing here?
You thought it was gonna get
easier after you passed the exam,
- but you were wrong.
- Awesome.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
If recent events
have taught us anything,
it's that we need to remain
ever-vigilant.
You probably think you know
everything about policing,
but you don't, for example...
what's the most important thing
you need on the street?
Is this a trick question?
Okay, well, the easy answer is my gun,
but I know that's not right.
So, um... my mind?
No. That's too esoteric for you.
Are you through
not answering my question?
Uh, my judgment?
Yeah, my judgment.
Your eyes.
"Cop eyes" stop crime and save lives.
Did you study explosive devices
in the Academy?
What? Yeah.
- I mean, a little.
- Good.
I hope you paid attention
because I had a buddy
from the bomb squad mock up an IED
and hide it somewhere
here in this park.
What?
You got 10 minutes to find it,
or I'm adding the duty hat
to your standard uniform.
- Go.
- I...
Go!
10 seconds.
Alright, alright.
What's the problem here?
The problem is this guy
trying to sell me
a colon-cleaning start-up
while I'm eating lamb chops.
Look, Colon Glow is patent-pending.
"Make it sublime
where the sun don't shine."
You can get in on
the ground floor for only $100K.
- You get this sort of thing a lot?
- You have no idea.
Sir, sir, sir, sir.
I admire your passion,
but you need to leave Mr. Cuban alone.
We get another complaint,
we're gonna book you
for public nuisance, okay?
Yeah.
- Mr. Cuban, sorry.
- Yep.
- Nolan, let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Actually, when I was in construction,
I invented my own...
it's sort of a fastbinder,
but the difference is, the heat sink...
You know what? Never mind.
You have a nice day.
I found it.
I found...
And... you're dead.
Because radio frequency energy
can trigger a bomb.
You gonna forget that lesson, Boot?
- No.
- Good.
Go get cleaned up.
You're supposed to carry an extra
uniform shirt in your war bag.
Oh, yes, sir. I didn't expect
to be in short sleeves yet.
This is the only one I own.
Hey.
I ordered a new set of
dress blues last week.
See if they're in?
Uh, yeah. I can go look in back.
Frank, um...
usually checks the computer.
Is he around?
- No.
- Oh.
- Everything good?
- Yeah, it's great.
How long you been working here?
Couple weeks.
- What's your name?
- Uh, Justin.
Justin what?
He's headed for the alley.
I'll cut him off.
7-Adam-15, 211 at Top Cop Uniforms.
Three suspects escaping on motorcycles
heading north, south, and east.
Send backup and airship.
What'd they steal?
Police uniforms.
- How many uniforms did they take?
- About 20.
That's a lot of potential fake cops,
which is why you called
Homeland Security.
I called you as a courtesy.
In most cases, stolen uniforms
are used for drug rips.
Well, that's a lot of risk
just to rob a few drug dealers,
which is why we're going
to be treating this
as a potential high-threat-level event.
- Like in '09 with the bus?
- Oh, God, here we go.
Jess' first year
with the FBI-LAPD Taskforce,
she convinced us that a missing
school bus was a prelude
- to a terror attack.
- Okay.
- And it wasn't?
- A third-grader
didn't want to take a
test, so he stole the bus,
so he wouldn't have to go to school.
- I mean...
- She had half the LAPD
hunting a 9-year-old.
Hey, overtime paid
for my Disney World vacation.
- I'm not complaining.
- Okay, you know what?
You picked the one time
- that I was wrong.
- The one time?
- Was there body-cam footage
of the man inside the store?
No. The cams weren't on.
I will put him with an artist.
We will send you a sketch.
- How about that?
- Great.
Look, I hope you're right
about this being small-time,
but... I don't think it is.
Will you walk me out?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Uh, is everything okay?
Yeah. Why?
Well, you know, I mean,
it's your first day back,
- already chasing bad guys.
- Yes, well, chasing, not catching.
Much like your 9-year-old.
Oh, I caught him.
He will not fool me again.
I'm sorry, you're still
keeping tabs on him?
Uh, Benjamin Smith
is a sophomore at USC,
and if he ever steps
back over the line,
I'll be there.
Wow.
You terrify me.
Missed a spot.
What?
Thank God. My wife's missing.
She never came home from work
last night.
She always comes home.
I texted and called her friends,
and nobody's...
Okay, sir, can you please slow down?
It's important I get the report
right for the detectives.
- What's your wife's name?
- Susanna... Brown.
She's a clerk
at the courthouse downtown.
We're trying to have a baby,
and she was supposed
to come straight home to...
- you... you know.
- Yes, sir.
Do you have a picture?
Uh... y-yeah.
No, hard copy's preferable.
Of course.
Hold on.
Poor guy.
Really?
- What?
- Cop eyes.
What? You... You think
the husband did something?
You always assume the
husband did something.
Officer Bradford's
first rule of domestics?
This isn't a joke, Boot.
You don't have the experience
to evaluate people yet,
so your default should be
suspicion, not compassion.
Understood?
Yeah.
Have I told you how sexy
you look in that uniform?
No, most of your compliments
come after I take it off.
- Oh.
- What?
Nothing, just a little, uh...
Really?
You couldn't just be in the moment?
You had to point that out?
What? You just had
a little something on your shirt.
I just...
- Hey. Ready to roll?
- Yeah.
- I'll see you at home tonight.
- Can't wait.
Hey, is everything alright?
Fine.
I thought living together
would be more fun.
Officer West.
Be in the shop.
You were in the cadet program
in high school, right?
Yes, sir.
Cadet leader all four years,
- and in college, too.
- Good.
They're sending a group over
tomorrow morning.
- I want you to talk to them.
- Yes, sir.
Happy to do it.
Very thin lips,
uh, a-and two gold teeth, right here.
Gold teeth. Gotcha.
This is so cool. I've never actually
sat with a sketch artist before.
Yeah, my first time, too.
I just got hired.
Congrats.
Okay, that should do it.
What do you think?
You drew me.
What?
No. I drew what you told me.
Yeah, except... you... didn't.
May I? If... If you just...
Yeah, so, I said he had...
Yeah. This hair will drop down
a little more,
and I said he had deep-set eyes, right?
Very thin lips.
There.
Yeah. I used to draw a lot
for my old job.
Got to go.
They found the bikes.
Great work.
Oh, yeah, that's...
those are definitely the
motorcycles from the robbery.
We're not gonna get any
forensics off them now, though.
There's a body.
- How can you tell?
- The smell.
A burning body's unmistakable.
Oh.
That's him. I see the teeth.
That's definitely the guy
from the uniform store.
Not on the crime scene! Go! Go!
7-Adam-15, change our call
to a homicide.
Send detectives and a forensics team.
And alert Jessica Russo at DHS.
So, they must have met up here
after they got away, but...
then his crew killed him?
Why?
Because we saw him.
Stay here.
How's it going?
- He threw up.
- I...
- Oh.
- ...couldn't help it.
It was the worst thing I've ever seen.
- And smelled.
- Yeah, well, no one can blame you.
Uh, actually...
- What?
- Never mind.
You know, a low score on the test,
and now I puke in front of Grey?
I'm gonna get bounced
before the end of shift.
Don't be so sure about that low score.
Tim spent the entire day making me
feel like I don't know anything.
Hey.
I heard you got him.
Yeah, he puked.
Stop telling people that.
It happens.
To you?
I'm gonna go talk to Grey.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
And my mortification is complete.
Still think they stole the
uniforms to rob drug dealers?
Let's skip
the "I told you so" s, please.
What does your intel say?
Print from the store got
a positive ID on our corpse.
Trevor Travis, 28.
Spent 18 months in Nevada State Prison
for armed robbery.
- Known associates?
- Too many to name,
but none in Southern California.
Well, whoever his new crew is,
they're ruthless enough
to kill one of their own
to stop our investigation.
And whatever they're planning,
no one's gonna see it coming
because they're all dressed as cops.
Hell, they could be
working the scene right now.
So, we'll implement new
identity verification protocols.
I'll call my guys,
have them start
an interagency task force.
We've got to get out in front of this.
- We need to get in on this.
- Not gonna happen.
We're stuck on perimeter duty
until end of shift,
away from the action.
Trust me, this is exactly
where you want to be.
Um, what are you doing?
Clocking out and heading home.
- "Rio Bravo's" on cable.
- No, no.
Why are you treating me like
it's day 1 all over again?
Because it is. Today was day 1
of stage 2 of your training.
So, what? Does that mean
I've lost all the respect
that I've earned?
You lost that
when you lied on a report.
- What?
- I read your account
of what happened
at the quarantine house.
O-Okay?
When I thought I was infected,
I told you I'd rather
take my life than bleed out.
- You failed to report it.
- That's what this is about?
Suicide ideations by a law enforcement
officer are extremely serious
and should have been
reported immediately.
I was trying to protect you.
They would have put you
on leave, required therapy.
- You weren't even actually suicidal.
- Not your call!
You should have detailed everything,
regardless of the consequences.
Oh, yeah?
Like I should have filed a report
detailing everything you've done
to protect Isabel?
You know what?
You wanna rake me over the coals
for the next six months,
you go ahead.
But don't pretend like it's
because you've got some code.
Hey.
This is gonna sound weird,
but if you see any cops
at the courthouse,
check their credentials, okay?
Yeah, they sent an e-mail around.
- What's going on?
- Eh, I can't really say.
What's the timer for?
Well, I wanted to discuss something,
and I figured this would be
a controlled way to do it.
We're gonna fight using a timer?
Basically.
Okay.
I spent an hour looking for
the remote when I got home.
- Found it under the bed.
- So?
So the TV's in the living room.
Look, I've been here a week
and I have found
coffee cups, bras, PopTarts
inside of, on top of, and underneath
almost every surface in this house.
Now, I'm super-glad that you feel
comfortable enough with me
to be yourself, but I...
- I also...
- You'd rather I was someone else?
No. Not at all.
I just think that it's important
to set ground rules.
- Ground rules?
- Uh, use the timer.
You think I'm a slob.
- No.
- 'Cause I'm not a slob.
I work my ass off in an
incredibly controlled environment,
and when I get home,
I just want to relax.
You might be anal-retentive
and fold your underwear
in a triangle...
which is weird, by the way...
but that's not me.
Folding your underwear is not weird,
and an orderly space helps me relax.
There's enough chaos in the world.
- I'd rather not live in it.
- You think this is chaos?
- Timer.
- No, screw the timer.
This is how I live.
I'm sorry if it upsets
your delicate sensibilities.
Wait, Angela, I-I didn't...
You think I'm overreacting?
You know what? I've had a long day.
I'm going to bed.
You should sleep on the couch.
I would, if I could find it.
Good morning.
- What's good about it?
- Uh-oh.
Looks like somebody's stressed
about their test scores.
Yeah, well, we both think
we got the 91.
Which means one of us got the 81.
Alright, take your seats.
As expected,
the stolen uniforms caused
a bit of paranoia out there.
Overnight, there were two fights
and a near shooting
'cause two officers
didn't recognize each other.
Alright, that being said,
it is vital that we remain vigilant.
Understood?
Now, to your exam scores.
You all submitted your guesses
last night,
and none of you guessed right.
Thank God.
Nolan, I'm sorry.
Save your concern, Officer Chen.
Officer Nolan got the highest
score, not the lowest.
That "honor" goes to...
...Officer West.
That's not possible.
I've seen a lot of
strange things in my 20 years,
but never would I have imagined
that the golden boy
would tank his test.
But there's a... th... like, I-I...
Uh-oh. Looks like Grey
broke your rookie.
Shut up.
Ah, Agent Russo.
You looking for me?
No. Actually, Officer Nolan.
Can you spare him for the morning?
I need his help running down a lead.
Nolan.
Alright, let's go back to work.
- Why didn't you call me back?
- What?
I left you a message last night.
Oh, well, I went to bed early.
Okay. And then this morning?
Did you have Sergeant Grey
assign me to you
- just so you could ask me about this?
- Mm-hmm.
Figured I'd kill two birds
while we're running down leads.
So, why didn't you call me?
Are you okay?
Yeah. Fine.
It's not like it's the first time
I didn't get the highest score.
Dude.
Look, um... after
the terrorist on the bus,
I just need a little bit of time off.
I figured I knew this stuff
backwards and forwards,
but clearly, that was a mistake.
Clearly, I should have kept studying.
- Jackson...
- Look, I let everyone down.
West, your cadets are here.
Hey.
Sorry to make you wait.
I am Officer Jackson West.
I am currently
a rookie patrol officer...
although, with the score I just got,
I could be, um, mall security
in my future.
Okay.
Um...
Good morning.
Good morning, sir!
Right. Um...
My whole life,
the only thing
I ever wanted to be was a cop.
Every class I took,
every sport I played
were all meant to make me
the best of...
You know what?
No.
You are looking at a cautionary tale.
The fallout of singular focus.
You were told your entire life
to study hard, stay in school.
Look, I am living proof...
that you need to skip school.
Stop worrying about overachieving
and acing every single test.
You know where
the safest place to be is?
The safest place to be...
the middle.
Stop... sacrificing...
and, uh...
...start living.
That was unexpected.
Yeah.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry about the test.
Tim had it made for Lucy,
but now you gotta wear it.
Seems fair.
Uh, hold that, please.
- Oh. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, no problem.
Hey, are you looking for something?
Oh, yeah, um... my wallet.
Ah.
Did you find it?
Yeah. Thanks.
Yeah.
What are you doing with that radio?
Hey! Stop!
7-Adam-19, chasing
a fake cop in the garage.
I need backup.
Hey! Stop!
- And you jumped from here?
- Yes, sir.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- You went right over after him?
- 'Course she did.
- I trained her.
- Mm-hmm.
You saying this guy stole a radio?
Uh, yes, sir, out of Car 26.
Actually, he...
he wasn't wearing gloves.
Maybe we can pull a print?
Well, you're gonna
have to tell me at some point.
I was just tired, and you were...
...you were laughing
over a burned body.
- What?
- Last night, at the crime scene.
And after Roskin,
you now think I'm heartless?
No. N... By no means, no. Not at all.
I-I get it.
You're a cop, and you've seen
a lot of bad things,
but nothing has ever
made me feel more like...
a rookie.
Grey wants us to go to Channel 9.
Go for 7-Adam-15.
We have a suspect
ID'd... Thomas Bernhardt.
Four possible addresses.
Sending one for you to check.
And stay off the main channels.
Bernhardt just stole a radio.
Copy that.
Why steal a radio?
You can listen to dispatch
from an app on your phone.
Because with a radio, they can
broadcast as well as listen.
They can feed us bad intel,
have us running all over
the city while they do...
Whatever it is they're
planning on doing.
Yep.
That's the house.
Wait just one second.
What are you doing?
Just want to run the plates
of the cars on the street.
Be nice to know
if Bernhardt has any company.
That's hot.
Thank you.
Oh, that's weird.
- What?
- That green car,
belongs to a missing person.
Tim and Lucy are on the case.
7-Adam-15 to 7-Adam-19.
We have eyes on a car
belonging to Susanna Brown.
Parked in front of
the fake cop's house?
That's correct. Who is she?
She's a clerk
at the criminal courthouse.
Didn't come home last night.
No idea how she could be
connected to our uniform thieves.
Do you need backup?
No.
- Negative, but we'll keep you posted.
- Roger.
Husband always did it, huh?
Do you have any surveillance
gear in your war bag?
Now we can look and listen.
It's time.
7-Adam-15,
requesting backup and SWAT...
- 9701 St. Andrews Place...
- Talk.
for a hostage situation...
not for public broadcast.
Hello, this is Susanna Brown
from Foltz Criminal Court.
Security code Apple-5, 2-1-4-2.
I have an... an urgent situation.
Judge Crawford granted
an unexpected appeal
in a homicide case...
and the evidence is on your truck.
I need you to divert from the route.
An escort will meet you there.
What is she talking about?
Every three months,
evidence from adjudicated trials
is destroyed
in a bonded demolition facility
up in Lancaster.
This is Overwatch. Road clear ahead.
Drugs, counterfeit money,
a huge cache of weapons
are all transported there
by police caravan.
That truck is driving into an ambush.
The escort that meets it
will be full of fake cops.
They won't hesitate
to kill that driver.
Truck 3 is diverting.
Copy that. SWAT will remain
with the convoy.
An escort should meet you en route.
Hey, it's me.
They're planning to hijack
the Lancaster convoy.
- Please.
- Okay. Copy that.
Please. I did what you asked.
Please just let me go.
Not until they make contact
with the truck.
As soon as that happens,
they're gonna kill her.
- We gotta get in there.
- He's in a room
in the middle of the house.
If we breach either door,
he's gonna shoot her first
and then come for us.
Raised foundation.
That means there's a crawlspace
under the house.
I can use that, come up through
one of the heating vents.
- John, John, this is way too dangerous.
- If we wait,
- and that woman is killed...
- We need to wait for SWAT.
- ...I won't be able to live with myself.
- No!
There it is.
Fake escort's already got them.
- Can't warn the truck
driver, because our heist crew's
jamming the signal
with their stolen radio.
- Shouldn't we wait for backup?
- We are the backup.
- Oh, please, let me go!
- Shut up.
Not until they make contact
with the truck and call back.
Please don't hurt me.
Shut up!
Yeah?
Sweet. I'll meet you at the rendezvous.
They got the truck.
Which means you're a loose end.
Thank you.
Okay. You're safe now. Okay?
I got you. Come on.
Oh!
Okay.
He's not gonna hurt you anymore.
Okay, get ready.
Remember, they don't know that we know.
- What's the problem?
- Radios are down.
We were sent to escort the truck
back to the courthouse.
Must be a mistake.
We're the escort.
So get out of the way.
No problem. We were headed
to lunch when we got the call.
- Tim?
- Yeah, I see it.
One last thing before we go...
real cops wear their vests
under their shirt.
Get out of the car!
Facedown on the ground!
Drop your weapon right now!
Down on the ground,
facedown, hands apart!
Don't you move.
Up.
You wanted to see me, sir?
So, how's the golden boy
dealing with almost failing out
of Field Training?
Fine.
You heard about the cadets?
I'm sorry about that, sir.
But you told us that self-reflection
was a necessary skill
for an LAPD officer.
And I've just had
a... pretty powerful dose of it.
My whole life has been about
getting here,
and now that I'm in uniform,
I realize that I'll never make it
if I, um...
if I don't find some balance.
Even if that means getting an 81
on a test or two.
And, uh... I can live with that.
That's admirable,
Officer West... truly.
But...
see, I'm not here to help you
find balance, son.
My job is to make sure
you keep your head in the game
at all times,
because lives are at stake.
So, I'm extending you in the program.
Tomorrow, you're back in long sleeves,
and your T.O. will continue
to write daily evaluations.
For how long?
Until I can trust you
in front of a room
full of cadets again.
You're dismissed.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
This is only gonna work
if we talk to each other.
You know that, right?
I've never lived with anyone before.
I've never been in love like this.
And I'm scared I'm gonna screw it up.
You won't.
I won't let you.
Good, 'cause we're getting a maid.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm glad, um, you called.
- Come in. Come on.
- Okay.
Can I, um...
get you something to drink?
No. No, I'm good. Thank you.
I just kind of, um,
just want to talk about
whatever it is that's bothering you.
Fair enough.
The last six months have been
the most intense in my life.
I... killed a man in the line of duty,
I watched my captain die,
I fought for my own life...
more times than I can count.
And I felt... every second of it.
Yesterday, you told me
I would feel less
the longer I did the job,
and a part of me wanted that so badly.
But I can't...
go numb.
It's not who I am,
and it's... definitely
not who I want to be.
So if I'm going to do this job,
I have to feel...
all of it.
No matter... what it does to me.
Damn it.
What?
I just, uh... I just...
...fell in love with you a little.
Wow.
Is that a bad thing?
I don't know yet.
I think now's a good...
I'm gonna come right in for a...
Do you wanna, um...
Do you wanna fool around?
Yes... I... do.
Mm.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com
Where are you going?
Uh, my place.
I'm not taking my clothes off here.
But you know what?
You can choose your house
over me, if you want.
Wait!