All jewelry must be removed
by the arresting officer.
Do I have your permission
to proceed?
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Hey.
Happy Half‐Year Anniversary.
That's not a thing.
Well, maybe not for
cynical police officers,
but for
tender‐hearted lawyers,
it's totally a thing.
But, hey, if you don't want
to go to n/naka tonight, eh...
You got a reservation?
You need to make those
like six ‐‐
Six months in advance.
I know.
I love your confidence.
Wait.
We've only been dating
for five months.
Yeah, well, technically,
but ‐‐
Did you make that reservation
for someone else
and hope I wouldn't remember
exactly when we hooked up?
If I say yes,
are you gonna say no?
Are you kidding?
I would kill to eat there.
But I'm gonna require
some serious
shower time...
Oh.
...for you
to make amends.
Deal. Yeah.
Whoa. Okay.
We've got a problem.
I just got an invitation
to a wedding.
Yeah.
I don't do weddings.
I don't know
what that means,
and I wasn't
inviting you.
Um, Lucy got
the same invitation.
The couple getting married
is her ex‐boyfriend
and her ex‐best friend.
Let me guess.
They hooked up while Lucy
was still dating him.
Living with him.
Mm.
She's obviously
devastated,
so maybe take it easy
on her today.
Look, Chen is my rookie,
not my friend.
My job is to train her,
not help her through
her messy social life.
Fine.
I'll dial it down, like, 2%.
That's my guy.
It is hot as the surface
of the sun out there.
Yep.
Gonna be like that all week.
Good thing we're all
in short sleeves now.
The uniforms
are still wool.
Today's gonna be
a nightmare.
I'm just saying ‐‐
I don't get out of the car
for less than a felony
when the needle
hits 100.
Your commitment to protecting
and serving is admirable.
As long as I can do it
in comfort.
You know the front row's
for the rookies, right?
You hoping
I'll sit by you?
I'm just telling you
how it is.
The day
I need that from you
is the day
I hang up my spurs.
You know you're losing,
right?
Good morning.
We've got ourselves a heat wave,
which means what,
Officer West?
Studies show
that a 1% loss of body mass
due to sweating
decreases
cognitive ability
and increases
anxiety levels.
Translation ‐‐
tempers will be short,
drug and alcohol use up,
so stay hydrated
and stay sharp.
Now, while the rest of you
are baking in the sun,
Officer Nolan
will be flop‐sweating
in his very first
preliminary court hearing.
Oh, no flop sweats here,
sir.
I have reviewed
the arrest report repeatedly.
I am 100% ready to testify
on all the facts.
Hmm. Bradford?
When did you graduate
the Academy?
Oh, that was September...
Exact date, Boot.
What's your weapon's
serial number?
I don't know the ‐‐
You need to know
the number by heart.
For a DUI arrest?
I didn't even draw my weapon.
If you don't even have
your personal information
squared away,
how could you possibly know
the facts of the case?
A defense attorney's job
is to screw you up on the stand
by any means necessary.
Which means
everything that connects
to your experience on the job
is in bounds.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
You're driving today,
Boot.
What?
You heard me.
Why?
Look,
if you don't want to ‐‐
N‐No, no. I do.
What's the catch?
Why does there
have to be a catch?
There's always a catch.
Not today.
Well, that can't be legal.
It's not.
Light him up.
You're not coming?
It's a low‐risk misdemeanor.
You got this.
Ahh.
Hey.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Well, it's your first time
in court.
I thought you'd ‐‐
you'd appreciate
a friendly face
in the gallery.
Well, thank God.
At roll call this morning,
Grey had me freaked out.
He told me this was
predetermined to be a disaster.
The first one always is.
Was yours?
Ugh. Especially mine.
Good morning.
Wesley. Whoa.
You got a case
on the docket today?
Yep. Yours.
Defense counsel ate
some bad lamb last night,
asked me to step in.
Outstanding.
N‐Not about the ‐‐
the lamb,
but that ‐‐ that it's ‐‐
that it's you.
He's a little nervous.
It's his first time
in court.
Yeah. I get it.
My first time was disastrous.
Look, I'll try to make it
as painless as possible, okay?
Thank you very much.
Hey, just remember ‐‐
whatever happens,
it's not personal.
Right.
What does that mean?
That I'm the only
friendly face here.
That's my guy,
the one with the ponytail,
Brant Reggie, 23‐152,
DUI Drugs.
How do I know
the guy next to him?
Oh, that's, um,
Oscar Hutchinson.
He was one of the prison bus
escapees we tracked down.
He's kind of the reason
we're together.
How romantic.
Good morning.
We've got a lot of cases
to get through today,
so let's just jump right in.
Uh, hi. Uh...
Mr. Hutchinson, you've been
in my courtroom enough
to know that
this isn't a Q&A.
Yes, Your Honor.
I just wanted to say
I don't mind going last.
I think
these men beside me
deserve to be heard from
first.
And you're in no hurry
to go back in the hole.
Interrupt me again,
and I'll have you gagged.
Call the first case.
People of
the State of California
versus Jonathan Ryland,
homicide
in the first degree.
Is everything okay?
That man killed our son.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you, sir.
Color's all off, man.
It's not even
the right color green.
What's up, Amari?
Man, this fool took
a counterfeit $100
without even checking it.
♪ Black and yellow ♪
♪ Black and yellow,
black and yellow ♪
They misspelled it
"hunderd."
Don't get me started.
You got
a description for us?
Oh, better.
♪ I run from my past,
I guess that makes... ♪
Come on. You took a $100 bill
from this clown?
How long ago was he here?
30 minutes or so.
I was at couple's counseling.
Everything alright
with you and Serena?
You know how it is.
Baby's teething.
We're not sleeping.
I'm working long hours.
Yeah. Well, look,
hang in there, alright?
Yeah.
Look, we'll put a BOLO out,
cruise the neighborhood.
Hopefully we spot him.
Thanks.
Oh, hey,
I'm still out $100, though.
Uh, unfortunately,
yes.
You should've gloved up when you
touched the counterfeit bill
in case we needed
to pull prints.
You're right.
Um, I spaced.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Why didn't you say anything
when we were inside?
No reason.
You always call me out
in front of people
when I screw up.
First you let me drive,
now this?
Why are you
being nice to me today?
I'm not.
Did Rachel talk to you?
She did.
I told her not to.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I didn't want her to,
either.
Look,
this isn't a big deal.
You know,
I ‐‐ I'm over him,
and I'm ‐‐
I'm happy for them.
So I don't need any special
treatment from you, okay?
Okay.
Then I'm driving.
What? But...
Hey. You called 911?
Yeah.
I was hooking up the car,
and I caught a whiff
of something really bad
coming from that warehouse.
Alright.
I'll check it out. Thanks.
Whew. God.
7‐L‐14,
possible DB at location.
Stand by for confirmation.
Hey.
Can I call you right back?
What?
You said visitation
was set.
I changed my schedule.
I haven't seen my daughter
in over a week.
Look,
I don't want to play nice.
I want my kid.
I got to call you right back.
7‐L‐14, DB on scene.
I need homicide
and forensic team.
But first,
I need animal control.
Officer Nolan, did you have
training at the Academy
for DUI suspects?
Uh, yes, sir.
40 hours of alcohol
intoxication recognition.
Did they test you
on that training?
Of course.
And did you score 100%?
No, but I ‐‐
Okay, so, on the date
in question ‐‐
March 16th.
Yes. That date.
Did you see my client
behind the wheel?
N‐No. Your client was
already out of the car
by the time
we arrived on scene,
but the driver of
the vehicle he hit ‐‐
Allegedly hit.
And please only answer
the questions that I ask you.
Now, did you get fingerprints
from the steering wheel
to prove that my client
was the driver?
No,
but the other driver ‐‐
The other driver,
as you call him,
suffered a head injury.
Are you telling me
that you identified my client
based solely on
that man's say‐so?
Your client owns the car.
Your Honor, can you please
instruct the witness
to answer my question?
Officer.
Yeah. Uh, yes.
I ID'd your client
as the driver of the vehicle
based on
the witness statement.
Okay.
How could I have known
he wasn't wearing pants?
No, not just pants ‐‐
bottoms of any kind.
I'll never be able
to unsee that.
Whoa!
My man, close it up.
You think I'm being stupid,
letting that invitation
bother me.
You said
it wasn't bothering you,
and I was relieved we didn't
have to talk about it.
Why the hell would they
invite me to their wedding?
To further humiliate me?
Maybe they're trying
to make amends.
Amends.
By making me
starve myself for a month
so I can fit into
a drop‐dead sexy dress and ‐‐
Hey. Up ahead.
That's the counterfeit guy.
Hey! Hands on the hood.
Let's go.
Alright.
Spread your legs apart.
This can't be real.
‐It's the emergency...
‐Look. You think this is real?
What's happening?
Go! Go! Go! Come on!
We got to get out of here!
What do we do?
Let him go.
We got to get
back to the station.
Order! Order in my court!
Order! Order!
Everyone, be still!
Clearly, we can't continue,
given the missile alert.
Deputy, take the prisoners
back to holding.
Let's go. Come on.
Screw that.
There's a nuke coming!
Got anything?
The ‐‐ The lines
are already jammed.
People are panicking.
We got to help them out.
Should we evacuate?
No. No. Um...
Hey, hey, everybody.
Excuse me.
Everyone, if I can have
your attention, please.
Uh, I'm Jessica Russo,
Department of Homeland Security.
Now, I haven't gotten
in touch with my office,
but there is a good chance
that this is not real.
That's right.
There was
a false missile alert
out of Hawaii
just last year.
There's no need to panic.
What if it's not fake?
Well, then you got
about 28 minutes
until you find out
what Hell feels like.
Okay, that kind of talk
isn't helping anything.
The DHS has scenarios
planned for this situation.
We have.
Yes, we have.
And, um, the most likely target
is downtown.
Where we are.
Okay. Wait!
Order.
Wait! Wait!
The blast radius is likely
between 10 to 15 miles.
And with an impact expected
in 27 minutes,
there isn't enough time
to get far enough away,
which is why we need
to get underground.
Judge, sir, i‐is ‐‐
is there a bomb shelter
in this building?
No, but the holding cells
are downstairs.
Let's go.
I hate to break it
to you,
but those cells leak
when it rains.
They're not gonna do squat
in a nuclear attack.
Okay ‐‐
Now. Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Damn it.
Here goes nothing.
Listen up.
LAPD has not been able
to verify the alert is real.
However, real or not,
everyone in the city
is panicking right now.
So I don't care if you've been
off the street for 20 years.
If you got a badge,
get out there.
First priority ‐‐
to secure sensitive targets.
Next, protect the community.
Ignore petty crimes.
Focus on people,
not property.
Look, I know you're scared.
I'm scared, too.
But people out there
are counting on us,
and we will help them.
Yeah.
Okay, let's get to work.
What can I do?
Stay here.
If this is real,
there's a place to seek shelter
in the parking garage.
Stay with me.
I can't.
I'm the guy
that catches the nuke.
It's actually
a pretty prestigious assignment.
You're an idiot.
Thanks.
The world could be ending.
I don't think anybody's gonna
begrudge you a little PDA.
Come here.
I'll see you later.
You better.
Why is everyone
running around, Mommy?
We're having a drill,
like we were having at school
when I picked you up.
But then why does
everyone look so scared?
Because
they're good actors, baby.
Detective,
why aren't you on the street?
'Cause I need to take care
of my daughter.
Understood.
Hi, there.
I'm Sergeant Grey.
Lila.
Nice to meet you, Lila.
Do you mind if I talk
to your mom for a minute?
Sure.
Uh, go get a snack
from the machine, baby. Okay?
Um, I can help her.
Thank you.
Of course.
Is it real?
I don't know.
Tell me ‐‐
how was the traffic coming in?
Any chance for people
to get clear?
No.
Why don't you just
let us go, man?
It's the end of the world.
Give us a few minutes
of freedom.
Don't make us die
in these chains.
Shut up, Oscar.
You're not getting out
of those cuffs.
We ain't asking.
Back up. Back up.
Right now. Right now.
Hey, um,
I can't get ahold of Angela.
Can I use your radio?
Yeah.
7‐Adam‐07,
go to channel 15.
Just turn the dial on top.
Thank you.
Angela, it's me.
Wesley?
Hey, how's it going?
Oh, you know, pretty good
for the end of the world.
I'm bummed we're gonna miss
our reservation.
Look, we're not.
This is just a false alarm.
Okay?
Yeah.
Hey. You alright?
There's a bomb shelter
at the public school
two blocks west, alright?
Head there.
Where are you?
I'm at the courthouse
with Nolan
and Jessica and a bunch
of scared people.
Two blocks west.
Head there.
Are you going down
to the bomb shelter?
Judge Stevens
said there isn't one.
Criminal courthouse
on Spring?
Yeah.
There's definitely
a fallout shelter.
I was down there once
as a rookie.
Hey.
Nolan.
Angela says this place
does have a bomb shelter.
Are you safe
where you are?
Angela.
Are you still there?
Yeah.
I'm heading underground.
Okay. I love you.
Love you, too.
The judge is gone.
So is the ADA, the ‐‐
the bailiff,
and a bunch of other people
from the gallery.
What's happening?
The judge lied to us
about the bomb shelter.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Step back.
What are you doing?
What I have to.
‐Back up. I'm closing this door.
‐And what about the rest of us?
If she's right about the nuke,
then this is ground zero.
Won't be safe
to go outside for weeks.
We don't have the supplies
in here for all of you.
So you're gonna kill a cop
and all these others
just to save yourselves?
And the rest of you ‐‐
you're all good with that?!
I'm not gonna
tell you again.
Back up
so I can close this door.
Okay. Okay, fine.
You win. I give up.
Pretty cool, right?
They taught me that
at the Academy.
Come on.
You're making
a big mistake.
And you're under arrest.
Sit down right there.
Get cozy.
Here we go.
Come in.
Hands.
No, no, no! Not him!
Hey. They're human beings
with rights.
He killed our boy
in cold blood.
Aw.
You better back up, mami,
or you'll be next.
You ‐‐
‐Get off me!
‐Okay. Alright. Alright.
‐Hey. Take it easy.
‐Hey, hey, hey!
Alright, we're not leaving
anyone outside, okay?
So everyone back up.
Here we go. Come on.
Back up.
Let's get these prisoners
over to the back here.
We can segregate them
on the benches.
Here. Take that.
Folks, in this way.
Keep moving.
Go ahead
and sit down, sir.
Is that everyone?
Thank you.
Alright.
Be a lot more comfortable
without this chain, you know?
We can keep the cuffs on.
Don't push your luck, Oscar.
Ah, that's all
I know how to do.
There's barely any air
moving in here at all.
Well, the judge
was right about one thing.
With this many people
in here,
these supplies
won't even last a week.
I'm surprised
we haven't gotten an update.
Control, 7‐Adam‐15.
Come in.
Control?
No bars.
Alright.
So, we know radio frequencies
and mobile signals
are blocked by the shelter.
Let's hope it does as well
against radiation.
This thing hasn't worked
since the Reagan administration.
So, now all we can do
is wait.
13 minutes.
Stop checking the time.
Are you serious?
We're about to be burned up
by a giant fireball.
"A," no, we're not.
It's a false alarm.
And, "B,"
counting down the minutes
wouldn't accomplish anything,
even if it was real.
So, what, you just want me
to think about something else?
Pretty much.
Can't be done.
Really?
Okay.
How would you sabotage
that wedding?
What?
Don't tell me you didn't
lie awake all night
fantasizing about it.
I ‐‐ I didn't.
Lying to me in your last moments
on Earth is a bad look.
You said
it was a false alarm.
Fine.
I'd cancel
the rehearsal dinner,
change the registry
to a bondage Web store,
pay a gang of clowns
to storm their wedding,
and hire a chopper to fly over
their outdoor reception,
see how well
their wedding cake stands up
to the rotor wash of
a Sikorsky helicopter.
Didn't think about it,
huh?
How is revenge what
we're focusing on right now?
It's tangible, okay?
You can hold on to it.
Imminent nuclear death
is totally unrelatable.
Now, speaking of revenge,
I have a friend at USC
who studies cockroaches.
I'm sure he could
loan you a few hundred
to release
at the wedding.
Mommy,
what's really going on?
I told you, honey.
It's a drill.
Please don't lie.
Daddy says that's why
we can't see you anymore.
Don't you want
to tell the truth?
Of course I do, honey.
I ‐‐
I just ‐‐
My previous job,
I had to lie a lot...
to fool criminals, so...
Why do you want
to fool me?
Are you mad at me?
Of course not.
No, honey.
I, um ‐‐ I love you.
I'll make you a deal.
I'll stop sleeping
with a night light
if you tell the truth,
okay?
Okay.
And here I thought the most
stressful part of my day
would be going to court.
At least we're together.
Yeah.
Thank you for coming
to support me.
You're welcome.
Can I, um ‐‐
Can I confess something?
You were already here
for a meeting.
You knew?
Yeah,
but it didn't matter.
10 minutes.
We still have time to get
to the fallout shelter
at the courthouse,
hook up with Wesley.
Yeah, maybe we should,
just to be safe.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
The worthy will
ascend into the heavens!
All hail
Children of the Stars.
We are not going
to the shelter, are we?
We will wait for your
arrival, Noon Star Harvesters.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Today the saviors
will gather our souls.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
The worthy
will ascend into the heavens.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Hey!
We await your arrival...
How about you come down
from there?
...Noon Star Harvesters.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
No.
It's almost our time,
but there's nothing to fear.
This was all prophesized ‐‐
"Like a clarion call,
word shall spread
of Our Saviors From Above.
Heed ye
the Noon Star Harvesters,
for they shall descend
from the heavens
so The Worthy
can ascend."
So sayeth
The Prophet Jedediah.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Okay. So, you're saying
the missile ‐‐
Isn't a missile.
It is a cloak behind which
our saviors will come to us,
and we will step out to meet
them at the appointed time,
ascending into
their interstellar embrace.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Today the Saviors will...
So, they're clearly crazy.
Can we go now?
All hail
Children of the Stars.
You can.
But I'm not leaving until I get
them down off that ledge.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Yeah, but if the missile's real,
it won't matter if they jump.
And if it's not?
We wait for your arrival,
Noon Star Harvesters.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Today the Saviors
will gather our souls.
Okay.
I mean, but they're
true believers.
How are we gonna get through
to them in nine minutes?
I'm open to suggestions.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Get out of here!
Put ‐‐ Put it down!
Get ‐‐ Get out! Get out!
Put it down! Put it down!
Amari, it's Tim!
Bradford?!
Yeah. You alright?
Yeah, but Lewis took a bottle
to the head.
Alright,
just put down the shotgun.
They're robbing me.
I got to protect my store.
We're here now,
so put it down.
Put it on the counter.
Put it down.
Okay.
O‐Okay. Alright.
Now we're coming in.
Check him out.
Hey. Let me see.
Ohh.
Okay, you're gonna need
stitches,
but it's nothing
life‐threatening.
Keep pressure on it.
Why don't you take him around
the corner to your house?
No, I‐I‐I can't leave
my store.
It's just stuff, Amari.
The missile is coming, alright?
You should be
with your family.
Yeah, but if it's not,
I'll lose everything.
No wonder you need counseling.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means that nothing
is more important
than the people you love,
and they need you right now.
We'll take care of
your shop.
O‐Okay.
Alright, come on.
Let's get him up.
Okay.
You're right.
Thank you.
Let's go. Come on.
Busted.
How much time
we got left?
Enough.
Uh, I'm not
a whiskey girl.
To the end of the world.
Whenever that may be.
This shelter
was built in the '50s.
Now, nukes are 10 times
as powerful today.
Odds are good that this building
collapses when the blast hits.
Shut up, Oscar.
It's basic science, my man.
Try not to sound
so happy about it.
What can I say?
I'm a happy guy.
Not like mami over here.
So sad.
Don't you laugh
at our grief.
He's trying to provoke you.
Don't let him.
You got me
all wrong, Counselor.
What we have here is
a cathartic opportunity.
Two paths ‐‐
forgiveness or revenge.
Oh, three, three paths.
I forgot.
I forgot about the missile.
Oh, I ain't looking
for forgiveness.
And little papi over there
can try for revenge
if he likes.
But he'll just end up
in the ground like his kid.
You ‐‐
Come here!
How dare you!
Sit down. Shut up.
Sit down now.
Sit down.
It's okay.
He's not worth it.
One more word
out of any of them,
we're gagging them all.
Happy to.
One more word.
You okay?
No.
Today the Saviors
will gather our souls.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
The worthy will ascend
into the heavens.
All hail
Children of the Stars.
Excuse me.
I hate to interrupt.
I just have a question.
The time
for questions is done.
Totally. I just ‐‐
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Hold on.
Hold on.
Who's Jedediah?
You mentioned him earlier.
He is the prophet
who helped us cast away
our earthly possessions
and see the truth.
About the aliens?
They're not aliens.
They're spirits
from another universe.
And where is he?
Jedediah.
He's joining us
in the heavens.
Does that mean
he's on another rooftop?
No.
This is the one true spot,
where ‐‐ where the chosen
will ascend.
And yet he's not here.
What's your name?
Aurora.
How old are you, Aurora?
19.
It is
the age of the chosen.
Aren't you scared?
No, I'm at peace.
It's just...
...I don't like heights.
I don't blame you.
It's a long way down.
So why do you have to step
off the roof to ascend?
'Cause that's the way
it must be.
Why?
The spirits love you.
Oh, yes.
And they're traveling
all this way to save you.
Do you think they really care
how you meet them,
as long as you do it
with open arms?
It is a test to our faith.
There is no doubt
you have faith, all of you.
So come down now,
and we'll wait for them together
on solid ground.
I promise it'll be okay.
Attention, all units.
Missile alert is a false alarm.
I repeat ‐‐ the alert
is a false alarm.
Oh, thank God.
What does ‐‐
What does that mean?
It means
they're not coming.
The danger's over.
Okay?
Okay.
Does that mean
Daddy'll be here soon?
Yeah. Yeah.
I know, right?
‐Crazy today.
‐This was unbelievable.
Oh, you know what?
Honey,
I will be right back.
Hey. Hi.
Um  thanks
for watching my kid.
Oh, my pleasure.
She's super cute.
Thanks.
Uh, hey, listen.
You work for Social Services,
right?
I do.
Can I ask you
a theoretical question?
Sure.
Okay, say, uh,
there's a divorced couple
and, uh, the dad
has sole custody
and the mom
has supervised visitations
and an emergency comes up
and she can't
get in touch with him ‐‐
So she picks her super cute
daughter up from school
to keep her safe.
Yeah.
Is that bad?
To the court,
it's not good.
You know that technically
it's a parental abduction.
Yeah, but even given
the circumstances?
I'm not saying a judge wouldn't
take it into consideration,
but if the factors that led
to the visitation restrictions
are serious enough,
it won't matter.
You could lose
all access to her.
Harper,
have you heard from Nolan?
He's the only cop
that hasn't checked in.
What?
Officer Nolan.
Your rookie?
Have you heard from him?
No, sir, I‐I haven't talked
to him since this morning.
One minute.
Will we know
when it hits?
Yeah. We'll feel the shock wave
and likely some heat.
Hopefully
not too much heat.
30 seconds.
Ohh!
Prisoner secured!
Nolan.
Everybody, be calm.
Thanks for the diversion,
buddy.
Let the judge go.
Sure I will,
just as soon as
I'm outside.
What about the missile?
Well, if it's real,
I'm not gonna
feel it anyways.
I'm just gonna wink
right out of existence.
I don't want to spend the rest
of my days in solitary.
If you even twitch,
I'm gonna cut your carotid.
No! Don't open it!
Hey.
Ugh!
Looks like you'll be spending
some time in solitary after all.
So, no missile?
False alarm.
Heat wave caused a malfunction
at Edwards Air Force Base.
Where's Wesley?
I don't know.
He was just here.
Wesley.
Oh, my God.
Get an ambulance!
It's okay, baby.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
35‐year‐old male
in hypovolemic shock,
stab wound to the left chest,
possible pneumothorax.
Alert the O. R.
This guy's jumping the line.
We've got him from here.
Is he gonna be okay?
It depends on the extent
of the internal damage,
but we're gonna do
everything we can.
Sorry. I've gotta go.
You can't really
blame a guy for trying.
To commit a felony?
It's literally what I do
for a living.
Was it all
just a game to you?
Did you feel any fear
at all?
Honestly? No.
Guys like me
are wired differently.
I don't really do fear
or anxiety.
On the flip side,
I have really poor
impulse control.
He, you think
I could get a soda?
No.
Is my daughter here?
Where's my daughter?
Where is she? Lila!
What's going on?
My daughter ‐‐ Lila.
Please tell me
she's here.
Daddy!
Oh, God.
Are you okay, baby?
Yeah.
Mommy picked me up at school
'cause of the missile,
but it's not real.
I‐I was trying to get
in touch with you ‐‐
You had no right!
I showed up,
and she was gone.
The school was closed.
I had no idea where she was!
Sir, I understand your fear,
but your child was safe here.
Y‐You don't understand.
She has no custody rights.
She kidnapped my kid.
I did not ‐‐
No, no, no, no.
I want her arrested.
Daddy, no.
Sir, with all due respect,
I think you're overreacting.
I'm what?
When you consider
everything that happened ‐‐
I‐I don't care.
This is the last straw.
She said things had changed,
that she had changed,
but it was just another lie.
No, it wasn't.
How the hell
would you know?
Because she's here,
back in uniform,
training me.
I couldn't figure out why
until just this moment.
I mean,
she had a golden ticket.
She could have gone anywhere
in the department,
anywhere she wanted.
So, why the hell
would she get back in blues
and spend her days
training a guy like me?
I knew whatever the reason was,
it had to be primal,
powerful enough to...overcome
her inherent arrogance.
And now I see your daughter,
and I see exactly why
she's willing to sacrifice
what she does best
for the person
she loves the most.
Please, Daddy.
I made her promise ‐‐
no more lying.
It's true.
I'm trying here, Don.
I have been lost,
and I am trying
to find my way back.
And I am gonna make
mistakes.
And I'm gonna
fall on my face a lot.
But when that alert
came in,
the only thing
I could think about
was making sure
that she was safe.
That is the only thing
that matters to me now.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Go hug your mama.
I love you, cutie. Okay?
♪ Laurel was a girl I knew,
made of dirt and stone ♪
♪ Pretty, hip
in younger years ♪
♪ But now she sits alone ♪
♪ With a hundred thousand
architectural disasters ♪
♪ That she calls home ♪
Thanks.
Seems like a great kid.
Yeah. She is.
♪ She tried to get the credit ♪
♪ Sometimes more
than she deserved ♪
♪ Like those cheesy
'80s movies ♪
♪ Epitomizing all things
we'd come to know ♪
Hey. Sure I can't
get you something?
I'm fine.
What's taking so long?
So, do you want me
to talk to my buddy
about the cockroaches?
No, thanks.
After today, I've decided that
I'm okay with the wedding.
I know they seem
really happy.
And truth be told,
I was only with him
because I couldn't afford
to move out.
And she knew that, so...
Does that mean
we're going to the wedding?
No, but I might
get them a present.
With a roach in it?
Maybe.
You are a bad influence.
Love you, too. Bye.
So, Henry says hello
and that I should move
the hell out of Los Angeles.
That's a smart kid.
What'd you tell him?
That there was never
any real danger
because you had my back.
And your front.
Hey.
I hope it's okay
that I'm here.
Yeah.
How's Wesley?
We're waiting to find out.
Join us.
Is he okay?
The surgery went well.
The doctor repaired
his lung.
As long as there are
no complications,
he should make
a full recovery.
Thank you.
They'll move him into ICU
in a few hours.
I'll come get you
so you can see him.
He's gonna be okay.
Corrected by
Flatto (subscene.com)