- Eric Weddle with a tackle just shy...
- Thattaboy, Weddle!
- Thattaboy, baby!
- ...of the first down marker.
- Come on! One more!
- Rams defense needs a stop here
- One more stop, that's all we need.
- to have any hopes of a win.
One more stop.
We're coming on
air live with a car chase
- in Los Angeles County.
- Oh, come on!
The driver has been eluding police
for the better part of a half-hour.
Dispatch, Officer Tim Bradford.
Badge 34831.
Log me in for overtime in
pursuit of a high-speed suspect.
LAPD!
Put your hands outside the window!
Now open the door from the
outside, and step out of the car!
You sidestep over to your left,
face down on the ground,
arms out to the side.
- You got him?
- All good.
The ball is tipped,
intercepted by Weddle...
- Yes! Run, Weddle! Run!
- He's at the 20, the 10...
Touchdown! Eric Weddle!
Um, I'm late.
Roger that.
- Breakfast is almost ready.
- No, no, no. I'm...
- I'm late.
- Okay, alright.
I'll just get you a... a coffee to go.
I've got a travel mug right here,
and you're...
- You're late, as in...?
- Yeah.
- Oh, boy.
- Or girl.
- How late?
- Three days.
Okay. That doesn't necessarily
mean you're pregnant.
There are two things in this world
that always run on time...
Swiss watches and my cycle.
Right.
Okay, um...
Wha... Uh...
First, we should be absolutely sure.
Yes, okay.
Um... I've got a staff meeting
first thing this morning,
but I'll pick up a test on the way in,
and I'll call you as soon as I know.
Okay, and...
and no matter what happens,
we'll make the best of this.
Okay.
I mean, talk about terrible timing.
Though...
Henry was born at a
less-than-ideal time,
and he's the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
Not that I'm saying I
hope she's pregnant.
I... Not that I'm saying
I hope she's not pregnant.
What am I saying?
Just wish she would call.
How hard is it to pee on a stick?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are... Are you talking to me?
- What's going on?
- Roll call.
- Is everything alright?
- Hundred percent.
Nice of you to finally
deign to sit with us.
Enh, the front row's
too close to the boss.
Lopez still out?
Yeah. Taking care of Wesley.
She's got him back on his feet.
Good.
Okay, listen up.
Why is community policing important?
Officer Chen?
Uh, because it builds trust
between the police and the public,
leading to a reduction in crime.
Exactly.
And today, we're gonna do
a little trust-building.
Officer Nolan, so,
you know Dr. Sawyer at Shaw Memorial?
Uh, we went - to the same college, sir.
Eh, before I got my now-ex
pregnant with my son and...
It was a yes or no question, Nolan.
Sorry, sir. Yes, I know her.
Good. She requested an officer
to assist with a seminar.
- You're going.
- What kind of seminar?
Don't know, don't care.
Whatever it is,
it's open to the public,
which means you have a
chance to show the community
that the LAPD does more
than just lock up people.
We do?
That's not funny.
And you don't want to piss me
off, Bradford.
Considering what I
have lined up for you.
- What's that?
- Watts Rams need additional coaches
for their fall clinic,
and you're gonna need company.
Officer West.
Your dad is always bragging
how you're a high-school football star.
- Is he lying?
- No, sir.
All-State safety, four years running.
I could actually pull up my
highlight reel if you
want to check it out.
- It's on my YouTube channel.
- That won't be necessary.
Change into your PTs,
head out with Bradford.
Harper and Chen,
you will serve as liaisons
to the Mid-Wilshire Community Council.
They're coming in for a sit-down.
What is this? The 1950s?
The boys go to football practice
while us girls attend a PTA meeting?
Fair point.
Guess there's really only
one way to settle this...
Challenge coins.
Chief gave me mine personally.
That was nice.
Mine was given to me by the governor.
What is a challenge coin?
How do you not know that?
It's a medallion bearing
an organization's insignia,
given only to those deemed worthy.
They're used to show respect
or, uh, settle minor disputes.
Okay. Closest to the edge wins.
Oh!
Alright. Harper, football's all yours.
Nah, Bradford can have it.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Nope.
Only football I watch is English.
Whatever.
Community Council will be here in 20.
Ma'am, would you like me to
prepare anything for the meeting?
Uh, coffee. Black.
- Officer...
- Uh, Chen. It's right there.
No, the only name I know,
is Nolan's, and you are not him.
So today, you are Not Nolan.
- I'm Not Nolan.
- It's often how I think of you.
Oh. Funny.
Do you have any advice on
how to get on her good side?
I actually don't know that she has one,
so good luck.
Hey, nice move.
Ooh! Great hands.
That is AJ.
Most pure talent on the team.
Kid's gonna get recruited hard.
Oh, we don't care about that.
When AJ joined us,
his grades were in the trash.
Now he's on the honor roll,
wants to go to college.
That's what we care about.
Hey, you, uh... you like that move?
It's alright against a 12-year-old.
You're gonna have to up your footwork,
when you get to real
competition, though.
Nah, I run footwork drills
every morning. I'll be ready.
- And at night?
- Catching drills.
Harder to see the ball,
increases hand-eye coordination.
- Any other questions?
- No, not at this time.
AJ.
What is she doing here?
I'll be right back.
His mom.
Just got released a few months ago.
Transition's been
rough on both of them.
- What was she in for?
- Armed robbery.
Pretty serious crew.
- It's Eric Weddle, man.
- Weddle, Weddle!
Hey. Can we play?
Weddle.
Tim Bradford, is that you?
You know him?
Man. We played against
each other in high school.
I sacked Bradford so hard
in the championship game,
he decided Fallujah was
better than turning pro.
Yeah, smart man.
The NFL's only getting
harder and faster.
Yo, you're Robert Woods.
I have your USC jersey at home.
- Whoo!
- Me too.
Hey, man, great to have
you back in L.A., bro.
Good to be back.
- Alright.
- Great.
Alright. Thanks, guys.
Yo. You just bro-hugged Eric Weddle.
Don't make it weird.
You know, it's not about what you want.
- I got to do what I think is best.
- Oh, now it's about you?
I don't want to go!
Everything okay?
AJ's dropping football.
Got a lot going on right now.
Come on.
...tops, and then we
go do real police work.
Oh, I see why you chose this.
Lowest impact on our day.
Yep. Community meetings
are quick and easy.
Just don't promise them anything.
Whatever the complaint,
just nod and say,
"We are aware of the problem,"
"and we have a task
force working on it."
Ooh, a task force?
Yeah, these busybody types love it
when cops say "task force."
Okay. Well, I'll just follow your lead.
Oh, I'm not talking. You are.
- Wh... What?
- I don't do community meetings.
Go on.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hi. Uh, I'm Officer Lucy Chen,
and the Mid-Wilshire Police Station
- is proud to partner with you today...
- There is no partnering with us,
until first you partner with the Earth.
- Oh, come on.
- What's LAPD doing
about the city's lack of
drought-tolerant plants?
Oh. Yes.
We are aware of this problem,
and we have a task force working on it.
Oh... Sweet.
Officer, can you do
something about my neighbor?
He's constantly feeding the squirrels.
Uh... yes.
We have a task force working on that.
A squirrel task force?
- Yes, ma'am.
- This is serious.
Squirrels attract coyotes,
and I have small dogs.
And any time I try to
talk to my neighbor,
he's just hateful.
I'm scared for the safety of my babies.
Yeah. Uh, listen,
why don't you give me his address,
and I'll make sure that the
task force is following up.
Is there a task force
for abandoned cars?
There's one - in front of my apartment.
I'll give you my address.
Hey, Jess, it's me.
I-I thought I would have
heard from you by now.
Are you... Are you
still in your meeting?
Are you having trouble peeing?
Because the trick is to...
You know, I got to go.
Call me when you know.
- Hey, John.
- Hey.
Appreciate you doing this.
My pleasure. What are we doing?
- They didn't tell you?
- No.
Oh, we're hosting our
monthly free seminar.
- Great. For who?
- Pregnant mothers.
- What's wrong?
- Uh, nothing.
I couldn't be more excited.
How's Wesley?
Driving me crazy.
He was stabbed.
Well, yeah, but it's not like
any major organs were damaged.
God, I miss cop humor.
Corporate world is so buttoned up.
Everyone's always
running scared of H.R.
- Is Stabby here?
- No.
His mom took him to physical therapy.
I was planning a spa day until you said
I can make two grand for 8 hours' time.
Yep, and trust me,
you're gonna love -
working private security.
I've done some moonlighting,
but nothing fancy like this.
- Who am I guarding?
- Mingus Kemp.
He's a high-end - jewelry
broker from Vegas.
Comes to L.A.
every month to buy diamonds.
You'll keep him safe while our
driver runs you around town.
Anything else I need to
know about the protectee?
He thinks he's a player.
Inherited the business from his dad.
He'll hit on you a little,
but he's mostly harmless.
Okay. Uh... I still get paid
- if he gets killed, right?
- Yeah.
I wouldn't let him know that, though.
Hello, Ms. Clemons.
I'm Officer Bradford.
This is Officer West.
- We met at the, uh...
- I-I remember. What do you want?
Just want to make sure
everything's alright.
Pulled AJ off the team so fast,
wanted to make sure
there wasn't a problem.
No problem. Thanks for stopping by.
- Everything okay, buddy?
- He's fine.
How about you?
You seem to be moving out in a hurry.
Something going on?
Um, it's none of your damn business.
Actually, it is, Ms. Clemons.
You're still on parole
for armed robbery.
Your P.O. know you're moving?
- So, what? You gonna violate me?
- No, nobody wants that.
We're just here to help.
Get down! Get down!
Control, 7-Adam-19.
We have a 246 with a
firebomb at our location.
Two masked suspects,
fleeing south on Gramercy
in a black Impala.
So, you have no idea who they were?
- Not a clue.
- Come on, Ms. Clemons.
I mean, two masked suspects
and a Molotov cocktail...
that wasn't some
random act of violence.
You were targeted.
Tell me why.
- Am I under arrest?
- Of course not.
Then can I go?
Not yet, look, I just need a list
of the personal property that
was damaged during the fire.
Hey, man. Hit me.
I wasn't gonna say it earlier,
but, uh...
you got some serious talent.
If you're running drills
every morning on your own,
you clearly love the sport.
Yes, sir.
I, uh... take this ball
with me everywhere I go.
Sounds like me.
You know, in some ways,
this game saved me.
How?
You know, growing up in my house was...
a bit chaotic.
Yeah, I, um...
I know a little something about that.
My old man had a hair trigger.
Never knew what would set him off.
And football was...
the only place I had any control.
Yeah, I, um...
I know a little something
about that, too.
Football taught me
discipline, teamwork.
It wasn't just a game.
Yeah?
And, uh, what game are we
playing right now, huh?
We connect over sports
and then I talk about
my mom behind her back?
I'd never ask you to do that.
But, look, if you ever need anything...
just let me know, alright?
You're too pretty to be a cop.
Sir, I think we should
keep this professional.
Of course. Of course.
- How about a selfie?
- Sorry, that would compromise security.
Right. Right. Yeah.
No, um... you know, I knew that.
That was... That was
...That was a test.
Hey, you want to see something?
By the end of today,
this will be filled
with $2 million in diamonds, Angela.
You ever seen, uh, $2 million before?
Saw 10 times that in a drug
raid in a cartel stash house.
Had a bunch of brains
scattered across it, though.
Cool. Yeah.
Control, 7-Adam-15,
show us Premise Check, Code 6.
Copy that.
Okay, so...
According to Mr. Elson,
there are vagrants -
squatting in the storm drain.
Great job.
We are about to go fishing
in the armpit of Los Angeles,
full of the complete
hepatitis alphabet,
not to mention rats.
- You first.
- Okay, it's disgusting,
but isn't the whole point
of community policing to...
No, Not Nolan.
The whole point of any kind of policing
is to do what I tell you.
Trust me, you don't want to
be good at community policing.
- Why?
- Once the higher-ups see it,
then running community meetings
will be all they will ever let you do.
Okay.
LAPD. Anyone in here?
What were they smoking?
Uh, it smells like burned
donuts from a plastic oven.
That's definitely meth.
And the pipe's still warm.
Keep your eyes open.
Mm-hmm.
Clear.
Aaah!
Are you okay?
Behind you!
- Hook him up.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
He got me good.
Forget what I said earlier.
Community meetings are
clearly all you're good for.
Trust me, there's gonna be
many times your child's first year
where you're gonna want
to rush to the Internet
to check out their symptoms.
Resist that urge.
- Yes?
- Um...
If the dad was doing drugs
when we... made my baby...
There's no evidence that a father's
addiction affects the baby.
Okay. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay. Now it's time to
introduce Officer Nolan.
John?
Yes.
Officer Nolan is gonna show you
how to properly install
an infant's car seat.
- Yes, I will.
- Yeah.
You can't... You can't do that?
No. I mean, pregnant mothers
feel more comfortable
when it comes from a police officer.
- Really?
- I mean, don't get me started.
Nine years to become a doctor
and they trust a handsome cop more?
Well, to be fair,
a handsome cop in a super-cool uniform.
Hi, guys.
I'm, uh, Officer Nolan, and, um, uh,
car seats are the safest way
to transport your
soon-to-be bundles of joy,
and... it's the law.
So, uh...
installation is super-simple.
We're gonna start with the base.
Guys, they make this
stuff just idiot-proof.
It's backwards.
And it's... it's... it's
...this is forwards,
which is, of course... is wrong,
'cause you want it backwards.
The baby has to face the...
Again, guys, idiot-proof.
So, simply take these security straps
and use the...
I think the
word that you're looking for
- is "latch."
- "Latch." Yes.
I'm so sorry. I have to take this call.
- It can't wait?
- It...
It really can't.
I'm... I'm... One...
Yes? Hey. How's it going?
- Um...
- No, no, I'm whispering
because I-I'm right in
the middle of a thing.
Right, no, no, you can just tell me.
- Get up.
- You can't be here.
- Get... Get up.
- No, you can't be here.
- Get up.
- The judge said.
- She's my kid, too.
- Hey, let her go.
Back off! This is between us!
Hold it. Get over. Give me your hands.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Thank you.
You're gonna need stitches.
Thanks.
Something on your mind?
No, ma'am.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
You're wrong about me.
Uh, no, I'm not.
I can do so much more than
just community meetings.
You're right. You're probably
really good at paperwork.
- But you can't fight.
- I can fight.
I've gone toe-to-toe with
plenty of suspects and won.
- Not that one.
- He's huge!
And yet, I took him and his buddy.
You want to hit me right
now, don't you?
Yeah, I see it in your eyes.
Someone a little more your size.
Well, come on.
What?
Hit me, Not Nolan.
That is an order.
- Hey...
- Do it for real!
Come for me like that
tweaker came for you!
Now!
Aah!
Stay down,
and get used to that position.
Because in case you didn't know,
you are not a 6'2", 180-pound man.
Now, Tim might be a good T.O.,
but he can't teach you
how to fight like a girl.
We get a higher show of
force, especially from men.
So, guess what, sweetheart?
You are always going to be tested,
and when you are alone
against a desperate suspect,
and you are between them and freedom,
your thoughts can never be,
"Oh, my, he's bigger than me."
Look here, Not Nolan,
if you're going to
survive these streets
as a 5'6" woman...
and one of color, no less...
you better learn what these
boys don't know to teach.
You ever think about
having another kid?
I did, for the first
three of four years
after Oliver was born.
Then what happened?
Then I spent too much
time in emergency rooms.
I don't have to tell you...
there's...
there's so much tragedy out there.
I just...
I can't bring another life into it.
Jess.
- Hey.
I-I-I couldn't get in touch with you,
so I called Grey,
and he said you were he...
Oh, my God. What happened?
Just a knife fight.
No big deal. Are you okay?
I'm gonna leave you two alone.
- It's nice seeing you again.
- Yes, yes, you, as well.
Thank you.
Uh...
I'm sorry it took so long.
I just, uh...
I needed to have some time...
to process.
No, okay. No, I get it, I see.
Um...
so, you're pregnant.
No, I'm not.
Okay.
O-Okay, yeah, that's great, too...
But I want to be.
I'm sorry,
you're gonna have to help me out,
here a little bit, Jessica.
I'm... I'm a little confused.
Yes, well, I was, too, at first.
And when I took the pregnancy test
and it came back
negative, I was just...
I was so disappointed.
And I-I-I couldn't shake it.
No, I... Okay. Um...
- It's just a little surprising.
- I know.
I was... I was surprised, too.
Look, I...
I never wanted to be a mom before.
But being with you...
it... it changed me.
You see the good in people.
You do the right thing,
even when it costs you.
I miss that part of myself.
Are... Are you...
against having another kid?
No. No. No, I ju... Um...
You're just throwing
a lot at me right now.
- I know, I know.
- And I'm not quite sure what to say.
Okay, then don't say anything.
- Okay? At least not yet.
- Right.
I've had the whole morning
to think about this,
and... now it's your turn.
We'll talk later.
Right. Good idea.
- Okay.
I am ahead of schedule.
I'm never ahead of schedule.
- You're good.
- Yes, I am.
You know, with my businesses
growing like crazy,
I actually think I need to hire
a security chief here in L.A.
I already have a job, Mingus.
But does it pay you a
quarter mill a year?
Not at the present, no.
I haven't even gotten to the perks yet.
Hey. Hey, hey.
Police! Move and you're dead.
What the hell are you doing?
This is my cousin, Lev.
I asked him to meet us here.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Yeah. What is her problem?
Only two more nuisance complaints.
We can knock them out once
we get back on the street.
You were right.
I should've followed your playbook
at the community meeting.
That was my bad.
So, uh, you got a challenge
coin from the governor.
- What's he like?
- You know what, Not Nolan,
I don't really do chit-chat.
Uh, okay. Uh, look.
Um...
I want to learn how to do
the job the way you do it.
Be like you.
No you don't.
Are you kidding?
Y-You're a decorated detective
with a storied undercover career,
not to mention the governor personally
gave you one of his challenge coins.
I mean, that's huge.
What's huge is the cost of
having a career like mine.
- What do you mean?
- Hopefully you never find out.
Because none of the commendations
or the promotions
or even the challenge coins
will ever make up for what I've lost.
So don't be me.
I don't even want to be me.
Are you sure you're
okay to keep working?
Officer Nolan.
What? Um... yes, sir. What did you say?
Your arm... you want to
take the rest of the day?
Oh, no. I'm... I'm... No, I'm fine.
Thank you, I'm good.
Alright.
Um, sir...
how long had you been a cop
when your daughter was born?
- Two years.
- What was that like,
having a baby at home
and being on patrol?
Long days at work, late nights at home.
Trying to master two
jobs at the same time.
It was hell.
Only good sleep I got was in the
back of my shop during lunch.
Yeah.
Yeah, but she was worth it.
Yeah, kids always are.
Why are you asking?
- No reason, sir.
- Mm-hmm. How's Jessica?
She's great, sir.
- Give her my best.
- I will.
Hey. Hey.
- I need your help.
- What's wrong?
I'm... I'm looking
for Officer Bradford.
He's out on patrol, son.
What's going on?
It's my mom. She's missing.
My mom went to borrow her cousin's car,
so we could get out of town,
but she never came back.
- When was this?
- Right after you all left.
Wait, that was hours ago.
- Have you spoken with your cousin?
- Yeah.
He said my mom never showed.
I-I tried calling, texting.
I'm telling you guys,
something happened.
We believe you, but now it's time
for you to be straight with us.
Okay. Does this have anything
to do with the people
who firebombed her car?
AJ, I know you're scared. I get it.
But you're not betraying
your mom's trust
by telling us what's going on.
Let us help her.
A few weeks back,
one of my mom's ex-boyfriends
started hounding her about being
a getaway driver in some
heist he was putting together.
- She agree to do it?
- Hell no.
My mom isn't about that life anymore.
She swore never to risk going back
to prison and not being there for me.
Okay, so she said no.
What'd the ex-boyfriend say?
He said he was gonna kill
me if she didn't do it.
That's why she pulled you off the team,
why she wanted to get
you out of the city...
to protect you.
What's the ex-boyfriend's name?
- Ian Shaunesy.
- So if he grabbed her,
it was to force her into
pulling the robbery.
Which means it's happening soon.
AJ, do you know what the target is?
No, all I know is that
it's happening downtown.
Alright. You guys get down there.
I'll get detectives on this.
Put a BOLO out on the
mom and the ex-boyfriend.
It's gonna be okay. Alright?
Outside of actually spotting
AJ's mother or her ex-boyfriend,
what exactly are we looking for?
Robbery targets.
There are a dozen banks
and payday lenders
between here and Flower.
So, how do we whittle it down?
Look for anything odd
or out of the ordinary.
Well, this is downtown L.A.
That describes everything.
- What's up? What's going on?
- Why are you patrolling downtown?
How do you know where we are?
I just saw you drive by.
We, uh, got intel on a
possible heist in the area.
- What's the target?
- Unknown.
I'm on 5th and Hill.
You just passed me,
working a security detail
on what could be a potential target.
Gotta be honest with you,
I wouldn't hate having an escort.
Excuse me. We need to leave now.
I am in the middle of a conversation.
No, you're at the end of it.
Say goodbye to the pretty lady.
- Hey, what...
- Come on.
Are you out of your mind?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Police!
Give up the damn case.
- What?
- You're insured.
Give up the damn case,
or they'll kill us.
No, your job is to
protect my merchandise.
My job is to keep you alive,
and I'm nine bullets from failing.
Give up the case!
Wait! Hold fire!
Let's go, let's go.
Cover me.
Open the door.
Open the door! Right now.
- Open it.
- Let's go!
Drop the guns!
Do it now!
Drop your guns right now!
Let's go, back up.
Back away from the car.
Get down on your knees.
Down on your knees! Spread your arms.
- You okay?
- I am now.
Step out of the car,
get your hands where I can see them.
Let's go.
They kidnapped me. Forced me into this.
I know. AJ told us everything.
But I got to place you under arrest,
until we work something
out with the D.A.
Put your hands up there.
- Is it safe?
- All clear.
Hey, hey, hey. No, no.
That's evidence now.
You'll have to come collect
it from the station,
after we process it.
- Can you do something?
- Nope.
And this marks the last stop
on our community policing tour.
Bradford and West are facing
off against heist crews,
and we are here to...?
To talk to a neighbor
about feeding squirrels.
Sorry.
Make it up to me by getting
a start on that paperwork.
What?
Sir, your neighbors are complaining
that you are feeding squirrels.
So what?
Los Angeles Municipal Code 53.06.5,
which says it is illegal
to feed wild animals.
Punishable by a fine of up to $1,000,
and/or six months' imprisonment.
They're squirrels.
Doesn't matter.
What happened to your hand?
It was a lawn mower. Are we done?
Yes, sir. Have a good one.
Hey, uh, so, should I mark that down
as being given a verbal warning?
No, run a background check.
You want to give me a hint
at what we're doing here?
The guy was missing two fingers.
Damage like that was caused
by an explosive device.
Maybe he was in the military.
He said it was a lawn mower.
Ernie Bosk.
Records check are negative
on any military or
law-enforcement service.
- You studied bombings in the Academy?
- Mm.
Did they cover the
UCLA bombings in 2009?
Yeah, of course.
They recovered an unexploded pipe bomb.
With a red hair inside of it.
You think that's him.
Well, we'll need a DNA
sample to be sure, but...
- Whoa, what are you doing?
- Getting a warrant.
We don't need one if we can get
a sample from his trash cans.
And I can search that
without a warrant.
Okay.
What happens if you get caught?
You know, if you're right,
this guy makes bombs.
You really want him
throwing one your way?
Not really.
Well, then you're gonna need
someone to distract him.
- Hi. How are you?
- What do you want?
Uh, to talk to you about the importance
of drought-resistant vegetation.
I know it's a boring topic,
but if you just give me three minutes,
I guarantee that I will
make it worth your while.
Uh, each year,
we waste millions of gallons of water
on plants and flowers
that are non-conducive
to Southern California's climate...
I'm gonna stop you right there.
I don't care.
Uh, uh, sir, please... Um,
could, could I have a glass of water?
I... I've been out all morning.
Maybe you should be
more drought-resistant.
Yes, sir.
The water?
Fine.
Sir? The water?
You a cop, too?
Uh, yeah.
That's my partner outside
conducting a lawful search,
so you just need to relax.
Harper, he's running!
- Hey.
- 7-Adam-15,
start me up another unit, 5611, Code 3.
Turn around.
Hands where I can see them.
What the hell was that?
Burglar alarm system.
I built it myself.
It's my own private DMZ.
There are pressure plates
all throughout the floor.
They're rigged to IEDs.
You take one wrong step,
they'll be cleaning you off
the ceiling with a squeegee.
- Chen!
- No.
Harper, don't come inside the house.
It's booby-trapped.
No, stay! Don't come in. It's rigged.
Where's Bosk?
In the back room.
He's arming a bomb, a big-ass bomb.
You got to get clear of the house,
radio the bomb squad,
and clear the neighborhood.
Mr. Bosk, you don't need to do this.
Why not?
I'm caught.
May as well go out with a bang.
How long ago did you rig the house?
Months? Years?
Almost a decade.
I've been waiting that long for cops,
to show up on my doorstep.
A decade.
Avoiding pressure plates.
Let go of the wire slowly.
Turn around. Hands behind your back.
Do it now!
Don't you want me to disarm
the bombs before you cuff me?
Nope.
My guess is you'd enter a code
that would set it all off.
So we're going out the window.
Hey.
Uh, house is still booby-trapped,
but he didn't finish rigging
the fertilizer bomb, so...
- Nice work.
- You got him?
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
- Alright.
- You gonna puke?
- No.
No. No.
Maybe.
How you doing?
Well, my hands stopped
shaking about 15 minutes ago.
That's a good sign, right?
Yep.
Oh, hey, um, I just wanted to say...
- thanks.
- You're welcome.
Sorry if I was such a... you know.
- Douche?
- Yeah.
Uh, but listen,
please come be my head of security.
I'll give you a 100K bonus.
No. It's not about the money.
All today did was remind me
how much I love being a cop.
All these officers,
including the two that
saved our bacon...
they're my family.
And I guess - I'm not ready to say bye.
However, I will take a
"save your life bonus"
if you're still feeling generous.
Hey.
Nice working with you today.
Yeah, you, too.
Look...
I was wrong to discourage you today.
Go as far as you want in this job.
You say you want to be a cop like
me, screw that.
Be better than me.
You got what it takes, Not Nolan.
I heard you call me
Chen back at the house.
I know you know my name.
Um... would it be alright
if I asked you for advice,
from time to time?
Sure.
Just not too often.
I don't want to mess up
the whole lone wolf persona
I got going on.
It's, um, presumptuous, I know,
but I was hoping - we'd
have cause to celebrate.
But we don't, do we?
I'm sorry.
And that's it?
There's...
There's no room for discussion?
Jessica, um...
I love being a father...
And... I would love to be a mom.
And I want that for you. I do.
But for me,
I'm not ready to be a father again.
Not just yet.
Okay.
What does that mean?
You're already through
the steepest part of your career,
but me, I'm...
I'm still just finding my footing.
And I gave up my first
path 20 years ago.
And I can't do that again.
But if you can just...
be patient with me,
we can come back to this
in a year, two years tops...
Years? No.
Yeah, Nolan, um...
it doesn't exactly -
work like that for women.
I mean, I can't... I can't just...
sit around and wait...
for the hopes that maybe
someday you'll be ready.
I would resent you.
And I would hate you.
I don't ever want that.
So, what does that mean?
I'm... I'm gonna go home.
And I'll come back tomorrow
for my stuff when you're not here.
Jess...
- There you go.
- Thanks.
You ready?
Hike!
- Attaboy!
- Nice!
- There you go!
- You know, AJ, back in high school,
I was ranked one of the top
quarterbacks in the state.
I could believe that.
The interceptions you threw me
were always perfect spirals.
So let's see - if you
still got the skills.
You and AJ versus me and the rook.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
Show 'em what you got, baby.
I always do, Mama.
Hey, uh, don't get your ankles
broke, old man.
Kid, I am 26. Don't play me.
Ooh, and you about - to get
dusted by a 14-year-old.
How sad is that?
LAPD has great medical coverage, right?
Yeah, yeah, very funny.
Real funny when you're gonna
be on the ground smashed.
Five-Mississippi.
Whoa! Old lady, huh?
Okay. Make it three.
- Hike!
- One, two, three.
You didn't say "Mississippi"!