JIMMY: And anything that already happened,
we're not going back over all that.
Let's just focus on from here on out.
Right. Past is past.
And moving forward...
If I have the urge to not tell you something,
then I've gotta tell you.
Right. Full disclosure.
And it works both ways.
Works both ways.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
And mute.
Okay, what if I have the urge
to not tell you something, but I tell you,
and you don't like what you hear?
I just wanna know what's going on.
- Yeah, but...
- Jimmy.
We'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
There he is.
So we're really doing this, huh?
Yeah, it looks that way.
- Am I late?
JIMMY: Nope.
Cool. Good morning.
- Thanks for coming.
- Good to see you.
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
Psst.
What's up?
Want me to hold the rings for you?
Oh, there's no rings.
Well, I can fix that easy.
I seen a clerk downstairs,
had a nice rock.
Probably about a half a karat.
Huell, no, I...
This is a different kind of thing.
Oh, it's like that.
Then we should do the right thing for the rugrat.
No, there's no rugrat.
Well, you at least gonna
take her somewhere after this.
Little honeymoon?
I got a friend who runs a B&B in Roswell,
get you a good deal.
How about we take a raincheck on that?
We just need to get this done. Feel me?
This is a legal arrangement.
This way, if I get into trouble,
they can't make her testify against me.
You getting hitched for that?
Yeah.
Yeah. That's all this is. You got it?
Is she gonna be a McGill or Goodman?
Wexler. I... I gotta go finish this.
Here you go.
KIM:
Thanks.
Sir, do you have documentation
of your two previous dissolutions?
Yeah.
Great. One sec.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
This okay with you?
Of course.
Yeah. I just mean, uh...
this might not be what you dreamed of
when you were 12.
Jimmy, it's not about that.
This is just, you know...
everything we talked about.
Right. Right. I know.
Just making sure.
CLERK:
All set. I just need 25 dollars.
I got it.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Been that kind of day.
[CLEARS THROAT]
So...
Wexler-McGill?
Yes.
- You picked the short vows, that right?
- Yes.
And you have your witnesses.
HUELL:
Mm-hm.
OFFICIANT:
Okay, then.
Here we go.
Oh.
Do you, James Morgan McGill,
take Kimberly Wexler...
Hmm. No middle name.
...to be your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health, till death do you part?
I do.
OFFICIANT:
And do you, Kimberly Wexler,
take James Morgan McGill
to be your lawfully wedded husband,
to have and to hold, from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
till death do you part?
- I do.
OFFICIANT: Mm-hm.
Do you have the rings?
- We, um...
- We didn't do that.
No rings.
Okey-dokey.
Then by the power vested in me
by the state of New Mexico,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss.
[CAMERA CLICKS]
Psst, psst.
[SOFTLY]
One more. One more.
[CAMERA CLICKS]
[♪♪♪]
JIMMY:
So lunch is definitely out?
Sorry, I just can't get away.
But I'll be home early tonight.
Me too.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
NACHO:
I've been calling you.
Yeah, I had a busy morning.
Go to lockup. Your client's waiting for you.
My client? What...?
Who got picked up this time?
Jorge De Guzman.
Who the hell is Jorge De Guzman?
Who do you think?
[DOOR OPENS]
WOMAN:
State v. Jorge De Guzman,
case CR2004003022.
Mr. De Guzman.
Murder in the first degree,
robbery while armed with a deadly weapon,
tampering with evidence, arson...
Your Honor, uh, my client waives
the reading of the remaining charges.
JUDGE:
How does he plead?
Not guilty. On all charges.
I'd like to schedule a pre-trial hearing in six weeks.
And I'm going to deny bond.
- Uh, Your Honor...
- That's my decision.
[GAVEL POUNDS]
RICH: Thank you for making time for us
on such short notice.
We wanted to tell you, face-to-face,
how much everyone in the firm regrets
what happened yesterday.
The situation in Tucumcari spiraled out of control,
and we take full responsibility.
Kevin, you chose me as your attorney,
and that was the best day of my professional life.
Yesterday was the worst day
of my professional life.
I can't tell you how much I regret
that I let you down.
But I want you to know
that if you choose
to move forward with me, and with us...
nothing like that will ever happen again.
No one's denying that things went off course,
but let's keep in mind that over the last 18 months,
we've opened 24 new branches.
And until Tucumcari, the legal work has been...
flawless.
Well...
Kim, you dropped the ball, that's for sure.
And, heh, with all your smarts,
whole office full of associates and fancy degrees...
you get rolled over by...
Well, you know what happened.
I expected more.
PAIGE:
Thanks for coming in.
Thank you, Kevin.
-Paige.
- Thank you.
Kim, ahem, one more thing.
This fellow, McGill, or Goodman, whatever...
You could do a whole lot better.
I'll say fifty-fifty. But we gave it a shot.
-Rich, we can't leave it like this.
- Oh, he'll stew for a bit.
-And then we'll see.
- And if he does stick with us?
- Then what? We walk on eggshells forever?
- Mmm.
What's our alternative?
[RICH STAMMERS]
-We counted at seven, right?
- Yes, but after the survey...
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Uh, sorry to interrupt, but do you mind
if we take just another minute of your time?
I guess.
Kevin, no matter what our relationship
looks like moving forward,
we owe you the truth.
And the truth is,
you ignored our advice.
Oh, so this is my fault?
KIM: We said Mesa Verde should reconsider
the site for the call center.
You declined.
We advised you to keep the purchase lot
as an investment.
You declined.
And we advised you to leave that meeting
when it became apparent
that the other side was negotiating in bad faith.
You declined.
At every point,
we gave you the best guidance we could,
and at every point, you chose to go your own way.
We are your attorneys,
and it is our job to advise you.
The decisions will always be yours,
but if you continue to ignore us...
then this is the wrong relationship.
And, Kevin, I have to tell you,
whoever represents you in the future...
I hope you're gonna listen to them a little bit better.
That it?
All right, then.
See you on Thursday.
Okay.
Well, uh...
I guess we'll get out of your hair.
Thursday.
[DOOR CLOSES]
"JMM." What's that?
- Oh, that's my motto.
- Yeah?
"Justice Matters Most."
Okay, brass tacks. Um...
How solid is this "De Guzman" thing?
Because if they find out
you're not who they think you are,
- that could be a little...
- It's not gonna be a problem.
Great.
Um, first up, we gotta get the murder rap
down to manslaughter.
Now I think that the DA's primed to cut a deal,
so I say, make them come to us, power move...
- No.
- No?
Nope. No deal.
- Here's the thing about going to trial...
- No, no, no.
No trial. No deal.
Okay, yeah, sure, it's just...
Well, what did you have in mind?
- You're gonna get me out on bail.
- Bail?
That's...
Well, the thing there...
I mean, I don't know how things work
south of the border,
but here, under these circumstances, uh,
well, that's a long shot.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
I'm sorry, I don't, uh...
You wanna be a friend of the cartel?
Hmm?
Time to get yourself a new motto.
Just.
Make.
Money.
MIKE: "'But what does that mean, 'ephemeral'?
repeated the Little Prince,
who never in his life let go of a question
once he had asked it.
'It means,
which is in danger of speedy disappearance.'
'Is my flower in danger of speedy disappearance?'
'It certainly is.'"
Hmm.
Okay, kid, we'll finish the rest later.
Now, good night.
Not yet, Pop-Pop.
Just two more pages?
Two more pages, that's it.
All right, now lie down.
"'My flower is ephemeral, '
the Little Prince said to himself,
'and she only has four thorns
to defend herself against the world...'"
She's out.
I think The Little Prince did the trick.
I think you wore her out with all that hide-and-seek.
I don't know, I think maybe she wore me out.
This girl at work,
she can't get her son to sleep.
The kid's 2 years old and he's still tearing
around the house at midnight.
MIKE:
Hmm.
Matty was like that.
Really?
Yeah. Really.
Never wanted to conk out.
Too busy.
He was such a cutie.
I love those pictures of him sitting on Santa's lap.
- Oh, that face.
- Mm-hm.
Cried his eyes out.
Every year.
And every year, he'd wanna try it again.
I'm better now.
What changed?
Decided to play the cards I was dealt.
Just decided he'll see us
at the regular Thursday meeting.
You spoke truth to power.
We'll see if he sticks to it.
How'd your day go?
I got married.
Yeah.
[CHUCKLING]
What?
[KIM MOANING]
I'm having the urge not to tell you something.
It's nothing. I'll... I'll tell you later, okay?
[KIM CHUCKLES]
Jimmy, wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
What?
Um...
I have a new client. He's, uh, connected.
I mean, he's a cartel guy. From Mexico.
Pretty high up.
Anyway, he's in for murder,
and he wants bail, which...
That's impossible.
I mean...
no way in hell this dude is ever seeing sunshine,
but if I could, you know, somehow find a way...
um, he said I'd be a friend of the cartel.
"Friend of the cartel"?
You know what that means?
It means money.
"Ranch in Montana" kind of money.
Like, uh, "private jet" kind of money.
Press conferences, TV news, the works.
But do you want to be a friend of the cartel?
No.
Absolutely not, I...
Anyway, it's a moot point.
Because the guy is the definition of a flight risk.
So, look, I'm gonna put up a fight, right?
Just for show.
There's no judge on Earth
who's gonna grant him bail.
I just... I didn't wanna tell you.
So I thought I should tell you.
You know what?
What?
I'm glad you did.
Oh?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey.
No, no, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
So, what's happening with 6th Street?
Mm-hm.
And the take?
Okay.
So, what are you gonna do about it?
Are you gonna send in Ocho Loco?
Oh. Even better. Nice.
Listen.
I got something for you to do.
I'm not telling you shit until we talk about my dad.
What you tell me
and when you say it is not up to you.
Listen, you said, when Lalo's out of the picture,
we'll talk about my father, right?
Well, he's out of the picture.
[MIKE SIGHS]
MIKE: Say your piece.
- I'm done.
I want out.
MIKE:
And you want me to square it with Fring.
NACHO:
Fring's not all of it, it's the cartel.
I disappear, they're gonna go after my father.
He's gotta come with me.
But no matter what I say,
with him, it's the cops or nothing.
The cops won't solve this.
You got a way?
Hm.
What are you holding out?
Lalo called me from inside.
He put me back in charge.
And?
And...
he wants me to burn down Pollos Hermanos.
Then he's not out of the picture, is he?
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
CLEO:
The Avocado Mania promotion,
which we've been testing in select franchises,
has been a smashing success,
contributing to an 18 percent increase in foot traffic
at participating locations
and a 12 percent bump in customer satisfaction.
We know a good thing when we see it.
So we are planning
to fully roll out Avocado Mania in Q2.
Additionally, our family fun remodel improved
the in-store Whiskerstay's experience,
resulting in increased repeat business
system-wide.
In fact, we are happy to share the news
that the latest ACSI survey
now places Whiskerstay's
in the top 10 percent
of limited-service chains nationwide.
SCHULER:
Very nice, Cleo.
Very nice. Thank you.
And now, let's hear from Gustavo Fring
of Los Pollos Hermanos.
- Thank you, Herr Schuler.
- Bitte.
I am delighted to report that the last quarter,
Los Pollos Hermanos revenues
have increased 8.3 percent.
Comparable restaurant sales
increased by 4.2 percent.
Representing the eighth consecutive quarter
of comparable sales increases.
[DOOR OPENS]
In addition to our continued focus
on our core menu,
we are very proud to introduce a new offering
that will extend our product line
while celebrating
our traditional New Mexican culture.
I invite you to taste our delicious Spice Curls.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
The curly fry with the Southwestern kick.
[APPLAUSE]
MAN:
Here we are.
[DOOR CLOSES]
The bathroom has heated floors.
You'll find the dial just under the light switch.
There's a steam shower.
And bidet.
This controls the drapes.
Many of our guests have enjoyed the rodeo.
It's in town tomorrow, Reliance Stadium.
I highly recommend it.
Oh, thank you. I'm only staying the night.
Next time, then.
Is there anything else, sir?
No. No, no, that will be all.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you, Mr. Fring.
- My pleasure.
[♪♪♪]
LYDIA: Peter. Look who's here.
- Hm? Oh?
- Hello, my friend.
- Oh.
Gustavo.
Always good to see you, my friend.
Oh, you look well.
Well...
I don't feel well.
Maybe things will improve, now that you're here.
Lydia tells me Salamanca is in jail.
This means you can continue construction?
Eduardo Salamanca has been arrested
for murder.
- Uh-huh.
- However, even from jail, he creates...
issues.
What kind of issues?
He ordered his men
to burn down one of my restaurants.
You're kidding. He's in jail. He can still do that?
I'm afraid so.
I know it's not exactly my area of expertise,
but don't people get killed in prison all the time?
I mean, shanked and shivved, and whatnot.
Anything happens to Salamanca
on this side of the border,
the cartel will assume that it was my doing.
It would mean war.
War for which we are unprepared.
SCHULER:
My God.
- This nightmare never ends.
- He's concerned about the money.
Concerned?
Four million eight hundred thousand euros.
It's a miracle I haven't been caught.
Last year, the auditors came this close.
One of them, a woman, I think she knew.
- Peter...
- At first it was a year.
Then it was two. Then, three.
And now you're telling me, how long?
I can't. I can't.
- They will catch me. And then it is over.
GUS: Peter.
- I can't.
- Peter.
Gustavo, please. I can't.
Listen to me.
Do you remember Santiago?
The two of us. Our backs to the wall.
I will never forget what you did.
You are still the same man.
You will do what is necessary.
You stay strong, my friend.
We have come so far.
We are so very close.
Okay.
Good.
Now, you eat.
LYDIA:
Tomorrow, you and I are going to the rodeo.
SCHULER: The rodeo?
LYDIA: Yeah.
To see the cowboys.
SCHULER:
I've never been to a rodeo.
LYDIA:
Well, you're going to love it.
Gustavo?
SCHULER:
Prosit.
LYDIA: Prosit.
- Prost.
[LYDIA CHUCKLES]
Uh, "Your guest will relax
in the elegant great room,
complete with soaring stone fireplace."
- Soaring stone?
- Yeah, that's the best kind of stone.
How about a lavender farm?
Seriously?
Yeah, well, it's lavender-adjacent.
Tell me more.
"Imagine a magical land called home.
Watch the sunset across your own private meadow
as wildflowers sway in the breeze.
This stunning desert retreat promotes
a casual yet luxurious lifestyle."
I'm casual yet luxurious.
Yeah. Totally.
It's got a five-car garage.
KIM:
What? How's that gonna work?
- We only get two-and-a-half cars each?
JIMMY: Yeah. Garbage.
Ha-ha. So that was wildflowers dancing in the sun?
- They're swaying in the breeze.
- Oh.
Okay. Well, either way.
They're having a very nice time.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
MIKE [OVER PHONE]:
I need a word.
Oh. A word? Yeah. Yeah, I have a word for you.
"Tunnel." Which is where I am right now.
Sorry, I can't hear you. Maybe try again later?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Coming.
[MIMICKING PHONE STATIC]
[IMITATING MIKE] Whatever it is, it's not for me.
But it should be for you.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Hey, forget your key...?
Oh.
Okay, yeah, come right in.
Make yourself at home.
You got me in my underwear, so enjoy the show.
You're representing Eduardo Salamanca,
aka Jorge De Guzman?
Yeah, he's a client of mine. Yeah. So?
Well, I need you to get him out on bail.
Wait, what do you have to do
with Lalo Salamanca?
I represent someone who has an interest.
Someone like who?
Someone your client can never know about.
Yeah, look, I don't take marching orders
from the man behind the curtain.
Mm? In this case, it's better that you do.
You know what Salamanca did, right?
I am aware.
What's this?
This is everything you need...
to do your job.
[CREAKING NOISES]
[♪♪♪]
[GAS HISSING]
[GAS CONTINUES HISSING]
[SOFTLY]
Go.
[CAR ALARM WAILING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Significant ties to his local community? What ties?
Did you actually think I wasn't gonna hear
about this private eye of yours?
- Excuse me?
- Dave Clark.
Dave Clark. The mysterious third party
who's coaching your key witness.
All right, good. You know what?
Do the dumb act for Parson. Please.
I can't wait to see him rip you both a new one.
Any idea what that asshole is going on about?
I'll call the librarian.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
Uh, play to the judge, okay?
But don't... Don't "play" to the judge. Don't overdo it.
Try not to be too cool. I mean, look humble.
A little bit scared.
No problem.
- Is that them?
- Yep.
Who's that?
[SOFTLY]
It's gotta be his family.
- Fred Whalen.
- Hm.
- The guy who died at the Travel Wire.
- Mm.
[JUDGE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
JUDGE:
Mr. Goodman?
Mr. Goodman.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
That's right, Your Honor. Witness tampering.
I have reason to believe
that the prosecution's key witness was coached
by a private investigator
who was hired to pervert justice.
Does the prosecution have a response?
Unfortunately, Your Honor,
it seems a person unknown to my team
may have interacted with our witness,
causing her to call Detective Roberts
and amend her statement
two months after the initial interview.
This only recently came to our attention,
and we are vigorously investigating.
I would hope so.
Having said that, Your Honor, this witness
is one small element of the state's case.
In light of the extraordinary violence of the crime
and the fact that Mr. De Guzman is
a foreign national with no ties to the community,
we ask that the Court recognize him as a flight risk
and as a danger to the citizens of New Mexico.
JUDGE:
Mr. Goodman?
Uh, all due respect, Your Honor,
but the witness is not just one small element
of the state's case,
she's the only witness tying Mr. De Guzman
to the murder scene.
And she's been manipulated.
Furthermore, the claim that Mr. De Guzman
has no ties to the community,
that's just patently false.
Mr. De Guzman has deep ties
to the city of Albuquerque.
I'd like you to meet his family.
That's his fiancée
and the love of his life, Beth McKinnon.
His stepchildren, Christopher and Ella.
And sitting with them is Beth's mother, Mary.
Now, Your Honor,
my client is the only father
that these kids have ever known.
They depend on him.
How can you possibly see fit
to separate this beautiful family?
Um...
I'm sorry.
The testimony, uh, implicating Mr. De Guzman
in this crime,
it's been fabricated.
You've already held him for three days.
Given the circumstances,
Mr. De Guzman should be granted bond.
Your Honor, a sidebar?
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
ADA GINA: Your Honor, I really...
JUDGE: Sit.
I accept the defense's argument
that bond is warranted.
But considering the severity of the charges,
I will set the amount at 7 million.
- Cash only.
- Oh, Your Honor...
[GAVEL BANGS]
All rise.
Seven million.
Listen, I am so, so sorry.
I can do that.
The thing is...
- I'm gonna need you to pick it up.
- What, me?
Mm-hm. I'll call you.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
HOWARD:
Hey, Jimmy.
Howard.
So, have you thought any more about the job?
The job. Yeah.
No, um...
I'm still giving it some thought.
Giving it some thought?
Yeah.
You know what? Don't bother.
It seems I've upset you. So offer's off the table.
You upset me... How'd you upset me?
You tell me.
This is getting a little weird, Howard.
You wanna know what's weird?
It's weird to offer a job to a man,
and in return,
have bowling balls thrown at your car.
And prostitutes sent to your business lunch.
That's weird.
[JIMMY SCOFFS]
Are you listening to yourself?
Ahem, I don't know
what you're into these days, Howard, but, heh...
prostitutes and bowling balls?
You sound unhinged.
Jimmy, I'm sorry you're in pain.
You're sorry.
You're sorry?
You killed my brother, and you say you're sorry?
Let me tell you something.
The job offer, it didn't upset me.
It amused me.
Ooh, big job at the illustrious HHM.
A chance to play at the palace. Little old me?
- I was trying...
- You have no idea what's going on.
You're a teensy, tiny man
in a teensy-weensy, little bubble.
- Oh, Jimmy.
- Oh, don't you fucking "Oh, Jimmy" me.
You look down on me? You pity me?
Walk away. That's right, Howard.
You know why I didn't take the job?
Because it's too small!
I don't care about it!
It's nothing to me! It's a bacterium!
I travel in worlds you can't even imagine!
You can't conceive of what I'm capable of!
I'm so far beyond you!
I'm like a god in human clothing!
Lightning bolts shoot from my fingertips!
[♪♪♪]