Why are you in the North?
To protect my family's interests.
Following Gustavo's men?
Spying on him?
And this business
at Travel Wire. Messy.
This is not how we conduct ourselves
this side of the border.
Look. I apologize.
It's my uncle's influence.
You know what Hector's like.
So suspicious, so unreasonable.
Hector has this crazy idea
in his head
that somehow, the chicken man...
might carry a grudge, after he shot
Fring's boyfriend in the head.
You don't understand Gustavo.
With him, it's all business.
All business?
Like what happened in Santiago?
Was that business, too?
I need to know
that this is done with.
You trust Fring?
He'll never be one of us,
but he earns.
As long as he brings in the dollars,
Eladio is happy.
That's all that matters.
Then there's nothing more to say.
- Give my best to your uncle.
- I will.