Is everything okay?
Yes. Of course.
Can I come in?
It's okay?
It's fine.
Can I get you anything?
Want a coffee?
So big.
And new.
How are you, Papa?
Gutierrez made me an offer.
He wants to buy the shop.
Really?
Don't tell me.
Does he want to turn it into another tire shop?
He wants to keep it as is.
But...
he offered more than it's worth
even with the land.
What are you going to do?
I always thought I was
keeping the shop for you.
Are you going to work 11 hours a day
for the rest of your life?
What do you think?
It sounds like a good deal.
Could be...
your chance to retire.
This is you, isn't it?
I don't know what you mean.
You put Gutierrez up to this.
This is your money he's offering me.
This is you trying to get me to leave town.
You want to run.
You want me to run too.
Deny it.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Look me in the eyes.
I've told you what you should do.
Give this up.
Go to the police.
Face what you've done.
If you want to run, run.
But me?
No way, I will not run away.
This dude. Good idea.