I replaced the stolen product.
Some went to your organization.
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
That explains everything.
As long as Salamanca is
on this side of the border,
we cannot continue as we were.
You keep your goddamn retainer.
Nonviolent felonies, 50% off.
I just can't see it.
♪♪
Next!
JIMMY: How about, uh, special discounts?
Um, for the next, uh, two weeks,
um, non-violent felonies 50% off.
- [MOTORCYCLE ENGINE RUMBLING]
- Yeah.
Okay.
- I'll take one.
- Yeah? That's for you.
50% off. Yeah. Alright.
Now we got some takers.
There you are. Oh, yeah?
Who else? 50% off.
There you are.
50% off.
- Dude, that's almost half.
- [CHUCKLES]
[CHAI'S "THIS IS CHAI" PLAYS]
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SCREECH]
♪♪
[INHALING DEEPLY]
[ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- ♪ Don't kidding me ♪
Ahh! Oh, my God!
♪ C-H-A-I, CHAI ♪
- Hey! You bastards!
- Whoo!
♪ We are CHAI ♪
- 50% off!
♪ C-H-A-I, CHAI ♪
[LAUGHS]
♪ We are CHAI ♪
Money, money, money!
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SCREECH]
♪♪
Yeah!
Aah!
♪♪
- ♪ C-H-A-I, CHAI ♪
- [TIRES SCREECH]
♪♪
Oh! [LAUGHING]
♪ C-H-A-I ♪
♪♪
Aah!
Aah.
Ah! Yeah!
- I got my buddy!
- Yeah!
♪ We are CHAI ♪
Mwah!
[LAUGHS]
Hyah!
[DOG BARKING]
Aah!
Come on!
♪ We are CHAI ♪
Get back here, you little shits!
♪♪
Aah!
I'm okay! [LAUGHS]
[ALARM BLARING]
- 50% off!
[BOTH LAUGH]
♪♪
[TIRES SCREECH]
♪ C-H-A-I, CHAI ♪
♪♪
♪ C-H-A-I ♪
- ♪ CHAI ♪
- Whoo!
♪ C-H-A-I ♪
Whoo!
♪ CHAI ♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[DOG BARKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNORES]
[GASPING] Yo.
Unh. Ahh!
- Ah. Yo.
- What?
- Dude.
What day is it?
Uh...
Tuesday?
- What?
- You know what that means?
- 50% off!
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- [ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
MAN: ... and have you
smoke-free in just seven days.
It's all-natural and nicotine-free.
And best of all, it's guaranteed to work
or your money back.
Order now to get Smoke
Away's new oral spray free.
Spray Away... it can stop
your cravings instantly.
Call now.
Thousands have already quit
smoking using Smoke Away.
Sh...
[FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
♪♪
[SCREAMING]
Baby, what's happening?
Aah! What's happening?!
♪♪
Get off me, man.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[CRYING]
It's okay.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
NACHO: Come on, man.
What's he want from me?
I switched the stuff. I
played it all like he told me.
♪♪
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
No.
♪♪
What are we doin'?
[GUN CLICKS]
Come on, man. Don't.
We got five people in there.
- Too bad.
- [VEHICLE DOOR OPENS]
Wait. Hey, wait. Wait.
Hey. Hey, wait! Wait!
Hey, wait!
- Why's he doin' this?
- [VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
Hey, why's he doin'
this? I did everything.
Wait.
Please, man. Please, man.
Please, no. Please, no.
Please.
Hey, please.
Please, man.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS]
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
Okay.
I get it.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
Lalo Salamanca.
I need to know where he is going.
What he is thinking.
What he is planning.
I need to know what he's
going to do before he does it.
I've been trying.
Okay?
He doesn't tell me shit.
He just keeps talking about
some guy named Werner Ziegler
and some gringo Michael.
That's it.
Gain his confidence.
Make him rely on you.
How?
Find a way.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
My father has nothing to do with this.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'll find a way. I'll make him trust me.
Okay?
[CONVERSATIONS IN SPANISH]
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS]
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
Pop's a nice guy.
[ENGINE STARTS]
JIMMY: Yeah. Uh-huh. Sure.
[CLEARS THROAT] Let me
see if I have this right.
Uh, a Mr. Bertram Moran, AKA "B-Mo",
claims that you solicited
him for the purchase of narcotics
when, in fact, you were simply
enjoying a Big Gulp in the park
when he approached and
attempted to sell to you.
Oh! I got a live one.
Yes, PJ. Go ahead.
Kim, sorry. My side is too full.
I'm gonna take some of
those back to Mrs. Nguyen's.
[HANGERS CLICKING]
Uh-huh.
Well, I think I got the specifics.
- [SIGHS]
- I'll call you later.
Geez. Chatty one.
So, uh, hey, how's it going
with, uh, "Cold Finger",
the mini-fridge mastermind?
You get a trial date yet?
Uh, no.
He took the deal.
He took the five months?
Yup.
- Well, you were right, as usual.
- [CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[CHUCKLES]
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
Yes, Miss, I... Uh-huh.
[CHUCKLING] Oh, no.
Well, that's not right.
Yeah. Go on.
[BAG ZIPS]
C-Could you hold for a moment?
Kim, how about dinner
and a movie tonight?
I'm... Scampi and Scorsese
'cause they got "After Hours"
on the Classic Movie Channel.
I love that one, but,
um, we'll have to see.
I might need to stay late.
Okay. Just let me know.
Yeah. I'll see ya.
[KEYS JINGLE]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Yeah, so, go ahead.
Something about a minivan?
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
- Kim. Jimmy, what are you...
- There's something I got to show you.
It's just three blocks from here.
- Look, I...
- [CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[CHUCKLES, SIGHS]
I know you got to get to work.
This'll only take a couple minutes.
Please. D-Drive.
If we go right now,
it'll be over like that.
Which way?
Take a right.
- There. Right there.
- The white one?
Yeah. That one right there.
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
Jimmy, we're not buying a house.
Maybe not today, but it
doesn't hurt to look, does it?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I drove by this place like
a week ago, and I'm curious.
Aren't you, just a little?
Look at all that space.
Hey, you're doin' great.
I'm gonna be doin' great.
I got 45 clients.
45? How are you gonna handle all that?
I got a system. But can we just look?
They're not even open yet.
Yeah, well...
They want to sell this
house. They'll let us in.
[SIGHS]
Alright.
[SEAT BELTS CLICK]
Hey, folks.
Do you mind signing in?
There's a guest book right over here.
[SIGHS] You know what?
Um, could we do that on our way out?
Sure. Yeah.
Just take your time. Have a look around.
Let me know if you have any questions.
- You got it.
- Thanks.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Man, look at all this wall space.
Imagine a plasma TV mounted right there,
one of the huge new ones.
This would be a big change,
but we could make it our own.
We could host movie nights.
Some comfy chairs and
smell of popcorn in the air
and... and...
check out these countertops.
Yeah.
Blue. Is this quartz?
I-I read somewhere that
it's good for healing.
KIM: Mm, so good for healing.
[SIGHS]
Hey, you know that, uh, 50%-off
thing I said I wouldn't do?
Well, I did it.
I, um, told a few potential clients.
It just kind of slipped out.
And don't worry. I know these people.
They're not gonna do anything
'cause of some stupid discount.
But it was a bonehead move,
and I shouldn't have done it.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
[SIGHING]
Jimmy, I know you were
trying to help, but...
I don't want to lie to my clients.
You're talking about the fridge guy?
That... That was a dumb idea.
I mean all my clients.
Of course. Absolutely.
Never again.
[CHUCKLING] Oh, my God.
This is the closet of your dreams.
Our dreams.
Sure.
[IMITATING ECHOING]
Where are my Louboutins,
- Louboutins, Louboutins?
- [CHUCKLES]
Hey. Check this out.
Oh, there's jets, too.
Yeah, it's like a mini-spa.
That'd be so nice after
a long day on our feet.
Yeah. And two sinks, so
plenty of room for brushing.
And spitting.
JIMMY: Hey, you got to see this.
I mean, look at all the nozzles.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
Is that what I think it is?
Uh, steam?
But, uh, how do you get it going?
JIMMY: Maybe the water's shut off.
Maybe.
- [LAUGHS]
- Hey!
Aw. Quit it.
[CHUCKLES] You're very mature.
Very mature.
Aah!
Thanks again.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Nice house, huh?
Yeah.
Maybe someday.
[CAR DOORS OPEN]
[CAR DOORS CLOSE]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS,
SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
♪♪
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Excuse me, Mr. Salamanca.
Uh, would you give
your uncle some of this?
It's Fizzy K. He needs to hydrate.
Fizzy K?
It's just a vitamin solution.
It's Very-Berry, his favorite.
Right, Hector?
Thanks. I'll make sure he drinks it.
Thank you.
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
♪♪
- [LIQUID SLOSHES]
- [CHUCKLES]
♪♪
[LIQUID POURING]
[SNIFFS]
♪♪
[SIGHS]
[BELL DINGS]
[BELL DINGING]
[CHUCKLES]
[GROANS]
♪♪
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GROANS]
[RINGING STOPS]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[SIGHS]
[CANS CLATTERING]
Yeah?
STACEY: Mike, hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
No, no bother, honey. What's up?
I don't know what your work
schedule is like these days.
I'm still making my own hours.
Well, I just got called in.
Emily's busy, and...
No problem.
Are you sure?
Positive. I'll be happy to watch her.
What time do you need me there?
How about now?
Now.
On the way.
Oh, thanks, Mike. You're a lifesaver.
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hey!
I thought we'd finish fixing
the ladder on the tree house.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Pop-pop!
Hey, kid.
She needs to finish her homework first.
Don't let her sweet-talk you.
Oh, not a chance of that.
She's gotta learn her times tables.
She's on the sevens.
Sevens?
There's lasagna in the oven,
and I should be back before bedtime.
Sounds good.
See you later, sweetie!
Bye, Mom!
Bye. [GROANS]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
What do we got?
Sevens are the worst.
Ahh.
I bet you know more
than you think you know.
- I do?
- Mm-hmm.
You remember when we
watched the Super Bowl?
MIKE: 7 times 3?
KAYLEE: 21.
Alright. 7 times 4?
4 touchdowns equals 28.
- Mm-hmm.
- Plus another one makes 35.
Go, Eagles! Kick ass!
You don't talk like that.
Who taught you to talk like that?
- You did.
- Oh.
[GRUMBLES]
Come on. 7 times 8.
Uh... that's a lot of touchdowns.
It's a lot of touchdowns.
It's a big game.
Where we at?
55?
Oh. So you think the kicker
missed the extra point.
Oh, no. It's 56.
- [CHUCKLES]
- 7 times 8 is 56.
- You got it.
- [CHUCKLES]
My dad liked the Eagles, right?
Yeah. He sure did.
Was... Was he good at math?
Thank you.
Yeah, he, uh...
Your daddy was a smart kid,
a good student like you.
Did he want to be a policeman
when he was my age?
When he was your age.
You know, I think he went back
and forth between an astronaut,
deep-sea explorer...
like Jacques Cousteau.
Who?
You don't know Jacques Cousteau?
Mnh-mnh.
Well, we'll fix that.
So, instead my dad decided
to be a policeman, like you.
Yeah.
You make sure those are nice and even.
And he was a really
good policeman, right?
Yes.
And you taught him.
Uh-huh.
But... the bad guys got him?
I told you to make those even.
- I am.
- No, you're not!
You're making a mess!
You either do it right
or you don't do it.
But I want to do it.
You're done. You are done!
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
- Hey.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Where's Kaylee?
She's in her room. She won't come out.
She didn't eat dinner.
Why? What... What happened?
Mike!
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[BEATS & RHYMES' "CLEAN
GROOVE MIX" PLAYING]
♪ Yo, well, I'm outta control
but never out of my zone ♪
♪ Take it down in my phone
before I'm outta my home ♪
♪ I'm the life of the
party everywhere I go ♪
♪ And they expect me to
glow, so I got to be cold ♪
♪ Like a baseball, shorty,
I just got to be thrown ♪
[LAUGHING]
♪ I ain't worried about beef ♪
So? Two?
Gonna be a 10 tonight.
- [LAUGHS]
- 10?
Yeah.
♪ I don't care what they were saying ♪
♪ I ain't wanting to know ♪
♪ I know hating's real bad
for your arteries, though ♪
♪ Every party we go, everybody we know ♪
[RAPPING INDISTINCTLY]
♪ You the lamest but you had
to be the cockiest, though ♪
♪ You're gonna play with
it all the time, dawg ♪
♪ Gonna play with it,
goin' wild, y'all ♪
♪ Yes, yes, y'all ♪
[RAPPING INDISTINCTLY]
♪♪
♪ From the hardest of streets,
them guys put me to sleep ♪
[BANGING]
Hey! Why you doing that?
Where's the cookie?
I sent it down.
Well, it ain't here.
- Yeah, it is.
- What up?
- No stuff.
- No stuff?
It's there!
No, it ain't!
Quit that, fool!
Who you callin' fool, fool?!
Don't make me come down there.
- Ohh!
Stop playin'.
Oh, you better come down here.
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
Shut up!
[POKER CHIPS CLINK]
[CAN OPENS]
Call.
[SIGHS]
Fairground spot's doing really good.
Lots of traffic.
Hey.
Shut up while I'm in a hand.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
You know what?
$200.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Oh, man.
It's too deep for me.
- [LAUGHS]
- Oof.
Ugh. Ah, did I get you?
Let me see what you had.
You had a set?
- Mm.
- [SIGHS]
You had three 8s on the
turn and you don't raise?
And then you fold at the river?
Too bad.
Ocho loco, this guy, huh?
- [LAUGHTER]
- MAN: Ocho loco.
Alright, guys, give me your cards.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Sorry.
Yeah?
Hold up.
Problem on Fifth Street,
some skells saying they
didn't get their stuff.
It's your crew.
[CARDS FLUTTER]
Off you go. Ocho Loco.
[LAUGHTER]
Alright.
[RAPPING] ♪ I go harder, they ball ♪
♪ I ball harder, they move ♪
♪ I move smart ♪
[RAPPING INDISTINCTLY]
♪♪
Yo. Maybe we could shoot
the pipe, like, with a gun.
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, we ain't shooting nothin'.
Oh, okay. Well, we paid for our shit,
so we're getting our shit.
Yeah. Where's our glass?
Uh-uh!
- We gonna kick your ass!
- Uh-uh!
- Yo, give me the mic...
- Mic!
- ... so I can rap about this pipe.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
[RAPPING] ♪ Yo, my name is Mr. Sticky ♪
♪ I'm pretty frickin' tricky,
gonna kick you in the thicky ♪
What does that even mean?
♪ 'Cause I'm Mr. Thicky
and I'm so tricky ♪
♪ Yo, yo, ya thicky ♪
- Whoa. Whoa.
- Whoa. Oh, shit.
- Hey, we're still gettin' our glass, right?
- Yo, Domingo!
[SIREN CHIRPS]
♪♪
Hey.
[MUSIC STOPS]
This your vehicle?
Uh, no, sir.
Wanna come down here?
No problem, Officer.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Whatcha doin' up there?
Uh, just fixin' the drainpipe.
Some kinda block.
[KNOCK ON PIPE]
Guess you fixed it.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Only Domingo got picked up?
Yeah.
The rest of us bounced,
but he was stuck up there.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[KNOCK ON WINDOW]
Shit. Whole block's crawling.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
You got the stuff?
You got it?
Nah.
I-I had to leave it.
They were on my ass.
Ay.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Shit's gone now.
These assholes are gonna turn
the whole place upside down.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
How much is in there?
Almost a full load.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
Wait. Wait. Where you goin'?
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- [SPEAKING SPANISH]
♪♪
Ahh.
There he is.
Ooh. [LAUGHS]
No.
No, no, no, no.
Oh!
Look at that. [LAUGHS]
He's a fool, right? [LAUGHS]
Oh.
♪♪
Oh, oh.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT TALKING]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
OFFICER: Police! Open up!
Got a fortified door. Need to breach.
- [GRUNTS]
- [POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
♪♪
Police!
Clear!
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Did they get him?
- They musta g...
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LAUGHS]
Ignacio Varga...
[ENGINE STARTS]
JIMMY: Suzanne.
Oh! Suzanne.
Suzanne, I think we
have something in common.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Suzanne, I think we
have something in common.
Bill!
Bill.
What?
Am I on "Candid Camera" again?
No, but, by the way, you looked great.
We gotta talk Bruno Leder.
Leder? Lost cause.
- Ah, beg to differ.
- He assaulted a minor.
That oaf? You call him a
minor, I call him a menace.
Hey, my featherweight was
simply defending himself
against your raging bull.
No sale. Leder's doing the full freight.
Welcome back to the law, McGill.
It's Goodman. And you'll be back.
[DOOR CLOSES]
- Hannah-Banana.
- Hi.
Hey. What's the word on
moving Tripp to Thursday?
Mm, it works on the calendar.
- I just have to check with the other side.
- Eh, consider 'em checked.
Veronica. [WHISTLES]
Hey, you got something for me?
♪♪
Muchas gracias. Alright, let's see.
Long sleeves covering the
tats. That's excellent.
And pull your hair back
and lose the hardware.
Her Honor doth protest a chin pillar.
But it's gonna close up.
Into every life a little rain must fall.
Meet me outside Courtroom 103 at 2:15.
Mitch, uh, what say you to
moving Tripp to Thursday?
- Mm, Thursday works.
- Great! Thursday.
♪♪
What did you do?
I don't know. What did I do?
Suddenly Leder has witnesses?
Oh, what can I say? People step up.
From the sewer?
Life's rich pageant.
Who are we to judge?
Anyway, they saw what they saw...
your beefy, if youthful, hooligan
cold-cock my small potato.
So, what do you say,
uh, sentence suspended,
6 months probation, 70
hours community service?
Yeah, I guess.
That's the spirit.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
♪♪
[SIGHS] So... Uh.
Suzanne, I think we
have something in common.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Suzanne, I...
Jimmy.
Howard. Hey.
Congratulations. You're
back in the saddle.
Yeah.
So...
Saul Goodman?
Yeah. That's me.
How's business?
It's good. It's very good. You?
Actually, it looks like it's gonna
be one of our best years ever.
I was wondering,
any chance you're available
for lunch sometime?
Lunch. Lunch? Really?
Yeah. Oh, have Julie call my people.
I'm in the book. See ya, Howard.
[SIGHS] Suzanne, I think we
have a few things in common.
Oh, I hope not.
Oh, we do, to the tune of 16 cases.
So, you're busy. I'm busy.
How 'bout we do a lightning round?
We'll settle these puppies, 20 minutes.
Don't you already have an
appointment with me on the books?
Yeah. Next Tuesday.
But, you know, let's
get it done right now.
How about we wait till next Tuesday?
My clients need answers.
Look, hey, you've got a problem with me?
That's fine. Don't take
it out on my clients.
This isn't about your clients.
- This is about your wallet.
- [ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
- Hey, slow down.
- You're looking for turnover.
You want to churn through
more clients, make more money.
- [SIGHS]
- That's your problem, not mine.
Uh, uh, Suzanne, I'm outraged.
[MAN SINGING IN SPANISH]
[SIZZLING]
♪♪
They're sayin' it's clear out there.
Should I tell the guys to move out?
Ignacio, it's your call.
♪♪
Okay.
Hey. [WHISTLES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪♪
[BOTTLES CLINKING]
Sit.
♪♪
[BOTTLE OPENS]
[BOTTLE CAP CLINKS]
♪♪
Your friend, um...
"Krazy-8"?
Yeah. Domingo.
I known him a long time.
Mm.
How?
My family knows his family.
Mm.
♪♪
Has he ever been inside before?
No.
♪♪
You worried about him?
No, man, he'll keep his mouth shut.
♪♪
Mm-hmm.
[BOTTLE THUDS]
♪♪
You want me to take care of it?
No.
I got something much better for him.
♪♪
Come on.
I need you to call Beau Bindler
and set a meeting for tomorrow a.m.
so we can prep him for the deposition.
- Got it.
- And maybe bring bagels.
The guy eats his feelings.
Bagels, check.
See ya. See ya tomorrow.
Alright.
Okay, let's review.
Your sister, Nancy,
attacked your girlfriend,
also named Nancy, with a curling iron?
I'm gonna need a face-to-face
so I know who I'm representing.
Look, I'm in an elevator.
Now I'm gonna lose you.
Uh, hello? Okay.
[ELEVATOR RUMBLES, THUDS]
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
No!
Hey! Hello?!
Ohh.
Hi. This is ADA Ericsen.
We're in the south bank of the
supposedly working elevator...
God damn it!
Please.
Sorry. We're stuck between
floors two and three.
Yeah. How long?
Thanks.
[TELEPHONE HANGS UP]
And?
They're sending someone.
It's gonna be a minute.
[SIGHS HEAVILY] I can't believe this.
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
[SIGHS] "Ladies and
gentlemen of the jury,
I ask you, what is
this trial really about?
The state may call it vandalism,
but I call my client's
brave act of social justice
'constitutionally
protected free speech'.
- Really?
- That..."
I-I got to use my time.
Can you do it silently?
Um, yeah, sure.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[QUIETLY] "My client is a
man of deep moral fortitude...
moral fortitude, with
a passion for progress".
"Puh, puh". Mm-hmm.
"A solid citizen..."
No. No. No.
"A dedicated citizen with
a voice that needs to ring out!"
Name one.
Hmm? I'm sorry?
One of the cases.
What, one of our cases?
Oh, let me think. Uh, Veronica Nix.
Motor vehicle theft?
With mitigating circumstances.
Such as?
It was her aunt's minivan.
That's already baked in.
It was parked in the driveway.
The old lady was berating her, so...
So, what?
So, you know, good luck finding a jury
that's never been
reamed out by a relative.
One year probation.
Sold.
- Just like that?
- Yep.
What do you say we look
at, uh... Jerome Sheehan?
So, full year supervised
for Drew Kirkman?
How about 18 months?
18 it is.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Next up, we got... Tanika Berman.
Ah. Um [INHALES SHARPLY]
four months jail?
The vampire stunt? That
was negligent arson.
Well, it was more of a prank gone wrong.
The knife was real.
Yeah, but it was used as a prop.
Was the fire a prop?
The blood was fake.
How is that relevant?
Petty misdemeanor.
Plus fourth-degree felony.
[SIGHS]
Uh, but ya, uh, drop
the property damage?
Keep the weapons charge.
Uh... 14 months jail.
[LAUGHS] 16.
Mm. 16.
Plus fines TBD.
Alright.
[ELEVATOR WHIRS, RUMBLES]
Oh.
Oh, hey, look at that.
Ugh. Finally.
Mm. 20 minutes.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Pleasure doing business with ya.
Sure.
See you next week for the last three.
[ELEVATOR DOORS CLOSE]
Legal services for the other half?
So, my brother's little problem?
Eh, his record will be cleaner
than "Doris Day's Greatest Hits".
Catch ya on the flip-flop.
[SIGHS]
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Mm.
70 hours is a breeze. Trust me.
Think of all the good that you'll do.
Bruno, good talking to you.
I gotta jump.
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
Miss Hower. Hey, have I got good news.
I had to strap on the old armor
and do some jousting, but...
It's, uh, what knights used
to do back in... olden times.
Uh, you know what? I'll call you back.
Mr. Varga, long time no see.
Get in.
Uh [SIGHS] your timing isn't perfect.
Um, I'm a little swamped right now.
We're just going for a ride or...
Uh...
Oh.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪♪
On the next episode of,
Better Call Saul...
[CAR ENGINE RUMBLING]
Call and make sure he's alright.
And ask how I can get in touch
with him, before his next hearing.
Leonard...
Who exactly did I just set up?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
If there's gonna be blow back,
I don't wanna be in the middle of it.
[FIGHTING GRUNT, BLOW LANDS]
[FIGHTING GRUNTS, THUD]
[MUSIC ENDS]