[LATIN AMERICAN MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[IN SPANISH]
MAN [IN SPANISH]:
[MUSIC SHUTS OFF]
[♪♪♪]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[IN ENGLISH]
Hey.
[IN SPANISH]
[♪♪♪]
[LALO LAUGHING]
SAUL:
What's so funny?
[LALO SIGHS]
-Ah, you wouldn't get it.
- Okay.
Okay, here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna take 25 South to Las Cruces.
You can pick up 10 West from there.
Hey, write this down, man, es complicado.
Ten West at Las Cruces.
A little past Deming, there's a state road. It's 146.
Uh, follow the signs to Antelope Wells
until Mile Marker 223.
Turn off at the dirt road and take it 30 miles south.
- Thirty miles down a dirt road?
- Fewer eyes out in the desert, you know?
Actually, it's 31.6.
So make sure that you use the little, you know,
trip meter thing on the odometer, whatever.
Anyway, once you get there,
you're gonna see a well.
It's really old. You know, broken down.
What does this well look like?
It looks like a well. It's the only one out there.
-Can you see it from the road?
- You'll see it. Don't worry about it.
My cousins are gonna meet you there
with the money, 9 a.m.
-You'll like them. They're good boys.
- I'll bet.
Um...
Hey, I have an idea.
Why not have these cousins of yours
bring the money just all the way here?
Cut out the middleman.
Yeah, see, the thing is,
this whole thing has
to be very low-profile, you know?
There are people, let's say competitors of mine,
people who wanna keep me in here.
And so, you know, my cousins come into town,
those people will notice.
What about Nacho Varga, right?
Would your competitors notice him?
He seems like he's got
a pretty good head on his shoulders.
You mean Ignacio?
Yeah, sure, I mean, he's good for a lot of things.
But with 7 million? Pfft.
A guy like that could get real dumb real fast,
you know?
Hey, you're the right guy for this. You're nobody.
I mean, no offense,
but nobody's gonna look twice at you.
Yeah, sure. Um...
Hey, look, maybe this isn't your thing, you know?
I mean, that's okay. I get it.
You did good in court. We'll leave it at that.
Well, thanks, that's... I appreciate that.
Don't worry about it.
I'll find somebody else, you know?
Yeah. Uh, so I guess we're done here.
Guess so.
All right.
I will... I'm gonna shred these.
And, uh...
if there's anything else you need,
any legal services...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got your number. See you.
[SOFTLY]
This stupid thing.
Ahem, hundred thousand?
Dollars?
- Yeah.
- That's a lot of money.
To bring back 7 mil? And I'm the best guy to do it?
Uh, that's actually less
than 2 percent commission. I think it's right.
So 100K for a little drive through the desert, huh?
That's the price.
Done.
[SHOWER RUNNING]
Hey, I'm home.
JIMMY:
Great. I'll be out in a sec.
Evening shower, huh?
Yeah. Got an early day tomorrow.
Hey, I hope you're hungry. I'm making fajitas.
- You're cooking?
- Yeah, why not?
I picked up some strip steak on the way home,
and it's been marinating for a couple hours
in a secret blend of herbs and spices.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Something I like to call "Old El Paso."
KIM:
Heh-heh. It sounds exotic.
JIMMY:
It'll be delicious, you'll see.
I, uh... I have some business news.
You're a friend of the cartel? Is that it?
Not exactly.
Maybe.
You got him bail?
Some evidence fell into my lap.
I was kind of obligated to use it.
You know, for my client.
When you said you couldn't do it,
I knew you'd find a way.
There's a complication.
Remember that time you had a PD case
with the kid whose parents kicked him out
because he got caught with a joint?
Yeah.
And you had to drive all the way out
to the uncle's house, I think it was in Moriarty,
to pick up the bail? Well...
Wait, what? So, what, you're saying
you're gonna pick up Salamanca's bail?
Yeah, only it's a little further than Moriarty
and a little more money.
- How much?
- Seven.
- Seven thousand?
- Million.
- Seven million?
- Yeah.
You're going to pick up $7 million of cartel money?
I know what you're thinking,
but it's safe. Completely.
- A quick drive down by the border, I'll be back.
- The border?
Jimmy, you are an attorney, not a bagman.
There's no amount of money that is worth this.
- Can't his people do it?
- He trusts me.
I'm his attorney, that's it.
You're making a bigger deal out of this
than you need to.
- What?
- I will pick it up in the morning, I will be done
and I'll be home before you will.
Okay. Then I'm going with you.
Well, they're only expecting me.
You know, one guy?
I mean, that's kind of the whole point.
You know, security through obscurity.
- Jimmy, this is insane, I...
- No, listen, it's just little old me
in my little old Suzuki Esteem.
And there has never been more than 50 bucks
in an Esteem in the history of Esteems.
So no one's gonna look at me twice.
You sound like you are talking yourself into this.
I will be okay. I swear.
If I smell even the faintest whiff of anything wrong,
I'll be out of there like a shot.
I don't like this.
I don't want you to do it.
Kim, listen.
I swear, okay? I'll be fine.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[JIMMY SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
L... Lawyer.
From Lalo. Eduardo sent me
to pick up the, uh, dinero.
[GRUNTS]
I'll just take these back to Lalo.
You guys are just gonna... Just go?
Well, that'll work.
[JIMMY SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
All right.
Woof.
JIMMY [SINGING]:
♪ Seven million dollars of cash in the trunk ♪
♪ Seven million dollars of cash ♪
♪ Take one dollar, pass it a "rollar" ♪
♪ Six million, nine hundred ninety-nine thousand ♪
♪ Crappy service ♪
♪ Ninety-nine dollars of cash in the truck ♪
♪ Take a buck, pass it for luck ♪
♪ Six million, nine hundred ninety-nine thousand
Nine... ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Nine hundred ninety-nine... ♪♪
Go by.
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
Oh, nuts.
Okay, yeah.
Coming out. Slowly.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
I think... I think I have a sense
of what you want here. It's in the trunk.
Yeah, good. Take those.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Whoa, whoa. What? No, no.
That's not what he meant.
No, this is a mistake. It's a big...
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
No!
[GUNSHOT ECHOING]
[MAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
[♪♪♪]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
MIKE:
You hit?
- Hit?
- Are you shot?
Get up.
Shot?
You're in shock.
You stay here and breathe.
[ENGINE STARTS]
MIKE:
Hey.
You're alive. Focus on that.
You'll be okay.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Get out. The alternator's shot.
Literally.
All right. I'm gonna need you
to put your back into this.
Push!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
JIMMY:
Oh, oh! Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
What is it?
Where is it?
[MIKE GRUNTS]
Did you know all this was gonna happen?
If I did, I would've brought more guys.
Let's get that to where it belongs. This way.
Well, uh, home is that way.
One of those guys got away in a car.
On the road. This road.
We gotta get off it.
[♪♪♪]
[JIMMY GROANS]
JIMMY:
Big mistake...
discontinuing...
thousand dollar bill.
Mm. Big.
These would've been so much lighter.
Hey.
How about we take turns
with these bad boys, you know?
So we both stay fresh?
Fine.
- I got an idea. Let's dig a hole.
- A hole?
Yeah. Walk out of here, get to civilization,
drive back, pick it up.
Work smarter, not harder.
You'll never find it.
Oh, I will because I'll memorize the landmarks.
Like this tree? You can't miss it.
That hill, that's distinctive.
It's got a hill shape.
Yeah, very different from the couple dozen trees
we've seen on hillsides that we walked past.
I will remember. I will find this tree.
MIKE:
Mmm.
That's hard pack.
If you manage to dig a hole big enough
for those two bags,
you might as well dig one for yourself.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, come on. That's not gonna work.
You are wasting energy.
I'm almost there.
It's working. Heh.
[♪♪♪]
Stop.
Put that away. They'll see it.
You take off anything that'll catch the light.
- Is it him?
- Oh, yeah.
It looks like they're doing a grid search.
Meaning?
MIKE:
Meaning they found your car.
I'd go easy on that.
Hey, why are we camping?
I mean, shouldn't we keep walking?
It's cooler at night.
You go out there in the dark,
you're gonna break your leg in a prairie-dog hole.
Hey, we gotta be halfway there, right?
Almost.
"Almost."
I should have been home hours ago.
This will be tearing her up.
Oh, she's just gonna think
you're out catting around.
No, she won't.
She's gonna think I'm chopped to pieces,
dead in some ditch.
And why is she gonna think that?
Are you saying she knows what you're doing?
Not, you know, the details.
She knows I'm picking up money
down by the border, that's all.
- You told your girlfriend what you're doing?
- My wife.
- Wife?
- Yeah, wife.
Congratulations.
And what's your wife gonna do
with this information, do you think?
- Call the cops?
- No.
No? People get scared, call the cops.
Pretty standard.
No, she's not calling any cops.
Her mother. Girls at the book club.
Gonna call her boss,
tell her about her missing husband.
No, she's not doing any of that, okay?
She knows better.
She's just gonna be scared out of her mind, is all.
Oh.
Well, let's hope you're right.
[SCOFFS]
She knows.
She's in the game now.
What? No. She's not in the game, all right?
She's not even game-adjacent.
I just told her the truth.
A little slice of the truth. That's all.
Mmm.
- She's not in the game.
- Yeah.
[GROANS]
Well, I can't make a fire.
Our guy may still be out there.
Oh...
I got two of these, you want one?
No, thanks.
- Gets cold fast.
- I'm fine. Thanks.
You suit yourself.
[KEYS RATTLING]
[LOCK CLICKING]
- Ma'am, do you want me to...?
- Yes, please.
Thank you.
[LALO GROANS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
I know I misrepresented myself
as a member of your legal team,
I apologize for that.
I wouldn't be here right now
if I didn't absolutely have to be.
[KIM CLEARS THROAT]
I know who are. Who you actually are.
We have something in common.
You wanna know where your money is,
I wanna find Saul Goodman.
If you tell me where you sent him,
I won't alert the authorities, I won't tell anyone.
I will find him and you'll get your money.
Mr. Salamanca...
Who the hell are you
that he tells you my business?
He didn't betray your confidence.
We're married,
which means I have spousal privilege.
Anything he says to me stays with me.
No one can make me discuss it.
It's as bulletproof as lawyer-client privilege.
So you're his wife?
Yes.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Huh.
So you're his wife and you love him,
and he didn't come home last night,
and you got scared enough
to come down here and talk to me.
[LALO LAUGHING]
What makes you think
he didn't run off with my money, huh?
He did not run off with your money.
Yeah, maybe not.
Not without you.
Just tell me where you sent him. That's all I need.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I don't think so.
Your man, he's, um...
He's like la cucaracha, you know?
Born survivor.
If trouble found him, give it a day.
If he's alive, he'll show.
And if he's...?
Well, then a day's not gonna make
a difference, is it?
All right. Well, nice to meet you, Mrs. Goodman.
Wait, um, Mr. Salamanca...
Done!
[LALO GROANS]
[HANDCUFFS CLICKING]
Hey. I wouldn't waste that.
Waste what?
I don't have enough of this for the both of us.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Just a lonely soul ♪
♪ Slowly dying ♪
♪ I was smiling hard ♪
♪ But I was lying ♪
♪ Then you sailed along ♪
♪ With your sweet dream ♪
♪ When you stole my heart ♪
♪ I was livid ♪
♪ Morning come ♪
♪ Sun don't shine ♪
♪ I'll get by without you ♪
♪ I was lost, but now I'm found ♪
♪ Tell me, love, it was you ♪♪
[SOFTLY]
More.
- No.
- More.
No. You want more...
All right.
Come on. Let's go.
Hold it. I have an idea.
[JIMMY GRUNTS]
- That's not gonna work.
- This is gonna work.
[JIMMY CONTINUES GRUNTING]
You gonna get that?
Get what?
Oh.
Got it.
Oh, crap.
[MIKE GROANS]
Hey. Aah! Shit!
[EXCLAIMS]
Ugh. Ah! That's it. I'm done.
Done!
Quiet.
Why? I'm quiet, I'm loud,
I'm gonna die in this dirt one way or the other.
Let's get it over with.
- Get up.
- No.
I'm not going.
I'm done.
Everything hurts.
God, I'm so thirsty.
You need to drink.
What's the point? So they can find a corpse
with a mouth full of piss?
That's not gonna happen. Now get up.
Come on.
[GROANING]
Oh, God. Oh, no. How...?
How the hell are you still going?
Because I know why I'm out here. That's how.
I know what it's for.
And I can't drag that money out of here by myself.
So you... You get up, and you get up now.
What it's for? What is it for?
I have people.
I have people waiting for me.
They don't know what I do, they never will.
They're protected.
But I do what I do so they can have a better life.
And if I live or if I die,
it really doesn't make a difference to me
as long as they have what they need.
So when it's my time to go,
I will go knowing I did everything I could for them.
Now, you ask me how I keep going?
That's how.
Stay down. He's back.
[♪♪♪]
Lie low.
We're gonna have to wait him out.
Hey, get that thing ready.
Come on, you asshole.
You want this 7 mil?
Come on, I'm just walking here
like a goddamn idiot!
Come and get some, you dickhead.
You son of a bitch. Look at me!
MIKE:
Yeah, there you go.
[SOFTLY]
Come on. Come on.
[GUNSHOT]
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]