(heavy breathing)
(grunting)
(distant screams)
(grunting, groaning)
(groans)
Fuck!
(distant screams)
(grunts)
(panting)
(distant screams)
♪ ♪
(grunting)
It's me!
(heavy breathing)
Anyone?!
(groans)
(distant screams)
(grunting)
(water breaks)
(groaning)
(grunting)
- (glass shatters)
- (Infected shrieks)
(heavy breathing)
(pounding on door)
(grunts)
(pounding continues)
(screaming)
(grunting, snarling)
(grunts, yells)
(grunting)
(baby crying)
Oh... oh...
Oh. Oh shit.
(grunts)
(crying stops)
(Anna crying)
Hi.
Hey.
Oh.
(baby crying)
Yeah, you tell 'em.
You fuckin' tell 'em, Ellie.
(Ellie quiets)
Okay.
Hi.
Oh, you're so tough.
I got you.
It's okay.
Yeah, it's okay.
(inhales, sniffles)
(pensive theme music plays)
♪ ♪
(crickets chirping)
(wind blowing)
(muffled singing)
Anna?
(stairs creaking)
Anna (singing):
♪ Hold me ♪
♪ Close to your heart ♪
♪ Touch me ♪
- ♪ Give all your love
to me ♪ - (door creaks)
(Ellie cooing)
- (exhales)
- (switchblade clanks)
Marlene: Oh God.
It's not your fault.
Marlene: We were delayed
getting out of the zone.
- I'm...
- She's hungry.
She needs to be fed, and I...
I didn't wanna nurse her.
I cut it before I was bit.
Before.
I want you to... take
her with you to Boston...
find someone to bring her up,
and make sure that she's safe.
I can't do that.
And I want you to give her this.
Anna.
Her name is Ellie.
I can't.
How long have we
known each other?
Our whole lives.
So you pick her up right now...
and then you kill me.
(Anna grunting)
(panting)
(groaning)
I can't kill you.
Please, please, please.
Please!
(Anna groaning)
Marlene!
(grunting, crying)
Here.
Hold her head...
There you go.
Take this.
(Ellie cooing)
(Anna grunting)
Cover her ears.
(Anna breathing heavily)
- (gunshot)
- (Ellie crying)
(Marlene shushing)
(crying echoes)
Joel (muffled): Ellie.
Ellie.
(clearly):
Ellie!
D'ya hear me?
No... What?
Well, I found this in there.
Beefaroni. Chef Boyardee.
Oh, cool.
And have you ever played this?
Boggle?
It's a word game.
Mm-mm.
Well, if you wanna beat me at
somethin', it would be this.
Well, all right then.
We're gettin' close.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hospital that way.
May be the one
we're lookin' for.
Got it.
Take this for me?
Thanks.
They had a guitar in that RV.
It was all smashed up
but got me thinkin',
maybe I should find one.
I haven't played in forever.
In fact, I was thinkin'
maybe I could teach you.
- I bet you'd be great at it.
- (slight chuckle)
Do you wanna learn
how to play guitar?
- Ellie?
- Hm?
Oh, yeah.
That'd be great.
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
Okay, so this is
what I'm thinking...
Cut through that building
to get around that stuff,
find the skyscraper,
go up and look around.
Uhh, actually, this time
I was thinkin' we blast
our way through that rubble.
I found some dynamite
in that RV back there.
Really?
No, so we're gonna cut
through that building,
find a skyscraper,
go up and look around.
But I had you goin', didn't I?
(water dripping)
Look at this place.
Talk about bad luck.
Military drops bombs...
not one of them hits the building
you're trying to demolish.
No way up.
I get you up there,
you can drop that ladder down,
maybe we go through that way.
Come on.
I'll give you a boost.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just you kinda seem
extra quiet today, so.
Oh... I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
- Did you hear what I...
- Yeah, boost.
Got it.
One... two, up.
(Ellie grunts)
- Ya got it?
- Yeah. (grunts)
(quietly): Okay.
Ellie: Whoa!
God damn it, Ellie!
Shit.
You stay there!
Ellie: You gotta see this!
Ellie?!
- (footsteps running)
- Ellie: Up here!
- Ellie!
- C'mon!
- Ellie.
Just wait. God damn it.
(heavy breathing)
(light violin music playing)
(birds chirping)
- (softly): Don't scare it.
- I won't.
- What are you doing?
- It's all right.
Come here, hurry up.
Come on.
- (giraffe grunts)
- (Ellie chuckling)
Hey there.
(giggling)
So fucking cool.
Aw, where's she going?
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Okay.
(birds chirping)
(giraffes vocalizing)
So...
is it everything ya hoped for?
It's got its ups and downs...
but you can't deny that view.
(Joel chuckles)
Look, I don't know exactly
where this hospital is...
Yeah, we'll find it.
Sure. It's just...
Maybe there's nothin'
bad out there, but so far
there's always been
somethin' bad out there.
- We're still here, though.
- I know.
I'm only saying there's risk.
We don't have to do this.
I just... I want you
to know that.
What do you mean? What
else are we supposed to do?
Nothin'. We just
go back to Tommy's.
We forget about
the whole damn thing.
After all we've been through...
everything I've done...
it can't be for nothing.
I know you mean well.
I know you wanna
protect me. You have.
And when we're done,
we'll go wherever you want.
Tommy's, sheep ranch,
the moon.
(Joel chuckles)
I'll follow you anywhere you go.
But there's no
halfway with this.
We finish what we started.
♪ ♪
(ambient nature sounds)
- Was this a FEDRA thing?
- No.
Army.
They put these
places up all around
the first few days
after the outbreak.
Emergency medical camps.
Obviously didn't last.
- They had me in one just like this.
- With Sarah?
- No, she was gone already.
- Oh.
So what was wrong with you?
- It was for this.
- Ah, the guy who shot and missed.
I figured that would've
happened later.
No.
- Second day.
- Well, I've gotta hand it to the Army people.
They were way better at
stitchin' you up than I was.
It was me.
I was the guy
who shot and missed.
There's no story.
Sarah died...
and I couldn't see
the point anymore.
Simple as that.
And I wasn't scared either.
I was ready.
I couldn't have been more ready.
When I...
went to pull the
trigger, I-I flinched.
Still don't know why.
Anyway, the reason
I'm telling you all this...
I know why you're
tellin' me all this.
Yeah, I reckon you do.
So time heals
all wounds, I guess.
It wasn't time that did it.
Well, I'm glad that...
that didn't work out.
Me, too.
- We should probably get going. (sighs)
- Yeah.
You know what I'm
in the mood for?
What?
- Shitty puns.
- Oh-ho-ho.
"People are making apocalypse
jokes like there's no tomorrow."
- Too soon?
- No, it's topical.
(laughs)
Oh, I love this one.
"Moon rocks taste better
than Earth rocks. Why?
- 'Cause they're meteor."
- Oh, that's terrible.
- Fuck you. That was actually good.
- That's a... That...
- That's a zero outta 10.
- All right, all right.
"What did the green grape
say to the purple grape?
Breathe, you idiot."
That was a three outta 10.
- Seven, minimum. Uh-uh.
- I'll give it a five.
- Five outta 10.
- Five?
(both coughing)
(high-pitched ringing)
- Ellie: Joel!
- Joel: Ellie.
- Ellie!
- Ellie: Joel!
(grunts)
Marlene:
Welcome to the Fireflies.
Easy.
Ya got hit pretty hard.
Patrol didn't know who you were.
- Where's Ellie?
- She wasn't hurt.
Not even a scratch.
She's mostly worried about you.
Where is she?
We lost half our crew
crossing the country.
I had five men whose only
job was to protect me.
And I still almost got killed.
How'd you do it?
It was all her.
She fought like
hell to get here.
She would've been
dead on day one.
You are the one person I
never wanted to be in debt to.
But I owe you.
- We all owe you.
- Just take me to her.
I can't.
She's being prepped for surgery.
What surgery?
Our doctor...
he thinks that the
Cordyceps in Ellie has grown
- with her since birth.
- Why is she in surgery?
It produces a kind of
chemical messenger.
It makes normal Cordyceps think that
she's Cordyceps. It's why she's immune.
He's gonna remove it from her,
multiply the cells in a lab,
produce those
chemical messengers...
and then we can
give it to everyone.
He thinks it could
be a cure, Joel.
A cure.
Cordyceps grows
inside the brain.
It does.
- Find someone else.
- There is no one else.
We didn't tell her, we
didn't cause her any fear,
- there won't be any pain.
- No. No, you take me to her.
You take me to her right now!
(grunts)
(heavy breathing)
Please... you don't understand.
I do.
I was there when
she was born, Joel.
I promised her mother
that I would save her child.
I promised.
So I do understand.
I'm the only one
who understands.
I'm sorry.
I have no other choice.
I do.
Walk him out to the highway,
leave him there with his pack.
Give him this.
He tries anything...
shoot him.
Firefly: I didn't hear
anyone say, "Stop."
Which way?
Down the stairs.
The fuck are you doin'?
Keep walking.
I said keep walk... (grunts)
(gunshot)
(groaning)
- Fuck!
- Where is she?
Fuck you.
I don't have time for this.
(gunshot)
Firefly (on radio):
Shots fired. Shots fired!
(distant shouting)
(tense music playing)
(gunfire)
(gunshot)
(Firefly groaning)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
(muffled gunfire)
(monitor beeping)
Surgeon:
Do we have enough power?
(indistinct)
Nurse: She's ready.
- Unhook her.
- (nurse gasps)
- Surgeon: How did you get in here?
- I said unhook her.
I won't let you take her.
- (gunshot)
- (nurses screaming)
Unhook her.
- (shouts): Move!
- Nurse: Oh, my God.
(monitor beeping)
Cover her arm.
- Fast.
- Nurse: Okay.
Turn around.
♪ ♪
(door closes)
(elevator moving)
You can't keep her safe forever.
No matter how hard you try,
no matter how many
people you kill,
she's gonna grow up, Joel.
And then you'll die.
She'll leave.
Then what?
How long till she's
torn apart by Infected
or murdered by raiders?
Because she lives
in a broken world
that you could have saved.
Maybe.
- But it isn't for you to decide.
- Or you.
So what would she decide, huh?
'Cause I think she'd
wanna do what's right.
And you know it.
It's not too late.
Even now...
even after what you've done.
We can still find a way.
♪ ♪
(Ellie groans)
- What?
- It's all right. You're with me.
Take it slow.
The drugs are still wearin' off.
I was with the Fireflies
and then...
What drugs?
They were runnin'
some tests on you...
and some others.
Turns out there's
a whole lot more like you...
people that are immune.
Dozens of 'em.
And the doctors, they
couldn't make any of it work.
They've actually...
(gunshot)
They've stopped
lookin' for a cure.
Where are my clothes?
Raiders attacked the hospital.
I barely got ya outta there.
We'll find you some
new ones on the way.
Were people hurt?
Yes.
Is Marlene okay?
I'm takin' us home.
I'm sorry.
(Marlene groaning)
(coughing)
(gasping)
No, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
(panting) Please.
Let me go.
You'd just come after her.
♪ ♪
Well, she got us close enough.
We gotta walk
the rest of the way.
Probably about
a five-hour hike...
but we can manage that.
Remember?
Yeah.
(ambient nature sounds)
You know, Sarah and I used to
hike like this all the time.
I wouldn't say it was
her favorite thing.
She wasn't a fan of the
mosquitoes and such.
But she was a big climber...
or scampering.
That's probably the right word.
That girl...
she'd see a big rock,
and just... pew.
She woulda liked you.
Not to say the two
of you are the same.
- Definitely different kids.
- How so?
Well, she was a lot more...
I wanna say girly,
- and I'm not sayin' that you're not girly.
- I'm not.
Yeah, you're not.
So that. (chuckles)
She was taller.
She had a killer smile.
Again, not sayin'
that you don't.
But you know why
I think she'd like you?
Ellie: Why?
'Cause you're funny.
I think you would've
made her laugh.
Anyway, I bet you
would've liked her back.
Yeah, bet I would've.
There ya go.
Not much further now.
Hey, wait.
(softly): Fuck.
Back in Kansas City,
you asked me about
the first time I killed someone.
When I got bit in the mall,
I-I wasn't on my own.
My best friend was there
(sniffles)
and she got bit, too.
We didn't know what
to do, and she says,
"We can just wait it out...
be all poetic and just
lose our minds together."
And then she did.
And I had to...
Her name was Riley...
and she was the first to die.
And then it was Tess.
- And then Sam.
- That's not on you.
- I know, but...
- Look, sometimes things
don't work out the way we hope.
You can feel like...
like you've come to an end...
and you don't know
what to do next.
But if you just keep goin'...
you find something
new to fight for.
- And maybe that's not what...
- Swear to me.
Swear to me that everything you
said about the Fireflies is true.
I swear.
♪ ♪
Okay.