Revelation 21.
"And I saw a new heaven
and a new earth.
For the first heaven and
the first earth were passed away.
And I heard a great voice
out of heaven saying, 'Behold...
the tabernacle of God
is with men.
And God shall wipe away
all tears from their eyes.'"
It's okay...
I've read this passage
too many times.
Do you remember what comes next?
"And God will wipe away
all tears from their eyes
that there will be no more death
neither sorrow, nor crying
neither will there be any more pain
for the former things
are passed away."
Do you know what that means?
Good.
When can we bury him?
The ground is too cold to dig.
We'll bury your father in the spring.
Bless you.
God bless you.
We'll get through this, Joyce.
How much do we have left?
Venison, elk, rabbit.
Keep the whole town on rations.
Maybe a week.
Two at best.
Josiah and Martin think they spotted
some deer the other night
couple miles east.
It was dark.
See what you wanna see sometimes.
Anyway...
James.
Yeah?
I sensed doubt in there.
They haven't lost faith
in you, David.
They're just scared.
Not from them.
I still believe.
It's been a...
The last six months have been hard.
For all of us.
But I need to know you're with me.
Yeah.
Good.
Now go get our guns.
We're going hunting.
All right.
You thirsty?
I'm gonna be right back, okay?
No fucking way.
Well, what do you think?
I don't see anybody.
You think we can just take it?
Yeah, quickly. Whoever shot it
is probably nearby.
Don't!
Drop your rifles!
Now!
Turn and face me, slow.
Any sudden moves,
I put one right between your eyes.
Ditto for buddy boy.
You're quite a hunter.
We didn't even hear you coming.
Turn around and walk away.
- Okay.
- Just go!
Okay, all I ask is
ten seconds of your time.
- I just wanna talk.
- I won't say it twice.
Please, just ten seconds.
My name is David.
This is my friend, James.
We're from a larger group.
Women, children,
and we're all very, very hungry.
I'm from a large group too.
Also hungry.
Well, even so, you can't drag this
back on your own.
We're not asking for charity.
We can trade you for
some of the deer. We have...
- What do you need? We have boots.
- Medicine?
Like, for infections.
We do. Back in our village.
- You're welcome to follow us.
- I'm not following you anywhere.
Buddy boy can go get it.
He comes back, you get half the deer.
- Anyone else shows up, I put one...
- Put one right between my eyes.
That's right.
All right, go talk to Howard.
He's got a case with some penicillin.
Bring back two bottles and a syringe.
It's not code, James. Do as I said.
Ten steps back.
Keep going.
That's your dad's gun?
He's the one that's sick?
That's why you're out here
on your own?
Well, look...
It's a four-mile round trip
back to our settlement.
It's gonna be a while
before James gets back.
I have some oil and matches
in my pack.
We could take shelter, start a fire.
Bring him with us.
Go.
You know, you really shouldn't be
out here all on your own.
From where I'm sitting, you shouldn't
be out here on your own.
Fair enough.
So, what's your name?
It's hard to trust strangers, I know.
But I honestly mean you no harm.
And for what it's worth
there's room for you
in our group if you want.
You're inviting me
to your Hunger Club? Thanks.
It's true, we're hungry
but we're still here.
I'm a decent man
just trying to take care
of the people who rely on me.
- You're their leader?
- Wasn't my choice.
It was theirs, but...
- Yes.
- They chose to follow you.
Is this some weird cult thing?
Well, you sort of,
kind of, got me there.
I am a preacher, but just
pretty standard Bible stuff.
- What?
- The whole world ended
and you still believe that shit.
I actually started believing
after the world ended.
Before that, I was a teacher.
Math. Taught kids about your age.
So you went from teacher to preacher
because, what, it fucking rhymes?
Yeah, exactly.
But, seriously...
Well, I found God
after the apocalypse
which is either the best time
or the worst time to find Him.
Hard to say.
But when the Pittsburgh QZ
fell in '17
Fireflies and FEDRA...
I left with a few others
and that's how I ended up
with our flock.
A long way from Pittsburgh.
Yeah, we'd settle somewhere
and then raiders would come
so we'd move again.
And as we wandered, we picked up
new people along the way until...
we ended up here.
Well, your luck had to run out
sooner or later.
Luck?
There's no such thing as luck.
No, I believe everything
happens for a reason.
It does.
- It does. I can prove it to you.
- Okay.
We didn't expect this winter
to be so cruel.
Nothing will grow.
Game has been hard to find.
So I sent four of our people
to a nearby town
to scavenge what they could.
And only three of them came back.
And the one that didn't was a father.
He had a daughter just like you.
And her dad was taken from her.
Turns out, he was murdered
by this crazy man.
And get this.
That crazy man
was traveling with a little girl.
You see?
Everything happens for a reason.
James, lower the gun.
She is the one
that killed Alec, isn't she?
She didn't kill anybody.
Lower the gun.
Did you bring the medicine?
- Yeah, but...
- Throw it to her.
David.
Back away.
I know you're not with a group.
You won't survive for long out there.
I can protect you.
So you're just gonna
let her get away?
Okay, the fuck do I put this, Joel?
Joel?
Joel, where the fuck do I put this?
Fuck it.
Only five more left.
What is it?
Venison.
Big one.
If you've heard a rumor
yes, we found a girl
who was with the man
who took Alec from us.
When the sun rises, I'll lead
a group out to pick up her trail.
Won't be hard to find in the snow.
We'll follow it
to wherever they're hiding
and we'll bring that man to justice.
You should kill him.
You should kill both of them.
I know you think
you don't have a father anymore
but the truth is, Hannah,
you will always have a father.
And you will show him respect
when he's speaking.
Thank you.
Lord, bless this food
and grant that we
may thankful for thy mercies be.
Teach us to know by whom we're fed.
Bless us with Christ,
the living bread.
- Amen.
Stay alert.
If this man's not already dead,
he's dangerous.
What about the girl?
We bring her back with us.
I don't mean to question
your sense of mercy, David.
We can let her go.
If we bring that girl back with us,
she's just another mouth to feed.
If we leave her out here, she'll die.
Yeah, but maybe that's God's will.
Joel. Joel, wake up.
Joel, wake the fuck up. Joel.
Okay... look at me.
There are men coming, okay?
I'm gonna lead them away from you,
but if anybody makes it down here
you fucking kill them.
You got it?
Joel.
Joel, do not fall asleep.
Come on.
Hey, motherfuckers!
Shit!
Go! Let's go.
Alive!
Keep coming, fuckers.
I got her!
Do it.
Two of you with me. Drag the horse.
The rest of you, stay here.
Go door-to-door.
You so hungry for vengeance?
Deliver it.
I started worrying
you wouldn't wake up.
Let me out.
Well, that's certainly the goal.
Hungry?
Why am I in a cage?
Because I'm afraid of you.
You're a dangerous person.
You've certainly proven that.
The others, they want me to kill you
for all that's happened.
Did you hear me say
the others wanna kill you?
Yeah.
- But I stopped them.
- Fuck you.
Why don't we just start
with your name?
Eat shit.
Hey, listen to me!
You can't survive on your own.
No one can.
But I can help you.
Let me protect you.
I'm not on my own.
Right. Your friend.
And how is he?
I can see how much
you care about him
so I know it hurts.
But even so
you gotta face reality.
That part of your life, it's ending.
And what I'm offering you
is a beginning.
But if you can't find a way
to trust me
then, yes, you are alone.
Timothy?
Oh, shit.
Stop, stop. Please.
- Leave him alone.
- You're next.
Please
I don't know any girl.
- Oh, fuck!
- Jesus!
- Marco.
- No... no.
He can't help you.
You focus right here.
Or I'll pop your fucking kneecap off.
She's alive.
Where?
Fuck! Fuck! The town!
What town?
Silver Lake.
It's not a real town name.
It's a resort.
A resort?
You're gonna point to where we are
and where your "resort" is.
And it better be the exact same spot
your buddy points to.
Okay.
That's where we are.
I swear.
Go ask him. He'll tell you.
I'm not lying.
No, no!
Shit! Jesus! No!
Why the fuck did you do that?
He told you what you wanted!
You motherfucker. Fuck you.
I ain't telling you shit.
- It's okay, I believe him.
- No, no.
No!
For what it's worth,
this is just deer meat. I swear.
You're gonna chop me up
into little pieces.
I'd rather not.
Please, just tell me your name.
- If you wanna judge me...
- Judge you?
You're eating people, you sick fuck!
Yes.
There are only a few of us that know.
But I would've told you.
Sooner or later. I guess sooner.
- You're an animal.
- Well, yes, we all are.
That's sort of the point.
It was a last resort.
You think it doesn't shame me?
But what was I supposed to do?
Let them starve?
These people who put
their lives in my hands
who expect me to keep them safe,
who love me?
Yeah, maybe.
You don't believe that.
I don't think
your friend would either.
Didn't he take another man's life
to save yours?
He was defending himself.
He was defending you.
But you knew that.
You see a lot.
So do I.
And you know what I see
when I look at you?
Me.
You remind me of me.
You're a natural leader,
you're smart, loyal.
Violent.
You don't know anything about me.
But I do.
If I let you out of that cage
right now
put that knife of yours in your hand
you'd stick me in a second.
You have a violent heart.
And I should know.
I've always had a violent heart.
And I struggled with it
for a long time.
But, then, the world ended
and I was shown the truth.
Right, by God.
No.
By cordyceps.
What does cordyceps do? Is it evil?
No.
It's fruitful. It multiplies.
It feeds and protects its children
and it secures its future
with violence, if it must.
It loves.
Why are you telling me all of this?
Because you can handle it.
The way the others can't.
They need God. They need heaven.
They need...
they need a father.
You don't.
You're beyond that.
I'm a shepherd surrounded by sheep
and all I want...
is an equal.
A friend.
What about my friend?
Like I said, loyal.
I can tell the others
to stop looking for him.
They'll spare him.
Really?
They'll just let him go?
Yes.
If he leaves us in peace,
they will just let him go.
They do what I tell them to do.
They follow me.
And they would follow us.
Lord knows I could use the help. I...
Look what's happened.
Think of what we could do together,
as strong as we are.
We'd make this place perfect.
We'd grow, spread out.
And we'd do whatever we needed
for our people.
Imagine the life we could give them.
Imagine the life we could build.
You little cunt.
Let's see what I go tell
the others now.
Ellie.
What?
Tell them
that Ellie is the little girl
who broke your fucking finger!
How did you put it?
"Tiny little pieces"?
No... no!
Get off of me!
Get off!
- Wait, wait!
- Shut up!
Wait... wait!
Don't! Don't do it!
Please, don't do it!
- Please, don't! Don't!
- You had your chance.
I'm infected!
I'm infected.
And now so are you.
Roll up my sleeve.
Look at it. Look at it!
What did you say?
Everything happens
for a reason, right?
David.
No.
No, she would've turned by now.
This isn't real.
It looks pretty fucking real to me.
There's no way out, Ellie.
The doors are locked
and I have the keys.
Ellie?
Ellie!
Ellie.
I know you're not infected.
No one infected fights this hard
to stay alive.
So how did you do it?
What's the secret?
Or are you just that fucking special?
No one likes being humiliated, Ellie.
You don't know how good I am!
You don't know
what I could've given you!
If you would just let me!
Well, I have news for you.
Neither one of us is dying today.
You see, I've changed my mind.
I've decided you do need a father.
So I'm gonna keep you
and I'm gonna teach you.
Ellie.
Fuck.
I thought you already knew.
The fighting is the part
I like the most.
Don't be afraid.
"There's no fear in love."
No! Get off of me!
Get off!
- It's me.
- Get...
It's me.
Hey, look.
It's me...
- It's okay.
- He...
It's okay.
It's okay, baby girl.
I got you.
Okay.