Freedom! Freedom! Freedom!
Fuck you, FEDRA!
Kansas City belongs to the people.
Collaborators, surrender now,
and you will receive a fair trial.
We have control of the QZ
and the open city.
Anyone caught hiding will face charges
of counter-revolutionary activities.
Kansas City belongs to the people.
Collaborators, surrender now...
You know, Perry,
I used to be so scared of these people.
Now look at them.
Did it feel good,
betraying your neighbors to FEDRA?
Watching us get thrown in prison,
watching us hang,
so that you could get medicine,
alcohol, fucking apples?
Did it make you feel better?
Did it make you feel safe?
How does it make you feel now?
Well, I'm not FEDRA.
Lucky for you
no one here has to die.
Yeah, we could put you on trial.
You're all guilty,
so that's how that'll go.
And you'll do some time. Easy.
But first, you have
to do something for me.
Where is Henry?
You're informers.
Inform.
Where is Henry?
I guess they don't know.
- Kill them.
- He's with Edelstein.
Edelstein was a collaborator?
Well, he was a lot more discreet
than you fucking idiots.
Where are they?
He said he was meeting up
with Henry and Sam.
'Kay.
He had a place to hole up in the open city
in case things went bad.
But things have gone great,
haven't you heard?
Kansas City is free.
Hole up where?
He didn't say.
I swear, I've told you everything I know.
Of course, you have.
You're a rat.
He's still in the city.
Okay, I want our people going door-to-door
until we find him.
- Now?
- I'm sorry.
How long do you think we should wait?
Should we wait a day or two?
Should we wait a week?
Fuck it. Let's give him a month.
I'm not sayin' we do nothin'.
We already got a perimeter
around the city.
We can wait him
out. Door-to-door would take a lotta men,
and there are other things that
probably need--
He's not my seventh priority, Perry.
Is that what he is to you?
No.
Are we really puttin' 'em on trial?
No, we are not really
putting them on trial.
When you're done, burn the bodies.
It's faster.
You sure they don't know about this?
I got it from a FEDRA officer.
Patient.
Owed me a favor.
He said he found it himself,
never told anyone about it.
- And what if they get to him?
- They already did.
- He won't be talking.
- Fuck.
Okay. Water? Toilets?
The apartments below
are tied into the QZ main.
We can use those,
but we have to be fast and careful.
- Food?
- Whatever you brought.
I barely made it out as is.
So we're fucked on food?
- Ammunition?
- Empty.
Yeah, so is mine.
We weren't shooting our way
outta this anyway.
No, so we'll sneak our way out.
How?
- Tunnels.
- Tunnels?
Why go to the trouble?
You can kill yourself right here.
Twenty cans, and six pounds of jerky
for the three of us.
If we stick to the minimum,
I think we can make it 11 days?
So that's how long we have
to figure it out.
Is he scared?
Yeah. Well, he saw a lot.
Nothin' I can do about that now.
He's scared because you're scared.
What?
Yeah, yeah.
Joel.
Joel!
Eyes on me. Eyes on me.
You don't have to worry about what to say.
We don't wanna hurt you.
We wanna help you.
Okay.
Okay,
I don't know what the next step is
with something like this,
but if I lower my gun,
we didn't hurt you,
so you don't hurt us,
right?
That's right.
That's a weird fuckin' tone, man.
That's just the way he sounds.
He has an asshole voice.
Joel, tell him he's okay.
- Everything is great.
- Dude.
Fuck!
Okay. Listen,
I'm gonna trust you.
Yes.
But if either of you guys try anything,
yeah?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Can I sit up?
Slow.
Get up slow.
Who are you?
My name's Henry.
That's my brother, Sam.
I'm the most wanted man in Kansas City.
Although right now
my guess is you're running a close second.
- Where'd you get these?
- From Bill.
He's dead.
He says thank you.
I'm guessing you don't have much,
so, this means a lot.
How old is he?
- He's eight.
- Cool.
I'm Ellie.
I'm Joel. Look, you ate,
we didn't kill each other,
let's call this a win-win and move on.
Well, I'm betting,
that y'all came up here
to get a view of the city
and plan a way out.
And when the sun's up,
I'll show you one.
Welcome to Killa City.
No FEDRA.
Not as of 10 days ago, no.
- We always heard KC FEDRA was--
- Monsters? Savages?
Yeah, you heard right.
Raped and tortured and murdered people
for 20 years.
And you know what happens
when you do that to people?
The moment they get a chance,
they do it right back to you.
But you're not FEDRA.
No, worse.
I'm a collaborator.
- I don't work with rats.
- Yeah, you fucking do.
Today you do,
'cause I live here and you don't.
That's how I followed you here.
I know this city, and that's how
I'm gonna help you get out.
Why help us?
I saw what you did,
the way you killed those men.
Now, I know where to go
but I don't know how to make it
through alive.
- Not if it's just me and Sam.
- You seem capable enough.
- You're armed.
- You're wrong, and wrong.
Never killed anyone.
And pointing an unloaded gun at you
was the closest I've ever come
to being violent.
So that's the deal.
I show the way,
you clear the way.
Haven't heard that in a long time.
So how are we gettin' out?
Highways, downtown.
Us.
This whole area belongs to Kathleen.
She's in charge?
Leader of the resistance.
You can see the way
we're bounded by highways.
They got people posted all around
the inside perimeter.
If we get close, we get caught.
No question.
So how do we get across?
Boom.
Kansas City has a subway?
No, but they do have maintenance tunnels.
There's a bunch of buildings all put up
by the same developers.
And they share these tunnels, including,
a bank building here.
So we enter the tunnels here,
travel underground, and pop up here.
Westside North. Residential.
There's an embankment on the other side
of the houses.
We head down,
pedestrian bridge over the river,
free as a bird.
You're right. It's a great plan.
So what do you need me for?
You noticed anything
strange about this city?
Other than the strange shit
you've already seen?
- No Infected?
- There's Infected.
Just not on the surface.
FEDRA drove them underground 15 years ago,
and never let them come back up.
It's the only good thing
those fascist motherfuckers ever did.
So you want us goin' into a tunnel?
Everyone thinks
that it's full of Infected,
including Kathleen,
which means that we're not gonna be
running into any of her people.
But you see, what I know is,
it's empty.
You've been down there?
No, but the FEDRA guy that I worked with
told me that it's clean, completely clean.
- They cleared it out. All of it.
- When?
Like, three years ago.
Okay, maybe, there's one or two,
- but you handle it.
- What if there's more?
Or one of those blind ones
that sees like a bat?
Wait, you ran into a Clicker?
- Two of 'em.
- And you're still alive.
You see?
You're the right people.
If it gets bad down there, we turn around,
and run right back out
the same way we came.
That's your great plan?
No, that's my dicey-as-fuck plan.
But as far as I can tell,
it's our only shot.
They're saying
they're going to help us escape.
Right?
We need to get outta sight.
I think it's this way.
This should be it.
You ready?
Get your gun out.
You see? It's empty.
The plan is good.
"The plan is good"?
We've been down here two seconds.
We don't know anything.
Your dad's kind of a pessimist.
- He's not my dad.
- I'm not her dad.
Just point your light forward,
and be ready to run.
No.
I heard about places like this.
People went underground
after Outbreak Day.
Built settlements.
What happened to them?
Maybe they didn't follow the rules
and they all got infected.
No way! I love these.
I have issues
four, five, six, 11.
So cool.
"To the edge of the universe,
"and back.
Endure and survive."
Endure.
Survive.
Endure. Survive.
Fuck yeah, man!
- Hey, keep it down. We're not out yet.
- C'mon.
Can we just rest here for a while?
There's actually shit to do here.
Wouldn't be so bad
to wait the light out a bit.
Safer in shadows when we pop back out
on the other side.
Yes! Come on! Yeah!
Come on. Pass it back.
Yeah!
Okay.
If you were
collaboratin' to take care of him,
I shouldn't have said what I said.
I don't know your situation.
And I'm not sayin'
they should let it go, but.
That was awesome!
All things considered,
seems kinda cruel--
Yeah.
to send a whole army after you for that.
- Yeah!
- You know, I wasn't
exactly telling you the truth before
about me not killing someone.
There was a man, a great man.
You know, he was never afraid,
never selfish,
and he was always forgiving.
Have you ever met someone like that?
Kinda man you'd follow anywhere.
I mean, I wanted to.
Well, I would've.
Yeah, but
Sam, he
he got sick.
Leukemia.
Yeah, anyway,
there was one drug that worked,
and, whoa, big shock,
there wasn't much left of it
and it belonged to FEDRA.
And if I wanted some,
it was gonna take something big.
So I gave them something big.
That one great man.
The leader of the resistance movement
in Kansas City.
And Kathleen's brother.
Yeah, so,
you still think they
should take it easy on me?
Or am I the bad guy?
I don't know what you're waitin' on, man.
The answer's easy.
I am the bad guy
because I did a bad guy thing.
But you get it, though.
You might not be her father,
but you were someone's.
See, I could tell.
Yeah, where'd he go?
We've waited long enough.
- And?
- We haven't found 'em yet.
What about the man who killed Bryan?
Well,
we're not doin' so good.
Who told you I was here?
Your mom.
Why are you talking to my mom?
We didn't know where you were.
Have you been back to the room
you grew up in?
No. Fuck no.
It's a couple hundred miles away.
It's not exactly worth it.
Right.
When Michael and I were little,
this room seemed so big.
I was really scared of thunder
so when there was a storm,
Michael told me
that this wasn't a room at all.
That this was actually
just a big, wooden box.
A big, wooden box
that nothing could get inside of.
And it didn't matter
if there was lightning
or tornadoes or gunfire.
He said as long as we were together.
in our perfect box,
we would be safe.
He did that for me.
And he did stuff like that all the time.
He was so beautiful.
I'm not.
I never was.
He would be horrified
by the things I've done.
And if you've come to tell me
that Michael wouldn't
want me to hurt Henry
that he would want me to forgive.
I know that, too.
He told me.
The last time I saw him alive in jail
he told me to forgive.
And what did he get for that?
Where is the justice in that?
What is the point of that?
Your brother was a great man.
We all loved him.
But
he didn't change anything.
You did.
We're with you.
Good.
- Do you know where we are?
- Yep.
The other side.
No. No one is here.
No one's gonna be here because
my plan worked.
So much goddamn talkin'.
I'm just saying, I delivered.
Make this right, go down the street,
embankment behind the last house
and we're out.
So we cross the river and then what?
- Where ya gonna go?
- Don't know yet.
Well, we're goin' to Wyoming.
What? It's a huge state.
It can fit two more people.
Yeah, maybe we just
call this one a success
and say our fond farewells.
No, he'll change his mind. Trust me.
This is how it goes.
He's like, "No, Ellie.
Never, ever, ever happening."
And then I'm like, "I'm gonna ask you
a million more times."
And he's like--
Move, move!
Go!
- The fuck is that comin' from?
- Shut up.
Shit. Alright, fuck. Let's move. Let's go.
- What are you doin'?
- Gettin' the fuck outta here!
Oh shit, oh shit!
What do we do?
All right.
Stay here.
What?
If you don't move, he's not gonna hit you.
I'm gonna go around,
try to get in the house through the back,
and then I'll take him out.
But if you go out there,
he's gonna kill you.
It's dark and he has shit aim.
Nobody's gonna kill me.
Then he's gonna kill us.
Do you trust me?
Put the gun down, slide it over to me
and then stay up here for another hour.
That's all you have to do.
Please don't do it.
Please.
Anthony? Anthony?
Anthony, hold them where they are.
We're almost there.
Fuck.
Run!
There's cars everywhere.
Why do you think you're in front?
Clear them.
Go! Go, go, go, go!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- He's up there.
- Fuck.
Two and two!
Around the back, take him out!
Dead end, Henry.
Gonna step on out?
Save us some time?
No?
That's all right. Doesn't matter.
I'll come out!
Just let the kids go!
No.
Sorry.
The girl is with the man who killed Bryan.
And Sam
- well, Sam's with you.
- You don't understand!
But I do.
I know why you did what you did.
But did you ever stop to think
that maybe he was supposed to die?
He's just a fucking kid!
Well, kids die, Henry.
They die all the time.
You think the whole world
revolves around him?
That he's worth
everything?
Well, this is what happens
when you fuck with fate.
Get ready to take him and run. Yes.
Do it.
It's time, Henry.
Enough!
Okay.
It ends the way it ends.
No!
Run 'em down! Run 'em down!
Run. Find cover. Don't look back.
Run!
Help! Get the fuck away!
Get the fuck off me!
Sam!
Come on, come on!
Go, go!
Stop!
This way now! Move!
"Pew.
"As the Raven 01
approaches the red planet."
You think they'll be okay?
Yeah, I think.
It's easier when you're a kid anyway.
You don't have anybody else
relying on you.
That's the hard part.
Well,
I guess we're doing a good job then.
What's that comic book say?
-"Endure and survive"?
-"Endure and survive."
- That shit's redundant.
- Yeah, it's not great.
No.
Look, I don't know exactly
how I'm gettin' to Wyoming.
I'm probably walkin'.
But
- you know, if you want to.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it'd be nice
for Sam to have a friend.
I'll tell him in the morning.
New day, new start.
"Bingo!
Should we knock?"
Hey.
"I don't see any weird movements.
"Stiff? Negative.
"Damage here in Sector 153.
"Stella, can you hear me?
I read you."
Okay, from here.
Do I not look scared?
"Never."
I'm scared all the time
of scorpions!
monster is it still you inside?
Fuck.
My blood
is medicine.
I promise.
Promise. Promise.
Hey.
- Nope, nope, nope.
- Joel!
Joel!
Ellie.
Are you okay?
Easy, easy, easy.
Henry, gimme the gun.
What did I do?
What-what-what did I do?
- Sam?
- Henry, gimme the gun.
Gimme the gun.
Gimme the gun, Henry.
Henry, no!
Oh God.
Which way's west?
Let's go.