Pew, pew.
Pew.
We have to do this every hour?
Gas breaks down over time.
This stuff's almost water.
Back in the day,
we'd drive 10, 12 hours on one tank.
-You could go anywhere.
-So where'd you go?
Pretty much nowhere.
Nice! How does that work?
It's a siphon.
It's when liquid
travels against gravity
-because pressure--
-You don't know.
I know it works.
No wandering.
Okay.
This is your fault then.
"It doesn't matter how much you push
the envelope,
it'll still be stationery."
"No Pun Intended,
Volume Too" by Will Livingston.
"Volume Too." Look. You get it?
-"Too"? Like, T-o-o.
-Jesus.
"What did the mermaid
wear to her math class?"
"An algae bra."
Like, algae bra.
-"I stayed up all night--
-No.
"wondering where the sun went,
and then it dawned on me."
-Feel free to wait in the truck.
-Okay,
but just know,
you can't escape Will Livingston.
He'll be back.
There's nothing you can do to stop him.
Must've been some truck.
Yeah, they used to stick
big-ass plows on them,
and clear the roads
for their tanks and such.
I wanna see a tank.
You will.
Tanks, choppers, all that stuff.
But they'll fight the wrong enemy.
Just scattered around now.
I got somethin'.
Here.
This make you all nostalgic?
This is actually before my time.
-Great.
-It's a winner, though.
Oh, man.
Got somethin' else.
It's light on the reading,
-but it has some interesting pictures.
-No, no, no. Put that back.
That's not for kids. Ellie.
How would he even walk around
with that thing?
-Please get rid of it.
-Hold your horses.
I wanna see what all the fuss is about.
Why are all these pages stuck together?
The--
I’m just fuckin' with ya.
Bye-bye, dude!
All right.
That's enough for today.
-Slow down.
-This is slow.
What am I even eating?
That is 20-year-old
Chef Boyardee ravioli.
-That guy was good.
-I actually agree.
How long we staying out here?
I figure I sleep tonight,
and drive tomorrow all day, all night,
get us to Wyoming by next mornin'.
So can we start a fire?
I'm freezing.
Now, why am I gonna tell you no?
Because Infected will see the smoke.
No. Fungus isn't that smart.
This is too remote for Infected, anyway.
People?
So what are they gonna do?
Rob us?
They'll have
way more in mind than that.
Okay.
Actually smells kinda good.
Well, that would be Frank's then.
Joel.
-Joel.
-What?
-Can I ask you a serious question?
-Yeah.
"Why did the scarecrow get an award?"
Because he was outstanding in his field.
You dick!
-Did you read this?
-No.
Now go to sleep.
Those people you said,
there's no way anyone
knows we're here, right?
No one's gonna find us.
Okay.
-What the fuck is that?
-You don't like coffee?
Is that seriously what those Starbucks
in the QZ used to sell?
Well, theirs was a lot fresher
than what Bill saved up,
but, yeah, this is what they sold.
Smells like burnt shit.
Eyes on the map.
76 west and then,
70 west for, like, ever.
Where in Wyoming
did you say your brother was?
Last contact came through a radio tower
close to Cody.
Cody.
Cody, Cody. Ah, man.
That is deep up in there.
-Yeah.
-And if he's not there?
Then odds are he'll be near a settlement,
probably close to another city out there.
Ain't too many of 'em in Wyoming.
Chee-Yen.
-Cheyenne.
-Che-- really?
Cheyenne, Laramie,
Casper?
What's his name?
-Whose name?
-Your brother.
-Tommy.
-Younger or older?
-Younger.
-Why isn't he with you?
-A long story.
-Is it longer than 25 hours?
'Cause I think that's what we got.
Tommy's what we used to call a "joiner."
Dreams of becomin' a hero.
So he enlisted in the Army
right outta high school.
A few months later,
they ship him off to Desert Storm.
It's what they called that war.
It doesn't matter.
Point is, bein' in the Army
didn't make him feel much like a hero.
Cut to 12 years later, outbreak happens.
He convinces me to join a group
makin' their way up to Boston,
which I did,
mostly to keep an eye on him,
keep him alive.
It's where we met Tess.
And that whole crew, we--
Well, for what it was, it worked.
And then Tommy meets Marlene.
She talks him into joinin' the Fireflies.
Same mistake he made when he was 18.
Wants to save the world.
Pipe dream.
Him, Fireflies, all of 'em,
delusional.
'Course, last I heard,
he quit the Fireflies, too.
So now he's on his own out there and
I gotta go get him.
If you don't think
there's hope for the world,
why bother going on?
I mean, you gotta try, right?
You haven't seen the world,
so you don't know.
You keep goin' for family.
-That's about it.
-I'm not family.
No,
you're cargo.
And I made a promise to Tess.
And she was like family.
-What if you don't find him?
-I will.
-How do you know?
-I’m persistent.
Ya got up pretty early.
If you wanna grab more sleep--
I'm not even tired.
Stay put.
-Where are we?
-Kansas City.
How far back do we have to go
to get around this?
Screw it.
What are you doing?
We can jog right around this tunnel...
take the next ramp...
and we're back on the road.
Minute tops.
Where the fuck is the highway?
I can't tell from this.
I'm all turned around.
Don't look at the state map.
-Look at the inset.
-I don't know where we are in that either!
This is my second day
in a fucking car, man.
I think we're heading north?
It's gotta be the right.
What the fuck?
Stop!
Is that the QZ?
Where the fuck is FEDRA?
Hey!
Please help!
Put your seatbelt on.
-Aren't we gonna help him?
-No.
Fuck!
-Go, go, go!
-Joel!
Fuck.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-You're not hurt? Nothin'?
-I don't think so.
Belts off. Fast!
Let's see you, motherfucker!
Give us your shit,
you make it through this!
I promise!
Hey, you see that hole?
Can you squeeze through?
Last chance!
When I say go, you crawl to that wall,
and you squeeze through
and you don't come out
until I say, okay?
And they're not gonna hit you.
Look at me!
They're not gonna hit you.
You stay down, you stay low,
you stay quiet.
-Okay.
Go!
Fuck!
You motherfucker!
Now you're gonna fuckin' pay!
What you fuckin' did,
you fuckin' killed yourself, motherfucker!
No, no, no, no, no! It's okay. It's okay.
It's over. We're not fighting anymore.
I'm gonna go home.
I'll tell everyone you're good.
I don't know what to do.
My legs don't work.
My mom isn't far,
if you could get me to her.
We could trade with you guys.
We could be friends. I didn't know.
I'm Bryan. I'm Bryan.
What's your name?
Wait, wait, wait.
You can have it.
It's a good knife.
Get back behind the wall.
No, no, no, no!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please, please.
We could just talk.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please, please.
No, no, no! Please!
No, please! Please! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! Please!
You don't have to!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please! No, no, no!
We can just talk!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Ellie, I gotta get in there.
I can't fit through.
-There's some stuff against the door.
-Well, can you move it?
-Let's go. Fast.
-Right.
I’m okay. I'm good.
I got some food in here still,
and I got your light still.
What now?
-We go up.
-To get a better look?
Hopefully, we spot a clear route out.
Stay close.
Got it.
Bryan!
Body, body!
They got fuckin' Bryan!
I told you. I was alone.
I haven't seen any of those people
since that night.
What else do you want me to say?
I don't know. The truth?
Kathleen.
The Bergquists? No?
Mark Anthony Halpin.
Carrie Schreiber.
You haven't seen them?
The Chans? Henry Burrell.
Okay.
You know where Henry is.
Lawyer.
Medical attention.
Family visit.
I wonder if this is the cell,
where my brother was beaten to death.
You were wronged.
And I'm sorry.
But this has gone too far.
It has to stop.
It has to stop now, you mean?
Now that you're in the cell.
But before, people dying was okay.
When you were safe and protected,
and ratting on your neighbors to FEDRA.
They put a gun to my head.
There.
Have I satisfied the necessary conditions
for you to talk?
Kathleen, for God's sake.
I delivered you.
I held you in my hands.
I never told them
anything about your brother.
But Henry did.
And we know that he's still in the city.
And I think that you know that, too.
Where is he?
You think I won't do it?
I'm your doctor.
Who did this?
We think it was outsiders.
We found a truck, loaded.
It's not a FEDRA vehicle,
but they were heavily supplied.
Could be mercs.
Well, if Henry has a radio,
maybe he found someone out there.
Maybe he called these guys in.
Will he live?
What if I had a doctor?
There's no chance.
I'm sorry.
Open it.
This is Henry's work.
Understand?
And he won't stop until we stop him.
Find who did this.
Find every collaborator
and kill them all.
They're not FEDRA,
and they're not Fireflies,
so who are they?
People.
Are we okay in here?
For a little bit, maybe.
Looks like they're checkin' out
apartment buildings first.
But they'll be coming through
these places soon enough.
There's a really tall building
four blocks away.
-Yeah. Saw it.
-So that's the one?
As soon as we don't hear a truck, we move.
Fast as we can.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Thing is,
is I didn't hear that guy comin',
and
you shouldn't have had to
you know?
Well, you're glad I did, right?
You're just a kid.
You shouldn't know what it means to--
It's not like you killed him.
But...
shootin' or--
I know what it's like
first time that you hurt
someone like that.
If you
-I'm not good at this.
-Yeah, you really aren't.
I mean, it was my fault.
You shouldn't have had to.
And I'm sorry.
It wasn't my first time.
Show me your grip.
Finger off the trigger.
-Now, who taught you that?
-FEDRA school.
Figures.
Your thumb
over your thumb.
Left hand,
squeezes down on the right.
You got it?
There ya go.
Look it.
Okay?
You put it in your pack.
You'll shoot your damn ass off.
We'll get through this.
I know.
No sign of them. You?
Yeah.
They're out of food.
Henry won't let Sam starve.
Double the guards around our provisions.
-He's fucking close. I can feel it.
-Yeah.
What?
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck.
When do we tell the others?
Not yet.
Let's just handle what we have to handle.
-We can deal with this after.
-Kathleen--
After.
Seal off the building for now.
Okay?
Yeah.
You're just gonna put your foot here.
One, two--
-Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
-Straighten up. I got you.
-Okay, I'm in.
-Take a look around first.
Ellie.
Goddamnit.
Where would you be without me, huh?
-By now, Wyoming.
-Oh, yeah.
Walked into that one.
We'll make our way up,
and come morning,
I'll take a look at the city
and find our way out.
We're goin' up 42 flights?
Forty-five.
But no, not all the way.
How far?
As far as I can make it.
Hey, you know that guy
who said he was hurt?
How did you know it was an ambush?
I've been on both sides.
It was a long time ago.
We did what we needed to survive.
You and Tess?
And the people we were with.
My brother, too.
Did you kill innocent people?
C'mon.
Holy shit.
-Yeah.
-Thirty-three floors. That's good.
It's gonna have to be.
-Come on.
-Gimme a minute.
Get up, you lazy ass.
Lazy ass.
Fifty-six years old, you little shit.
Joel?
Joel.
-What?
-What are you doing?
I don't want someone sneakin' up on us
while we're sleepin'.
I get it.
Crunch, crunch, crunch.
Are you sure you're gonna hear it?
Of course, I'll hear it.
That's the damn point.
Okay.
Well, good night.
Yeah, good night.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
When we were talkin' about hurtin' people
what did you mean
it wasn't your first time?
I don’t wanna talk about it.
All right.
You don't have to.
I'm just sayin'
it isn't fair, your age
havin' to deal with all of this--
So it gets easier when you get older?
No, not really.
But still.
The reason I asked
whether you'd hear the glass or not
is 'cause I've noticed you don't hear
too well from your right side.
Is it 'cause you were shot there?
Probably more from shootin'.
So if you wanna keep your hearin',
you stick to that knife.
Joel?
Did you know diarrhea is hereditary?
-What?
-Yeah.
It runs in your jeans.
Jesus.
That is so goddamn stupid.
-You laughed, motherfucker.
-I didn't laugh.
-Yes, you did.
-Jesus, I'm losin' it.
You're losin' it big time.
-Go to sleep.
-You go to sleep.
Joel?
Joel!