Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Come on, you gotta help me.
Come on.
Leave.
- Leave.
- Shut up, Joel.
- Take the gun.
- Joel, shut the fuck up!
You go. You go.
You go north.
You go to Tommy.
You go.
Give 'em back!
Then pick up your pace.
I'm not running doubles again
because of your shitty attitude.
I don't wanna fight about it.
Fight about it?
You don't fight.
Your friend fights.
She's not here anymore, is she?
What's goin' on?
You've never been
what I'd call well-behaved,
but the last few weeks?
Bethany started it.
Well, Bethany's in the infirmary
with 15 stitches.
- Good.
- Okay.
Just put me in the fuckin' hole.
I put you in the hole three times.
It doesn't work.
- So I'm gonna try something new.
- What?
I'm gonna tell you the truth.
You're smart, Ellie.
You're so smart, you're stupid.
You can't see where this is going?
Let me help you out.
Two paths ahead of you.
First path.
You keep acting like a grunt,
so you get the life of a grunt.
Up at dawn.
Walk the streets, walk the wall.
Ya eat shit food, ya do shit jobs,
ya take shit orders
from your patrol leader,
who'll probably be Bethany.
And that'll be your life from now
until ya catch a bullet from a Firefly,
or fall drunk off a roof,
or get your hair caught
in a moving tank tread.
There's the other path.
You swallow this pride of yours.
You follow the rules.
You become an officer.
You get your own room.
You get a nice bed.
We eat well.
We don't go on patrol.
We're cool in the summer.
We're warm in the winter.
And best of all,
when you're an officer,
you get to tell the Bethanys of the world
exactly where to shove it.
Why do you even care?
I care because no matter what
anyone out there says or thinks,
we're the only thing
holding this all together.
If we go down, the people in the zone
will starve or murder each other.
That much I know.
There's a leader in you.
And one day, it could be your turn.
Or not.
So, which way?
Keys.
Good.
- Is that it?
- That's it.
Can I have my Walkman back?
Lights out, ladies!
Turn 'em off!
Riley! Where have you been?
What the fuck is wrong with you,
sneaking up on me like that?
It was a joke, okay?
I thought it would work better.
In my mind, you loved it.
So
how's it going?
- Okay, it's bad.
- I thought you were dead.
You've been gone for three weeks.
I should fuckin' stab you.
No, I appreciate your mercy.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I just ran away for a bit, that's all.
If you're going through some shit,
you're supposed to, I don't know,
talk to your best friend about it?
I came back.
- Wait, who gave you the black eye?
- Tell me where you were.
Gimme a name and I'll fuck 'em up.
It was Bethany
and I already fucked her up.
Where were you?
- I joined the Fireflies.
- Fuck you.
I'm not in the mood for this, Riley.
I'm really not in the mood.
- You're a Firefly?
- Jesus!
I told you I'd fuckin' do it.
Talking about "liberating the QZ"
is not the same as--
- Fuck. Where did you even--
- Slow down, slow down.
I will tell you everything.
But first,
you have to promise me something.
Sort of crazy, and you're gonna say no,
but then you have to say yes.
Come with me for a few hours,
and have the best night of your life.
No.
- Okay, now say yes.
- I'm not going anywhere with you.
It's-- Great.
It's 2:00 AM.
And in a few hours, I have drills
where we learn to kill Fireflies.
Get dressed.
So stupid.
- Turn around.
- You're so weird about that.
If you're thinking about
hanging in the park,
we can't go there anymore.
There's a new patrol
that they just put in.
Well, we're not going to the park.
Okay.
- So where are we going?
- Secret.
Trust me.
You trust me, right?
I don't know.
Should I trust you?
Of course, you should. With your life.
- Guards?
- No, 'cause FEDRA's fucking stupid.
- Ready?
- This better be good.
Not that fuckin' stupid, are they?
Okay, rocky start.
Could've been worse, though.
- Could've been a 7-11 situation.
- No thanks.
I'd like to keep my other eyebrow
in one piece.
Well, since you're so interested
in self-preservation all of a sudden,
maybe you should stop
fucking with Bethany.
- What's that about?
- Nothing. It's stupid.
She had to get 15 stitches.
Maybe you shouldn't mess
with people like that.
I'm sorry.
Are you telling me not to beat people up?
You put Carol in the infirmary
for a fuckin' week.
I'm just saying,
you can't fight everything and everyone.
You can pick and choose what's important.
Oh, are they teaching you this
at Firefly University?
Kinda, yeah.
And fuck Carol.
Fuck Carol. Fucking Carol.
- Where are we going?
- Through a damn window.
Wow.
Look at how that water trickles down
those rusty mailboxes.
This really is the best night of my life.
- See?
- Yeah.
Firefly lights are better.
Congrats.
One point for the anarchists.
- We prefer freedom fighters.
- Whatever.
- How many floors?
- Like two.
What the fuck?
Okay, I'm sorry.
- Two floors. Fuck you.
- I was a tad bit off.
Oh, shit.
- Is he dead?
- Yeah.
- Is this the big surprise?
- No.
No, this guy wasn't here yesterday.
So disgusting.
- Is that real?
- Bottle's real.
This isn't moonshine either.
It's, like, from before.
This guy must've spent every card
he had to get this.
No one told him he couldn't mix pills
with that shit?
I think he knew what he was doing.
You're sick.
You know that, right?
You laughed, too.
You're laughing.
Okay, we drinkin' it or what?
Yeah.
- Yum.
- Gimme.
Oh, okay.
It's great.
Was that the first dead body you ever saw?
No.
My parents.
Yeah. Sorry. I know--
I mean, I knew that.
No, it's fine. It's fine. Gimme.
Can I hold your gun?
They kinda made me swear
not to let other people handle my sidearm.
"Not to handle my sidearm
'cause I'm such a fuckin' Firefly."
- Give me your gun.
- All right, fine.
It's heavy.
'Kay.
Thank you.
So, what happened?
You started dating some Firefly dude,
and was like, "Oh, this is cool.
I think I'll be a terrorist."
Yup. That's it.
We're getting married.
But really. Why?
Okay, one night, you were in the hole.
I got bored, so I snuck out.
I was on my way back,
being stealthy like I am.
And this chick popped outta nowhere.
- Chick, like our age?
- No. Like, 40.
Or 50.
Whatever.
Anyways, old.
She said she was impressed
watching me sneak around,
avoiding guards,
and she asked
what I thought about FEDRA.
So I told her the truth.
They're fascist dickbags,
and they're the ones
that should be getting hanged
for their crimes, not the people.
She's like,
"All right. If you want in, you're in."
That's it?
No weird initiations?
Nope. I said yes,
and now I'm a Firefly.
That easy to give up everything, huh?
By "everything," you mean
becoming a fascist dickbag?
I don't know if it's that simple.
Like, in a way, FEDRA
kinda holds everything together.
Ya know, as much as I love
arguing with your stubborn ass,
we're on a mission here.
Okay, stop, stop.
- Gimme a second.
- Okay.
Those lights are new.
Yeah, they wired up the block
a couple weeks ago.
You know, more people in the QZ,
so more apartments.
So FEDRA's not entirely bad.
Fascist dickbags
starving their own population.
Fireflies blowing up the storage depot
didn't help.
- Propaganda bullshit.
- Yeah? So you don't bomb stuff anymore?
- Not when civilians are around.
- That's propaganda bullshit.
- What?
- One,
it's okay you don't know everything.
Agree to disagree.
And two, we're here.
The mall?
You out of your fuckin' mind?
They sealed that place off for a reason.
It's full of Infected.
If it's sealed off, then,
why isn't it sealed off?
It's slimy.
Yeah. It's been exposed for a few years.
So, turns out when FEDRA
connected that block up to the grid,
this place got connected, too.
Not that they know.
So what are we doing here?
Trying to get electrocuted, or--
Pay attention.
You're gonna go through there,
then turn right.
- You'll see a door. Go through it. Wait.
- No.
Fucking turn right, open the door,
tell me when you're there.
- Go.
- Fine.
Are you gonna kill me?
This seems like a perfect place to do it.
I'm aware.
- Are you there?
- I'm here! Now what?
You fucking piece of shit.
Come on.
So
what do you think?
It's
it's fuckin'--
Wait. The lights.
We're fine.
You saw outside.
It's like a big bunker.
No one can see shit but us.
Just me and you.
And you ain't seen nothin' yet.
Tonight, I'm gonna show you
the four wonders of the mall.
You planned stuff?
No way!
Electric stairs?
- Escalator.
- Escalator?
Go ahead.
No way!
Check me out, man!
This is so cool!
Look! Backwards.
Forwards! And backwards!
And now I'm not goin' anywhere.
I'm not moving!
- So this is the first wonder, right?
- Yeah, sure.
There can be five wonders in this mall.
Be careful!
- I'm coming for you.
- What are you doing?
Ooh, shit.
- Jesus, Ellie.
- No, I'm good.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine. I just tripped.
Okay.
See?
You are just a graceful ballerina.
- But chop, chop. We're on a schedule.
- Okay.
Not exactly "full of Infected," is it?
Okay, you were right.
Can we, like,
stop and check some of it out?
Nope. Time is of the essence.
Why are some of these stores empty
and some not?
My mom said when the outbreak happened,
people started looting
until the military shut it down,
so the stuff that's gone
is the stuff that people
needed the most, or wanted, I guess.
Right. So, sneakers
and not soap.
Or that shit.
I don't get why people back then
wanted all this stuff.
- Do you need me to explain it to you?
- No. I know why.
- It just looks uncomfortable.
- Yep.
What?
Nothing. I was just trying to imagine
you wearing that.
Shut up.
All right, come on.
We're almost there.
- Ellie!
- I'm on my way!
Stop right here.
Close your eyes.
- What for?
- Close.
- Do you trust me?
- With my life, apparently.
Well then, give me your hand.
Come on.
Almost there.
- Now?
- Almost. I said almost.
Okay.
Open your eyes.
Shit.
What?
- No way.
- Yep.
- What?
- Nothing.
- You're drunk.
- No.
- Yes.
- Not yet.
Gimme.
- Ya need help?
- No.
Yeah.
Come on. Damn it.
Let me see if I can fix it.
Wait.
Did you really leave because you actually
think you could liberate this place?
Don't say it like
it's some type of fantasy, Ellie.
They've done it in the other QZs.
Set things right,
the way they used to be.
Yeah, we could do that, too.
If you come back, I mean.
We're, like, the future.
You know, we could make things better.
We could be running things.
You could be running things.
I turn 17 next month.
That's when you get your assignment.
You know what Kwong gave me?
Sewage detail.
Fuck.
Standing guard while people shovel shit.
That's what they think of me.
Why didn't you tell me any of this?
I don't know.
I just-- I panicked.
And I ran,
and the longer I was away,
the harder it was for me to come back.
Is that making sense?
No, I get it.
I would've gotten it back then, too,
ya know?
You know, you're the one thing I missed
from that fucking place,
if that makes a difference.
No?
You know what?
We're two wonders down,
three more to go,
if you wanna keep going.
I mean, I'm on a magic horse
with, like, a million lights.
I don't know
how it's supposed to get better.
Is that a time machine?
Come on.
Can you be cool like me?
Strike your best pose.
Hey, being cool ain't free.
-Please insert five dollars.
- Fuck you.
Well, look at that.
I came prepared.
Have you done this before?
No, idiot.
I was waiting to do it with you.
- Remember, strike your coolest pose.
- Let's go, bunny.
Oh shit!
What should we do?
Lookin' great.
Okay, bunny ears?
- Wait.
- Say "cheese."
Find another pose.
- Back-to-back?
- Yeah.
- Do scary, do scary.
- Okay.
Time's up.
- Thanks for all your cool poses.
- Okay, yeah.
- Get off of me.
- Okay, okay, sorry.
- I gotcha.
-Your photos are almost done.
Let's see how ya did.
- Oh, yeah.
-Thanks for hoppin' on by.
There we go.
Oh, fuck.
That one's not bad.
If you like it, it's yours.
Come on. We got places to be
and wonders to see.
Are we going to whatever number
we're up to?
Fourth wonder of the mall,
and I hope you're prepared
because it's pretty dang awesome,
- and it might break you.
- Don't oversell, man.
Listen.
Riley?
Yeah?
This is the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
- Yeah.
This is an emergency broadcast.
The Earth is being invaded
by flying saucers from Mars!
Ohh, yeah.
Select a racehorse.
Cool.
Do you have any money?
No, not that useless shit. Coins.
We can't even play once.
- You asshole.
- Yeah, I'm the same asshole
that spent an hour yesterday
breaking this fucker open.
Thank you.
Dude.
- Dude.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- Ya ready?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Raiden.
Fuck yeah!
-Mileena.
- Mileena.
Dead Pool.
-Round one. Fight.
- Wait, how do I play?
- Smash the buttons.
- There's so many of them.
Boom.
- Use the joystick more.
- Okay.
Mileena wins.
That is such horseshit.
Flawless horseshit.
You ready?
-Round two. Fight.
- No! I'm-- Shit.
Okay. Joystick.
- You're doin' so good!
- How am I doing that?
Finish him.
- Finish him!
- Do not finish me.
But then you wouldn't get to see this.
- Fuck!
-Mileena wins.
-Fatality.
- Fatality.
Okay, that was pretty cool.
Yeah, I know.
How many times have you played this?
I mean, I've been here a few times.
So you don't wait
to do everything with me.
Go again?
Goddamn right.
- Ready?
- Round one. Fight.
- Not for long.
- Oh shit.
- You're cheating!
- I'm not cheating. You're just losing.
Okay. Just for that. Boom!
Boom!
Here we go.
That was a good punch. I can't lie.
- Yeah! Gotcha.
- You are beating my ass.
Jesus!
- Now, what do I do? What do I do?
- Okay, back, forward,
down, forward, low punch!
Come on.
Next thing.
It's getting late.
I have to wake up and make my bed soon.
So.
We still have a few hours left, though.
Yeah, I just can't get in trouble again.
But I'll meet you here tomorrow.
I got you a gift.
I mean, I do like gifts.
- Is it a spider?
- No.
- Is it a new shirt?
Is it a water pistol?
- Better.
- Better?
- Is it a dinosaur?
- Possibly.
I mean, I'll be your best friend again
if it's a dinosaur.
Really, my best friend again?
Ellie, you are already my best friend.
Wait, wait.
Is it tacos?
Okay, not tacos.
Is this where you've been staying?
Mostly.
"Volume Too."
Shut up! They made a second one?
Where did you get that?
"What did the frustrated cannibal do?"
- Lay it on me.
-"He threw up his hands."
- Gimme. I wanna go. Okay.
- Okay.
"What did the triangle say to the circle?"
"You're so pointless."
Okay.
Okay, "How does a computer get drunk?"
"It takes screenshots."
- What are screenshots?
- I don't actually know.
Okay, gimme.
Give me a second.
Here we go.
"What do you call an alligator in a vest?"
Did you make these?
Yes, Ellie, put it down.
To kill soldiers?
You didn't find this mall, did you?
They posted you here.
A new recruit guarding their stash?
We would never use them on you
or anywhere ever near you.
I would never let them do that.
You would never let them?
Right,
and you think they're gonna listen to you?
I mean, I guess we'll find out.
- Ellie.
- It's okay. I'm going.
Ellie!
Ellie?
None of this shit was even about me!
- Would you stop?
- Fuck you!
Ellie!
Ellie, I'm leaving.
They're sending me to a post
in the Atlanta QZ.
I asked if you could join
so we could go together.
- But Marlene said no.
- Who the fuck is Marlene?
Marlene is the lady that helped me get--
It doesn't matter.
Ellie, I tried.
Tonight's my last night in Boston.
Why did you bring me here?
Because I wanted to see you.
And?
And
and I wanted to say goodbye.
- This isn't easy, Ellie.
- It actually is.
You just did it.
Goodbye.
Shit.
Riley?
Riley!
What the fuck?
Surprise.
The fifth wonder.
I thought you'd like this one the best,
so I saved it for last.
I guess that was stupid.
- I'm fucking stupid.
- Gimme the book.
So you leave me.
I think you're dead.
All of a sudden, you're alive.
And you give me this night,
this amazing fucking night.
And now you're leaving again.
Forever.
To join some cause
I don't even think you understand.
Tell me I'm wrong.
I think that you don't know everything.
You don't know what it was like
to have a family.
To belong.
I didn't have them for long,
but I had them.
I belonged to them.
And I want that again.
Maybe the Fireflies aren't
what I think they are
but they chose me.
I matter to them.
You mattered to me first.
Goddamn it, I wanna punch you so bad.
If it makes you hate me less.
And you're sure about this?
About leaving?
Yeah.
Okay.
And I'm not saying it all pissy and shit.
You're my best friend
and I'll miss you.
Well
night's not over yet.
One last thing?
Sure.
Hey.
What am I supposed to do with this?
- Put it on, stupid.
- But why?
'Cause it's fun.
And this music sucks.
- You little thief!
- I was definitely
probably gonna give it back.
Right.
Really?
- Come on.
- I don't--
Get your ass up here.
Come on.
I got you, babe
What?
Don't go.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
For what?
What do we do now?
We're gonna figure it out.
Get ready to run.
Go! Go! Go!
Get the fuck off of me!
Holy shit!
No.
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
You motherfucker! Fuck you! Fuck!
You mother-- Fuck!
There's more stuff over there
you can break.
What are we gonna do?
Way I see it, we got two options.
One,
we take the easy way out.
It's quick, painless.
No, no, I don't like option one.
Option two,
we just keep going.
What are you talking about, Riley?
It's over.
It will be, but not yet.
It ends this way for everyone
sooner or later, right?
Some of us just get there faster
than others.
But we don't quit.
Whether
it's two minutes
or two days
we don't give that up.
I don't wanna give that up.
We can just be all poetic and shit
and lose our minds together.
What's option three?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay, okay.