(pensive theme music plays)
♪ ♪
(ambient nature sounds)
(light music playing)
♪ ♪
You want your jacket back?
I've never been in the woods.
More bugs than I thought.
- Look, I've been thinking about...
- I don't want your sorries.
I wasn't gonna
say I'm sorry.
I was gonna say that I've been
thinking about what happened.
Nobody made you
or Tess take me.
go along with this plan.
You needed a truck
battery or whatever,
and you made
a choice.
So don't blame me for
something that isn't my fault.
How much longer?
Five-hour hike.
We can manage that.
♪ ♪
(frog croaking)
You've gone
this way a lot?
- No Infected?
- Not often, no.
What are you
looking out for?
- Joel: People.
- Ellie: Oh.
- Are Bill and Frank nice?
- Frank is.
- How'd you get that scar on your head?
- (sighs)
What?
Is it something lame?
Like you fell down
the stairs or something?
- I didn't fall down any stairs.
- Okay, so what then?
Someone shot at me
and missed.
See, that's cool.
You shoot back?
- Yeah.
- You get him?
No, I missed, too.
It happens more often
than you think.
'Cause you suck at
shooting or, like, in general?
In general.
You know, seeing as
it's just the two of us,
- I was thinking I should pro...
- No.
Cumberland Farms.
Hang back a minute.
I gotta grab some
stuff I stashed.
Stashed?
Why do you have
stuff stashed here?
You ask a lot of
goddamn questions.
Yes, I do.
So, are you gonna
answer me or what?
Joel:
We hide supplies on routes
in case we find
ourselves short on gear,
- which I currently am 'cause...
- No way!
You ever play this one?
I had a friend who knew
everything about this game.
There's this one character
named Mileena
who takes off her mask
and she has monster teeth,
and then she
swallows you whole
and barfs out your bones!
Ah. Oh, man.
You forgot where
you put your stuff.
No. I'm just zeroing in on it.
- It's been a couple of years.
- Okay, well, I'm gonna
take a look around, see
if there's anything good.
- Trust me, it's all been picked over already.
- Maybe, maybe not.
- Is there anything bad in here?
- Just you.
Ah. Getting funnier.
Fuck.
- Joel: You all right back there?
- Yep!
(debris thuds)
Fuck yeah.
(Infected snarls)
(tense music playing)
(wheezing breaths)
- (snarls)
- (gasps)
♪ ♪
(snarls, gasps)
(heavy breathing)
♪ ♪
(Infected gasps)
Ellie?
(metal clanking)
Ellie!
(gun clicks)
Ellie?
Picked over, my ass.
What are you doing?
There's not much ammo
out there for this thing.
- Makes it mostly useless.
- Well, if you're just gonna leave it there.
No.
(ambient nature sounds)
Holy shit.
You fly in
one of those?
- A few times, sure.
- So lucky.
Didn't feel
like it at the time.
Get shoved
into a middle seat,
pay 12 bucks
for a sandwich.
Dude, you got
to go up in the sky.
Yeah, well,
so did they.
Grim.
Ellie: So, everything came
crashing down in one day?
- Pretty much.
- How?
I mean... no one was
infected with Cordyceps,
everybody's fine, eating in
restaurants and flying in planes.
And then, all at once?
How did it even start?
If you have to get bit
to be infected,
then who bit
the first person?
Was it a monkey?
I bet it was a monkey.
It wasn't a monkey. I
thought you went to school.
FEDRA school.
They don't teach us
how their
shitty government
failed to prevent
a pandemic.
(pensive music playing)
No one knows for sure,
but, best guess...
Cordyceps mutated.
And some of it got
into the food supply.
Probably a basic
ingredient like flour or sugar.
There were certain brands of
food that were sold everywhere,
all across the country,
across the world.
Bread, cereal...
pancake mix.
You eat enough of it,
it'll get you infected.
So the tainted food
all hits the store shelves
around the same
time, Thursday.
People bought it, ate some
Thursday night or Friday morning.
Day goes on...
they started to get sick.
Afternoon, evening,
they got worse.
Then they started bitin'.
Friday night,
September 26, 2003.
And by Monday,
everything was gone.
♪ ♪
It makes more sense
than monkeys.
Thanks.
Sure.
What?
- We'll cut across the woods here.
- Isn't the road easier?
Yeah, it's just...
There's stuff up there
you shouldn't see.
- Well, now I have to see.
- I don't want you to.
Serious. Ellie!
Can it hurt me?
No.
You're too honest, man.
Should've said
axe murderer.
Uh...
whatever it was...
think it's gone.
(somber music playing)
About a week
after Outbreak Day, soldiers...
went through the countryside,
evacuated the small towns.
Told you you were goin'
to a QZ, and you were...
if there was room.
If there wasn't...
♪ ♪
These people
weren't sick?
No, probably not.
Why kill them?
Why not just
leave 'em be?
Dead people
can't be infected.
(tense music playing)
(baby crying)
(indistinct chatter)
Mother:
Mommy's here. Mommy's here.
♪ ♪
(door opens)
(floor creaking)
(footsteps approach)
(radio static, chatter)
Solider: No, sir. We're in the
basement now. There's no one here.
Solider (on radio): Let's
check back with the others.
(door closes)
Not today, you New
World Order jackboot fucks.
♪ ♪
(radio chatter)
(heavy breathing
through gas mask)
(ambient nature sounds)
("I'm Coming Home to Stay"
by Fleetwood Mac playing)
(alarm sounding)
♪ I'll be comin'
home soon, baby ♪
♪ Please be waitin' outside
your door ♪ - (tires screeching)
♪ Yes, when I get
back with you, baby ♪
♪ You know I ain't
gonna leave no more ♪
♪ Yes, when I get
on that train, baby ♪
That was fast.
(accelerates)
♪ When I get
on that train, baby ♪
♪ You'll know
it won't be long ♪
♪ I'll give you all
the love, little darling ♪
♪ I've had in store for you
since I've been gone ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
(bottles clinking)
♪ Ahh yes ♪
- ♪ Mmm ♪
- (generator starts)
♪ Well, I ain't gon' leave
no more, little girl ♪
♪ This time I'm
comin' home to stay ♪
♪ Well, I ain't gon' leave
no more, little girl ♪
♪ This time I'm
comin' home to stay ♪
♪ I'm gonna give you
a no-good mother ♪
♪ Every night and every day ♪
♪ Ohh yes ♪
(clucking)
♪ ♪
(sizzles)
Mm.
(alarm sounds)
(ominous music playing)
Keep comin'.
♪ ♪
- (shrieks)
- (laughs) Oh.
Mm.
It doesn't get old.
("White Room" by Cream playing)
(clicks)
♪ In the white room ♪
♪ With black curtains
near the station ♪
♪ Black roof country,
no gold pavements ♪
♪ Tired starlings ♪
(on radio): ♪ Silver horses
ran down moonbeams ♪
♪ In your dark eyes ♪
♪ Dawn light smiles on
you leaving ♪ - (alarm sounds)
♪ My contentment ♪
♪ I'll wait in th... ♪
(beeping, clicks)
(bird cawing)
- (Bill sighs)
- (gun clicks)
Person in pit:
I'm not infected!
Are you armed?
- Person: No.
- Why did you take that long to answer?
Person: I don't know. I... I thought
about lying for some reason,
but... a reason didn't come.
Look, I-I'm just
trying to get to Boston.
Bill: Alone?
We started with 10.
But yeah,
I'm-I'm alone.
From where?
Baltimore QZ.
It's gone.
Are ya hurt?
There's just,
just a bruise.
(heavy breathing)
Oh fuck.
- (clanking)
- (sighs)
Stop there.
How'd you get that?
(scanner beeps)
Boston is that way.
- You can make it by nightfall.
- I'm really hungry.
I haven't eaten
in two days.
It doesn't sound very long
out loud, does it? (chuckles)
- It feels long.
- I'm letting you go, so go.
All right, look.
- First, my name's Frank...
- Oh, yeah?
Here's the thing, Frank.
If I feed you, then every
bum you talk to about it
is gonna show up here
lookin' for a free lunch,
and this is not an Arby's.
Well, Arby's didn't have
free lunch. It was a restaurant.
I-I won't talk about it
to any bums,
or hobos or vagabonds,
I promise.
(scoffs) I mean, you
already know I'm bad at lying.
(floor creaking)
(shower running)
I left some clothes here for ya.
Frank: What?
Clothes!
Frank:
Thank you! Almost done.
Although can I have
five more minutes?
Sure.
Sure!
Frank: Thank you!
This is amazing!
(light music playing)
(clanking in kitchen)
♪ ♪
Mm.
What the fuck?
Everything tastes good
when you're starving.
Yeah, but not like this.
(chuckles)
- My God.
- (cork pops)
(Bill clears throat)
A man who knows to pair
rabbit with a Beaujolais.
I know I don't
seem like the type.
No, you do.
Mm.
(Bill pouring wine)
Oh.
(Frank chuckles)
(bell tolling)
- There is more, if...
- No, I can't. (chuckles)
I want to,
believe me.
But... whoo!
(laughs)
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, I guess I'll be going then.
But first.
Uh...
I've been staring
at this the whole time.
- Is it antique?
- 1948.
Wow.
You know how much
these are worth?
Currently, nothing.
Ugh, "Fur Elise." "Tales
of Hoffmann"? Yuck.
- These aren't yours. Ah, ah.
- My mother's. Could you not...
- (bench closes)
- This is you.
Ha, ha!
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
It's my favorite.
(sniffs)
(sighs)
(playing "Long, Long Time"
by Linda Ronstadt)
(singing badly):
♪ Love will abide ♪
- ♪ Take... things in stride ♪
- (hits sour notes)
♪ Sounds like...
Sounds like good advice ♪
♪ But there's
no one at my side ♪
- ♪ And... ♪
- No. No. No, no, no, no. So... No, thank you. Sorry.
- Not this song. Not this song.
- (scoffs)
Well, I'm not a professional.
Well, neither
am I, but...
And then I'll leave.
(plays piano softly)
Bill (singing softly):
♪ Love will abide ♪
♪ Take things in stride ♪
♪ Sounds like good advice ♪
♪ But there's
no one at my side ♪
♪ And time washes clean ♪
♪ Love's wounds unseen ♪
♪ That's what
someone told me ♪
♪ But I don't know
what it means ♪
♪ 'Cause I've done
everything I know ♪
♪ To try and make you mine ♪
♪ And I think
I'm gonna love you ♪
♪ For a long, long time ♪
So, who's the girl?
Girl you're singing about?
There is no girl.
I know.
What's your name?
Bill.
Go take a shower, Bill.
(softly): Okay.
(light music playing)
♪ ♪
Have you ever
done this before?
Not with anyone?
- With a girl a long time ago, but...
- Yeah, I know, so...
- I'm gonna start with the simple things.
- (both chuckling)
- Okay.
- Okay. (chuckles)
But before I do, I want you
to know that I'm not a whore.
I don't have sex
for lunches...
not even great ones.
So, if I do this,
I am gonna stay
for a few more days.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
Yes.
Frank:
Oh, fuck you!
Come on! Hey!
Would you stop?
Do I ask for things? Ever?
Ah, why am I
even saying that?
This isn't for me.
This is, this is for us.
Who cares what
they look like?!
I do!
Our home isn't
just our house.
It's everything
around us!
- Give me a fuckin' break!
- Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot.
I live in this world.
You live in a psycho bunker
where 9/11 was an inside job,
and, and the government
are all Nazis.
- The government are all Nazis!
- Well, yeah, now! But not then!
(Frank sighs)
I am asking
for some paint
and some gasoline
for the lawnmower.
That's all. I'll do
everything else myself.
- It is not a mat...
- Bill, if you say "resource management,"
so help me, I will run
through one of your trip wires.
(exhales) Okay, okay.
- Just tell me why.
- I did.
Paying attention
to things...
it's how we show love.
This is my street, too. Just...
just let me love it
the way I want to.
And I'm fixing up
some of the shops.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa...
- Not the stupid ones.
Just the, the wine shop
and the furniture store.
And the clothing boutique.
The boutique?
- Are-are we hosting formal garden parties now?
- No.
But we are gonna
have friends.
(scoffs) Excuse me?
We're gonna
make friends,
and we will invite
them to visit.
We don't have
friends, Frank.
We will never
have friends
because there are
no friends to be had.
Well, I've actually been talking
to a nice woman on the radio.
You what?!
Tess: Well, this really
is just... it-it's amazing.
- Frank: Right?
- Tess: Mm-hmm.
Can you not, please?
- I'm the same way.
- Oh, you're a paranoid schizophrenic, too?
I'm not schizophrenic.
(Tess clears throat)
Well, can I just say,
uh, gun aside, which I get,
by the way...
how nice this is
to have a civilized meal
in such a, a beautiful place?
It's been so long.
I mean, I just, uh,
I wanna thank you.
Even if we don't
end up working together.
I really needed this.
We are working together.
We are.
You know what?
Let's go inside.
Tess, I wanna
show you something.
- Actually, I have been...
- Bill: No.
- ...wanting to see inside.
- Bring your wine.
- Bill: Not inside.
- Thank you.
- Frank: Yes.
- Bill: Frank.
Frank!
(Frank, Tess laughing)
- (door closes)
- I understand.
If my, uh...
if mine...
brought strangers
into our situation,
I wouldn't be
happy either.
But of all the people he
could've found on the radio,
we're actually decent
people just tryin' to get by.
Oh... Well, aren't
I the lucky one?
There's stuff we have in the
QZ that you don't have here.
Books, medicine,
machine parts.
We can help
each other,
and get that gun
outta my face.
So, what,
you were a...
prepper or somethin'?
"Survivalist."
Maybe you are decent
people, maybe not.
Doesn't matter.
We're self-sufficient here.
I don't need you or your
friend complicating our lives.
Is that clear?
That fence has got
a year on it, tops.
Galvanized wire already
started to corrode.
I can get you 10 spools
of high-tensile aluminum.
Last you the rest
of your life.
Lives.
- Tess: Are you sure about this?
- Yeah. I mean, it's not a gift.
- You'll come back, we'll trade.
- All right.
Oh, and I had this idea
that we should, uh,
we should use codes for the
radio in case anyone's listening.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Like, with what?
Frank: Like, I was
thinking, like, the decades.
- Like, '80s, trouble, of course.
- Tess: Yeah.
'70s, uh, uh...
FEDRA's never
gonna come up here.
And you're well protected
against stray Infected.
But sooner or later...
there'll be raiders.
And they'll beat that
fence and your tripwires.
They'll come
at night...
quiet and armed.
We'll be fine.
(tense music playing)
(metal creaking)
- Pick it up.
- Hey... I c... I can't.
Just one more
loop around.
I got something
to show you.
- Huh?
- (chuckles) Not that.
(groans)
(panting)
- Nearly there.
- (Bill breathing heavily)
(laughs) You can make it.
(laughs) What?
What? It's okay.
- Ready?
- Yes.
- Oh.
- (both chuckling)
- Oh!
- I traded Joel and Tess
one of your guns
for a packet of seeds.
Which gun?
A little one.
(light music playing)
(both laughing)
Mm.
(laughing)
I'm sorry.
For what?
Gettin' older
faster than you.
Ah, I like you older.
Older means
we're still here.
What?
I was never afraid
before you showed up.
♪ ♪
- Not on, not on the strawberries.
- (both laughing)
Right.
(thunder rumbling)
(tense music playing)
(sensor beeping)
- (loud boom)
- (distant yelling)
(gunshots)
- (explosion)
- Shit.
(shouts): Bill!
Bill!
Bill?
- (booms continue)
- Bill!
(bullets whizzing)
(gun clicks)
♪ ♪
(gunshots)
(rain falling)
(bullets whizzing)
(screaming)
Bill! Bill!
Get inside! Oh!
♪ ♪
- No!
- We gotta get you inside.
- No! No! No!
- Bill, inside, now! Hold on to me.
- (Bill grunts)
- I gotcha. I gotcha.
(screaming)
- (Bill groans)
- Okay.
There we go.
- (Bill groaning)
- Okay, okay. We got this.
We got this.
(Bill groaning) - You hold
your hand there for me?
Hold, hold
your hand there.
(panting) Frank.
- Frank!
- I'm right here.
Frank, leave the gas on!
- I'm right here. I'm right here.
- Leave the gas on.
The fence, the fence'll
kill the rest of 'em.
Okay, yep.
I made a list
for you.
Uh-huh.
Tell me about the list.
I have copies of all,
of all the keys.
Frank: Good.
(groans) Call... Joel.
Frank: Uh-huh.
You can't
be here alone.
Well, I'm not alone.
- You're here.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
- (struggling) Call Joel.
- Okay, here we go.
- No. (groans)
- It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
- Call Joel. Call Joel.
- He'll take care of ya.
- (softly): There we go.
(light music playing)
(softly): Okay.
Okay.
(echoes) Bill?
Bill.
Bill: Mm?
It's getting cold.
Bill: Okay.
- Let me bring ya inside.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
Okay. There we go.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- We'll get you warmed up.
- Yeah.
(ambient nature sounds)
♪ ♪
(soft, classical music playing)
- Did you take your pills?
- Oh, no.
(Frank grunts)
♪ ♪
(clears throat)
One orangey...
a little whitey,
and... a big roundy.
(Bill grunts)
♪ ♪
(grunts)
Mm-mm.
(Frank inhales)
(Bill groans)
(crickets chirping)
(groaning)
Took most of the night.
(laughs) I'm exhausted.
Goddamnit.
You gotta be
kidding me.
I don't want you fallin'
asleep in the chair.
- I won't.
- You will, and then your feet get blue.
- Bill...
- I'm not fighting about it.
- Back in bed.
- I promise you, I'm gonna stay up.
- Why?
- 'Cause this is my last day.
What...
what if we find
a doctor?
What if, what if someone
shows up who can help?
Who's coming, Bill? The
door-to-door MRI salesman?
(scoffs) There wasn't
anything to cure this
before the world
fell apart.
I've made up
my mind.
Bill.
Oh.
Come here.
(groans)
(chuckles, sniffs)
Well, I'm not gonna
give you the
"every day was a wonderful
gift from God" speech.
I've had
a lotta bad days.
I've had bad days
with you, too.
But I've had... more good days
with you than with anyone else.
Just give me
one more good day.
Starting now.
Make me some toast.
(both chuckling)
Then take me
to the boutique...
where I'll pick
outfits for us.
You'll wear
what I ask...
and we'll get married.
And you'll cook
a delicious dinner.
Then you will crush
all of these up...
put them in my wine.
I will drink it.
Then you will
take me by my hand...
bring me
to our bed...
and I will fall asleep
in your arms.
(sobbing)
(sniffles)
Uh, I ca... I can't.
Do you love me?
(heavy breathing)
Yes.
Then love me
the way I want you to.
(somber music playing)
(wind blowing)
(leaves rustling)
♪ ♪
(inaudible)
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
(door opens)
(groans)
Will it be enough?
Yeah.
Were there already
pills in the bottle?
Enough to kill a horse.
This isn't the tragic suicide
at the end of the play.
I'm old.
I'm satisfied.
And you were my purpose.
(sighs)
I do not support this.
I should be furious.
But from an objective
point of view...
it's incredibly romantic.
(both laughing)
(sighs)
Take me to bed.
♪ ♪
(Frank sniffles)
(metal squeaks)
(gate creaks)
Stay there.
(keypad beeping)
(fence clicks)
(door creaking)
- What the fuck?
- Bill?
Frank?
You stay there. Ya hear
anything, you see anything...
yell.
What if they're gone?
(door opens, creaks)
(flies buzzing)
(playing notes)
(light music playing)
(door closes)
Ellie?
♪ ♪
It's from Bill.
"To whomever...
but probably Joel."
I figured I fell
under "whomever."
Came with this.
So they're dead?
Mm-hmm.
You, you wanna?
Go ahead.
You do it.
"August 29, 2023.
"If you find this... please do
not come into the bedroom.
"We left a window open
so the house wouldn't smell,
"but it will
probably be a sight.
"I'm guessing you
found this, Joel,
"because anyone else
would've been electrocuted
"or blown up
by one of my traps. Hehehehehehehehe.
"Take anything you need.
"The bunker code is the same
as the gate code but in reverse.
"Anyway...
I never liked you,
"but still, it's like
we're friends... almost.
"And I respect you.
"So, I'm gonna tell you
something because you're probably
"the only person
who will understand.
"I used to hate the world, and I
was happy when everyone died.
"But I was wrong
because there was
"one person worth saving.
"That's what I did.
"I saved him.
"Then I protected him.
"That's why men like
you and me are here.
"We have a job to do.
"And God help any motherfuckers
who stand in our way.
"I leave you all of my
weapons and equipment.
Use them to keep..."
(somber music playing)
Stay here.
♪ ♪
(pensive music playing)
Show me your arm.
I just finished makin'
a truck battery.
It's charging right now.
- Okay.
- And I have a brother out in Wyoming.
He's in some
kinda trouble,
and I'm heading out
there to find him.
He used to be
a Firefly.
And my guess is he knows
where some of them are out there.
Maybe they can get you
to wherever this lab is.
All right.
Uh, listen,
about Tess, uh...
If I'm takin'
you with me,
there's some rules
you gotta follow.
Rule one, you don't
bring up Tess. Ever.
Matter of fact, we can just
keep our histories to ourselves.
Rule two, you don't
tell anyone about your...
condition.
They see that bite mark,
they won't think it through.
They'll just shoot you.
Rule three, you do
what I say when I say it.
- We clear?
- Yes.
Repeat it.
What you say goes.
(sighs) Okay.
(inhales, exhales)
So, what now?
We grab what we can.
(ladder clanking)
("Chains of Love"
by Erasure playing on radio)
Ho-ly shit.
This guy was a genius.
- (turns music off)
- Why was the music on?
If he didn't reset the
countdown every few weeks,
this playlist would
run over the radio.
'80s.
Grab some cans
from over there.
Nothin' dented
or swollen.
- Dude.
- No.
There's a wall of them.
(mellow banjo music playing)
Joel:
Needs another hour.
They have hot water!
I'm takin' a shower.
And then
you're showering
because seriously.
♪ ♪
- (piece clatters)
- (sighs)
(solemn music playing)
(footsteps approach)
(softly): Oh shit.
Well, don't you
look pretty.
Shut up.
Nice.
- It's your first time in a car?
- It's like a spaceship.
No, it's like a piece
of shit Chevy S10,
but it'll get us
there... I think.
- Seatbelt.
- Hm?
Seatbelt.
So cool.
(seatbelt clicks)
(engine starts)
Would ya leave it?
Put it back... Ellie.
(tape plays)
- (Linda Ronstadt singing)
- Oh, no, wait.
No, leave it.
Leave it.
Oh, this is good.
This is Linda Ronstadt.
Do you know who
Linda Ronstadt is?
You know I don't know
who Linda Ronstadt is.
♪ ♪
Oh, man.
Eh.
It's better than nothing.
♪ Wait for the day ♪
- ♪ You'll go away ♪
- (remote beeping)
♪ Knowin' that you warned me ♪
♪ Of the price
I'd have to pay ♪
♪ And life's full of loss ♪
♪ Who knows the cost ♪
♪ Livin' in the memory ♪
♪ Of a love that never was ♪
♪ 'Cause I've done
everything I know ♪
♪ To try and change
your mind ♪
♪ And I think
I'm gonna love you ♪
♪ For a long, long time ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Love will abide ♪
♪ Take things in stride ♪
♪ Sounds like good advice ♪
♪ But there's
no one at my side ♪
♪ And time washes clean ♪
♪ Love's wounds unseen ♪
♪ That's what
someone told me ♪
♪ But I don't know
what it means ♪
♪ 'Cause I've done
everything I know... ♪