My lord...
My sun and stars...
My horse...
Blood of my blood...
No, I must ride.
He fell from his horse.
A Khal who cannot ride is no Khal.
He's tired, that's all.
He needs to rest.
We've ridden far enough today.
We'll camp here.
This is no place to camp.
A woman does not give us orders.
Not even a Khaleesi.
We'll camp here.
Tell them Khal Drogo commanded it.
You do not command me, Khaleesi.
Find Mirri Maz Duur.
Bring her to me.
The witch?
I'll bring you her head, Khaleesi.
Bring her to me unharmed or Khal Drogo
will hear why you denied me.
You did this, witch.
Stop it!
I don't want her hurt.
No? No? You don't want her hurt?
Pray we don't hurt you, too.
You let this witch put her hands on our Khal.
Rein in your tongue.
She is still your Khaleesi.
Only while the blood of my blood lives.
When he dies, she is nothing.
I have never been nothing.
I am the blood of the dragon.
The dragons are all dead, Khaleesi.
This must not be.
This must be.
Witch.
No, you can't.
No further, horselord.