- [Gypsy] When Ryan and I got
married, it was by a bathroom.
- [Ryan] Gypsy's always
needed that white dress moment.
- Yeah, I can see it.
- It's beautiful, right?
- Is this the life that we
really wanna lead for ourselves?
- But I still would
like you to remarry me.
- The timing needs
to be at a little bit
of a more convenient time.
- You know, I'm not her mother.
I'm not trying to prevent
her from living her life.
- If I see that I am being
controlled, I'm leaving.
Still crying, you know?
I said, "I miss Ken."
- Gypsy's gone to her
parents without me.
- All right, well, I gotta go.
Sometimes it's actually really
nice not to have him around.
I just don't know what to do.
I gotta delete my social media.
- Baby, that is revenue.
- I don't care!
- Yes! All of a
sudden, now you're not.
[tense urgent music]
- I don't wanna split up,
but I mean, it's not up to me.
It's never been up to me.
[foreboding music]
[tense music]
[traffic whirring]
[birds chirping]
- So Ryan and I are having
an argument right now.
- Really?
- Well, I didn't, he
texted me something
the night that I first got here,
and I didn't wanna show
you or Mom right away
or at all, so I just
kept it to myself.
And this morning, we start
having more of a fight.
This is what he said,
the very middle text
is what he said the first
night that I was here.
- "I'm gonna be honest
about something,
I could really give a
[bleep] about your dad's..."
[melancholic music]
Wow, [tongue clicks]
that's unbelievable.
It's a shame he feels that way.
Can't believe he would say that.
- Yeah, and-
- [Kristy] He doesn't get it.
- No, I'm like-
- Is that his true colors,
like, coming out?
- When things are good,
things are really good,
but he's so selfish when
it comes to my time.
I give him a call and he's
like "Well, video call with me."
You know? And I'm like,
"You know, we don't need
to do that right now."
And he's like, "Why?
Is there somebody there that
you don't want me to see?"
Like, the way he was
hinting as if Ken was here.
- Yeah, right?
- [Gypsy] I know.
- Like, we would
allow that to happen.
- [Gypsy] I know.
- [Kristy] Exactly, exactly.
- And I think I texted him,
and I was like, "I'm not dealing
with this [bleep] right now."
- Good.
- And when I stand my
ground, he'll back down,
and he will apologize
because that will pacify me,
and it'll lead to us making up,
but no real solution happens.
I understand if he's insecure.
I get it, but to sit there
and almost nonchalantly
accuse me of cheating on him
while I'm here spending
time with y'all.
- Right.
- I mean, I love Ryan,
but we have been going
through this cycle
for years, three years.
The cycle is,
I have a little freedom
and Ryan gets jealous
and possessive.
And I shy away from that,
and I try to stand my ground.
- To me, that's a big red flag.
- It is a red
flag, and I see it!
- It's not good.
I think he doesn't get it.
I think he doesn't get that it,
you know, it's all triggers.
[bird cawing]
You feel confined,
you feel trapped,
you feel like
there's no way out.
And every time he does
something like that,
he's trying to put you
back into this box.
- And I fight it too.
It's not like I sit
there and take it.
I stand up for myself,
and I'm like,
"Don't be selfish."
- Right, right.
- And I called him out on it.
And then his divert back is,
"I was just kidding."
- [Rod] You don't say
that if you're kidding.
- [Gypsy] No, it's blame.
- [Kristy] It's always
that, right?
- It's always that.
- Look, he knew
what he was getting.
He knew he was
getting you that was,
had been confined all your life.
And he had to realize that
you're gonna feel like
you want some freedom.
And he should have
understood that
he's gonna have to
give you some of that.
And he needs to deal with it,
and let you do your thing,
and let you find your
little place in the world.
- I wanna make it work.
So I keep making it work,
but I feel like I'm
ignoring some inner voice
that tells me that, "You
know what you should do,
but the journey there is
gonna be long and difficult."
[contemplative music]
[melancholic music]
[traffic whirring]
[birds chirping]
I am glad that I had this
solo time with my dad.
My dad just wants my happiness.
But the fight that
Ryan and I are having,
I mean, Ryan and I are
gonna have to talk about it.
How that goes, I don't know.
- Okay, we're ready.
[door creaking]
- [Gypsy] Hey!
- Thank you for coming.
- [Kristy] Yeah, we'll get you
a bike next time.
- You did? You had fun?
- [Gypsy] I had a lot of fun.
- We'll go camping again?
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
- Really glad you had fun.
- I did, I did.
- My gut reaction after
seeing the text from Gypsy
is I gave him a 50/50 chance,
and maybe I was wrong.
It's gonna be harder
than we expected for them
to work through this.
Ryan's gonna have to man up,
and really give her a
little bit of freedom,
and just lighten up.
He's pushing her away.
[door creaking]
[luggage wheels rattling]
[traffic whirring]
[tense music]
[Gypsy sobbing]
- I'm back home.
[Gypsy sighing]
[Gypsy sniffing]
Ryan bought me flowers.
[sad music]
And he said he was sorry.
[sad music continues]
I just don't know what to do.
[hopeful music]
- Gypsy went to
visit her parents
in Cut Off this past weekend.
And you know, I
knew she'd be busy.
Rod felt like he hadn't
had that one-on-one time.
And I guess when I'm there,
it feels like, you know,
I might get in the way of that.
And I was like, "Okay,
that's fine, I understand."
And I was very understanding.
- So when I came back
from my parents' house,
my dad and Kristy had
carried my suitcase
up to our apartment,
and Ryan was waiting for us.
And I step into the door,
and the first thing
I see is, like,
a big bouquet of flowers.
Then when we start
talking, I told him,
"You were being
selfish this weekend.
The thing that you said
about my dad was unfair."
And he's like, "I
was just joking.
Didn't you see where
I said, 'Ha, ha'?"
- I know what I did was
wrong in certain aspects.
I hit a trauma trigger.
And I hate that we fought the
first weekend we were away,
like, that was the
first time we were apart
since she's been outta jail.
It was just a bad weekend.
We eventually made up.
And now, we're great.
- We sat down and we
talked for a little bit.
And he's like, "I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have said that."
- Currently, things are fine.
- I mean, that's one
thing I love about me
and Gypsy is that if
we have an argument,
we grow from it and
we move forward.
[tense music]
[foreboding music]
- So you did that
video today, huh?
Let me watch this thing.
See what the big fuss is about.
All right, so here we go.
- So to anyone watching...
- Ah, it's too long.
- No, let me watch it. Ow!
they asked me
what was my feelings
about my co-defendant
and how did I feel that
he is doing life without parole?
- You talked about him.
- [Gypsy] And in comparison
to my sentence,
and I was honest with them.
- And [indistinct].
- I've always felt that,
I feel like more than one life
was taken that
night because of me.
They put two stipulations
on me, mandatory therapy
and no contact with
my co-defendant,
absolutely no contact.
And that's fine as well.
I'm gonna be honest,
I got carried away
in the hype of everything.
Social media is, like,
literally a doorway to hell.
Like, it's so crazy.
[both chuckling]
I can't even wrap
my head around it.
- Doorway to hell.
[Gypsy chuckling]
- It's contemplating deleting
it in a couple months.
I don't know.
To all the people
that I offended
with a lack of accountability,
I'm sorry, I'm learning.
So thank you for watching, bye.
That's my video.
- [Ryan] That was good,
baby. I like that.
- I did that while
you were at work.
- And I'm proud of you.
- I was tired of
feeling like I had to
watch this and watch that,
like, be careful what I say.
- I've been trying to
tell you that for a while.
- I'm like, I'm
trying so careful
not to make any wrong
moves for my parole,
and I feel like I
get lost in that.
- Right.
Baby, I've been on this
journey with you, I get it.
Like, I've been telling
you from day one,
like, just be yourself
'cause you're great.
- Yeah.
[uplifting music]
- We'll talk about
the delete later,
but right now, we're
not deleting that.
- Well, I said in
a couple months.
- We'll see.
- I said in a couple months.
- I don't mind if you
stop posting as much,
but we'll talk about it later.
- I'm just not gonna tell
you if I'm gonna delete it.
- No, you're not gonna.
- Oh, it's gone! I don't
know what happened.
- No, you're not.
[melancholic music]
[clock ticking]
- What did you guys think about
Gypsy's Taking
Accountability video?
[tense music]
- Nick Godejohn is currently
serving a life sentence
plus 25 years for the murder
of Gypsy Rose's mom,
Dee Dee Blanchard.
Gypsy Rose then got released,
and she's just out here
doing the most, the most.
- If you watch her videos,
she shuts down the
conversation about Nick,
redirects the question
back to herself,
and is like, "I can't think
about that for my healing,
and my this, and
my that, you know?"
[tense music continues]
[soft pulsing music]
- [Gypsy] I'm ready.
- [Parole Officer] And I
have that piece of paper
saying you're off
of supervision.
- [Gypsy] Right.
And that's my ultimate goal too.
- [Parole Officer] Then you
got the rest of your life
to make as many
documentaries, and books,
and whatever you want to,
you know?
- Right.
Very true, very true.
- [Parole Officer]
Okay, all right.
- All right, thank you.
- [Parole Officer] If you want
my soapbox, you have my card.
- Thank you for calling.
- [Parole Officer]
All right now, Gypsy.
- All right, bye-bye.
- Okay, bye.
- I gotta delete my social media
because people, that one
little thing where I said that,
"I'm responsible for my
co-defendant being incarcerated.
I felt like two lives
were taken that night."
Somebody reported
that to Missouri
saying that I'm trying
to communicate with him.
- But you're not.
- Like I said,
people have the upper hand.
- Delete that.
Delete those videos.
- That's not good enough.
- Baby, that is revenue.
Does he know that?
- I don't care!
- I know, but did
you tell him that?
- I don't care!
- I get it! Then delete it.
- If all you care
about is [bleep] money-
- I don't! Delete it then.
Just let us pull that money out,
at least, before you do that.
[Gypsy chuckling]
[moody downbeat music]
- Baby, that's what I was
saying, tell him that.
'Cause he's always
saying, "Get a job."
- [Gypsy] [bleep].
[Ryan sighing]
[raven cawing]
[distant thunder rumbling]
- I can't believe
you have to do that
because of one [bleep] comment.
That was a great video.
- [Ryan] I know you can.
- [Ryan] I know, but you're not.
Look at me.
- [Ryan] You are.
- You are doing
everything right.
[Gypsy sobbing]
You're doing everything right.
That's what sucks.
- [Gypsy] I know.
- [Ryan] That's what [bleep]
sucks about this.
[Gypsy sobbing]
Word for word, what'd he say?
He said, "Stop,"
or he just said,
"You have to do it"?
- [Gypsy] It's not
in my best interest
to have any public
social media right now.
- [Ryan] I don't want
you have to delete
because one person called.
- [Gypsy] That's the
position that I'm in.
- I know, but I get it.
If you'd have done something
wrong, then I would be like,
"Baby, you gotta
delete that video."
- It's wrong to them, and
that's all that matters.
- [Ryan] But it's
not wrong, baby.
- It's not, doesn't
make it right.
- [Ryan] But who is it?
- But it's wrong to them.
- But a judge can't put you
back in jail for you saying,
"I am guilty of my crime,
and I did my time."
Just breathe for me.
That's all I'm asking you to do,
'cause he didn't come
here with handcuffs.
[sad music]
I don't want you to
go back to prison.
I mean, it's [bleep] ridiculous.
- It's all I care about.
There's not enough
money in the world
that can get me out,
does that make sense?
- Baby, I get it.
I get it.
[troubling music]
Baby, you haven't
done anything wrong.
And your directive has
never said no social media.
- No, my directive does not.
- You have to get a job,
and you have to bring in income.
This is your income.
Social media is your income.
That's my point
when I said revenue.
[wary music]
- It's not a good idea
to post anymore on
public social media.
- Okay.
- And I'm gonna heed those words
regardless of what you say.
Would you put a
price on my freedom?
- No, of course not.
Of course not.
[wary music continues]
[Gypsy's throat clearing]
[Gypsy sniffing]
- Okay.
[wary music continues]
Okay, I'll just,
I just wanna sit and think
on things for a bit, okay?
[tense music]
- Okay.
[tense music continues]
[suspenseful music]
You look really nice.
- [Gypsy] Thank you.
- That halter top you
bought last night, huh?
- No, this is a different one.
- Is it?
- This is actually
athletic wear.
- I like it.
You're tired, huh?
- I'm so tired.
- Well, snap out of it,
baby, it's date night, wow!
[Gypsy groaning]
[Ryan laughing]
I didn't realize I
don't like that sound.
I don't like my
wife going [groans].
When I said it's date
night, you're like, [groans]
"Date night with my husband."
- I am talking.
[car engine whirring]
[melancholic music]
- [Gypsy] Hey, okay, thank you.
- [Ryan] Okay, thank
you very much.
Thank you very much.
- [Gyspy] All right, thank you.
- [Server] You guys enjoying?
- [Ryan] Hi, thank you.
- [Server] Yeah, of course.
- [Ryan] No, little plate.
- [Gypsy] Little plate?
- Yeah, that's for,
like, soy sauces, so.
- [Gypsy] Oh, okay.
- [Ryan] You never had 'em
like completely fresh, like-
- Yeah, nice and steaming.
[Ryan munching]
- [Patron] Yeah, yeah, sweet.
[Gypsy moaning]
- Good?
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, I just want
to take you somewhere.
I wanna do something.
You know, I don't want,
we go to the mall all the time.
We, you know, we haven't
gone to the movies yet.
You know, before you
got out of prison,
we always used to talk about
going to bed and breakfasts
and things like that, we
haven't done that yet either.
You know, we have time.
We can go to New Orleans.
We have time to do something.
And like, I haven't been to
the French Quarter with you.
- There's nothing much to
do in the French Quarter
for someone that is
can't go in bars though.
- You can go in bars,
you just can't drink.
- Can't go in an establishment
that the primary thing
being sold is alcohol.
- [Ryan] Really?
- Said so in my paperwork.
- Oh, that sucks.
- [Gypsy] Mm-hmm.
- There's places you could shop.
There's restaurants,
there's the aquarium.
The Degas House
would've been awesome.
- [Gypsy] Yeah, it
was really pretty.
- [Ryan] It was gorgeous.
- Yeah.
- I mean,
that would've been
an experience.
We should have done that.
- Well, we weren't ready.
- [Ryan] Well, it's just-
- Had too much going on.
- I'd still say yes.
Would you still say yes?
- Yeah.
- [Ryan] Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- You'd remarry me?
- [Gypsy] Huh?
[troubling music]
- Can we not do this on camera?
- Okay.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- So that's a no, right?
- No, it's not a no.
It's just kind of
one of those things
that you could ask
those questions
when we're not filming.
- Okay.
- You know?
[patrons chattering
indistinctly]
You know what I'm saying?
Like, some things can
be just between us.
- Yeah, but we
can always say no.
We're just talking.
- Right.
You're like, "Ah, oh my God."
- No, we're just talking.
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- Oh yeah.
[dish sizzling]
- [Ryan] Oh wow.
- Be careful with her,
she's feisty today.
- [Ryan] That looks great.
- [Gypsy] Hey, fancy.
- [Ryan] That's nice.
- [Maria] Seaweed and Naruto,
and then that's gonna be
snow crab with all that.
- Thank you so much, Maria.
- The forks,
and I'll leave now, so enjoy.
- All right, thank you.
- All right, thanks.
- [Maria] Back in a little bit.
- How's the chicken?
[Ryan munching]
- So have you felt
cooped up any this week?
[patrons chattering
indistinctly]
- Well, have you?
[foreboding music]
No?
I'll take that as a yes, okay.
[patrons continue to
chatter indistinctly]
[foreboding music continues]
- What you mean?
- It's like, it's very routine.
- That's not true.
That's so not true.
- I'm just saying
that, I don't know.
I'm gonna have times where I
feel cooped up and I'm tired.
- I know, babe.
I know you'd have been happy
just sitting at home tonight.
You know?
[patrons chattering
indistinctly]
[Gypsy munching]
Be right back.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
[foreboding music]
- I think, like, tonight, I'm
just in a mood. [chuckles]
[door creaking]
[tense music]
[door thudding]
- Okay, I know you're cold.
Ooh, God, baby,
your chill bumps.
[Gypsy chuckling]
[tense music continues]
[keys clinking]
[Ryan sighing]
[engine revving]
[car signal beeping]
[engine whirring]
[wary music]
Anything else going on?
- [Gypsy] Nope.
- [Ryan] Okay.
[wary music continues]
[car engine whirring]
- [Ryan] Huh?
I mean, I'm...
It's, whatever, baby.
[Gypsy whimpering]
[distant traffic whirring]
- Yes!
I don't know why
you think I'm not.
And all of a sudden,
now you're not.
- Okay.
Tell me why.
Talk to me.
[Ryan chuckling]
- We are different
people, but like not,
we're not heading
toward different things.
Like, baby, it's okay to
be different, but we...
- I don't know.
[Bleep], you're probably already
talking to him anyway.
[vape pen clinking]
- You're not? Okay.
Then why all of a sudden
are you not happy?
When did this happen
all of a sudden?
When did you feel this
unhappiness? Tonight?
- No.
- Let's do marriage
counseling then.
Let's go to, let's at least try.
Instead of just
throw in the towel,
let's at least try.
- I know, but I'm
saying together.
I'm saying together.
We go in and we talk
about this together.
I don't want you to
make a rash decision.
- You make rash
decisions all the time.
All the time.
We were fine.
- The majority?
Like, right now, you're
having a bad day,
so therefore, you're not
happy with this marriage.
Not every day is gonna
be hunky-dory, baby.
Marriage is hard.
Nobody said it was easy.
[soft emotional music]
There's gonna be days
where you're like,
"Oh, I just want a break."
Or, "Oh, I just wanna do this.
Oh, I just need to get away."
But you have to work at it.
- Okay, right?
And are you not wanting
to fight for this anymore?
[traffic whirring]
No?
Okay.
[vape pen clinking]
[car engine roaring]
- Yeah.
[foreboding music]
[Ryan chuckling]
- Okay.
- [Ryan] Yeah.
[foreboding music continues]
[traffic whirring]
[Gypsy sniffing]
[Ryan breathing heavily]
[car door thudding]
[Gypsy sobbing]
[foreboding music continues]
[car door thudding]
[troubling music]
[Gypsy sobbing]
[crickets chirping]
[introspective music]
- You know, I just wish my
wife would stop doing this.
[introspective music continues]
Being with somebody like
her, it happens a lot.
You know, I knew
her being released,
it would be hard
on her, you know?
But I mean, I know she loves me.
I mean, that's not
even up for debate,
but it's, like, my heart
just got ripped out.
And I have to pick
it up all the time,
and I do it every time.
She feels cooped up,
and she feels freer in
Cut Off on occasion.
And you know, of course,
she felt free this last time.
It was a [bleep]
Disneyland trip.
Like, they go, and they
have all this stuff planned,
and they're gonna have fun
and [speaks gibberish].
That's not normal life.
But with me, it's a normal life.
And it's like, I don't know,
I guess she's still
stuck in fairytale world.
I don't know.
Like, I've created this
life for her and all this,
and it's, I guess, it's just
not what she imagined, yeah.
And you know, I don't
know what else is at play.
You know, she still mentions
her ex from occasions.
He continues to, like,
always is in the background.
And I'm like, "Are you talking?"
And she's like, "No."
And I'm like, "Okay."
And I have to believe that,
like, I can't think otherwise
'cause I'd go [bleep] crazy.
You know what I mean? Like,
I would go [bleep] crazy.
And then I'm the jealous
controlling one, you know?
It's just hard.
I mean, I don't wanna split up,
but I mean, it's not up to me.
You know what I mean?
It's never been up to me.
[tense music]
It's her decision, you know?
Like, she knows I'll
love her and always have.
[hopeful music]
All right. [sniffs]
[hopeful music continues]
[keys clinking]
[car doors thudding]
[Ryan breathing heavily]
[hopeful music continues]
[car engine whirring]
[birds chirping]
[serene music]
- I packed an overnight bag
so I can spend the
night with Mia.
Tomorrow night, Mom and I are
gonna go to the apartment,
gather some of my stuff,
and just spend the next
two weeks in Cut Off,
and see where my head's
out in two weeks.
- I think I'm probably
just gonna have space.
It's just ultimately I know that
I'm in a codependent marriage.
I am in a codependent
relationship.
When I went to hang
out with y'all in Cut Off,
he was feeling that
need to have me home.
So he has that
codependency to me.
Can't we-
- That was a task,
and I'm glad you, yeah.
- Have some healthy
level of boundaries?
- Boundaries?
- And independence
for the both of us?
[tense music]
- That Thursday night,
we didn't have a good
night that night,
but we talked and then,
like, we kinda made up some,
and we went to bed.
And then I come
home the next day,
and she had, like, permanently
moved into the spare bedroom.
She's like, "I'm in
the spare bedroom."
And then next thing
I know, she was gone.
And I hadn't seen her since.
And it's one of
those where, like,
she had never experienced
anything before.
You know, I knew being married
would be hard for her, you know?
Like, but in my head,
I thought, like,
her having a safety net,
somebody to rely on,
somebody to hold her at night,
somebody to tell her it's
gonna be all right was good.
But other people
who have influence
didn't see that.
- What I'm getting
from all of this,
I mean, you went from one
prison to another prison,
and now, you're in
another one and-
- [Mia] I wouldn't
go that far, Mom.
- Well, I mean, she's
stuck in that house.
You have never lived
like you should have growing up
and now is your chance.
And he should remember that.
It seems like he wants the
Gypsy that was in prison,
that was okay with him
that he stayed home
and all of this stuff.
- Not compatible.
You may love him
and he may love you,
but ultimately, when
it comes down to, like,
the things that obviously
y'all want in life
are very different.
And how are you supposed
to be in a relationship
and live your life that
you've been so eager
to live if that's who
you're married to?
- You know, I mean, yes,
y'all have been
married, you know?
It's gonna be, you know?
- I'm coming up on two years.
- But y'all, to me-
- [Mia] It's been a few months.
- Y'all been married
just a few months.
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- [Mia] To me too.
- And now, you could
see the concern that me,
and your sister, and all had.
- Yeah.
- [Kristy] You know,
like, go out and live.
- Yeah.
[depressing music]
- Gypsy's very impulsive,
but people influence her.
She's already an
impressionable young girl.
And to feed stuff in her
head, put stuff in her head,
I mean, it just
poisoned her marriage.
I know we still
have what we have.
And so does she.
That's why, I mean, I know her,
I know her family doesn't
want me to see her.
Where she's at, I would not be,
I would not feel welcomed.
I wanna show up, but
at the same time,
I wanna respect her family
'cause I've never done
anything wrong to them.
You know, the way they paint me
is I'm controlling and all this.
Well, if I show up there,
that fits their narrative more.
It's just, it's sad.
I'm sad, sad over...
[depressing music continues]
- I texted my PO,
and I asked him.
I'm like, "If I am not
happy in Lake Charles,
could I move in
with my parents?"
And he's like, "Yeah, I mean,
if you're not happy there,
I can transfer your case,
your paperwork, whatever.
to where your parents are."
- [Kristy] Yeah.
- You know, I thought I
could have been happy in
Lake Charles with Ryan,
but I also thought
that our marriage
would be a little different
than it actually is.
I've always been a people
pleaser my whole life.
And this is the one
time that I'm like,
"Okay, I'm gonna
take a step back,
and, you know,
reevaluate the situation,
and come back when
I have a clear mind
that this is honestly
what I want."
I'm not gonna say that
I'm getting a divorce
because I haven't made
that choice up yet,
but I will say that the living
environment that I'm in,
I can't get my mind right.
[contemplative music]
[car engine whirring]
- 25 minutes to be there.
- I let him know.
- You did?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Or I could do it, you could
just hand stuff to me,
you know, come to the door,
hand that to me.
- Yeah.
I mean, honestly I
just wanna, like,
get the guitars to you.
That'll be the first
thing I can give to you.
- Yeah, I'm gonna let you
bring the big suitcase.
- Yeah, I'll get
the big suitcase.
And then I have a little
small list of stuff
for you.
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]
[hand brake creaking]
Dear Lord,
I'm asking You to give Gypsy
all the strength that
she needs to go in
and do what she needs to do.
Let it go calm.
Everything's gonna be
okay, Gypsy. [smooches]
Jesus' name,
amen.
- Amen.
[dramatic music continues]
[keys clinking]
[footsteps plodding]
[light switch clicking]
Hey, baby girl. Hi, honey.
[Gypsy smooching]
Hey, honey. I know, girl, here.
Yeah, Mom.
- [Kristy] His car's not here.
- [Gypsy] He's definitely here.
[luggage bag zipping]
[clothes hangers clicking]
- [Gypsy] This is all
my hanging clothes.
- [Kristy] Gypsy,
there's a box right here.
[box clacking]
[Gypsy sniffing]
- [Gypsy] Man, I leave
the place for a little bit,
it goes to [bleep].
- [Kristy] That's
what I just said.
- [Gypsy] That's
some of my clothes.
- Pix.
Pixie, Pixie.
[boxes clacking]
- Yeah, that's it.
Oh, is that like...
Okay.
I'm gonna go make sure
that he's been
feeding her and stuff.
Okay, she's got food,
she's got water.
All right, other than
that, I think that's it.
- Jacket?
- Yeah.
- [Kristy] And the guitars?
- Bring your white puffer
because you may need it.
- [Gypsy] It might get cold?
- [Kristy] Yeah, you didn't
want your Saints jersey?
- No.
- [Kristy] I'm just thinking-
- It says Anderson on the back.
- [Kristy] Oh, that's true.
- If change was comfortable,
then I don't think anybody
would go through change.
It's just something
that you have to go
through the rough stuff to
get to where you belong.
[Gypsy sobbing]
- I'm sorry, baby girl. [sobs]
If it's separation,
that's the one thing.
If it's a divorce,
that's another thing.
- [Kristie] Pixie, you're
making my heart break.
- [Gypsy] Oh, is it the
right thing? I don't know.
Is it the wrong
thing? I don't know.
[door thudding]
[dramatic music]
He keeps texting me.
He's like, "Just tell
me you don't love me."
And I'm like, "I can't tell you
I don't like."
- Yeah.
- [Rod] She made a
mistake marrying Ryan.
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard
and her ex-fiance
that she got
engaged to in prison
have gotten matching tattoos,
- Their matching tattoos
broke my heart.
[Ryan breathing heavily]
- She needed to know the
real reason why he ended it.
- Did she?
- [Kristy] Yes,
she did because I-
- He should have told
her that, not you.
- I want a divorce.
And in six to nine months,
I'm gonna be with Ken.
I'm happy again,
and I don't wanna do
anything to mess it up.