- Birth control. Did
you figure that out?
Do you want kids right away?
- I mean, I want kids.
I just, I don't think that
right away would be smart.
- Agreed.
- Ken texted my stepmom.
- Why do you think he decided
it's time to pop back up?
- I don't think that he has
respect for my marriage.
- He doesn't like me.
- Is this the life
that we really wanna
lead for ourselves?
- But I still would
like you to remarry me.
- The timing needs to
be at a little bit
of a more convenient time.
- What?
- [Kristy] Gypsy's first
true relationship was Ken.
- I loved him so much.
I have to stay loyal
to my marriage.
I've never orgasmed
with a partner.
I have that past history
with being molested too.
Getting past the
mental blocks is hard.
- [Ryan] Who are you texting?
- I'm just texting
my sister, honey.
- He thinks Kristy's trying
to sabotage our marriage.
- If something happens
with Gypsy and Ken,
it's gonna be your fault.
- [Ken] I just feel like
it's important for me
to share my thoughts
and opinions on her
and the time that
we spent together.
[pensive music]
- It is hard to
hear about an ex.
It absolutely is hard for Ryan.
I mean, he's my husband.
And Ryan feels like Ken
is possibly a threat.
But I love Ryan,
and I want to work
on our marriage,
even if it means that
we have some things
that we need to work
through with trust.
I understand that.
- You know, now that
she's happily married,
now he's trying to come back
and try to weasel his way in?
It's like my guard's
up, you know?
But, at the same time, it's
like she's never gonna want it.
I feel like it, I don't think
she's gonna do that to me.
[pensive music]
- This is for
training, so, like,
whenever you wanna start
training for tricks,
like, you say a
command, like sit.
- Mm-hmm.
[clicker clicks]
- And then, you give a
little treat when they do it.
- I've never trained
a dog before.
- I haven't either.
- Like, I've trained it to like,
I know, like, rub
its nose in pee
when it pees in the house.
- Oh, that's not nice.
- I know, but it works.
I can't believe we're
actually getting a dog.
Like, we talked about it,
and then next thing you
know, it's like, here it is.
Did I expect to
have a puppy today?
Absolutely not.
I just wanted all my ducks
in a row before we got it.
You know, we made one phone
call and the lady was like,
"Yeah, meet me
here, here, here,"
and I was just like,
"Whoa, what just happened?"
You know, but this is a
milestone for me and Gypsy.
- Let me grab my purse.
- I have always wanted my
own family to call my own.
You know, when I was growing
up, I didn't have a dad,
so it was one of those, it
was me, my mom, my brother.
And then, my stepdad came in
and, you know, then it
became him and my mom.
And, you know, it
was just one of those
where I never had a
family where I felt like
this is my family, you know?
And it's cool now,
'cause I'm setting it up
the way I wanna set it up.
So it's my family
and I like that.
You want me to warm up
that burger real quick?
- No, let's just go.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Well, I think now that we are,
like, bringing a new addition
and a fur baby into our life
that it will make
this a little closer.
All right, think
we can roll out.
- [Ryan] Baby, where was
that towel? Did you see--
- I got it!
- Oh, my baby's on point.
- When I tell you
I got everything,
I got everything.
- My baby's on point!
I love my wife. [kisses]
[gentle music]
- [Rod] Yeah, well, I was
on the boat when Ryan-
- Ryan called you?
- Texted me.
He texted me telling me
some stuff about Ken,
and you were involved,
and he felt like you were
stepping inside the circle
or whatever.
- Right, yeah.
- That's when I called
him and talked to him,
and I agreed with him.
- Yeah, I mean, think about it.
Ken was a big part of her life,
and he has the right
to speak his opinion
and set the facts straight.
- You know, he chose not
to be with her anymore,
to give her that freedom.
But then he's gonna
come back around,
I don't know, I feel
like he's maybe trying
to worm his way
back in, you know?
- No, I think when Gypsy
and Ryan did a podcast,
and you haven't
heard it, I heard it,
they dogged him out.
He had told me, he says, "My
story needs to be heard."
- Gypsy and Ryan's
relationship is fresh, fragile,
and she needs to be happy.
That's all I want.
- I mean, I hope and
wish that they last.
If it doesn't, then we'll be
there to pick up the pieces.
- I would hope Ken
sincerely feels
that he wants Gypsy to be happy.
And in order for her to be
happy, and move on from it,
and have that closure,
just stay quiet, stay away,
and give her and
Ryan the best chance.
I do, honestly, gut-check
feeling is that he's gonna try
to somehow worm his way
back into the situation.
[tense music]
- Getting nervous.
- Why are you so nervous?
- I'm just nervous,
babe, it's a pup.
Who you texting?
- I'm texting Mia.
- I saw that address.
What does she want?
- [Gypsy] For what?
There's no address.
- Scroll back down, that's.
- Oh, that's ours, that's
for the free stuff.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I saw that, and was
like, "What the hell?"
- Yeah, that's for
the free stuff.
- That's why I was like,
"Who are you texting?"
[tense music]
Has there been any
thoughts to reach out?
- For what?
- To, you know,
has there been any desire
from you to reach out
to what's his face?
- You can say what's
his face's name?
- To Ken?
- No.
- No desire whatsoever?
- No, we're good.
- Okay.
That's what I just
wanted to know.
Like, I believe it.
The situation's done, right?
- Situation's done.
- That's one reason I love you.
What kind of stuff you
trying to get there?
- I'm just texting
my sister, honey.
[tense music]
- Okay.
- So, relax.
- I'm very relaxed.
I'm just asking,
what's going on?
- I know.
[gentle music]
- [Ryan] Hey, how
you doing? I'm Ryan.
- [Gypsy] Hi!
- [Ryan] This is my wife.
- [Gypsy] Aw, hello, baby.
- Yes, yes.
- Thank you for doing this.
- Please text me, call me
if y'all have any
problems or any concerns
with her at all.
- [Gypsy] Okay, okay.
- Thank you so much.
- You're so welcome.
- [Ryan] You just made
our family complete.
- See you, girl.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Hi, baby.
Aw, she's so little.
[Gypsy giggling]
- She loves licking on you.
- She's a good girl.
You like the name Pixie?
- I like the name Pixie.
- Okay, Pixie it is.
- [Gypsy] Hey, baby.
It's cold.
- It is cold, Pixie.
- Aww.
She's a little cold right now.
Hey, baby.
This is where we live.
Come here, baby.
I love her already.
She's only been home
for like an hour
and I absolutely love her.
She's so sweet.
You know, I think
that this breed
kind of fits our situation,
our living situation,
and us in our home right now,
so I think she's
perfect for our family.
[gentle music]
It feels like this is a good
decision for me and Ryan,
and I think it'll
give us something
to kind of bring us
closer together.
♪ Can you feel that,
babe, can you feel that ♪
♪ When I see your face,
when I see your face ♪
♪ Got me all the way,
never felt this way ♪
♪ Gotta seize the
day and feel it all ♪
- It's like we're
here in the present,
you know, we don't
live in the past,
and that's one thing I
love about me and Gypsy.
We focus on the future,
and we live in the present.
- That's a promise.
♪ Make my way to you
♪ It's new love, it's new
love, it's new love, baby ♪
- You know, it's not that I
don't like Ryan, 'cause I do.
I mean, when I
see them together,
you know, you could see that,
you know, they have that love.
Ken was her first
real relationship.
Lord, I'm friends
with all my exes.
- Since Ryan got in the picture
and they decided to get married,
I thought Ken would've
never been mentioned again.
But, apparently, it's not
gonna go away like it should.
- Now that she got closure
of really why things ended,
I don't think we'll
hear too much of Ken.
- Well, I just hope from here,
you know, if they
got their closure,
let's close the book on
Ken and don't talk to him.
- I'm not getting involved in...
- Just do like I asked
you and don't ever...
You allowed a door to open up.
If Ken wants to
reach out to Gypsy
and they wanna communicate,
you should have told Ken,
"I can't help you."
If something happens
with Gypsy and Ken,
it's gonna be your fault.
- I'm not gonna lie to
Gypsy, that's the thing.
I promised her that I would
never keep anything from her,
because that's what Dee Dee did,
and I'm not like that.
If she needs to hear
whatever he has to say
for her to heal,
let her freaking heal.
My gut, I think that
it's not fully closed.
- I'm not even gonna
call it a saga,
but it's a seed I
feel like that can,
you know, grow some bad grass.
There's not a lot I
can do to stop it.
If it's gonna happen,
it's gonna happen.
But I don't want Kristy
to be to blame for it,
or me to be to blame for it.
[pensive music]
[gentle music]
- I'm excited to, you know,
hang out with my sister.
- [Ryan] Yeah, I wish I was
going to hang out with you.
- [Gypsy] Well, we're just
gonna be doing some girl stuff,
so you probably wouldn't
be that interested.
- [Ryan] No, I wouldn't.
- I wore these
pants 'cause I knew
that she would probably
be wearing leggings,
and if she's gonna show
her body I wanted to too.
- That's nice.
[Gypsy laughing]
- Sorry, I think them
things on your chest
are bigger too now, I think.
- Well, she's got
the flat stomach.
She's got the flat stomach,
she has smaller boobs.
But she's got like
that athletic build,
and I've got that, like..
- Got that kaboom!
- I got that stripper
body. [laughing]
- Okay, now we're
turning around.
[Gypsy laughing]
Trip's canceled.
- [Gypsy] If I had
to rate myself,
I'd rate myself a solid six.
I look in the mirror
and sometimes I'm like,
"Yeah, my mom was right,
I'm not desirable."
And I look at, you know,
my sister and I'm like,
"You are so pretty."
Like, I wish I was born pretty.
- Yeah, y'all never had,
like, one-on-one girl time.
- Right.
- Oop, let me get over.
- Yeah, I mean, I just, like,
I don't know what kind of stuff
she's like into and stuff,
so, I mean, it'd be a good time
to get to know her that way.
- Yeah.
- Even though we're
10 years apart,
Mia just wants to be someone
that I can lean on and talk to.
I know that I'm
the older sister,
but, in many ways, she is the
one with the most experience,
and I go to her for advice.
- Just don't let her
talk (bleep) about me.
I know she's going to.
- She's not gonna talk
(bleep) about you.
- Yeah.
- She's not!
- Okay.
- Like, I mean,
she hasn't talked
(bleep) about you.
All she said was that
sometimes she likes you,
sometimes she's iffy about you.
- She has no reason
to be iffy about me,
that's the thing it's like...
I get it though, she's
being a protective sister.
- Yeah.
- I get it.
Mia feels how she feels.
Like, I can't change
that just over time.
Like, all I can do is be
me and be there for Gypsy,
and that's all I plan to do.
- Hello!
- Hey!
I brought your stuff.
- Perfect.
- Hey, girl.
- You look cute!
- Thank you!
- This wind ain't nothing nice.
- Sorry, it's not
better weather.
- All right.
- Y'all ladies have fun.
Y'all have a good day.
Be careful, you got
precious cargo now.
- [Mia] I know, all
right, be careful.
- [Ryan] Okay, y'all have fun.
- Love you!
- Love you, baby.
Mwah!
- Mwah.
[bright music]
So how have you been?
- Good.
- [Gypsy] How's school going?
- It's all right.
I have my first exam on Monday.
- You know, nursing is
definitely something
that I think that you
have the heart for.
I know my experiences
with doctors and nurses
hasn't been all that great,
and I have a complicated
history with it.
But, you know, I think that
it's a good profession.
I scheduled my appointment,
it's for the 27th.
- For your nose?
- For my nose.
I'm so tired of how
the profile side looks.
- I hate my profile.
- Because it's like,
it dips down and
then it dips back.
Like, it goes back up.
And if they can just shave
the bump down a little bit
to where I have a
more feminine slope,
I would be happy with that.
- Dad screwed us.
[Gypsy laughs]
People are so mean about it too.
- They are, I watched one video,
there's this dude that said,
"Big nose, beady-eyed,
Ninja Turtle looking B."
They wanna hate on anything.
- Yeah.
- And they're gonna try and find
what they can to hate on.
[gentle music]
- Well, hello, ladies.
- Hi.
- How are y'all?
- Good.
- Good, so--
- This is my first time.
I've never had one.
- Oh, is it really?
- So I have no idea
what to expect.
- I am honored to
be the first one,
'cause I will set
the bar very high
for the next one that comes.
- Yeah, so I'm like, I really
don't know what to expect,
or what to do, or anything.
My short, little legs. [giggles]
Mm, it's massaging me.
- This is you first
time in a massage chair?
- Uh-huh.
- That's crazy.
- I'm like, ooh, this
feels nice. [giggles]
Ahh. [laughs]
So things have been
a little bit weird.
- Why?
- You remember how everybody
was like, "Yeah, you
don't know someone
until you live with them"?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm learning that.
- Mm.
- I mean, it doesn't
change my love for him,
but I didn't know that he
snores like a grizzly bear.
I sleep with earplugs.
But I'm like, I didn't know
that before I married you.
- What about laundry,
and dishes, and all?
- Okay, he's good at
keeping up the dishes.
I do the laundry.
He is, I'm not gonna
say he's a hoarder,
but there's a lot of clutter.
I hate clutter, my
mom was a hoarder.
- That's what I was thinking.
- It's a problem for me.
Like, it is like an OCD
thing, I don't like clutter.
The closet, there was
clothes everywhere.
I took out everything,
and then piece by
piece, "You want this?
If not, it's going to Goodwill."
Made two Goodwill bags,
yet there's still so much.
So it's just differences
in personality,
and sometimes it
gets overwhelming.
And I have to tell him like,
"I need to go and sit
outside for a second.
Have a moment away from you.
I'll come back, I love you.
I might text you, but right
now I need this me time."
You know?
- Yeah.
- Things have been
a little bit weird
between Ryan and Kristy lately.
- Why? Because of Ken?
- Yes, so--
- I knew that was gonna happen,
I don't know why she did that.
- I mean, it was just
one of those things
that we were talking and
it led into it so easily,
and it was kind of
like out of left field,
"Yeah, I talked to Ken the
other day for like two hours."
She's like, "Yeah, he told
me, like, the real reason,
like, why he broke up with you."
And, of course, that was,
like, a huge thing for me,
because, like, I never
got closure with that.
She's like, "The
reason why he left you
is because he felt like
he was doing the
right thing by you."
So she's like, "He made
the ultimate sacrifice,
by, like, he loved you so
much that he let you go."
And then, that got me crying.
I'm like, "I loved him so much."
Okay, so stirred up
a bunch of feelings.
Okay?
I had to tell Ryan about it,
because I'm like, I don't
keep stuff from Ryan.
So I was like,
"Kristy talked to Ken,
and not only does he
regret leaving me,
but he also is single too."
[tense music]
Oh, his reaction was
something to the fact of,
he thinks Kristy's trying
to sabotage our marriage.
It's a slap in his face,
and duh, duh, duh, duh,
and so he texted Dad.
- I wear my heart on a
sleeve, I'm very sensitive.
And with Kristy, I
know she accepts me,
but it's one of those like,
quit bringing old stuff up.
You know, especially with
that situation with Ken,
I was kinda like,
"What is your purpose?"
So I called Rod and was like,
"Hey, Dad, here's the situation.
I feel like Kristy is not
respecting my marriage."
And he was like, "Man, I'll
hit you back, just hang tight."
And then, Rod called
me and he's like,
"I told Kristy if she ever
brought him up again,
that she'd be in trouble.
You know, like if Gypsy
wants to reach out,
you let Gypsy reach out."
Said, "You are not
gonna be the reason
that that door
stays open, Kristy."
And that's all I could ask for.
Kristy didn't want
us to get married.
Just accept the fact that Gypsy
made the right
choice with her life.
I wish they would stop
trying to protect her,
and trying to look for
reasons for her to leave me.
[tense music]
- Well, I don't understand
why he got Dad involved.
You're a grown man, why
you getting Dad involved?
He could go to Mom and say,
"Look, I don't like that,
you know, you said this.
Can you please not talk to
her about this anymore?
It makes me uncomfortable,
and I don't think she needs
to hear this kind of thing."
- I don't think, he's
not comfortable yet.
And he can't vent to
me, 'cause I'm like,
"Well, stop bashing Mom for
just giving me closure."
And I told him I cried too.
And he's like, "Well,
do you want him?
Go be with him.
If that's what you want,
now's the time to tell me."
- Did you think about it?
- I mean, no. [giggles]
- [Mia] That wasn't
very convincing at all.
- No, of course
not, no. [laughs]
No, I mean, I can't
focus on anything else,
but this marriage.
- You're right, you're right.
Everybody always wants
what they can't have.
- Mm-hmm.
Even though, as
much as I love Ryan
and I love our life together,
a part of me wonders that,
like, me pushing a wedding
and getting married in prison,
did I change the
course of my fate?
[tense music]
- So, did you find
a gynecologist?
- I'm working on it.
I needed to set up a
primary care first.
So I have my first primary
care doctor on Tuesday.
- Okay.
- You know what the
really sucky part is?
- What?
- I still haven't orgasmed.
I've never orgasmed
with a partner.
- Can you orgasm by yourself?
- I don't even know that.
- Okay.
- Like, I have that past
history with being molested too.
So getting past the
mental blocks is hard,
'cause I'm like,
so self-conscious.
- No, I get it, it's
just being a woman.
It's like, I don't
know any gynecologist--
- So something happened though.
- What?
Did he (bleep) in you?
Are you pregnant?
[tense music]
- You know, I don't want
Kristy to be involved
in their stuff or myself.
You know, they gotta
hash out some things.
But, you know,
when she feels like
there's something she can't
communicate with Ryan,
that she can reach out,
and she's doing that.
And that's all we can hope for,
is we're there for her to help
her make the right choice,
what's right for
her in her heart.
You know, we want
her to be happy.
[tense music]
You know, she's 30 years old.
She's making 17, 18-year-old
person type decisions.
- No, I'm not pregnant!
It only happened two nights ago.
- Did you take anything?
Oh my God, you still
can, there's still time.
I'm not even joking.
My test is on this stuff.
Gypsy, you cannot
have a kid right now.
- I just, I mean, it wasn't...
Okay, this is the
situation, all right?
- You are not on anything.
- I'm not.
- Your chances are very high.
So you could take
something up to 72 hours.
It hasn't been 72 hours has it?
- No.
- Do you even care
to take anything?
- I mean, sure.
- Because it seems
like you don't want to.
- No, I don't care, like,
I just, I don't feel like
it's going to happen, becuase--
- You don't know that though.
- It didn't happen last month.
- He did it again last month?
Gypsy!
- It may have been one time
that it was an accident.
- It doesn't matter.
- But, I mean,
it didn't result in anything.
- It doesn't matter.
Like, it...
- You're so stressed out
right now. [laughs]
[pensive music]
- She's gonna learn.
We all want her to
take a step forward
and two steps back a
few times, you know,
and on her own.
I think that's important
that we give them that space
to have some issues and be
able to reconcile those.
You know, that's how you
build a relationship.
That communication skill
helps you to better make it
through bigger and bigger
battles, I find, you know?
[engine sputtering]
[tense music]
- It's like, I'm torn.
I wanna start a family,
but then, at the
same time, I'm like,
I also wanna give
me and Ryan time
to know that this
marriage is going to work
before bringing in a child.
- That is my big thing.
Y'all are fresh, in a
sense of living together
for the first time,
y'all are learning, you
know, being dog parents.
He just went back to work,
and I don't want it to
be six months from now
and you're pregnant,
and you're like,
"Do I even want to
be with this man?"
For them to not be
careful right now,
it's kind of scary
when she brings it up
and she hasn't taken
the precaution of,
you know, going
to get that extra,
you know, medication to make
sure that it doesn't happen,
all I could do is
give that advice.
- I have, like, what
I ultimately want
in the big picture,
but then I also have, like,
the things that I'm like,
okay, well, I have a
full plate right now,
and I can't donate my time
solely to raising a
child at this point.
- I want you to get all the
things that you want first.
You won't be able to
get your nose done.
You might not be able
to get your teeth done.
- I won't.
- There are things that--
- If you're pregnant, you
can't undergo rhinoplasty.
- [Mia] Yeah, there's
a lot of things that--
- We may need to
stop at the store
and get the morning-after pill.
- We will, we can, for sure.
[Gypsy laughs]
[pensive music]
[tense music]
I'm thinking about
giving Ryan a call
and just letting him know,
you know, that I wanna take
the morning-after pill.
- Okay.
- Just as a precautionary.
- Do you wanna
call him right now?
- Sure.
- Okay.
- Okay, heh.
So, oh, wait, there he is.
Hey.
- Yeah, I, uh...
Well, I told Mia about,
you know, a few
nights ago's event.
- You know, our little
tussle in the sheets.
- So, I also, like,
you know, told her that,
you know--
- For contraceptives,
like, emergency contraceptives,
like, a morning-after
pill type of thing.
You don't got
nothing else to say?
- I don't know.
- Well--
- It's 72 hours.
- It's 72 hours, it
hasn't been 72 hours.
- Yeah, it hasn't
been that long.
- Okay.
- [Mia] I'm getting a
sister for the first time,
so I wanna protect that.
You know, you live
and you learn,
so she's gonna
make those choices
and at the end of the day,
she's gonna do what
she wants to do.
But if I could give her
some guidance in a way,
then I absolutely will.
- What are you doing?
- All right, well, we're
pulling up to the place.
Love you.
- [Ryan] Bye.
- Bye.
- [Ryan] Uh-huh.
- He's so mad. [laughs]
- [Mia] He's mad?
- I could just tell
he's not happy.
- He's not happy about you
telling me or you taking it?
- Me telling you, probably.
- Like, he's not gonna not think
you're gonna tell me all about
y'all sex life all the time.
- All the time, right.
- But, I mean, I think
this was appropriate enough
for you to get my opinion
and for me to be able
to give you my advice,
as to I think you should.
- Right.
- And, you know, I
guess y'all didn't know
that you could take
it up to 72 hours.
- Nope.
- You wouldn't have known
that if you wouldn't
have talked to me.
Who knows? Maybe you
would've had a little kid
running around in nine months.
- Right.
- You know?
- Yeah.
- But, okay.
[gentle music]
- Okay, Ryan texted me.
- And said?
- He said, "You had
to do that on camera?
I will pull out from now
on, no worries." [laughs]
- Pull out from now on?
You should've been doing
that all this time.
Oh, I'm not judging
him for it, it happens.
- No, I mean, it happens, it's
whatever, you know, I mean.
So I should probably
take it, right?
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah, I should probably--
- Go get it.
- Okay.
I know in the big picture,
Ryan and I want a family.
But Mia's right, like,
that doesn't mean
that we can't be responsible.
There's a lot of roadblocks
that we're having
to face right now,
and so I just wanna make sure
that I'm 100%, he's 100%,
that we're stable for the child,
and that's just not right now.
Wow, literally one pill.
- Yes.
- 40 bucks for one pill.
This is ridiculous.
- It's either 40 bucks
for that one pill
or thousands of
dollars down the road.
What do you want?
- You're right, you're right.
Down the hatch.
- [Mia] Mm, dinner.
[tense music]
- Cheers, to not
getting pregnant.
- [Mia] Good job, I'm proud.
I'm glad you were smart
enough to take something.
- Honestly, I mean,
I feel the same way.
Like, I wanna make sure
that going into it,
we know, 10 toes down,
that this is something
that is for the long haul
and we're both ready.
'Cause, I mean, even
if we were both ready
emotionally and mentally,
I just don't think that
the timing for right now
is where it needs to be.
I think I'll know when I'm
ready when I can fully say
that I could put myself
aside and put a child first,
and right now, I can't say that.
Oh, my Uber's here.
- All right, I'll help you out.
- All right.
- Okay.
- [Mia] Today was very,
like, different for me.
Like, I never had a sister
I could go shopping with or
get my nails done, you know?
And I feel like I'm getting
a sister and a friend.
I hope to be somebody
that she could talk to
that's not Mom or Dad.
That's somebody that
could understand,
but also give advice, but
listen when she needs it,
and, like, I want
to be that for her.
- All right, Mimi, I love you.
- All right, I love
you too, be careful.
- All right, I will.
- Let me know whenever
y'all make it back.
- [Gypsy] All right,
I'll text you.
- All right, don't slip.
- All right
- All right, love you.
- [Gypsy] Love you.
[gentle music]
This is Ryan flipping out,
because I told my sister
about our difficulties.
- No, you told the
world about it.
Not your sister, the world.
[door thuds]
[birds chirping]
[gentle music]
- He needs to understand
that I have been living
my whole life in a cage.
How I used to be with my
mom, I felt powerless.
When I am feeling powerless,
my reaction is to
take back control.
I'm just trying to
find warning signs,
and maybe I'm looking too hard,
maybe I'm overanalyzing,
but I wanna make sure that
I take care of myself.
- You know, with Gypsy and her
childhood traumas and stuff,
I have to be careful,
because I don't want her to
think that is the situation,
'cause it's not,
it's not at all.
You know, I'm not her mother.
I'm not trying to prevent
her from living her life.
You know, like, it just...
I hate when she feels that,
like, if I hit a trigger
and feels that for a second,
it makes me take a
step back and be like,
"Okay, well, let's rethink it,
and then we'll come back to it,"
because, you know,
that's not who I am.
- I feel like, you know,
there's gonna come another
time and another time
where he gets in his
emotions about something
and wants our whole world
to be just about us.
And I'm gonna
continue keeping up
that feeling and
that demeanor of,
that's my family and I can
talk to them if I want to.
But I will say that
if there comes a time
that I see that I am being
controlled, I'm leaving.
[tense music]
- Take this little part here,
just slide it up
underneath your face
kind of on the shirt
right down here.
[tense music]
- I've never done
an interview before,
because, in the past, I
didn't wanna play a part
in the media circus.
- It is, it's crazy.
Yeah, she's blown up more
than I ever thought she could,
you know, or wanted her to.
We talked about what
kind of dog we wanted,
and I always wanted a husky
my whole life as a kid.
And if I got one, I was
gonna name him Balto,
and she loved that,
'cause she always loved
that movie as well.
And, you know, yeah,
she just told me
that was her
favorite dog as well,
and that she always
wanted a husky as well.
We actually planned on
that for our future,
that we were gonna get a husky.
That was one of the things
that we bonded over.
Come here, drop it.
Ready?
We were not together when
I got Parker, you know.
That was years after
our separation.
- Well, I'm more separated
from her than ever,
and I just feel like
it's important for me to
share my thoughts and opinions
on her and the time
that we spent together,
and everything will
unfold as it should.
[tense music]
- [Producer] Were you
supportive of the marriage?
- No, I wasn't.
- Anytime that anybody
has reservations
about our relationship,
they're not in your
favor so much anymore.
- What things would you
change about your nose?
- That looks so much better.
- Wow, that is crazy!
- Woke Ryan up, I
said, "I miss Ken."
- Gypsy's gone to her
parents without me.
It did hurt not
being asked to come.
- Captain Gypsy Rose.
- [Ryan] So I still can't
get a video call, huh?
Is there somebody there
you don't want me to see?
- All right, well, I gotta go.
- [Ryan] All right, fine.
- Sometimes it's
actually really nice
not to have him around.