- I was in prison, restricted,
now I'm getting all glammed
up and I'm in New York City.
I was engaged once before.
- To Ken?
- Yeah, to Ken.
The day that I got outta
prison, Ken texted my stepmom
and I'm like, "You know he's
sniffing around."
- Gypsy is amazing, you know,
it's so cliché, you know,
like baby you complete
me, but she really does.
- So this will be where
all of your tables
are set up for the reception.
- [Ryan] That place
was beautiful.
- Yeah. But the timing needs
to be at a little bit of
a more convenient time.
I was close with my
mother's side of the family
when I was really little,
but I think that I have
bonds to mend still.
I know I didn't turn out
how you wanted me to.
He sent me a lot of pictures.
He mailed them to me.
- Kristy has continued
conversation with Ken.
Sorry dude, you had
your shot, move on.
- Ken is single.
What's gonna happen when
Ryan and I have an argument?
[tense dramatic music]
[soft music]
[Gypsy sighs]
I can't sleep.
I had a nightmare about my mom.
Snuck out of bed while
Ryan was still asleep.
So I came out on the patio.
[sirens in background]
Thinking about that house.
Thinking about the
coulda, shoulda, wouldas.
It's not easy to
live with, guys.
- Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Nightmares I've had for,
since my crime.
So, and I mean, it's not
always about the crime,
it's about my life with my mom.
It always involves my mom.
There's nothing that I could
do to stop the nightmares.
It's my psyche going over things
that I wish I could have
or should have done differently.
And so I just keep
going back to that.
[tense suspenseful music]
It was my choice to
commit this crime.
I don't even know
like the road to
self-forgiveness.
Like, like who shows
you the first step?
[clock ticks]
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard
suffered horrible abuse
at the hands of her mother.
- She destroyed Gypsy's
computer and phone
and then she chained her
to her bed with handcuffs.
- This is not Gypsy Rose
Blanchard's belly button.
This is actually
a scar left over
from the feeding tube that
Gypsy Rose Blanchard's mother
forced her to have.
- She was fed very little,
forced to go to the
bathroom on herself.
And Dee Dee also connected a
dog leash to Gypsy and herself
so she would feel any time
Gypsy moved in the night.
- Gypsy says that she is
looking forward to a new life
and a new start now that
she's out of prison.
[cars humming past]
[soft music]
- I've only been
here what, once?
I've only been here once and
it looks completely different.
- Yeah.
- Like completely different.
It looks like a different house.
- Yeah, we've done a lot
- Uh huh.
- I don't know,
it's kind of crazy.
Like, I don't know,
I've been having a picture
of me and her in there
since like middle school.
Like she's my sister, you know?
I wanted her in there
and like she has short
hair in the picture
and she's in a
wheelchair holding me
and now like she's
walking through the house
and she's not in a
wheelchair no more.
- [Rod] Let's go!
- [Mia] Are y'all
just going ride?
- We're going to
stop at the cemetery
so she can see her
grandmother, Emma.
And we're gonna go through
the Golden Meadow Park.
Yeah.
- I think I know
where Mama's grave is.
- Really?
- Yeah. I haven't been to her
grave since I was like 10, so.
- Would you like to bring
some flowers or anything?
- Yeah, that would be nice.
- [Rod] All right, let's go.
[gentle music]
Golden Meadow baby. Look.
- [Gypsy] Yeah, this used
to be my favorite park
in Golden Meadow.
Like this used to be my
favorite spot as a kid.
- I think it was a lot
of our favorite spots.
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- [Rod] Like in the
spring it's really nice.
You can go park under
those oak trees.
- [Kristy] Yeah.
- Y'all want to stop
right here for a minute
and maybe take a picture?
- [Gypsy] All right.
- [Rod] Under the
trees right here maybe?
All right.
- Hey.
[lips smack]
- You liked this park as a kid?
- Yeah, I did.
My mom used to take me here
when I was really little.
It was one, I don't remember
much from my childhood,
but this is like
my favorite spot.
It was such a simpler
time when I was little.
Like nothing was complicated.
The things, I mean, my
life was complicated,
but my perception
of my life wasn't.
Like all I knew
is mommy loved me.
Grandma loved me, Papa loved me,
my aunts and uncles loved
me, my cousins loved me,
and that's all I knew.
- [Ryan] That's cool.
- Who's gonna take a picture?
- Go ahead and get in
there with your people.
They are my people now, too.
They my family, too, so.
- Yeah. You're
part of the tribe.
- [Ryan] I'm part
of the family now.
All right.
I like it.
- [Rod] Okay,
let's go. We gotta go.
Remember I said your mom
and I got back together
for a little while?
- {Gypsy] Uh-huh.
Me and Dee Dee lived, I
think it was this street.
- [Ryan] There's a
little spot right here.
- I can't quite remember man.
It was one of these little
houses in this neighborhood.
I'm not exactly sure.
- I'll never know.
- We didn't, it was
like three months.
Okay. And I was trawling so I
might have spent a week there,
you know?
But that's when you had
the breathing machine.
- [Gypsy] Oh yeah.
- [Rod] Yep.
- [Gypsy] That's what
came first, wasn't it?
The sleep apnea machine?
- [Rod] The sleep apnea
was the first, the first thing.
- [Ryan] How old were you?
- She used to tell me.
- I was little little.
- She used to put
you sleeping on her.
- God baby. She put you
in that sleep apnea machine
that young?
- [Gypsy] Yeah, very little.
- That's terrible.
- It wasn't easy to
sleep with all that [bleep].
[gentle music]
- Straight up in the front.
Okay. I'm gonna let you
go do your thing, Gypsy.
- My grandma Emma, we
all call her Mama Emma.
But I called her Momsy.
She was a great grandmother.
And from what I
remember, you know,
she always said I was the
favorite grandkid to me.
And she would dress me up in
these little frou-frou dresses
with the cute little
socks and everything.
And I think I was
seven when she passed.
And like, that's when
my mother really started
to spiral out of control.
Like I remember my mom
was so angry at God
when my grandmother passed away
she took all the angel statues
that she had in the house
and just was smashing
them on the ground.
She was devastated.
My mom always wanted to be
buried with my grandma Emma.
Like if it was in my control,
I would've done that right away.
But I need to do something
to get a sense of closure.
Hey Mama.
[sad gentle music]
We had good memories
together when I was a kid.
- Yeah.
- This is my husband Ryan.
And he's a sweetheart.
You would've liked him.
He treats me good.
He cooks a great gumbo.
I know I didn't turn out
how you wanted me to,
but you know I love you
and I know you wished
better for me and my mom.
I wanted to put
Mama where you are.
Unfortunately that was a little
something outta my control.
And I'm hoping that you
and her are in heaven.
She could be at peace finally
and feel the love that she
needed to feel all along.
So, I love you, Mama.
I feel like I failed
her as a granddaughter
and I'm sorry that
I made the mistakes that I did.
[gentle music]
- [Gypsy] This wind is kicking.
- [Bobby] What's going on?
- Hi!
- Gypsy!
- Hey!
- Good to finally see you.
- You too.
- I was close with my
mother's side of the family
when I was really little,
but I think that I have
bonds to mend still.
I'm a big believer in that
it's like never too
late to do that.
Is this where you live?
- [Bobby] Yeah, I live here.
- [Gypsy] Oh, okay.
- [Bobby] So this is
my dog and my cat.
- [Gypsy] Aw. Hello!
- The last time I seen
Gypsy, she was four years old
and she was pushing other
kids around in the wheelchair.
My parents, my dad really,
he knew some things.
He would hear hearsay
from the aunts, you know,
from his two sisters.
They would tell us, you know,
"Gypsy's going back
into the hospital.
She's got another surgery."
So I just knew her as
being a sickly kid.
I really didn't know much else.
It's been a long time.
- You know that I,
whenever I was going through
my mom's wallet, like,
or whenever she would
pull credit cards out,
she kept a picture of you.
- [Bobby] Yeah?
- In the back of her wallet.
A little wallet size.
- Yeah.
- [Gypsy] Her whole life.
- We were good friends.
We were really good friends.
Like as far as I thought anyway.
- [Gypsy] Mm-hmm.
- [Bobby] Like she was like, she
was closer to my age, you know?
- Yeah.
- So all the other aunts were
like my older aunts, you know?
- Yeah.
From what I gather,
everyone of the family
keeps on telling me
that they knew my
mom was different.
Like by different,
what did they mean
when they say different?
- It was like she was
bipolar or something.
- She actually was
diagnosed with bipolar.
- Oh yeah. Look, one day
your mom was still
very much a teenager
and we were on the trampoline
and would peel open this orange
and she picks off this
one little whatever,
a little pocket,
little packet of, and
so it's sitting there
and she's talking to
it like it's a baby
or something like that.
And she's real genuine about it.
- What?
- And like she's going on, she's
like it's name and whatever
and then how much she's
gonna love it and treat it
and then just smashes it
and then she takes off
and I'm like, what the
the [bleep] was that?
- What?
- Yeah. But it was just so
traumatic to me as a kid
'cause I was buying
her little story,
whatever she was
saying, you know?
- Well sometimes whenever
you're a young kid like that,
we hear things and we see things
and things go on and
we're kind of like,
we don't really pay
attention to it.
Like when my mom would
say she heard voices,
I should have told
someone then like,
"Hey, mommy hears voices."
- [Bobby] Yeah.
- But at that young of a age,
I didn't wanna make her
feel bad about herself.
It's just kind of like,
what do you say when
you're that young?
You know, family member
after family member was like,
"We knew your mom was weird."
She was different, but that's
all they attributed it to.
I mean, I knew there was
times that like she saw shapes
and she heard voices.
But growing up I
didn't even know
what mental illness
was back then.
In the family that I grew up in,
there wasn't much education
about mental health,
therapy, and things like this.
So there was not that foundation
of an understanding
enough about it
to know how to
help the situation.
- I didn't know how
far it had gotten
because like I say, I hadn't
seen her since you were four.
And once in a while I
get a little snippet of,
okay, Gypsy's doing this.
She's back in the hospital.
I remember Kristy come
and get tattooed with me
and she was talking about you
being in the Special Olympics
and I was just like, "Yeah,
of course, she could walk.
Of course she's dominating at
Special Olympics," you know?
[Gypsy laughing]
But I don't know why
she hadn't stepped up
and said anything
about, you know,
there was so many
people that failed you.
- Now after the fact, I've
been told multiple times
"We knew something
was a little off,"
or "We suspected,"
and I'm like,
"Well, could I ask why
didn't you say anything?"
And they're like, "We
just didn't wanna risk
upsetting your mom."
- Yeah. Well I was second
guessing my own mind
because after seeing
just pictures of you,
tubes in your mouth, you
know, tubes down your throat.
So I'm starting to think
maybe I'm [bleep] up,
maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe she can't walk.
Or maybe Dee Dee
has told her so long
that she can't walk,
that she really physically
can't do it anymore.
Like her mind is triggered
the whole situation itself.
Her legs completely.
- Have you talked to anybody
from that side of the family
about how they feel about me
and having
communication with me?
- No, not so much.
I can't see how they don't
see your side of the story.
You know what I'm saying?
Like they, or maybe
they just shut it off
because they feel a certain way,
that's their baby sister.
You know what I'm saying?
- Yeah. Of course.
I have my perception,
but other people
have theirs too.
So it's nice to kind of
listen and take it in.
I can't undo the past, you know?
All I can do is move forward.
I mean, but it was
so good to catch up.
- It was so great catching up.
- Talking to you.
- We got so much
more living to do.
- I know.
- [Bobby] Let's get
some pain going.
- Okay. Oh, I'm nervous.
I want to have my
cousin tattoo me
because I always said if I
get a tattoo, number one,
I want it to mean something
and I want Bobby to do it
because he had did my mother's,
he did my dad's,
he did Kristy's.
He's done my cousins.
So it's like a family thing.
Like he's the tattoo artist.
He's the place to go.
- [Bobby] Do you like the
size of the fleur-de-lis
as opposed to this?
- Yeah, I like that.
- [Bobby] Okay.
- So I'm getting a unalome
with a fleur-de-lis on top.
The unalome is a symbol for
basically life's journey.
So it means that the twist
and turns of life happens.
That's part of our journey,
but it doesn't make
it any less beautiful.
And the fleur-de-lis is
obviously for French culture,
which I am Cajun, so.
[Gypsy laughs]
Yeah.
This is my first one.
- [Producer] It's
your first tattoo?
- It's my first tattoo.
- [Bobby] Her first
professional tattoo.
- I have a pick 'n poke
that I did in prison.
- You gotta sharpen up a staple.
Yeah.
Take some gel pen ink and
drive it into yourself.
- Yeah. This one right
here. It was a K for my ex.
Once he dumped me I was like,
this freaking K needs to go.
- Yeah. Scrubbing
off with Brillo.
- I may have to make
another appointment.
[gentle music]
[Gypsy laughing]
- [Gypsy] I'm gonna
get comfortable.
- [Ryan] Oh, that's what
it's gonna look like, huh?
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- You excited?
Oh, that's gonna be beautiful.
That is beautiful.
You got this.
[tattoo machine whirrs]
- Ever thought about
getting big tattoos or no?
- No, I never thought about it.
I've had my fair
share of labs and IVs
and tests and over the course
of eight and a half years,
I think my threshold
for pain has shortened.
But the tattoo is less painful
than the labs that I had.
[Gypsy chuckles]
- [Bobby] Some people say
tattoos hurt
more than childbirth.
I don't believe that.
- I don't know.
I haven't experienced
the other yet.
- [Bobby] That makes two of us.
- [Gypsy] I think it hurts
less than the pick 'n poke
that I did.
Is that it?
- [Gypsy] Oh my God.
That wasn't bad at all.
- [Bobby] No, I told you
it wasn't gonna be nothing.
- I wouldn't go that
far but it wasn't bad.
- The pain will wear
off and you'll be like,
"All right, what
can I get next?"
[Gypsy laughs]
- I'm so proud of myself.
I got a tattoo.
[laughing]
Like definitely a moment of
independence right now for me.
Like I never thought
that I'd get a tattoo.
And it looks so pretty.
The fact that like, this is
just a moment of freedom.
It's a choice.
Like getting a
tattoo is a choice
and I finally get to have
the choice to do one.
- That's cool.
- [Gypsy] That is cool.
[gentle music]
- Well, Ryan was
supposed to help me cook.
- I didn't plan on
getting a tattoo,
but I'm getting one
just hanging out
and he's like, what you want?
Next thing you know,
I just started talking
and he is like, "Oh, I'll draw
you up something real quick."
And I was like, "Let's do it."
I was like, why not?
I'm here, let's make it happen.
He's gonna do like a rose
and then the leaves are
gonna be like a fleur-de-lis.
- [Gypsy] Ooh.
- You know, I wanted a rose.
- I know.
[lips smack]
- Gypsy Rose.
- I love that she gets
to try some of this food.
Maybe she'll want the recipe.
It's been passed down
from Kristy's mama to me.
So I'm just happy that
her and Mia are both here
at the same time.
You know.
Coming here to my house,
I mean, I'd like for her
to just feel at home.
Waited for her to come back
here a long time, you know?
And I'd like for her to see
where she could have
lived, you know?
And I wish she could
stay, you know.
- Told y'all it's
a mess in here
'cause I'm looking, I'm going
through so much pictures
to put in albums.
I think I have, when she
first started dating Ryan.
He sent me a lot of pictures.
He mailed them to me.
Gypsy's first true
relationship was Ken,
where she experienced struggles
and experienced laughter
and experienced heartache.
[paper ripping]
This is stuff that she had
when they were still together.
They lasted for about like
two years, I wanna say.
And what I thought at the time
is that he couldn't
take the heat.
People are trying to
find the information,
calling his family and you
know, calling him at work.
And next thing you know,
she called me
hysterically crying
that he broke up with her.
When they did
split I was pissed.
You know, you promised you
would be there for her.
And when the [bleep]
got real, you left.
I loved Ken.
Me and Ken still
have a friendship.
And I don't care
who likes it or not.
When my kids break
up with somebody,
I don't break up with them.
- I mean, having Ryan,
the kind of guy he is,
he's really easy to
like, I don't know.
He's not shy, you
know, he is outgoing.
So, I mean, Ryan got her
through those last couple years.
And you know, and
I told him, I said,
"You're gonna have
your hands full, Ryan."
You know it's gonna
be a job for you
to like keep her in
check a little bit.
She's spontaneous and she can
make some quick decisions.
And that's why I say he is
gonna have his hands full.
- Ryan is a great guy, you know,
but if her and Ken would
still have been together
and she got outta prison,
I knew in my heart
she was gonna be safe.
I wouldn't have worried.
And I didn't know there
was more to the story
of why he ended
it until recently.
He reached out and he said,
"I need to talk to you."
He called me and
he explained to me
that people were telling him,
"If you love her
enough, let her go.
Let her find
herself on her own."
And he said, look, you
know, if he would've known,
she would've dated some,
like, found somebody else
and got engaged, he
wouldn't have let her go.
[tense dramatic music]
[gentle music]
- No. Mine don't hurt at all.
- Not yet.
- [Ryan] Not yet.
[car door slams]
- [Rod] What up?
- Look at it!
- It looks good.
- I know it looks good.
I want you to see Ryan's.
- I can't even tell
it's covered like.
- I know. I know,
- What you got, bro?
Oh, check that out!
That's awesome man!
- Isn't that badass?
- Yes!
- With the rose and the
fleur-de-lis and the rose.
- [Rod] Good. Very original man.
[soft music]
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- [Ryan] All right, we're coming
Everybody bow their heads.
Let's hold hands, too.
Heavenly Father,
we come together tonight
tonight on a joyous night,
joyous occasion, a new
beginning for all of us,
mainly Gypsy.
Lord we ask that
you bless this meal.
You bless our family,
you bless Gypsy,
and we give you
praise and thanks
for where you've
brought us today, Lord.
In Jesus' name. Amen.
- [All] Amen.
- [Ryan] Yeah. Very nice.
- Let's eat.
I hope y'all enjoy it.
- [Mia] Where's the plates?
- [Rod] We got plates
here. Forks.
We got some drinks in here.
Other drinks.
We got a tong for the shrimp.
- [Ryan] Okay.
- [Mia] Are you gonna
eat some crawfish, Gypsy?
- No.
- [Mia] Why?
- Oh, thank you.
I'm nervous about it.
- [Mia] What if I peel it for
you? Will you try it then?
- Yeah.
- No I haven't. I haven't.
I know I'm from Louisiana
and I never had crawfish.
- I'm the butt of people's
jokes. It's okay.
It's so good.
I'm feeling comfortable
in this element
because it's like I'm
comfortable around my dad.
I'm comfortable
around Kristy and Mia.
This is home for me.
[upbeat music]
In this environment,
I'm not a celebrity,
I'm just Gypsy.
People see me for
who I really am.
And this is my element.
This is my home.
♪ So it's you
♪ I don't even care
if you turn into ♪
♪ Yesterday
- You know, me and my
family, we're humble people
and we don't walk red carpets.
I was never the type to
say, I wanna be famous.
I wanna sing, I wanna dance.
I wanted to be a veterinarian.
I wanted to help little animals.
This is, you know, the phase
where I'm analyzing my life.
I realize I'm not
in the past anymore.
I'm in the present.
I want to just be a
good wife to Ryan,
a good friend, a good daughter.
I don't wanna take that baggage
from my past into my future.
So leaving all that behind
is something that I
definitely am working on.
But we'll see how it goes.
[gentle music]
[soft music]
- Make sure I got everything.
There's my USB port, batteries.
This has been a great
two weeks, three weeks,
whatever it's been
like a whirlwind.
But now it's time
to get back to work.
But at the same time
it's eight hours.
I'll be away from Gypsy a day.
I need a towel.
Where's our towels?
Did we wash 'em?
- Yeah.
- Hold on.
- Damn it.
Oh [bleep]. Oh [bleep].
Crap, crap, crap.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
- Oh crap, crap, crap.
- [Ryan] It's okay.
Just go grab a towel.
- [Gypsy] Okay, yep. It's
all over my magazine.
- [Ryan] It's okay.
Wipe the magazine.
It's okay.
We can get you another one.
[Gypsy mutters]
It's just coffee baby.
- We'll just buy another copy.
- [Ryan] Yeah, we're
probably gonna have to.
- Just throw it away.
It'll be all right for now.
I don't wanna leave you.
- I'll hold the fort down.
- I know.
- I'll walk you to the car.
- Okay.
Gypsy not going nowhere today.
- I'm not going nowhere.
Spending time with my family,
I felt like a sense
of connection.
And I know this is gonna
sound a little messed up,
but I went from living all the
time in a house with my mom
where we really didn't
go a lot of places
except to New Orleans
or to Kansas City
for doctor's appointments.
We would be posted
up in our house
and then going from
that to prison.
And then now I'm here
at the apartment.
I don't feel a need to
go out and make friends.
But I don't feel like
I'm completely satisfied
with being so
constricted either.
Good thing I like to organize.
It took me six hours
to straighten it up.
All of this was a
pile of dirty clothes.
He's already dirtying
up my closet.
I said the moment he
would dirty my closet,
we're having a fight.
I've had many tasks
as a housewife so far.
This is something that I've
been needing to get to.
I mean he does understand
that I have a history
of living with a hoarder.
And so this kind of
stuff irritates my soul.
Growing up there
was a whole room
that was just like this
junk room with piles
and piles of clothes
that needed to be washed.
Like it was traumatic in
a way that it makes me
where I don't like clutter.
Ryan, he's, well, you know,
he was a bachelor
before he met me.
So he knows that we
are built differently
and he knows that it gets
on my everlasting nerve.
[gentle music]
Hey.
- How's your day going?
- All I'm doing is piddling
around the house, watching tv.
I went through the
closet and for a guy,
he has so much clothes.
- Oh, Ryan's calling in.
I declined it for a second
just so I can finish up.
It's fine.
He'll be fine. He'll be fine.
Well, I cleaned it out and
I washed all the clothes.
[soft music]
- Yeah. I was just calling to,
well, texting you to check in.
And, uh.
- What?
- [Kristy] Yes.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- So is that why he
ended things with me?
- You know, I, like,
before I met Ryan, mom,
I was holding on so hard
I never let go
because I thought maybe
at the end of it all,
maybe a week before I got out,
he'd come back in and say,
you know, "I'm ready.
I'm ready to be with
you through this.
I'm sorry I wasn't
there for you.
Can we pick up
where we left off?"
But it never happened, and...
[emotional music]
- I loved him so much.
There's not a day
that goes by that
he doesn't pray for you.
- I just don't, I
just don't understand
because it's like he
found someone else.
- Of course not.
- [Kristy] No. Right.
- And it would
cause an argument.
Ryan and I, we have like
a complete open line
of communication and everything.
But also like, there was a
time that maybe like I wanted,
you know, not to have it.
So in case Ken would text,
but then I'm like, that
would be still harboring
an omission.
I'm gonna tell Ryan
about it later.
But knowing what
you just told me,
in a different world,
if I wasn't married to Ryan,
knowing all of this.
[snaps fingers]
- [Kristy] I know.
You don't even need
to say it, girl.
- Okay. I'm gonna
hop off of here.
I love you.
- All right. I love you, too.
- Okay. Bye.
- [Kristy] Bye.
[contemplative music]
- God, for years,
he never gave me like
an answer of like,
what was the final straw.
And for years I went
through like a huge,
like self-doubt tunnel.
Like I know that he is
interested in blondes.
I'm not blonde, I'm a brunette.
So I'd go in the shower,
take fingernail clippers
and just cut my hair off
trying to do everything I can
to get his attention again.
I would've given
anything to that man.
I would've bought the sun,
the moon and the stars
and gave it to him on a platter.
And that hurts me that
I loved him that much.
- Because I feel like no
one is ever gonna love him
as much as I loved
him at that time.
And it makes me
feel better knowing
that he's truly
sorry for hurting me.
But it doesn't change anything.
Like I married Ryan,
I have a marriage now.
I'm wearing this wedding ring
that belonged to Ryan's mom.
Like I have a commitment
to my husband.
And I wanna keep that.
But what's gonna
happen when Ryan
and I have an argument?
Is that little thought
in the back of my head
gonna say, "Ken is single.
And he's always understood me."
Like he was my
best friend first.
So I can't take it.
I have to stay loyal
to my marriage.
I can't entertain the
thought of anything else.
[soft music]
[door clicks open]
- Baby!
- [Gypsy] Hey!
- [Ryan] Hey sweetie.
- How was your day?
Did all the students
talk your ear off?
- I had some.
- Lemme show you what I did.
- You know, I had a full
eight hours at work, right?
- Now it's gonna be a
little bit of a shock.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- I see you threw
out our spaghetti
that was good that I
ate for lunch. Okay.
- All right. Ready? Ready.
- Good God.
[Gypsy chuckles]
Where's our food, baby?
- I knew you were
gonna say that.
- [Ryan] We had food.
- Yeah, but it
was all old stuff.
Okay, so you've got onions.
- Baby, what happened
to that chicken
that I just cooked?
- The chicken is right
here. I saved it.
- Okay.
- And the rice was
good too, right?
- Didn't know that.
I kept the bacon.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I kept the bacon.
So yeah, you had a
whole lot of condiments
- And you throw those away?
- Just the empty ones.
- What empty ones?
- They had a lot
of empty [bleep].
- It is like we had food.
- Yeah, but honey, that was old.
- Gypsy...
I said make it your
home and you have.
Damn, you just hit me with
a lot in like five seconds.
- I know. I cleaned
out the fridge,
I cleaned out all [bleep]
that was in my closet.
- Well I didn't know you were
cleaning out our whole life.
- It didn't take me
very long either.
- Well no, it doesn't
take people long
to throw [bleep] away.
[Gypsy chuckles]
All right. Anything else
I need to be aware of?
- Uh uh.
- [Ryan] What are these?
- [Gypsy] That's
them yucky pillows
I don't know why were keeping.
- [Ryan] What? That were where?
- That was in your closet.
- Baby, 'cause you don't
throw pillows away.
- You absolutely do.
You absolutely should
change your pillows,
especially when
they look like this.
This is gross.
Ugh!
- Don't throw these away.
Look, throw the food out,
but not that big Tupperware,
you don't throw that
big Tupperware away.
- You don't even
drink that stuff.
Where did these come from?
- In case somebody ever
came over and did it?
Maybe my ex-girlfriend
came over.
- Okay.
I got something to
tell you tonight.
- [Ryan] What's that?
- I'll get you back for that.
- [Ryan] Oh really? No.
Get away from me.
No.
- Come here.
- No.
I don't like that.
No.
Get away from me. No.
[soft music]
[birds chirp]
- Yes. Kristy has continued
conversation with Ken.
He's been reaching out to
her just to ask questions
and things like that
because Gypsy has blocked his
number, has refused contact,
has chose to move
on with her life.
And now that she's outta prison,
he's like trying to
weasel his way back in.
And Kristy has continued
to allow that door,
like she keeps cracking
that door open.
I'm mad at Kristy over this
because it's like,
what are you doing?
What is the point?
- So I knew that he
would get a little
ticked off at Kristy.
He got a little
ticked off at me, too
when I told him that I
started to get all emotional
and I'm like, what
do you expect?
Like, does it break
my heart a little bit
to learn that Ken left me
because he thought he
was doing the right thing
for me at the time?
Yeah, of course
it broke my heart.
And of course his
reaction was like,
"Well if you wanna
go be with him,
then go be with him."
And I am like, "We are married."
I am like, "I love you.
I am invested in our
life together here."
- I mean, I'm sure
he regrets it.
I mean, why wouldn't he?
She's out. She's beautiful.
And I'm sure everybody
in his circle's
telling him he's a
dumb mother [bleep]
'cause he is a
dumb mother [bleep].
Pardon my language, I'm sorry.
I'm just pissed off.
He left a wonderful woman,
a beautiful, wonderful woman.
And he left her and I came
along and swooped her up.
You know, that's what happens
when you leave a good woman.
There are options.
You know, like, and
Gypsy's happy with me.
So it's like, dude, go on.
Apparently the D is
fire or something.
Like, sorry dude, you
had your shot move on.
[tense music]
I'm tired of talking about him.
I wish he would just go
away like he needs to.
Like, pretty soon I'm
gonna get involved
and you do not want that, Ken.
Believe me, you
do not want that.
- [bleep]
- Dang. I love my wife.
- [Gypsy] I want to
work on our marriage.
Even if it means that
we have some things
that we need to work
through with trust.
- Just do like I asked you
and don't ever reach
out to Ken ever.
She's 30 years old.
She's making 17, 18-year-old
person type decisions.
- I don't know.
- So something happened though.
- Are you pregnant?
Oh my God.
- [Producer] Why do
you want to talk now?
[suspenseful music]