- [Woman] Gypsy was
Dee Dee's daughter,
but also her prisoner.
- Hospitals is what I knew,
surgeries is what I knew.
I have always had
a difficulty letting go
of my ex-fiance, Ken.
- Gypsy Blanchard
will be set free.
- She's ready to go home to
Louisiana with her husband.
- Oh my God. I did not sleep.
Oh, it feels so
weird being in a car.
- Yeah. You're free.
We're being followed.
[Gypsy groans]
- [Bystander] Any plans?
- Lots of them.
- Made it.
- Hey!
We got another situation
going on though.
- I just need a minute, okay.
I'm so sorry. [sobbing]
I don't know...
- [Kristy] Don't be sorry!
- I do not feel free right now.
I am in a different
form of prison.
[suspenseful music]
[Gypsy crying]
[gentle pensive music]
[Kristy faintly speaking]
- [Kristy] It's okay.
- [Gypsy] [sobbing] I'm sorry.
- [Kristy] Like I said, there
is nothing to be sorry about.
[tense music]
[people chattering]
- [Gypsy] I'm just
scared about them saying,
okay, you're being
argumentative.
Okay, you're
getting a violation.
- [Mike] Okay.
- [Gypsy] You're
getting sent back.
- So first of all,
you have to actually
commit a violation
for them to revoke
you, which you haven't.
Right now the guy that
we need to deal with is,
sounds like he was missing
a piece of information.
- Mmm-hmm.
- We'll sort this out.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- Okay?
- [Ryan] Thanks, boss.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- Thank you.
[gentle music]
I'm a very responsible person
and I'm not gonna
argue with anyone.
If they give me a
directive, I will follow it.
They always say,
the justice system is meant
to fail an individual,
but I'm not gonna let them.
It's whatever it
takes to keep me free.
[gentle tense music]
[phone ringing]
[people chattering]
- [Ryan] This is Ryan.
Hold on one second for me, sir.
Let me get Gypsy.
[people chattering]
[Ryan murmurs]
[somber music]
- Hello?
- Okay, would that
be immediately or,
or tomorrow morning.
- Okay, tomorrow morning?
- If that is yes,
if that is okay,
because we have like, literally
not even slept two hours.
- Twelve.
- Yes.
- Yes and it takes
roughly about 13 hours.
- Okay.
- All right. Thank you.
- [Parole Officer] Thank you.
[phone beeps]
- Okay.
- [Rod] It's settled. Good.
- It's settled.
- [Ryan] It's settled.
- I could live with that.
Let's enjoy today.
- I can live with that.
[people laughing, chattering]
- That's the main thing
is I don't wanna go back.
I didn't know what
all was gonna happen
and I'm just kind of like, I'm
overwhelmed with everything.
And I'm like, I don't
wanna go back to prison.
I don't wanna do anything
that they are not okay with.
- [Ryan] Right.
- I'm like, I feel
like I've done my part.
- Right. You have.
You have. Look at me, you have.
- Okay.
- And you know,
it sucks we won't be able
to stay in [indistinct].
But it's okay.
- I'm okay with that.
- [Ryan] Yeah.
- I'm just kind of like
the going back to
Louisiana right now.
- Right. That's the kicker.
We didn't wanna do that.
- Right.
- And now we got directed,
we can enjoy the day,
enjoy the night, wake up have
breakfast in the morning then go
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- and well go back to our home.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- [Gypsy] I love you.
- [Kristy] So, what'd
you do last night?
- Was the bed comfy?
- The bed was comfy and,
it was so nice.
It was so nice.
We consummated our marriage.
[Kristy laughing]
[Gypsy laughing]
- [Kristy] Silly
girl, silly girl.
- You're so happy for me.
- [Kristy] You're a silly girl.
[Gypsy laughing]
[laughing]
- Bragging rights.
Girl, you deserve that.
- I'm happy that, you know,
it was with the right person.
You know, that's important.
- [Mia] I just wanted to have
a little girl talk with you.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- Birth control, did
you figure that out?
- Okay.
Do you want kids right away?
- I mean, I want kids.
I just, I don't think that
right away would be smart.
- Agreed.
- I'm not gonna say that,
if it happened,
I would be sad.
I just don't think
that, I'm not gonna try.
I just wanna settle
into marriage.
I know in my heart that
the marriage is stable,
It's like, is this my life.
but I just wanna
feel it out first.
- Do you think that
all the medication and the
surgeries may have hindered
your ability?
- I'm not, I'm hoping not.
I've had regular
periods, you know,
I've had two pap
smears in prison.
They all came back normal.
But like, I don't know.
- You should probably schedule
a gynecologist appointment.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Soon.
Probably could find out
how many eggs you have left
and all that.
And if you are able to.
- Mmm-hmm.
- And me talking
to you about this
is not me telling you to
have babies or me like-
- [Gypsy] I know.
- I want you to have kids.
I just don't want-
- [Gypsy] No, I know, I know.
- To prevent that.
- [Gypsy] Right, you
just wanna make sure
that I'm doing the right thing.
- Yeah.
- I get it.
- [Mia] When it's on your time.
- Yeah, I understand.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Somebody has to.
Now, you have a sister
to talk to about this.
- Thank you!
Thank you, sis.
Love you.
- Love you, too.
- Okay.
- I'm very hopeful
and I'm worried,
for sure.
I'm worried about the world.
It's like she's a
new little born baby
and I don't want
anything to hurt her.
I know she wants to do
things with her life
and she wants to
find her purpose
and she's excited for that.
And I'll be there to
help her figure it out
as much as I can be.
[gentle bright music]
- To freedom.
- Let's pop one up, right?
- [Gypsy] Right.
- All right, one, two, three.
- Three.
[bottle cap pops]
[everyone exclaims]
[Gypsy laughs]
- The color palettes of freedom
are so bright and fibrous.
- [Mia] Smile like you're happy.
- Smile like you mean it.
In prison, it's
white walls, gray,
strong metal.
[family laughing]
This is what I've
been missing out on.
It's amazing. [laughing]
Hmm, oh, that's so good.
I feel very weird.
Being in front of an
audience. [laughing]
Oh my goodness.
These, I think, will fit!
I have fat calves.
- Suck it in. I'm just kidding.
[Gypsy laughs]
- [Ryan] You see, I was leaving?
- You're about
ready to get kicked.
- Her road right now is hills,
spirals, u-turns, everything.
Everything has been
thrown at her, you know,
from having all this family
time to cutting it short.
But it is what it is.
I mean, she's gonna have
to put her seatbelt on
pretty tight. [laughing]
That's what I'm gonna say.
Hold on 'cause it's
gonna be a bumpy ride.
But she always has me.
We're her tribe.
- And this is my
big present to you.
- Okay.
Ooh!
Christian Louboutin!
These are really nice.
- [Kristy] Those are stunning.
- Okay.
Awwww!
- [Kristy] Read it.
- Never forget that I love
you forever and always.
I hope that you
believe in yourself
as much as I believe in you.
Always keep me in your heart.
For you are always in mind.
Nothing and no one, not even
time will ever change that.
You are braver than you believe,
stronger than you seem,
smarter than you think and
love more than you know.
I can't promise to be here
for the rest of your life,
but I can promise to love
you for the rest of mine.
Love, dad.
- [Ryan] Aw.
- Aw.
Don't make me cry now!
I have been solid!
And this is gonna
make cry. [laughs]
- I've always been
daddy's little girl.
It's different having
a sister come in.
But I've had my
dad for 22 years.
She hasn't.
I know that what I have
with my dad is a good thing
and I want them to
build that, as well.
I want them to have that.
And I can't wait to watch it.
- Now you gotta get
a hug [indistinct].
Let's throw all this
trash. [laughing]
- [Rod] I love you.
[gentle music]
[clock ticking]
- This morning, Gypsy
Rose Blanchard posted
her first social media post
since being released
from prison yesterday.
It was a selfie on Instagram
with the caption "First
selfie of Freedom."
- She truly looks so happy.
- Gypsy Rose's family
had a welcome home party.
Mia captioned the
photos with saying,
"The sweetest, hello.
Welcome home sister."
- Some really disappointing news
just came out about Gypsy Rose
and her going to the
Chiefs' game tomorrow.
Unfortunately, she
will not be attending
because she has been ordered
to leave the state of Missouri
by her parole officer,
according to TMZ.
[worrisome music]
[jewelry clanks]
- Crap.
[pensive music]
- I'm trying to
get this necklace.
- I love spending
time with my husband.
We've been having sex the
last two nights. [laughing]
Even in here. [laughing]
I was like, "Shut
up!" [laughing]
- Even with the
family. [laughing]
That's why I slept so
good last night. [laughs]
- [Mia] We gotta go home.
I see you getting antsy.
- [Rob] Yeah.
- What time is y'all flight?
- [Mia] I'm hungry, too.
- [Rod] 12:30.
- [Gypsy] 12:30.
- So y'all be careful.
Have fun. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- I will, I will.
- [Kristy] Yeah.
- [Gypsy] I love you.
- [Rod] Roger?
- I love you, too.
- I'll see you soon.
[tense music]
- [Mia] All right, love you.
- [Kristy] Love you, too.
- Love you.
From start to present,
I think it has just been a
whirlwind for me of emotions
and ups and downs.
I feel like the
stakes are high as far
as that I have to
do good on parole.
That is literally my biggest
fear is going back to prison
for another year and a half.
I don't wanna risk
that for anything.
My first priority will
always be my freedom.
[reflective music]
[tense music]
- [Ryan] You ready
for this [bleep]?
- [Gypsy] Yeah, I'm just
ready to get out on the road.
[tense music]
There's just two of 'em
right now, which is good.
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
That [bleep] is right behind me.
- Just ignore 'em.
[tense music]
- [Ryan] All right, you
gonna call the PO?
- [Gypsy] All right.
- All right, be good.
[phone ringing]
- Hi, this is Gypsy
Rose Blanchard
and I just wanted to call
and let y'all know
that we are driving
back to Louisiana as we speak.
- [Parole Officer] Alright,
I do appreciate you calling.
- [Ryan] Absolutely.
- Thank you so much.
All right, have a good day.
- [Parole Officer]
All right, thank you ma'am.
- Okay. Bye.
- [Parole Officer] Bye-bye.
- Yep, I just wanna keep
them on the up and up.
- Good, baby.
[gentle xylophone music]
Look at this [bleep].
- Yes. Paparazzi,
we were hungry.
- [Ryan] Yep.
- And we gotta eat, you know.
- Not really.
There's a guy taking
our picture right there.
Like now I'm about to
give him a closeup.
This is Gypsy Rose Blanchard.
- Hi.
- [Worker] Oh, that
must suck. I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- Yeah, there's nothing
that they can do.
- Second day out, you know,
it's something I
gotta get used to.
- [Worker] Yeah, how it is?
- You know? [laughing]
- [Worker] Here you are.
- I just wonder how
many pictures does
he actually need of us?
- [Worker] Well, I hope
you have a better day.
- Thanks, thank you, guys.
- [Gypsy] Thank you.
- All right, don't
eat in front of him.
- Oh.
[pensive music]
Oh, these are so good.
- [Ryan] Are they good, baby?
- They're very good.
- [Ryan] Good.
- Hmm.
I am concerned.
Is paparazzi gonna follow us
all the way back to Louisiana?
Are they gonna follow
us back to our home?
That's not what I want.
I think there was
a mass difference
of what my expectation was.
I expected it, but
not that intense.
[tense music]
[cars whirring]
I think this necklace looks
so pretty with this sweater.
- [Ryan] Oh, it's gorgeous.
I just wish my name was in it.
- Later on in life, I
wanna get another one
where I could have.
- Yeah.
[Ryan laughs]
[Gypsy laughs]
- [Ryan] No!
- "I'm so happy
she's outta prison."
- [Ryan] RG?
- [Gypsy] KU.
- No!
- Yes.
- Mother.
[Gypsy laughs]
And of course Kristy
let you know about it.
- It's not like she singled
him out and was like,
"By the way, Ken texted me."
- Too late, buddy.
[tense music]
- [Gypsy] Ken is my ex-fiance.
Ken and I first started
dating in September of 2017.
We were together for two years.
Even though he was in the free
world and I was in prison,
this was my first
actual relationship
that was long term.
Right before we were
gonna get married,
he ended the relationship.
It devastated me.
I think he pretty much
gave me every breakup line
you can think of in the book.
[tense music]
- Of course! Baby.
- I just wouldn't
have told you that.
You know what I call him?
Dumb mother.
[tense music]
[heavy pensive music]
- [Gypsy] Is that guy
still following us?
- Oh yeah, he's back there.
Vultures, man.
Another thing...
- Bye, thank you.
Bye-bye, go home.
- Yes, they pulled off!
Yeah!
[suspenseful music]
Hey, baby, how do you feel?
We're about to be out of
the state of Missouri.
- Oh, I feel relieved.
- Yeah, we are so close.
- [Gypsy] I feel relieved.
[laughing]
- [Ryan] Hey look, here we go.
You see it?
- I see it.
[hand tapping] I beat you.
- [laughing] You're so silly.
[Ryan laughs]
- Goodbye, Missouri.
- Yep. Goodbye, Missouri.
- I don't wanna be back.
I'm just happy to leave
all of that behind.
Go with a fresh start.
You know?
- New state.
- New state. New start.
- New life.
[reflective music]
[light bright music]
[light bright music continues]
- Alexa!
Play, "Shake It Off,"
by Taylor Swift.
- [Alexa] Should I
start your free trial
and play, "Shake It
Off," Taylor's version?
- Yes.
- [Alexa] You're
missing a payment method
so I can't sign you up.
- [Gypsy] Are you
still unpacking?
- [Ryan] Yeah, we got
a lot to unpack, baby.
We got Christmas presents.
We gotta figure out
where we're gonna put
some of this stuff.
- What drawers would be mine?
- If you want this
whole thing, it's yours.
- Okay.
Who do you think is
gonna take up more space?
- [laughing] Not
even up for debate.
- I think a lot of
people felt like
I should have waited
in getting married
and I know that.
Now they feel more comfortable.
Like my family feels more
comfortable with Ryan.
and now that they've got
to spend time with him.
But I think my dad is skeptical.
I mean, it's
something I expected,
I expected my dad to
still have, not concerns,
but almost like prove it to me
that things are gonna be okay.
But the transition from
prison relationship
to full-fledged marriage,
I feel like it's
transitioning beautifully.
Oh, this is so cute!
- [Ryan] Isn't that cute?
- I love this.
Okay, I gotta look at all the
different cat pictures now.
- Yep.
Being home with Gypsy is great.
I'm glad to be
doing my own thing.
I got her to myself.
You know, it's funny,
I have been waiting a
long time to be with her.
So has her family.
And I know they're
probably a little jealous
that I got a lot of
her time and I get it
and I'm okay with sharing her.
At the same time, nobody knows
her quite as well as I do.
She wanted me to pick her up.
She wanted this, she wanted
to move here with me.
But like her parents are
planning on coming over tomorrow
and spending more time with
her and I'll give their time.
You know, it's no biggie.
But that's my time too, so.
- I'm gonna turn on the light.
This is
a bra
that if you put
it in a nice bow,
it's like a Christmas
present bow.
And as you can see,
it's very short.
There's nothing to it.
So he bought these for me
about two and a half years ago.
We just started dating
and I think he had
like full confidence
that we would work out perfect.
I always wanted to wear
this one for the first time,
but I ended up just
being like [exclaiming],
"All right, let's
do this." [chuckles]
A big part of womanhood is
learning to be comfortable
with our sexuality.
And for years I wasn't.
I'm self-conscious because I
have scars all over my body.
And I had a lot of surgeries
that were unnecessary.
And so I'm like, "Am I gonna
be what he wants me to be?
Am I attractive to him?"
And even to the
point that I'm like,
"Don't even look
at me down there!"
You know, don't because.
And he's like, "It's okay."
For a long time I actually
kind of like questioned
like my own sexuality
because as a teenager
or a preteen,
I felt that I was
attracted to girls.
And I got to experiment
with that in prison.
I think I've kissed more
girls than I have guys.
I had such big fears
that I was like,
"What happens if I'm
just not gonna like sex?"
I feel like I don't
have a sex drive.
There is a rule against
masturbation in prison.
Not only do you have the risk of
if you get caught masturbating,
but for me, I can go six
months and just be fine.
And I'm like, what
happens if I just,
I'm not a sexual being?
And so I'm discovering
things about myself.
I'm like, I'm a
freak! [laughing]
[light rhythmic music]
- All right, we got a couple
special treats for y'all.
- All right.
Some non-alcoholic.
- [Rod] And then sparkling rose.
- Stuff.
Okay, I'm gonna love
the sparkling rose.
- That's what I figured.
Because it's you.
Gypsy's never had steak before
so I made sure to get
a nice cut of ribeye.
- Been while since I got a kiss.
[lips smacking]
- Hmm.
- Thank you.
- Give me another one.
[lips smacking]
Hmm.
[Rod] All right, you
ready to do this?
Thank you.
- Can I tell you something
that I've never told
you guys before?
- [Kristy] Tell me.
So you remember
whenever you and dad
came to my wheelchair games,
you know the wheelchair
races that I was in?
So after,
when y'all left,
my mom said that dad was
making fun of me and that-
- Like, as if.
- I know.
But she said, "This is why I
don't invite them to anything
because you know
what your dad said?"
And I said, "What?"
She's like, "He
called you a retard."
[tense music]
- No, that's how she saw you.
And we didn't see you like that.
Never once!
Never once would we-
- And it-
- [Kristy] But it
just goes to show.
- Yeah.
- [Kristy] You know how much
she tried to pull you away.
- It's like it was just
comment after comment
and after so many years,
comments build up.
- [Kristy] Yeah.
- You know?
And opinions are formed, so.
- [Kristy] Yeah.
- I wish that my mom could
have been honest with me.
I mean, she twists
things in stories
to make herself seem
holier art than now.
But with my dad,
I think we're headed to a
really, really good place.
I think we're in
a good place now,
but I think we're gonna be able
to foster that relationship
we always wanted to
have with each other.
- [Rod] Where's the beef?
- [Gypsy] Take a picture
with me and the steak.
- [Kristy] Take more than one.
[gentle banjo music]
- Lord God, heavenly
Father, we gather tonight
to give you thanks, Lord.
Thanks for bringing
Gypsy back home to us.
In Jesus' name, Amen.
- [All] Amen.
- All right.
- Very nice.
- Oh, yeah, this is amazing.
Mmm-hmm.
- [Kristy] Aurora's gonna beg.
She'll be looking
straight at you, Dad.
[all laughing]
[gentle music]
[inaudible dialogue]
- [Gypsy] So I was thinking
about wearing this.
It's a shame we don't
wear the same size.
Try to do it before-
- And the shoes.
- [Kristy] Ooh, that's
gonna look nice.
- I know!
- You've come a long way.
- Mmm-hmm.
[reflective music]
- When I was fixing her makeup
and she closed her eyes,
all I saw was Mia.
And that's when I
was like, "Oh my God,
You know, I could have been
helping you with everything."
And to be able
for a dream to
become a reality is
unmeasurable.
Look, see?
- I like that. Yeah.
- Rub.
Go. Up and down, up down.
There you go. There you go.
[Gypsy laughing]
You see, y'all
learning the tricks.
You see how it makes it look?
A little more
pronounced, you know?
- Yeah.
Oh, the necklace.
- I have never been
dressed like this before.
You know, looking
at myself right now,
like I never thought that I'd
look this pretty, you know?
This is just not something
that I ever saw for
myself. [laughing]
I guess I just, I
knew that my mom
would never let
me look like this.
Having long hair
and wearing a really
low cut dress.
I'm not used to
looking in the mirror
and liking how I look.
So this is definitely
a little bit of a shock.
Kind of like a little
Cinderella moment. [laughing]
I'm killing it! [laughs]
[gentle reflective music]
- [Rod] Oh, wow.
- [Ryan] Wow.
- Gorgeous!
Sparkly.
Gypsy Rose Blanchard Anderson.
[men exclaiming]
You look beautiful.
- How do I look?
- Oh my God.
That's my wife.
- I know.
This is your wife.
- [Kristy] That is your wife.
- What you whatcha
gonna do about it.
[Kristy laughing]
- [Kristy] He's like,
I'm gonna [indistinct].
- You look so good.
I love the necklace you got on.
- Thank you.
- [Kristy] She has on
her dad's necklace.
- Yeah, this is the
necklace that dad got me.
Yeah.
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
- [Rod] All right,
Ryan, come around.
I wanna do a toast.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- I just wanna say a few words.
Ryan, you're a good guy.
I like your family.
Gypsy, I'm so proud of you.
You've come so far, darling.
I love you so much and
I'm just [heavily sighs].
I'm so happy for you.
- Thank you, daddy.
- So to y'all wedding
and your new life.
- Cheers.
- All right. Let's party.
Let's dance!
- Woo.
- Thanks, Dad.
[gentle reflective music]
- [Rod] 10.
- [All] Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One!
[bottle caps pop]
[all screams
- We are in 2024!
- Happy New Year, baby.
[lips smacking]
Happy New Year, y'all.
- [Gypsy] Happy New Year. Yay!
- [Kristy] We did it!
[Gypsy yells]
♪ I can be myself
with all this room ♪
♪ Like a flower
blooming in spring ♪
♪ When we're together
we have everything ♪
♪ After every setting sun
♪ Yeah, we always get it on
♪ A new days come
- [Rod] I never thought I'd
dance with her standing up,
you know, maybe in a wheelchair
one day or something.
But it was really nice
to see how beautiful she is
and just dance with her.
Hold her.
♪ And I know it's never easy
- You're a good dancer.
♪ You hold me up
together like the moon ♪
♪ I can be myself
with all this room ♪
♪ And we're always
on the upswing ♪
- [Rod] Just to live
what she's been through
and what she's done,
she's taken it all.
She's taken everything
her mom has thrown at her.
And what society's
given her so far.
I think she has
something more to give.
I really believe that.
[gentle music]
- As a little girl,
I didn't imagine that
I would be dancing
with my dad one day, you know?
'Cause I didn't think
that he was gonna be
a part of my life.
So that was special for me.
[gentle music]
[giggling] That was beautiful.
- It was.
Fit me in?
Nine, eight, seven.
- [Family] Six,
five, four, three,
two, one.
♪ When we're together
we have everything ♪
[gentle music]
- The person that got arrested,
I think it's a version of myself
that I have completely
left behind.
[gentle music]
Yes, I'll always have
the stigma on me.
[fireworks explodes]
But I'm working to change that.
No one thing stays the same.
People evolve.
Creatures evolve.
This is my evolution.
[gentle music]
[clock ticking]
- I cannot get over this.
Gypsy Rose Blanchard
has been pretty active
on her new Instagram account
since her release from
prison a few days ago.
And she just posted this
picture with her husband,
Ryan Anderson.
She captioned it, "A New Year's
Eve Eve kiss with my hubby."
It looks like in the background,
they have a little
just married sign.
They have a Ryan and
Gypsy sign up there
and it seems like
maybe this could be
where they're living together.
It is so sweet.
[light upbeat music]
- You know, like Ryan's
a really good cook.
My mom was a really good cook.
Kristy can't cook. [laughing]
The only thing I've learned
to cook is these pasta sides,
which are my favorite.
Instructions are
pretty simple so far.
But that's all that I've
tested the waters with.
Gotta start somewhere, right?
I was worried about that
when we got married.
I'm like, you know, "I
don't know how to cook.
Hadn't had a sex
life to speak of.
So I'm like, God knows.
Why did you marry me?"
You know?
I didn't want him to feel
like I'm a dependent on him.
My whole life I had been
a dependent on my mother.
She drove us everywhere.
She cooked, she cleaned,
she did everything.
So basically, all I had to
do for 24 years of my life
was just exist.
All I needed to do is be
taught and there we go,
another gain of independence
checked off my list.
[Ryan sighs]
- You back?
- Never send a big man to
the store hungry, baby.
[Ryan sighs] [bleep]
[Gypsy laughing]
- Let's see what you got.
I'm gonna wait for you to come
in here so I can show you.
- Show me what, how
to make a nasty rack?
- Yeah.
[Ryan gags]
When I was still in prison,
I told them about a
favorite drink of mine.
It's instant coffee with a soda.
For flavor, you crush
up some Jolly Ranchers,
add that to it.
You mix it all together,
and also juice.
And then you serve it over ice.
And we call it a rack.
- So how often would you
drink this in prison?
- I drink it like
every other day or so.
[Ryan scoffs]
Or at least twice a week.
So look how thick
that is because-
- You don't cook, but
you do this [bleep]?
- I know, right?
[hammer thudding]
- I hope your PO don't
come in right now.
"Look at this
powder everywhere."
- Okay, this is gonna
foam a little bit.
- [Ryan] Good God!
- All right, now the
foam will dissolve.
- [Ryan] Oh, so it's done?
- Yeah, it's done.
That's all it is.
[Ryan gags]
Pour it.
[Gypsy laughs]
[Ryan scoffs]
You might not like
it because it's coffee.
- I can tell you right
now I'm not gonna like it.
Do you see that chunk of [bleep]
just laying on top? [exclaims]
- It's the Jolly
Ranchers. It's flavor.
- You really expect
me to drink this?
- Come on. [laughing]
[curious music]
- Things you do for love.
- Cheers.
- I love you.
- Oh yeah, that's
good. [laughing]
- Baby, that's so bad.
- It's not bad. [laughing]
- It's so bad.
- It's not bad. It's good.
[playful music]
So, let's talk about
this whole puppy thing.
- I know you want a dog.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I know you want
one right away.
- Mmm-hmm.
- But like, there's
other logistics
we need to think about.
- Like what?
- Well like, you know
we're in an apartment.
- There's lots of
people with dogs.
- If it was up to, you'd
go get the puppy today.
[Gypsy laughs]
- Maybe.
- When Ryan goes back to work,
I just don't wanna like lonely.
I've never been alone
a day in my life.
I have always had my mother.
Then I went to prison and
had three other roommates
and lived in communal
living within a prison.
So I've never been alone.
And I don't know
how that will feel.
Independence and
freedom is scary
because at least in prison,
things are controlled.
Freedom, you never know what
the next day is gonna bring.
- I mean, what is a Malshi?
- [laughing] Did you google it?
- A Malshi is a Maltese
and a Shih Tzu combined.
That's what it is. Look.
[Gypsy laughs]
- I see quite a
few Husky puppies,
but a husky, we can't
have a husky here.
- I want a Malshi.
- All right. I'm working on it!
[both laughing]
- So violent.
- I'm not violent!
Take it back.
- I take it all
the way back, baby.
- You better.
Done. Fine.
[curious music]
You're hovering.
Thank you.
[Ryan groans]
[curious music]
- [Ryan] I don't know, babe.
Like I would love for
you to have the dog.
- Mmm-hmm.
- When I'm at work.
- [Gypsy] I don't
see any issues.
- I mean, it's a lot
of responsibility.
- I mean, I don't
see any issues.
I stay at home.
- True.
- While you're at work.
It's not like I'm
going to a nine to five
and leaving the puppy by itself.
I'm gonna be here at the
apartment by myself, so.
- And you want a puppy, puppy?
- Mmm-hmm.
- [Ryan] You wanna start
from the ground up?
- Yeah.
- [Ryan] What do
you wanna name it?
- Oh, we haven't
even picked one out,
let alone ready for a name.
- True.
I say we call it hormonal.
- I'm not hormonal.
I'm just a woman.
- Okay, well let's
call it a woman.
- No.
- Okay.
Because at an apartment, baby,
you have to take 'em for walks.
- Dang it.
- And you have to
pick up their pee
and you have to pick up
their poop and stuff.
- Mmm-hmm. I'm not an idiot.
I know how to care for a dog.
- I didn't say
you were an idiot.
Baby, I didn't say
[tense music]
[door slams]
I didn't call you
an idiot, baby.
- [Gypsy] Why are you
treating me like one?
- [Ryan] I'm not.
I'm not.
- [Gypsy] That's the kind of
[bleep] that you tell a child.
"It's a lot of
responsibility, you know?"
[somber music]
- Baby, you're gonna
be great with a dog.
I'm all for it.
I think you're gonna
do great with it.
- [Gypsy] I've had
animals before.
- I know.
- Just, please, don't
treat me like I'm a child.
Like I don't know
what I'm doing.
I know a dog is a lot
of responsibility.
I'll walk it, I'll feed
it, I'll do everything.
Like...
- Okay, sweetie.
- I think a lot of people,
they have this perception of me
that just because I have
not experienced something,
that attributes to
being childlike.
And for me, it's not.
My mother used to
treat me like a child
and she wanted me to be a child.
I'm not stupid.
You don't have to talk
to me like I'm stupid.
It irritates me.
- I never treat
you like an idiot.
I never have.
You know, I get mad when
people treat you like that.
- I know.
And you are starting
to act like them.
- I'm walking a thin
line with Gypsy.
Like I want her to live her life
and I don't wanna be a
controlling husband and I'm not.
But it's one of those things
that if I say something that
a normal husband would say,
then I'm like controlling
her and I'm like her mother.
And it's like, whoa,
that's not fair.
Any little thing
could be a trigger.
I got things in my
past that trigger me.
You know, like, I don't
like being abandoned.
I like knowing that
people are there for me.
You know, I get
where she comes from.
How are you not cold?
I'm over here freezing
my [bleep] off.
- Because I'm mad!
- I apologize if you think I
was treating you like a kid
'cause I'm not meaning to.
- Thank you.
We haven't had major conflict,
but in the little
tiffs that we've had,
I'm pretty open about
what I'm mad about.
I don't wanna be controlled.
I push back 10 times harder
if I feel like I'm
being controlled.
I didn't back then with my mom
and there was so many
times that I could have,
but I was so scared.
Now? Bring it!
'Cause I got that
confidence now.
[tense music]
Nobody ever said this
was gonna be easy,
you know, I love
her unconditionally
and you know, I'm just happy
to be along for the ride.
No matter what me
and Gypsy go through,
we will always come
together in the end.
[dramatic music]
- I'm more nervous about the
PO meeting than New York.
Literally my biggest fear
is going back to prison.
- We're gonna get on
the [bleep] flight.
You better get
in the other lane.
- He's got it. [groans]
- [Ryan] So baby you excited
to go shoot at The View?
- I'm nervous.
- The attention on social media,
like I'm not used to it at all.
- [Ryan] Very quick.
- [Gypsy] Right quick.
Ken texted my stepmom.
- Why do you think he decided
it's time to pop back up?
- I don't think that he has
respect for my marriage.
- He doesn't like me.
- I go into my messages
and I will have death threats.
Am I at risk for
dangerous people?
I'm feeling a lot of stress
from everything else
going on right now.
- I just want to have
a family with you.
- Is this the life that we
really wanna lead for ourselves?
[dramatic music]