- [Gypsy] This is
Ryan flipping out
because I told my sister about--
- No, you told the
world about it.
You're hovering.
Thank you.
I'm not gonna say
he's a hoarder,
but there's a lot of clutter.
- Just don't let her
talk (bleep) about me.
I know she's going to.
- I don't see any issues.
- Well, it's a lot
of responsibility.
I'm not an idiot. I know
how to care for a dog.
- Who are you texting?
- I'm just texting my
sister, honey. Relax.
- I'm very relaxed.
- If I see that I am being
controlled, I'm leaving.
- What?
- Gypsy's first true
relationship was Ken.
- Something happens
with Gypsy and Ken,
it's gonna be your fault.
- For years, he never
gave me like an answer.
I went through like a
huge, like self-doubt.
I know that he is
interested in blondes.
I'm not blonde, I'm a brunette.
- It's important for
me to share my thoughts
and opinions on her, and the
time that we spent together,
and everything will
unfold as it should.
- [Gypsy] Woo!
- Captain Gypsy Rose.
[Gypsy laughing]
- I am kind of
rushing into things
and kind of like wanting to
do everything all at once.
You had an issue with Kristy,
you had an issue with Mia.
- Well, they question
our relationship.
Am I wrong fighting for our
marriage? That's what I'm doing.
- I miss Ken.
I have two men in my heart.
- Talking about me,
reaching out to me
right before her wedding,
phone conversations
that we've had since?
[tense music]
[gentle music]
- I'm obviously like a
little nervous about it
'cause I've never
been on camera before.
- Yeah.
- I'm sure Kristy's told her.
- Why wouldn't I be?
[pensive music]
You know, Gypsy was never
Gypsy Rose Blanchard,
to me at least, you know,
not after we got
to know each other.
She's just Gypsy,
just Gyps, that's it.
It's a long time
to think back to.
This is almost seven years ago.
When I wrote her the first time,
it wasn't because I was like
looking for a girlfriend.
I can't tell you what I
was thinking at the time,
at the age of 24, but like,
I just wanted to let her know
that you have support out here.
But she would get, you know,
hundreds of those kinds of
same letters all the time,
so I don't know why
she wrote me back,
but I'm happy she did.
And then that eventually
graduated to phone calls.
She started calling
me and I mean,
I would talk to her for
sometimes, like, no joke,
3, 4, 5 hours, you know?
We just connected
in a lot of ways.
You know, there
was kind of like,
not talked about maybe
lingering feelings in the air,
but it didn't really
come to fruition until
that first visit,
I would say, yeah.
You know, you can't wake up
and decide how you
feel about somebody
or how you connect
with somebody.
Sometimes, it just
happens organically.
She's an incredible person.
I mean, she's one of the
sweetest people I've ever met.
You know, back then I
would, I mean, even today,
I would have a very like,
overactive, overthinking,
like million miles a
minute racing kind of mind.
And Gypsy had a way of like,
kind of calming me down and
like centering me, again.
She was a huge, huge
part of my everyday life,
so cutting ties was extremely
hard and very difficult.
[gentle music]
[phone rings]
- [Gypsy] Hey.
- [Mia] Hey.
- [Gypsy] Did you
watch my video?
- [Mia] Which one?
- The videos that I sent you
last night or this morning?
- [Gypsy] Ryan had a
whole freak out moment.
- [Mia] Oh, Lord.
- He's like, "You had
to do it on camera?"
and I'm like, I didn't mean
for it to be like on camera.
- [Mia] Okay.
- So there's that.
- [Mia] All right, I'll
text you about it.
- All right, love you.
- [Mia] All right.
Love you too, bye.
- I know you want some water.
[water running]
What time we going
rock climbing?
- Four something.
- So who were you
on the phone with
when you were on
the balcony, Mia?
- Yeah.
- I'm sure you told her that
we had an argument, huh?
- Yep.
- Did you really?
- Why? It wasn't even that bad.
I love that you take
these little disagreements
as like massive arguments.
- I didn't say
they were massive.
- Okay.
[tense music]
[birds chirping]
[chimes ringing]
- I think I feel
a little bit like
I haven't had a chance to
spend some time with Gypsy,
just me and her.
- I know, and that's the truth.
- I don't know how
to fit that in with,
you know, she's
real busy, I'm just--
- I mean, look.
- Trying to find a
time when we could
just kind of, just me and her.
- Well, you need to, you
need to tell her, B.
You need to have a
conversation with Gypsy.
- I'm trying to have a
conversation with you,
but you not letting me talk.
- [Kristy] I'm sorry, you
know, that's how I am.
- Yap, yap, yap.
- I know I'm that
way, but finish.
- I'm good.
- No, say what you wanna say.
- [Ron] No, I think
you got the point.
- No, say it, say it.
- I said it, babe. I don't know.
I just feel a little
jealous, that's all I mean.
- I get that.
- Of Ryan, of you.
Of, you know, all the media,
just all the things
she's got going on.
I just feel like we haven't
had a chance and you know,
I haven't told her that, but I
don't want to tell her that.
- You have to tell her.
- But I don't know, I'll feel
guilty for feeling that way.
- You should not feel guilty,
Rod, because you were robbed.
- Because it's just been so
crazy since she's gotten out.
We haven't really had that...
- Yeah.
- Look, I mean...
- I got tears in my
eyes because I'm hurt.
I feel bad for you.
- It's okay.
- I told Ryan,
"You've been waiting
for her for two years,
we've been waiting eight plus."
- Yeah.
I mean, I feel like I'm
being selfish about it.
- [Kristy] You have
every right to selfish.
- But I feel like I'm
worried about my happiness
and not hers.
The last thing I want
is to push too hard
and she draws away.
- [Ryan] All right, baby, you
ready to go have some fun?
- [Gypsy] Yes.
[gentle music]
- You got my wallet?
- Yeah, wallet.
- You excited?
- Yes.
[indistinct chatter]
Get up there.
What keeps me drawn to Ryan
is he has a very
compassionate heart,
and he is able to
understand me emotionally
in a way that I don't feel like
a lot of people understand.
He loves me in a way
that nobody ever has,
regardless of how
many fights we have,
or the ups and the downs,
like, he loves me for me.
Love is always
worth fighting for.
- Look, we got this
whole spot. There you go.
- Thank you.
- Oh, it's delicious.
Are you super mad
at me for texting
that video to my sister?
- A little.
- Why?
- Because, babe, that video
didn't help the situation.
Does that make sense?
- I don't wanna do anything
that hurts your feelings.
- I know.
- Or hinders your
relationship with my family,
but anytime that
anybody has any sort
of reservations about
our relationship,
they're not in your
favor so much anymore.
You had an issue with Kristy,
you had an issue
with Mia, like.
- Well, they question
our relationship.
I'm a prideful person.
Like I don't butt into
their relationship.
- And it's coming
from protective.
- I understand that.
Baby, I have nothing against
Kristy. I call her mom.
I have nothing against Mia.
- You know, what's funny
is it's like, "I love them,"
but then you say all these
like, snarky remarks.
Like, "Yeah, Kristy just
loves the attention."
Like you said that
literally when we were
in the car waiting
to come in here.
- But I also joke
around a lot too.
- You do.
When I was 13, I went
through this phase.
My mom hated it.
Every little
sarcastic attitude is,
"Oh, you took offense to
it, oh, I was just joking."
It's like a fall back,
it's like an excuse.
Hi, thank you.
- Chicken nuggets.
- Thank you, oh,
these look delicious.
- Oh, thank you very much.
- Y'all need anything else?
- I'm good. Thank you,
Amanda. Thank you.
- Thank you.
[tense music]
- I guess I do
say snarky things,
but I'm joking when I say them,
and I am defensive when
people have talked (bleep)
about our marriage
and everything.
Like, 'cause I
know what we have.
Like, am I wrong for feeling
like fighting for our marriage?
That's what I'm doing.
I'm an emotional person, I
wear my heart on my sleeve.
- [Gypsy] I know.
- And you know when I'm upset.
You know when I'm happy,
you know all that.
Like, I'm not
going to deny that.
I'll stop with the snide
comments. I'll give you my word.
I'll work on it.
- I know how he is.
Okay, you say that
you're gonna, you know,
be a little bit more
open with my family.
Okay, let's wait and see.
It's nothing that you
can tell me right now.
It's not a promise you can make.
Let me just see if you
make good on what you say.
[pensive music]
- I like to get up
early in the morning,
put my teeth in
before Ryan gets up.
I'm comfortable around
him enough to be myself,
but we're still newlywed,
so I still try and
look good for him.
I only usually let the people
that I'm closest to
see this process.
My teeth is something
that I've always been
really insecure about.
I just don't feel
pretty without my teeth.
Okay.
My mom told the dentist that
my teeth were chipping away,
and that I was
experiencing tooth pain.
So what they did was they
decided to extract my teeth.
Oh, this is when they
took the very first tooth.
See how it started off
at one at the bottom.
I was given partials,
free partials from an
oncology dental clinic.
And they were free
because my mom told them
that I went through chemo.
What I remember is when the
dentist talked about extracting
my teeth, my mom
said, "Oh, it's fine.
She's not a vain child.
She's not concerned
with her looks."
[somber music]
Concern with my
looks was forbidden.
I couldn't be concerned
with my looks.
So, I mean, when I look in
the mirror and I see my smile,
I mean, I see like
messed up teeth.
Like I don't see it as
a smile, it's imperfect.
It's not my choice.
Normal girls don't
have this going on.
Normal girls don't have
to wake up every morning
and go brush their teeth and
then take their denture cup
and put them in, take them out.
It's, um, it's sad.
[bright music]
- Hey, look at all
the toys you got.
You want your dragon?
[toy squeaks]
So Ryan won't be coming out much
'cause, you know,
he's been sick for
quite a while now.
- Oh, he needs to stay in there.
- [Gypsy] And like...
- He needs to rest.
- Yeah, there's this
giant rumor going around
that I'm pregnant just because--
- That's what I
was about to say.
- You know, and I don't
think that it should be okay
that people take pictures
of people at the hospital
and be able to post
them on the internet.
That's not cool.
- Yes, guys, the
speculation is on.
- Is Gypsy Rose pregnant?
Well, apparently that's
what people are saying.
- They were caught visiting
a hospital together.
This is the picture of the
cake and the pregnancy test.
They've been telling people
that she might have
a bun in the oven.
- Like you, we were literally
walking into the hospital
so Ryan could get
his chest X-rayed,
and they're saying that
they overheard me--
- Right.
- Say that I'm pregnant
and checking on the baby.
None of that was said.
And then like--
- Anything for attention
- Part of me wants to
dispel the rumors,
and the other part
of me is like...
- Because they live for
it. They live for a drama.
I'm not holding you.
- I'm gonna check
on Ryan right quick.
[tense music]
Can I get you anything?
- [Gypsy] Okay, okay.
- [Gypsy] I love you.
Pixie.
- Wait, Aurora, wait, come here.
[pensive music]
- [Kristy] Pixie.
- Baby!
- She's like, I wanna go play.
- Girl, come on.
- You wanna go swimming?
- Pixie does.
- No, Aurora, you're
not going swimming.
Me and dad were sitting
down and we were talking
and he said, "When's
my time with Gypsy?"
He wants that
one-on-one without Ryan.
He's hurt, he said he's jealous.
Dad doesn't want
to really tell you,
and I'm like, you
need to tell her.
- I mean, he could
tell me anything.
- He knows that the
way you were raised
was all under a
controlling thumb.
- Right.
- And he doesn't ever want
you to think that he
is controlling to you.
- I would never feel
that way about him.
I mean, if he just told me--
- Exactly.
- How he feels,
I could implement
that into things.
My dad has never said anything
to me to make me think
that he was jealous of
the people around me
getting to spend time with me.
So it does kind of
shock me a little bit.
And even more so
that he doesn't feel,
I'm not gonna say
not comfortable,
but he has fears of letting
me know these things.
- I think he just feels like
he doesn't want to be her.
- And he's not.
- [Kristy] And he's--
- And he never will be.
- [Kristy] And that's
what he's scared about.
- But he's still
my dad and he needs
to learn how to be a dad.
- I just wanna thank
everybody that has continued
to support me
throughout my journey.
I know that there is quite a
few support, quite a few hate.
The hate doesn't bother me.
I'm pretty secure in
who I am as a person.
And I just don't
let it get to me.
To all the supporters,
thank you, I love you.
To all the haters, no comment.
Because I'm not gonna
waste my time on you guys.
All right.
- So Gypsy, if I gave
you a magic wand,
what few things would you
change about your nose?
- The bump, and I just
want a more feminine slope.
I've been teased about
my nose for forever.
- [Surgeon] Yeah.
- And I hate the profile shots.
- It's mainly profiles, gotcha.
- And I just want a more
feminine looking nose.
- [Surgeon] You got it,
I'm gonna take a look.
- All right.
- Your septum's a
little off of the track,
but we can fix it,
take the bump off,
and then maybe lift your
tip up just a smidge.
I think that'll give
you a more feminine nose
and kind of let
everybody see your eyes
and not let the nose block you.
- Right, I can see
my nose from here.
Like, it's embarrassing.
- I know what you mean.
- She wanted to know
if you did two for one.
- Yes. Absolutely, that's
why I went to tag along.
- Perfect.
- When I was little, I got
teased 'cause of my nose.
But then, like now being
a public figure in a sense
on social media, it
doesn't help the fact
that I already had
this insecurity,
and then I have people calling
me The Nose on social media.
I am kind of rushing into things
and kind of like wanting to
do everything all at once
because I have that ability.
Like, okay, let's do
a massive makeover,
and make yourself the
best version of yourself,
so I could disassociate
from my past.
- So the first thing I
think we ought do is I think
we ought to shorten your nose
and tilt it up just a teeny bit
to make it a little
bit more feminine.
- Okay.
- Okay?
And now the next
thing we're gonna do
is we're gonna take
you a little bump down.
- Oh, wow.
- Wait, I need to look.
Wow.
- That's looks so much better.
- That is crazy.
- I think it looks, so if you
look at this picture, right?
You see the nose because
it's kind of overpowering
and it's like your eye
is always gonna be drawn
to the thing that's
a little different.
So if you look at this
picture, you see your eyes,
because the nose
basically goes away.
- [Gypsy] Right.
That looks so nice.
- I know.
- I'm like, wow, it
looks so different
and it looks so feminine
and like it doesn't
look ugly anymore.
- We kind of have to
work with what we have.
- I'm gonna look like
a different person.
So yeah, I wanna schedule
the surgery like ASAP.
If could do it
today, I would do it.
Thank you.
- Good seeing you.
- Thank you so much.
- Awesome seeing you.
- Nice to meet you.
- See you next?
- Hopefully.
- [chuckles] All right.
- All right, thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- It looked good.
- I looked.
- So are you nervous at all?
Like being that you've had
so many surgeries before
and this is like your first
one on your own accord?
- I mean, this is a surgery
that I'm choosing to have.
This is a surgery that I've
been looking forward to having.
So no, not really.
Every other time it was to
take something away from me.
This is to give
me something, so.
- [Kristy] Yeah.
- It's a little different.
[pensive music]
Well, the times that
like Ryan's at work,
like in the morning, it's
kind of like I do my thing,
I get my texts outta the way,
but then by three o'clock
when it's quitting time, oh,
I'm ready for him
to come back home.
- Yeah.
- I'm like, I miss you.
I'm ready for you
to come back home.
- Right.
It's good to miss him.
- And then that's a sign
to me that I'm like,
this marriage is good, you know?
But couple days ago I
went to the bedroom,
woke Ryan up.
I said, I need to
tell you something.
He's half asleep.
I said, I miss Ken.
- He must have woke up quick.
- He did, and he was like,
"You need to let that go.
You need to let him
go. You are married."
And I'm like, I know I am,
but I think that we both
need to come to terms
with the fact that I
have two men in my heart
and he's still
there in my heart.
It was the day before
Valentine's Day too.
Not only did I call Ken two
weeks before the wedding,
but the conversation
that Ken and I had,
I was honest with Ryan about it.
I asked Ken, I said, if you
don't want me to get married,
then you need to tell me now.
- And what he told you?
- And he told me that,
"I want you to do
what makes you happy.
I think you should wait."
But he didn't say,
"Wait for me."
If he would've said,
"Wait for me..."
- You would have, I
know you would have.
- Do you wish that Ryan
would've done what Ken did?
Not in leaving me, but
waiting to get married.
- Yes, yes. I will not
hesitate with that answer.
And y'all knew that I
wanted y'all to wait.
- Yeah.
- You know,
I wanted you to get out and
live and try new things,
and see if it was really real,
and that you weren't
holding onto a pipe dream.
- Yeah.
The what could have been
with Ken weighs on my heart,
and I can't allow myself to
dwell on what could have been.
- It'll drive you insane.
[tense music]
[pensive music]
- It wasn't that I had like
fallen out of love with her,
or I didn't care about her,
or that I met somebody else,
or it wasn't any
of those things.
There were a lot of
people that were kind of
in my ear about what our
relationship was doing
for her and how it was affecting
her in a negative context.
I felt that I was hindering
her from self-development.
That was what ultimately
led to our separation,
and in hindsight, I didn't
realize at the time,
I mean, it makes
so much sense now,
but like when somebody is
kind of codependent like that,
and I would say that
Gypsy definitely was,
that that role is just gonna
be fulfilled by somebody else.
That she had reached
this new platform of fame
that she now has hundreds
of people writing her
with ill intentions.
Sure, I mean, I don't know.
You know, but a lot
of them I don't trust,
and that's what happened,
like almost immediately.
- No, I wasn't supportive of
any of her other relationships.
And I've seen interviews that
she's given talking about me
that she was
devastated, you know,
and that it was hard for her.
And I mean like even
just small components,
like her reaching out to me
right before her wedding,
and phone conversations
that we've had since.
- No.
- The last time Gypsy and
I spoke was right before
she got outta prison.
I made the decision that I
thought was best at the time
in the environment that I was in
and the people that
I had in my circle.
You know, I can't do
anything to change it,
but all I can say to her now
is that I really honestly hope
that you have real
joy in your life,
and I'll always defend you,
and I just hope that
you get everything
that life has to offer.
[gentle music]
- I'm gonna be
right back. Oh yeah.
You think daddy has
a treat for you.
That's not for you.
You wanna come sit down?
- [Ryan] Yeah.
You had your appointment
with the doctor.
How was it? Like,
do you like him?
- Yeah, he was very nice.
It went really good.
I scheduled it for
April 5th and they said
that recovery time
I'm looking at,
you know, six, eight weeks.
- I mean, that's a
lot on your body.
You know, you're
messing with your teeth
and this, I mean, is
there any other work done
that I need to know about?
- I mean, not like
surgical work,
but I wanna get my
hair done again.
- Not what I meant.
Baby, that's real blonde.
- Yeah, I want it to actually
be like super noticeable.
- So you're gonna
get a nose job,
you're getting your teeth done
and your hair's gonna change.
You're not even gonna be my
wife anymore. Like who are you?
- I am gonna be your wife, I'm
just gonna look super hot.
- You already there.
- You might feel that way,
but I wanna feel that way.
- I just hope it doesn't
change your looks up too much.
I know you're gonna
look beautiful.
- I hope it changes a lot.
- It's hard for me sometimes
to think about all these
changes 'cause it's like,
"Well, is it gonna change how
she perceives everything?"
You know, it's just
one of those like,
you just don't know, you know?
Like somebody could see
themselves in a different light
and be like, "Well,
I'm better now.
I could do this instead."
You know, like it's
just one of those like,
I have to be self
secured myself,
knowing that these changes
won't change her as a person.
[gentle music]
- Right now, I think that I
am at a point in my evolution.
I'm trying to figure out
what the future holds for me.
This is the phase where
I'm analyzing my life.
So much of like why Ryan and
I have had a lot of issues
with breaking walls
down, trust walls,
is because of the
breakup with Ken.
With Ken, I was an open heart,
open mind and then I got hurt,
and so my baseline to enter
into my relationship with Ryan
was still coming from
a place of healing.
So going into it,
I was already mistrusting
of relationships.
I have silver crowns
on all my back molars.
Two of them have fallen off.
I like the the blonde
coming from the root.
- Okay, so no more shadow root.
- Right.
- Okay.
- I don't think I
express my affection
in the way that he deserves
because there is that
little part of me
that is still so
broken over Ken.
[tense music]
You know, part of me wonders
had I just waited and stayed
single after Ken broke up
with me to see what would
happen later, but I didn't.
I went to a rebound
as soon as I could
because I was hurting.
I love Ryan, I'm
in love with Ryan,
but Ken had unlocked
something inside my soul.
Oh my God, they look so good.
Definitely different.
Cute, I like it.
I know he's gonna like it too.
- [Ryan] Hey, Pixie Pix.
Hey, baby.
- [Gypsy] Hey.
- [Ryan] Oh, let's see.
- [Gypsy] Hey Pixie.
- Oh wow, oh my God.
- Looks very
different, doesn't it?
- Oh wow, it's cut too.
- You like it?
- I love it.
- I do. Look at that, baby.
- Four hours in the chair.
- Is blonde. I thought you
weren't gonna go all blonde.
- Well, it's blonde so.
- It looks good.
- Thank you.
How was your day at work?
- Good, look at that.
- Yeah.
- You look so good.
- Good girl. Hey baby girl.
- Oh, you ain't
gonna sit with me?
So I can look at you?
- There you go. Did she
poop skidoo anywhere?
- I didn't see anything.
You got a cut too, huh?
- Yeah.
- You didn't go short
like you wanted?
- No, I mean like
I told her that
I wanted just like an angle cut.
- Looks good.
- [Gypsy] Thank you.
- You look so good. Yeah,
you changing all of you.
You ain't gonna be
my wife no more.
- I am too. I just look
a little different.
- You look a lot different.
Did you ever think
you'd ever go blonde?
- I mean, maybe.
- Like really blonde, not
like reddish blonde or?
- I mean, I wanted to.
- I know, but like...
- I don't know.
- Looking now in the mirror,
do you like notice like...
- Oh yeah, I can see
that it's blonde, yeah.
- Okay, did she put any toner
in? Is it gonna get lighter?
- It has toner. Yeah.
- So it will get lighter?
- Mm-hmm.
- You look just different.
Did you miss me today?
- Yeah.
- No, you didn't.
- I almost fell asleep in
that chair. I'm not gonna lie.
- You showed anybody, you
took a picture of anybody?
- Yeah?
- Really?
So I'm not the first
person to see it.
- Well, you are the first
person seeing the person.
- Well, I'm not the
first person to see it.
- [Gypsy] No.
- Who'd you send a picture to?
- My dad and Kristy.
- What'd they say?
- [Gypsy] They like it.
- Yeah, your boyfriend like it?
[Ryan laughing]
He did? Good.
Just joking.
What you think,
Pixie? You like it?
[pensive music]
- I think that there is that
wall of guilt between me
and my dad that we both
have been putting bricks
on it and adding to it.
I think instead of keep
on piling on the bricks,
we need to start
taking them down.
- You know, it was asked of
me to stay in Lake Charles
and let her parents have
Gypsy for the weekend.
It did hurt not
being asked to come.
It's not one of those
things I'm mad at,
but I have to bite my tongue,
I have to walk that thin line
of I can't be controlling.
I can't be this,
I can't be that,
Like I have to be,
I have to be aware of
her trauma and her past.
So, I mean, it's a tough
road to walk, but it's okay,
'cause I chose it.
[gentle music]
- You know, being able to show
Gypsy all of this stuff.
It's, you know, it's all
about culture down here.
This is our blood.
I mean our roots go
really deep here.
I just wanted to give her
a taste of some of this.
Get some mud between her toes.
So the way you do it,
just grab the rope,
make sure the
rope's not tangled.
- Okay.
- Drop it like that.
- All right.
- Stand right there. I'm
gonna tell you when, okay?
- All right.
Woo! [laughing]
I do that to everybody.
You're initiated.
- That's what I was gonna say.
I'm like, that's my initiation.
- Perfect. Good job.
[gentle music]
Cool.
- Ooh!
- So come up and drive.
- Oh my God.
- Get right here.
- Woo!
[laughing]
All right, let me take over.
- All right, go ahead.
Okay.
- Okay. Pull it up fast.
Come on. Big crab, big crab.
- They took the bait.
- [Rod] Took the bait?
[laughing]
God, Gypsy, you ain't worth
(bleep) at crabbing, girl.
- Hey!
I think we both feel
a mix of emotions.
Like at times, you know,
I feel like I don't
always know what to say.
I don't know if it's just like
that comfortability level.
It comes from like, wanting
to have a dad in my life,
and I just don't
wanna do anything
or say anything
that'll screw it up.
- [Gypsy] Woo!
- [Rod] Put it right
here. Tie it to this.
All right, we'll leave
them there 15, 20 minutes.
So I've noticed you took down
a lot of your social
media and everything.
- Yeah, like, I'm
seriously considering like,
just deleting at least
like the public ones.
It's just like, it doesn't
mean anything for me
to have a bunch of strangers
comment on my life.
- Yeah.
- And it's not worth it either.
- That's good, it's
good to hear that.
You can't win all those battles.
Everybody's gonna have
opinions, some good, some bad,
but then you try
to defend yourself
and then you're spending
so much mental energy
on stressing out about this
when you don't have to.
- Yeah.
- It really doesn't matter
as long as you're
good with, you know,
your family and the
people that that matter.
- And I don't wanna go
through my whole life being,
you know, Gypsy Blanchard,
the girl that
murdered her mother.
- I don't want people
to look at you like,
this is Gypsy
Rose, she's famous.
- [Gypsy] I don't either.
- For killing her mother.
You shouldn't be famous
for something like that.
- Exactly.
I hate that that F-word, famous.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, do I think
I'm famous? No.
- This is Gypsy Rose,
she survived this,
and went through
this, but, you know,
I'd rather be like that
then, you know, she's famous.
- So that's why I'm just like,
I really just wanna fade back.
- The way she analyzed
how social media
and was affecting her and
all this negative stuff,
it reflects a lot
on her maturity
and I'm real proud of that.
[screams]
- Two crabs, yay!
- Yes, yes!
[Rod laughing]
Success!
This guitar was my dad's
guitar. It's a good guitar.
[guitar playing]
Sounds great.
So you can use it as long
as you try to play it.
- I will.
For the first time in my life,
I have an actual dad
to teach me things.
- This is a pick.
- Okay.
I'm starting to
learn his personality
and get a sense of
who he is as a person.
He always just
wants my happiness,
and that's what I've learned.
- And this 12th note.
[guitar playing]
- My dad is the one that
named me Gypsy Rose.
I never knew that
because my mom told me
that her and my
grandma had named me,
and he's like, no,
you're Gypsy Rose,
because I'm a fan of
the band Guns N' Roses,
and I'm like, I didn't
know that. [laughs]
[guitar strums]
- Hold on. Okay, try again.
See? See how that feels?
- Yeah.
- You got a feeling in it.
You're feeling it
with the words.
- Yeah.
- Okay. So that's one chord.
- Oh, wow.
- It's one chord song.
- I guess I should be on my
own two feet at 32 years old,
but in a lot of ways
for experience wise,
it's like I'm back being 12,
16 years old all over again.
All right.
- Good?
- Oh my God. Okay.
- It feels high?
- It feels really high.
You're around the
people that you love
and if they're
teaching you something,
it's like a flashback to a time.
So it's almost that I'm
catching up on those memories.
Ooh.
[laughing]
- I've missed so much that it's
a little hard to catch up.
We just want to enjoy that
and I'm so happy to have that.
So blessed now.
- I got a wedgie!
[laughing]
- Turn the way you fall.
[laughing and yelling]
- (indistinct) a Band-Aid!
- Aw (bleep), that
ain't nothing, girl.
Your first bike crash.
It ain't gonna be your
last, don't worry about it.
[phone rings]
- Hey.
- Oh, I'm about to eat some
crab and some crawfish
and some shrimp.
- Not right now, honey.
- How was your day?
- Good? What'd you do?
[laughing]
- Me and dad went crabbing
and we caught three crabs.
- Yeah, that's it.
- But you got the
pictures I sent you?
- Thank you.
- I'll video you later.
- Like who?
- All right, well I gotta go.
[tense music]
- Sometimes it's actually really
nice not to have him around.
Ryan and I are having
an argument right now.
This is what he said.
- [Ron] "Could really give a
(bleep) about your dad's..."
Well, to me that's
a big red flag.
- It is a red flag.
- Baby, that is revenue.
- If all you care about
is (bleep) money.
- Baby.
(bleep).
Will you remarry me?
- Can we not do this on camera?
Sometimes I just think
that I would be happier
somewhere else.
- You have never lived
like you should have.
[indistinct whispering]
[Gypsy crying]