- She is going home today,
but she is not free yet.
- [Ryan] We're being followed.
[Gypsy grunts]
- [Gypsy] I am concerned.
Is paparazzi gonna follow us
all the way back to our home?
- We consummated our marriage.
A lot of people felt
I should have waited
in getting married.
- It's a lot of responsibility.
- That's the kind of [bleep]
that you tell a child.
Like, it's a lot of
responsibility, you know?
Just please don't treat me
like I don't know
what I'm doing.
If we don't get on that flight,
we don't do "Good
Morning America."
[somber music]
There's so many people.
- [Ryan] Quickly.
- Am I at risk for
dangerous people?
- Gypsy!
- Come our way.
- [Paparazzi] Gypsy.
- I was engaged once before.
Ken texted my stepmom.
He's sniffing around to try
and break me and Ryan up.
If you're not gonna be there
at my worst, you do not
deserve me at my best.
- Deserve me at my best.
[somber music]
[calm music]
- [Ryan] You know,
it's been nice
just me and you being here.
- [Gypsy] It's been nice not
having to do anything either.
- I love that you took up for
me last night on social media,
although it created
some drama, you know?
But you know I don't
listen to them yahoos.
- I know.
I'm trying to be really smart
with my social media right now.
I feel like everything
I do is on a microscope.
I posted one comment and
it's blowing up right now
on all the media channels.
- Gypsy Rose
Blanchard clapped back
against haters in her
husband's Instagram comments.
- "They jealous because
you are rocking my world
every night.
Yeah, I said it.
The D is fire."
- I'm sure after the many years
that Gypsy Rose was in prison,
she is very happy to
be getting that D.
- Oh my God.
- What?
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard, my
hubby gets it every night.
- Oh, you never said that.
- I never said that.
Well actually on a low
key way, I did say that.
- You did, you did
now that I think about it.
- A low key way.
Oh, my God.
- You did and now
that I think about you said,
"He's rocking my
world every night."
You did.
- Oy.
- We're newlyweds.
It's not like we're, you know,
not human.
- [Ryan] I know, but damn.
- You know who's
probably seeing this [bleep]
and getting so mad?
Hehe, my exes.
I love it.
- [Ryan] Don't even get
me started on them, baby.
[Gypsy laughs]
- Ryan was getting quite
a few negative comments
and they were being
very ignorant.
I feel a sense of
responsibility to defend him
because he's coming
into this with me.
We're experiencing
this whole whirlwind
of social media
attention together.
I want him to know
that he's not alone.
- Look, I got strips or nuggets.
I got either one for you.
I'm gonna start
packing some, you eat.
- Ryan and I are
going to New York City
to do interviews.
A little bit nervous
about all the press
that we have planned out for it.
- All right, so I got my pants.
I am about to throw
in my undershirts in there.
- I'm only packing
what we gonna wear.
We're not packing
our whole life.
- [Ryan] Speak for yourself.
- I know you want to.
- Speak for yourself.
Fine.
Fine baby, fine.
This is my first trip with
my wife leaving our home.
So it's like our
honeymoon in a way.
- [Gypsy] I'm nervous.
- I am too.
- I'm more nervous about the
PO meeting than New York.
- [Ryan] Well, it's
understandable.
- I'm about to go and
see my parole officer
in the state of Louisiana
for the first time.
It's actually pretty important.
I wanna make a good
impression with him.
I wanna like let him
know that like...
- [Ryan] You are gonna be great.
- I hope he knows
that I'm not some stuck
up, fame crazy person.
He kind of decides
where I can go,
what I could do,
my restrictions and everything.
So this is just the
first official meeting.
I just wanna be on
the real road with him
and be like, listen,
I left Kansas City
because they said to
and I didn't wanna
jeopardize anything.
- Right, we did exactly
what they asked.
- I was a responsible inmate.
I'm a responsible person.
- We did exactly
what they asked of us there.
- [Gypsy] I know that my PO
probably has been reading
a lot of the stuff that's
being put out by tabloids.
So I just really kind of
wanna put it out there that,
listen, I came out of prison
just wanting to live my life.
- Baby, I'm gonna carry,
remember what I told you about
carrying one load of clothes
in your carry on, right?
- [Gypsy] Yeah, you got your
blood pressure medicine?
- [Ryan] Yep, I got everything.
- Just making sure.
- Booyah, baby.
- Good job.
My freedom is at the
forefront of my brain 24/7.
Literally my biggest fear
is going back to prison
for another year and a half.
All right, we're on our way.
- [Ryan] This is one meeting
we cannot be late for.
- I'm nervous.
This appointment
is very important,
above all else.
- [Driver] All right.
- I mean I've talked
to plenty of people,
parole officers,
institutional parole officers.
- But I just don't like how
they intimidate inmates.
- Yeah, they do it a
weird way in prison.
- Here it is.
- All right, we made
it in good timing.
[intense music]
- This is bull [bleep].
Of course I'm nervous.
My wife's in there.
I don't know what's going on.
So I'm hoping that
there's no issues
and she gets her travel permit.
I don't know what we would do.
[intense music]
All right, we gots to go.
I had to do like a whole
questionnaire, paperwork.
- All right, you can tell
me all about it in the car.
I'm worried about the flight.
We're like two and
a half hours away.
So we just gotta get there.
- [Gypsy] Yeah, okay.
- How'd that go?
- It went really good.
- You were taking so long,
I thought you were in
there squalling, like.
- No, they had to do hand
prints, fingerprints, DNA.
- Damn, baby.
They say try to
keep a low profile?
- Just more like be
aware of what you do,
what you say.
Like if I take a selfie
and there's a vodka
bottle in the back of me,
you don't wanna give anybody
any reason to nitpick
and then report back
to him or to Missouri.
Be like, oh yeah, there's
a vodka bottle in the back
and here's the proof.
- Let me ask you this,
does he have control over
you now or does Missouri?
- They both do.
I'm being supervised by
two different states.
[intense music]
- Man, this say arrival, 7:42.
[bleep] we're cutting it close.
- Damn, we are cutting
it close, boss.
[phone rings]
- Hello?
Oh, okay, hi.
- [Rep] You need to
make this flight.
- We need to stuff
everything in our carry-ons
'cause if we don't
make this flight,
we don't arrive till six-
- Baby, I can't.
Like we have to check.
- If we have to, we
will leave our...
- No, I have to have it.
Like, baby, we got
one set of clothes.
Like what do they
- I know.
- want us to do?
All right, we're gonna
do the best we can.
- Okay.
- No, we're not.
- All right, I will.
- Okay, bye.
- Baby, no we're not.
- Okay, here's the situation,
if we don't get on that flight,
we don't do "Good
Morning America."
- I understand, but we're
gonna get on the [bleep] flight.
All my clothes are in my bag.
My meds are in my check bag.
You get what I'm saying?
- Well, then that's
why you put your meds
in your car-
- [bleep] [bleep] whatever.
- I'm just the messenger.
- Gate C's this lane, bud.
Gate C's over here.
Other lane boss.
- [Driver] Okay, okay.
- [Ryan] You better
get in another lane.
- [Driver] Yeah, yeah, gotta go.
- He's got it.
Quit badgering the man.
- [Driver] Says C
to the right.
- Yeah,
that's what I'm telling you.
[Gypsy groans]
- This is the most stressed
out I've been in a while.
- Zoom around this [bleep].
- What did I say about language?
- Sorry.
- Oh my God, we have
to make this flight.
He has everything.
[clock ticks]
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard has
now done her first interview
since getting out of prison
and it was with "Good
Morning America."
Ryan joined her on this,
but one of the takeaways
that I got from this
was the fact that she has stated
she is now becoming the woman
she's always wanted to be.
- When asked if this was
her happily ever after,
she said quote,
"It is, I had to kiss a couple
frogs to get to this one."
And then she leaned
in, kissed his face,
and said, "Handsome face."
[intense music]
- [Ryan] Baby, I love our view.
- I know, it's so beautiful.
- Like, we don't even have
to leave the hotel room.
We can just hang out
in New York like this.
- That was insane.
We were late to the airport.
Her PO meeting took
longer than we,
than it should have.
And we were like, oh God, are
we gonna make this flight?
- He started getting nervous
and he started freaking out.
And then I'm just kind of like,
I'm just the
messenger right now.
Like, don't freak out on me.
- I was mad.
I was throwing my
luggage basically.
But Gypsy calmed me down.
To me it was like, baby, focus.
And I was like, okay.
And it's kind of cool
when she freaks out,
I'm the calm one and
then when I freak out,
she's the calm one.
- So what are these little jars?
- [Makeup Artist] Concealer.
- Concealer?
- Yeah.
- My mom didn't like
want me to wear makeup.
She didn't even want
me to wear lip gloss.
- Mom restricted everything.
Couldn't even wear blue jeans.
[sad music]
- It is kind of polar
opposites, honestly,
where I was in prison,
restricted, hardly any makeup,
and now I'm getting all glammed
up and I'm in New York City.
Kind of like I've stepped
in the twilight zone.
And then like the
attention on social media,
like I'm not used to it at all.
And so right now, I think
there's a huge adjustment
that needs to happen.
It's like, is this my life?
[lively music]
- So baby, you excited to
go shoot at "The View?"
- I'm nervous.
- Baby, you got this.
- I came out of prison just
wanting to live my life
and all this media attention
is not something that I said,
hey, I wanna be famous.
It's just, it's happening
whether I like it or not.
- Gypsy.
- Come our way.
- So there's our security.
- No selfie.
- Pressed for time.
- Yup, no time.
- All right.
- Okay, come out on this side.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- How are you?
- [Ryan] Is there
a restroom in here?
- There's a private
restroom in there.
- Thank you so much.
- [Producer] Gypsy, there's
a little gift for you
on the table.
- Awe.
Oh my goodness, I
wanted one so bad.
I watched the show and
I was like, oh my God,
I hope I get a little mug.
Thank you guys.
This is awesome.
This is gonna be in
front of a live audience.
So part of me is scared
that my brain is just
gonna shut off and be like,
focus all on the people.
So I can stutter
when I'm nervous.
So I just hope I don't stutter.
- [Ryan] You got this, babe.
- Yeah.
- [Ryan] Haters gonna hate.
Let 'em hate
- Right.
- because I mean,
I'm that awesome
when I pulled this.
So, you know, it is what it is.
Yeah, no, but I love
that she did comment.
Come to my defense.
I love that she's willing.
- I'm a tiger.
- Yeah, she's [Ryan growls],
she gets you.
- I'll get you.
- [Ryan] She'll maul your face.
- Not literally.
[audience applause]
- So Gypsy Rose Blanchard made
worldwide headlines when she
was convicted of orchestrating
her mother's murder.
[intense music]
- I don't wanna be
remembered as the girl
who killed her mother.
I'm always gonna struggle
with wanting my privacy,
but also wanting a voice.
[audience applause]
- Please welcome
Gypsy Rose Blanchard.
You were released from
prison just a week ago.
- Yes.
- How are you doing?
- Well I'm doing great.
I'm in New York City
for the first time.
I know I am enjoying my freedom.
I'm taking it day by day.
But with the massive amount
of platform that I have,
you know, the 6 million
followers
on Instagram and TikTok,
I really wanna get
into advocacy work.
You know, if there is someone
out there watching right now,
please listen to
me, heed my words
that you are not alone in
this, you know, situation.
There are other ways out.
I did it the wrong way.
You you know?
- [Joy] No, no, no, no,
don't say that.
- But I did.
- [Joy] You had
no choice really.
- I did something wrong
and I paid my dues for it.
- [Joy] Oh, you mean that part?
- Yes, the part of it.
- Oh yeah.
- You know, that part of it.
- Never mind.
- Where are you going
with this story?
- No, no, no, no.
You know, so I did something-
- Murder is wrong, Joy.
- Yes, murder's wrong.
[lively music]
That was so good.
- Was it good?
You do all right?
- They were so nice.
[paparazzi chatters]
- No time, we got places to go.
Thank you, we love y'all.
We love you.
- Possible.
[Gypsy giggles]
Probable, possibly when I say
possibly.
- Possible or something.
[Gypsy laughs]
- Possible.
You did so good, gimme a kiss.
So proud of you.
- That went a lot smoother
than I like was preparing for.
- You looked so good up there.
Like, I was like,
that's my wife.
I kept telling the audience,
y'all realize that's my wife.
- [Gypsy] Okay, so we
just have a podcast.
[lively music]
- Go ahead, sweetheart.
- Gypsy, how are you?
- Hello, hi.
it's nice to meet you.
- So nice to meet you.
So nice to meet you.
- Ryan.
Nice to meet you, buddy.
- So nice to meet you.
This is my fiance, Natalie.
- Hi, hi.
It's nice to meet you.
- Right on, I love that.
- Thanks, man.
- It looks good.
Hey, I'm Ryan.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Oh, I get a hug, nice.
- Yeah.
[lively music]
- Gypsy, welcome to
"The Viall Files".
Congratulations on being out.
- Thank you.
- We're very excited
to be with you.
- Thank you.
- What has this
been like for you
since being released for prison?
- You know, it's a
bit of a little bit
of a whirlwind for me.
I never expected to have such
a big social media following.
So I'm kind of like,
okay, I have a voice now.
I'm free, it's my turn now.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- It's cool watching
everything unfold
because it's just
like, you know,
I have to like pinch myself.
Like, while during
"The View" I was like,
you know, I'm actually
married to this woman.
Like, in my head I'm
like, that's my wife.
Like, can you believe that?
Like, that's my
wife right there.
It's surreal.
I love that she picked me.
- Do you have a
desire in the future
to kind of disappear or go away?
- I've always had a very
love hate relationship
with the media and the
attention from all of this.
- [Nick] No, that won't go away.
- That's actually, I
was engaged once before.
- Mm-hmm. To Ken.
- Yeah, to Ken, yeah.
And we were together
for two years
and then our engagement
was announced
and he is a very private person.
And so he didn't
like the attention.
And so I attributed him
breaking off the engagement
and breaking my heart and
devastating me to the fame.
So that made me hate it
and then seeing how
I've been welcomed,
that makes me at least
feel more comfortable
in being who I am.
- Well now that you're married,
should we bring him in here
and get to know Ryan
- Yes, yeah.
- a little bit?
All right, let's do it.
- Let's get him in here.
- [Nick] Get in here, Ryan.
- [Gypsy] Come sit next to me.
- All right Ryan, we have to
ask you, how is your heart?
- It's been a
rollercoaster ride,
but I'm enjoying it.
This fame thing is so new.
It's kind of overwhelmed
me in a sorts of like,
I didn't realize it'd
be as big as it is.
You know, she's always been
worried that I was gonna leave
for the fame, you
know, because of it,
because of past relationships.
And I've told her that
I'm not going anywhere,
- You know, being
open and honest
around the day that
I got outta prison,
Ken texted my stepmom.
- [Natalie] Ah, stop
- And she told, yeah,
she told me about
it and I'm like,
oh, so now he wants
to come around.
So I told Ryan about it.
- [Natalie] Yeah.
- I was open and I'm like, you
know, he's sniffing around.
[suspenseful music]
- Ken texted my stepmom.
- I don't like him at all.
- And he was like,
hey, what's up?
- Why do you think he decided
it's time to pop back up?
- Because I think now I'm free
and I don't think that he
has respect for my marriage.
- Well, he doesn't like me
'cause I've called him names.
- Names.
- Like I have, you know,
he's known as something to me.
- Yeah.
- I don't see why
you should like him.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I call him a dumb mother,
you know?
- Yeah.
- Beep, beep, beep, beep.
- So every time I-
Every time that like-
- You can swear
on the podcast.
- He's reached out to me before.
- Has he?
- Well, actually Gypsy has
like asked me to text him.
- He still has my stuff.
- Apparently he has
stuff of hers
- Like he has stuff of mine
- that he like holds.
- like old pictures and stuff.
I've asked him to just
ship my stuff to my stepmom
and then I can get it from her.
And he's like, no, you know,
I still have all that
stuff, but like, you know?
- [Natalie] You can come get it.
- You can come get it.
- You can come get it, yeah.
- You know, if he's sniffing
around to try and like,
break me and Ryan up
or see if I will leave
Ryan to get back with him,
this is how I feel about it.
If you're not gonna be there
at my worst, you do not
deserve me at my best.
- Deserve me at my best.
Okay.
- Yeah, that's right.
- And if you know anything
about Gypsy's Instagram
and you've seen the
recent comments,
she's not going anywhere.
- I'm glad.
- Turns out the D
is fire.
- Come and get it, baby.
- He's missed his chance.
It is what it is.
[calm music]
- Good, trying to figure out...
Is there like a secret
to this or something?
- Should I wear my
black shoes with this
or my brown one?
I'm a wear my brown though.
- Brown shoes look good.
- Okay, well I got
a black jacket.
That's the only problem.
And a black scarf.
- It's just warm.
- Okay.
- All right.
So what are we gonna do?
We just go and go walk?
- Yeah, let's go
to Times Square.
[lively music]
This is the first chance
we've had to walk New York,
so I'm actually really
excited right now.
- So number one on the agenda
list is to find a store
where we can get an I
love New York T-shirt.
- I saw it.
I saw one when we drove
through Times Square.
- Yeah, but there was a lot.
There were so many of them.
- That's where we're going
first in Times Square,
just so you know.
♪ So I'm gonna stand my ground
♪ Got something to believe in
- So this is Times Square.
- Holy [bleep].
- Look, they changed
the color of the ball.
- So many people.
Hey everybody.
So we are in Times Square.
Look at this.
- [Ryan] Can you believe
we're actually in New York?
- I know.
- Oh, I like love
on you in here.
My glasses.
- Be good.
Be good.
- Yeah.
- Hello.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
[intense music]
- We hear that a lot,
aren't we?
- Yeah, we're being recognized.
- [Ryan] This is weird.
Alright, let's go that way.
- Gypsy.
Gypsy Rose.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- [Gypsy] Hi.
I'm like really
uncomfortable right now.
- [Bystander] I cannot
believe that a mom
could do that to their child.
- [Bystander] My heart
goes out to her
because she endured so much
from the hand to the
person who's supposed
to love her the most.
- I'm in college right now.
It breaks my heart that she
didn't get to have a childhood
that I had.
Like, I'm 19, not having
a normal 19-year-old life.
It makes me feel so
bad for her life.
- She's so strong,
she got out of it.
I mean, not the way
she should have,
but I mean it, I
feel bad for her.
- [Gypsy] When
people come up to me,
they have the best
of intentions,
but it's actually really
hard to get used to it.
- All right, everybody smile.
All right, I got three or four.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
[sad music]
- [Gypsy] I don't wanna
be defined by the things
that happened in the past.
Like when people pity
me, I don't like that.
I am not living a
life of abuse anymore.
I just want them to be like,
I'm happy you're happy
in your new life.
- [Gypsy] Hey, you're welcome.
♪ Back to the time when
we were anonymous ♪
- [Ryan] Guys, if we take
one, we take a million.
- [Gypsy] It just kind
of seems like everybody
has just gone Gypsy
bat [bleep] crazy.
I was expecting to
just get out of prison
and nobody really notice
anything about me.
It didn't turn out that way.
♪ Is it too late
to say I regret? ♪
♪ Is it too late to
make you forget? ♪
♪ How can I be so blind?
- [Gypsy] Yeah, let's
take a photo.
- [Gypsy] I mean, I'm just
starting to see that that's
just, you know,
what I have to live with.
- Very quick.
- [Ryan] Quickly, quickly.
- [Gypsy] I'm not
one of those people
that go looking for attention,
but it just kind of found me.
♪ But I can't take it back, no
[calm music]
- I love that we're
no longer having
our relationship on
the phone anymore.
Now it's real.
We've been on this trip together
and it's been amazing.
- What we're doing right now
is what we've been
planning all this time.
We just needed the bars to
open up for me, you know?
- That's right.
We just needed her out.
[lips smack]
- It feels like I leveled up.
It feels like I leveled
up from, you know,
the freedom that I had in prison
to freedom in the real world.
And actually I'm starting to
get why people are like, wow.
She said she feels
free in prison?
That's messed up.
She must have really had it bad.
- Gypsy is amazing.
This is my other half.
I've been waiting
for it for so long
and I'm glad she's
home, you know?
Like I, you know,
it's so cliche,
you know, like, baby
you complete me,
but she really does.
You know, like that
Jerry McGuire, like-
- You did not just say that.
- Yeah, you complete me.
[Gypsy giggles]
No, like, but you know,
it's funny, I can't
stop smiling, you know?
It's great just having
her around all the time.
- We spent some money
today on some shirts.
- [Ryan] Yeah, we did.
- I think that-
- She hasn't paid for anything.
What is she talking about?
She ain't had to
touch money yet.
- Yeah, that's actually,
that's very true.
I haven't had to pay for
anything honestly in my life.
My problem is, is
if I want something,
I want it.
- [Ryan] She's gonna get it.
Yeah.
- I mean, I say that
in a way that it's not-
- It didn't sound
too good there, baby.
- That sounded terrible.
- It was awful.
If I want something, I want it.
I'm gonna get it by
any means necessary.
- Not like that though.
- [Ryan] It's terrible, baby.
- But the things I
want are not expensive,
minus those shoes.
I just had wanted one pair of
You know what, I
wanna look this up
how you say it.
but what I bought you
- I'm gonna get the bag and
I'm gonna prove it to you.
- You know your husband's right.
You about to be like,
oh, I'm sorry hubby.
- Okay, so-
- [Ryan] What do I get
if I'm right?
Do I get a kiss?
- All right.
- What does it say?
- It...
- Yeah.
- It's Christian Loui...
- [Ryan] No, no, no.
- Dang it.
- Come here.
[calm music]
- [Gypsy] Ever since
I got out of prison,
it feels like I've been
dropped into a movie.
Like the scene of a movie.
- [Ryan] You know, challenges
ahead for me and Gypsy,
it's gonna be, you know,
right now we're living a
glam style life right now.
I'm not gonna say
I'm not worried
that when the honeymoon's over,
is things gonna change?
I just want her to be happy.
- Gypsy Rose has only
been an influencer
for roughly around
two weeks now.
And in that roughly
two week time span,
people have already started
to change their opinion
and turn on her.
- Just a little
overexposed right now
and it's really only
gonna get worse.
- People have
decided to un-stan.
- They felt she should
still be in prison.
- There's also the fact that
Gypsy became so famous so fast,
which has a lot of people
feeling like we're rewarding
very bad behavior
by allowing someone
who helped take
someone else's life
have such a massive
platform right after prison.
[sad music]
- I've been looking
at my DMs more
and I will have at
least 10 death threats.
This person said, "You
stupid waste of space.
Wait until you are cancelled
by real people that
ruin your life.
You are going to wish that
you were back behind bars.
I can't wait to be a part of
tearing you down bit by bit.
You deserve nothing but
to be six feet under
or locked away forever.
There are real kids with
cancer and real life problems,
unlike you that just
went along with it
because mommy told you to.
You poor excuse
for a human being
and I wish nothing
but the worst for you.
You attention-
wanting whore self.
You deserve nothing good and
I will make sure I'm a part
of making your
life a living hell.
Go to hell. Go hang
yourself [bleep]."
I understand that a lot of
people are upset right now
because I came out of prison
and the first thing
that I was jolted into
was this sense of fame.
What happens if I get a hater
that is a little too
comfortable with how they feel
and they come up to me and punch
me or get physical with me?
You know, that is a
dangerous situation.
When the backlash comes,
am I at risk for
dangerous people?
[calm somber music]
- [Ryan] You excited to
eat my mom's cooking?
It's really good.
- Yeah, yeah.
This is gonna be great.
- [Ryan] This is gonna be great.
[Gypsy chuckles]
[car door slams]
Hey.
- Hey.
- [Gary] Y'all made it.
- We made it.
- [Ryan] We match.
- I cooked for the first time,
my first real well
semi-real meal by myself.
- [Joy] Tell me.
- So it was just a
Nora pasta side.
I'm playing on my
phone, you know,
checking Instagram and whatever.
All of a sudden, [Gypsy
imitates crackling]
it like, no.
- [Joy] It overflowed?
- It started foaming.
I thought I was gonna
set the house on fire
my very first try.
- She sure did.
She come running out, ahh.
- Smile.
There we go.
Oh, that's a cute picture.
- Oh, that's a good one.
- That's a good one.
- Let me see.
- [Gypsy] You want
me to send it too?
- Oh, it is good.
- I only take cute pictures,
[Gypsy laughs]
despite what the
haters online say.
- I feel like I want to
engage on social media
because it's new
to me, it's fun.
I'm showing my life
to my followers.
I'm not doing anything that
anybody else wouldn't be doing.
But everybody wants
to find a negative
in something that I do.
- [Joy] Y'all ready to eat?
- [Ryan] Mom, this
looks delicious.
Where are you sitting me, baby?
- Right here.
- [Ryan] Okay, sweetie.
- Next to me.
[calm music]
This is delicious.
- I love it.
We're gonna cook this at home.
- Yeah, right.
That's why I was telling you
we got that exact chicken.
[phone vibrates]
- [Joy] Did you see those
stuffed potato?
- That's my boss,
I gotta take this.
[intense music]
Hey, what's going on?
- [Ryan] Yes ma'am, yes ma'am.
That's when I plan
on coming back.
[intense music]
- [Ryan] I was worried
about my kids' parents,
how did they feel and
that was my main concern.
Well trust me, we got our
hand slapped for that one.
So no worries on that.
I understand.
All right, thanks, bye.
- [Gypsy] Everything okay?
- Yeah, she just
wanted to touch base,
see if I was coming
back on Tuesday
and she thanked you for the
D is fire comment by the way.
[Joy laughs]
- Yeah, she thanked
you for that one.
But she said they've had one
negative call from a parent
and if she's like, you're
kind of the celebrity
of the school now.
So one teacher thinks
I'm not coming back.
She thinks I'm too famous and
I'm like, y'all are crazy.
[Joy laughs]
I'm like, I need my job.
- [Gary] Yeah, you
wanna keep your job.
- I have to ask her first
if she wants to, but...
- You were trying to get
her to do it the other day.
- Oh.
- Well she's the prettiest
girl in school, I like her.
[Joy laughs]
- [Ryan] Zoom in a little bit.
- Maybe I should
take my hair down
because this is going
on my Instagram.
So I gotta look good.
[Gypsy giggles]
I would love to
just kinda be free
to not care what people think.
But I'm in a position where
even the littlest things
that I do are being scrutinized.
The negative comments make
me feel like I can't be
my authentic self
on social media.
Your nose is too big,
you look fat, you're ugly,
you're a killer,
you're a murderer.
There's only so much that
someone can take of that.
I like this one way better.
- I like this one.
- [Joy] Let me look at it.
Lemme see it, lemme
see it, lemme see.
- You'll be the judge.
[calm music]
- [Ryan] You excited?
Check out our wedding venue.
- Yeah.
Or a potential wedding venue.
- A potential.
Right, potential being the word.
Ryan and I got married
and the ceremony was not
the ceremony of our dreams.
We just wanna have something
that we can invite everybody
that we care about
and that loves us.
And so we're looking
at wedding venues.
Slidell, that's
where I used to live.
Tulane, that was my hospital.
- [Ryan] Uh-huh.
- Yes.
- [Ryan] Oh gosh.
- That was one of
my hospitals, Tulane
Medical Center.
- [Ryan] Oh wow.
- This bridge looks familiar.
- [Ryan] The bridge?
[Ryan and Gypsy laugh]
That bridge looks familiar.
That stop sign looks like
something I would talk to.
- [Gypsy] Very funny.
I'm having deja vu.
- [Ryan] That bridge
looks familiar.
All good baby, I'm glad.
- [Gypsy] Coming
back to New Orleans,
you know, it brings
back a lot of memories.
It's like you're
coming back home.
The houses look so beautiful.
- [Ryan] Isn't
that cool looking?
You excited?
- Yeah.
- [Ryan] Degas
House, it's this one.
- Ryan and I got married
and it was by a bathroom.
- Yeah, I mean it was,
it was the visiting room.
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- You know she's wearing khaki,
I'm all dressed up looking nice,
but you know?
- Yeah, he looked great.
- Gypsy's always needed
that white dress moment.
- Hi guys.
- Hi.
How are you?
- I'm Ali.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- I'm Ryan.
- I'm Gypsy.
- Nice to meet y'all.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
- All righty, so y'all
ready to get started?
- Yes.
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
- [Ryan] We had a lot of
negative people in our family,
especially her family didn't
want us to get married.
They want us to wait.
So now that she's
out and everything,
it's like now y'all get
to share in the happiness
that we already feel.
- These tables and chairs come
out of the center courtyard
and we put them up here
in the arrival garden.
- Okay.
- So everybody can
have a seat, kind of relax.
- Yeah, that's pretty cool.
- I like that.
- Yeah.
So this will be where
all of your tables
are set up for the reception.
- Yeah, I can see it.
- It's kind of cool.
The lights would
be lit probably.
- Yeah.
It's cute.
- it's beautiful, right?
- Yeah.
[calm music]
- [Ali] So this would
be your main bar.
- [Gypsy] I'm a
sucker for chandelier.
- Yes.
It is actually an
antique from France.
- It's gracious.
- Can I offer y'all
some king cake?
- Yes, I would love some.
- Yeah?
- [Ryan] She would
like some, okay.
- [Gypsy] I'm a
sucker for king cake.
- [Ali] Oh, of course,
how can you not be?
- {Ryan] First spot.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Appreciate it.
- [Ryan] Oh yeah, I'll
definitely get a bite offa that.
- [Ali] It's good.
- You want a bite first?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, a little bite.
Get in there.
[Gypsy giggles]
- [Ryan] I mean,
I'm still in shock
that I married this
beautiful woman.
Just picturing all this,
even the day of would
just be breathtaking.
Like I never thought my life
would be this, that's for sure.
- [Ali] The best
part about the room.
- [Gypsy] Oh wow.
- [Ryan] That's so cool.
Look at that little balcony.
Oh my God.
- [Gypsy] Oh my goodness.
I like it.
- [Ryan] Oh wow.
We got a lot to think about.
- I will get y'all's information
and I can send y'all a proposal
with all of the pricing
- Absolutely, absolutely.
- and everything.
- Yeah, that sounds good.
Okay, perfect.
- That's what we'd like.
This is great.
- Nice, thank you.
- Awesome, beautiful.
- Of course.
- The next time
that we say I do,
we're going into it knowing
that we really, really,
really mean forever.
Not that there was
a doubt before, but-
- There wasn't.
There wasn't.
[calm somber music]
[cars buzz past]
- [Ryan] So you liked
you therapist?
- She was nice.
It was just a
first consultation.
She asked a little
bit about my life.
I told her about my mom.
She's like, "I'm
gonna be honest.
I don't know much about
Munchausen by proxy,
but what I would be
treating you for is trauma."
I said, "Okay."
She's like, "What sparked this
whole social media thing?"
And I'm like, honestly,
it just happened.
Whenever I got out, I
posted my first selfie
and before I knew it, I
had 5 million followers.
It just happened.
- [Ryan] Overnight.
- I wasn't, overnight,
and I'm like, I
didn't ask for it.
It just happened.
But she did gimme like warnings.
There's just a word of caution
that like prioritize myself
instead of everything
else around me.
- I agree.
- From the one session,
it was like 45 minutes,
I got a lot out of it actually.
And trying to remember
just who I am.
I know who I am, I
believe in myself.
Like positive self talk.
[sad music]
♪ This moment
♪ Broken bones, oh
♪ Redefined
- This post right here
is, is just honestly,
it's a message to
anyone that supports me
for me being me.
♪ Feel safe here
- At the end of
the day, I'm human,
I'm flawed, I make mistakes.
[Gyspy sighs]
Like I would've never
done this four years ago.
Me wearing athletic wear
because it shows my
feeding tube scar.
For the longest time, I
felt very embarrassed.
It's one of those things
that it's a reminder
of the things that
happened to me.
So I wear it proudly
in my picture.
Like this is a part of me.
There's a lot of negative
comments on social media
and some of them have been like,
girl, eat a salad, you're fat.
And considering the fact that
I used to be malnourished
and severely underweight when
I was living with my mom,
yeah, I packed on some weight,
but I'm still good with myself.
So this is basically
me being fed up
and I'm saying I'm not
letting the hate get to me,
but to everyone who does still
support me, I see you guys.
If you're just here
to see my demise
or to see me fail,
well you might as
well unfollow now
because it's not gonna happen.
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard
has gone from receiving
a ton of love and
support to now receiving
a ton of hate and backlash.
- Now she's too successful.
Now she's kind of annoying.
- Gypsy Rose is
disappointing so many people.
- At this point,
she's just going to get
herself into more trouble.
[eerie music]
- You remember the lady at
the Degas House we met, Ali?
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- She emailed me and she said,
we have to give 50% of
how much the quote was
to hold that day by
like two days from now.
- I mean...
- I mean baby, that
place was beautiful.
- Yeah, I mean it was beautiful,
but you know, right now,
it's just, I'm feeling
a lot of stress
from everything else
going on right now.
Like I've only been out
of prison for a few weeks.
- Right.
- You know?
And like my version of how
like I want things to be
after the hype of
everything dies down,
is me to just have like
a nine-to-five job,
go to the grocery store
and people say hi to me
because they know me,
I'm their neighbor,
something like that
instead of, oh my God,
it's Gypsy Blanchard,
can I take your selfie?
Like I just wanna be just Gypsy.
- Married you, the person, you.
Didn't marry the fame,
because when I met you,
you know like you
were in prison.
- I know.
- I was in love
with you.
- I know.
- You know that.
- So we got our sights
set on a normal life.
- You know, I just wanna
have a family with you.
- Okay, we need to
start taking that route.
- Well, we're going to.
- There comes a point
that is this the life
that we really wanna
lead for ourselves?
- Right 'cause we
wanna have kids.
- Having to be
in the spotlight all the time.
- Trust me, I'm on
this journey with you.
[sad music]
But I still would like
you to remarry me.
- I would, I just,
the timing needs to be
at a little bit of a
more convenient time
than just right now.
[sad music]
I had a nightmare about my mom.
I know I didn't turn
out how you wanted me to
and I know you
wished better for me.
- [Friend] How's
it feeling, Gyps?
- I think it hurts less than
the pick and poke that I did.
It's a K to
symbolize Ken, my ex.
- What?
- [Stepmom] Yes.
- If I wasn't married to Ryan...
[fingers snap]
- I know.
Well he's not with
anyone right now.
- Of course not.
I have my commitment
to my husband,
but I also just feel like no
one is ever gonna love him
as much as I love him.
- He's a dumb mother [bleep].
Pretty soon I'm
gonna get involved
and you do not want that, Ken.
Believe me, you
do not want that.