- I was engaged
once before, to Ken,
he didn't like the attention.
And so I attributed him
breaking off the engagement
to the fame.
- What?
- I have two men in my heart.
I miss Ken.
- Marriage is hard,
nobody said it was easy.
But you have to work at it.
- And are you not wanting
to fight for this anymore?
No?
[tense music]
It's not up to me. It's
never been up to me.
- It's just something that
you have to go through
the rough stuff to get
to where you belong.
Is it the right
thing? I don't know.
Is it the wrong
[tense music]
- That was the
hardest part, huh?
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- Just let it out all right
now if you want to, Gypsy,
scream if you want to.
It's okay.
Let it out.
- He keeps texting me,
he's like, you know,
"If you don't, just tell
me you don't love me,
tell me that--"
- [Kristy] It's
not that you don't.
- And I'm like I can't--
- You don't love him.
- I can't tell you I don't.
- You don't love
him like you should,
or love him like
how he loves you.
[emotive music]
- I thought that I tried.
- [Kristy] You
did, baby. You did.
You did.
- I mean, I'm not perfect.
There are some things that...
- [Kristy] Who is?
- I could've done different.
- But who is perfect, sweetie?
Nobody.
Nobody's perfect.
- And I mean, it's...
It's heartbreaking
because it's like,
I know he feels like
our relationship
was like maybe something just
for prison, and it wasn't.
♪ Did you know the day
the Earth stood still ♪
♪ Is when I found you
- I married him
because I thought
that this marriage could work,
and then three months
into us living together,
it's like, things come up.
- And nobody faults
you for that.
Not at all.
- And I mean, I know I'm a
lot to handle too, you know.
- [Kristy] You're
not a lot to handle.
Don't, you're not.
- Like--
- [Kristy] But--
- The fact that he stood
by me through everything,
I love him for that, and
I'm grateful for that.
♪ Take my hand, wreck my plans
♪ And if you lost your wings
♪ Take mine instead
♪ Wherever we are
racing through ♪
♪ Every time I look
at you, our love ♪
- Seeing what she's
going through right now,
and I told her that, "Gypsy,
the way you're feeling,
I felt the same way
with your mother."
And she made a mistake
of marrying Ryan,
and it takes some courage to
accept that you feel that way
and you made a mistake,
and realize it,
and say it, and
take some action.
I think it's gonna
help her grow a lot,
and that's what I wanna see.
[soft music]
- [Gypsy] You got it?
♪ You should know the day
the Earth stood still ♪
- Ready?
- Ready.
♪ Is when I learn
to love again ♪
- [Gypsy] [laughs] Hey.
- Welcome home.
- Hey.
- [Kristy] Surprise!
- It's been a long day.
- Welcome home.
- Thank you.
- Make yourself at home.
- [Gypsy] I will.
[light music]
All right.
- Start making a list
of things that, any...
We'll turn this into your own.
It is your own.
- Today's been
emotionally exhausting.
Having to leave Pixie
behind, that was hard.
I know why I'm doing
what I'm doing.
It's no offense to Ryan, I
think that he is a good person,
but he himself has baggage that
he brings into our marriage,
and I have hella baggage
that I bring in our marriage.
I'm just trying to do what's
best for me right now.
Like I texted Ryan and I'm like,
I wanna hold you, I
want to make it better,
I want the hurt to
go away for you,
but I know I'm not that
person right now for you,
I'm the person that's
making you sad.
- He cussed me out,
and I understood.
Things were going good
until the day that
it wasn't going good.
[somber music]
- She texted me and said,
"But I still love
you, and I miss you,"
you know, things like that.
And I'm texting her,
like, "Hey, I miss you,
I really wish you'd call me,"
or whatever, da da da da.
And the first thing she does
is send me a picture
that people have got
that released of her and Ken.
This is it.
"Ken came to visit."
Her not wearing her ring.
She wrote, "We just hung out."
It was surprising
to say the least,
it was, but in my head I was
like, "Of course he came."
And she goes on to
tell me that you know,
"Don't worry, we're
just friends."
I wake up to the next day, I
see them get matching tattoos.
And when you put 'em
together, it's a heart,
of two huskies, the dog they
always talked about getting.
So what I do is I take a picture
of our actual dog, Pixie,
and I said, "Are you
really gonna take that dog
over your actual dog
that we bought together
that's here right now?"
And she couldn't say nothing.
The matching tattoos
broke my heart.
[tense music]
It was like, did
I mean anything?
Did I mean anything?
[Ryan crying]
[clock ticking]
- So this is the picture
that's circulating,
this is Gypsy and her ex
Ken, at the tattoo parlor.
- Gypsy is living her
single girl fantasy,
so maybe they're just
having a spring fling,
maybe they're getting
back together.
Who knows, I don't care,
I'm obsessed with this.
It'll be interesting to
see how this pans out.
- [Ryan] Don't even act like
I don't have you for adultery.
- [Gypsy] I don't wanna
be hit with adultery,
not for, you know, a friendship,
I mean we haven't done anything
that consists of adultery.
- [Ryan] Gypsy, you're
honestly gonna sit there
and tell me y'all
didn't have sex?
- [Gypsy] We didn't
do any of that.
- [Ryan] Honest to God?
- [Gypsy] Honest.
- [Ryan] I'm not gonna
sit here and admit
that, "Okay I believe you,"
I'm not gonna admit to that.
- [Gypsy] So you're gonna
try to get me on adultery?
- [Ryan] I don't know, Gypsy,
I don't know anything right now.
You know, this week's
been a whirlwind to you,
it's been a whirlwind to me too.
We haven't even seen
each other to talk.
- [Gypsy] I know, the last
time that we seen each other,
we were very heated
in this argument.
- [Ryan] No, the last
time I saw you, you said,
"You know I love you," and
then you walked outta the room.
- [Gypsy] I do love you!
I wanted to find out what
my life would've been like,
had it not been like
that we got married.
I don't want this to be
something that you hate me for,
which, I mean if I was
you, I'd probably hate me.
I've broken every
vow that I made.
[somber music]
And it hurts me that I hurt you.
- [Ryan] 'Cause
you still love me.
- [Gypsy] Of course I love
you. And I always will.
- [Ryan] You're still
technically my wife,
and I do miss you, I'm not
gonna lie, I miss you terribly.
- [Gypsy] Ryan, it's too late.
I've set down a path I can't
change, even if I wanted to.
- [Ryan] Yes you could, if you
wanted to, you could, baby.
I mean, come on, at
least let me see you.
- [Gypsy] I told
you I needed time
to figure out how I felt.
- [Ryan] But you
haven't even seen me!
It's not fair.
- I've lived with you
for three months.
- [Gypsy] Do you think
that if you saw me
anything would change?
- [Ryan] Maybe, but I
mean, me not seeing you
after one fight is
(bleep), it's (bleep).
- [Gypsy] I just don't
think it's a good idea.
- [Ryan] Why?
- [Gypsy] [sighs]
Because I don't--
- [Ryan] So you know.
- [Gypsy] I don't wanna
give you false hope.
- [Ryan] False hope?
- [Gypsy] Even this call
is giving you false hope.
I shouldn't have called.
- [Ryan] Babe,
when I married you,
I knew this would be difficult,
I knew that.
But you gotta know,
I'm still right here,
I've been here this whole time.
- [Gypsy] I know, but I'm not.
- I want a divorce,
and in six to nine months,
I'm gonna be with Ken.
- [Ryan] You are still
Gypsy Rose-Anderson,
you know that, right?
- [Gypsy] Trust me, I know.
I'll text you later.
[tense music]
[Gypsy sighing]
[phone ringing]
- [Ken] Hey!
- [Gypsy] Hey,
what are you doing?
- [Ken] I'm driving. [laughs]
What are you doing?
- [Gypsy] I talked to Ryan,
I just got off the
phone with him.
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
[Gypsy groaning]
- [Gypsy] He wants to meet up.
- [Gypsy] Obviously, I don't
think it's a good idea.
I told him point blank, I
said, "I want a divorce,
and after this six to nine
months, I'm gonna be with Ken."
- [Gypsy] Mm-hmm.
- [Gypsy] He's still like trying
to like work it out with me.
- [Gypsy] Any part of
me that wants to? No.
- [Gypsy] Honestly, no.
- [Gypsy] I know. I trust you.
- [Gypsy] I love
you, too. Be safe.
- [Gypsy] I will. I'll
talk to you soon.
Bye.
Ken has always been in my heart,
and I needed to find out what
it was that I was feeling,
why can't I get,
like, not let go?
And he came to visit me,
so this is the first time
we've been able to see
each other in person.
We had a great weekend.
We went to New Orleans, we
just hung out, got caught up.
The idea of getting
a husky together
has always been like a thing
that we've bonded over.
So when we reconnected,
I was like,
"Let's get matching
husky tattoos." [laughs]
This was my idea. [laughs]
I'm like, "Let's do it!"
I'm like, "This feels
right, this feels good."
For the first time,
I'm like, "Hell yeah!"
Like I'm happy right now,
like this is freaking awesome.
We just create happiness,
where it's almost like
a giddy teenager happy.
Having that taste of what
it could be like with Ken
just solidified my
feelings for him.
The heart wants what it wants,
it's a complicated organ.
[gentle music]
- [Kristy] My keys
are in the car?
- [Gypsy] I think so.
- [Kristy] Well, today's the
big day for her rhinoplasty.
She whispered to me
that she was scared.
- [Gypsy] I wasn't
told when I was a kid,
oh, I'm pretty, my
confidence was nothing.
So, regardless of what the
comments are that come my way,
I wanna go in for the best,
but if the worst happens,
it's not the end of the world.
♪ No one can stop us now
♪ We've made it this far
- [Kristy] To
think of everything
that she went through before,
hundreds of surgeries
that she has gotten
because of her mom, and
this time it's her choice,
it's nobody else but
hers, she's in control.
[upbeat music]
I was proud when she
decided she's doing this.
It's a milestone for her.
♪ This is our moment,
this is our moment ♪
♪ We could feel
it in our bones ♪
♪ There's no letting go
- [Gypsy] I'm like,
getting queasier,
so I just can't think about it.
- [Doctor] You wanna look at it?
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
- [Gypsy] Oh, wow.
- [Kristy] Wow.
- It looks so good.
- [Doctor] So if you feel,
like right here where
your bump used to be,
you'll feel that's
kinda sponge-y.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- [Doctor] And that's important,
'cause you're gonna get the skin
to kinda get where the new level
of the bone and cartilage is.
- [Kristy] Girl.
- [Doctor] You survived.
- [Gypsy] I survived it.
- [Doctor] Yeah, I like
it, I think it's cute.
- [Gypsy] I think it
looks really good.
- [Doctor] So if
you look at your--
- [Gypsy] You did
good work! [laughs]
- [Kristy] Good job.
- [Doctor] If you
look at your old nose.
- [Kristy] Wow.
- [Doctor] You can kinda
see the difference.
- [Kristy] Wow.
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
In the beginning
of me getting out,
I had tried to go through
a physical transformation,
just with like my
hair, my style,
different things about myself.
So I think this is something
a little bit more permanent,
and I like it though,
it's a good choice for me.
- [Doctor] So that's
your before nose.
- [Gypsy] Oh, wow.
It looks great.
- [Doctor] Yeah, I think--
- [Kristy] It does, I'm like,
I can't believe it, that's...
- [Doctor] You did super.
- [Gypsy] I'm happy with
myself going forward,
and I think it's
more internal work
that I need to do on myself.
[clock ticking]
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard's
officially changed her look,
undergoing plastic
surgery on Friday.
The procedure went well,
and Gypsy's super stoked
to see how she looks
after she's totally healed up.
- You absolutely do not
need plastic surgery
Ms Gyp Gyp, you are
beautiful the way you are,
but of course, it seems
like this is something
she's been thinking
about for a while.
- think it's only
a matter of time
before we find out that they
have gotten back together.
[tense music]
- Remember when she
said the D was fire?
I guess it has burnt out.
- [Gypsy] I feel like I did
the right thing on my part
by filing for divorce, like...
Regardless of what is
going on behind the scenes
with me and Ken,
the right thing to
do was acknowledge
that this marriage is not
what I want and not working,
and file based on that.
- [Mia] That's awful to say.
- [Kristy] But--
- [Gypsy] No, it's
really true, though.
- [Kristy] It's the truth.
- [Gypsy] She said
it since day one.
- [Kristy] 'Cause me and
Ken never lost touch.
- [Mia] But see,
that's what makes me--
- [Kristy] No, it was like--
- [Mia] Don't cut me off.
- [Kristy] "Happy birthday,"
and stuff like-- you cut me off.
It was, it got less and less.
Like when they first split.
- [Mia] You played a big
role in their thing, though.
- [Kristy] Well you know, she
needed to know the real reason
why he ended it.
- [Mia] Did she?
- [Kristy] Yes she did, because-
- [Mia] He should've
told her then, not you.
- [Mia] Did she?
- [Kristy] Yes she did, because-
- [Kristy] Ryan
didn't want her--
- [Gypsy] I did block him,
because Ryan wanted me to.
- [Kristy] Right, so--
- [Mia] If you ever came to me
talking about one of my
exes while I'm with Andre,
like married, like that is-
- [Kristy] No, no.
Y'all situation's different.
She needed closure.
And she didn't have it, so I
took it upon myself to do it.
He let her go,
because he wanted her to
find herself without him.
The main reason why he ended
it was not what we thought.
- [Mia] Yeah, I don't know
if I believe that, either.
I still gotta, I
gotta talk to him.
I gotta make my own...
- [Gypsy] And that's something
that I want you to do.
Like, on your own
time, you know.
- [Kristy] I wouldn't
have liked if
Ryan would've dogged Ken
after he knew the real truth.
- [Gypsy] He did.
- [Mia] That is
still not your place.
- [Kristy] Well, I
didn't say it was my,
I said this is my opinion.
- [Mia] And he had every right
to hate Ken and all that.
He has every single right.
- [Kristy] Exactly.
- So let him feel the way he-
- [Mia] Then why are you
saying that you wouldn't
want him talking
about Ken like that?
That is his feelings.
- [Kristy] No, he has
a better understanding--
- [Mia] Oh my gosh.
- [Kristy] Mia, of why.
- [Mia] I'm not gonna,
okay. Conversation done.
Before I get pissed off,
I'm not talking more.
- [Kristy] I just see things
at all different angles
than you, I guess.
- [Mia] No, 'cause you're
saying one thing and then,
I say something else, but
then you agree with me
and it's just flip flop like a-
- [Kristy] I don't agree
with, I'm telling you why
I told her, why I told Gypsy-
- [Gypsy] Y'all have
the worst communication.
- [Mia] She don't know
when to stop talking
and she keeps talking
on and on and on--
- [Kristy] In circles.
- [Mia] And don't even
make sense sometimes.
I'm like, "What are you
even trying to say?"
- [Kristy] Well, I'm just trying
to make the whole thing--
- [Mia] I get, but do
you see my whole point?
You don't like to,
you say "I, I, I."
- [Kristy] I, I, yeah.
Because that's how
I, and I told you,
I, this is my opinion.
- [Mia] All right.
- [Kristy] Not Gypsy's, not
the man in the moon's opinion,
my opinion.
- [Mia] There just
have been many things
from many different angles
that have bothered me.
And I don't know.
Maybe just different
values, different morals,
but I mean, it is what
it is. It's not my life.
- [Kristy] Well, like I said--
- [Gypsy] Normally,
it's not my values, but.
- [Mia] A little different
thing between Ryan and Ken,
for me, is that Ken knew
that Gypsy was still married.
Where's your respect for Ryan?
You may not like the
guy at all, but like,
for me, that says a lot
about your character.
And I don't feel like he
was trying to protect Gypsy
in the best way.
How are you protecting her,
from what these people
are gonna say about her?
How are you protecting her from
what the world is
gonna think of her?
You are not doing
anything, at all.
Y'all are making
irrational decisions
based on short-term
happiness instead of,
you know, thinking long-term.
- [Gypsy] Watching
Mia and Kristy fight,
I'm just like, "Mm-hmm."
People get affected
by my choices.
I get affected by my choices.
But at the end of the
day, I have to also
live with myself and, if nobody
else is gonna make me happy,
I have to do what's
gonna make me happy.
- [Kristy] I don't regret
a thing. You know why?
She's my priority.
I want her to be happy.
I want her to live, bottom line.
[soft music]
- [Ryan] Come on,
Pix. [smooches]
Come on.
Hey.
- [Joy] Who's here?
- [Ryan] Pixie Pix.
- [Joy] Pixie Pix!
- [Ryan] Yeah.
[dogs barking]
- [Joy] Did you sleep
in here last night?
- [Ryan] Yeah. I sleep fine.
I get a text at like
three in the morning,
"Hey, I'm awake. Please
let me know you're okay.
How's our baby doing?"
- [Joy] Oh, now she
wants to know about Pix.
- [Ryan] Now she wants to know
about, "I miss her so much,
how's our baby?"
Stuff like that gives
me hope and it's...
- [Joy] But, I know, Ryan,
but is that healthy?
- [Ryan] Mom, that's
what I'm dealing with.
That's, I have to fight that.
- [Joy] I know, I know.
I know, it's such a
rollercoaster ride.
- [Ryan] Last night, she
told me "I'm selfish,
I'm sorry I'm so selfish."
- [Joy] If she wants to go, go.
But why the continual contact?
- [Ryan] You know, I'm
struggling with that,
I'm wondering how much
longer I can take.
- [Joy] You're gonna know
when you've had enough.
You're gonna know.
But that don't mean there's
not a lot of heartbreak
in between that.
- Yeah.
[soft music]
She got out, we went to
New York and we had this
honeymoon romance in New
York and then we came back
and started living
our regular life.
I think she expected it to stay
that honeymoon perfect phase
like, living carefree.
- [Joy] Do you think
she had that envisioned
in her mind before
she was released,
that that's the way
that life's gonna be?
- [Ryan] Yes.
- [Joy] Well, it's
not like that.
- [Ryan] So when Ken came
to visit, it was a vacation.
It was wonderful,
it was a vacation.
'Cause it was.
- [Joy] Yeah, it was. It was.
- [Ryan] That's not real life.
- [Joy] Mm-mm.
- [Rod] So how was
your time with Ken?
- [Gypsy] It was amazing.
- [Rod] Really?
- [Gypsy] Yeah.
We went to New Orleans and
we did like a swamp tour.
We got Jazz Fest tickets.
- [Rod] Yes.
- [Gypsy] I talked
to Mia about it.
- [Rod] Yeah.
- And she's okay
with him coming.
She copped an attitude with me.
Rightfully so.
'Cause she asked me, she's like,
"Oh, you going to get a tattoo?"
I said, "Yeah, I'm
gonna get a tattoo.
Ken's getting one, too."
She didn't ask me if we were
getting matching tattoos.
So I kind of left that part out.
- [Kristy] Did you show him?
- [Gypsy] No, no, I didn't.
- Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Oh, it is bigger.
- [Gypsy] Yeah, it's a lot
bigger than what I thought.
And then, like his
is the same thing,
but it doesn't have this,
and it doesn't have
the little dots.
- [Kristy] Hers is the girl one.
- [Gypsy] Mine's the girl one.
- [Rod] So they're
not matching tattoos.
- [Gypsy] They're not identical!
[Rod laughing]
- [Rod] At least
it doesn't say Ken.
- [Gypsy] [laughs]
No. It doesn't.
- [Joy] And this tat.
What's up with the tat?
- [Ryan] That was too...
- [Joy] Don't wanna
talk about it. Okay.
- [Ryan] That's one I
don't like talking about.
- [Joy] All right.
- [Ryan] That was a scar that
I probably will never get over.
- [Joy] Probably so.
- [Ryan] That one was
a scar that cut deep.
[pensive music]
- [Rod] I guess we're
moving on to Ken.
I have to start accepting..
- [Kristy] Ken's a good guy.
I like, I've talked to
him a lot more than you.
- [Rod] I'm not saying
he's not a good guy.
- [Kristy] Right, you just,
I mean, she needed to
find out who she was
without anybody else, and the
way a lot of people see it is
what Ryan did was
selfish on his part.
When she finally told me
and I asked her straight up,
I said, "So you didn't
want to come live here
because you were 32 years old
and you thought you
would be a burden?"
She said yeah.
- [Rod] Really?
- [Kristy] Mm-hmm.
That's the reason
why she married him.
Did she wanna love him like
he loved her? Of course.
But when it's not
there, it's not there.
- [Rod] I feel like
a failure now that..
We had all that time
to make her feel like
she had a place to come to and
she still didn't feel that.
- [Kristy] Look, if
you would have said,
"I'm totally against it, no,"
that's what she
wanted you to say.
She was craving that from you.
But you know how you said, like,
"I don't want to
tell her what to do
because that's
what her mom did"?
- [Rod] I'm just thinking
about what you said,
about why she married Ryan.
[Rod sighing]
- [Kristy] It's a
hard pill to swallow.
- [Rod] Well, I mean, I'm gonna
try not to carry any guilt.
And I'm not gonna
tell her no next time
if I don't like it, either.
She's gotta make
her own decisions.
- [Kristy] You're
right. You're right.
- [Rod] I'm not carrying that.
- [Kristy] But I
know, right, exactly.
- [Rod] She might be mad
right now, living here,
"Oh, I should have married Ryan"
if I cracked down and act
like this hard ass daddy.
You know? "No, you gotta
be home by 10 o'clock."
- [Kristy] Rod, we wouldn't
have told her that, though.
We wouldn't have told her she
had to be home by 10 o'clock.
- [Rod] Well--
- [Kristy] What the
hell you talking about?
- [Rod] That's the kind
of daddy that is, though.
The kind that says, "No,
you can't get married,"
is the kind of daddy
that says, "No,
you gotta be home
by 10 o'clock."
- No, no, no.
- I'm not that person.
- [Kristy] I know
you're not that person.
Don't get mad at me!
- [Rod] I'm not,
I'm just saying.
- [Kristy] No, dude,
bro, let me tell you.
You take that anger out
on his ass over there
in Lake Charles and not on me.
I saw your face, I saw
your reaction. I know.
- [Rod] I'm just
making a point. Sorry.
- [Kristy] Now you're
freaking pissed.
And it's okay, but
don't get mad at--
No, uh-uh, you throw that
attitude somewheres else.
- You know, I feel guilty
that I didn't tell her no.
'Cause I really didn't,
I really felt like
it wasn't gonna work.
It was just the
dynamics of her being,
you know, controlled
all her life
and getting out and being free.
I mean, I don't know if it
would have worked with Ken
when she comes out, you know?
So, I need to let her make that
choice and we'll deal with,
I'm not gonna say I
haven't learned from it,
I think I can probably be
a little bit more honest
with her now, you know.
So I have some daddy issues
that I have to deal with myself.
[pensive music]
[phone ringing]
- [Gypsy] Hey.
- [Ken] Hey, how's it going?
- [Gypsy] I'm good.
Where you at?
- [Gypsy] Okay, that's not bad.
That'll be here in no time.
How are you feeling?
- [Gypsy] I been tracking you.
- [Gypsy] Mm-hmm.
- [Gypsy] And stalking you.
[light music]
- [Gypsy] This weekend,
Dad, Kristy, me, and Ken
are all gonna go to Jazz Fest.
And we're just gonna have
like a really nice weekend,
I'm very excited.
I haven't seen him since
probably about three weeks ago.
[laughs] All right,
well, drive safe.
- [Gypsy] Love you. Bye.
My hope is that Ken and I will
have that fairytale dream life
that we always wanted
to have with each other.
But I'm only planning
as far as a week.
You know, 'cause
that's all you can do.
'Cause things always change.
He's on 21st.
- [Kristy] He's right there.
Why?
- [Gypsy] I'm not
nervous, I just--
- [Kristy] Nervous excited?
- [Gypsy] Nervous excited.
- [Rod] I'm kinda struggling
with how I'm gonna
handle this whole Ken scenario
now that it's a thing.
You know, he broke her heart.
And I really never had
any closure with that,
I never talked to him about it.
The relationship
I have with Gypsy,
you know, I'm walking
a line with her,
I don't wanna be too
pushy, but be supportive
and you know, provide her
with some good advice,
which I'm learning to do that.
- [Gypsy] This would be the
first time my dad has seen Ken
since 2019.
My dad has always expressed that
it's not that he
doesn't like Ken,
it's he didn't like
how Ken broke my heart.
I think Ken's headspace
is trying to get back
in my dad's good graces.
Trying to make up for that
bridge that was kind of burned.
[tense music]
- [Kristy] There he is.
I wanna see Parker.
Where's Parker?
- [Gypsy] Hey!
- [Ken] Hey, you.
[Gypsy squealing]
[dog barking]
[smooches] Good to see you.
- [Gypsy] You too.
- [Ken] Let me get
Parker real quick.
- [Kristy] Yeah, get
Parker. I want Parker.
- [Gypsy] Hey, buddy!
- [Ken] Come on out, buddy.
- Hey, buddy.
- [Kristy] Parker!
- [Gypsy] Miss me?
Parker, Parker!
He's like, "Where's Jas?"
- [Kristy] What you doing? Huh?
You wanna know who loves
me? Parker loves me.
- [Ken] Yeah, he missed you.
Hey, Kristy.
- [Kristy] Hey.
- [Ken] I like your
hair. Looks good.
- [Kristy] Thank
you. You smell good.
- [Ken] Oh, thanks.
How's it going, Rod?
- [Gypsy] Oh, you're already
shedding all over me.
- [Kristy] That's why I
have the lint roller.
- [Gypsy] I made the mistake
of wearing these pants.
[Ken chuckling]
(bleep).
I'm gonna sit on you.
- [Ken] Okay, come here.
- [Rod] You did good.
- [Ken] Yeah.
- [Rod] Just an hour late.
- [Gypsy] You're wearing
the cologne, I can tell.
- [Ken] I got it for you.
- [Rod] Okay, well,
while we're all here,
I got a few things I wanna say.
- [Gypsy] Oh, boy.
- [Ken] Okay.
- [Rod] First of all,
thanks for coming.
Right?
- [Ken] Thanks for having me.
- [Rod] I could tell
last couple weeks
how happy Gypsy's been.
Kristy brought
something up to me,
saying I wasn't telling Gypsy
how I felt on everything,
you asked about marrying Ryan.
I may not have been
completely honest with you.
I wanted to let you make
that decision on your own.
I didn't want to make you feel
like I was controlling you,
you know?
You made a mistake, I made a
mistake. We're gonna move on.
And we're gonna be
proud of it. Okay?
Ken.
You broke her heart once. Right?
That scares me a
little bit still.
And I hope that
doesn't happen again.
Gypsy, I want you to know,
you married Ryan, that's
just a piece of paper, baby.
I don't want you to
hide if you're in love.
If y'all are in love--
- [Kristy] Show it.
- [Rod] That's the best
feeling in the world.
You were controlled your
life, baby, your whole life.
Don't hide your feelings
anymore, be you. Okay?
You know, your whole
life was based on lies.
Let's start this off right.
If you're in love,
tell the world.
"I love Ken.
So what, I got married.
I made a mistake," baby.
And I'm not worried
about how it looks
to the other people.
The biggest thing you lose
is some respect from me,
your mom, your sister, your mom.
You know, that integrity
is what matters.
Oh, and the last
thing I wanted to say.
She wants a baby.
- [Gypsy] What?!
- [Rod] I can tell, bro.
[Kristy laughing]
- [Gypsy] What?
Where did this come from?
- [Kristy] I don't know.
- [Rod] I'm gonna tell both
of y'all, just wait. Okay?
Make sure y'all give y'all
relationship a chance
to develop without
the stress of--
- [Kristy] Well, one baby.
- [Rod] Additional burden, okay?
- [Gypsy] We'll have babies--
- [Rod] I mean, I
want a baby, too.
You know, I'm not gonna lie.
I want a little
grandkid, but you know,
I don't want to be raising one.
[laughing]
- [Kristy] We want it
where it can go back home.
[Gypsy laughing]
- [Rod] Please, please.
I'm gonna be really
disappointed.
- [Ken] No, I 100%
agree with you on that.
It's definitely, you know.
- [Kristy] Y'all enjoy each
other first and foremost.
- [Ken] In time.
- [Gypsy] Lots of time.
[tense music]
So it is the end of May
and I am late on my period.
So I texted Ken and I'm
like joking with him,
I'm like "Well, I guess
you've been spared
my PMS for the month, 'cause
I guess I'm not gonna,
I skipped a period."
So he's like, "Or, maybe..."
And I'm like, "No,"
like, [scoffs].
And he's like, he gave me
like the big eye emoji.
I'll go and take a test.
So I go in the bathroom,
I take the test.
And it came back positive.
[pensive music]
- [exhales] Okay.
I'm breathing.
My first thought is "My dad's
gonna kill me!" [laughs]
'Cause he had just said, like,
"I know you want a baby,
but I would prefer
you guys wait."
Yep, two positive tests.
Not just one, two.
- Oh, he was happy, like
he had to take a moment,
like he took an hour, we
had a good FaceTime call,
he was excited, all smiles.
And then like he had
to process for an hour.
And then he calls me
back and he starts like,
he's happy crying and I'm like,
"Aw, I've never heard you
like cry before." [laughs]
I've been having
a lot of anxiety.
Because it's like,
I wanna make sure I'm
doing everything right.
There's too many what-ifs
and I can't go into
that rabbit hole.
[pensive music]
How have I changed in
the last seven years?
- [Ken] You're more transparent.
- [Gypsy] Mm-hmm.
- I mean, you're still
the same impulsive,
like do what you want type
person, it's a good thing.
- [Gypsy] Are you gonna
remind yourself of that
when things get hard?
- [Ken] How much more
rough could it get?
- Rough.
- Okay.
We'll figure it out.
- [Gypsy] All right,
are we done? [laughs]
[Ken and Gypsy laughing]
- [Ken] Everything's
gonna be just fine, okay?
[tense music]
- [Producer] Did she tell
you? What was it like?
Can you give me a
little snapshot?
- [Ryan] [sighs] I mean, I
don't know what to think.
You know, a month before,
right after she left,
Gypsy texted me a bunch
of pregnancy tests
and said she was pregnant.
Okay, well, who's the father?
It could have been me
or Ken at that point.
So, she didn't know.
She was like, "I don't know."
The previous month, she sent
me pictures of pregnancy tests.
But this time,
there's no pictures.
No proof, so like, I don't
know what to believe.
Like, it's one of those I don't
believe it, I still don't.
You know, it's hard for me
to wrap my head around that.
Like, secretly Gypsy and me
were trying to get pregnant.
Well, Gypsy always
wanted to be pregnant.
It's so confusing. Such
a confusing time for me.
Like, my world's in turmoil.
- [Producer] What
happens next, for you?
- [Ryan] I have no idea.
My mind is mush a lot and Gypsy
said the same thing to me.
She doesn't know up
from down sometimes.
But like, we always
had each other.
Gypsy's always come back to me.
You know, I mean, I
do love her enough to
want her to be
happy, but you know,
is she that happy?
I mean, if she still contacts
me, is she that happy?
[pensive music]
- [Gypsy] I'm scared that I
bring a certain level of drama
to his life that I
don't mean to bring.
It just, it's like my baggage.
He could leave me right now,
and it's completely
out of my control.
And that's scary, it
was scary back then
and it's still scary now.
But he has my heart, and
I can't control that.
- Yeah.
I mean, I trust
that he loves me,
I trust that I love him,
but that fear is there.
And right now, I just
think I'm happy again.
And I don't wanna do
anything to mess it up.