[dramatic music]
- [Reporter] Startling
new developments
in an already bizarre
murder case in Springfield.
- [Reporter 1] 24-year-old
Gypsy Blanchard admitted
to killing her mother,
Dee Dee Blanchard.
- [Reporter 2] Gypsy shocking
many of those who knew her
because she was not
using a wheelchair.
It is a twisted story.
- [Reporter 3] Experts
say she's the victim
of Munchhausen by Proxy Syndrome
and suffered at the
hands of her mother.
- [Gypsy] From a very young
age, my mother had claimed
that I had seizure disorders,
hearing impairment.
I was forced to
use a wheelchair.
As I got older, she
started shaving my hair off
and telling people
that I had cancer.
- [Kristy] Gypsy
was Dee's daughter,
but also her prisoner.
- [Gypsy] Doctors
is what I knew,
hospitals is what I knew,
surgeries is what I knew.
I wanted that life that
I was living to be over.
- [Rod] I was gone a lot,
I wasn't the best dad.
I shoulda went and checked,
and I had suspicions.
One of the bigger regrets I have
is not making her feel
that she could come to me.
- [Gypsy] I met this
guy, Nick, online.
I thought that he could be the
one that would take me away
from this existence
living with my mother.
He starts talking to me about
how he would kill
my mother for me.
He arrives at the house,
I get down on the ground,
and I hear screaming,
and that's when I
hear her call my name.
And she's like,
"Gypsy, help me."
And to this day, I can't
get that out of my head.
- [Mike] What in
the world happened?
You know, we didn't
know what to think.
- [Kristy] Oh, if I
could go back in time,
I would rewrite the script.
- [Mike] While, yes, she
was involved in the murder,
she just went from
one prison to another.
- [Reporter] Gypsy pleaded
guilty to second degree murder,
she was sentenced
to 10 years in jail.
- [Gypsy] Since my
incarceration, I am finally free
to build relationships
and friendships.
And I have been
keeping a secret.
I am engaged!
[chuckles]
- [Ryan] Her story,
you know, just hit me.
And I thought,
"Gosh, she's cute."
- [Mia] Fan boying huh?
- Well, yeah, well,
yeah, at that point,
yeah, at that point
I guess I was.
- I wish they would
wait a little bit.
- [Kristy] Why now?
Why rush?
- [Reporter] Gypsy Rose
reportedly married a man
named Ryan Scott Anderson
in 2022 while in prison.
- [Gypsy] He calms,
almost like a storm
that's inside my soul.
- Gypsy Blanchard
will be set free.
- [Reporter] The
Department of Corrections
granted her early release.
- Gypsy Blanchard says
she's ready to go home
to Louisiana with her husband.
- [Gypsy] I feel like
the Gypsy Blanchard
that entered this institution
has been through a
great deal in her life
but has overcome a lot.
- [Mia] When she gets
in the real world,
she don't know
what it's like yet.
- But wouldn't you prefer
her have somebody to lean on?
- [Mia] Yeah, but she has us.
- [Kristy] There will
be bumps in the road,
but that's what
she has family for.
- I just want her to be happy,
that's all I really care about.
- [Gypsy] I want to
live a simple life
that everybody else
takes for granted.
I don't wanna be
remembered as the girl
who killed her mother
who
was abused by her mother.
I want this to be,
okay, you know my story.
Alright, now let's see
what I do with my life.
[suspenseful music]
[clock ticking]
- Missouri's most
famous prisoners
will be released tomorrow.
Gypsy Blanchard
will be set free.
- The state granted
her request for parole.
- She served eight years
for the murder of
her abusive mother.
- [Reporter] Her case has
been turned into documentaries
and a TV series, some even see
Gypsy Rose as a
sympathetic hero.
- [Reporter 1] Now the
32 year-old Blanchard
moving forward with
the world watching.
- [Reporter 2] Whether you
look at Twitter, X or Facebook,
even TikTok, it's
trending everywhere.
- Tomorrow she is
getting released.
Wonder if she'll get TikTok.
- This woman is iconic,
like she's a legend.
- This is insane, like
Gypsy Rose Blanchard
is getting out of prison.
[ominous music]
[wind blowing]
[locks clicking]
- Hi.
I'm a little nervous.
- [giggles]
- I don't know, I just
always get nervous.
It's like little jitters.
- [laughs] I know, it's so nice.
- I feel like ever
since my case was
all over the media,
all over the news,
people have been on
this journey with me.
And I think that I've outgrown
this prison version of
myself that I think a lot
of people have come
to associate me with.
I wanna be Gypsy Rose Blanchard,
a survivor,
an advocate for
people that have been
through what I
have been through.
And I wanna be someone that
my family could be proud of.
[uplifting guitar music]
- [Ryan] Oh, you decorating
the tree, I like it.
- I like a lot of
lights, a lot of lights.
- [Ryan] Do you?
- Oh yeah. [whispering]
- What's her favorite
kind of cake?
- White icing with buttercream.
- What do y'all want on it?
- Umm...
- Like on, like
letters on the cake?
- Yeah, like a saying.
- [Mia] We're not gonna have
a plain white cake.
- Yeah, just say,
"Welcome home Gypsy Rose."
or have like couple roses on it.
- I'm overwhelmed.
Yesterday I was
saying, you know,
"Eight years left,"
and now it's here.
[melancholy music]
Countdown her last night there.
Tomorrow night
she'll be with us.
- [Ryan] You need any help
dad, you need anything?
- [Rod] No, I'm good right now.
Everybody keeps asking me,
you know, "What you think,
"how it's gonna go, you know,
are they gonna last or not?"
And I mean, this is
a whole new chapter.
Everything's new and she's
got stuff to look forward to.
You know, you have
to make mistakes
and learn from them, you know,
and everybody could tell
her how they feel, and
but, at the end of the day,
she's still gonna make her
choice and that's what she
did through this you know,
deciding to get married
in prison and everything.
And I wanted her to
make that choice.
And I want her to like
have to live with it
and learn from that.
- [Ryan] Oh man, smells good.
Marrying Gypsy wasn't easy.
Of course, I asked for his
approval and he gave it to me.
But you know, you never know
if you truly get that approval.
It just smells better
and better in here
each time I come, you know.
Right now I just
want this to work.
You know, everybody's giving
us a 50 50 shot, you know?
But I feel it's 100 percent.
Can you believe this
day's actually here?
- [Rod] I know it, bro.
- Isn't it crazy?
I mean, I've only
waited three years.
Y'all been waiting
eight and a half.
- I know.
- Part of me like has to
put that in perspective,
y'all been waiting so long
and I come in and
I go pick her up.
- [Rod] Yeah.
I ain't gonna lie, I'm jealous
bro but that's all good.
[bacon sizzling]
- [Ryan] And I'm the lucky
one that gets to pick her up.
A lot of people wanted
that honor, I got it.
I don't know how, I
pinch myself sometimes.
- [Rod] I'm going to
tell you this though.
- [Ryan] What's that boss?
You pick her up and y'all do
some crazy [bleep],
I got a lot of guns.
[ominous music]
- It is hot in here.
It is so hot, man.
- [Gypsy] What makes Ryan
like so different from my exes
is because I think with
my exes, they were in love
with the idea of me rather
than they were in love with me.
They were so hyped up
to wanna get to know
the Gypsy Blanchard they
saw on the TV screen.
And when I showed
that I'm human,
I'm not a character,
I have flaws
because
the level of emotional baggage
that I carry,
I put that so deep inside
that the only person
that gets to see that
is my significant other.
And I kind of feel like
everyone else ran and he didn't.
- [Ryan] [nervous sigh]
I'm super excited,
super nervous,
but in a good nervous,
like it's ready
for, it's actually
happening, you know.
I didn't think this
day would come.
I always talked about
it and, you know,
I remember when a year happened
and I just made a
countdown clock on my phone
and little by
little I'd check it
and be like, "Okay,
250 days, 100 days."
Then when it got to
like 30, I was like,
"Baby, we're at 30 days,"
like that month flew by too.
So I think the countdown
clock says two days.
So one day,
it's crazy, it's crazy.
[gentle music]
- [Mia] I like Ryan, I do,
nice guy, you know, respectful.
But until I see them
interact one-on-one together,
I think I will be skeptical
of the whole situation
until I see it for myself.
I don't want
anything to hurt her.
But I'm happy if she's
happy and I'll support
whatever decision
she wants to make,
I'm there 100 percent,
I'll always be there.
How old are you?
- [Ryan] 37.
- [Mia] Wait, your birthday's?
- June.
- [Mia] June too?
- What day in June?
- [Mia] 25th.
- I'm 23rd right on,
you're a cancer too, right on.
- Oh really?
I didn't know that.
- And we gonna get
along just fine.
- [Kristy] Gypsy and I, over
the years, have created a bond
and, you know, she felt
comfortable calling me mom.
And like I told her the
first time we went to court,
she thought after
we heard everything
that we were gonna leave.
And I do not condone what
she did but I understood.
And I put my hand on that glass
and she put her
hand and I'm like,
"You know, I will
never leave your side,"
because that's what moms do.
We protect,
we love,
we love hard,
we protect harder
but also
the bond.
- [Ryan] Alright, party people.
- [Kristy] Heading out?
- [Ryan] I gotta go.
- [Kristy] Be careful.
- Alright, next
time y'all see me,
I will have ole girl with me.
- Go get her brother.
- I will, Dad.
I love you man.
- [Rod] I love you brother.
- Alright guys, love y'all.
- [Kristy] Love you too baby.
Be careful.
- Always.
- [Kristy] Try to get
some sleep tonight.
- [Mia] Yeah.
- I will.
I'm gonna do the best I can.
- So much, honestly, you know.
Just neglect, general
neglect, you know.
I mean I could have
done so much more,
dug in a little
deeper, you know.
I think there's some
reconciling that we have to do.
I think we probably both have
questions for each other.
But we need to start
it on a good foundation
where we can be
honest, you know,
of how we failed in the past,
things we've done wrong.
Could start something
fresh from there knowing
where we stand with
each other, you know,
we got a long way
to go, I know that.
You know, it's a gonna be
a tough balance, you know?
[upbeat music]
- [Ryan] Hey baby.
- [Ryan] Are you?
- [Ryan] Well baby, you
know, you gotta think
this is your last day in prison.
- [Ryan] They just asked me
what we plan to do tonight
and I said, "love
on you, sleep."
- [Gypsy] [chuckling]
- [Ryan] Baby, I wanna say
this is the prison calling me.
Can you hold on a second?
- Hang on.
This is Ryan.
- [Ryan] Yeah, hey,
what's up Major?
- No sir, I haven't had
any, anything that's
out of the ordinary.
- Yeah, what time you thinking?
- [Ryan] Okay.
- Absolutely,
absolutely, like I said,
just gimme a call,
I'll be in town.
- All right brother. Bye.
- The prison, he was just
double checking where I was at.
I tried to get him to tell me
the exact time and
he would not do it.
Damn, he wouldn't gimme a time.
- [Ryan] No, I haven't
baby, but I will.
- [Ryan] I love you too.
Bye baby.
That's Gypsy Rose.
[gentle guitar music]
She's so good.
I love her.
That's my wife.
Really, man, I'm not even
gonna lie, I'm so nervous.
I get to finally
have my wife home.
Still, gonna be different,
her being at home,
it's a new ball game,
but I'm ready for
it, I've been ready.
[gentle music]
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard,
the most famous victim
of Munchausen by
Proxy is going to be
paroled tomorrow,
December 28th.
- This has been
very controversial.
Some people believe that
she should not have gotten
any time, some people believe
she should have
gotten more time.
- You guys, I
cannot stop thinking
about Gypsy Rose Blanchard
getting out of prison.
[upbeat rock music]
- Gypsy says that she's bracing
herself for the spotlight
and scrutiny she's
going to come home to,
but that she's looking
forward to spending time
with her father
and her stepmother,
and her new husband, Ryan.
[gentle music]
- [Ryan] That's her ring.
Family heirloom.
My mom gave me that for my
wife and this is Gypsy's.
I know she wanted that the
moment we got there, so.
I've been waiting for
this day for three years.
It's finally here.
Nerves are just.
[popping noise]
Oh, there he is.
This is Ryan.
- I'm good man, how you doing?
- [Ryan] I can do that.
- Yeah, I can do that. I'll be
there at 3:15.
Thank you buddy.
- [Prison Major] You need
something holler. Thank you bye.
- Alright, bye.
Alright.
Alright Ryan, moment of truth.
[tense music]
I am so nervous. Excited though.
I'll spray my cologne
on. She loves my cologne.
Put her in the mood.
Alright, all done
[tense guitar music]
- [Prison Radio] 3 point
31-901, for a message.
- How you doing buddy?
- Hey man, stressful.
- Yes sir.
- [Ryan] Okay.
- [Security] Alright?
- [Ryan] Alright thank you sir.
- Yeah.
- Ah.
Yeah.
[signal beeping]
- [Ryan] Yeah I got you boss.
There you go.
[radio static]
- [Security] David.
- [Radio] 10-17 out of the hall.
- [Ryan] Yes sir.
[door slams]
So how's she doing? She nervous?
- [Ryan] Good.
[suspenseful music]
[doors clangs closed]
- [Ryan] The boots don't fit?
- [Ryan] Oh no.
- [Gypsy] Oh my God.
- [Gypsy] Thank you.
- [Ryan] Hey, thank you.
- [Gypsy] [chuckles]
[kiss sound]
- [Ryan] I love you.
- [Gypsy] I love
you. I'm ready to go.
- [Ryan] You look so good.
You look so good.
[Gypsy chuckles]
You are so sexy.
- [Gypsy] Oh my God. The
car is moving. Oh my God.
- [Ryan] Yeah, baby, we're out.
- [Gypsy] Oh my God
I did not sleep.
[camera beeping]
- [Ryan] You didn't sleep?
- I did not sleep. I was
like trying to be awake.
- You look so good
in regular clothes.
- I know. I just wish that
it fit a little better.
I'm like trying not
to show too much boob.
- [Ryan] Oh, it's hot.
- [laughs loudly]
- It's so hot.
- Oh, it so feels so
weird being in a car.
- [Ryan] Yeah, I get
to touch your leg.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, I missed you.
- I missed you too.
[upbeat music]
This all just feels like
so surreal right now.
Like, I don't even know
how to feel right now.
Woo.
- [Ryan] You're free.
- [chuckles] I'm free.
Woo. This car is
going really fast.
♪ Every moment
♪ Led me to this one
♪ Could I shine
through the dark ♪
♪ Shine through the dark
[gypsy chuckling]
- [Ryan] Here, gimme your hand.
♪ Oh, I feel like my
blood rushing ♪
- [Ryan] I can't stop smiling.
- [Gypsy] This whole scenery.
- Got your ring in my pocket.
- Oh, get it, get it.
- You want it?
See a moment at
truth, see if it fits?
- [chuckles]
Oh, it's so pretty.
- [Ryan] Isn't it nice?
- Oh, he did shine
it up really good.
And it fits
perfectly. [chuckles]
- Does it?
Yes! Look at that.
Gimme another kiss.
- It fits perfect.
Don't wreck.
- [Ryan] Now Kristy
wanted us to call them.
- Oh my goodness,
this is all so.
- [Ryan] It's surreal, right?
- It's crazy.
It's all kind of
hitting like at once.
Oh, you're calling
her right now?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Hey!
[indistinct chatter]
- It's, it's feeling a
little surreal right now.
- I know.
- [Ryan] We're going
straight to the hotel.
- So, we should be alright.
- Yeah, we're gonna try.
Well, I just wanted
y'all to say hey.
- I love y'all.
- I love you guys.
- Okay, see you soon.
- Bye guys.
[chuckles]
- [Ryan] They gots to go.
It's my time with my wife.
- Oh [chuckles].
[gentle chime music]
- Alright babe,
come on, let's roll.
You look so good.
- You just can't
stop staring at me.
- I can't.
You want some fries?
- Um no.
- You don't?
- No, I just want
- Want me?
to just be right now.
- Alright, you want
me to leave you be?
- No, I don't want you to leave.
I just trying to process.
- [Ryan] Okay. Okay.
Well baby, I got chips.
I got fries. I got
whatever you want.
- We don't get fries in there.
- [Ryan] Well, look, taste
'em before I warm 'em up
because they might
still be alright.
- Trust me. I'm sure
they will be amazing.
- So don't need to warm 'em up.
- They are so good. [laughs]
- I will take a couple.
- Okay.
- [Ryan] They taste alright?
- Mmm-hmm.
Not bad for three
in the morning.
- [Ryan] [laughs].
I've never been able to
feel this part of your arm.
So it's new to me.
- [laughs] It's different.
- Yeah, it's a different feel.
I know.
- You are gonna get to see
me in all my quirky glory.
- Well, good. That's what I've
been waiting for, sweetheart.
I've been waiting for
that for three years.
- What if I snore?
- Well then we gotta get
a divorce right away.
[laughs]
- [laughs] I mean, what do
you think? What if you snore?
- I don't know.
Because none of my roommates
ever said you snore.
- I'm gonna get get you a
sleep apnea mask and
then we'll really.
[laughs loudly]
- Nope.
- I know. You don't need that.
I thought moment I said that.
I thought,
I'm not your mother.
- No. No. I mean I know.
Look at you vaping, like what?
- Tastes so good. You
didn't taste this one.
- Alright, let me
try it one time.
- [Ryan] Cherry peach Lemonade.
Don't hit it too hard.
- [Gypsy] [coughs]
It's just a little
harsh. [coughs]
Damn.
- It's harsh at first.
- It's so harsh. Ugh.
- I'm sorry baby.
That was harsh.
- Oh, it's okay.
- [Ryan] Are you getting sleepy.
- [Gypsy] Little bit.
This bed feel so comfortable.
- You the one that
feels comfortable.
- Just wanna lay
in it for a second.
- Lay down.
- Yeah. That feels nice.
- That feel good?
I just wanna hold you.
I missed you.
- I was cold all night,
but I'm not cold anymore.
- You not? Look, I
can actually rub up.
- [laughs] No one's
telling you don't do that.
- That's so hot. I'm
actually love on you now.
[guitar strings]
[clock ticking]
- Am I the only one that woke
up looking for live footage
of Gypsy Rose being released?
What the heck?
Where's the live footage?
- Gypsy Rose Blanchard
is now a free woman.
She has just been released
from prison in apparently
a very secretive way.
[dramatic music]
- We don't know where she
is or what she's doing,
but it should stay that way
until she decides to share.
- [Ryan] Alright, baby.
- [Gypsy] Did I show
you my first selfie?
That's first selfie.
- Oh.
Fine as ever.
- [Gypsy] [giggles]
It looks good?
- [Ryan] Yeah.
Looks really good.
- [Gypsy] How do you
text people back?
- [Ryan] Alright, so
you click on messages.
- Okay.
- [Ryan] And you text the person
and well, you'll
learn sweetheart.
- Wow, it's even got
like smart thingies
where I said we're
just leaving the,
and it says house,
office, airport.
Creepy.
- It is so cute. How you don't
know that stuff. Gimme kiss.
So cute.
- This is my first cell phone.
- [Ryan] I know. It is adorable.
- [Gypsy] So once
we get out of town,
I'm gonna wear these
boots that don't fit.
- [Ryan] Right, I gotta.
- To get out into the car.
- [Ryan] Yep.
- And then we're gonna
go find somewhere
where we can get some
shoes that do fit.
- Oh, last night
was great. Great.
We got to, yeah, we got
to love on each other.
- We got to consummate
our marriage.
- [Ryan] We did get to do
that. She was so nervous.
- [Gypsy] Not for
long. [laughs loudly]
- [Ryan] Not for
long. She got into it.
- [laughs]
- [Ryan] No, it was great.
- That's all the
details y'all get.
- [Ryan] It was great, I
married the right woman.
Let tell you that
- [Gypsy] He always use to say
'I'm a dynamo'.
And I'm like, every
guy says that.
No, he's a dynamo.
- Y'all heard that?
[clicking noises]
- Oh my God.
- It's cold.
Alright back seat.
Woo it's cold.
[upbeat music]
- Where's my brush? My
hair looks like [bleep].
- It's fine.
- [Ryan] Alright,
we're rolling out.
- [Gypsy] Alright.
Whew okay now,
long car ride.
[upbeat music]
So this is Chillicothe.
This is where I've been
living this whole time.
- [Ryan] Yep.
Oh, I love your glasses.
- [Gypsy] I know
they are adorable.
Yeah, okay, I can see
a little better though.
- How was it being in
the room by yourself?
- When you went
to take a shower?
- [Ryan] Yeah.
- I was putting on my makeup
and it was really nice.
It was just kind of.
- [Ryan] It's just
nice being a alone.
- It was just nice kind
of doing my own thing.
- Yeah, that's what
I'm what I'm saying.
- It's just a whole
different feel to life.
[gentle guitar]
- [Rod] Oh, hey.
- [Corrine] How are you?
- Good.
- [Corrine] Good.
- Better than I've
ever been, I guess.
- [Kristy] Oh God, Mike.
- What's up buddy?
How you doing?
- [Mike] Good.
How are you doing?
- Good man.
- [Mike] I've been doing this
for sixteen and a half years.
I've handled probably
over four thousand cases.
There's really never
been one like this.
It was extremely hard
for me to accept that
her going to prison was going
to have to be an outcome.
This is the final chapter of
what I worked so hard on.
And what I really hoped
would be the outcome
for Gypsy is she finally
gets to come home to her dad,
to her stepmom, and she
gets to live a normal life.
- I don't know what
y'all have planned today,
but y'all, could even
sleep on this. [laughs]
I mean.
- We're here.
- [Corrine] Yeah, that's what
we had planned.
- [Mike] Yep.
- [Rod] Awesome.
- It's too important.
- Broadway Shoes. There we go.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
Okay, I gotta walk
in these things.
- [Ryan] Baby,
just for a minute.
- Alright.
Oh it's cold.
- Ah.
- Thanks.
- [Ryan] Welcome
sweetheart.
[trunk lid clunks]
You're covered.
[chuckles]
- [Gypsy] [laughs]
- I'm huge.
- [Gypsy] It's warm.
- [Ryan] Alright.
- [Gypsy] All right,
hold my hand.
- Come on baby.
- [Gypsy] I'm trying to
not walk extremely fast
so I don't trip and die.
- [Ryan] Who is that?
People we don't know.
[tense music]
- [Man] Where we
going? Where you going?
[tense music]
[Gypsy speaks indistinctly]
- It was fun.
- Bought these new shoes.
- Lots of them.
- Nope.
[car doors thud]
- What the hell? Who was that?
- You see him? He's
in the car right now.
Like, I just don't
want these [bleep]
to know where we're going.
[suspenseful music]
We're, we're being followed.
Can't we like call the police?
- [Gypsy] Ugh.
[engine revving]
- [Ryan] Damn I just want to go.
- Don't crash.
- [Gypsy] Hey dad,
we're being followed
by media right now,
but we don't know what to do.
So, what happens if
they're gonna show up,
they follow us to the
Airbnb? What are we gonna do?
- [Rod] I would say
just come here darling.
- [Mike] Yep.
- Just come here.
Y'all can park in the garage.
- [Gypsy] Alright.
- [Rod] And we'll just
close the curtains. I mean.
- We'll deal with it.
- [Rod] We won't let 'em come on
the property or anything.
- [Gypsy] Alright.
- Alright, will do, I think
we're about 30 minutes out.
- Well, can't wait
to see you, darling.
- [Gypsy] I know. I love you.
See you soon. Bye.
- [Ryan] That's
just crazy, baby.
They must have been
on us the whole time.
- Maybe. Maybe they knew
what hotel we were in.
[clocking ticking]
[clock ticking]
- We now have the
details of Gypsy Rose
Blanchard's prison release
and the first pictures of
her since she's been freed.
- And as she was
leaving, people noticed
that she did not
have on any shoes.
- Literally this picture
of her bag went viral
because people
were talking about
and debating every single
item that she had in this bag.
- Buying new shoes, Gypsy was
asked if she had any plans.
And she responded.
- Lots of them.
- And she's already
planned her first outing.
She's going to be going
apparently to a Chief's game
and hoping to meet Taylor Swift.
- Even though she knows
Taylor may not be there
because of her tour schedule,
she's still going
to the Chiefs game
because apparently she's a
big football fan.
- All we can hope is
that Gypsy is happy
and able to live her best life.
- Look, you see
that right there?
- Oh, okay.
- That white car.
- Okay, that white
utility looking truck.
- [Ryan] Yeah.
- Hope, okay, he's going
the other way, so hopefully.
- No he's not, he's right there.
- Oh, nevermind.
- [Ryan] Just pulled
in behind him.
I hope he didn't get my number.
- [Gypsy] I don't
know how that works.
- [Ryan] I got a voicemail.
Let's see who this
voicemail is from.
- Alright, I better call him.
- [Ryan] Here you go.
- Yeah.
- We'll call 'em right now.
- Alright.
- [Officer] Interstate this is.
- Hi, this is Gypsy Blanchard.
- Umm...
- Umm, is...
- Ah, I...
- Yes, that is correct.
I had pre-okayed that with
my parole officer way before
and I haven't gotten
to give him a call yet
because I got released at like
three o'clock in the morning.
So I was waiting
for a decent hour
and right now we're
headed to Kansas City.
- To meet her family,
- To meet up with my family.
Like I discussed
with the IPO in Chillicothe
Correctional Center.
And so I was just getting ready
to call my PO so I can kind
of know what my
reporting directives are.
- No they don't.
- Uh-huh.
- Drive.
- Our plan was we were gonna,
- Our plan was already set.
- Our plan was already set
to stay a few days
in Kansas City.
- Yeah with our P.O.
- Shh!
And with my parole
officer's permission.
He said that that's fine.
And to report to him in
Louisiana after the holiday.
- Yes.
- Yes, he does.
- On New Year's Day.
- The 1st.
- Okay.
- Okay. That sounds
good. I will do that.
- Okay, that sounds
good. I'm sorry
for the miscommunication,
you know?
- Okay, thank you.
- [Officer] Okay,
thank you ma'am.
- [Gypsy] Okay, bye-bye.
- [Officer] Bye-bye.
[phone beeps]
- Jesus.
- [Ryan] They need to chill.
Like you need to go
to Louisiana now.
- I'm like, we've
already, clarified.
- No we've cleared
this [bleep] so...
[traffic whoosh]
[gentle music]
- Well ,I mean, what are your
thoughts on the Chief's game?
The media portraying it as
you know, she's going there
to meet Taylor Swift.
- Right.
It could be bad.
- [Mia] I don't like it.
- [Rod] Considering her past
meeting all the celebrities
and using her illness to get
her to meet all these people.
- [Corrine] Right. That's what
her mom trained her to do.
- [Rod] After the murder,
they found a bunch of receipts
and stuff from
charitable foundations,
from some country music singers,
like some checks and things.
That's resurfacing
some of that mentality.
- Exactly.
- And something her mom
used to get her to those
celebrities, and now.
- [Corrine] Right.
- I just don't wanna
see that fester in her.
- [Mia] I don't think it
was a smart idea at all.
But at the same time, I
feel like she's just ready
to do whatever she wants to
do without anybody telling her
what she can and can't do.
And she wants to experience
and that's what she's doing.
And it's not like she's
gonna really listen to us.
She's gonna do whatever
she wants regardless, but.
- [Mike] And then you've
got Ryan in the mix too.
So I mean we don't have just,
it's not just
talking to Gypsy now.
You have to take
into account that
she does have somebody there
also offering advice and.
- Brings in another
element of navigating.
- Correct.
- We'll have to
stay tight with them
regarding everything
she's doing.
I know she's got a obviously
check in with a parole.
- [Mike] Correct.
When you're on parole, you
are still under the custody
of the Department
of Corrections.
And so you don't have
the same freedoms
that the average person does.
She is going home today,
but she is not free yet.
[dramatic music]
[traffic humming]
- [Ryan] Damn [bleep]
right there.
I could lose him right now.
- [Gypsy] You know, Dad
said just drive safe.
Don't get in a car crash
worrying about losing him.
- [Ryan] I know.
- That's stressing me out.
- What's stressing you out?
- Just drive safe please.
- Okay baby I will.
- Thank you.
- I feel my heart
getting faster.
Faster and faster.
If I wanna run about ten laps,
'cause I have all
this nervous energy.
I'm on two and a half
hours, three hours of sleep
and not too long
she's gonna be here.
My mind just keeps going.
[can pops open]
I still can't believe
that it's here.
- Look, he stopped
in the mid-traffic.
[bleep] [bleep]
- Be safe.
- He's about to
see where we turn.
- [Mia] They're here.
- [Rod] Coming in hot.
He ain't lying.
[tense music]
- Did they get in
the garage?
- [Kristy] Yeah,
I hear the door.
Okay. Shut these.
[phone rings]
- Hello?
- Yes.
- The institution wanted me
to go directly to Louisiana
and I said I'd called my PO
in Louisiana
to work out.
- Alright, okay.
[dramatic music]
[Officer] It doesn't matter.
- [Gypsy] Okay
- Okay.
- Alright.
- [Gypsy] Okay.
- Thank you. Bye.
[phone beeps]
- That's some bull [bleep].
Nun-uh, [bleep] you man.
You do not have permission.
- [Gypsy] So we can just
go back to Louisiana
and they're happy, la-di-da.
It is what it is.
[paper rustling]
You know?
- [Ryan] That's a
thirteen hour trip.
- [Gypsy] I know.
- [Mike] Okay, now
I'm getting nervous.
- Oh y'all I'm shivering.
- Okay, let's go inside.
Let's try to be joyous.
- I know. It'll be all right.
[gentle music]
- Might as well leave
our stuff in the car.
- Yeah, might as well.
♪ I know that we don't have to
♪ Walk this road anymore
♪ I will find
- [Gypsy] Hi!
♪ My way back
- You made it.
- Hi.
Little scared?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- Yeah?
- A little bit.
It was a little scary
there for a second.
- You look beautiful baby.
- Thank you.
[uplifting music]
- [Gypsy] I know.
- [Rod] Gypsy's home!
- I'm crying on you right now.
- I've been crying off
and on all day, okay.
- My sis.
- You had a good time?
Your first night?
- Yes.
Mike, come give me a hug.
- Little bit.
You made it.
- Good to see you.
- It's good to see you too.
- [Kristy] So...
- Welcome to the crazy
world. All eyes on you.
- I welcome it.
- [Kristy] I had just said,
we're gonna run into them.
I look into my rearview mirror I
saw your lisence plate so...
- Oh goodness. It was a
little scary for a second.
- Really?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- I bet.
- A little bit.
- The best thing just to
come here though, you know?
- Yeah.
- We'll just leave
the windows closed.
- Yeah, that's
probably good idea.
- Hopefully they'll
leave us alone.
- Yeah, I'm hoping. I'm hoping.
- We'll be fine here.
We got another situation
going on though.
- She has to get
to Louisiana now.
- Really?
- [Ryan] And we were like, we
cleared this, like your P.O.
we're reporting on the third
and like he knows that.
That's when our intake
is and he's like,
nope, I don't care.
You gotta go to Louisiana now.
So I'm trying to get
in touch with her P.O.
So that's why we were
still in the car.
'cause that just happened.
- Wow.
- [Mike] Looks like I am
gonna be working today.
- [Kristy] Yep.
- [Rod] We'll figure
out what's going on.
- Yeah, what we need to do.
- We'll talk to somebody and.
- [Ryan] It was just crazy.
He said we got reports she's
going to a Chief Bengals game.
Y'all can't go to the
Chief Bengals game.
- Let me see what
I can find out.
I think this is an example
of how things are going to be
for Gypsy herself.
I don't think this is something
that would be an issue
for anybody else.
Because of the media
frenzy, probation and parole
wants her to get to Louisiana
wants her to get checked in
so that Louisiana can
take over supervision.
If this were just
any other person,
I don't think it would've even
registered on anyone's radar.
- [Ryan] Alright, there,
you wanna talk?
Right here.
- Hello?
- [Gypsy] Yes, this is Gypsy.
- Our plans was to stay
a few days in Kansas City
and drive back on the
first to Louisiana.
- Okay.
- Okay, thank you so much sir.
[laughs]
- [Gypsy] I know.
I don't wanna do anything
in violation of my parole.
I'm a very responsible woman
that just wants to do right.
And what she's told and
whatever that means.
- [Gypsy] Alright.
Thank you so much and
we'll let you know
if we know anything.
- [Gypsy] Bye.
- [Mike] That's a
really good P.O.
He seems to understand
the situation
and is willing to
work it out with you.
- Thank you.
- [Rod] Don't worry.
- [Gypsy] Oh God.
- [Rod] We good. We good.
Yeah, worst case you'll have
to leave in the morning.
- Right.
- Which we can have
a great time today.
- Right, we can have
it. We still have today.
- We got today
planned out perfectly.
- Right, let's have
a good time today.
- It's not going nothing
like we planned yet.
[Gypsy laughs]
We'll get there.
- [Rod] Which is good.
[Gypsy gasps]
[Gypsy laughs]
[phone ringing]
- [Gypsy] Hello?
- Yes. I understand.
- Okay.
- Yes, make sure the
[indistinct]...
- Okay, sir, my name
is Mike Stanfield
and I was her attorney
during the case.
We just spoke to her
Louisiana probation
or parole officer on the phone.
He has no problem with
her not being in Louisiana
until after the
first of the year.
- So the issue is, is
you just want her out
of the state of Missouri.
- Well, so they've been up
since one o'clock this morning.
So her traveling from
Kansas City where she is
to Louisiana tomorrow morning
would not be sufficient.
[Indistinct whispers]
- [Gypsy] [sobbing]
- [Mike] Okay, they're
not, their office isn't
open until January 3rd.
She couldn't report there,
if she got to Louisiana
by 8:00 AM tomorrow,
she couldn't report tomorrow.
- Okay.
She literally has
already reported
to the Louisiana officer.
I spoke to him personally
30 minutes ago.
- [Gypsy] I just
need a minute, okay?
[sobbing]
- [Kristy] It's, baby.
Listen. Listen to Mom.
Listen. It's okay.
It's okay. You did
the hardest part.
[Gypsy sobbing]
- [Kristy] They're not
gonna send you back.
[Gypsy sobbing]
- [Kristy] They not gonna
send you back Gyps.
- [Gypsy] [sobbing]
I'm so sorry.
- [Kristy] Don't
be sorry, please.
- [Gypsy] I'm sorry.
I feel like I've got
all these people.
- [Kristy] No, no listen.
These are your people.
There is nothing to be
sorry about. Not a thing.
- [Gypsy] This was
supposed to be a good day
and I wanna have a good day
with everybody else too.
But I also just want to do
what I'm supposed to on parole.
I don't understand why
I have to be different.
I don't understand what
makes me different.
Because to me I'm just
another average bear.
And I guess I'm getting
a huge culture shock.
So.
At the end of the day I will
still do whatever it takes
to make me free.
I do not feel free right now.
I feel like I am
in a different form of prison.
I had a nightmare about my mom.
It's not easy to live with.
- [Man] Gypsy can we
get a quick selfie?
- [Ryan] Come here.
- [Gypsy] I have my freedom now.
[Gypsy laughs]
Whoa!
- I'm terrified.
I don't know how to cook.
- That's so bad.
- It's not bad.
- It's so bad.
- Hadn't had a sex
life to speak of.
We consummated our marriage.
- Apparently the D is fire son.
- Oh my God!
- [Gypsy] I feel like everything
I do is on a microscope.
Am I at risk for
dangerous people?
I've been getting death threats.
My parole officer
received a complaint.
My biggest fear is
going back to prison.
I don't wanna be the old Gypsy.
[uplifting music]
- What would you
change about your nose?
- The bump.
I am kind of rushing into things
and wanting to do
everything all at once.
- She's 30 years old.
She's making 17, 18-year-old
person type decisions.
- What?
- If something
happens with Gypsy
and Ken, that's going
to be your fault.
- [Ryan] He's trying to
weasel his way back in
because now Gypsy's
out of prison.
- We had sex. It
wasn't protected.
- Are you pregnant?
- Who is that?
Who are you texting?
- You're mad at me
because I confided in someone.
Are you happy?
- [Ryan] I'm very
happy with you.
- [Gypsy] I just think
I would be happier
somewhere else.
- Go call Ken.
You're probably already
talking to him anyway.
[tense music]
- [Ken] I've never
been on camera before
talking about
anything like this.
- [Ryan] I need to have faith
that you always come back.
- [Gypsy] I sent him
a text and I'm like,
I'm gonna want a divorce.
- Hey you!
[chuckles]