Him on the ball,
from Dunbar.
He junior college now,
but he goin' bigger places
if he can make
them grades, yo.
He our edge,
right there.
Where he going?
I don't know.
Terps, Hoyas,
Missouri, Kansas,
they all want this cat.
Okay, so,
we in the mix too now.
You know
what I'm talkin' about?
Blow Proposition
Joe's mind.
He ain't got nobody
ballin' like this.
He better not
have one motherfucker
ballin' like this.
I'm sick
and tired of losing
to these Eastside bitches
every year.
It's been three years
runnin' now, man.
Fuckin' with
my morale, for real.
What happened
to the faggot?
Omar?
That nigger
in the wind, man.
Yo, what you mean
he in the wind, man?
This city
ain't that big.
You know what
that nigger do
when he hole up
somewhere?
He peeled off
one or two packages,
roll around
the neighborhood,
givin' away
free vials and shit.
Oh, yeah, on some real
Robin Hood type shit.
If we try
and get at him,
we gonna have
two dozen niggers sayin'
that we on our way.
If you want us to hunt
that nigger, we gonna hunt.
But the smart play,
I think,
we call a truce,
put this thing on hold
for a hot second.
Let the faggot
get comfortable,
and when he do,
he gonna pop out his head.
Boom, we got him.
Yo, what motherfuckers gonna
be sayin' while we waiting?
Hmm?
What people gonna say
when they see this
cocksuckin' faggot
out in the sunshine?
Like it ain't no thing
to take my shit.
(door opens)
Kid's everything
I said he was, huh?
Yeah, he straight.
Yeah, don't know
what we're gonna do
without him next year.
How come
you ain't signed?
Lot of schools
lookin' at me.
I'm listening.
10 large, though,
that ain't bad, right?
Naw, naw,
it ain't.
Well, 10 for the kid,
plus five.
A donation
for the program.
Done.
Good.
Give me 30 from the line
and get out of here.
- Yo, man, good job, baby.
- All right, big guy.
All right, man.
And I assume there's
another five right here,
for making
this happen?
Ain't shit
for free, right?
Yeah.
(theme music playing)
♪ If you walk
through the garden ♪
♪ You better
watch your back ♪
♪ Well, I beg
your pardon ♪
♪ Walk the straight
and narrow track ♪
♪ If you walk
through Jesus ♪
♪ He'll save your soul ♪
♪ You gotta
keep the devil ♪
♪ Down in the hole ♪
♪ All the angels sing ♪
♪ About Jesus' mighty soul ♪
♪ And they shoot you
with your wing ♪
♪ Keep you close
to the Lord ♪
♪ Don't pay heed
to temptation ♪
♪ Oh, your hands
are so cold ♪
♪ You got to
keep the devil ♪
♪ Way down in the hole ♪
♪ Way down in the hole. ♪
So, what you
do for money?
Can't live
without it, right?
You still fucked up behind
that stick-up, man?
Shit ain't on you.
It ain't
on me neither.
Motherfucker who robbed
the stash shot Sterling.
He gonna get got no matter
what you or me do.
I just don't wanna play.
I don't wanna play no more.
All right?
I was thinkin' about goin'
to school over at Edmondson,
ask if they'll let me back in
at the end of the semester.
- What grade?
- Ninth.
Ninth?
Shit, you how old?
- 16.
- 16?
Damn, man, you supposed
to be a junior by now.
I heard
Stinkum got killed.
Yeah.
Damn.
Yo, I said
I don't want to play.
- I heard you.
- I said I don't
want to play.
And you ain't
got to do nothin'.
I heard you.
Take it.
Hurry up, nigger,
people lookin'.
Look here, man,
you a smart
little motherfucker.
You start back up
at Edmondson,
you likely to finish
up at Harvard or some
shit like that.
Believe, B.
And you...
you got a good heart
in there, too.
Not like the rest
of these niggers.
(phone ringing)
Yeah?
Greggs:
Ronnie Mo on
tower phone two.
Right.
Ronnie Mo:
Where the fuck
you at, man?
You comin' to get
this shit or what?
Wee-Bey:
Keep cool,
we makin' rounds.
You know I ain't movin'
like I used to.
A'ight, couple hours,
we be at you.
A'ight.
Wee-Bey pickin' up
at the towers.
In a couple hours,
give or take.
Time enough for us
to make a play.
- What's up with Wallace?
- Nothin'.
Nothin'?
Nothin'.
It's all good,
just leave him be.
(pager beeps)
Damn.
Fuck.
I'm tired of not havin'
a phone up in this joint.
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
Have a nice hike.
(phone rings)
(with Chinese accent)
Hello, you make order?
- Who this?
- You make order?
- Good yockame.
- What?
Oh, no delivery.
You make order,
you come get.
Good yockame,
good noodle.
Extra ketchup.
The fuck was that?
That was
my Korean counterman.
Sounded Chinese.
Like you can fucking
tell the difference.
It's a brave new world
for you, boys.
- Greggs: 12-14.
- Man: 12-14.
- Request a lateral
with 12-08.
- Go ahead, 14.
0-8, can you go
to channel three?
12-08, I got that.
- Greggs: Where you at?
- McCulloh above Preston.
We're on a good pay phone
that the pit boys are now using.
I'm up on the church.
Hang close, boys.
We might have a nice
jackup for you two.
I can't believe these boys
still in business, man.
Tester, testers
comin' in five.
Hey, what's
the new package, man?
Yellow tops.
Shit is the bomb.
Now the shit
is the bomb.
Check it, check it,
check it.
A man who wants
to get high more than
he wants to get clean.
He was doin' good too.
Told you, all that shit
was bullshit, man.
Them meetings
were just fronts.
The man sounded strong,
you know?
Whatever.
- It's about that time.
- Aw, shit.
What happened?
That's the boy that
beat me down, man.
Hey, yo.
These shits right here is
yellow tops and they right.
So, remember where y'all
caught this blast
and tell your
fiend-ass friends.
Line the fuck up.
Back up, back up.
Get to the end
of the line.
What the fuck?
Line the fuck up.
Get the fuck
outta here.
- Damn, fuck y'all.
- There you go.
Hurry up, hurry up.
They're over here.
I got one, girl,
over here.
I got one.
You get one?
Hold up, hold up.
Hey, hey,
you catch one?
'Cause, you know,
I got three if you need.
You was
at the meeting
- over at Samuel Morse.
- Mr. One Day man.
- It wasn't even that.
- Stood up though.
So, why you down
at the tester line
if you ain't chasin'?
Tryin' to get my little
nephew off the corner.
His mama sent him up
to Cumberland, you know?
Try to keep him clean
at my grandma's.
He ain't anywhere
near his bottom.
Gotta see that bottom
comin' up at him.
Hard, too,
'cause he's young, 24.
Most people don't get tired
'til they're 35, 40.
How old are you?
Young at heart.
Walon, man.
Bubs.
Give 'em a long rope.
The farther away from
the projects you pop him,
the less risk
to the wire.
- Herc: Hell with the wire.
- Excuse me?
Gotcha, McNulty.
You're too easy.
Freamon:
We can come
at this a few ways.
First thing is
we need the names
of all front companies,
limited partnerships,
LLCs, and all that mess
LLCs?
Limited liability
corporations.
Start with the nightclub
which Barksdale owns.
Look up Orlando's.
By address,
you match it
and you see
it's owned by who?
It's on Baltimore Street,
right?
Got it.
D&B Enterprises.
Hand that over to Prez,
who's gonna get off his ass
and walk on over
to the state office buildings
on Preston Street.
Preston Street?
- Corporate charter office.
- Corporate who?
They have the paperwork
on every corporation
and LLC licensed to do
business in the state.
You look up D&B Enterprises
on the computer.
You're gonna get a little
reel of microfilm.
Pull the corporate charter
papers that way.
Write down
every name you see,
corporate officers,
shareholders,
or more importantly,
the resident agent
on the filing who is
usually a lawyer.
While they use
front names, you know,
as corporate officers,
they'll usually use
the same lawyer to do
the charter filing.
Find that agent's name,
run it through the computer,
find out what
other corporations
he's done the filing for,
and that way we find
other front companies.
While he's doing that,
what do I do?
You're gonna keep your head
in this here assessment book.
Look up any properties that
you can connect to Barksdale.
How do you know it connects
to Barksdale, right?
For one thing,
you work off of
what Prez gets you
from the corporate
charter documents.
Whatever companies
he links to Barksdale
or people connected
to Barksdale,
you look for those companies
in the city land records.
- Huh?
- For example,
McNulty said that
he heard that Barksdale
owned an apartment building
up on Druid Park Lake.
You look up all the blocks
on Reservoir Hill.
See if there's anything
owned by D&B Enterprises
or any other company
that Prez finds through
corporate charter
or anything similar.
If you find something
that fits,
you write down
the folio number
so that you can look it up
later at the courthouse.
You don't
find anything,
just take the names of
all the corporate listings
for the multi-units
near the lake.
You call that list
over to Prez,
who pulls
the charter papers
and he'll look
for connections.
This is like
a scavenger hunt.
Yeah, but what if
Barksdale is careful?
I mean, what if we can't
find his name on anything?
In this country,
somebody's name has got
to be on a piece of paper.
A cousin, a girlfriend,
a grandmother,
a lieutenant
he can trust,
somebody's name is
on a piece of paper.
And here's the rub,
you follow drugs,
you get drug addicts
and drug dealers.
But you start
to follow the money,
and you don't know where
the fuck it's gonna take you.
While we're running
around on this,
what are you gonna do?
- You need something?
- Yeah.
Let me get the...
campaign financial reports
for the western districts,
and actually,
any citywide race.
You want quarterly reports
or individual donor lists?
Both, please.
It'll be a couple
hundred pages.
Really?
I'll take all of it.
(siren blares)
What the fuck, man?
Driver,
with your right hand,
reach through the window
and open the door.
- Herc: C'mon, hurry up, man.
- Step out of the car.
Drop the cane.
Toss the cane.
Come around
to the back.
All right.
Turn around.
Sir, is there
anything in the vehicle
we should know about?
Nope.
No guns, no drugs?
We ain't got shit.
This money right here,
I didn't just pull this
out of your truck?
What money?
Damn, we'll be counting
this limp dick cash all day.
Where you guys
going with all this?
Like the man said,
it ain't ours.
It ain't yours, huh?
So, you don't mind if we just
take it off your hands?
Do what you feel.
You pretending to take
money up out this truck
I didn't even know
was there.
You know, I know
how that shit is.
The other day,
I took up the sofa
cushions off my couch.
Found a buck 40
I didn't even
know was there.
Y'all ain't
got no charge, right?
No, fucko, we do not
have a charge.
We just
got your money.
You want it back,
you can explain it
to the state's attorney
where you got it.
Y'all enjoy
your day now, you hear?
(man rapping)
♪ As I wake up in the morning
and get out of my bed... ♪
Man:
Yo, give me three.
♪ The brothers I deal with
locked up... ♪
♪ As I wake up in the morning
and get out of my bed ♪
♪ I'm thinkin' about the people
I grew up with long dead ♪
♪ The brothers I grew up
with locked up ♪
♪ I'm freestylin'
off the top of my head ♪
♪ You know, it's swell,
Patti LaBelle, I like her ♪
♪ But Regina Bell
is better. ♪
Motherfucker!
Yo, motherfucker,
tryin' to steal our shit.
(grunting)
Motherfucker!
Fished your wish, Bubs?
Oh, yeah.
And you should've seen
the one that got away.
I nearly got killed
behind this caper, you know?
It's all
in the game, Bubs.
Oh, yeah?
Yo, Bub...
this ain't shit.
I'm not high neither.
It's fuckin'
Arm & Hammer.
We just been
firin' baking soda.
- Fuck.
- It's all right, man.
I'll just come up
with another plan.
- I did it once, right?
- Just...
Fuck me.
Carv. You go
to a restaurant
and say the waitress
gives you good,
decent service.
How much do you tip?
How much do I tip?
For good service.
I don't know, 15%.
Some people tip 20.
Some people
got money.
What you think
Wee-Bey would tip?
You'd be
a clever motherfucker
if there wasn't
a wiretap running.
What do you mean?
Say we turn in 20
and this afternoon
the bosses are listening
to the wiretap
and they hear we took
30 out of that car.
Didn't think of that,
did you?
We're finding a lot of stuff
on the Westside of downtown
that might be his over by
that Howard Street corridor.
- What kind of property?
- Low-rent commercials.
A lot of vacants.
The fuck does
Avon Barksdale want
with a string of
empty storefronts?
- This feels premature.
- What does?
Chasing up assets.
We're not close to putting
a charge to the man.
That should
be the priority.
We put a charge
to Avon Barksdale,
the deputy shuts us down,
tells us to go home.
You want the moneyside
of this case,
it's now or never,
Lieutenant.
Whoop-whoop!
- Hey, I'm working here.
- Whoop-whoop!
- Herc: Maybe 20 or 30.
- Dollars for donuts.
You should've seen
the looks on their faces.
- What did Wee-Bey say?
- "What money?"
The only hassle is
we need to sit here
and count this shit.
Do the ECU
submissions.
And it's all limp-dick,
dime-vial money.
Dirty bills
right off the corner.
McNulty:
You all got the pit boys
on a fresh pay phone, right?
- Yeah, on McCulloh.
- You take pictures?
- Fuck, yeah.
- Good, we're gonna need
an additional affidavit
to get up on that phone.
Another 30 days, McNulty?
- (door slams)
- What the fuck did I do?
One day he fights,
the next day he's ready
to roll over.
Does he want this
fucking case or not?
Freamon: Give him
some slack, Jimmy.
He's wrestling with
the angels on this one.
Where's my lucky pen?
(music playing)
- Man: You ready, bitch?
- Woman: Yeah, I'm ready.
I wanna get on
my hands and suck you
like a great big lollipop.
Oh, yeah, suck it.
Yeah, I know
that's your favorite.
Let me lick that.
You like that?
I want you
to butt-fuck me.
Prez:
You know, we're supposed
to turn off the tap
when it's non-pertinent.
Hey, fuck, no,
this is too good.
- Man: Fuck me.
- Woman: Oh, daddy, yeah.
You comin'?
There's no way
I'm transcribin'
this stuff.
Touch yourself.
Oh, yeah.
Phone sex?
Shit was hilarious.
You know you're supposed
to shut down
after 90 seconds
if it's non-pertinent.
You gonna look
like a glazed donut,
you know that?
Is that right?
I'm gonna get there
and fuck you in all
three holes.
So, you're gonna come
past here?
Tomorrow, yeah.
But I need to go past
Argyle Street tonight.
- Check in with Wallace.
- Wallace?
He off the hook since
we helped the tower crew
get that stickup boy.
I'm tellin' you,
Wallace is buggin'.
Don't hardly even come
out of that room no more.
Why he be like that?
I think he might
be gettin' high.
Wallace?
Boy scarin' me
with his shit.
A'ight, well,
you holler at me later.
That'll work.
Pertinent now, right?
Well, it is if you
can explain why we're
still on the line
after 10 minutes
jerking off.
You gotta
justify that.
Maybe three holes
was the code for
three stash houses.
(laughing)
Omar.
Hey, yo.
Omar!
Omar, comin', yo.
Omar's comin'.
Did you hear me?
I said Omar comin'.
Get outta here.
Omar's comin'.
I said Omar's comin'!
Somebody in trouble now.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, yo.
Hey, yo!
Y'all need to open
this door, man,
before I huff and puff.
C'mon, now, by the hairs
of your chinny-chin-chin.
Terrell:
Omar, you best roll out.
We up in here with a Mac-10.
I thinks not, Terrell.
I thinks not.
Y'all might need
to think this through
and stop
wasting my time.
'Cause Omar
can come back tomorrow.
And the next day.
And I will put a bullet
in all y'all behind
what happen right now,
you heard?
Fair enough.
(dog barking)
Here you go,
keep it.
How do you wanna
play it?
Hard and tight,
like she's got no choice.
Greggs:
Shardene Ennis.
Miss,
we need to talk.
- About what?
- It's a downtown talk.
This way.
C'mon, c'mon.
(music playing)
Wallace:
Gimme two and two.
Man:
It's the bomb.
Better get it
while it lasts.
Yo, what's up?
What you got?
Family affair,
two-for-one, you up?
Naw, not me.
A'ight.
How you figure
these little pebbles
get up on top
of the roof?
Where's everybody at?
Maybe the whole thing
is over and no one
bothered to tell us.
Maybe we won.
Something ain't right.
C'mon, let's take a ride.
I like these.
Yeah?
The toy furniture
is great.
Doll house
miniatures.
It's a hobby.
My sister had a dollhouse
when we were young.
But nothing as nice
as these. Can I?
Sure.
That's a walnut
marble-top vanity.
Renaissance revival,
late 19th century.
Do you have
a house for 'em?
No.
I just make them
and sell them.
That seems kinda sad.
You should
have a house for them.
We can use
the lieutenant's office.
(children chattering)
(doorbell rings)
No.
I ain't, I ain't
even asked for nothin'.
Oh, what's up, Tosha?
You got too pretty, girl.
Go inside, Tosh.
I'm thinkin', um--
I'm thinkin'
about gettin' clean...
again.
I'm thinkin', you know,
I ain't got no other place
to go, maybe...
that's wrong, right?
That ain't right,
right? Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Back door only.
There's an old sofa
in the basement
and I'll throw you
down some blankets.
You try to come
up those stairs,
and I'm gonna call
the police on you.
I swear I will.
(thunder rumbling)
West fucking Baltimore
is on vacation.
No crews slinging
in the low-rises,
the towers.
(cheering)
What the fuck?
Who's playing who?
West against east.
Baltimore?
The projects, man.
The braggin' rights
to the projects.
The projects
got a ball team?
How long you been
working at Orlando's?
- Four or five months.
- You like it?
Pays the rent.
You must see a lot
there, I imagine.
What do you mean?
Well, there's a lot
of players there.
A lot of game
being played.
I don't know
nothin' about that.
I just work for tips.
- Greggs: For tips?
- Tips, drinks.
You know,
I'm just a B-girl.
I don't mess with
nothing beyond that.
Some of the girls in there,
they're into drugs and whatnot.
Some of 'em turn tricks
in the rooms upstairs,
but I mostly just
stay at the bar.
You know, Miss Ennis,
it's a rare thing
when we ask somebody
to come on downtown with us,
and we don't
have a charge on them,
we don't tell them
what we're gonna talk about,
and they come along
without complaining.
- That hardly ever happens.
- Rarely, if ever.
I figure
you got your reasons.
The crew
that runs Orlando's.
They've dropped about a dozen
bodies over the last year.
And they're running the drugs
in every housing project
west of
the Martin Luther King.
I don't know
anything about that.
I just work for tips.
But now you do know, right?
'Cause we're telling you.
You know a girl
named Keisha Michaels?
She dances with me.
- How's she doing?
- All right, I guess.
Will you excuse us
a moment?
So, what do you think?
I think
she's a sweetheart.
I think if we push
her hard, she'll tumble.
You want to show her
the pictures?
I want to do better
than that.
(cheering)
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
C'mon, man,
play defense.
- D up.
- Let's go!
D up, B.
Avon:
Who is he?
That's Marcus Rivera
right there, man.
He out of Lake Clifton.
That nigger played
in Italy and shit.
Hey, yo, Slim.
What's up, man?
You gotta go all
the way over to Europe
to get you a ringer?
Naw, he home now.
But I see you pullin' boys
out the junior colleges.
He from Eastside,
went to Dunbar.
Hey, yo,
what's up, playboy?
How come you wearin'
that suit, B?
For real, it's 85
fucking degrees out here
and you trying to be
like Pat Riley.
Man, look the part,
be the part, motherfucker.
Nigger, please.
You walkin' around with
a fake fucking clipboard.
You can't even
read a playbook.
Be for real.
You bunch of bitches.
Yeah!
Let's go.
That was nice.
That boy was talkin'
to God, right?
- Ain't y'all
on the clock?
- Ain't you?
- We on break.
- Then we on a break, too.
What's up
with this game?
Naw, just something we do
every year, you know?
Eastside versus
Westside niggers.
Loser gotta throw
a big-ass party
up at Droodle Hill
next weekend.
Who's favored?
Eastside won
the last two years.
My boys.
Coroner:
Found nude Monday morning
in a Dumpster
off Reisterstown Road,
above Northern.
Toxicology is positive
for heroin and cocaine.
- In a Dumpster?
- Freamon: Rolled up in a rug.
She overdosed and whoever
was with her didn't do shit,
but roll her up
and throw her away.
'Cause that's
how they do.
Coroner:
Positive for semen in vaginal,
anal, and oral cavities.
Three different blood types,
all secreters.
They fucked her
and threw her away.
The only reason
we knew who she was
or what she was about
or what she might mean
to someone like you,
is because we've been keeping
an eye on the people
who run Orlando's
for some time now.
We got ways of knowing
what they're saying,
what they're thinking.
You know what they said
about this one?
Greggs:
That the stupid bitch
didn't know how good
the snort was
at Little Man's party.
That it was her own fault.
That's how they do.
They use people,
and when they throw
them away,
they find a way
to say it ain't on them.
Lying motherfucker.
He said they took her
to a hospital.
Hell, yeah.
That's what
I'm talkin' about.
Now, get back on D.
Check out Avon.
He freakin'.
Shit, man, we gotta
win this one.
Yo, I think
Avon's here.
Where?
Like I know
what he looks like?
He's a black guy
rooting for Westside.
(phone rings)
We might have
a visual on Avon.
Street ball game
up at Cloverdale.
Where's Greggs
and Freamon?
Pressin' the stripper
they picked up.
You and Carver
stay on the radio.
- We should follow him.
- Why?
He ain't gonna
touch drugs or money
anywhere you can see him,
Lieutenant.
In Narcotics
we follow guys.
We do it well,
we make cases on it.
Mount up.
We've been on this guy
three months.
Don't you even want
to get a look at him?
Wouldn't know
Avon Barksdale
if I fell over him
in the street.
The thing is,
I don't need to.
We get him by voice alone
or we don't get him.
Yeah, baby!
(blows whistle)
Half-time.
Got yourself
a fine ringer.
Well, yeah, baby,
it's not your year,
you know what
I'm talkin' about?
It look that way,
but you never know.
Oh, I know, man,
we up 12.
Yeah, you is,
but, hey...
I got a proposition
for you.
Okay.
Double down?
Let's give this wager
a clean six-figures.
You serious?
I don't give a fuck, baby,
it's your money.
You can waste it
if you want,
you know
what I'm talkin' about?
Daniels:
Anyone got him?
(radio chatter)
12-10.
- 12-10.
- You have him?
Lieutenant, I don't even
know what I'm looking for.
Whoo!
(whistle blows)
Foul.
Got him marked.
On the sideline,
red shirt, white visor.
I think he's coaching
or somethin'.
Who this
fucking midget, yo?
Get that midget
outta here, B.
Hey.
Man:
Why you holler at me?
Man #2:
Yo, man, we gettin'
down to it.
I get to you
when I get to you.
That's it,
we're on the stash.
- We are?
- Uh-huh.
How can you
put that down
when Sydnor
wasn't on the roof?
Yes, he was.
No, he's not.
He's with Daniels.
No, he isn't.
Get the fuck
outta here.
Yo, yo, ref, ref, ref,
what the fuck?
(blows whistle)
What the fuck?
Yo, ref, yo, ref,
what the fuck?
The boy was fouled.
Clear, straight up!
How you gonna
not call that?
Look, if you want,
I can put time back
on the clock and replay it.
You talkin' about
a do-over, baby?
Are you talkin' about
a fuckin' do-over?
That's not how
the game is played!
You can't do that!
Fuckin' believe
this shit?
Nigger talkin' about
doing it again.
Look, I don't want
any trouble, okay?
Ain't gonna be no trouble
over no ball.
Man, you supposed
to be the ref, right?
Why don't you stand up
for your fucking self?
You pussy.
You can't just let any
old motherfucking nigga
get in your face,
you understand?
Now, walk away.
Walk away.
Turn around
and walk the fuck away.
Ignorant motherfucker.
- We cool?
- Yeah, we cool, baby.
You tell your people
to come out here to
the park Saturday at noon.
'Course you come
on the Westside again,
baby, without a ball,
I'm gonna
light your ass up.
D'Angelo, huh?
You know him?
At this point,
it feels like I do.
We sorta
moved in together.
He seemed like
he was different.
I have
to quit the club.
Yes, you do.
But not just yet.
We need your help.
Which is why
we came to you.
I don't know
what else you--
Keisha was
not the first.
Unless somebody steps up
a little bit,
she's not gonna
be the last neither.
Do you like that one?
Why don't you keep it?
Thank you.
He's getting into
a black Ford Excursion.
Herc:
Copy that.
Daniels:
He's pulling out,
north on Collington.
(rap music playing)
11-71.
You got the parallel
on the north,
I got him on the south.
11-71, I got him.
Looks like he's going
east on Oliver.
He just parked.
East of Oliver.
12-10,
you keep the eyeball.
11-71, take up
a position on Federal,
west of Montford.
I'm coming up
from the south.
11-71, I copy that.
He's just
sitting there.
- He's doubling back.
- Copy.
He's south
on Montford.
He's at the light
at Preston and Milton
and is south on Milton.
Be advised that he didn't
make it to Chase.
11-71,
what's your status?
Herc:
He couldn't have
gone past us.
Sydnor:
11-71, nothin'
on this side.
Must have
went to ground.
All right,
hold your positions.
I'll take a look.
(rap music playing)
He called again,
same pay phone.
Same voice?
The main stash house,
it's gotta be.
The pattern fits.
Who took the call
at the projects?
Who knows?
There was no one
on the roof.
Sydnor was off with Daniels
chasing Avon in the street.
We had a good day, too.
Kima turned
one of the dancers
over at Avon's club.
The one who's
fucking D'Angelo.
(muffled TV playing)
(laughs)
This guy's good.
We threw everything
we had at him.
Well, you know
what they say,
stupid criminals
make stupid cops.
I'm proud to be
chasing this guy.
We got four front
companies so far,
buying up
all kinds of shit.
A club,
an apartment building,
the funeral home.
And a whole lot
of real estate on
the Westside of downtown
by that
Howard Street corridor.
Shop fronts
and warehouses.
Barksdale's name on it?
Fronts, mostly.
Relatives, some.
Mind if
I have a seat?
The point is,
he's had the projects
for more than a year now
and it's a money factory.
We popped Wee-Bey coming out
the other day with $22,000,
and the boys
talking on the wire
were saying that it wasn't
that much of a loss.
22?
And that's just from one morning
from the towers and the pit.
Add the avenue corners,
you're probably up near 30.
Another take
for the evening...
$60,000.
A day?
That's 20, 25 million
a year, conservatively.
You take out 20%
for running expenses
and spillage
and you are still clearing
a million dollars a month.
So, where's it all go?
He shows no flash.
He's got no house,
no car in his name,
no jewelry,
no clothes.
Just front companies
and the property.
And political
contributions.
$75,000 in last month alone,
all from his front companies
or their
listed officers.
And that's just
at a quick glance.
I'm just totaling up
the legal contributions.
You've got the likes
of Damien Price,
aide to a state senator,
driving out $20,000 in cash
from the projects
whenever he feels it.
Now, I know you don't want
to hear this, Lieutenant,
but the money is real
and it's everywhere.
And more than the drugs,
it's the money that matters.
I ain't fucked nobody else
if that's what you thinkin'.
A'ight, I mean, fuck it.
Fuck it,
if you wanna go, then go!
But you could give me
a goddamn reason.
What do I look
like to you?
What you mean?
What do I look
like to you?
You look like a girl,
a woman.
A beautiful woman.
You fine, what?
I don't look like
trash to you?
Baby, this ain't
about what you do.
I don't look like something
you could roll up in a rug
and throw in the trash?
Shardene.
Shardene!
Lieutenant,
you paged us?
We were almost home.
Sit.
- Yeah?
- Checked my count
again, yo.
- How bad?
- Not too bad, man.
Not too bad.
We, um, we got hit
by a 22.
- 22?
- That's all.
A'ight.
I got towers two,
three, five and six
and another one
labeled "P" for the pit.
Where's one and four?
It's on the wire that
we took them for 22.
You shitheads
turned in 15.
- Where's the rest?
- Lieutenant, we ain't got--
You have 'til
roll call tomorrow
to crawl back to whatever
rock you hid it under.
It comes back
and it goes to ECU.
This doesn't happen.
Not with me.
Not with my unit.
I wouldn't steal
and not tell you about it.
This some of
Avon's shit.
You got Avon Barksdale chasin'
your ass all around town,
and you still find time
to take his shit.
- It's your shit now.
- What I want with that?
What anybody want
with that, man.
How much you askin'?
Oh, we free.
Free?
I'm sayin', I got a little
proposition for you.
Proposition is, you get
four G-packs for free
and you give me some better
idea on how I can reach Avon.
How to contact him?
Y'all just had
a game, right?
How you get ahold
of him to parlay?
We talk now and then.
I page his ass.
Okay. Okay.
That all you need?
A number?
Oh, I'll make
do with it.
And a code for
one of his peoples.
What Wee-Bey use, 07?
07.
What makes you think
I just ain't gonna take
this shit off your hands
and throw your ass
up outta here?
C'mon, man,
Avon goes down,
the projects be open
market again, right?
Let me understand.
Avon loses
a hundred large
to me on a bet,
then you bring me
some of his shit
so that I can put your
predatory self on his ass?
Not his day, is it?
Fuck.
(sighs)
Fuck it.
- Where was it?
- The wheel well.
You remember
when the bag broke?
Think Daniels
will believe it?
Would you?
You didn't
believe me.
I'm sorry.
Savino late, man.
I'm ready to make
this money-run,
get the fuck
outta here.
- You tired, huh?
- I'm tired, man, I'm hungry.
Shit, me, too.
You want something
to eat from the diner?
Yeah, you goin'
over there?
Get a cheesesteak, man.
Oh, you hungry, too?
Yeah, I could
do a burger.
All right.
Let me get onions
on that, man.
I got you.
You organizin' it right?
You got my 50s with my 50s,
and my 20s--
and my 100s with my 100s.
The way you want it.
All right, ladies,
goodnight.
I see y'all tomorrow,
on time, ya hear?
(dialing)
Count this money, baby.
(pager beeps)
- What the fuck?
- Who's that?
Wee-Bey swingin' me
an emergency call.
(dialing)
(pager beeps)
Fuck.
Bey?
Yeah.
911 call.
No, no, no, no.
We got rules, right?
(dialing)
- (beeping)
- Fuck.
(dialing)
(music playing)
Hey! They had
cheese fries, baby.
I got you some.
(car alarm beeping)
(grunts)
Wee-Bay:
Avon, stay down, man.
I got you covered.
(beeping)
(theme music playing)