(helicopter hovering)
How many bags
you got?
C'mon, c'mon!
(camera clicking)
Another bag here.
Christ.
- Sergeant?
- Yeah.
Who are
the primaries?
Cole and Norris.
Cole's here and Norris
is at the hospital.
What do you need?
Room to work.
I keep ordering people
off the scene,
and between narcotics,
DEA and the two districts,
we keep collecting more
and more bodies around here.
Nobody move!
I said,
nobody fucking move!
If you have not been
assigned a specific task
by a homicide detective,
you need to step away
from this crime scene.
Is there anybody doesn't
understand a direct order?
If you have not specifically
been instructed otherwise,
then remove your useless
interfering asses from the area.
Now!
Slow this thing down
to a crawl.
Give these bastards no chance
to fuck up in a meaningful way.
Okay.
Aah!
Wedged all the way
to the back.
She couldn't
get to it.
Well, she taped it
up front,
but as soon as
she put any weight
on these
worn-ass car seats,
they pulled
the tape off.
Gun slid back behind the mesh
as they drove, probably.
Christ.
Where was
her support?
There were
two follow cars,
they were several
blocks distant.
I think she got turned
around in the alleys,
she gave her 20
as the north side
of Warwick.
They went there
on the shots?
This, uh... Foxtrot
finally found her.
So, we had two units
covering the north side
and a helicopter
up on top.
And no one saw
any vehicles in flight.
(police radio chatter)
Bunk.
Terry, Mike, c'mon.
What the fuck
happened?
(theme music playing)
♪ If you walk
through the garden ♪
♪ You better
watch your back ♪
♪ Well, I beg
your pardon ♪
♪ Walk the straight
and narrow track ♪
♪ If you walk
through Jesus ♪
♪ He'll save your soul ♪
♪ You gotta
keep the devil ♪
♪ Down in the hole ♪
♪ All the angels sing ♪
♪ About Jesus' mighty soul ♪
♪ And they shoot you
with your wing ♪
♪ Keep you close
to the Lord ♪
♪ Don't pay heed
to temptation ♪
♪ Oh, your hands
are so cold ♪
♪ You got to
keep the devil ♪
♪ Way down in the hole ♪
♪ Way down in the hole. ♪
You didn't
have an eyeball?
On those streets,
there's no way
you can eyeball it.
She was throwing out 20s
as best she could.
Understood,
I'm just asking.
The link we have to this
is Savino Bratton.
A minor lieutenant
to our target, Barksdale.
I gave your people
all that at the scene.
And we're hitting
his last knowns.
We're on that.
The set-up
was more than him.
Casings are
different calibers,
and her Glock
was full up, so...
How bad?
Chest wound, no exit.
Through-and-through
to the throat.
She wasn't stabilized.
They had the pressure
pants on her.
Trying to push up
the pulse.
They put those pants
on you, it ain't good.
Right.
So, you're on Baker
when you hear the shots.
Where was the second car?
Um, Warwick, I think.
Okay. You've got everything
to the east well-covered
and to the west
is the railbed.
What did Foxtrot see?
Nothing moving
except our units.
Lieutenant...
I know just
how you feel.
This is the toughest job
a police commissioner has.
I don't think
I'll ever get used to it.
Um, this is
Lieutenant Daniels.
Oh, right,
right, of course.
This entire department
stands behind Detective Greggs
in every
possible way.
I just thought
you should know that.
Yes, sir.
P.A. system:
...please report to room 12.
Please report
to room 12.
Jaybird.
We have a runner.
Yeah, we're gonna need casts
of these two imprints.
Put the lab tech on.
11-39.
It's not that the money
is anyone's primary concern.
I understand that.
I'm not going to be
standing here
giving a shit about the money
when you people have lost...
well, one of your own
who might...
I mean, Jesus,
this is awful.
On the other hand,
if we can get to this
Savino character quick--
Hey!
Fuck your money.
Jimmy?
You hurt?
No.
It's hers.
C'mon, get up.
Let's go,
up with you.
C'mon.
Couldn't talk,
couldn't breathe.
Nothing.
She went into
the ambo that way.
Is she, uh...
what the fuck did I do?
C'mon, walk.
What's that?
What's our plan, Ray?
Bunk and Jay
stay with the scene.
Keeley and Crutchfield
are at the office
typing the warrants
for this Savino fuck.
Who's on the autopsy?
Me, I'm at the morgue.
Norris and Holley
stay at shock trauma
in case she sits up
and talks.
We're laser printing
the car, right?
'Course,
Worden's on that.
You're in command
for the city, right?
Major Rawls, homicide.
Anything you need
from my office,
men, money, whatever,
you just ask.
Right.
Cooperator, your girl's
down shock trauma.
Let's get to work.
Fuck you.
Fuck me?
- We got a wire up.
- So?
So we got a wire up
on some motherfucker
that just shot a cop.
If somebody talks,
if somebody gets
on the wrong phone
and says the wrong
fuckin' thing about what
happened here tonight,
where the fuck
do you want to be?!
Church roof?
Yeah, you and me.
Sydnor takes
the McCulloh street phone.
Anybody get in contact
with Kima's people?
Shit.
I'll do that first,
meet you at the church.
Bunk, Mike.
Wonder who
that bitch was.
Always some shit, right?
Yeah.
(phone ringing)
- Male: Yo.
- Done.
All right.
Let's get outta here.
Yeah.
Lab tech
to this spot.
Photos and casts.
- 11-39.
- Woman on radio: 11-35.
Can I get 18-12
up here?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yeah, yeah.
(chuckling)
You're camped here.
Nobody touches this shit,
nobody even comes near it
until the tech
does his recovery.
Whoa.
Hello.
He stopped running.
Either he
got tired or--
- Or he got into a car.
- Right.
- 11-34.
- Man on radio:
Go ahead, 11-34.
I'm in the 3,000 block
of Lanvale
backing up
to the CSX bed.
I need a lab unit
and a DPW crew
with a jackhammer.
A jackhammer?
Gonna keep
a bit of road, KGA.
Alive.
In the OR.
My people at the scene
have heard this already.
It's a copy
of the original.
Okay, we brought
a machine--
- where the fuck is--
- Sir.
Oh, here it is, here.
Yeah, put it there.
(music playing)
Savino:
Don't fuck with this count.
That's Savino.
I'll be right back
with ya shit.
Greggs:
Where are we?
That sign said Longwood,
but I could swear
this is Warwick.
Orlando:
Hoppers be turning
the sign poles
to fuck with y'all.
Greggs:
I make it we're on
the north side of Warwick,
in an alley,
I don't know, shit,
half a block west
of Longwood, maybe?
I hope y'all
copy that.
This got the right
feel for you?
Orlando:
He better not be long
'cause, see,
I don't know
where the stash is,
and if they draggin'
us all over this part
of town, you know--
Greggs:
What's that?
Oh, Jesus.
- Somethin' ain't right.
- Orlando: What?
- Greggs: Shit ain't right.
- Oh, Christ.
- Man: You snitchin'
motherfucker.
- (gunshots)
Greggs:
Signal 13, signal 13.
What the fuck?
- She can't reach the gun.
- What the fuck?
Two males, black hoodies,
both of 'em, one is--
(gunshots)
Shut it off.
P.A. system:
Dr. Mells, line six.
Listen to me,
you fuck.
You did a lot
of shit here.
You played a lot
of fucking cards
and you made a lot
of fucking people
do a lot of fucking things
they didn't want to do.
This is true.
We both know
this is true.
You, McNulty,
are a gaping asshole.
We both know this.
Fuck if everybody in CID
doesn't know it.
But fuck if I'm gonna
stand here and say
you did a single fucking
thing to get a police shot.
You did not do this,
you fucking hear me?
This is not on you.
No, it isn't, asshole.
Believe it or not,
everything isn't about you.
And the motherfucker
saying this,
he hates your guts,
McNulty.
So you know
if it was on you,
I'd be the son of a bitch
to say so.
Shit went bad.
She took two
for the company.
That's the only
lesson here.
Police! Police!
Police,
let me see your hands!
Get on the ground!
Down on the ground!
Search warrant,
get on the ground!
Police, police,
get down, get down!
- He ain't here!
- Who ain't here?
- Zach, he ain't here!
- Zach?
Naw, honey,
we're lookin' for Savino.
Savino?
No, he's my baby.
Yeah, well,
your baby shot a cop.
Man:
Yo, they kickin'
in the doors,
lookin' for a Savino.
Man #2: What?
What up with that, man?
Man:
Some shit about
he killed a cop.
Man #2: Who, Savino?
Savino ain't shot no cop.
Man:
Man they kickin' in doors,
they actin' like he did it.
- Shit.
- I'm tellin' you, man.
(beeping)
They're talkin'
about it anyway.
Ripples in the pond.
Talkin' ain't
knowin', is it?
Skin this cat
another way.
Two pages to Stringer
tonight, right?
Only this one
after the shooting.
Who's 0-7?
And what phone is he asking
for Stringer to call him back?
- Shit went good,
but there was--
- Hold on.
Radio:
...around 12:30
this morning.
The officer may
have been undercover...
(machine humming)
- All right, so talk.
- Like I said, it went good.
Except there was this bitch
curled up in the back-seat.
- Surprised
the shit out of us.
- Uh-huh.
Didn't even see her
till the shit popped off.
I mean, and if it
was up to me,
I'd let the girl walk.
She didn't look like
the talkin' type.
But Little Man
seen her,
and bugged out,
let a couple go.
Savino didn't tip y'all
off to that bitch?
Wasn't no time for that.
He get up out the car,
we see him go up the block
like we said, right?
After that,
he out of sight
and we bring it home
like we planned, baby.
Well, shorty was a cop.
And she ain't dead.
Where'd y'all
put the guns?
She wasn't no cop, man.
She look like
one of Orlando's ho's.
Bey, where the fuck
are the guns?
A storm drain off
of Park Heights, man.
What the fuck is wrong
with Little Man?
I mean, this motherfucker
bugged out one time.
Well, he gonna
bug out again,
when he find out
shorty's a fuckin' cop?
I mean, c'mon, man.
Savino got a story that
he can keep to and he know it,
but Little Man, he always
been fuckin' weak like that.
Little Man gotta go.
Yo, you hear me?
Yo, this shit
gonna get real heavy.
You understand me, Bey?
We gotta fall back.
I wanna see how it go
with this Savino bullshit,
see how they
go past that.
But if the shit
don't hold,
or if this motherfuckin' cop
wake up and start talkin' shit,
then you gotta go sky up.
Where you got
your peoples at?
New York...
Jersey, Cleveland.
All right, so, um,
Philly, D.C.
You know what I'm sayin'?
No profile,
no connections,
no noise.
You feel me, right?
All right.
We gotta be careful.
(muffled voices)
Jesus.
- Jesus.
- I'm sorry.
It's alright,
you just scared me.
I, uh...
I work with Kima.
Uh...
Kima, she, uh...
Kima--
Kima's at work.
What?
W-w-what are you--
Dust the receiver,
the coin return,
and the metal top.
The can, too.
P.A. system:
Dr. Jones to the nurses'
station, please.
Dr. Jones to
the nurses' station.
We can't really
know for sure.
Lieutenant?
I'm sitting over there
with Kima's girl and,
I mean, maybe somebody
from the department
or the city,
maybe might want
to say something.
Who's here
from the family?
- A daughter, you say?
- A daughter?
Officer Greggs
has a girl?
A roommate.
The family's in Richmond,
driving up first thing today,
but the roommate's
already here.
I'll do it myself.
No problem.
If we lose her,
he can always pose
for the funeral.
Still need a right door
for Savino.
His last knowns,
his girlfriend, his mama,
all empty holes.
Tracers picked up a couple
hairs on one of the hoodies.
That's something.
So, either these motherfuckers
are a pair of neighborhood yo's
who lucked into $30,000
on a street stickup or...
Or they're pros
who set up in an alley
on one side of the tracks,
then slip over to
the other side
where they park
their ride.
What about the post?
Cause and manner of death
on Mr. Blocker is homicide,
to wit, close-range GSWs
to the shoulder,
chest and left arm.
Nine millimeter,
six left twist,
suitable
for comparison.
We pulled something
different from the back seat
of the car, right?
Yeah, 380,
semi-jacketed.
Casings were
different, too.
So, we confirmed
the two shooters.
Print hit.
Wynton "Little Man" Rice,
enforcer in the 221,
a definite connect
to Barksdale's world.
- A print hit?
- Print hit from what?
Soda can.
Dropped at the pay phone
at Park Heights and Belvedere.
Still had a little fizz
in it when I got there.
What the fuck is this pay phone
at Park Heights and Belvedere?
It's a phone from which some
motherfucker paged Stringer Bell
20 minutes
after the shooting.
I dusted the phone, too,
but it was smudged.
So, we got a Barksdale pro
in the northwest,
ringing up the boss
minutes after the deed.
So much for
the amateur-hour theory.
Good pull.
You are?
Freamon,
Lester Freamon.
Where you workin'?
Pawn shop unit.
I mean, how you gonna
shoot a police, yo?
Ain't no percentage in that,
you know what I'm sayin'?
For real.
Somebody around here
do that shit,
you know every knocko
in the world be down here,
bustin' heads.
I guess them
Park Heights nigga's
just ain't got
no fuckin' common sense.
A lotta heart,
just no sense.
Hey, yo, Poot.
Wallace on
the phone, yo.
- Yeah?
- Wallace?
Nigga ring me up
twice a day
whether he got shit
to say or not.
Homesick motherfucker
makin' me bug, yo.
Yo, where's he at, yo?
At the shore
with his grandma,
down there...
Probably surfin' or
some bullshit.
Or something.
P.A. system:
Dr. Zellesky, you have
a call on line five.
(pager beeping)
(tires screeching)
You just
use that phone?
Yeah, a little
earlier, man.
Y'all might wanna go
to Mosher Street.
- Just now, you used it?
- Yeah.
Man downtown
needs to talk to you.
Man downtown?
Okay, make some sense
for me, please, all right?
I ain't been so clean
in my whole damn life.
- Look, man,
I'm just doin' my job.
- Okay.
What up,
Mr. Beachfront Property?
Wallace:
Naw, fool, I told you,
I'm bayside.
My grandmother
on the bayside.
Still, man, you on vacation
and not bringin' me with you.
How you get all the way
down there, anyhow?
- I took a bus.
- Well, shit.
Tell me how to go
and I grab a 'Hound, too.
Come down there
and hang with your ass.
No, man,
it ain't like that, yo.
The air down here all sticky.
Worse than Baltimore, yo.
And these crickets,
louder than a motherfucker.
Can't get no sleep.
I don't think I'm cut out
to be no country-ass nigga, man.
Operator:
Please deposit $2 for
an additional...
- Shit, I gotta go.
- You can take a nigga
up out the Westside,
- but you can't take--
- (dial tone)
What's your name?
Look, I didn't
do shit here, okay?
I asked you your name.
Naw, this shit
ain't right.
Who'd you try to page,
shitbird?
Why the fuck
do you care, okay?
I mean...
you have exactly
three more seconds
to explain yourself
to me, asshole.
One shooter definitely
opened the passenger door,
so any latent prints
from that side of the car.
- I didn't do nothing, man!
- (thumping)
- Why'd you
page her, shitbird?!
- Get off me, man!
- Get off me!
- You think this
is a fucking game?!
I wanna talk
to Detective Greggs.
- You can't, motherfucker.
- Then, McNulty then.
This shit
ain't right, sir!
Savino, Savino.
Mope ain't around.
(dialing, ringing)
Yeah, one of them
low-rise hopper's
on tower phone two.
Okay.
(camera clicking)
Maybe he forgot
the number.
(camera clicking)
What the fuck was that?
You don't know?
We just caught a re-up
off a tower stash.
Fourth floor, south side,
second unit down.
(dialing, ringing)
Daniels:
Put that away.
Put that away
and work the case.
Can I ask you something?
How much of this case would
you give up to get her back?
That's not the point.
Well, how much?
All of it.
But it doesn't
work that way.
You can't give it back.
I'm sitting here with
a hospital progress report
that shows
no fucking progress.
She's not conscious,
she's intubated.
She's had a trach
and a lung collapse,
and if she's got
a shred of luck,
the shot she took
to the neck didn't
catch any spine.
(phone ringing)
It wasn't worth it.
Homicide for McNulty
on line two.
Do your job.
Yeah?
Bunk:
So how you doing
with it?
I'll live.
Yeah?
Well, listen, Jimmy,
we had a little
dust-up over here.
Holley mighta beat one of
your girl's CIs on spec.
What is he,
a short guy?
Mumbles a lot?
Yeah, that's him.
You might wanna roll past
and squelch this shit
before it gets outta hand.
Yeah.
- It ain't worth it, man.
- Naw.
It ain't worth it
at 10 times the price.
A fucking cop, man.
A cop!
How stupid
is this motherfucker?!
If you see a bitch
in the car, change it up.
We can go to Orlando
another fuckin' day.
Savino say
he was tryin' to signal,
but he in the dark,
he don't know
where Bey's at,
or where
they comin' from.
Nothin' breakin'
our way, man, damn.
We gotta
burn this shit.
This is cop money,
it's probably marked somehow.
The guns are in the sewer,
Bey's a rock, so that's cool.
But it's the bitch cop.
If she wake up
and start talkin',
she gonna put Little Man
in there, Bey in there.
- What up with Little Man?
- He's scared.
- He shot a cop.
- Fuck.
But I put Bey on that.
What about Savino?
Well, Savino,
he gotta eat the charge,
but he knew that.
So if he keep
his story tight,
he gonna be all right.
Yeah, we knew Orlando was
a snitchin' motherfucker, man.
Fuck him, but this cash
got us caught up.
I know, man,
that's my fault, man.
Bey and Savino came to me
with the idea that, yo,
if they take Orlando,
they can take the cash, too.
I was like, all right,
y'all get your payday.
Yo, how the fuck is Orlando
gonna front this type of cash?
What it say?
I know, I know.
I fucked up, I know.
A'ight, take this trash
outside, fuckin' burn it.
Tell Wee-Bey to clean up
the mess before he jet.
He was throwin' 911
messages to her pager.
I asked him why,
he raised up.
Shit got outta hand.
- Does he know?
- Uh-uh.
Bubbs:
Hey, McNulty, man.
What they doin'
over there, man?
It's fucked up,
they beatin' on me.
Last night,
she got shot.
Bubbs:
Where the fuck
were you at?
- Where were you?
- I was there.
Hey, Bunk.
We got no good latents
on the passenger side door.
What about the dash?
Call the lab.
So, what can I do?
Well, for one thing you can
roll around the projects,
see who's missing.
Who ain't around.
You okay with that?
Yeah, yeah,
I just, um...
I been keepin' it
kinda close, you know?
Ain't been around
the projects much lately,
you know
what I'm sayin'?
You beefin' with
someone down there?
Naw.
No, I'm not
beefin' with...
Eyes open, Bubbs.
For Kima.
Hang loose,
I'll get you a ride.
Where are we
with Savino?
Still MIA.
Enough of
this bullshit.
Well, if he calls me
for anything,
I'll tell him
to turn himself in.
You know
I'm going to do that.
- Not good enough.
- Excuse me?
We need him now.
No, thanks.
Perhaps as
an officer of the court,
- you could endeavor to--
- Ronnie's being polite.
She's a member of your
twisted little tribe,
so she's putting it into
your twisted little language.
Me? I wouldn't wipe my ass
with a Baltimore lawyer,
no offense.
None taken.
I mean, I'm willing
to let you little ratfuckers
suborn perjury,
and blow smoke up
a judge's ass
and jury-tamper
your balls off
without losing the slightest
bit of my sunny disposition.
And fuck me
if I don't let you
structure your cash
into briefcase fees, either.
That's between you
and the IRS.
And neither one of you
is anybody's friend, right?
I think what Jimmy
is trying to say is--
No, what Jimmy is saying is
if you want me to keep my nose
closed to your shit,
then you're gonna have to
throw me something
when I need it,
and right now
I need Savino Bratton
in bracelets.
I don't know
where he is.
Well, you repped him
the last four felonies.
I'm guessing you can get word
to him if you want to.
A police may die, Maury,
and Savino was there.
He comes in
this afternoon
he takes the drug charge
at least.
Or what?
Or we send tactical
teams into his momma's
house every night,
till there's no house
left to worry about.
And you get a target
letter from the state's
attorney's office,
followed by subpoenas for
every fucking bank account
in your fucking name
and let's see if all
those cash deposits
match the reported income.
I'm hearing this
from him,
and I understand
that he's distraught.
I understand that.
Am I hearing this from
the state's attorney's
office as well?
You are.
I'll see
what I can do.
Fuck you, Jimmy!
You didn't tell me
that was coming.
He'll bring him in.
He will if he can,
that's not the point.
Well, what's the point?
The point is that Maury Levy
is a past officer
of the Monumental
Bar Association,
and unless I want
to spend my whole life
as a fucking ASA,
I can't spend my afternoons
pissing on people who matter.
Another career
in the balance.
- Fuck you.
- No, fuck you.
If only half you
motherfuckers in the state's
attorney's office
didn't want
to be judges,
didn't want to be partners
in some downtown law firm,
if half of you had the fucking
balls to follow through,
you know
what would happen?
A guy like that
would be indicted,
tried and convicted.
And the rest of 'em
would back up enough
so we could push
a clean case or two
through your courthouse.
But no,
everybody stays friends.
Everybody gets paid.
And everybody's got
a fucking future.
You'll just use anyone,
won't you?
So, I've been
searchin' the logs
for pager hits that used
an 0-7 code, right?
It comes up now and then
on D'Angelo's pager.
Stringer's too,
but less often.
Most of the time,
there's nothing
to place the guy,
but check it.
And this is
on Stringer's page?
It comes back to the pay
phone in the emergency room
at Maryland
General Hospital.
Let me guess.
The date of this page
is the same day that
Stinkum got killed.
And Wee-Bey
got shot in the leg.
That was the talk
on the wire, anyway.
You go
to Maryland General
and pull the ER records
for that morning,
you're gonna find
Wee-Bey in the pile.
0-7 is Wee-Bey,
it's gotta be.
And we have Wee-Bey
and Little Man
at the pay phone
at Park Heights
20 minutes
after the ambush
throwing a page
to Stringer.
We're all over town for
this piece-of-shit Savino.
With ties to
the Barksdale organization?
- Yes, sir.
- What else?
Well, the case
is progressing.
We're starting to glean
some possible shooters
from the wiretap.
You know, I asked
for the controlled buy.
I put one of our people
in harm's way.
So right now
I want to make sure that
we are doing everything.
We are, sir.
We're on it.
Good. The commissioner
wants raids citywide.
Every door
we can take.
Any addresses
we can write on.
Anything connected
to a narcotics case.
CID, Tactical,
the DEUs,
and tomorrow
on the 6:00 news,
we put a lot of fucking
dope on the table.
A lot of it!
Dope on the table?
We need to let them
know who we are.
We can't for
one minute let them
think that this will stand.
The commissioner wants
to send a message, Lieutenant.
You make sure you
and your people
do everything possible
to see that it is heard.
Dope on
the damn table.
Hey, it's like
the man said.
We're letting them
know who we are.
Yeah?
And who the hell
are we?
Again, for the record,
let's make clear
that Mr. Bratton
has not been Mirandized
and that what is said
at this juncture is for
purposes of a proffer.
- Agreed?
- Agreed.
Okay, then.
Here you go.
That's baking soda.
Which Mr. Bratton intended
to sell to Orlando Blocker.
You can keep it
with our compliments.
Where's the money?
Mr. Bratton did not
receive money.
He left it in the car
when he went to retrieve
the sham cocaine.
If you were recording
the transaction,
the tape will
confirm this.
And he wasn't around
for the shooting either.
In fact, he doesn't know
who the shooters are.
Jay:
And God knows he wasn't
in on the setup.
I mean, it was pure dumb
luck that he left them
in an dead-end alley
and they were shot-to-shit
just two minutes later.
This is bullshit!
A police is down.
Mr. Bratton
had no knowledge
that the young woman
was a police officer.
And no intention
of doing anything
other than defrauding
Mr. Blocker of $30,000.
Ms. Nathan?
No charge if he gives
us the shooters.
And if he testifies,
we'll find a way
to squeeze him
into the federal
witness program.
As I indicated,
Mr. Bratton has no idea
who shot Mr. Blocker
or the undercover officer.
Best you can do
is 286-B.
What the hell
is that?
Distribution of sham CDS,
three year maximum,
$5,000 fine.
That's it?
If he took the cash,
we could go to felony
theft or fraud,
but the tape has him
leaving the money.
Three years.
A cop was shot, Maury.
So if we convict,
he'll do every damn day
of the three.
I can do the three,
ain't no thing.
Bunk:
And the $5,000 fine?
Oh, shit,
you still up 25, right?
Nicely done.
Gimme two, yo.
(radio playing)
Damn, Orlando, yo.
I still can't
believe that shit.
Man, all this shit
behind this motherfucker.
Who the fuck was he?
He ran a club
for my uncle, yo.
Yeah?
Yeah, first Stink,
and now him.
Yeah, man, and I heard
the cop's been all in
Savino's shit, too.
- He ain't been around.
- Little Man, neither.
Somebody could get
to cleanin' up shit
around here.
True. You can't just
be goin' around, droppin'
five-O like that, yo.
You know how your uncle
is when people get to
fuckin' up, man.
He start takin'
that shit personal, man.
Look like a couple more
nigga's gonna get dropped.
- Yo, what up?
- You Dee?
Yeah.
They sayin' you need to get
with Stringer, right away, yo.
See? You movin' up
in the world.
As long as you don't fall in
with the trash they takin' out.
Yeah, whatever, nigga.
I'll be right back.
Tower boys
all nervous and shit.
Little Man
ain't post for work.
Ain't answerin'
his page, neither.
See?
I'm not gonna lie.
She's got swelling
around the vertebrae
from a through-and-through,
and some indications
of partial paralysis.
That might go away
when the swelling goes down.
And it might not either.
Her family
is with her.
What the fuck is up
with homicide?
Are we on
the shooters yet?
They're working it hard.
The departmental response
is gonna be to take doors
tomorrow morning.
Citywide.
Every unit, every district
is kicking in
any drug-connected address
they can write on.
We're gonna
do the same.
Lieutenant, is that--
Except...
we're gonna hold back
on the main stash,
the house up in northwest
we tracked off the wire.
For one thing,
we advance this case more
by sitting on that location.
For another,
raids that are too much
on the bulls-eye
will have Barksdale
changing up.
We might blow
the wire altogether.
We got two addresses
in the low-rises
that are probables,
and another two rowhouses
off the avenue
that have been used for stash
as recently as last week.
But this...
this here is the best bet
for a good rip.
Herc picked up
on it yesterday.
Fourth-floor,
end unit on the south side
of the 221.
They're droppin' the re-ups
out the window
to the hoppers
who run it off.
What if they change up
the apartment?
Well, they do that
every day.
Yesterday was the fifth floor
on the north side.
We're gonna have
a man on the church
watching with a cellphone.
They change up,
we call the duty judge
who orally
amends the warrant.
We hit everything
at 1100 hours.
But the squad
that takes the high-rise
needs to stage at 0500.
We need to be inside before
the building even wakes up.
Anyone who wants
to sleep tonight,
he needs to start typing
his ass off right now.
What's up?
Why ain't
the club open?
You goin' with Bey.
Hey, yo, Bey.
Keep it clean.
Don't make no mistakes.
Goin' where?
What the fuck you
waitin' for?
(muffled talking)
Stop bullshittin' me!
The main stash.
He knows we're on it.
He knows
we held it back.
The deputy.
We grab a senator's
bag man in the projects,
he knows that.
State police come in here
with a cooperator,
he knows that, too.
- It's like
fucking clockwork.
- He's got a rat.
Here, in the detail.
In the beginning,
when we started,
Burrell had me.
I pipelined everything
to that motherfucker.
- But now...
- He lost you.
So now he's picked up
someone else.
That's how they do.
(chattering)
(laughing)
Can we talk?
Excuse me a moment,
gentlemen.
It's Burrell, he's gotta
back off already.
What now?
We're on
a prime location.
Barksdale's stash.
Instead of sitting on it
and making cases off it,
he wants us
to write a paper
and take the door.
- Why?
- Dope on the table.
It's a photo op
to make us all feel better
about Kima Greggs
catching a bullet or two.
Oh, Christ.
You need to rip him
a new one, Your Honor.
Uh...
I don't know, Jimmy.
You back on
the ticket, huh?
It was just
the usual bullshit.
They're just, um,
dickin' me around,
trying to get another
black face on the ticket,
make it four-and-one
to even up for the last time.
The governor had to promise
two new appointments,
so now we're back
where we were.
That's all it was.
That's all?
Half-assed hack
politics, Jimmy.
It has nothing to do
with your case.
I need you on this.
So, who's my daddy now?
(music playing)
I just do what the fuck
they tell me, you know?
It ain't on me to know what
the fuck they have in mind.
Look, Bey.
Now it come down
to this crazy shit.
Yo, turn in this alley
right here.
Right there.
♪ What's the sound,
out of bound ♪
♪ Another nigga down and out,
a crackhead with no name ♪
♪ Yo, it's just
an unfriendly game... ♪
What the fuck
you stoppin' for? Go!
♪ Cats keep playin', some got
hit hard and wound up payin' ♪
♪ Out in the field
but the fans keep payin' ♪
♪ Understand what I sayin',
it's just the... ♪
(dog barking)
Inside, man,
let's go.
This dude is crazy.
- Yo, Bey, man.
- Get in, motherfucker.
We ain't got all night
for this shit.
Man, get in here.
Go ahead, man.
What's wrong with you?
Check it out, Dee.
I need you to feed 'em
while I'm gone.
You gonna give 'em
different food for each tank,
too, all right?
But don't worry,
I'm gonna show you
what to do, c'mere.
These are my tetras.
You got Kimmy,
Alex, Aubrey
and Jezebel
in here somewhere.
I don't know,
she think she cute.
You take two pinches
of whatever food
I got next to
each tank.
They set for the day.
You see,
they ain't no problems.
Just beautiful
as hell, Dee.
I'm gonna go upstairs,
and pack some shit.
Yo, Bey!
Where we goin', man?
Philly.
You gonna take
the truck back,
but first I got to go
upstairs, grab some shit,
show you what to do
with my tanks, right?
Philly, yo?
We shot a knocko, Dee.
♪ Different I been told ♪
♪ Shoo-wee ♪
♪ I want some
sugar in my bowl ♪
♪ I want some steam
on my clothes ♪
♪ Maybe I can fix things up,
so they'll go ♪
♪ What's the matter, Daddy ♪
♪ Come on, save my soul... ♪
(sobbing)
♪ I want some sugar
in my bowl ♪
♪ I ain't foolin'... ♪
No Savino,
no Little Man,
no Wee-Bey either.
And the Barksdale kid
from the pit
he's out the mix, too.
You think it was
them that did it?
McNulty:
Wee-Bey, Savino,
Little Man.
Yeah, that's what
we're hearing, too.
We got pick-ups
on these motherfuckers
and miles of
NCIC bullshit.
Warrants
for blood and hair, too.
It's Bey and Little Man,
shooter one and shooter two.
I feel it, Bunk.
Yeah, well, right now,
we need our girl
to wake up and say so.
All right.
You did good, Bubbs.
McNulty, you know, um...
the situation
is different for me.
- I mean, for me, I'm--
- Mount up.
I gotta go.
Prez will
get you a ride, okay?
(helicopter hovering)
Move out.
(tires screeching)
Man:
Five-O, five-O!
- Police, police!
- Go, go, go!
Show your hands,
asshole!
- Down on the ground.
- Move it, move it!
McNulty, Freamon,
check the basement.
- Clear?
- All clear.
- Bathroom's clear.
- Check the mattress.
Check under the bed,
check all the drawers,
check every fucking inch
of this room.
- Got anything?
- No.
- Bingo.
- Look at this.
Got it.
There she goes.
Bag it.
Let's do it.
(cameras clicking)
That's fine
police work, Erv.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what you see on the table
in front of you,
represents our department's
answer to a culture
of death and drugs.
And when an officer
falls in this war,
others stand ready
to take up the challenge
and carry the fight
to the very doorstep
of those responsible.
Now this is only the beginning,
I can assure you.
But today,
a message has been sent.
And believe me,
this message is being
heard loud and clear
by all those who seek
profit and power
in the importation
and sale of illegal drugs.
Slow.
Bullshit on
the McCulloh street phone,
nothing on the towers.
Who's on the rooftop?
No one.
Fuck it.
Wallace: Hey, yo,
where the money, man?
Man:
How much you need?
Wallace:
Yo, the bus cost
like 18, man.
Man:
Your grandma
ain't got it?
Wallace:
I ask her, she gonna try
to stop me from bookin'.
I'm tellin' you, boy,
this country-ass shit
got me all messed up.
I'm sayin' you need to send me
something for the bus, yo.
I'm dyin' here,
all broke and shit.
Man:
Yeah, I feel you.
Well, when do you
want to come home?
Wallace:
When the fucking
money get here.
Man:
All right, I'm gonna
probably send it today.
(machines beeping)
(theme music playing)