This is the second
time this week
I had to pay for a sitter
'cause he was working late.
With all that money you
making, you can afford it?
Lord.
What's up, Bubs?
Hey.
Well, there you go.
- Man: well, what you got?
- I got some starters.
( theme music playing )
* If you walk
through the garden *
* You better
watch your back *
* Well, I beg
your pardon *
* Walk the straight
and narrow track *
* If you walk
through Jesus *
* He'll save your soul
* You gotta
keep the devil *
* Down in the hole
* All the angels sing
* About Jesus' mighty soul
* And they shoot you
with your wing *
* Keep you close
to the Lord *
* Don't pay heed
to temptation *
* Oh, your hands
are so cold *
* You got to
keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole
* Way down in the hole.
My fault, A.
I should've never
left you alone, homie.
Naw, shit.
Man, you ain't pull up
when you did, I'm gone.
Listen, what I want
to know is how the fuck
we come back
on this cocksucker?
We don't.
Not now.
You feel me?
Listen, your advice,
Stringer, your advice
was good advice.
I want to
let you know that.
What I want you
to do now,
I want you to put
the word out there.
I want you to let him know
we willin' to squash this,
if he is.
And then what the fuck
if he ain't?
Naw, this nigga
lives in the town too,
he gonna listen,
if we parlay.
And then when he creep out
of his hole and shit.
- Boom.
- Okay.
- Smoke him.
- Say no more, got you.
- Put that out there, yo.
- A'ight.
What about them
police, though?
They was on your ass
after the game?
Yeah, man,
it was like two cars.
See, if they on you,
then they got a name.
If they got a name,
then they know you
ain't got no license.
Yeah, but they don't want
no traffic charges,
you know what I'm sayin'?
They don't want no humble shit.
I think they was tryin'
to see where I might go.
Where the fuck was you
gonna take their asses?
I was takin' them
to the barbershop.
For real, I was goin'
to get a haircut.
Get a fade?
I know, B, but...
these motherfuckers are on us.
What the fuck?
They always been on us,
we just got to be careful.
Well, you not been
talkin' on any phones.
And you not been
touching any drugs.
And from now on,
you are not doin'
the money runs.
Me and Bey, we gonna
take care of that shit
until this
whole thing cool off.
Let me
get that pager.
Oh, what's up,
you serious?
Serious, I'm gonna get you
a New York supply number only.
Any of these motherfucking
local cats want to talk to you,
they gotta talk to me.
We gotta build
a wall around you, B.
Another month
on a fresh phone?
Yeah, they ripped out
the pay phones in
the low-rises.
Now they're walking
a block or two away.
I'm just asking,
how much longer
until you bring
this case in, Jimmy?
The quicker you can,
the better for everybody.
Yourself included.
Look at this,
Judge Gwynn sends
his regrets.
He can't make lunch.
Like I got the plague
all of a sudden.
There's your new phone,
30 days.
A couple of weeks ago,
when Burrell wanted
to take down the wire,
you were the one
breaking it off in his ass.
Jimmy, Jimmy,
there's a lady here.
Rhonda talks more trash
than both of us, Your Honor.
I have never been anything other
than lady-like, Your Honor.
Detective McNulty
is going out of his way
to insult an officer
of the court.
McNulty,
I hold you in contempt.
Who doesn't?
What's with him?
- You haven't heard?
- No.
What's wrong
with the picture?
- Don't know.
- Phelan isn't in it.
What, he's up
for election?
I thought judges
had 15-year terms.
They do, but Phelan was named
to finish Halpern's term,
which only had
two years left.
So he has to run
on his own in the primary.
What, he's not
on the ticket?
Why the fuck not?
Maybe it's
the company he keeps?
Oh, fuck.
No, see, you ain't
thinkin' about
how much room
the baby gonna need.
Especially when
he get to growin',
'cause, I mean, there are
things we got to have.
Like a real crib,
a play desk,
and you know, he got to have
one of them little tyke cars.
I'm not sayin' your place
ain't nice enough.
'cause for you,
it do just fine,
but if we gonna
be a family,
we need at least
one more room,
if not two.
So you add
the bedroom set,
a nice bedroom set
like the one they got
down at that baby store
on Howard Street,
and that's a room
right there.
And I think we might could
get some better furniture
and put your stuff
in the other bedroom,
like it was a den,
'cause the sofa you got
seen better days.
I think you
know that much.
Dee, where you goin' at?
I told you I need money
for the new bedroom set!
- ( door closes )
- Dee!
Man:
Why you holler at me?
Man 2:
Yo, man, we gettin'
down to it.
I get to you
when I get to you.
That's the main
stash house.
Say what?
The incoming call is the guy
who runs the main stash
- for Barksdale's people.
- Who is he?
McNulty
We don't know.
So, you all just guessing
he's on the stash, right?
No, he's on it.
Lester was checking the logs
a couple of weeks ago
when he picked up
the pattern.
Every time they get down
to the ends on a package,
somebody in the tower
hits that pager number.
And then, within a half hour
every fucking time,
a call comes back
to the tower pay phone
from that number
in Pimlico.
Which is?
It's a pay phone
at a Mondo Mart
in Reisterstown
at Cold Spring Lane.
You see it now?
Hmm?
When the supply gets low,
they page this mope,
who always calls back
from a pay phone
way the fuck out
in northwest.
Same phone,
same pattern.
So, y'all think that
he's taking the re-up order
and that the stash is somewhere
near the Mondo Mart, right?
You are on it,
Detective Sydnor.
Okay, so what do
you do with this?
What do we do?
We're gonna be sittin'
on that pay phone in Pimlico
all day and all night,
waitin' on Mr. Mondo Mart.
Herc, too.
Herc's out this whole week.
In-service training.
That's too bad.
So, instead of three
eight-hour shifts,
you two are gonna
have to pull 12 hours.
Just fucking
kill me now.
( chuckling )
Heard from Omar?
Nope.
I'm gonna go try
to scare him up.
Where you gonna be?
Well, everyone on the wire
keeps talking about
how this kid's all tore up
about the dead stickup boy.
- I'm gonna see for myself.
- All right.
You need us,
we're on the radio.
Okay.
( car radio playing )
Hey, what up, man?
This first time,
I can go four ounces of rock.
But hey,
if the shit is right,
then next time
I can step that up.
Almost ain't
worth it for four.
Just this
first go-round.
You do right by me,
I'll turn around
and come back on it.
Where your
money at, man?
We good.
So, where the shit at?
( laughing )
( dog barking )
Woman:
Ain't nobody been there
but you.
Nobody came in my house
- Man: Everybody been.
- Nobody but you.
You're the only person
that came in my house.
So, what you got
goin' for you?
Ain't got nothin' left,
burnt it away.
Family?
Mother dead.
Father, who the fuck know?
Brothers, sisters?
A sister.
She lets me
stay in the basement,
but she lock the door
so I can't go upstairs.
About the best
she can do for me.
I got a kid,
a son.
Imagine me bringing life
into the world.
What's his name?
Keyshawn.
His mother took him up
Jersey way,
said I wasn't fit
to be with the boy.
I ain't disagree.
Well, at least
you got your health.
Ha ha.
Here's to health.
I got the bug.
Had it since '94.
Gave that shit
to my ol' lady.
Worried about passing it on
to my baby girl.
Naw, I was spared
that at least.
Damn, how you carry it?
You ask her
forgiveness?
'Course.
What she say?
What she needed to say.
Look, forgiveness
from other folks is good,
but ain't nothin' but words
comin' at you from outside.
You want
to kick this shit,
you got to forgive
your own self.
Love yourself some,
brother.
And then drag your sorry ass
to some meetings.
- Meetings?
- What the fuck
do you wanna hear?
That you strong enough
to do this by yourself?
Gettin' clean's
the easy part.
Now comes life.
McNulty:
It's this one here
with the orange cord
coming out of the back.
They're pirating juice
from the other house.
You fucking
gotta be kidding me.
Now I'm policing for BG&E?
They're not
there yet.
But when this kid
here posts,
snatch him up.
Park our asses
outside this shit hole
and wait for some little
project yo to raise up?
Mrs. McNulty
raised no fools.
Four Faidley's crabcakes
in the bag,
24 Dutch beers
in the box.
- Faidley's, huh?
- You're alright, McNulty.
I don't care
what all them other fucks
downtown say about you.
11-35,
what's up?
Greggs:
Our friend wants a meet.
Same spot.
Copy that, 15 minutes.
What's the deal
with the yo boy?
What he do?
He stumbled
into my world.
* If you leave,
I'll go crazy *
* If you forget me,
* 'Cause I love you
* You gotta live
for yourself *
* For yourself
and nobody else *
* You gotta live for yourself,
for yourself and nobody else *
* If you leave,
I'll go crazy... *
Five minutes, c'mon.
- I have to go.
- Shardene.
I said,
I have to go.
- I can't have five minutes?!
- No, not right now.
Fuck!
* You gotta live
for yourself *
* For yourself
and nobody else... *
How close
did you get?
Y'all be chalkin'
that nigga
if Wee-Bey ain't pop up
at the last second like.
Remember when
we last talked?
You were gonna lay back,
let us work our case.
I said I'd do
what I can.
Still, I thought
I might let y'all know
Avon's people
got in contact,
talkin' about they want
to end the beef.
They offered me
some kind of amnesty.
Amnesty?
Look, I chill out
on the manhunt
and stop hittin' them
in the head for they product.
They gonna
call off the bounty.
Take the truce, Omar.
I might, if they ain't
tryin' to play me.
They said they want
to parley on it.
- Parley?
- Look, I don't know, man,
but right now I need
some assistance from y'all.
Yo, son, I go to the ER
and word get back to Avon,
you know he gonna
have his henchmen
waitin' in
the parking lot for me.
Look, I know y'all friendly
with a couple of doctors, right?
Right?
He says
he can buy weight.
Says he runs with
some decent-size locals.
Like who?
Avon something...
Barksdale.
Avon Barksdale.
Run it through
the Dex and HIDTA,
see what comes back.
All right,
I'm gonna check around,
see if anybody's working
these names you're giving us.
And if you full of shit, pal,
I'm gonna know it quick.
But, what happens to me
while you checkin'?
Eager Street.
City jail,
motherfucker.
Philip came home
last week.
I ain't seen him
since Afram. Uh-huh.
Yep.
I can't believe it.
( belches )
Damn, Carv,
you's triflin'.
Yeah, I admit it,
I'm disgusting.
Cheese Puffs
and fuckin' Ring-Dings?
Yeah.
( phone ringing )
The big fuck
from the high-rise,
what's his name?
- Little Man.
- Yeah, him.
All right.
( phone ringing )
Yo.
Be ready,
we're on it.
Look at this
pretty motherfucker.
Too fucked up
to drive home, McNulty?
Hey, Bunk.
Kid gave us
a murder.
More than that,
he's put in Stringer Bell.
Oh, yeah?
Picks out Wee-Bey, Bird
and Stinkum from photo arrays.
Puts them all up
at the Greek's
the night they grab up
Omar's boy Brandon.
Puts Bell
in the truck, too.
Says Stringer told him
to point out the stickup boy.
Geez, what do you
have over him?
Not a fucking thing.
Kid was ready,
barely had to push him.
Whose case?
Norris's.
How old?
16.
Lives in a shit-hole vacant
over on Argyle.
When I grab him up,
I swear he's halfway
into a nod.
- Using?
- Hmm.
When they killed
the stickup boy,
the motherfuckers dumped
the body in the alley
right behind where this kid
and all the other
low-rise hoppers
lay their heads.
Can you imagine?
All he can think about.
You tell him he's gonna
have to testify?
Not yet,
we'll get there.
Problem is, what do
I do with him now?
( camera clicking )
( phone ringing )
Yep.
Big boy picking up.
Okay.
You holler at me, right?
Where you at, man,
we all the way down.
First thing tomorrow, man.
- ( phone ringing )
- Yeah?
- It's him, stay on it.
- All right.
I didn't do nothing, man.
Get me outta here.
Man on radio:
The two-two grounded
slowly towards third
and gets foul
at the last moment.
Suzuki's at the plate,
here's the pitch.
Line drive, up the middle,
a base hit for Suzuki.
Suzuki's very patient
at the plate.
Yeah, man, it's me.
Guess who's up in here.
Pimpin' ass Orlando,
from the club.
Yeah.
Courtside.
( beeping )
Daniels:
So how long
you been slingin'?
Since I was,
maybe, 12.
And how long were you
with Barksdale's crew
in the low-rises?
With D'Angelo?
Not long.
He came down from the towers
at the beginning of the summer.
Before that I worked
for Ronnie Mo.
D'Angelo ever talk
to you about
what happened in
the 221 building?
With Pooh getting shot?
How about anything else
like that?
Like what?
Killings, murders.
He say anything about
a girl getting shot
in an apartment up
on the eastside?
He--
naw, Dee,
he was good to me.
He all right.
But D'Angelo, he was
who you called that night
when you saw the stickup boy
at the Greek's, right?
Yeah, but he didn't
go up there.
It was mostly
those tower boys.
And Stringer.
You said Stringer
was in the truck.
He called you over,
asked you to point out
the stickup boy.
All of it corroborated
by the beeper logs
and the pen registers
from the project pay phones.
Stinkum's dead.
We've already got Bird
for the Gant killing.
- This ties them all in.
- D'Angelo, too.
Maybe, but since he didn't
show at the Greeks,
he takes the stand
and tells the jury he didn't
see the murder coming.
Well, it's enough
to charge him, anyway.
- Parents?
- Alcoholic mother.
In the wind,
no fixed address.
Says he's got a grandmother
down on the eastern shore,
- but he hasn't
seen her in years.
- How about a hotel room?
On whose dime?
No way the deputy
approves the manpower
to stash a 16-year-old,
much less
the room service.
McNulty, line two.
How about you run this
up to front office?
See if the state's attorney
will kick in.
He's a kid, Cedric.
Even if
we clear the money,
do you really want
to put a juvenile
in a hotel for six months
waiting on a trial date?
I think you all need
to get with grandma
down on the shore.
Now?
She's doing this
right now?
They don't have to
set a hearing date
or something like that?
Christ, yeah, okay.
Yeah.
I fucking need
a fucking lawyer.
What?
Still, you can see that
they got the security bars.
And look there.
Cameras...
that see over the yard
out to the street.
And I checked
with Verizon,
there's no phone service
at that address.
Well, that's a telltale
right there.
So what?
We try to write a warrant
for this place, right?
Right?
What are you seeing?
No pattern, really.
Except this cluster
of old storefronts
and warehouses on
the westside of downtown.
Around Paca, Eutaw,
Howard Street, mostly.
- Storefronts?
- Vacants, usually.
Three different
holding companies.
Detective Prezbylewski.
What?
You have a gift
for the paper trail.
Tomorrow calls for
some street work, though.
Are you street ready?
Um, you know the lieutenant
has me in-office.
I don't have my gun
until the grand jury.
- You won't need one.
- On the street?
- No gun?
- No gun.
Not for this.
Furthermore, Mr. McNulty,
having utilized his sons
in an act of police work,
involving a criminal suspect,
actually lost track of them
in a crowded municipal market.
This is simply unacceptable,
Your Honor.
Be that as it may,
an emergency ex parte order
is an extraordinary
request, Mr. Palmer.
You actually want me
to limit visitations
to afternoons only
and you want
Mrs. McNulty present
at all visitations?
Come on.
Palmer: It is not
a single lapse, Judge.
Mr. McNulty
has time and again
failed to properly care
for the children
when they're
in his custody.
I have a list of recent
events, Your Honor,
that justify an order.
Ms. Pearlman
do you have a response
you'd like to offer up here?
Nope.
Nothing?
If this were
possession with intent,
I'd be a prosecutor
with a plan.
But a domestic
order hearing?
Your Honor,
I'm officially clueless.
In fact, as an employee
of the state,
I should not
actually be here.
All right,
listen up, people.
Before you have
me make a ruling
on an emergency petition,
everybody here just needs
to take a deep breath, huh?
Literally, come on.
( breathing deeply )
Now, then,
is Mr. McNulty capable
of having a civil conversation
with Mrs. McNulty?
Yes, Your Honor.
And is Mrs. McNulty
equally capable
of having a conversation
with Mr. McNulty?
Yes.
Good, then
I'm going to lunch.
And let's see when I return
if we can't busy this court
with something just
a little more engaging
than the problems
of the McNultys.
Look, the charge
is on me.
I understand that,
I'll carry that.
But the least
our people can do
is throw down a little
something to pay the bondsman.
That's the deed
of transfer for the club.
And the other thing
is a license transfer
application
for the liquor board.
They're both backdated
and notarized for last week.
What?
A front
has to be clean.
And right now,
you ain't that.
Sign.
I want my bail paid.
You send me a bondsman,
I'll sign.
Is that what you
want me to tell him?
That I asked you to sign
and you wouldn't?
Hmm?
You wanted to be
in the game, right?
Now you're
in the game.
Unbelievable,
you show up with her ?
Elena, you went for
an emergency ex parte.
I grabbed whatever lawyer
was standing around.
Oh, she was standing?
Hey, ask her if she wants
the pictures back.
Let's see, I've got her
at the restaurant
with you
pulling out her chair.
I've got her at
the motel parking lot
with you opening
the car door for her
because you're such
a fucking gentleman now.
Yeah, well, I can't
believe you hired Buckman.
Son of a bitch never made
a case that counted.
Yeah, well he caught
your cheating ass.
Elena,
why are we here?
Because you can't--
you can't have
Sean and Michael
around criminals.
You can't lose them
in a Baltimore market.
- That's why.
- It wasn't a criminal.
I know the guy.
It was a game
we were playing.
It was daylight
on a crowded street.
They could've been
following Al Capone.
It would've been fine.
Look, Elena,
these are my sons.
I love them.
Do you hear?
I'm not gonna
let them get hurt.
I love you, too.
I still do.
Does she know
about the detective
and the pictures?
No, why would
I tell her about that?
And are the two
of you still...
No.
Yes.
A little.
Come on, let's make nice
for the judge.
Okay.
Man on TV :
We know we have
a month more to go
and we're not
gonna let up.
We are going to raise more,
we are going to spend more,
and on election day,
we are going to be out there,
pushing the vote
in every precinct.
You ready?
Come on, we'll get
dinner first.
Ain't so hungry.
Come on.
How much
were you using?
I'm asking if you're
gonna be sick in my car.
A cap now and then.
You just snorting?
You'll be all right
in a day or two.
Come on.
Yo, this nigga comin'
or what, man?
Said he would,
if I guaranteed a parley.
And I'm here on it.
'Course, he said y'all
would be paying my fee,
rather than his ownself.
Your fee?
I'm doin' like one of them
marriage counselors.
Charge by the hour
to tell some fool
he need to bring
some flowers home.
Then charge another hour
tellin' the bitch
she ought to suck some cock
every little once and a while.
You know, keep a marriage
strong like that.
Speakin'
of cocksuckers.
Don't believe we met.
Proposition Joe.
You ever steal from me,
I kill your whole family.
All right. Y'all both here
on my guarantee,
so respect that shit
and say what you feel.
I'm up outta here.
I gotta man who say he gonna
give you your life back, yo.
Who, Barksdale?
My man say,
tell that motherfucker that
if he can find a way
not to dip in our pockets,
we're gonna call
this shit even.
Y'all aced Bailey,
and what you did to my boy?
So, y'all think after
what you did to Brandon,
we supposed to find
some even on this, huh?
Yo, I don't know
shit about shit, a'ight?
I'm just the messenger.
Whatever, man.
You know there's dead
on both sides, right?
And there's gonna be
a whole lot more
if this beef keep up.
But the truth be told,
there be more soldiers
in one half than the other.
You know what
I'm sayin'?
Hey, look here, son,
you tell Barksdale,
that he's been paid back
for what he did to my peoples.
But as for
his product,
well, a man's got to
earn a living, you know?
I don't know nobody
called Barksdale, B.
The man
I'm talking about,
can't have his shit
taken like that.
That won't do.
A'ight, tell him
throw me some cash then,
and we'll see.
'Bout five
or 10,000.
You know what I mean?
For my retirement, homes.
Five if you can
keep quiet about it.
Send my money
through Joe, man.
You go through Joe,
you're not gonna see
2,000 of that.
Why don't you tell
my man where you at--
Naw, naw, naw, naw.
We gonna figure something
else out, you heard?
I'll be in touch, homes.
How careful
is Stringer Bell?
"I don't know no one
named Barksdale."
Shit.
Still we got him tied
to the Brandon killing.
That can be enough
for one day's work.
Did what I could
for y'all.
You sure, right?
Yeah, I spent a summer here
when I was nine.
When was the last time
they saw you?
When I was nine.
( crickets chirping )
- What's that?
- What?
That noise.
It's crickets.
Cricket.
Crickets.
He tried to go
in my pockets again ?
This nigga talkin'
'bout five Gs, B.
Oh, shit.
( knocking )
Oh, what's up, baby?
Antwon said
to bring these up.
- Y'all want anything else?
- Naw, we cool.
I'm sayin' though,
how we supposed to pay that?
He talking about
goin' through Joe,
but I'm like, fuck Joe.
Hey, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Thank you, mon amie.
You look good
and your services
are appreciated.
Keep them tips.
I hope you makin'
them, baby.
Avon:
Make the motherfucker
come down to the towers
to get the rest
of his money, you know
what I'm sayin'?
If he stupid enough
to come down to the towers,
he gonna get got.
It's a wrap, pow.
How you supposed
to pay that?
A'ight.
Y'all think you can hang,
but, look.
No, no, no, you see,
I went to journalism school.
All right?
Northwestern.
So, y'all can't stay
with me on this.
Girl, you talkin' like
you some crusty old reporter.
Well, excuse me?
Bitch, you work
at a TV station.
It's the same thing,
all right?
Look, come on,
stop talkin'.
Here we go.
- Bring it.
- Come on, Kima.
Come on.
I gotta work tomorrow.
All: Aw!
Candy ass.
That's all
I have to say.
Okay, you see?
- I'm with you.
- All right.
Look at Tonya.
And she run a damn
art gallery.
You see, police in
this town ain't about shit.
- Guess not.
- Mm-hmm, thank you.
- Can't hold our liquor.
- Mm-mmm.
Can't hold a donut.
( laughing )
And if you ask me,
I guess we...
ain't good in bed,
neither.
Oh, don't go there,
Officer.
Don't go there.
Kima, how did you know
you wanted to be a cop?
I mean, how did
you choose that?
When you were little, did you
think about it at all, or...
Come on, Kima.
I remember when I was
in the northeast,
still field-training
as a cadet.
I didn't know if I was gonna
stick with it or not.
And then we got
this one call.
We chased this purse-snatch
up into these apartments.
I got separated
from my FTO
and shit, I ain't
even no police yet.
You know,
I'm just a trainee.
And I'm alone.
Anyway, I mean,
I don't know how,
but I find the guy.
So I catch him
and I hold on to him
and I manage
to get to my radio.
And we in the middle
of this parking lot,
and we're rolling
around and shit
and this motherfucker's
steady kicking my ass
trying to get away.
And I look over and I see
these black patents,
and these uniform
blue pants.
I look up
and it's Charlie Smoot.
Charlie fucking Smoot.
You know, this guy's a legend.
He looks down at me
and he smiles,
you know
real quiet-like.
And he drops his cuffs.
He says,
"Here ya go, rook."
That's all he says.
And then he dropped
the bracelets and walked away.
I mean, I know
you don't like it.
But, shit,
I was proud.
Ooh.
Goddamn.
Lester says we ain't gonna
write a warrant on this place.
How do we not
with all this PC?
Greggs:
We're on the main stash,
right?
Why would
we kick the door in
when all we have to do
is park a van down the street
and follow the entire
westside drug supply in
and out of the place?
We're gonna start picking up
pieces of Barksdale's world
we never even
knew about.
Been hell looking
for you people.
What the hell's the name
of this unit anyway?
- What up, Wig?
- Aw, shit, Kima in the house.
- What's up, girl?
State police, CID
out of Pikesville.
Name of Troy Wiggins.
But pay no attention
to the man,
'cause he about
90-95% pure bullshit.
Kima, she just
talk like that
'cause I had her
when she was good.
Shit, you
the ugly-ass motherfucker
- turned me the other way.
- Shit, a'ight.
Here's the thing,
boys and girls.
I'm doin' a reverse buy
down in Arundel, right?
And I get this
westside asshole nibbling
on four ounces, right?
- A whole four ounces?
- I know, he ain't much, but...
I get him in the boat
and he starts floppin' around
sayin' he can buy weight
from some motherfucker
name of Barksdale.
I never heard
of no Barksdale.
But I put
the name into Dex,
and the computer
has Avon Barksdale entered
as an active
Baltimore City target.
So, I go down to city
narcotics and Dawson,
he sends me down here
to see y'all.
So, what's the name
of your fish?
Wendell O, as in,
Oh-Shit-I-Tried-To-Buy
From-A-State-Police Blocker.
That wouldn't be
Wendell Orlando Blocker
would it?
Yeah.
You on it.
Orlando.
They keep that
back room locked.
And even if I do get
back there on an errand,
then they
kinda shut down.
They get real quiet.
You said you heard
one say something
about making someone
come into the towers.
- Yeah.
- Which one was talking?
He was tall,
I think.
All right,
but who else was there?
I don't really see that well
without my glasses.
Where are
your glasses?
You can't see faces
without those?
You don't wear those
while you're working,
do you, darlin'?
Would you?
I gotta live off
drinks and tips.
- No way!
- Why not?
Because a player
wouldn't be the name
on the liquor license.
And a player would
have a connect for
Barksdale's coke.
He wouldn't walk
into state troopers.
He caught a charge and now
he's talking out his ass.
I mean, face it.
You're never gonna
get Avon or Stringer
in the same room
as the dope.
We'll make this case
on their voices alone.
So, maybe he can't
buy from Barksdale.
Maybe he can only buy
from Savino or Wee-Bey.
Greggs:
Well, fuck him, then.
We already got Wee-Bey
tied to a murder
and Savino's the runt
of the litter.
We can take what Orlando
gives us about the club.
The money laundering,
maybe, or the girls.
For that kind
of cooperation,
I'll drop a few years
and call it fair.
( knocking )
- Daniels in here?
- Yeah.
Call from Deputy
Commissioner for you.
You want it in here?
No.
He doesn't miss much.
( pager beeping )
I need
some help here.
Come on, Bubs
You got me comin'
across town
in the middle
of a fucked-up workday
just so you can hold 10?
That shit ain't right.
Hold on,
I don't need 10.
Okay, I don't know.
I need a place
of my own.
All right, some bed,
some sheets, some clothes.
I definitely need
some new clothes.
How long you been clean?
Three days.
You serious about it?
Who knows?
What the fuck am I gonna do
with a clean informant?
Did you think
about that?
A'ight,
I'm on it with you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yo, what the fuck,
gimme some love.
Okay, I mean,
I think I can get,
you know, a mattress,
my own place,
everything for like
a couple hundred dollars.
A'ight.
We'll talk.
I gotta be somewhere tonight,
so hit me on my page tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I got you.
The cooperator says
he can buy weight.
Daniels:
Not from Barksdale
or Bell.
How can you be sure?
How much dope or coke
do you think
gets Avon Barksdale
into the room?
A kilo?
Two kilos,
20 kilos?
We are not going to buy
our way up the ladder here.
These people
do not touch the drugs.
They don't go near
the drugs.
The wire is what
gives us Barksdale.
It gives us
the whole crew.
Day by day,
piece by piece.
Buy-bust, Lieutenant.
It's what I asked
you for months ago.
It's what we do
successfully
time and again
to make these cases.
Why New York?
Must be somethin'
happenin' out there, man.
Too big a town,
you know what I mean?
You don't believe
in the truce?
That's why I asked
for that money.
If he had said,
"We ain't paying you.
Just be happy to live,"
I'd have been like,
a'ight they keepin' it real.
But he say, c'mon down
for $5,000,
I'm, like, man, please.
Hey, look here, homes,
I ain't asked for much,
but, um, I'm a little light
on traveling money.
I'm sayin' I could go around
the block and get myself paid,
but I'm thinkin'...
You keep in touch
with my pager.
We're gonna need you
for the Gant trial.
Go easy, Omar.
Stay free!
Man on tape:
You be pickin' me up outside
the Cut-Rate on Lex and Fulton.
I'll be up there
after 10:00, right?
Man 2:
That'll work.
Listen up, people.
We've got 30,000
in buy money
courtesy of our friends
over at DEA,
but the thing is,
they can't have that
money walkin' on them.
Definitely not.
So Kima will be
in the car for the buy,
fronting as our CI's girl.
Lookin' the part, too.
( laughs )
Now, where's your
weapon gonna be?
He might pat me,
so it has to stash
in the car.
I figure when Savino
gets in the car
at the Cut-Rate,
I'll be going in back.
It'll be up under
the rear seat.
And we probably
can't be close enough
for an eyeball on this,
but the car
will be a live wire
and Kima will be throwin' us
20s whenever she can.
Rhonda?
I only want to remind
Mr. Blocker here
that his plea agreement
is contingent on cooperation.
A buy-bust on Savino Bratton
is less cooperative
than a buy-bust from someone
higher up on the food chain.
If you can get Savino
talking about Avon or Stringer,
that's better for us
and better for you.
They already know
that he got jacked
on a reverse buy, right?
Why wouldn't they assume
he's snitchin'?
I need money
for a lawyer, right?
That's the story.
He got popped
and now he needs
to get right back into it
to pay the bondsman
and the lawyer.
All right.
Let's make this work.
Careful.
That's my career
you're holding there.
- You got a unit?
- Parked in the mezzanine.
- Gimme the keys, man.
- Naw, I'm driving,
motherfucker.
Come on, man.
Death row here.
Ain't up.
Death row.
( car radio playing )
That's my girl.
Half the money hers.
( turns up radio )
Baby, since we goin'
down North Avenue,
stop by the carry-out
so I can pick me up
some cigarettes.
They're goin' up North,
stay loose.
( turns up radio )
- Shit.
- It's too loud.
Does any unit
have the eyeball?
Negative, 11-35.
C'mon, Greggs, tell us
where the fuck you are.
Pull in there.
What?
( music stops )
( baby crying )
Don't fuck
with this count.
I'll be right back
with your shit.
Where are we?
That sign said Longwood,
but I could swear
this was Warwick.
Hoppers be turning
the sign poles
to fuck with y'all.
I make it we're on
the north side of Warwick,
in an alley.
I don't know, shit,
half of block west
of Longwood, maybe?
I hope y'all
copy that.
Yeah, that puts us
about eight blocks away.
I'm pushing in
a little closer.
All units be advised.
Warwick near Longwood
in the northside alley
or near that 20.
Greggs:
This got the right
feel for you?
- ( starts engine )
- You creepin' closer?
He better not be long,
'cause, see, I don't know
where the stash is,
and if they draggin'
us all over this part
of town, you know--
What's that?
- What?
- Something ain't right.
- Shit ain't right.
You snitchin'
motherfucker.
- ( gunshots )
- Signal 13, signal 13!
- Gunshots, gunshots.
- Shit.
- McNulty: 11-35.
- Man on radio: 11-35.
McNulty:
Signal 13, Warwick
near Longwood, officer down.
Greggs:
Two males, black hoodie,
both of 'em. One is--
- ( gunshots )
- Signal 13.
Warwick, near Longwood
in the alleys.
Check the alleys!
Northside,
2800 block.
- Nothing.
- Jesus.
McNulty:
We got an officer down.
she's a number one.
- Two of 'em undercover.
- ( siren blaring )
Radio
89-33, 3100 block
of Baker clear.
- 2900 is dark.
- ( tires screeching )
Woman on radio: Unit 35,
10-38 is responding.
10-4.
11-71, does anyone
have a visual?
Does anyone have
a visual?
- Foxtrot.
- What are we lookin' for?
11-35 to KGA.
We can't find
the officer down.
We need Foxtrot
looking for a green
Lincoln Town Car
with a brown vinyl roof
parked in those alleys.
Foxtrot:
Foxtrot en route,
3-1-4.
Woman on radio:
3-14, be advised,
we have a signal 13.
Foxtrot:
70-20, rear odd-side.
3300 block of Baker,
clear.
Visual, rear even-side
of Warwick and Longwood.
( police radio chatter )
Foxtrot:
SUV west on Warwick,
make the next right.
Be advised,
no movement at scene.
( sirens blaring )
She's here!
Get a medic!
( helicopter hovering )
We got an officer down.
We need a medic!
( police radio chatter )
Fuck!
Where the fuck
is the medic?!
Signal 13!
We got an officer down!
Woman on radio:
10-38 is responding.
( sirens blaring )
Man on radio:
Do we have a description?
Woman on radio:
Any unit on scene,
do you have a description
of the suspect?
That's a 10-47.
( theme music playing )