♪ Timmy is an average kid ♪
♪ And no one understands ♪
♪ Mom and Dad and Vicky
always giving him commands ♪
Bed, twerp!
♪ Doom and gloom
up in his room ♪
♪ Is broken instantly ♪
♪ By his magic little fish
who grant his every wish ♪
♪ 'Cause in reality,
they are his Odd Parents ♪
♪ Fairly Odd Parents ♪
Wands and wings!
Floaty crowny things!
♪ Odd Parents,
Fairly Odd Parents ♪
♪ Really mod, pea pod,
buff bod, hotrod ♪
Obtuse, rubber goose,
green moose, guava juice,
giant snake, birthday cake,
large fry, chocolate shake!
♪ Odd Parents,
Fairly Odd Parents ♪
♪ It flips your lid when you're
a kid with Fairly Odd Parents ♪
Yeah, right.
♪ Bop! ♪
"Dear Trixie Tang,
"instead of going
to the big school dance
"with somebody handsome
and popular,
"how about going with me,
Timmy Turner,
"the least popular
and handsome guy you know?
Think of how good you'll look
next to me in comparison."
Well? What do
you guys think?
( cackling )
Man, no matter how hard I try,
I can't write a good letter.
Well, forget
the mushy stuff.
Try a threat.
What?!
Watch.
"Dear Trixie,
we have your parents.
If you ever want
to see them again..."
FATHER:
Timmy...
( doorknob jiggling )
My parents!
Activate fish mode!
Hi, sweetie.
What are you doing?
Hey,
you're writing
a threatening love note.
That's how I met your mom.
BOTH:
"If you ever want
to see your parents again..."
( both laughing )
You know, I never
did get that ransom.
It's not a love note.
I'm trying to invite a girl
to a dance.
But you've got to
let her know it
in a sweet,
romantic, nice way.
That's moderately
threatening.
If there's one thing
girls love more
than being told they're pretty,
it's being told they're prettier
than other girls.
FATHER:
Well, than mention her hair.
It's so much shinier
than yours, honey.
"And your hair,
which is so much
shinier than
my mom's."
And her eyes, honey.
Tell her that
her eyes resonate
with a depth
of intelligence
that greatly surpasses yours.
"And your eyes--
shining, intelligent,
"deep and limpid pools
of shining love light...
Gooey, gooey,
gooey, lovey, goo."
But-But-But I wouldn't say
any of that mushy gunk.
And that's why
you don't have a date.
Hmm. This is still
missing something.
The threatening reason
that'll make her say yes.
"Say yes, and I promise the
safe return of your parents."
And our work
here is done.
Let's leave Timmy
alone so I can
talk to you more
about my not-so-limpid eyes
and my not-so-shiny hair.
Okay. I-I...
I'm in trouble, aren't I?
Let's go.
Wow. That's the most beautiful,
romantic, touching
and slightly threatening E-mail
I've ever read.
COSMO:
It's threatening and romantic.
It's threatmantic!
And horrifyingly
embarrassing.
But Timmy, I thought
you really felt that way
about Trixie.
Actually, my love for her burns
with the white hot intensity
of a thousand suns.
But I can't tell her that.
But I can.
Thanks to my parental
battering ram.
It's the latest thing
in tough love parenting.
"Burns for you...
intensity...
thousand suns."
Send!
( musical tones play )
FEMALE VOICE:
Message sent.
Hey, why'd you do that?
If I have to be miserable
because of your letter,
so do you.
MOTHER:
Get back here.
Still in trouble.
Got to go.
Aah!
Dad sent my
threatmatic E-mail.
I wish the
E-mail was back.
Make it come back!
BOTH:
We can't get it back!
Why not?
It's a love letter.
And our magic can't interfere
with true love.
If you guys can't bring it back,
there's only one thing to do.
I wish
I was inside the Internet!
( whirring )
( ding )
You want us
to come with you?
( voice echoing ):
And leave
the computer vulnerable
so my dad can send
more stupid letters
that you can't help me with?!
No way.
I wish you guys would stay here
and guard this computer
no matter what.
Got it?
Got it.
Did you really need
to wave your wands for that one?
( both muttering )
BOTH:
No.
Now attach me to an E-mail.
( ding )
( whirring )
Let's get digital.
Your message has been sent.
( beeping )
Cool.
I'm surfing the Web.
Literally.
There it is, my E-mail.
Sir? Oh, sir?
Got it. Whoa.
Whoa!
( musical notes play )
You've got mail.
Oh, no you don't.
All I have to do
is delete this thing.
"Dear A.J., thank you
for allowing us
"to scrape some
of your brain cells
"for our cloning program.
"Stay smart!
Your friend,
The President."
Wait a minute.
This is a letter for A.J.
I'm in A.J.'s room.
Oh, man, I must have followed
the wrong letter.
So, Doctor,
if you attach the seed thrower
to the back of your satellite,
it'll plant seeds
while it orbits the earth,
thus ending world hunger.
That's brilliant, A.J.
NASA thanks you,
and the World thanks you.
And...?
And the money has been placed
in your account.
Well, time to check my E-mail.
Hey, something opened my letter
from the President.
Is that a computer virus?
I got to get of here.
( door thumping,
doorknob jiggling )
A.J.'s MOM:
A.J.?
( gasps )
( buzzer sounds )
( whirring )
( loud knocking on door )
A.J.'s MOM:
A.J., I'm both respecting
your privacy
by knocking
but asserting my authority
as your mother
by coming in anyway.
Honey, you really should think
about redecorating.
Ah-hoo!
Rats. At cyber speed,
I can use the worldwide Web
to be anywhere in the world
in the blink of an eye.
Wow.
I'm in Australia.
Crikey, is that
a computer virus?
I'm in the heart of Africa.
Lyle, Kevin--
a computer virus!
Good heavens, Bruce,
the humans must have discovered
the location
of our secret society
of super intelligent gorillas!
Well, if it's so
secret, how did
they discover it?
You know, Lyle,
he's got a point.
Oh, get off
my back, Bruce!
Chinese letters.
Technology's amazing.
I'm as far away from home
as physically possible,
and I got here in a millisecond.
Golly, good thing this
Chinese restaurant
is only three steps
away from house.
That'll be $7.95.
Here a fortune cookie.
"Confucius say,
'You will use a battering ram
to violate your son's privacy.'"
Well, okay.
I don't want
to make Confucius a liar.
( knock at door )
FATHER:
Oh, Timmy?!
Oh, no!
It's Timmy's dad's eye!
I'm respecting your privacy
by knocking,
but asserting my authority
as your father
by coming in anyway.
( in Timmy's voice ):
Do you mind?
I'm doing
my homework.
In the bathroom?
But that's where I pay my bills.
WANDA:
He's coming in!
What do we do?
Pull my wand.
( sniffs )
Whoa! What is your mother
feeding you?
Uh, I'll use the computer later.
Let me know when you're done.
I need to look for a contractor
to fix this wall.
Oh, man, this light speed
searching is cool and all,
but there are too many places
to look.
And I got
to find Trixie's computer
before she opens
my threatmatic E-mail.
You've got mail.
From a desperate boy!
I should just delete this,
but that would be rude.
I like to personalize
my rejections.
MAN ( knock at door ):
Trixie,
I'm both respecting your privacy
by knocking,
but asserting my authority
as your father
by coming in anyway.
Phone for you!
Whoa, this place is creepy.
Where am I?
What's with all
the fairy pictures?
"www.fairies'r'real.wand?"
A photo of me
on a fairy Website?
Cool. I'm being downloaded.
I mean, oh, no,
I'm being downloaded.
( beep )
Huh? Wait a second.
"Nutjob replaced
"at New Baltimore
Community College
"for using funds to build a trap
for fairy godparents.
"Crazy single Caucasian male
"seeks equally crazy
single female to discuss belief
that fairy godparents exist."
Oh, my gosh!
I'm must be in the computer!
My crazy fairy-believing
teacher, Mr. Crocker!
Yes, I'm Mr. Crocker.
Using my new website
at fairiesarereal.wand
we'll soon have gathered
enough evidence to prove
the existence of...
fairy godparents!
Ah! I better hide!
I must record this glorious
moment for posterity!
I shall record this
for future generations
so that all may learn...
WOMAN:
Denzel!
Denzel Crocker?!
I'm both respecting
your privacy by knocking,
but asserting my authority
as your mother
by coming in anyway.
Could you stop with the crazy
long enough to help Mommy?
Mother, stop
interrupting!
Can't you see
I'm busy...
ranting?!
But you need to put on
this rubber dress so I can hem
it for the big dance tonight!
I hate modeling
your dresses!
Although it does
make me feel pretty.
Oh, well.
At least no one I know
can see this.
This is gold!
And it's digitally
recorded gold.
I'm saving this.
Oh, no! I pinged!
Hey, who pinged?!
Someone opened my files!
Busted.
Most people would assume
it's the work of a hacker,
but I know some child
must have wished himself
into the Internet
with the help
of his fairy godparents!
Must trace data back to source.
( screams )
Way to bust
a move, son.
Go, Denzel.
COMPUTER:
Must get digital proof
of fairies.
Fairies. Proof of fairies.
Okay, the room's fixed,
and the computer's
still safe.
Now what do you want to do?
Recording proof of fairies.
I don't know.
What do you
want to do?
I don't know.
Let's have a magic fight
just for the heck of it.
Oh, why not?
It's not like anybody
can see what we're doing
in here.
Yeah, it'd sure stink
if somebody was actually
recording this...
and had irrefutable proof
that some kid had...
Fairy godparents! Yes!
Denzel.
Mother.
Excellent.
( laughs )
I, Mr. Crocker, finally have
irrefutable video proof
that fairies exist.
Now all I have to do
is upload this data.
Then, using the Internet,
transmit it to every computer
in the world.
And with the unparalleled speed
of my computer,
it should take no time at all.
COMPUTER:
Download commencing.
One percent.
Yay!
Zero percent.
Boo! Curses, obsolete,
one-month-old technology!
Negative one percent.
Drat!
Look at that massive stream
of e-mail.
Maybe my threatmantic letter's
in there.
Junk mail, junk mail. Oh, man.
My letter isn't anywhere
in this batch.
I'm doomed to be
a total laughingstock.
What happened? Where am I?
( screams )
Trixie?
"Trixie, how are you? Veronica."
Wow! I'm in a chat room
with Trixie and Veronica.
Hey, Veronica, I am
fine and popular.
I'm just about to read
all my e-mail.
No!
Dear Trixie, as
your best friend,
I wish you nothing but happiness
and eternal joy
for your whole life long.
Why can't I be you?!
WOMAN:
Veronica,
dinner.
Don't call me that!
Call me Trixie!
I'm Trixie!
I've got to follow
Veronica's e-mail
back to Trixie's computer.
I'll just send a message,
attach myself to it,
and end up on her screen.
But I have to say something that
she'd expect Veronica to say.
"Do you think Timmy Turner
is neat?"
Do I think Timmy Turner
is neat?
Why? Do you?
Do I think Timmy Turner is neat?
Actually, my love for him burns
with the white-
hot intensity
of 1,000 suns,
but I can't let Trixie
know that.
"No way. He's gross."
Aw, great.
The crazy one likes me.
My letter! Yes!
( laughs ):
This rocks!
I've got my letter,
and I'm not a laughingstock,
and best of all,
for the first time ever,
things didn't fall apart
when I made a big wish.
Finally, I have proof, proof,
of the existence
of fairy godparents!
You guys!
Shh, Mr. Crazy is talking.
Say hi, Timmy.
Shh! If he doesn't know
whose fairies we are,
then we don't have
to go away forever.
Once I upload this video file
of you fairies
and send it to every computer
in the world,
I'll cease being
a laughingstock.
Then I will be the man
who proved that fairies
actually exist.
Cosmo, Wanda,
turn the computer off!
But we've got
to get you out first.
Who did that?
No, now, before he figures out
whose fairies you are.
Um, that's off, right?
Cosmo? Wanda?
Must've destroyed the computer.
Crocker's video footage.
I've got to get it before
it gets back to his computer.
WANDA:
Uh, Dad,
the computer's busted.
( gasps ):
Giga-gasp!
COSMO:
Can you fix it?
Sure. I'll make a new one.
Almost to Crocker's computer.
I must be in Crocker's
hard drive.
Oh, no! Crocker's uploading
the video clip!
COMPUTER:
Now uploading proof of fairies.
One percent,
two percent, three...
( screams )
A firewall!
Ha! Once this upload
is complete,
I've programmed it
to hack into the mainframe
of the Internet and route it
to every computer
and television screen
in the world!
Then everyone will know
that fairies exist!
The pink-hatted computer virus!
I'm ready for you
this time.
Destroy that pink hat!
( screams )
Here's the hard drive.
Here's the monitor.
Here's the keyboard.
And here's the power supply.
Run, Eddie, run!
COMPUTER:
You've got mail.
Ha! I'm a genius.
Now I'm going
to make ice cream
out of birdseed
and gum.
Come on, we got
to find Timmy
in this thing.
I'll never get the footage
with these guys dogging me.
I've got to give 'em
the slip somehow.
( gasps )
Low bandwidth ahead.
That's it!
So long, fellas.
Now to find that video footage.
COMPUTER:
66%. 67%.
Yes. Yes.
Denzel, will you come
and sponge Mommy's feet?
Yes. I mean, no!
79%.
Whoa. I'm in the central hub
of the Internet.
All the data
from around the world goes
in there, gets copied in there,
and gets sent out of there
to every computer in the world.
And that's where
my data is going!
( screams )
COMPUTER:
91%. 92%.
No!
94 percent.
92%. 91%.
Hey, when we went
through the data stream,
we erased some of it.
That's it!
Hey, crockpot-
dot-dork,
hungry for some
information?
Well, come get some.
85%. 79%.
What?
No!
Come on, pal,
I'm right here.
62%. 58%.
I can't get it
to turn on.
( panting )
Huh? Oh, no, not me.
There's no way
I'm going to...
Run, gerbil boy, run!
15%. Six percent.
Upload aborted.
No!
Must send the data again.
Where's that file?
Where is that file?!
Oh, you mean this file?
( complimentary whistle )
Upload commencing. One percent.
What?!
Whoo-hoo!
You've got mail.
Hey, I've got mail.
No, I've got mail.
I'm the alpha male.
Hey, I'm the
alpha male.
It's for you.
I mean, you are
the alpha male.
You've got mail.
( screams ):
Krikey! I knew you'd come home.
Several sightings of the
pink-hatted Internet virus
were reported today,
and in a press release,
authorities stated:
"It does make me feel pretty.
Oh, well, at least
no one can see this."
( laughter )
Oh, the humiliation.
Can this get any worse?
There he is!
This is where
I've traced the source
of the pink-hatted
computer virus.
No, no!
Oh, Denzel,
where did I go wrong?
You've got Timmy.
Guys!
BOTH:
Timmy!
Timmy.
How's the new computer?
( gasps ):
Egad!
You're not supposed to be
on those kinds of Web sites.
But that's my teacher.
Well, it does
make him look pretty.
Nice party, Timmy.
Aren't you upset
that you're here without a date?
Are you nuts?
I got to surf the Internet,
become a virus, humiliate
Crocker on a global scale,
and most importantly,
prevent Trixie
from reading this mushy,
threatmantic letter.
Hey!
Trixie, no, don't!
Oh, Timmy, that's the sweetest,
most threatening thing
I've ever read.
Uh, really?
Sure. And if I didn't think
you only wanted to date me
because I'm prettier
than your mom,
I'd totally go out with you.
What?!
Security!
Wow! She likes me,
and I creep her out.
                                                