and nine-time national champion Tony Cooper
- How do you feel?
- Great.
****
your****
You sure you don't wanna go to law school?
I hate lawyers.
And so do I, go get him baby
Ready to go.
Let's hear it,folks!
And it's casey alfonso by
less than half a car length!
What a spectacular finish
for the young phenom.
Casey alfonso with an amazing finish.
What'd you do at the end there?
Yeah,heh...
At about 250 feet,the car got out of
shape a bit.But about halfway down...
I just got into the zone or something.
I pedaled it back into the groove.It
was the coolest ride of my life!
How does it feel to beat
nine-time national champion
tony cooper?
I'm sorry.Can you repeat that?
How does it feel to
beat nine-time national
champion tony cooper?
Casey!Casey! Casey!
Out of the way!Out of the way.Casey!
Casey! Get the
ambulance! Brian, get the ambulance!
Casey...
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET - ÏûÉùÄä¼£
House.M.D
Season4 Episode 6
Whatever it takes
68-year-old
male,non-smoker.
Ah,68's a good run.
That'll leave something in
the lockbox for the rest of us.
- Next!
- That's your breakfast?
Technically,it's Wilson's lunch.
- 20-month-old baby,persistent
rash,fever... - Too much crying.
- Female college student with...
- Too much drama.
You don't care about
the crying or the drama.
'cause you won't see the patient.
And you'd treat methuselah if
his snot had an interesting color.
It means you've already decided
which case you wanna take next.
Tell me about speed racer.
Female,seizure with visual and
auditory processing deficiency.
- I did a consult and
- What kind of race car?
Dragster.
- Continue.
- You're gonna take a case based on the car she drives?
Nothing says "thanks for saving my life"
like a test drive in a car that
accelerates faster than the space shuttle.
You can't save her
life,'cause she's not dying.
Her lab shows signs of dehydration.
That means the problem's
just likely...Heatstroke.
Kinda hard to get
heat-struck in 41/2 seconds.
Not when you're wearing a
three-layer fireproof suit.
Excuse me.
Dr. House?
No,lazy ass called in sick
again.We can give him a message.
May we talk in private?
So...either it's heatstroke,
in which case we take the afternoon off,
or it's one of the diagnoses that you
guys are gonna have for me in two minutes.
- You're in charge.
- I know.
- Cop?
- He's not packing.
Your dad's either a
cop or a security guard.
Or she carries a weapon.
You're with the CIA?
One of our employees just
returned from an assignment sick.
We believe he may be the victim
of an assassination attempt.
Sure.You wanna close the door?
Door?
Well,I assume you're gonna drop
trou at some point during the dance.
- I don't see why I should share.
- This isn't a joke.
If you're willing to help
us,we need to leave now.
If I have to walk somewhere,there
better be at least five girls involved.
And they better be working
their way through college.
Okay,what do you got?
Hereditary brain
disorder,transient ischemia,
or paraneoplastic syndrome.
None of those go away with
iv fluids.It's heatstroke.
Or cushing's or calcium deficiency.
- Who's your friend?
- We use the term "life partner."
Get a fresh history,neurological
exam,and an mri of her head.
15 minutes for the lap dance,a half
hour to scrub the guilt off my soul.
See you in 45.
Dr. House...We need to hurry.
Yeah,we need to hurry.
Little advice, I mean,obviously the village
people played out the whole cop thing.
But,come on,CIA?
Do you seriously expect
anyone to believe that?
It helps when you have props.
Keep your eye on my pen.
Very good.
Any nausea or vomiting
before the seizure?
no.
My dad had some,but he's
always like that before a race.
It could have been food poisoning.
- You two eat breakfast together?
- no.
Any history of sciatica
or spinal injury?
no.
Abnormal deep tendon reflex.
Really?
Let me see.
- It's there.
- I didn't say it wasn't there.I said it was abnormal.
We're gonna give you an mri to be sure,
but I'm guessing your symptoms were
caused by just dehydration and the heat.
You're guessing?
Look,I make a living
driving 300 miles an hour,
which makes the ability to stay
conscious kind of important.
I'm sure it's just heatstroke.
But we're gonna do an
mri to be extra careful.
you said you left your
cell in your office.
I lied.
I wasn't going to take it,
just tell you to turn
it off for takeoff.
I know...just wanted to see if
you could tell that I was lying.
Useful information.
- Yeah?
- Where are you?
I'm on a top-secret
mission for the CIA.
Right.There was nothing on
your racecar driver's ct,
and the history and
physical were normal.
Her deep tendon reflexes
seemed a bit weak to me.
Areflexia could mean miller fisher.
Yes,areflexia could mean miller fisher,
but since the reflex
was weak,not absent,
it doesn't mean
anything.I'm releasing her.
- You can go back to your poker game.
- Poker's illegal.
CIA would never allow illegal activity.
Have you considered miller fisher?
Why? What happened?
She just had another seizure.
And now she's getting
a vertical nystagmus.
We think it's miller fisher,
an inflammatory process.
In rare cases,it can cause
respiratory failure,but...
Wait,she could stop breathing?
You said there was nothing
wrong.You said you were sure.
You just had another
seizure.Clearly,there's something wrong.
So why should I trust you
to figure out what it is?
Where's Dr. House?I'm
at this hospital bec...
It's gonna be all right.
We just need to start
the plasmapheresis.
no!
It's not going to be all right,
because you obviously don't
have a clue what you're doing.
I'm not letting you touch me.
- Honey,come on.
- I wanna see House!
Where is he?
Looks a lot better on24.
I take that back.
Dr. Samira terzi.
It's a pleasure to meet you,dr. House.
We really appreciate the
consult on such short notice.
There's nothing that gives me more
pleasure than helping out a colleague.
This is Dr. Sidney curtis
from the mayo clinic.
He's also agreed to
help with the diagnosis.
- Dr. House.
- curtis on immunology sidney curtis?
Oh,you've read it?
Nope! But it is keeping my piano level.
"Cutthroat Bitch"
So...where is the poor,sick fella?
- What do we do?
- I don't know yet.
- She needs treatment.
- This is a test,right?
You're reporting back
to him everything we do.
Yeah.And I asked the
patient to be uncooperative.
Personally,I think she overplayed it.
She's being uncooperative because
you made us all look like idiots.
We're only gonna look like idiots
if we can't figure out how to get her
to agree to the treatment.
What would House do right now?
Pop a pill,insult
us,and trick the patient.
We can do that last part.
She's never met House
before,has she?Who's got a cane?
House isn't here.
We're not gonna act like him.
What do you want?
I,uh...
I'm gonna do what doctors
aren't supposed to do:
admit I made a mistake.
I shouldn't have been so
quick to dismiss your symptoms.
But you need to let us
start the plasmapheresis.
What do you want?
Case?
Honey,do you know where you are?
She's burning up.
- Start the treatment.
- We can't.
- You've got my permission.She's obviously confused.
- It doesn't matter anymore.
Miller fisher doesn't
cause delirium and fever.
I don't know what this is.
I'm afraid there are going to be some
limitations on his medical history.
Just let me know what you need,and
I should be able to provide it.
Fyi,my malpractice insurance
doesn't cover alien autopsies.
That's fine. X- files are the next wing over.
Where was the patient
when he first felt ill?
Sorry,that's classified.
But assume there aren't too many
places in the world john hasn't been.
And,yes,john's a cover name.
And what makes you think it
was an attempt on his life?
Sorry,can't tell you that either.
What can you tell us?
did oswald really have
sex with marilyn monroe?
Good lord.
Very professional.
Five days ago,he was 185 pounds.
Perfect health.
Cool.
Fever and delirium rule out...
Uh,he's not gonna hire you just
because you call him the most.
Especially since it's obvious
he doesn't wanna be called.
Symptoms rule out miller
fisher.M.s. Fits better.
Progression's too
fast.More likely meningitis.
Areflexia doesn't fit as well with...
- Does with amyloidosis.
- That's even slower than m.s.It's lupus.
I'm with the little man on this one.
It's attacking the body and
the brain.Classic autoimmune.
Flirt all you want,but
I should warn you:
shiksas are for practice.
Lupus this aggressive
wouldn't spare her kidneys.
It's primarily neurological.
- Let's start her on
- Why no plaques on her mri?
Mri was inconclusive.
- So I don't know
- So now you're sure that it's m.s.
Just like you were sure it was miller fisher
an hour after you were sure it was heatstroke.
The symptoms fit.Start
her on interferon.
We're not gonna score any points with House
if we solve this just by running your errands.
- I get that you want to be right.
- You don't?
I'm just trying to save a
patient,not score points with my boss.
Would it hurt the patient
if you let us run some tests?
You've got three hours.
We've run six complete tox screens,
tested for every heavy metal,poison,and
biological agent we can think of.
It says here he ate a lot of chestnuts.
Hold on a second.
If the squirrel liberation
army's involved,I'm outta here.
- Those little rodents are
- Horse chestnuts are poisonous.
- If someone switched them
- Horse chestnuts may look like chestnuts,
but they taste like a
horse's lower-than-chestnuts.
Which makes the theory that he accidentally ate
a couple of hundred slightly less persuasive.
And seeing as how he was prowling
the back alleys of...tehran?
It wasn't tehran.It was..
oops.You almost got me.
Unless we know the local
environmental factors...
- Poisonous flora
- You know I can't tell you that.
Well,then,why are we here?You
might as well just google "poison."
All they would tell me is...
He spent the last 11 months in bolivia.
Who you gonna kill in bolivia?
- My old Housekeeper?
- We don't kill people.
I'm sorry.Who are you gonna marginalize?
If it is my Housekeeper,she
has it coming.
Cleaning the windows means cleaning
both sides.Am I right,or am I right?
What does it matter what he was doing?
- The guy's dying.
- Not anymore.
I know what's poisoning him.And who.
John.
It's just pancreatitis.
He's not an alcoholic.
And unless his pancreas
is in his fingers...
Spies can't get fungal infections?
- And the burns on his skin?
- Spies can't get sunburns?
Bolivia doesn't have sun?
So,either we go with his theory
of the non-drinking drunk,
or he was poisoned by some group with the
resources to make it completely untraceable.
Some customized isotope.
Let's treat for radiation poisoning.
The iodine's to protect your thyroid.
Antibiotics are to handle infections.
Should start working
in a couple of hours.
We should celebrate...
With a beer.Or eight.
I don't drink.
Oh...me thinks he doth protest too much.
He's deathly ill.Why would
he lie about drinking?
Guilt over killing a man.
Make anyone hit the sauce.
- We don't kill people.
- Right.
You just lie to your friends and family,
establish false identies,trick
people into betraying their country.
He'd never cover up his
drinking-- he's too honest.
Hey. Something I've
always wanted to know.
That poison lipstick that
ginger used to kiss gilligan...
Why didn't that kill her?
Okay,drum roll.
Lp is negative for meningitis.
Sorry,cole.
Fat pad biopsy is...
Oh,wait for it...
Negative for amyloidosis.And
thirteen goes down.
- Could we hurry this up?My son has
- Can I have a kid too?I'm working too hard.
I could hook you up.
If I had two minutes and some
anti-nausea meds,i'd take you up on that.
And for the gold...
Protein 65,glucose 70.
It's m.s.Start her on interferon.
Turn to the last page Sed rate's
95.A.n.a.'s weakly positive.
- Positive? It's lupus.
- Weakly.Not lupus,it's m.s.
We obviously don't know
what it is.Treat for both.
No. I gave in on the test.
I'm not treating her for two
completely separate diseases
because you think lupus
will win you a prize.
- Still think it's lupus?
- Yeah.
Me too.
In case of emergency,go
to the emergency room.
Could be lupus.That's what we figured.
- Then why are you here?
- You're an immunologist.We wanted to confirm
Who are you looking for me to
help you sell down the river?
House or cuddy?
Foreman.
- Sorry.
- He's pushing m.s.
Thinks that because he's in charge,he has
to prove he's the smartest guy in the room.
All I've heard about you: you put
the patient above everything else.
That's why everyone
finds you so annoying.
All House cares about is results.
I know. I'm talking about
how to do deal with Foreman.
So am i.
Fever's down to 101.5.
Treatment's working.Why are we out here?
Trying to figure out
which treatment's working.
It's kind of tacky doing
it in front of the patient.
You put her on steroids too?
We had no choice...The
sed rate pointed to lupus.
And the a.n.a.Ruled it out!
Doctors!
Legs hurt?
I can't feel them at all.I
don't think I can move them.
Vitals stabilizing.
Tummy ache's gone as well.
So the treatment's working.
Wanna ditch Dr. Killjoy
and...hop in the company jet?
Little trip down mexico way.
And I'm not talking about
the country or the plane.
Do you think acting like an idiot
and talking about sex works on girls?
Well,if it didn't,the human race
would have died out long ago.
You're pretty cheery for
someone who was just proved wrong
about his pancreatitis theory.
I'm appropriately cheery for
someone who's being proved right.
John hasn't vomited in six hours.
What's to vomit?I'm eating his lunch.
Withholding nutrients is the
treatment for pancreatitis.
That and the antibiotics you put him on.
I did unhook your iodine,though.
Didn't seem to fit with the whole
I'm-just-jerking- You-guys-around gestalt.
You're unbelievable.
Well,let's ask john if he'd rather
be sick honestly or cured dishonestly.
John.
Any chance he's just...
Overwhelmed with gratitude?
Paralysis.
Uh...It's a new symptom?
Big white space on the
board where it would fit?
Nice,multicolored markers?
I'm not writing it because we
can't know if it's a real symptom.
When these two went rogue and
pumped her full of steroids--
Steroids don't cause paralysis.
She was also on interferon!
Giving her both probably
fried her immune system.
Who knows what infection
you could cause--
We consulted an immunologist.
- She said we have
- She?
You talking about dr. Cameron?
- She thought lupus was
- She tell you to start treating?
Yes,they've ignored you.They screwed up.
And it's fun watching you spank them.
But can we get back to the medicine?
The last thing any of you give
a damn about is the medicine!
Look...
I'm not saying you're
bad doctors or bad people.
But House is.
He created a nasty
little cutthroat world,
planted you in it,and
is watching you play.
And none of it works
for anyone except him.
And whoever wins.
Given its quick progression,we
gotta assume botulism.
I'll go to her place,check
out her fridge and pantry.
It's not botulism.It's polio.
Brilliant.We should search her home
for fdr's remains or a time machine.
She could have contracted it from
anyone who's been to africa or...
She's been vaccinated.
Vaccines wear off.
There hasn't been a single
american case in over 20 years.
I've seen this disease.
- I know what it looks like.
- That's why you're finding it
Because you're looking for it.
Polio...it's crazy.
House wouldn't think so.
So go find House and
tell him your theory.
Take a personal day.Seriously.
Get outta here.
You don't have the power to fire me.
But I do have the power to
kick your ass off my case.
We're starting the botulism treatment.
The rest of you,look for confirmation.
- He should be brought up on charges.
- Okay,relax.
I'll take your book
out from under my piano.
He's dying of radiation sickness.
He's obviously in pain.
All of which could have been avoided
if you hadn't interfered with...
What was that for?!
Radiation sickness kills
specific cells at specific times.
His hair should be coming out in
clumps before he's writhing in pain.
Since it's not,I know
who's trying to kill him.
God.
It's blood cancer.Waldenstrom's.
Radiation can cause
infections,which set off--
If had any real evidence of foul play,
you'd be torturing bolivians instead of putting
me into a state of anticipatory sexual arousal.
- Can we treat for both?
- Bad idea.
Unless you're the one
who's trying to poison him.
I'll arrange for
plasmapheresis and chemo.
Are you gonna trust
him after what he did?
I don't have to trust
him to agree with him.
You make a good point.
I've been wrong every time,and
she still won't listen to you.
So either she really likes
me or she really hates you.
And I got a ride in the jet.
Oh. Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Just came to say hi.
Hi again.
Where's...mrs. Bearman?
- Sent her home.
- I was scheduling her for an mra.
If we gave mras to every
patient with a headache--
This wasn't just a headache,it
was the worst in her life.
Then lucky for you I'm a neurologist.
She went to a wine and cheese tasting.
- Both triggers for migraines.
- She's never had a migraine before.
And I never hagel before
the first time I had one.
Bagels don't kill people.
This is a classic
ticking-bomb aneurysm.
This taught me a lesson.
I guess when I mess with
other people's patients,
I risk looking like an officious bitch.
We're gonna have to
track down mrs. Bearman.
Wait...
Never mind.
- That's funny.
- It's not funny.It's totally immature.
It is funny.You just can't appreciate
it because you're the victim.
Yeah,I deserve shame and
ridicule for offering a consult.
Unheard of for a doctor.
You didn't offer a medical consult.
- You offered a "dealing with Foreman" consult.
- For the good of the patient.
It's what House would have done.
Maybe House will hear about
it and tear up with pride.
You think I'm trying to impress him.
I think that,for someone
who's not involved in his team,
you're remarkably involved in his team.
Let it go.
Let him go.
And that's mature?
120 over 80.Let 'er rip.
Now we got the medical
stuff out of the way.
Why don't we meet back at your place
for some enhanced
interrogation techniques?
My safe word
is,"help,please,please stop."
It's two pleases.
Anything less than that,you keep going.
You actually cure this guy,i'll
show you my private water board.
We need to consult an
oncologist about the chemo.
Oh,I'm sorry,I thought...
You were still euphemizing.
My valet knows a little oncology.
I was wondering when you'd
grow bored of avoiding my calls.
Oh,I can never grow
bored of ignoring you.
What's the latest
protocol on waldenstrom's?
- Where are you?
- CIA headquarters
How much
fludarabine--
Either you're sprawled
naked on your floor
with an empty bottle of
vicodin,or collapsed naked
in front of your computer
with an empty bottle of viagra.
Please tell me which,because
chase has another pool going.
They flew me in to help
deal with a sick employee.
- How much
- Hallucinations.Damn!
I shouldn't have bet on the viagra.
Okay,call the langley
switchboard,ask for extension...
- 3578.
He asked an awful lot
of questions for a valet.
You know,I happen to have a
position available on my penis.
Wait a second-- I think
I screwed up that joke.
You offering me a job?
I'd settle for that.
As tempting as a
position on your staff is,
- I like it here.
- Pays better.
And we've only had one
assassination attempt.
And I'm sure you're a great boss.
That's why your fellows left
en masse a couple of months ago.
I have satellite images.
Inspector gadget.
My god.You're actually at the CIA.
You've gotta get down here.
They've got a satellite aimed
directly into cuddy's vagina.
I told them the chances of
invasion are slim to none,
waldenstrom's.
Recommended dose is 25
milligrams per meter squared.
They do a background check on you?
25 milligrams?
They did a background check on you,
they did a background
check on your friends.
Relax.
I'm sure they already know that you
brought heroin back from afghanistan.
That...that's not true.I've
never been to afghanistan.
House?
- She's getting worse?
- Fever's risen slightly.
But it's definitely,um...
What...botulism?
Right?Because if you're wrong again,
and you're treating her for
something she doesn't even have--
The antitoxin hasn't
had time to work yet.
I know it's hard,but try to be patient.
Excuse me.
I know you're pissed I interrupted,
but you're gonna be even
more pissed in a second.
You tested her without telling me?
Yeah. And I know,I'm
really,really sorry.
But...on the other hand,it's a positive.
She has polio.
Now what,boss?
Where's House?
He's blown off four hours of clinic.
He's consulting for the CIA.
Seriously.Call langley
and ask for extension 35...
3536?
There's definitely two threes.I
- I wrote it down.
- I have it somewhere.
- He's gonna make up twice his skipped hours in the clinic.
Okeydoke.
And for protecting him,you're
gonna make up twice that.
Why are you punishing me worse than him?
Because House never learns.You might.
How are you feeling?
Like crap.
Yeah,cancer can be that way.
My hair is falling out.
That the chemo?
No,it's too quick.
So what does it mean?
It means you don't have cancer.
Someone actually did try to kill you.
You're stubborn.
- You're arrogant!
- There's no need to yell.
You may have cost that man his life.
He's getting the radiation treatment.
24 hours too late!
I didn't yell at you when
I thought you were wrong.
- I wasn't wrong!
- This isn't productive.
There is no productive.It's too late.
Because of your
inexperience,your poor judgment.
And your failure to
recognize a reckless fool!
Cordyceps sinensis.
It's,uh...it's an herbal treatment derived
from a parasitic fungus,comes from caterpillars.
Along with dimercaprol chelation,
it's been shown to mitigate bone
marrow damage from radiation poisoning.
In monkeys.
I'm sorry.I was stubborn and arrogant.
Self-recriminations won't help her.
Nothing's gonna help
her.She's got polio.
There's no cure,but
there are treatments.
- She's dying.
- Yeah.
Every death's a tragedy.
Funny how you weren't so depressed
when she just dying because
me and Amber screwed up.
And I'm also self-centered.Thanks
for clarifying.
Don't forget self-pitying.
Vitamin c.
Extremely high doses.It was experimental
treatment protocol in the '50s.
- And they haven't finished yet?
- They...lost funding.
That's because there's no logical
reason vitamin c would cure polio.
Well,someone thought there was.
Someone thought black people
made excellent farm implements.
I'm not talking about hurting anyone.
I just wanna force feed
her some orange juice.
You wanna throw in some
bacon and eggs as well?
If there's anything you learn today,
it's gotta be that you can be wrong.
John,can you hear me?
We're going to start you on
an experimental treatment.
Tea?
It's a chinese herb.
- Which has been effective in
- I'm dying,aren't i?
Probably.
We're gonna attempt an
experimental protocol.
- A new drug?
- An old one.Vitamin c.
Ultra-high doses have been shown to destroy
the polio virus and heal nerve damage.
She could regain use of her legs.
It's unlikely.
But we're gonna try.Don't give up.
Nausea's...
not as bad.
Radiation sickness has a latency period.
You'll get better before you get worse.
You wanna know what I
really did down there?
Only if it's interesting.
The women there...
During carnival they...
They do this dance.
They call it the devil dance.
Not interesting.
I spent all 40 days with this
attache to the minister of defense.
The most...
buttoned-down woman
you'd ever meet.You know?
'cept when she did this dance.
She agreed to tell me stuff...
Okay,we have half a good story there.
Karma.
Best way to rid yourself of that
guilt is to confess your sins.
This pain is...right.
It's comforting.
It makes me think
that...Somehow,it all makes sense.
What do you mean,40 days?
When they found out.
What she...told me.
Carnival in bolivia's only eight days.
You have any idea what
a chestnut looks like?
You idiot.
Who are you calling an idiot?
Whoever knew that john
was stationed in brazil,
- not bolivia.
- Brazil?
Well,then,I guess I'm
talking to you,idiot.
It's the same region.
It's the same parasite,same diseases.
But not the same language.
In bolivia,chestnuts are chestnuts.
Brazil,on the other
hand,hascastanhas-do-para,
literally,"chestnuts from para."
Because it would be stupid
for people from brazil
to call them brazil nuts!
So he ate brazil nuts.Big deal.
No,he ate a lot of brazil nuts.
Which is a big deal,because
they contain selenium.
Which,in high doses,causes fatigue,
vomiting,skin irritation,discharge
from the fingernail beds,
and hair loss.Any of
that sounding familiar?
Can you treat it?
We've already started.
Treatment's chelation,same
as for radiation sickness.
The only difference is it works
a lot better on nut poisoning.
So what's the problem?
You're an idiot.
Why is she shivering?
Low serum calcium is a side
effect of the treatment.
I can give her a calcium supplement.
My arm hurts.
Infusion rate has to remain
high for the treatment to work.
Is it working?
- You feel that?
- Yeah.
It hurts.
It's working.
This is fantastic.
There's a lot you can
learn in my fellowship.
A few new procedures I could teach you.
Course,we'd need a nurse to prep.
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
Actually,I was just trying to
make another euphemism for sex.
- So was i.
- Oh,god.
How can you flirt with this idiot?
He lied to us again and again.
He broke
laws,ethical codes--
I was right.
That doesn't mean everything.
It means a lot.
Dr. Curtis.
Dr. House.
Appreciate your help.
- Hey.
When...
when you were dying,you
tried to infect me.
Because you knew i'd fight for you
if I thought I was dying too.
You bringing this up now so I'll
forgive you for messing with my patient?
I'm happy I changed jobs.
But I know I'll never
have that sort of...
- Excitement.
- You Miss people trying to kill you?
no.
I miss...people doing whatever
it takes to get the job done.
I guess that's why I'm
having trouble giving it up.
I shouldn't have helped
them mess with your patient.
They had to screw with me.
I've gotten everything wrong.
I don't believe it.
You're not...
Gonna get everything right.
But you're never gonna
get everything wrong.
Morning!
Uh,where have you
been the last two days?
- Overslept.
- We saved speed racer.
She had polio.
We cured it with vitamin c.
Yeah.
I cured depression
with tonic water once.
Actually,I think there
was some gin in it too.
150 grams over six hours.
- It worked.
- No,it didn't.
I told you you can't cure polio.
That means either she's not
cured or she never had it.
Since she's walking out of here...
I tested her blood from admittance.
no polio.
that means brennan
screwed up the lab tests.
or you screwed up your lab tests.
you must have.she got better.
so it's relapsing and remitting.
maybe...porphyria.
nah,that's a stretch.
if she had porphyria,you
would have seen purple urine.
you think it's more
likely he cured polio?
they believe it.
her symptoms fit perfectly.
and the alternative is
unbelievably convoluted.
some doctor would have
to poison her with valium
so it looks like
polio,then fake a lab test,
then give her vitamin
c and stop the poison
so she magically gets better.
actually...it is kind of doable,right?
so what do you think?
should we test her for thallium
before you contact stockholm?
you poisoned her?
the really shocking thing is that
Foreman was right about the heatstroke.
vitamin c cures polio.I've seen it.
yeah...in some bush clinic.
you need polio in a
place with a proper lab.
the only problem is that places
with proper labs don't have polio.
there is no money in finding cures
for diseases that only kill poor people.
this will make them do research.
and what do you care
if I faked a lab test
if it saves a few thousand lives?
I did what I had to do.
isn't that what you hired us for?
which is why I'm not gonna fire you.
you're gonna quit.
go on,get out of here.
so you're just gonna let him go?
absolutely.
I'm gonna let him get as far away
as possible before you call the cops.
guy's a nut job.
who the hell did I leave in charge?
- Foreman.
- there was a reason for that.
next time,listen to him.
where have you been?
- and don't say the CIA.
- okay.
by the way,one
of my employees--
either you're gonna have
to get someone from the CIA
to call and confirm your story,or
you're doing eight clinic hours
and Wilson is doing 16.
I was in the hamptons.
I was helping some rich hedge
fund jerk treat his son's sniffles.
fascinating as that sounds.
for your honesty,I
will forgiveyourhours.
thank you.
no!
the only thing less likely
than your helping the CIA
is your helping some
rich guy on long island.
you're doing your hours andWilson's.
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
who doesn't?
- hi.
- Hi
I'm going to take you up on your offer.
yeah?
well,i,uh,I live a
couple miles from here.
that's not the offer I meant.
I gave notice today.
you said you were happy at the company.
I lied.doubt you'll hold it against me.
i'll see you at 9:00 on monday.
House.M.D
Season4 Episode 6
Whatever it takes
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET - ÏûÉùÄä¼£
Proudly Presents