Today on Chrissy's Court,
lounge singer Joey Valenza is suing
David Oganesyan for the cost of a speaker
that was damaged when David
startled Joey
with an outlandish song request.
David says it was Joey
that knocked the speaker over,
so...
The people are real.
The cases are real.
And the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise
to the Judge--
Honorable Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Oh, are we using that?
- Yeah.
- "For the Judge
Honorable Chrissy Teigen." Okay.
Hello, everybody!
- Hi.
- Joey v. David.
Joey, you look so familiar.
- I have a generic face.
- No! You don't have
a generic face.
- I do.
I had a nose job, but it grew back.
- Did we date?
I think we might have dated.
Joey, present me your case.
- I was singing in a restaurant.
Uh, I just finished a Sinatra song.
I was walking back to the stage,
and I heard a voice behind me say...
"Hey, you do any rap songs?"
- Wait, how did he say it?
- Yeah. "Hey, you.
You sing any rap songs?"
I turned around.
It was a nice-looking young kid.
I said,
"Uh, this room isn't right for rap.
Sorry about it."
And the look on his face scared me.
I went back, and my shoulder hit
the-the speaker.
And fell off the table.
So I'm suing David
for the value of my speaker,
which is approximately $999.
- So, David, your defense.
- So, I walked into the restaurant.
I ordered some takeout.
Uh, decided to listen to some music.
I saw he was singing good songs, you know?
- Yeah.
- Like, you know,
I just wanted to hear my own style,
maybe joke around...
- What song did you want
to hear?
- A rap song.
I mean, do you look at him
and do you think that he knows a rap song?
- I mean...
- I mean, like, were you drinking
a little bit?
- No.
- No, not at all. No.
- No? Okay.
Well, that's not helping your case.
You should've said you were drinking.
Um, okay.
- He got worked up, and, uh,
he backed up into his speaker,
knocked it down,
and he broke his own speaker.
So I don't owe him anything.
- We actually have an expert
in music, and he's gonna
come out and help me out.
So come on out.
Thank you.
So, John is actually a professional judge.
- I'm actually a coach.
I'm not a judge.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
You're a coach. That's right.
- But I do judge people.
- So, can we hear a little bit
of music from you?
- Now, I don't know if it's go--
It's working.
- Oh.
- Now it works.
- That sounds good.
- So it's not even-- it's not even broken.
- It works perfectly.
- It won't work
for half hour, an hour.
But you never know.
- I want you to sing for me,
and I'll know if the speaker's working.
- Can I have one thing to myself ever?
I just want to dance with you.
- Wait, you're singing that type of song,
and then David walks up to you
and says, "Hey!
Can you...?"
- "Play some Dr. Dre!"
- "Can you play some Dre?"
- Exactly.
- Okay, John, can you go ask him
to perform a so-- a rap song?
John will approach you...
- Yeah...
- Let's get the mic for you.
- ...and apparently scare
the shit out of you.
- Look at me. I'm scary.
Excuse me, sir.
Could I hear some rap music?
- I'm sorry.
This room is con--
not conducive to rap music.
But I can tell you
how they got the word "rap."
They took the "C" out of "crap."
- What?!
- And I hit the speaker.
- Right, right, right. Automatically.
- It's not funny, Judge.
It's not funny.
- David, is that how it happened?
- That's not. I can reenact it.
- Okay, David,
please approach.
Can you do it in the way that you think
that it happened?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- John, you sing "My Way."
Thank you, everybody!
- Very nice. That was very nice.
- Thank you.
- That was very good. Can--
Do you have some rap music?
Maybe you could twist it...
- Don't do it again, please.
That's exactly how he did it.
- That's exactly...
- Wow. So, I mean, either way,
that was terrifying.
Uh...
- That's right.
- John, how do you feel as an artist
if, uh, anyone approaches you
to sing something different?
- Yeah. Well, I just think
the audience has a responsibility
to request responsibly,
if you know what I mean.
- Yes.
- So he shouldn't have asked you to rap,
especially he's a takeout customer.
Like, how does a takeout customer
get to request songs?
- Okay, so,
I mean, you backed up to your
own [bleep] speaker, Joey.
Um...
I mean, David, just know
that you don't go up to an entertainer
in a restaurant
and ask for rap music.
I'm gonna go ahead and rule
in favor of Joey for $999
for the speaker.
- Wow.
- But I'm gonna cover it.
'Cause I love you both.
Joey, you get a new speaker.
- One breath, John.
- Good job, Mommy.
- Thank you.
- What did you say, Luna?
- "Good job, Mommy."
- Oh, thank you, baby girl.
- Next time I want to request
a song, I'll ta--
definitely take a extra look
on the performer.
- Justice Christy-- Chrissy Teigen,
uh, did the right thing.
Thank you very much, everybody.