Today on Chrissy's Court,
Milton Jenkins is suing
his ex-girlfriend Sona Durham
for the cost of a car he sold her.
Sona claims that ever since
she bought the car,
all she does is drive him around,
and her time is more valuable
than some car.
The people are real, the cases are real,
and the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise to the Honorable
Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Ta-da!
Good afternoon, everybody.
Hello, Mom.
- Hi.
- Hand it over.
Milton v. Sona.
Milton, go ahead and explain your case.
- Well, me and Sona started out dating,
and we became real close.
We got to know each other real well.
And as a partner/girlfriend,
she needed a-a way around,
and I had two cars.
So I decided, like,
maybe she needs to just go
and purchase this car from me.
- Basically, you started dating.
- Mm-hmm.
- You call it a "situation-ship."
- Yes.
- How do you define
a situation-ship?
- All right.
You know, a ship
is supposed to take you places.
Whether it's a relationship
or a friendship.
- Oh, it's like a ship, then.
You've actually made this into a... Okay.
- Right.
- I thought you would do
the "situation" part,
but you're focusing on the "ship" part.
Okay. Okay.
- Right, right.
You got friendships,
you got relationships.
- Uh-huh.
- Either this relationship
is gonna take you somewhere,
-or it's gonna sink.
- Mm.
- This relationship turned
into a situation-ship.
Like, you scratch my back,
I scratch yours.
- Did you think you were
in a relationship?
Like, an actual boyfriend,
girlfriend relationship,
not a situation-ship?
- I felt like I was in, um...
- Limbo?
- ...a sex-ship.
- Sex-ship.
- Ooh.
- Yay is into it.
- So,
you are just asking for this car payment.
- Right. And then she can have
the title and the car.
- Okay.
- This is the car right here, Your Honor.
- Oh, [bleep], that's a nice car.
- Beautiful.
Looks like a good car.
- Do you have a contract?
- Yes.
- You do?
- Let me see that.
- Now, most people say
that the power is in the tongue,
but clearly, the power was in the pen
when she wrote that letter.
- Mom, do you think this
is legally binding?
- Looks good.
- All right. I mean,
you knew what you signed on for.
- No, because once I started driving that,
he made me his personal driver,
and I'm like,
"Okay, this wasn't the plan."
- So, Sona, what's your side of this?
- I think, for the most part,
he's just really ungrateful.
I cook dinner for him every night.
I do not even charge him, but...
- Well, if you think
you're in a relationship,
you wouldn't charge for it.
Like, I wouldn't sit John down
and be like,
"Okay, I'm gonna give you a massage,
and you have to pay me."
- Would you charge somebody for a car
if you were in a relationship?
- Yes. I mean, I-I...
It's... No, because he's rich,
so it's like...
- Okay, that's it for everyone.
- Okay.
- I take him to and from work
in this vehicle, like...
- That I put gas in.
- So you sold her a car that
she has to take you to work in?
- Not every day.
- Where's this second car?
- I still have it.
It's just in the shop.
- Okay.
- Your Honor, I have pictures,
if you don't mind, of...
- Yes, no, please.
- ...of me actually
driving him around, okay?
- You have pictures of you
driving him around?
- Yes, I do.
I have pictures of him
being a passenger, okay? Um...
- There's the proof, right there.
- Literally, pictures of...
All right, this is you
in the passenger's seat.
She is literally driving you.
- We weren't going nowhere.
- Sona, you paid for the gas,
you paid for...?
- I paid for the gas.
- I mean...
- I also have a list
of other things that I've done.
I've bought lingerie for his pleasure.
- That was part of my birthday gift.
- Sona, your breakdown-- which is titled
"A Very Great List
of Why I Owe Milton Nothing."
Re-twisted his hair; pain,
suffering, time and energy.
- Her energy?
She thrives off of my energy.
- That's a discount.
I was just being humble.
- She thinks she the sun.
- Yes.
- This is all totaling $81,000.
- So he owes me, basically,
you know what I mean?
- No.
- You're not even asking for that much.
You're just saying, like,
"This is what I've done for you."
- Right.
- I mean, I honestly get all of this,
because this is worth something,
um, in a relationship.
- Okay.
- But since you won't
call it a relationship,
this is where it gets
a little muddy for me.
Milton, do you feel like you
could owe her a dollar, even?
Do you feel like you owe her
for any of this stuff?
- If I owe her for anything,
it'd be twisting my hair.
The rest of that stuff, I mean,
the things that she's given,
I give her also.
- I understand your point.
- You know.
But this car is totally different.
She-she needs to make that payment.
You know, she tries
to give me sex instead of money.
I feel like I'll take that ass,
but she still has to pay me my $4,400.
- "That ass"?
- That is not appropriate.
That is not appropriate.
- If she don't want me to go out
and get another girlfriend,
then I think she should...
- How would you feel
right now if you found out Milton
was dating somebody else tomorrow?
- Um...
- Be honest.
- No, that would hurt my feelings,
'cause I don't date anyone else.
- You see potential in this relationship.
- I do. I do. I just don't like
to be manipulated.
- Would you like to be with her, too?
- I thought about it.
- I don't know why you're
putting on this front of, like,
"I could do any... I get anything I want."
Like, she seems great. So...
I do feel like you should
get paid for your time,
your energy, twisting his hair
and the pain.
I feel like there was some pain
involved, no offense.
Um...
But at the same time,
you also do owe him for this car,
so I'm ruling
in favor of the plaintiff for $3,000.
Thank you guys so much.
- Thank you.
- They're gonna get back together.
- Yeah.
They're gonna...
they're gonna [bleep] tonight.
That's for sure.
- I guess I did owe him some more money,
but he just needs to know
you can't manipulate people
to get things to go your way.
- The judge made some sense to me.
She talked to me
and made me look at the way
that I look at things differently now.