Today on Chrissy's Court,
John Walker is suing
his friend Fred Fields
for an unpaid loan
that started in a Sizzler.
Fred says, "Sizzler?
He doesn't even know her!"
The people are real, the cases are real
and the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise for the Honorable
Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Hello, everybody.
- There she is.
- Hello, Mom.
- Hi.
- All right.
You guys may be seated.
Today we have John Walker v. Fred Fields.
I know a little bit about your case,
but please, go ahead
and present it to all of us
in the courtroom here.
- In 2018, I came into
some retirement money,
and so Fred and I, we were
having lunch at Sizzler.
- Oh, my-- How often
do I talk about Sizzler?
- He mentioned
that times were tough and how
he didn't have a lot of money at the time.
When he said that, I said,
"Well, you know,
"that-that ain't right.
My friend shouldn't be broke."
- Aw.
- So I reached in my pocket
and I pulled out $1,000.
And I handed him $1,000 and...
- You had $1,000 in your pocket
at Sizzler?
- I had about...
I had about $8,000, actually.
- Damn!
I think you can buy
an entire Sizzler for that.
- Oh, yes. Yes, yes.
- Wow. That is very
generous and kind of you.
- And I told him pay me back
whenever you get a chance.
And so he's never paid me back.
- Fred.
What's your defense here?
- When John gave me the $1,000,
he did it out of the kindness of
his heart; I didn't ask for it.
He told me I could pay the money
back when I make it big,
which I have yet to do.
- Make it big how?
- With my music career.
- Okay.
- I'm not small, but I'm not big.
I consider myself "medium."
- A comedian?
- No. "Medium."
- Medium.
- Oh, a medium.
I thought you were a comedium.
- Nah.
- And I was like, "Oh, shit,
you do music and comedy,"
which seems awesome as well.
- And so, I think that's
an important stipulation.
- How long have you been
in the music industry?
- In 1989, I had my first record
in the stores.
- Wow.
- Then I came out here in '92.
I got with Walt Disney,
I did some songs
for The Mickey Mouse Club.
Then I hooked up with Death Row,
and one of my teachers is Dr. Dre.
While I'm over there with Dr. Dre,
it looks like something is finna happen.
- Honestly, I don't know
a lot about music,
but I do want to call out
our expert witness
to maybe be able to help us out
with this case.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's John Legend.
John is obviously a judge on The Voice.
He also has an EGOT.
Is there anything else
you want me to say about you?
- I'm happily married...
- Yes.
- ...Your Honor.
- You heard the case, right?
- You went from Disney to Death Row?
That is an incredible trajectory.
Not to be ageist,
but rap tends to be
a young man's game.
I don't know how old you are, but...
if you were making music in 1989...
- John, he's 19 years old.
- Oh.
- Age don't count in the booth
when your flow
stays submerged
in the Fountain of Youth.
- Okay. Okay.
- Ruling is in... Sorry.
- Uh, I'm not doubting
that you're talented.
Perhaps you can make it more as a writer
or b-behind-the-scenes kind of person.
- That's where the money is, anyway.
- Well, it's in all of it, but
that's a way to make money...
- In our prenup,
you told me it was mostly...
- Oh, well...
- Your Honor...
- She crazy.
- The crux of the matter
for him, how do you define him
making it big,
or how do you define him
being able to pay you back?
- The problem is, I don't
remember that stipulation.
- I don't think he's taking
into consideration
the barbecues that I threw
and how he used to be able
to eat unlimited, free.
I used to do them every month.
I'm talking about premium...
- So you went
to Sizzler and then
you also held sizzlers.
- Oh, I get busy
with the culinary arts, now.
- Okay.
- You know what I'm saying?
I'm dangerous in the kitchen.
I even brought some to prove it to you.
- Well, maybe that should be your dream.
- Here, Judge.
- Oh, my gosh! Yes.
- Let me get in on this. Yes, please.
- John, you want to come up?
- So you want to talk about the money
and how your food ain't free...
- Mm-hmm.
- What do you think those Lakers
and Dodgers tickets cost me?
- That is good.
- That is really good.
- Did you have a good time?
Did I ask you for a dime?
- Judge?
Don't forget about Pepper.
- How'd you like your seat?
You told me it was sweet.
- Are you rapping right now?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- He's rapping. He's rapping.
- Okay.
- We get to eat and listen to rap.
- What about your seat?
You told me it was sweet.
- When your ass needed cash,
I gave it to you in a flash.
- Oh!
- You got $1,000.
You didn't even need to holla.
So you want to talk about money again?
For 15 years, I've been your friend.
- Ooh...!
- Boy!
- Okay, so-so he want
to play like that, right?
I got the rib eyes,
the carne asada, plus filets.
I can do this all day
in all types of ways.
Man, please, my macaroni and cheese?
One bite, it'll have you
down on your knees.
Plus, I got the greens
and the barbecue beans.
The way I do my thing, man, ya boy mean.
If you caught that, you can roll with me.
'Cause in the hood, I'm Chef Boyar-G.
If you don't get a taste...
- Oh!
- ...then homie, you lost.
And you gonna know I'm a boss
when you taste my sauce.
Please excuse my French,
may I approach the bench?
You can adjust your face
and I rest my case.
- Oh!
- Okay!
- Legendary.
- First of all,
no one's ever fed me on the bench before,
and I feel so good now,
I'm also so-- super tired.
- She got the itis.
You gave her the itis, man.
Congratulations.
- I think...
Your food is legit good. Like...
- Well, thank you.
- ...it's actually delicious.
If you were to ever do a company
where you wanted a food truck
or a restaurant,
I would love to be a part of that.
- I appreciate that.
- But you know you owe John $1,000.
Ruling is in favor
of the plaintiff for $1,000.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for the food.
Absolutely beautiful.
- I'm gonna eat some more.
- Oh, we got corn bread, too,
I didn't even see.
- Oh, Lord.
- This is so good.
- Right. I need to get some.
- He loaned it to me,
I got to give it back.
That's what it is.
- Like Charlie Sheen said, "Winning."