Today on Chrissy's Court,
Monique Hooks is suing her sister
Devon Hines for the cost
of Tupperware, shirts
and lighters Devon has stolen
over the years.
Devon claims she's entitled
to whatever she wants
because she's the older sister
and it's her Devon right.
The people are real, the cases are real,
and the judgments are legally binding
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise
for the Honorable Judge
Chrissy Teigen.
- Hello!
- Hi, Judge.
- How are you, Yay?
- I'm good. How's yourself?
- I am feeling great, actually.
Thank you.
Been studying... law.
Oh, you may be seated.
Monique versus Devon,
suing for $171.97-- very specific--
for various things your sister
ate, stole, broke.
Wait, so you're both 30?
- Mm-hmm.
- How many months apart are you?
- She's 61 days older than me.
- Wow.
- And she likes to harp
on those 61 days, like they matter.
- They do matter.
- We're practically twins.
- Yeah, you are.
- But I'm still older.
- Okay, remember that.
- We've been best friends and sisters.
We found out we were sisters
in high school.
- You were best friends before you even
found out you were sisters?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Aw.
- That's amazing.
- Well, actually,
we were gonna fight first.
- Then we started to like each other.
- I love you both already.
How did you find out you were sisters?
- It was our sophomore year
of high school.
So, we had went through
a whole school year together.
And I've never been big on my father.
And then me and her
are having a conversation.
She was saying things that
really were kind of similar.
So, I was like, "Do you have a picture?"
And she pulls out the picture,
and I was like, "Wow."
- If I found out I had
a sister right now...
- You have a sister.
- I know I have a sister,
but if I found... like, if a...
if a new one existed out there,
I'd be so excited!
That's a big deal, you guys!
That's amazing.
- I was actually excited.
I grew up in a household
with boys, so I never had
a sister, so it was like,
"Yay, now I have a sister!
- So, Monique,
explain your case.
What are some of the things
that Devon has taken from you?
- She has stolen all my good Tupperware.
She doesn't even cook, um...
- What are you putting in this Tupperware?
- Her food from her house that I buy.
- Yeah, she steals my food.
Uh, she takes all my lighters.
- We lose a lot of lighters.
We won't say what
we're lighting up, but...
- It's for a barbecue.
- Our barbecue!
- Sure, barbecue.
- Yes!
- She's taken my shirts,
which you can look at her and look at me,
and tell they won't fit the same.
- Well, [bleep]
- I-I mean her... chest!
She made a video about
how I wasn't getting my Tupperware back.
- Can we see the video, please?
- Is this your Tupperware?
Is this your
Tupperware?
A real-ass bitch give a [bleep]
about your Tupperware?
Is this your Tupperware?
- I can listen to this all day.
- Is this your Tupperware?
A real-ass bitch give a [bleep]
about your Tupperware?
- And she got that piece by me being nice
and making cupcakes
for her daughter's birthday.
- I want to hear it one more time, please.
- Is this your Tupperware?
Is this your
Tupperware?
A real-ass bitch give a [bleep]
about your Tupperware?
- Uh, that is incredible.
So, you were teasing her
about the Tupperware?
- I was.
- You knew you were gonna
get under her skin.
What do you have to say for yourself?
- I don't feel bad.
- I think it's funny, personally.
- I thought it was hilarious.
- Really?
- So, Devon,
you have things that you've done...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...that-that you feel like
negate this entire situation.
- I have the list right here
of all the things
that I do for her.
- I don't want to hear this.
- This is a very short list.
You didn't need a whole piece of paper.
Okay, so, "When her phone was
broken and I had two phones,
I let her use one of my phones."
Why do you have so many phones?
- 'Cause she's a trap star.
- Oh! I don't even know what that means,
but it just sounds so cool.
- She got two phones--
one for the hoes and one for the pros.
- It be like that.
- Oh, that's one I don't understand.
- I mean, I'm sure John has,
like, five, but...
Tell me about these shorts and the shit.
What the [bleep] is this show?
Yes, tell me about
the shit on your shorts.
- Her dog pooped on my shorts,
so I feel like...
my shorts are gone, your shirts are gone.
- Is your dog notorious
for shitting on stuff?
- No.
- Okay. Okay.
- She drug her shorts and her clothes
out to the middle of the floor
and took a shit on the shorts.
- She's just sitting there laughing,
like, are you serious?
- You're an adult.
- Get your animal!
So, Monique, do you feel like
anything on this tiny list is valid?
The groceries...
- Just the groceries.
- The groceries are more
than you're suing for.
What is with this $171.97?
- That's 'cause I know how much
those Tupperware cost.
- I like it, 'cause it makes me feel like
you've thought about this,
even though I have no idea.
- Oh, yeah, every time I go
in Walmart and walk down
the Tupperware aisle, I'm like,
"I used to have this!"
- Okay.
- But you can come get them.
They're in the cabinets
with all the lids on them.
- Oh, when I tried to come
get them last time, you're like,
"Well, I have chicken in
that one, and that one has..."
- Okay, so, now, how far
do you live apart?
- Seven minutes.
- How far are you?
- Seven minutes?
- Yes.
- And you can't share
T-shirts and Tupperware?
- You see, you see what I'm saying!
- What can I do with a shirt
after she puts those boobs in it?
- In the Tupperware?
- You guys, these are sisterly benefits!
- I don't benefit from this sisterhood.
- Exactly.
- To me, looking from outside in,
it's incredible that
you two found each other.
It's a good thing you found
a family member for life.
But you can't just steal shit.
My ruling is actually
going to be, I'm going to give...
you both full sets of Tupperware.
And, also, Devon,
I'm gonna shit on your shorts.
- Verdict-- case dismissed.
And here is some Tupperware
for the both of you.
Yay!
- You both are fantastic, okay?
Get it together.
- Court adjourned!
- No, I don't give a [bleep]
about her new Tupperware,
and I'm probably gonna end up with
some of the new Tupperware as well.
- I'm gonna take her set
of Tupperware, too.
My Tupperware!
I'm so used to not having it.