Today on Chrissy's Court,
Tiphani Lampkin is suing her ex-boyfriend,
Fred Pillow, for his half
of a canceled trip to Houston.
Fred says he doesn't owe her anything
because he tried to save her
from having to go to Houston.
The people are real, the cases are real,
and the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise to the Honorable
Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Good afternoon, everybody.
- Hi, Judge.
- Hello, Mom.
You may be seated.
Okay, so we've got Tiphani
versus Fred today.
Tiphani, go ahead and tell me
your side of the story here.
- I had booked a trip to Houston,
uh, for my 30th birthday.
It was gonna be me, my best friend
and my boyfriend at the time-- Fred.
- Now an ex?
- Oh, yes, definitely.
- It's okay.
- I paid for it on my card.
- Okay.
- And he agreed to pay me back.
- And you were gonna go to Houston...
- Yes.
- ...as a joint romantic, little...
- Yeah.
- With your best friend.
- Oh.
- No.
- Prior to the trip,
I had driven by his house
on my way home from work
and saw another girl's car parked there.
- So you were just doing
a drive-by, or you happen...
It was on your way?
- I... It was on my way.
- Doing a drive-by.
- No, I don't do drive-bys.
Literally, I drive past his house...
- Okay.
- ...to go home.
- It's the easiest way.
- One of four easy ways.
- Okay, hold on. Hold on.
You'll get your chance, Fred.
- I drove by, I was blowing up his phone,
calling, texting.
Nothing. Didn't hear from him.
- Mom, what would you do?
Would you have stopped?
Would you have gone in the house?
- I would go in with my phone and record.
- Mm.
- Okay.
- To use as evidence. Evidence.
- That is a lot.
Oh, yeah, to get evidence.
Now you know.
Now you know that we need evidence
for everything.
- Yeah.
- So, you actually forgave him, though?
- Well, he gave me,
"Oh, she's just a crazy ex-girlfriend."
- You believed him,
or you just decided to drop it?
- I dropped it, basically.
- Okay.
- And then, something just--
Like, it was woman's intuition.
- Uh-huh.
- "Check his Facebook."
"I bet..."
- Wait. Like, his account, or just
- kind of on his page?
- Oh, no. His log-in
to his account.
- You log in to his account.
- What did you find?
- Nothing.
- The first picture
that pops up was a picture
of him and some ex,
like, hugged-up
next to each other, smiling.
- There's nothing wrong with that.
You know, went to a friendly wedding.
- But I thought she was
the crazy ex-girlfriend.
- No, no.
This is a whole different person.
- Oh!
- Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
The other person had nothing
to do with it.
- But I don't know
if that helps your case at all.
- It should.
- But could you have seen this
if you weren't logged in?
- I would not have seen it
because, even though we were friends,
he had me set so I didn't see
shit that posted up. Yeah.
- Oh, my gosh!
- You not set no different
than anyone else on my page.
- Yeah, okay. Okay.
- Everybody sees the same thing.
- You're claiming that it's a public thing
that she could have seen?
- I don't know.
I mean, I don't know
how Facebook really set up.
- Ay-ay-ay. And so, this was
your last straw basically?
- Right, and I told him
I no longer felt comfortable
with him going on the trip,
but you still owe me for it,
because it's your fault
that you're not going.
- Got to say,
it's not looking good for you, buddy.
- When I tell my side of the story,
it's all gonna make sense.
- So you're only suing for...?
- $397. Just half of it.
I just want what he would have paid
if he had gone.
- Okay. That seems reasonable.
Okay, Fred, let's hear from you now.
Were you upset
about her canceling the trip?
- Oh, yes, 'cause I offered
to still go on the trip.
- Well, yeah, you...
- Yeah, I was ready.
I got swimming trunks.
Like, I...
Yes, I was ready for the trip.
I was gonna have
a good time no matter what.
- I bet you were, Fred.
I bet you were.
Okay, so let's go back then.
- So, it was...
- You think the relationship
was fantastic, was great, um...
- It was cool. It was good.
I mean, we had our ups and downs
like every relationship, but...
- Yes.
- One day, we was about to have
sex, and I wasn't in the mood,
so Miss Tiphani decides
to tell me, because
I didn't want to have sex,
that she was gonna go find
someone else to ..., so...
- It was a joke.
- I am a male.
Don't joke with me.
- It was a joke!
- Did you giggle after you said it?
- I texted it to you, so no.
- Did you... LOL?
- No.
- No. Okay.
So it's not a joke.
- Winky face, nothing?
- Yeah. I'm-a need something.
- Nothing.
No. 'Cause I was angry.
- So when she said this,
you genuinely thought it meant she...
- Oh, yeah. Okay.
You're gonna do your thing, so,
okay, I'm gonna do my thing.
Someone invited me to a wedding,
I went.
After she finds out I'm at a wedding,
she also spends, like, over
$1,500 on my Amazon account.
Yes, which I have right here.
- She spent $1,500 buying things
for herself?
- Oh, no, I bought shit...
- Sending random... random shit.
- ...and put it on his card
and sent it to his house.
- Okay, that's funny.
I like that.
Can I see that itemized list?
So, Mom, we actually, I think,
have some of these things.
Got him a Segway...
- This is so heavy.
- Segway.
- An electric skateboard.
Kind of got him, like, good shit, though.
Like, why wouldn't you get him,
like, silly...?
- I know I did.
I picked, like, really nice stuff.
- Does it look like I ride skateboards?
- You got him a bunkbed.
Like, an Army bunkbed.
- I'm not finna go hiking.
- All the stuff was really nice.
Who does that?
You're supposed to send, like, dildos
and, like... So, yeah.
It's about $1,500, so...
- There you go.
- Did you end up returning all of this?
- Yes, I did. And got no...
- And got his money back.
- And I was nice enough
to not even press charges.
- Why didn't you buy yourself stuff?
- Because I did not want
to get in trouble.
Well?
- Oh. That's some shit
I would do, honestly.
So it's hard for me now.
Sorry. How long was
your relationship in total?
- A year and a half.
- A year and a half
calling each other
"boyfriend" and "girlfriend"?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, this isn't an off-and-on thing?
- Oh, no, it was
consistently a year and a half.
- Fred, did you ever cheat
in this year and a half relationship?
- Nah.
- Fred?
- Such a lie.
- No.
- Fred, I'm...
- Nah, I didn't cheat.
- Fred, I love you.
- No.
She speculated, but I never cheated.
- Okay.
- Fred?
Oy.
I feel like, honestly,
you both can get away
with murder because
you're just both so charming.
I've seen a lot of couples
in this courtroom,
and-and they've just--
It's-it's been rough
seeing some people.
And seeing you two, it still seems like
there is potential there
for a relationship.
- Oh... no.
- I'm... good.
- With other people.
- I am gonna rule in favor
of the plaintiff,
Tiphani, for $395 for the cost
of your ticket that you made her cancel.
Case...
- Closed.
- Guys, you're dismissed.
Thank you so much.
- I feel like she heard my case,
and she understand it,
and she agreed with me.
- I can't help it.
I'm charming.
- He's a damn good cheater, honestly.
I will say that.
- You can see it in his eyes.
- I know, right?