Today on Chrissy's Court,
Cynthia Taylor is suing friend Gigi Moisé
for impound fees and a key replacement,
after Gigi got Cynthia's car towed
and lost the key.
Gigi is countersuing
for unpaid cat-sitting fees
because, well, you'll find out.
The people are real.
The cases are real.
And the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise...
to the Honorable Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Hello, hello!
- Hi.
- Hello, Mother.
Ah, you may all be seated.
- They're our case of the day.
- Thank you.
Case of the day!
- Yeah.
- So, Cynthia?
- Yes.
- You are suing Gigi?
- Yep.
- Uh, Cynthia,
explain your case.
- Oh, yeah, I had
a family emergency.
And Gigi had offered
to check up on Smoogler,
my kitty.
- Can I see a picture of Smoogler?
- Yes, you may. Here.
- I don't know why,
but I just love animals.
Oh, Smoogies!
Super cute cat.
- Yeah, he's my baby.
- And, Gigi, your sole job
is a caretaker for animals?
- Yes. I do watch dogs.
- Okay.
- I love all animals,
you know what I'm saying?
- Okay, so, Cynthia, continue.
- In-in leaving so quickly,
'cause of an emergency in the family,
I forgot to get his treats for him.
- "Treats"?
- Yeah.
- So, Smoogler has specific treats
that Smoogler must have.
- Yes, he does treats--
dry food, wet food.
And he has, like, a water
fountain water bowl and...
- Okay, high maintenance.
- He's-- that's my baby.
- A running water bowl,
a running water bowl constantly running.
- I didn't even know cats
had to be taken care of,
so this is all new to me.
I thought you could just
leave a cat for, like, a week.
- Right.
- A month.
- Yeah. I mean, a year.
- He doesn't drink the water
if it's not running.
- Well, Smoogs has fine taste,
and I think we would all do that
if we had the option...
granted to us by Cynthia.
- Anyways, uh, so I told her
to take my car
and go to Petco and get
the treats for him.
And she took my car
and she ended up venturing off
to visit a friend,
and parked my car in a red zone.
It got impounded.
That cost me $678.20,
which I have the receipt for you.
- Yes, I would love to see the receipts.
- Okay, all right.
And then she lost my keys.
- Oh.
- My God! Okay.
Gigi, you are countersuing
for $1,400, the amount
Cynthia owes for watching the cat Smoogler
for seven days straight at $200 a day.
Holy shit. $200 a day?
- It's like a Beverly Hills cat.
- Well... I'm about to learn
a ton of shit, I think.
So, now I want to hear your side.
- I feel like I need to get paid.
My time is not for free.
Gigi, what do you typically charge?
Did you charge her less than
what you would charge a...
client?
- I have some receipts here,
you know, for the time
I had her cat and the cat food
and the cat box I had
to bring to my house.
- What is she talking about?
- I had to go to big measures
to get that cat in my house
and make the cat
feel comfortable.
- You took my cat to your house?
- Well, yeah, honey.
- Gigi, I asked you to go check
on my cat once a day.
- I should charge you for the bite marks.
- Oh, my God.
- Let me go through Gigi's fees here.
- Hello, hello.
- She says there's a one-time fee of $73.
- Hello.
- A $875 overnight fee.
- And she got a $25 discount.
She got lucky.
- You had to buy a cat box?
- Yeah,
it needs to litter somewhere.
- She wouldn't have to
if you hadn't taken him anywhere.
- And my house smells like litter.
I forgot to add the cleaning lady.
- Oh, God.
- How about that?
- Okay, what is this "break fee"?
- Um, my break fee.
- So, you get paid for working
and then also get paid
for not working?
- Yeah.
- Oh,
Mom's loving it, personally.
Okay, but, Gigi, you know
you know...
- What?
- You owe for this car
and the impound fees.
- I'm gonna say I didn't know
where I parked,
I lost the keys,
and I didn't know what happened.
And that was it.
- Wait, where did you go?
- I went to a friend's place and,
like, I got kind of wasted
and I lost my keys and my phone.
- Honestly, that happens
to me a few times a month.
- Tell me about it.
And when I came back, the car was gone.
How do I know she didn't have a copy,
she had her boyfriend take it,
and then just hid the car...
- Serious?
- and then charge me for this fee...?
- Yeah, there's no guessing game on this.
Like, we actually have
paperwork for it, so...
- Oh, okay.
It wasn't my fault
that the red zone was there.
I didn't know it was there.
- I mean, the impound
was your fault, though.
- You know, it could've been.
But I don't feel like it is!
- It was!
- I didn't see the red zone.
- "It could've been"!
- I didn't know where I parked, okay?
But, you know, I had a hard time
taking care of that cat,
so I actually had to borrow
some of her watches.
- Watches are also involved in this now?
- Well, she didn't know about those yet.
- What is... what's the watch deal?
- So, I needed money because
of her cat needed some stuff,
and I didn't have the money to cover it,
so I actually took two watches
and pawned them.
- Are you serious?
My watches in the drawer?
- Sure did.
- Those were my grandmother's
watches, Gigi.
- I pawned them--
I got the receipts right here.
- Those were heirlooms.
- Hold on, Cynthia?
I want to let you know that
we actually have the watches.
They're safe and sound.
- At least I didn't sell 'em.
- Uh, that's an actual felony
you committed by stealing
the watches.
Um...
Okay, so, wow, this is a lot to take in.
Okay, so, Cynthia, I am going
to award you these watches back.
Gigi, I have to, I'm-I'm gonna
dismiss this countersuit.
But we're doing you a solid here...
on letting the felony go.
And, uh, you, you owe for this car.
I'm gonna rule in favor
of the plaintiff for $838.20.
But, Gigi, I appreciate your spirit.
- I need to get paid.
- Court is adjourned.
- Can I get the watches back?
- Thank you guys very much.
- Thank you very much.
- She just stole two watches.
Part of it is, like,
the confession alone, like,
the confidence in saying, like,
"Yeah, I took those watches."
- I'm scared of her.
- She shouldn't have got that car
and the watches and her money.
I got nothing but a felony washed off.
I could've done that myself.
- Would I ever let her,
uh, watch my cat again?
No, and I wouldn't recommend her
to anyone.