Today on Chrissy's Court,
Claudia McClellan is suing her roommate
Cooper Kelly for using her car
without permission
while she was out of town.
Cooper can't believe
he's getting sued for $30.
And the only thing
he's guilty of is killing it.
The people are real, the cases are real
and the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise to the Honorable Judge
Chrissy Teigen.
- Hello, everybody.
- Hi, Judge.
- Hello, Mom. Ooh.
- Hi. I like your hair.
- Nice hair.
- You, too.
- Thank you.
None of it's mine.
You may be seated.
Claudia and Cooper.
You guys both live in Utah?
- Yes.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay. I was born in Utah.
- Ooh.
- Claudia,
you are our plaintiff,
so go ahead and explain your case here.
- I went on a family vacation
to the Bahamas,
and left my car key with Cooper,
who is my roommate, so that
he could move my car for emergencies only.
But I came back home and realized
that my gas tank was on E.
Side note: I filled up my car
right before I left.
- So, Claudia, you actually have witnesses
that were home at the time
that Cooper drove your car.
Do you want to bring them out?
- Yeah. Let's bring them out.
- All right.
Welcome to court.
This is very serious.
Game faces only here.
Please welcome Kylee and Aspynn,
who are also your roommates, right?
- Yes.
- You guys have a four-bedroom house?
- Five.
- Five-bedroom house? Utah, man.
- I know.
- So, Kylee and Aspynn,
tell us a little bit about,
uh, what you witnessed.
- So, we are actually here
to sue Cooper and Claudia...
for the security deposit,
for everything that
they've ruined in the house.
- Honestly, who gives a crap
about their $30?
- Yeah.
- When we are worried about
our $1,500 security deposit.
- Oh.
- Okay, wait. Okay, hold on.
So, Claudia, you go ahead and go next
to Cooper now, I guess.
We have not experienced
this kind of twist here
at Chrissy's Court yes.
- This is a plot twist.
- Kylee Barrett and Aspynn Adams
are suing their roommates
for the security deposit
on the house they all share.
And you already know these guys.
- Kylee, Aspynn, tell us
about this part of the case now.
- We actually have video evidence.
- Okay, let's go.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, my God. This is the Utah
I want people to know exists.
This is the Utah I love.
Okay, whose room is that?
- So, that's my bedroom.
- Did you do that with the intent
of crashing through the door?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
- And there is, there definitely
is a backstory to this, uh, door-breaking.
- Yes.
- It was already broken.
- But it was already broken
because those two were fighting
like they always do.
- So, Kylee and Aspynn,
you guys have any proof
of this security deposit?
- We have our lease right here.
- Okay, perfect. I personally lost...
- Please.
- ...every security deposit I've ever had.
I have bulldogs. I have never
gotten my security deposit back.
What is your rent for the entire house?
- $1,690.
- $1,600 is, like, my Postmates weekly.
So the security deposit
was $1,500 for the entire house?
- Yeah.
- This is just gonna...
I'm never gonna get tired
of hearing-- This is amazing.
- So, we...
- And you don't believe
you're gonna get that back.
- I don't.
- No.
- Just the security deposit?
I mean, does that even cover a door?
I feel like a door is more than $1,500.
- Not a door
from Utah.
A door from Utah's like 20 bucks.
- I need to do my research here.
- And she has a family dog
that she likes to bring over
quite frequently, and his name is Ozzie
and he broke some of our blinds as well.
- Ooh. Shredded.
- Okay, so Claudia and Cooper,
I-I understand this was
completely sprung on you.
Do you have any kind of defense?
- I do not think that $1,500
is-- in damages.
Maybe $300 at most.
- Okay. Let me think for a second.
I'm gonna rule in favor of the plaintiffs
for the damages incurred to the house.
Um, I'm assuming the doorframe
came off the hinges, everything,
so we're gonna do $200 for that,
the blinds: $100.
Any kind of paintings
that are around the house
just from, I'm sure, random frolicking,
which probably occurred as well: $50.
And an installation fee
for all of that: $100.
So that's $450.
$225 from each of you
go to the plaintiffs.
And then that $30 gas
from Cooper to Claudia.
That is my ruling, so...
court is dismissed.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- I was not expecting for my own
witnesses to turn against me.
And those girls Aspynn and Kylee
are messy, too.
They're not just angels.
- They owe us money now to get that fixed
and then, I think they're
a little upset about it,
but here we are.
- Sounds like fun house, though.
- I know.
I honestly think it seems super fun.
I would definitely have
Snapchatted that body slam, too.
That was really good.