Today on Chrissy's Court,
Stormie Lolles is suing her ex-lover,
Italia Roberts, for the cost of a camera
that was broken
during a physical altercation
after a date at Six Flags.
Italia claims that their relationship
was an emotional roller coaster,
so they both share the blame.
The people are real, the cases are real,
and the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise for the Honorable
Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Killing it.
- I know.
- Amazing job.
Hello, everybody.
You may be seated.
Stormie v. Italia.
Stormie, go ahead and explain your case.
- I am suing for $280
for the value of my camera
that Italia broke.
- How did you meet?
- I met her off of POF.
- Oh, Plenty of Fish. Okay.
- Plenty of Fish, yes.
- Mom is on there as well.
If anyone is interested.
How long were you talking
on Plenty of Fish?
- So, we started talking in January.
We didn't stop talking till March,
'cause in March, that's when I got
arrested with her and went to jail.
- So, just two months in, you...
you were in jail.
- Yeah. Two months in...
- The both of you?
- ...we were in jail, the both of us.
- Okay. So tell me
about this Six Flags incident.
- So, we got to Six Flags.
And then we literally get
in a verbal argument
on which way the ride for the swing was.
- We actually have a map,
a complete map of the Six Flags.
Italia, if you'd like to come to the map,
I would love to see
the trail that you went on.
- So, she starts going in that direction,
and I told her, "Stormie, the direction
to the entrance is in this direction,
going this way."
Um, and then, at that point in time,
she [bleep] just go...
...starts going crazy and is like,
"You stupid-ass [bleep]."
And I'm like, "What are you tripping on?"
- Okay. So she's going in
the complete opposite direction.
- Right.
- How did I go the wrong way
when I made it to the swing first?
Because I stopped.
I didn't [bleep] follow you.
Dumbass. You're dumb.
- You-you...
- Sometimes these relationships
are passionate
when they're...
when you have these fights, right?
And did you kind of get off
on that a little bit?
- She liked to fight as [bleep].
I don't know.
So, either way.
- What?
- You ride the swings.
Immediately after, what happens?
You guys are going back to the car.
You're over it. You're done.
- And then, on the way home,
we get in another big argument.
She's like, "You're just
a huffy little bitch.
Da-da-da-da-da. Get the [bleep]
out of my car. Da-da."
- I told her to get out of the car,
because she was just,
like, yelling at me.
- I'm like,
"Bitch, I ain't getting
the [bleep] out of shit."
And so she was like, "Yes,
you [bleep] are. Yes, you are."
So she-she comes
all the way in my face, right?
And I nibble on her cheek.
And then we start swinging.
She starts swinging on me.
- You nibble on my cheek?
- Yep, I sure did nibble on your cheek.
- You practically bit
my [bleep] cheek off.
- I sure did nibble on your cheek.
- You are [bleep]...
- Order.
Okay.
- She just has to do something...
- Yeah.
- ...every once in a while.
She's getting paid to do this, so,
every once in a while, she yells out.
Can you nibble on my mom's cheek
in the way that you think you nibbled
on her cheek?
- Yeah.
- Mom, honestly, I want to know,
like, if this is an accurate
portrayal of the nibble.
- Do you really want me to...
- Yeah, we don't care.
- Okay.
- Ooh.
- I did that.
- That-that was not how she did it,
because I had puncture...
I had punctures.
- It was punctures
'cause I socked yo' ass.
- No, you...
- Stop playing.
- No, you're [bleep]
dump as [bleep].
You [bleep] dumb.
- Order.
Talk to the judge!
- Order, order.
Yes. Good job, Mom.
Okay, so that, in no way,
was an accurate portrayal of the nibble.
After the nibble of the cheek...
- That's when she, um, swung on me.
- No, I did not touch her at all.
- You-you didn't swing at me?
- Not one [bleep] time.
Okay!
- That's why
I broke your [bleep] camera,
and that's why we're here,
'cause I didn't touch you.
-Literally. She snatched,
'cause I had a wig on.
- Yeah, your fake-ass hair.
Fake-ass hair. Take it off.
- I had a pretty, long wig on.
- Ugly-ass. Ugly-ass.
- She hated that I looked so good in it.
- She snatched it off. She was like...
- What?
- ..."You ugly little bitch.
You little..."
- No, she came over, and she jumped
over the center console,
and we both fall out of my truck together.
I fall out on my back.
She falls out on top of me.
- I fall on top of her?
- And she's just whaling on me.
- Yeah, I'm beating the [bleep]
out of you.
- After she got up off of me,
I grabbed her camera
and just slammed it against the wall.
- So, the cops were called,
and you both get arrested.
- At first,
they were only going to arrest me.
And, at that point, I said,
"Why am I getting arrested
when I'm the one..."
I said, "Look at my face.
Look at my..."
You know, I had bruises.
I had her teeth marks in my cheek.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I [bleep] did. How do you...
How are you gonna know?
- Which-which side? Which side?
- You were hella far from me.
- Which side?
Which side did I bite you?
- Shut up. My...
My left side.
- You're [bleep] lying.
- My left side. My left side.
- I bit you right here,
you dumb-ass bitch.
- You bit my mom
on the left side of her face.
- ...which side, you dumb bitch.
- I bit you like that, you dumb-ass ho.
- Okay, stop being dumb-ass hos.
Um... I'm just kidding.
I just never get to say that, ever.
I feel like my whole heart hurts
just from saying it out loud
that one time.
Um, but I do want to go to Six Flags now.
Okay, so only you're going to jail.
And then what happened?
They saw your face. They saw...
- And then they finally
arrested her after.
- You were in jail for three days.
- Mm-hmm.
- I got bailed out.
My mama came to bail me out.
- The same day?
- The same day, I got...
I was in jail for six hours.
- You don't know that she's
bailed out that same night.
- Mm-mm.
- You go three days in jail.
- Mm-hmm.
- Did you not want to ask anybody,
or just nobody could or...?
- No.
My mother was going to bail me out.
- How much was the bail, if I may ask?
- My bail was at $10,000, I think.
- Oh, my God!
- I told my mother.
She goes, "Do you want me to do it?
I can do it."
I said, "No, don't worry about it."
- You ended up losing your job
because of the time you were in jail.
So what happened?
- Take your time.
It's okay.
You're not buying this?
- I'm not buying shit.
- She's upset.
- It's just stupid,
'cause she's so [bleep] twisted.
- I'm twisted?
- And it's like the shit
that she says is, like...
You know, it's crazy. And she...
She's the type who--
she lives her whole life,
you know, having people pay for her shit.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know?
She doesn't know
how it is to be independent,
how to only count on yourself.
- Yeah.
- And to have nobody there, you know...
- You're 35 years old. Get a grip.
- My age has nothing to do
with what I'm talking about.
- It does.
It does. It does.
- And, obviously, you know...
Whatever.
- Whew. I'm really glad
you two are not together.
Yeah, I mean, the fact
that you both went to jail
means the police thought you were
both guilty of something, so...
My first gut was that, obviously, like,
you deserve this money
for this camera, but...
I think, like, there... Uh-uh.
- No. Oh. Oh.
- Uh, uh. Hold on.
- Oh, my God.
- I feel like there is
emotional distress that goes into
going to jail for three days.
And you guys did this together.
So, my ruling, I'm gonna do
a case dismissed here, um, and...
- Can I say something to her?
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- Can I hug you?
- 'Cause this is... this is closure to me.
- Aw.
- This would be incredible to me.
- This is closure to me.
And I've been wanting
to get this out of the way
for a long time,
even if I won or if I didn't win.
I just really wanted
to get this out of the way.
- Ah.
- So, can I hug you?
- Yes.
- Oh, Lord. Thank you, guys, so much.
- I'm sorry, Italia.
- It's all good. It's all good, babe.
- Are you gonna get back together now?
- Ugh. 'Cause, honestly, I swear,
this is the first case
where I would've went back there
and I would've...
Honestly, like, my heart hurts.
I hope you guys never have to
act this way with other people.
So... court is adjourned.
Um, thank you, guys, so much.
- It's cool.
- Thank you.
- You may leave.
- Ooh.
- I have closure, and I feel better,
even though I didn't get
my camera or my money for it.
I absolutely stand-stand by
my decision to break her camera.