Today on Chrissy's Court...
Gracie Wilks is suing roommate
Cassie Ledbetter for driving her new car
1,800 miles to a Phish concert.
Cassie says Gracie would've done
the same thing if she
were in her boat and thinks
that she should be let off the hook.
The people are real,
the cases are real,
and the judgements are legally binding
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise for the Honorable
Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Good morning, everybody.
- Here she is.
- Good morning.
Gracie...
so, you are suing for $542.
You guys are both 20 years old.
You're so young.
Baby's first lawsuit.
So, why don't we go ahead
and start with you?
- Okay, so,
Cassie's car was having some problems,
so I let her borrow mine, um,
just to run errands around
the town for the weekend,
um, while I was staying with my boyfriend.
But when I got back, um,
I realized that there was over 1,800 miles
on my brand new car.
Um, yeah, found out that
Cassie actually drove my car
to Maryland without telling me
for a Phish concert from Alabama.
- So, it's, it was a brand-new car?
- Brand-new car.
I had literally gotten it, like,
a month before.
Brand-new car.
- Okay, I was like, "Holy crap,
I would never notice
something like that ever.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Here's the funny part
is I never would've known anything
if I didn't get a speeding ticket
in the mail,
like, six weeks later
that Cassie got on the way to Maryland.
I didn't even know that I got it,
okay, in my defense.
- Okay.
- It was like one of those pictures...
- Oh, the flasher ones, okay.
- Exactly.
- The ticket is $42
and the 500 is the wear and tear.
- $42 for a speeding ticket?
Oh, my-- that's like--
How much is it here? It's, like, $500.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Plus, you get dings on your insurance--
that's, it's--
that's crazy.
- Your nanny got it all the time.
- Our nannies get them often.
I don't drive, 'cause
I'm me.
Cassie, now you are free
to tell your side.
- She loaned me her car.
She didn't give me any stipulations
of like, "Oh, you can only drive
to work, you can only do this."
It was like, "Here's my car.
Use it while you need it."
A friend of mine who lives in Maryland
texted me the day before the concert.
And it's a 12-hour drive,
so I literally had to leave, like,
four hours after he texted me.
- I think you should be incredibly
grateful
this is only a $42 ticket.
That is bonkers-- we got to move.
- Yeah.
- But the thing is, like,
the reason why I don't feel like
I even owe her the $40,
me and Gracie live together
and her boyfriend eats all of our food.
Like, all of our food,
and that's been, like,
an ongoing dispute with us.
And so, when I owed her $40,
I was like, "Consider us even
for all the crap
that I paid for
for your boyfriend to eat."
- Yeah.
- Okay, um, who wipes up
all of your cat litter
that's all over the floor?
- Wait, so you both share,
you share a place,
your boyfriend lives there as well?
- No, he's just over plenty.
- He lives there right now.
- Well, Mom,
what are you thinking about this?
- You know what?
The Phish show, what is it?
- Oh, Phish.
- It's a band.
- I thought it was a fish!
What, you thought it was, like,
a fish show, like a dog show?
- Yeah.
- Also worth driving to Maryland for!
- It was a band she went to go see--
it's not a dog show.
- Oh, oh, oh, I thought...
- There are no fish shows.
- Oh, yeah, oh, okay, okay.
- So, yeah, okay, well, Mom gets it now.
Um, so this number of 500--
where does this come from to you?
Is this just a number you thought of?
- I looked up the book value of my car
and the damage that driving it that far
puts on my car--
that's the price value on it.
And, you know what, I'm not budging on it,
because I can't do it anymore.
- Here's the funny thing.
I looked up the book value,
and the difference is
$26 in value, not even close to 500.
- Ooh! Okay, so do you have evidence
you'd like to present?
- Yeah, let's go for it.
- I have evidence as well.
- Yay, can you grab it? She's like...
- Yes.
- She's got stuff to do!
- Evidence...
It's up there.
Wow, so you, Cassie,
you did your research,
and you actually found out
that the Blue Book Value
- For the amount of mileage
that I put on the car,
not even close to $500.
It's a $26 difference.
Honestly, I'd be willing to pay the $26,
plus the $40 ticket, like...
- So, would you accept the ticket price
plus the $26 as a settlement?
-No, I'd accept
the ticket price and $100. I need to get
an oil change anyways.
- 1,800 miles?
You know how frequently
you should get an oil change?
- How frequently should you
get an oil change?
Tell me, mechanic.
- What they say is every 3,000 miles.
- Oh, every 3,000 miles?
- But... yes.
Gracie, you are a terrible negotiator.
- Okay, you know how much
an oil change costs?
- $45?
- Okay, a hundred bucks.
- Sounded like Luna.
- So, let's say
an extra 20 bucks for that.
- Yeah, that's my daughter.
That's how Luna does it.
Oh, they're just going.
- Okay, you know
that I can't afford to pay you
that $500, Gracie.
- Okay, well,
I can't afford to have
to go and get my car fixed
when it breaks down because
you've driven it 2,000 miles!
- You drive your car long distances for
work all the time.
- Exactly, because it's for work!
- You guys, stop!
It's making me so sad, honestly!
- Talk to the judge, talk to the judge!
- Okay, what about
a payment plan of sorts?
- $142, or a payment plan, sure!
- Why don't...? Why haven't
you guys just communicated
about this, though, you live together,
you're good friends...?
- Because every time we try
to communicate on about it,
it's like this.
- It ends up like this.
-It's like this.
- It's us pointing fingers
and never getting anywhere.
- Just butting heads.
- So, we need you as
a moderator, please, help.
- Okay.
- You know what I really, really want?
- What?
- I want you, Cassie,
to pay $142 to Gracie.
And I want you to hug so badly.
- Aw!
- Is that okay?
Can we do that?
- Yay.
- I love you.
- Ruling goes to the both of you!
I'm gonna find you Phish tickets,
and I'm gonna get you Phish tickets.
- Yeah, you got to go together.
- And you can take my mom.
- Yes!
- Yay!
- We'll have a great time.
You'll love it.
- What is it?!
- Everybody wins here! Case adjourned.
- Let's go VIP!
- Bye-bye.
- Even though I have to pay $142,
I would definitely still have gone
to the Phish concert.
- I love Phish even more
after this whole experience,
and I'm actually really glad that Cassie
has gotten to see them, too, now.
- Let's go have a beer.
Thank you, guys!
- Court adjourned!
I'll see you at the bar.
What are you doing? Hey, let me out!
I'm going to the bar!
- Ow!