Today, on Chrissy's Court...
Isaiah David is suing
his former best friend,
Chandra Bouchard,
for an unpaid loan of $300.
Chandra claims that Isaiah
is just a hater,
and the only thing she's guilty
of is living her best life.
The people are real, the cases are real,
and the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- Please rise...
to an Honama...
the Honorable...
Oh, my God.
Please rise...
to an Honoma...
Honorable Judge...
for an Honorable Judge...
- For the Honorable Judge Chrissy Teigen.
- Judge Chrissy Teigen.
Hi, Judge.
- Hello, Mother.
You may be seated.
So, Isaiah, you are suing Chandra...
- That's correct.
- ...for a $300 loan.
- Yes. Um, my ex-friend here, Chandra...
- Ex-friend?
- Ex-friend, yeah.
- Okay.
- I no longer deal with her.
Chandra, aka Budget Barbie,
was struggling financially.
She was, like,
crying, breaking down.
I was like, "Hey, like, don't worry.
"As a friend, I got you.
Here's $300, but as long
as you pay me back..."
- Was this an oral agreement,
or is there a contract?
- We didn't sign anything.
It was basically a verbal agreement.
Like, she was my best friend, so I tri...
I put all of my trust in her
that she was gonna pay me back.
So I gave her the $300,
and the next thing I know,
I see her on Instagram,
she's out in Vegas
living her best life.
I'm like,
this is the same girl
that was crying broke,
and now she's, like, poolside in Vegas
turning up with bottles and...
- Awkward.
- So, I do have a photo
that I, uh, was able to screenshot...
- Okay.
- ...from her Instagram
before she blocked me.
- Oof. Ooh, you blocked him.
Oh...
- He deserved it.
He deserved it.
- Oh. Living best life.
"LBL."
Okay. So, Chandra, your defense.
- Throughout our whole friendship, he was
a great friend to me,
I was a great friend to him...
- How long was this friendship?
- We've known each other
for, like, seven months,
about, eight months.
- I honestly thought you were
gonna say seven, eight years.
- No.
- So, I was out of work
for three months,
and I had a family emergency.
So he being the good friend that he was,
he let me borrow the $300.
- You had a family emergency in Vegas?
- No, no, this is before Vegas.
- Okay.
- I ended up going to Vegas
for my 21st birthday.
And that wasn't something I funded myself.
My friends took me out for my birthday,
because, you know, you don't pay
for your own birthday.
Like, you know what I mean?
So, I mean...
- Well, some people do.
- I think that he got really irritated
'cause I didn't invite him.
And I think it was because
he wants something more
than a friendship,
so that's why I think that
I don't have to pay the money back.
- Really?
- Yes.
- This is definitely false.
I've never tried to take her on a date
a day in my life.
- What has he ever done
to make you think that
he's into you, romantically?
- Honestly, nothing.
No, literally nothing. Like...
- You guys might have to drug-test her.
- We do not do drug tests here.
I wish we did.
Not on me, but everyone else.
- I have a text here, too.
- Okay.
Can I see that?
Thank you.
Basically, Chandra, you ghosted him.
- Yeah, because he's being so rude.
- Well, he said,
"Hey, where have you been?"
You responded, "Who's this?"
- Yeah, like...
Like, at that point I was pissed.
I'm like, okay, like,
this is the same person...
- Like, did you delete
his number or something?
- Yeah, I deleted his number,
and it's like, I don't need
that negativity in my life, like...
- And then he says,
"You've been ghosting me.
I lent you money. You ran off.
What the ...? Seriously?
This is how you treat me? Wow."
You go on to say, "You text me
every day about all of this.
Of course I'm gonna ghost you."
I mean, he...
he wants his m...
- But he won't text--
he won't text me,
like, just to hang out.
He's only texting me
about the money, it's like...
- 'Cause you don't have money to hang out.
You don't even have money
to pay your bills.
Where are we gonna hang out at,
the street?
Like, where are we gonna go?
Like, you don't...
Like, I can't pay for everything, like...
- I mean, yeah, at some point
you have to resolve
this part of it so you can go out again
and hang out as normal friends.
So, I mean,
what is your defense here, even?
Because... you know you owe that money.
- It wasn't like I wasn't trying
to pay him back, though.
Like, I was out of work
for three months before
he loaned it to me, so I basically...
- But you were working
when I first met you,
and then you took a break,
'cause you had a family emergency.
You came back, and you're
still at the same job,
because I spoke to Alexis,
and she says
that you're still working there.
- Ooh...
- So I know where you're at.
I know that you're making money.
- Yeah, I know.
You've been there. You've been stalking.
- You're working.
- You've been stalking me.
- You make good tips.
- Like, you can say
that you don't go there,
but you stalk me there.
- Order.
Talk to the judge, please.
- Thank you, Mom.
- You're welcome.
- So, you both work
in the same mall,
so you see each other often.
- We see each other often,
but you haven't paid me back,
and you've been working...
- Yeah.
Because you've been rude about it.
Like, it's a-- it's, like
a pride thing at this point.
- It's my money. It's my money.
Like, I need my money back.
Like, I can be as rude as I want to be.
- He wants his money.
- Yeah.
And I wanna give it back,
but he has to ask nicely.
- No.
It doesn't matter how he asks for it.
What's he supposed to do?
I mean, this...
You can't ghost somebody
that you owe money towards.
Like, he did you the solid.
He did you the favor.
That's obvious.
You owe him $300.
So my judgment is for the plaintiff
in the form of $300.
I will see you at the mall.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
Thank you.
- You guys can go.
Is that not the most obvious case ever?
- Yeah.
- Was that not
the most obvious case you've
ever heard in your entire life?
- Good job.
- Like, why should you have
to ask for your money back nicely?
Please can you pay me back?
- The situation will
definitely make me think twice
about asking a friend for money.
Never doing that again.
- There's just no possibility
that I would ever want to date her.
And that's that.
- I should have charged her more
just for being
such a brat about it
- Yeah. Get her for interest.