Today on Chrissy's Court,
Cassie Sanchez is suing
her ex-boyfriend James Fowler
for the cost of a car title loan
that she took out for him
and he never paid back.
James believes he's paid her back...
in other ways.
The people are real, the cases are real
and the judgments are legally binding,
no matter how unqualified the judge is.
- This is Chrissy's Court.
- All rise...
...to the honorable... Judge Judy.
I know, I cannot do it.
Very sorry.
- All rise
to the honorable-- honor...
- To an-- the honorable, um...
- You got it.
- The honorable Judge Chrissy Teigen.
My daughter.
- Wow. That was incredible.
- Judge Judy.
- Hello, everybody. Please be seated.
Cassie, you are suing James,
your ex-boyfriend.
Cassie, explain your case.
- James and I began dating
about three years ago.
We've been on and off.
Right now we're off.
He was expecting a settlement.
- From what kind of case?
- It was from an auto accident.
So I agreed to cosign on a title loan.
And the agreement was
that he was gonna pay it off
in a month or two,
when he got the settlement.
- Okay.
- You know, it's been over a year.
He's not been able to hold down a job,
he's been in and out of jail
and when he does have money,
he refuses to pay me back.
He just-- he wants to spend it
on his remote-control car.
- James.
- Yeah.
- I will say that I love those things.
James was expecting
a settlement of $10,000,
and it ended up only being $500.
Why is that?
- 'Cause my attorney sucked.
- That's what I thought.
- Did he help with any payments
throughout this process?
- No.
- James.
Do you have a job?
- Um... Not at the time.
- No.
Not really ever.
- I was dealing with, um, incarceration.
- And it's hard to get out of that,
honestly. It's...
- Yeah. Probation...
- It's a tough thing to climb
out of once you are in.
- He had money to pay for his car.
It was over $1,000.
- Your shoes are killing me,
with the... the-the squeakiness.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Stop squeaking.
God!
That was an expensive remote-control car.
Can I see it?
And play with it?
- Yeah, can I approach?
- Yes, please.
- Can I see the car, please?
Ooh.
Your shoes are [bleep] killing me
right now.
They are-- are they not
the squeakiest things on the planet?
- It's a little bit...
- Oh, God.
Oh. Don't put it up here. Put it down.
You do it.
- No. I don't want to ruin it.
You're telling me this is $1,100,
this car?
- Yeah.
- So...
- This is what he's put
before our relationship.
- Here, Judge, you try.
Ooh!
- Oh, that's so cool! I love it.
Case goes to the plainti-- I-- no, I'm--
case goes to the defendant, sorry.
- Try to go backwards.
- Shit!
- I...
- Oh, my God, I'm...
Oh, this is cool.
- There you go. You got it.
- Holy shit.
I'm so scared!
No, I don't want to do it anymore.
Can you drive it? Show me, like, tricks.
Like, go in between things and do stuff.
- Probably can go on turbo.
- Dude, that's awesome.
Like, honestly, I swear to God,
I love this already.
- Oh...
- You got to admit, that's cool.
- It's a sore subject.
- Do you play
with other people, or are you just going
in a circle by yourself? Like...
- He spends money on trips to tracks.
- Yeah, let me see that.
Trips to tracks.
That sounds like a good website.
So when you have this money,
because clearly you have this money
to buy things like this,
why haven't you made a payment?
- I just feel like
I don't owe it to her because
we spent the money
that we got from the loan
on rent and bills for the house
that we were both living at.
- He spent it on his part of our bill.
- But, like, all our money's
been shared the whole,
the whole time we've been together, so...
- All of my money.
- What have you paid for,
in the grand scheme of your relationship?
-Nothing money-wise, but...
- James!
If this case didn't exist
right now at all, tomorrow morning,
are you s-- are you looking back
at having some sort of payment plan
or being able to do this?
- No.
- I'm trying to help you out here.
I've spoken to so many people
that have been incarcerated
and have been
in that position of-of having
to figure out life after,
and it's not an easy thing to do.
- Yeah.
- And I don't want you to think
you're alone in that feeling.
But ultimately,
my judgment goes to the plaintiff.
Cassie, for $2,500.
If you can, please let him
set up a payment plan
so he doesn't feel like he is struggling
immediately from the beginning.
Court is dismissed.
Thank you guys so much.
Can you leave the car, please?
- Can we play with it?
- No. Leave the car.
- I love him. He just needs
to start being responsible.
- Toy cars is my hobby,
and I love to travel around
and meet new people and be able
to go to new tracks and stuff.