Room service came for sure.
Get orange juice ...
Yasemin?
Well ... it's
actually time to talk.
Yasemin I know how it looks. But make sure ... But make
sure, it's not, it's not what it seems.
So nothing is really how you know it.
You know, I was trying to tell you. I was going to tell you, Yasemin.
Shall we go down a bit?
You want?
I'm going to say something. Come in if you want, let's talk like this. This place looks ridiculous.
Will you shut up, please?
What did I say?
I said let's talk.
Derin.
... Is everything okay? ...
... Lamb? My mom, my sister is sleeping.
I scream, I scream ...
... it doesn't sound. I'm very ...
Scared.
- Okay, mom. All right, Ece. Do not be afraid! - What happened?
- Okay mom? I'm coming now. - What happened? - Do not be afraid!
- Don't hang up the phone, okay? - He still hasn't woken up, Mom.
- Well done, well, well, est ... - Yasemin, did something happen to the children? What happened?
As if he cares so much!
- I care, of course, they are my children. - My dear. Well well.
- What happened, Murat? Is there something wrong? - I don't know, I'll let you know.
- Yasemin. - It's okay, Ece, dear. Look, don't be afraid.
Your sister slept deep. You have become a huge girl, my dear.
Yasemin. Come on, let's go with my car.
- Look, let's go in the car, please! "I'm not going anywhere with you, Murat!" Leave me alone!
Look, please, we are in a difficult situation. Our children are there. This is not the time to fight. Would you ride it, please?
Yasemin, they are my children too. Look, he's going to fight now ...
... not us. Please! Please let me go together. We'll talk later.
Okay, I'll continue, okay. Please!
You have a lot of persuasion!
It lowered the woman a lot!
Anyway.
Let's see what it had to do with it.
Room Service.
Just in time.
Ece'cig ...
... My dear. Never fear! Get out of the room. Trust me.
Nothing will happen to your sister. Well?
Just a little tired. It's OK darling? Girl, come on, baby. Ece calm down ...
- ... dear, okay? - Murat, get out of here, what would you be?
What would you be
How can you do this to me?
How do you do it? Well done mom. Well done dear.
- Yasemin, Yasemin, I'm sorry! - Do not do! Don't do this to me, Murat! Do not do this to me!
Well done, I am one. Well done dear.
"If I were you, I'd act first.
If you get what you can ...
... you're not for me anymore."
You feel good. Don't be naughty, okay?
No mom. No mom. Get out of the room, okay? I'm coming soon.
Well.
Ece, let's go.
- Murat, look ahead, what's wrong? - I'm looking forward.
- What are you doing Murat? - I'm looking for an ambulance, I can't step on it. Please take it, I'm driving!
- So you're angry. - Honey ...
Look, your dad will talk, Mommy. It's okay. Well well. I gave it my dear.
My dear daughter. Do not hang up the phone! We are coming, we are on our way, my dear.
Is it alright my dear? Calm down, calm down my beautiful love.
- Calm down. - Hello?
Well, you need an ambulance. Urgently, my daughter fainted.
No, no, I don't know what happens. I'm not at home, she's with her little sister.
Derin? My Ece!
We'll see the patient for a second.
- My daughter. - What happens?
- Miss, are you okay? Sir, wait a second. - The pulse?
- Pulse, calm down, sir. - Look at your pulse again.
Sir, the pulse is good. I am sorry. Bring a stretcher.
- I called but he didn't hear me. - Oh my God, well done! No, nothing, look.
Isn't that Murat? It'll be good. My dear. Good for you.
There is nothing, girl. Come let me look, let me look, sit like this.
Oh my lamb! How beautiful you looked, you reported. Good for you dear. What happens?
- Loss of consciousness. Get clear information from the hospital. - Well.
- Can we go with you? - Better if you follow me.
Ah okay! We will come from behind.
- Come on Murat. - The coat? - Down, let's go!
Derin?
Ah okay.
Why hasn't he come back yet?
The doctor will respond more clearly.
Is my sister sick?
No lamb, no. OMG!
- What is the patient's condition? - Loss of consciousness. Your blood pressure is high. Nine sixteen.
- There are signs of dehydration. - How was it?
We do not know. We weren't at home.
A medication that we do not know, illness, etc.?
No, there is no medication.
So what is this smell? Drank?
I do not know.
Let's get the patient inside.
Take blood pressure, blood count, tomography of the patient.
Get three. Faster Faster!
Come, my lamb, come.
Come my love, come.
Moron!
You can't do this to me!
You can't do this to me ...
... not Murat.
Yasemin, look.
- I want to talk. - The doctor is here.
- Doctor. - Alcohol related toxicity occurred.
- We washed his stomach. - Is it alcohol?
Drank?
... eat alcohol. But do not worry.
He is fine now. We have done everything necessary.
We are entering your room right now.
You will rest for a few hours and will be discharged.
Nothing, huh, doctor?
It's OK now. Just get some rest.
- Thanks. - Get well soon.
How? So much to go into an alcohol coma like this?
How did I skip this? This child is turning into this ...
- How can I not see this? - Yasemin, it's okay.
Do not be so hard on yourself. Little boy.
Shouldn't it charge?
Murat, are you aware? We are in the hospital now.
- Okay, nothing. - God bless ...
... something could happen to our daughter.
Who am I talking to?
Isn't it all because of your indifference?
Insult and belittle my concerns ...
... not your indifference?
You exaggerated, you said you said you stopped!
Take a look, where are we? I wish you too ...
- ... you were a little over the top with me. - Did all this happen because I did not exaggerate?
That's the problem? Murat, what are you saying?
what do you mean? That's!
I do not know. You say. Are you mad at me for this?
Or why are you so mad at me?
Why don't we tell the truth?
Why don't we talk tonight?
Why not talk about what you saw in that hotel room?
- What? - Do not do it! Do not do this!
Ece is sleeping there. Do it with you at the hospital right now ...
Of course I won't talk.
Of course you will not speak.
We will talk.
Do not do this to me!
Don't do this to me, Murat!
Do not do this to me! Do not do this to me! Do not do this to me!
I'll make you pay for this! I'll make you pay for this! I will pay for this! You will realize this! I'll make you pay!
You will regret, you will regret.
Okay, I know you won't talk. But I will speak.
Please, Yasemin. Look, you have to listen to me.
Before you blame me like this ...
... you have to listen.
Look Yasemin. For a long time ...
... because you are away from me, myself ...
I was feeling lonely.
Everything looked beautiful from the outside, but it wasn't really good at all.
You know it too.
Yasemin has grown inside of me over time.
You never got close to me.
You wouldn't let me get close to you, Yasemin.
One minute, one minute, one minute.
Am I guilty of cheating?
Never! I do not want to say that. I was telling you what's inside.
No, since I said ...
... my mistakes, the bad things I did against you ...
... you keep counting, I think.
I never meant to say that! I'm telling you what's inside
- Why don't you want to listen to me somehow? - Murat! Because these are all excuses. This ...
... what you're saying is false.
A bundle of lies?
What I say are my feelings.
I feel like that!
We take our patient to the room. You can see if you want.
Thanks. Here you have. Ok I'm on my way.
Murat. Get Ece and the bag.
I'm taking it, darling.
My daughter?
My daughter, come the sister woke up, sister woke up.
Oh my beautiful daughter, my dear daughter.
Here. Number nine. Here you are.
Thanks.
Children don't know anything.
We were so scared, Mom!
But what did you do? How scared we were!
My only. How scared ...
- ... Ece was. - I am sorry.
Irresponsibility, but this is it. We trust you.
We left his brother. What if something happens to you?
We go out with your father!
Are you better dear?
... Thanks god.
Did you sleep with your sister?
Yes my sister. I am sorry.
I called my mom. Spoke to me.
Because I cried a lot.
My daughter, everything is fine now. Look, your sister is fine.
Very good.
What's on your arm? Serum.
They also wore me. Isn't it mom?
Yes my mom. They also brought it to you.
- Did you get very sick, sister? - Not!
I'm fine, my lamb. Do not worry.
I also ruined your romantic evening. So sorry!
Not you, my dear, not you.
I will take care of the payment process.
Lady?
Ma'am, can you open the door?
Ma'am, are you okay?
I am not.
I am not fine at all.
Call me a taxi.
My mom. Ok, I'm fine! I can walk alone.
You came here by ambulance, my lamb.
Your father opened, come on.
Go.
One minute.
- My daughter, may you get well soon, dear. - Thanks Dad.
- Good night darling. - Good night.
Mom, it's okay. I'm good. Thanks.
It is intertwined. - What are they?
So pain relief. Well ... I ...
... my head hurt a lot. Of course ...
- ... I leaked before assigning. - Ay Derin?
My mother! What happens Look, you opened your eyes again.
I drank, I got drunk. I am sorry.
I fainted because my body is not durable.
But it will never happen again. I promise!
Sight! Grow and dramatize everything. But I am overwhelmed.
Please!
Ok, now you sleep, rest.
We will talk later, but this topic. Here ...
... this problem is not closed.
Well.
Good night.
Yasemin.
Actually, it was time we talked.
Yasemin. I know how it looks.
But be sure, it is not. It's not what it seems. So nothing is really how you know it.
You know I was trying to tell you. I was going to tell you, Yasemin.
Shall we go down a bit? We can talk? You want?
- Yasemin. - Don't waste your breath, Murat!
While I was trapped in Derin there two days ago ...
... this subject here with you ...
... I won't speak. All these things ...
we should ignore ...
Do we tell ourselves the lies we tell our children, Yasemin? How it will be?
Not! But for the goodness of our children we will hold back, Murat. Ourselves.
We will act like adults!
- Good Morning. - Good Morning.
- Good Morning. - My dear daughter? - Good morning Dad.
- Good morning dear. - You're drinking tea, right? - Oh please.
Daddy? Can you convince my mom?
- Because? What happened to my daughter? - Because I'm fine.
I can go to school, I say. But it does not allow it.
What your mother says is my daughter. I can not do anything.
According to the plan of throwing us at each other, falls into the water ...
... take your omelette.
Eat. Murat, omelette?
- Please. My daughter, can you give me? - Comadamente.
What am I going to do at home all day?
- I'm going to explode with boredom. - Ece, dear, look ...
- .. all the cheese will be finished, lamb, come on. - You should eat it my father.
Ece'cig. You have become a huge girl.
You can eat it yourself. No way. Go.
My mom?
If I arrive early? Sight! I have a lesson in harmony.
If I don't go, then the teacher uses those things!
Derin. No. You have a report.
No one can say anything at this time.
When I come from school, my sister Bahar will come.
He plays with you. You never get bored.
Isn't it mom?
Mutton. Bahar's sister quit her job. It will no longer come.
Why is that?
True mother. Didn't he say anything?
He had another important job.
But I miss it. Come to see us.
I'll call her today.
I asked. Let's see what matters.
- ... back again? - Super! Super!
- What happened? - I'm going to work, girl. I'm late. See you later.
- I'm also under tea. - C'mon darling.
Take care of yourself.
That's enough.
Barlas Bey does not eat bread. You do not know?
I'm sorry Mr.
- Good Morning! - Good morning honey.
Thanks.
What have you done Are your plans for war ready?
I'm preparing.
So have you set a location? What work will you do?
- I do not know. Maybe I'll take your job. - Is that so?
You know, you work late at night. Maybe it will help.
Is the horn in your ear, Sitare?
Making use of your experience for Onur ...
... is a great opportunity darling.
Here you have.
I had a terrible night. They took me to the hospital. I am now under house arrest.
What did that stupid drug do to my head?
We go up to ten minutes.
You go anyway. I have several jobs. I see you mom.
- Mommy? - Air kiss, don't forget.
Ah, mother.
A goal in minutes. Here's your son.
"My beautiful son, my dear son."
Sitare is loosening up from day one.
Look at your son. But the language is as much as you say.
Would you have breakfast without bread?
What's going on?
I am sorry.
I didn't get a chance to call. Last night ...
- I don't even matter, do I? - You do.
Because nobody cares what Bahar ...
... happens to him.
You left me like shit.
When I called you, you didn't open it. Until this time ...
... I didn't even think about it!
It does not even matter!
I think you do now you know
Go away!
Decide what you want to do first.
Because I'm so sorry.
- Do you understand? - Yes. - I ...
- ... I'm so sorry. - Bahar?
Please open the door. Let me explain what it is about.
Bahar was a bad thing yesterday. Derin was in very bad shape.
We took him to the hospital. I waited all night.
I also didn't get a chance to call.
Go down?
So sorry. You are right. I just left you there and left.
Bahar?
Are you going to open the door? We cannot handle such a thing.
Sight! The first chance I got, I jumped up and came.
To tell you what happened.
I couldn't talk to Yasemin. I can not speak.
Or to recover the situation after yesterday ...
... I'm trying. So don't be mad.
So that Yasemin wouldn't get mad. So nobody is upset, Bahar!
My daughter really got sick. When he said it was an ambulance, it was a hospital ...
... I couldn't call.
Bahar, will you open the door?
Can you open the door please?
Damn!
Curse!
- Onur? - Hello Aunt Yasemin.
I came to see Derin.
Is that so?
What did you do right
He will be very happy seeing you. Come.
Derin? Look ...
- ... Onur came to see you. - I know mom.
- We talk in the morning. - Oh, is that so?
- How are your parents Onur? - They're good, they're good.
How good that you came. I'm going to get my car.
- My eyes won't be back now. - Where's your car?
I'll tell you. Come on, let's go out.
- See you mom. - See you later.
Mrs. Filiz?
I'm going to get my car. Whatever happens, keep an eye on Derin.
- You know. - Don't worry ...
... Mrs. Yasemin. I got it. Do it comfortably.
- ... your work. - OK thank you.
Children are entrusted to me.
No I do not understand! How? These drugs will give you ...
How can he touch it? That's fair for me ...
... to count. Did they tell you something at the hospital? This ...
... is it normal? No, if it's not normal ...
Let's call the doctor. Let's say: like this.
The medicines you gave us touched us.
Well, I mean, medicine, ...
doctor ...
What?! What does Derin doubt? Tell me.
Onur, yesterday I had a glass of drink.
They touched him when he took the medicine.
But how do I know? So it's ridiculous.
Did the doctor tell us something like this? I do not remember.
Otherwise my mother saw the medication.
- So what did you say to your mother? - I said pain relief, of course.
I said I didn't take it. Then I threw it all away.
If you tried to tell the truth, Derin.
Impossible, Onur! While the tension between them is so tense ...
... I don't live! They both take my nerves away.
- What tension? - I said, either, it's not good.
No, I thought this weekend getaway would be good ...
... I got it on my face.
So my mom goes to the hotel to take her car.
Ece looked for my parents when he saw me here.
They hurriedly came with my father's car.
It's a total disgrace, so you'll understand! So my mom is taking medicine ...
... if she learns, she'll get cold!
So now is not the right time! Onur, please look! Anyway ...
- ... don't say ok? We can't hug my mother. - Well.
I will not say.
So it's still broken.
Do not ask. There is a strange tension.
No, they think they didn't show us either. But ...
don't they say anything?
No, why did you put it so much on this topic?
- You know something, right? - No dear, what does that have to do with it?
You always get along ...
I'm in awe of that.
My mother and getting along.
- Anyway. Change the topic. - What topic?
It is a question of drinking.
Come!
Do you drink something? Tea coffee?
I can have a coffee.
I am preparing sister Filiz. Do not bother yourself.
I am arriving right now.
We can talk at lunch.
I can come to you.
I'm waiting.
What happens? Are you okay?
My daughter, don't ask! Very bad things happened.
So it is complicated.
What happened?
The doctor gave me antidepressants.
Here I was wrong when I took the medicine and the drink together.
Then Ece arrived. He tried to wake me up.
We cried, we cried, my parents called.
They rush to the hospital.
I opened my eyes. Serum or something. I mean misfortune.
It was pretty bad.
That bad. Then?
- Are you OK? - When
I eat the serum ... ... of course I got up like a stapler. Remember.
The man with the medicine is not taking the man.
By the way, I was heading towards you. But my mother ...
... forbade me to leave the house until a second request.
Here's the classic drama queen Yasemin!
By the way ...
Onur is here!
I was going to say come, but ...
I guess my mom is a little mad at you.
Why is that?
- Said something? - Oh no. He said nothing.
How can I say? When your name is like this ...
... my mother has a state of anger that she tries not to show us.
Are. Frost!
So you say goose bumps.
Exactly. Or ...
Ece loved you so much.
I guess he got mad about quitting.
I suppose.
Whatever. Say goodbye
... we can see any guy.
Sure dear.
Say hello to Onur.
Well, he is here. Hey you say.
Hello? Onur'cug. Hello. How are you?
Well.
That is good.
Anyway, young people. Then I closed.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
I'm going to ask something.
Do you really love Bahar?
Yes! Why is that?
Then...
... How should I know. After all, you are from different circles.
She is also a girl who has passed through the circle of the angel.
What does someone like you share with him? I am thinking about her.
A girl who passed the angel circle?
I've never heard anything so ridiculous in my life, Onur!
And where did he come from now while he was standing?
Didn't you introduce it to me?
Since you have a friend, I think he can be my friend, right?
Bahar is not my friend.
So what?
So ...
Friend is something different for me.
We only meet Bahar, that's all.
Anyway. I just said my idea. You know.
What is Onur? Why are you so angry now?
I have to go out.
Well, you haven't had your coffee yet!
I will see.
Rude! Look at this!
What madman came again, I wondered?
I know you are home, Bahar. Open that door!
I said open.
Come!
It was upstairs, I hadn't heard it. What the hell to eat ...
... do you knock on the door?
Not me dear. You tell these stories to others.
I am standing, Onur. Here, sit down!
Come here.
Let me tell you up front if you have a long speech.
I had a really bad night. My head hurts.
- I'm not in the mood. - The man will get a divorce because of you!
No, will he marry you later? Do you think it will be like this?
Who?
- What divorce? - Don't fake me!
I'm talking about the divorce you're working on.
I couldn't understand which one he said because there were a few.
- Are you talking about your mom and dad? - Bahar.
Sight! Do not mess with me! Did you understand?
Don't work according to your head!
Otherwise I will regret you.
I'm honored to be so scared right now ...
... trust me, we don't have to talk.
So I'm better off going horizontal.
You know the location of the door.
Uncle Murat ...
Does he know you used it to get closer to my father?
I do not believe it.
He does not know.
Because there is no such thing.
Is that so?
It is.
So why are your fists clenched?
Your face is like paper.
If you want to sit.
There's no need.
- Tea? - Tea.
- Yes, Yasemin? - I came.
I'm down here
Well. Nobody ...
- ... not here. We will talk here. - No no no.
We can't be comfortable there now.
I think you come here.
Well. Come.
Good now.
If you continue my relationship with Murat now ... You
threaten to tell him everything.
I did it well?
It is not exactly a threat.
Just asking. Does he know he did it?
See what he thought. I think go and say.
Let it all come out.
Who is my father ...
... you know this relationship and you come to Derin ...
... you didn't even tell your dear Aunt Yasemin.
Let all our dirty clothes be dumped!
Okay for me.
What you don't understand is this Onur'cuk:
I have nothing to lose.
But you have a lot to lose.
Welcome.
Thanks. Let's go to a quiet place where we can talk.
I will follow you.
Finally!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
- What are you doing? - I broke the procedure, right? I am sorry.
I've been thinking since yesterday, Yasemin.
You came to the hotel last night.
... it was the worst moment of my life.
So blame ...
I'm sorry I gave you something like this ...
I couldn't realize that I was sad because of the sadness I felt for ...
I realized something.
Because I couldn't see.
We had such a thing.
How can you wait until this time to speak?
How can you stop? How? I can not understand. I do not mind.
Yasemin, it's called maturity!
This is officially insensitive, soulless!
But are you the emotion boy, Murat?
So you are in the vortex of your emotions.
while pulling from there to there
you also drag us.
Wait. You know why?
Because I'm not selfish like you.
Do you think it is easy to wait?
I am ruined. But unfortunately ...
... being a parent, being an adult ...
- .. something like that. - Adult?
Adult!
It is understandable without even knowing the word.
Sight! You see it? You do the same again!
That is all you do.
You do this so much Yasemin ...
... such a step is retreating. "I'm fine like this, I'm fine like this ...
... I'm so responsible, you're not an adult, ...
... you're not mature. Once you understand me ...
... can't we play according to my rules?
Everything has to be what you want!
We all have to be what you want, Yasemine!
No! Let's play how you want.
This time, let's do what you want. What do you want, ...
... I don't understand! Example, let me enter the company, everyone in the office ...
Should I yell at you?
Do you want this from me?
Here it is!
I wish you would scream, Yasemine.
- I want you to scream! - What's up, Barlas?
Well. You?
Well. We work. You know.
What happens? Did you come to chill your husband?
It is not a good sign that you are coming here.
God help me!
No. I'll miss Murat for lunch.
Food? Isn't it a little early?
Come on, you're fine again. Taking your wife out to dinner. You tore.
I'm not going to dinner. We are not going anywhere.
Murat. We need to talk. You know.
We don't have to do anything, Yasemin!
We don't have to do anything.
- See you later, Yasemin. - I will see.
What's going on, Murat?
Lemon situations?
You were just looking at the head. What happens?
Nothing, Barlas.
No. We will know if there is a situation. Maybe one of our benefits will touch, huh?
Nothing. We argue a bit.
You go on, brothers. All right, Barlas.
I don't like this guy at all. It doesn't come from inside me.
What does Aga work on? Why do you bet on each other?
You got caught being a libertine, right?
No. You are not the man who goes to wife and daughter.
What did you do? Forgot to take out the trash tonight, huh?
What! Oh laugh like that! Laughing at you is not appropriate either!
These days are like this.
What meeting were we going to have? Where are you?
- Are you coming? - Hello Sadri Bey. - Hello everybody.
We were going to eat, dad. So we give up earlier.
Well. You did it well.
No, Mr. Bey? No. He didn't come.
He doesn't open his phone either.
From day one ...
I'm in my room. You let me know
Let it come, prince. We do the meeting.
What is wrong with that?
I did not understand! Again. I think he fought with his wife.
Why?
Murat says nothing. It is absolutely ridiculous.
Exactly.
- Anyway, I'll let you know when I see Onur, dad. - Well.
Don't bother me with these things.
- I already have a lot of work! I'll go out, go to the club. - Well well.
- I'm on it. I'm even calling now. - Seeks! What the hell are you!
Not a company, the nursery is blessed! He turned to the nursery.
I told you.
You are not listening!
It would be better if I stayed in the office tonight.
I think this is the best.
Well.
You know.
Excellent!
It was literally great, dad.
Flowers, candles.
Murat is the heart of a woman ...
... he knows how to take it.
We had lots of fun!
It sounded like medicine.
Since we left Ece to Derin ...
... our eyes are not far behind either.
If you see Derin.
How is she so responsible ...
she became a thoughtful and wonderful young woman.
In fact, if we go together for a weekend ...
... you love it too, I'm sure.
We haven't been here much, but in the woods ...
... a delightful place.
We have to go back, Murat said.
He too fainted.
I guess it was good for both of us.
I feel better too.
More rested. Happier. Really.
I'm so happy!
Sometimes this should be a dream I think.
I won't wait for you from morning to afternoon!
- I have power! I'm going! - Ok dad.
- I'll talk to him when he comes. - Well. Let's talk.
I think it's early.
He wants to work, but it's early.
He is excited.
Are you saying that?
I think its purpose is not to work.
Provide some kind of status between friends.
Are you busy? There is.
Does anyone see your face when it comes to work? No.
As if we see your face a lot!
Don't get used to it, don't worry! It gets used like that.
- Did I say why, Dad? - Put this in your mind ...
Barlas, he's my heir!
You are not!
Come on thanks.
Really?
Yes.
- Yes. Aydan? - What happen dear? - I'm good.
Yasemin'cig. Did you have that singing girl?
What was your name?
Bahar.
Can you send me your number?
Why Aydan?
I said let's arrange for souls to celebrate company.
That day I had entertained everyone at your party.
Beautiful girl. Attractive ...
... her voice is also pleasant.
Then.
What happened honey? You're sad?
No. No. I'm a little tired.
Rest my life, rest.
Look, they say there is an epidemic. People at the hospital ...
... waiting in line.
- Good, Aydan. - So Bahar is home?
- Give me the phone if you want, let me talk now. - I don't quit work.
- Why is that? - I don't know Aydan!
What happened? Is there a problem?
Did the girl do something?
Did I break the pot?
No, I'm tired, I'm tired. We were at the hospital yesterday.
Derin poisoned.
Get well soon.
Thanks.
Anyway, I won't hold you back then.
It would be great if you sent me the girl's number.
- Good, now I'm sending Aydan. - Thanks love.
It was a great thing to find this Bahar!
Do you bet?
- Did you come? - I came.
Filiz Hanmcm, can you make me a simple Turkish coffee?
Sure now.
Thing?
There is something I have to tell you!
Tell. What happened?
Ms. Yasemin, I overheard you on the phone to Derin.
What did you hear, Filiz? Tell!
Let's talk in the kitchen if you want.
Let me tell you something like coffee.
You, sit down.
I'm fine. You want?
- Sit down. - I sat here.
Look at me!
You have everything in your eyes, right?
- It is very bad! I got so dirty! - Really?
- Is it that bad? - Disastrous!
Are you ready?
- Yes. I'm listening. - Yasemin ...
... Bahar and I in a hotel room ... trapped brother.
How is that?
Bahar has surprised me. I found a note.
Waiting at this hotel right now. I went too.
We were chatting.
Everything was so beautiful. Then the door knocked.
I opened a room service ...
Yasemin.
Misfortune!
Then Ece called.
Derin sick. The ambulance has arrived.
When we said Derin to the hospital or something ...
... we talked in the morning, but we couldn't.
We just couldn't talk in the parking lot and we got into each other.
That's!
So sorry.
- It's very bad Murat. - You or I?
Actually, I want to run and apologize.
I want to tell everything but ...
... we can't talk. Yasemin doesn't speak.
Then. Isn't it normal, Murat? The woman is in shock!
So how do we solve this without talking, brother?
I want to take it and tell you everything, I tell you Ruhi!
Ruhi, I fell in love with Bahar. I like!
What I can do?
But as long as I don't talk about it with Yasemin ...
... I feel like I'm cheating.
Look Ruhi I said once. I'll say fifty times!
I loved Bahar, I love brother. Well?
This is so temporary, three days, four days ...
It's not an adventure, Ruhi!
Murat, dear, come slowly. What's going on?
Why am I being slow? Look at me! Look at me!
I feel like I have been living for the first time in many years!
I started to enjoy life for the first time!
I feel the sun, I feel nature.
I see the city where I live and live, Ruhi!
For years with Yasemin's authority, with her emotion ...
... heals all her wounds.
That is why I fell in love with Bahar!
Well. Handsome. Well.
- What about the sores you opened? - What wound?
What wound have I opened for years?
Yasemin ...
Couldn't he be affected at all?
Really ...
Does she feel nothing?
So even with a little pain, huh?
Of course he is sorry.
But I think you are unfair to her. Look brother.
Me?
I will tell.
You are being unfair.
I got your number from Yasemin. I'm a friend.
I would like to talk about a job.
What are they doing?
Will they offer money or something?
How absurd!
Trying to hug your friends in my head? I did not understand!
What is it?
Hi Bahar. I am Aydan. Yasemin's friend. I got your number from her.
Y?
Well ...
My husband's company is on the anniversary every year ...
..it is celebrating. At this year's party ...
I thought you would go on stage.
- Ms. Yasemin gave my number? - Yes.
... Is there a problem? No.
There is no problem.
- It just surprised me. - I know, sugar.
You are no longer working with them. But ...
... I think it's perfect for our organization.
I already told Yasemin.
I don't think there is a problem.
I think you thought it was great.
On what dates?
So ... How can I say that, Ms. Yasemin?
Derin, to your friend ...
... he said over the phone.
Just because the drink doesn't kill the person.
You're sure? I listened with my ears.
So he actually said more of a joke but ...
... I thought you'd better know it anyway.
What are they?
So pain relief. Thing ...
... my head hurt a lot ...
Of course, I leaked before assigning.
I can pass?
You have already come.
- Are you okay? - I'm good. Mother.
Please.
No ... I ... you know ...
... I wanted to ask.
You want to talk?
- Really? - Yes.
But we have to talk!
Derin, my ...
I have concerns.
My mom! I am sorry.
I had a drink even though I promised, I know.
But it will never happen again! Agree?
I don't want you to promise me, Derin.
I want to be aware of your responsibilities.
Look, you're not aware, but ...
... you changed.
what do you mean?
So I want to say that we are together ...
sometimes our friends ...
... can negatively affect.
What friend of mine are you talking about?
Is it from Onur?
Nerd! I told him to give an example.
So only.
The people who came into our lives ...
I'm talking about what changed us.
My mom. What friend are you talking about?
Can you say it openly?
Is it a problem with Bahar?
What is this Bahar? Since the morning, every number, ...
... of listening to Bahar in every conversation ...
... I get sick! Who is this girl?
Who is this Bahar? What is our deal with Bahar?
I don't understand that our lives are enough to confuse us ...
What can I do with Bahar? What can you do with Bahar?
Bahar is your equivalent?
Oh God!
... this equivalence issue! What should I do?
Mother, do I take the exam? They meet my high criteria, my family, ...
... to suit my location. Let me bring it up and then take the quiz!
- Did I say Derin? - What are you saying? Mommy!
What are you saying? You are the usual, but right?
You always want everything to be what you want! Managing us all ...
... you want to play with all of us! Once ...
... once you understand me, according to my rules ...
... if we play this game. No way, huh?
It always has to be what you want, but right?
Let everything be as you want!
We all have to be what you want!
Let's all be what you want!
What did I do to you?
What if I'm breaking down
Mommy.
Yes Aydan?
Now I threw in Bahar's number. You call sometime.
Why are you throwing me Bahar's number now?
I do not understand.
... for the company dinner. The girl was empty at the time.
- You talk about other details. - What detail?
Ruhi so he can go on stage. Singing girl.
He appeared on the stage of Murat's birthday.
Aydan ...
... what are you doing according to your head if you ask me?
I don't understand that either!
- You said she was beautiful. - No, that girl.
No way! Lets talk later. I have a job.
Go. Well.
I guess something has happened.
Why is he so angry?
It broke a lot.
Hearing Bahar's name is freaking out today.
They know. After all we ...
... made our offer. I think it was a very good idea.
I agree.
There must be a problem with the girl. Why did he
leave ... ... from Yasemin?
Do you know something?
No. Who knows?
... I have to go to the company, honey.
I will take care of my son.
They never get along with Barlas.
Let me look up a situation, but you must not put each other, father and son.
Well. I'll go to my date too. I wait a bit there.
- Thank you. you waited with me. - Oh honey!
Kiss, goodbye.
Account, please?
I've been waiting in the meeting room for two hours. What is there, what is salient!
I asked my grandfather, "Where?" is already out.
Murat's brother doesn't know the world anyway!
You got them caught up in these ridiculous reports, I've been analyzing them for two hours.
These are last year's reports!
What are you trying to do?
I'm trying to work, boy, but you're like this ...
... how do I do it?
These high school jokes aren't yours?
Let me tell you if you are trying to intimidate me with this. Not that way!
You need to find something more solid.
Well, that's it son. If you don't like it, go out with your friends.
This company works like this.
I do not go anywhere.
But I think you take care of yourself!
Eolueek.
- Sister Filiz? Where is my mom? - In the garden.
Derin?
I don't think you check it now. Morale is very bad.
Let's calm down a bit. Come on, huh?
Well, it's too cold.
But I don't think I'm cold right now.
Welcome ma'am.
Welcome Mrs. Sitare.
What did you mean that night?
It is not so difficult to understand.
You can never replace Yasemin!
What are you waiting for?
Do you think Murat and Yasemin will marry you?
Look darling.
These guys are occasionally ...
... can eat fast food. But ...
... finally ...
... he will go home.
Because they are used to home cooking.
Actually, that's what they want.
You just ...
... how to put it?
So ...
Understand.
You are a lover, darling.
Unfortunately, it will continue to be.
I recommend you ...
On the baby's lap ...
... all alone ...
... if you don't want to cry in a damn house ...
... blow your mind ASAP.
This is not the right place to hunt, honey.
You will be lost.
It was the baby in her arms!
You will see that baby!
I'm not my mother, Mrs. Sitare.
Everyone will see this!
All of you!
- Father? - My beautiful daughter?
- Don't be late at night! - What?
I say late. Don't be late at night! I will cook.
- You? - Yes!
I put together a big menu ...
... no dessert. It would be great if you get dessert while you come.
Well, my daughter is fine. I'll get one, okay.
- Good, see you. - Goodbye.
I came.
Hi Yasemin.
If Murat?
He just called Derin.
I'll cook in the evening. "Come," he said.
- I couldn't say I'll sleep in the office. - I'm not aware of that.
- Are you ... aren't you at home? - I'm not at home.
I'm at home, but this dish ...
... has nothing to do with me. I didn't look for Derin.
I don't think so, Yasemin.
Are you okay?
In the afternoon ...
- ... let's not reveal anything, okay? - Well.
If I go home. Please ...
... let's sit down and talk, okay?
You didn't speak when you had the chance, Murat.
I said I won't talk about this with the kids!
Yasemin, don't do it. Come on, what would you be?
We'll see you at home.
Your office is set up threatening me. I am ...
... I am your blood. I'm your dad.
As a father, if I can't tell you two pairs ...
Where is my father? I'm a donkey?
Shall we go out to dinner with Murat and Yasemin?
For the love of God, Sito! Don't call me Murat and Yasemin!
They are fighting.
- How do you know that they are not doing well? - In the parking lot today ... wait a minute.
I saw them in the parking lot today.
They obviously fought. If you see Murat, without encouragement.
Murat has finished. Then Yasemin arrived.
"Let's have dinner, husband," she said.
"I'm not going anywhere with you," he said.
Misfortune! They all saw it. It is there in front of the company. Misfortune!
Well. We have to make sure.
We even called Aydan and Ruhi.
Do we even have to go everywhere, dear? Well.
Murat, Yasemin is fine. Wherever you go with them.
He retires. But ...
... Don't call Huri and Aydan, let me love your eyes.
Huri, don't say it and keep it.
He gets mad, you know. I can't shoot Aydan anyway!
The woman did not shut up! The car asks ...
... order a burrito, order a muffin. She is not a silent woman.
Penalty, Barlas.
- Well, think of it as a gift. - Dinner?
It was nice.
Great misfortune, Sitos!
Great misfortune!
In the parking lot! In front of everyone!
I brought spare shoes with me.
Welcome.
One minute.
Me or you first?
Here you have.
I was very impulsive in the morning.
You are right.
You have obligations and responsibilities.
So sorry!
You are also right. I should have reported. Me too ...
... sorry.
Bahar.
I'm in the vortex ...
... I can't tell.
Actually, I tell Yasemin the whole truth and talk to her ...
... you and her and all of us ...
I want to save this ridiculous situation.
Even though I promised you, I can't talk to Yasemin anymore.
Why is that?
Because Yasemin ...
... doesn't want to talk to the children.
It was weird.
I do not know.
Maybe Yasemin is causing the guilty kids not to talk to you.
Or maybe this situation ...
... is trying to ignore it.
Perhaps.
This is ridiculous, but ...
Maybe he's doing it. I do not know.
Look, Bahar! I've always been honest with you.
Now I will.
I told Yasemin all the things ...
... without solving this situation ...
... I don't want to meet. So our ...
... it's not right to meet like this. My purpose ...
... to cheat on you or my wife
Not to put him in a position I don't want.
Not really!
Do you get it?
Thanks.
Sight! This is between us and you ...
... so beautiful I never want it to end. But ...
... I don't want it to be used like that either.
Being upset ...
I don't want anyone to get mad about breaking it.
I know.
You are very nice!
I have time.
I can wait.
I miss you like crazy.
But I can still wait.
Also ...
... this is a cavalry you're doing.
- Come on, dear. - But it is.
So ...
I'll talk to Yasemin and figure everything out. Well?
I say it one more time. My purpose is not to cheat on my wife ...
... and put you in a situation I never wanted. Well?
Well.
Like I said ... I
'll wait.
Please don't feel compressed from my point of view.
Well.
I have a person who listens well.
I have one person listening.
It's really nice to see that!
It is very cold outside.
Will I make you a herbal tea, Mom? It warms up for you.
- Need help? - No.
My mother. You come ...
Come, look, sit like this.
Stretch your feet too. So enjoy your tea, huh?
Aga, I can't hold this woman.
Ulan was right here. It means exit.
Where are you aga? I made friends with a passenger.
- Welcome Sitare. - We thought it was nice, sugar.
What happens?
We decided to. We will have dinner together tomorrow.
I do not accept excuses.
Is there any news from Yasemin? I'll ask him.
Maybe he made a plan, Sitare.
No way! We decided, okay.
Barlas will take us to a great place. Isn't that so, darling?
Then yes. A wonderful place aga. Just ...
I already made a reservation. Destination!
Great place order.
Thank you.
Ms. Yasemin? I bother you ...
... or I complain.
So, I wanted to get your news.
Good thing you said!
Now I have spoken with a psychiatrist.
Let's see, I'll try to convince.
Mrs. Yasemin. Don't worry, okay?
Oh, everything looks amazing!
- Really? - Yes.
I couldn't make this salad sauce like yours.
Let me see.
But this is very good.
This is even more beautiful than mine!
I am very serious! What did you put in that?
Tell me. I'll do it too. I put tarragon.
My mother?
So sorry.
I'm sorry too! Derin! So sorry!
I went too far.
My intention was never to hurt you!
A bit of balance has been broken during this time.
But I promise you. It will not happen again!
Honey, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I wasn't supposed to go over so much, but ...
... something will happen to you.
Derin?
... I spoke to a psychiatrist.
Not! No mother!
Let's go once for me. What would you be
Maybe it's good for you too, huh?
You have a problem, you said.
Mom, I'm fine. Really.
Well. Let's go then. Doctor ...
... "Good." Let's say, let's go back. What happens.
Not! I think there is no need.
Derin?
Those drugs?
You didn't show me those meds. Why is that?
Because mommy ...
... I knew you would bring the event here.
Or are you growing a lot! But I tell you. I'm good.
Derin? Sight! Don't worry about going to the doctor, right?
Of course, no!
Well! Let's go. But I tell you.
There will be a waste of time.
I have enough time.
I'll take care of your sister.
- You were going to help me with dinner. - Not!
You said I would do everything myself.
I also know a little quick. Your father will be here in half an hour.
Ugh mom!
OMG!
I just got home from work, girls. But you are executing me.
Well, I've been cooking all day, Dad!
- I also played games. - Good for you, my little bug.
Good for you!
- I brought it. There is nothing else. - Okay, mom. You, sit down.
Bread. I take the bread and come.
My daughter, this dish ...
... is there any special meaning?
Actually there is.
Give it daddy. Let me put the salad.
I ruined your last night and ...
... an apology for worrying you all.
- Well. We appreciate. - Mom, salad?
But do not worry.
I will make up for my mistake immediately and ...
... arrange a new weekend vacation for you.
Good enough.
No. One night was enough for me.
One more heart will not rise.
I miss you so much.
- Dad where? - A courier would come from the company ...
... let me look at it. Well?
Well.
My sexy and beloved wife.
What's for dinner?
- There is artichoke, good. - God!
Dad not here?
No.
Ay Barlas, I ask you to eat in the middle.
- For example, my plate? - Serve daughter.
Without Onur?
Not!
- I think it's more broken than you think. - Broken?
How are you broken?
The brat as much as the leg kept telling me.
Sitare has sent me as you know. What are you going to do?
Well, we'll take care of the rest, daughter.
Along with the employees ...
... the habit of talking back and forth ... you have to give up, Barlas.
Sitar! Then don't put my demons on top!
For your knowledgeable son ...
What about father and son?
It shouldn't be too big.
I'm growing?
I'm growing? Look, I'm eating, Sitos.
Your son who didn't come to dinner. Tell him, not me! No problem.
You go too much, Barlas.
How much my father Onur cares. You know. Your kindness ...
- ... makes him happy. - You crush me too!
- You crush me too! Well done Sitare. - Where? - I'm going out!
- Food? - Did you stop your appetite, Sitare? Did you leave your appetite?
- Artichoke? - What artichoke?
Barlas?
- We'll be late again. - Nothing will happen dear.
I reported that we stayed in traffic.
They will wait half an hour.
This traffic won't open for half an hour!
We can't catch up on life!
Is everything okay, Ruhi?
Yes!
- Why is that? - I do not know.
You got really mad today. I did not understand.
No, I tried hard and I wish you a good celebration.
I'm also a contributor ...
Let me know, I wanted a touch to help. Suddenly ...
I didn't understand anything when I yelled.
But then this is not your help, Aydan.
This is your command.
You could consult me before you call the girl.
I also don't like getting you involved in my work.
You know.
Also that girl ... for the celebration of our company ...
... is not a suitable musician.
Why is that? Didn't you tell me ...
... I really like it?
What's going on, Ruhi?
Said!
Said! Well.
A Turkish guy.
I thought of another musician for the company celebration.
Opened.
We go too.
Here you are.
Here daddy.
Thank you, my beautiful girl, thank you.
Enjoy it. I am depositing Ece today.
The world has come to an end, my daughter.
What a shame, dad. These are the things I always do.
Sure dear! Things you've always done, girl!
- Thanks. Bless your hands. - Enjoy your meal. I swear ...
... I'll deposit Ece, one day a housewife broke me up because.
What should your mother do, my daughter? Doing the same thing every day.
My mom is already one.
- I love you so much mom. - I also.
- Come on. Good night. - Good night darling.
Good night.
Even if Yasemin doesn't go, we can sit and talk.
Murat.
I've said it many times.
One thing we're both so angry about ...
... I don't want to talk when there are kids at home.
But we have to talk. Even a duty.
We don't need to do anything. You told me this.
We don't need to do anything!
Yasemin?
Why can't we just sit and talk?
Why don't you want to know the facts? What happened?
You don't want to know, huh?
We can't do anything about this! What would you be
- What happened? - Yes!
I can't pick up my head, Murat.
It's yours to worry about Derin's health ...
... whatever you say, I can't pay attention to it. I am sorry!
I am sorry!
What was in Derin's health, for God's sake? Little boy.
He tried to kill himself, Murat.
What else do you need to do to get their attention?
You're exaggerating again, Yasemin. You're exaggerating again.
I'm exaggerating?
Do you know the madicines, Murat?
"The curses in Derin's room?" - No. What medicine?
I'm talking about this.
If you try to understand a little before blaming me, listen a little ...
- ... maybe we will move more easily. - About the things I don't know ...
... maybe if you don't blame me ...
... we can talk better.
Well.
I am notifying then.
I made an appointment with a psychiatrist.
At least I'll be sure. Am I exaggerating ...
... am I not exaggerating?
At least I make an effort, Murat! I'm trying.
Am I not trying?
If you come to the psychiatrist tomorrow morning ...
... at least you'll be convinced of this.
This makes no sense! Derin has nothing.
By ignoring what happened ...
... we couldn't ignore, you said.
I will not fight you. I know.
... try to disturb but will not be successful.
What annoyance?
I'm not trying to do something like this! What are you saying?
Twisting and turning my words to me when the time comes ...
... you are the one who carries it like a spear to your head, Yasemin.
- Don't yell Murat! - Don't piss me off, then I won't scream!
Will you come to Murat yourself? Please.
It was like a spear!
I'll just remind you.
You were the first to say that phrase, it wasn't me.
I'm not telling you to talk, Yasemin.
I express my feelings.
So it happens when you do the same thing ...
... but it doesn't happen when I say it. Is that so?
Why can't we talk about it, Yasemin, huh?
Because Murat yells at me.
You want to be right all the time.
And you stop and distract the subject! So we can not talk!
Well!
I'm getting up. I go!
Can we talk to you?
Now?
Yes.
Is there a problem?
No.
- Good. - Go ahead.
I see that you are nervous.
Ah, please don't stress.
Especially in our young clients ...
... from time to time, we have meetings with a close circle.
A moment ready to see you ... I
just wanted to meet you.
I understand. Here you are.
How many years have you been married? Twenty.
Congratulations!
- Did I say something funny? - Then "Congratulations!" ...
... as if we were successful.
Although Yasemin may be right.
About?
In all aspects. Especially when it comes to marriage. He wrote his book.
How to behave? How not to behave? What is done?
What is not done? You know it very well.
That's all!
This is exactly what you do!
This is your behavior, this is your speech ...
... your ridiculous words.
When you do this, are there no bad intentions?
As the name says. I'm kidding, Yasemin.
I am sorry. I failed again.
I couldn't deserve you again.
Do you really want to do this now?
Come on, for the love of God!
Does it matter what I want?
It is?
No.
Because everything has to be what you want!
If everything is not what you want, you are having problems!
We all have to be what you want!
Oh, let's not be one! Let's not be one!
You take us away from you immediately ...
... you punish us without love, Yasemin.
As we crawl on the ground, we suffer, you ...
... with all your cold blood ...
... come in, you see us.
But you never forgive! Never!
Am I wrong because I didn't scream my pain?
Well. Let me tell you then.
You will always be happy ...
... every year without catching a cold ...
... because I prepared a birthday very carefully, sorry.
It will be said behind me ...
... or you will talk to your friends ...
... come and just say, "I don't want to." You can say!
But then there is no flavor, is it Murat?
I'm tired of this, you have nothing to say about Yasemin!
You think I blame you for Ece's illness.
Yes! You are right. I blame!
But I also blame myself!
With you, that child ...
... we could not protect that child that we must protect, Murat.
I am sorry.
I say "What should I do?" In my mistakes ...
I can't forgive myself as easily as you!
It was an accident.
What will we do?
This child is like
this ... ... this patient will continue to live ...
... I can't get out of it ...
As long as I felt something ...
... act without thinking ...
.. I can't!
Even if it hurts ...
... I hold on not to worry them.
This may seem like insensitive to you!
But believe me ...
I'm suffering a lot, Murat!
I am sorry for the injustices I have done to you ...
... to spend a night with you ...
... when I surprise you, you open the door ...
... when you are half naked with your lover ...
... Trust me, I'm sorry, Murat.
So sorry!
But then, when my daughter was at home in fear that she would die ...
I bury this pain in me
For days, it's like he's responsible for fooling
me ...
... blaming me, making fun of me ... ... making fun of you, I'm sorry, you ...
... was making fun of your phrase, right?
Trying to endure all of this ...
... on the other hand, "Could I be right?"
Because I'm a terrible person, make me ...
... could he have had to cheat?
If Murat.
I have a lot of pain.
Forgiveness.
Did you want to talk, Murat?
How well we were talking! What happened?
Well ...
... I think Derin is fine.
But if you want ...
... you can come with your husband.
Here you are.
Forgiveness.
Mommy?
Why did my father leave at that time?
I asked. He didn't say it either.
I think he was crying. Very urgent ...
... had to go to work.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I think I'm fine.
Mom, your car, drawn!
Mommy, your car was dragged the whole time and you didn't!
Your mood is really broken.
No longer.
- Come on, aren't you coming? - Well ...
... mom, I'm going to Bahar.
Well.
What happened?
Nothing. See you later.
See you.
What is happening with this woman?
Handsome. Well. What about the sores you opened?
What wound?
What wound have I opened for years?
... Yasemin ...
Couldn't it be affected at all?
So he doesn't really feel anything ...
... Is it possible?
So even with a little pain, huh?
Trying to endure all of this ...
... on the other hand, "Could I be right?"
"Because I'm a terrible person ...
... could he have had to cheat?
Yes Murat.
I'm in a lot of pain.
How happy are you!
Happy?
Are you kidding me?
No. Oh, you hit until You made it. What could it be?
This is what you wanted.
I didn't want such a thing.
Is that so?
What did you want?
Come. Let's sit like this.
Our boy?
Break the one he loves the most.
To understand that he is loved, those cardigans stop ...
... both you and yourself.
Indifference kills the lover.
Once you are used to seeing, hearing ...
... to be unique.
Otherwise they hesitate ...
... get angry.
Because to not be seen in the eyes of the loved one ...
... to not be heard ...
... it feels like you're not there.
Without Eva ...
... if I didn't look at him and yell, Adam ...
Could it be Adam?
I ...
... did these things?
Let me tell you a story.
The story of Yusuf and Zleyha.
Zleyha aa ...
... lives in wealth.
But he has become a slave to love.
One day he says to his slave ...
"Go! Find Yusuf, put him down ...
... stay well.
But leave him for your stick ...
... from here, from afar ...
.. . I can hear howls.
By order of the slave ...
... he's going to beat Yusuf.
But ...
... I can't see him when you see your beautiful face.
He sees a sheepskin there. He shakes his cane at him. .
Every time the slave shook his staff, Yusuf is also out of line ...
... oh, howl ...
... it starts.
Zleyha, who heard Yusuf's screams ...
... " Shoot! "He says.
" Shoot more. "" Shoot well. "
The slave says ...
" O sun-faced Yusuf!
Now Zleyha comes from behind ...
... if he doesn't see stick marks ...
... he takes me into account, he punishes me.
Now take off, open your shoulder ...
... grit your teeth.
The stick I'm hitting now will hurt you.
says ...
What should Yusuf do?
He undresses, opens his shoulder.
Lower the slave stick in such a way that ...
seven times ...
... heaven to earth ...
... groans.
It is a noise.
Who heard this last act ...
Zleyha ...
"Enough is enough!"
"Enough!
This is" Ah! "...
" came out very deep "
" Ah! "There is" Ah! "There is our boy.
... human beings will stop to love you.
When you hear, believe.
But he cannot bear the pain.
Like Zleyha ...
... "Enough!" she cries.
All of this I ...
... did I do it on purpose?
The real question is ...
If I say I did it without knowing ...
... does it reduce your pain and regret?
Change things ...
... will it heal the wounds you hurt?
- Coffee? - Well.
- I guess the permit is out. - What permission?
I come from the doctor, not from home.
My mother got me to be a psychiatrist.
So how did it go?
My father also came. The woman took two of these. Fight inside the apocalypse!
Well, my mom said, "Nothing," she says but ...
... my father was very flat.
Since he still sees me as a child, of course, he doesn't tell me anything.
Mothers generally do this.
But you have to show that you are growing, now Derin.
How can I do that?
Making your own decisions.
Well, I already make my own decisions.
You're sure?
So, for example, you decided to quit school. But what are you doing ...
... you don't dare say or do.
You are right! Actually, you are quite right.
Well. After that, I will be brave!
Handsome!
So brave decisions!
Get ready at seven at night!
We are ready and we go out together.
We can't, Barlas.
What can we say?
My belly button broke until I got the reservation. Why can't you come?
I guess Yasemin doesn't want it. I do not know.
Now I can't fight her, we're not coming!
There is no such thing! There is no such thing! Sitare takes care of that situation.
Aga does not interfere with women's work.
Get ready at seven thirty at night. Half past seven.
Bahar, thank you very much.
I didn't do anything, honey.
What else will you do? I feel great!
- See you. - Goodbye.
What happened again?
Did you come to pull my hair out?
I can pass?
This is not a topic to be discussed at the door.
Do you drink something?
There's no need.
You stay standing.
- I'm listening. - What?
So ...
Since you were the one who seduced my husband ...
I guess you have something to tell.
I didn't seduce your husband, Yasemin! Your husband seduced me.
I don't know what he told you, but ...
... I have no intention of being with a married man.
But Murat is married. With me.
You said well. Thanks!
Well ...
... is there something you want to tell me?
Like what?
Stop chasing my husband!
... and so.
How long has this relationship been?
Two years.
You didn't wait, did you?
Joke, Yasemin, joke!
What a bad idea came here ...
... I think I can talk to you. This is an absurd idea.
There is no relationship.
We only met several times.
We had a good time, that's all.
So will you continue the conversation?
I do not know.
You haven't talked to Murat yet, have you?
Yasemin, look.
Truths ...
... sit like this.
There's no need!
I'm fine. No Yasemin.
Let's sit down and talk.
- I'm listening. - Well.
You want to learn the facts.
I don't want to make you dumb anyway.
Then I will explain everything.
What it really is.
You are someone trying to take advantage of my husband's money and location.
Why should I trust you?
Because Yasemin ...
- I think your friends are not trustworthy. - What does that mean?
Beware of your friends, that means.
what do you mean?
Maybe they know everything.
But they are hiding from you, Yasemin.
What are you talking about? Who is that?
You better ask them.
After all, nobody likes snipers.
You are lying!
Could be. This is also a possibility.
I'll say something, did you break?
But you are quite right.
If I find out that my friends are stabbing me in the back ...
... I'm scattered too.
I do not have anything to talk to you!
If you say so, it is.
This is number one, I know.
Telling your friends like this ...
You're trying to make me paranoid.
Goodbye Yasemin.
If Sitare?
The reservation is complete by eight at night.
Barlas took care of that.
- Why is that? - What do you mean 'why?
We will go to dinner.
No. Why now? So did something happen?
Now there is not always space.
With cancellation reservation ...
What's the ridiculous question?
I answer like crazy!
What's going on honey We will go to the bottom of the dinner.
Do you have a problem Yasemin?
There is nothing. There is nothing.
... I have no taste, Sitare. If you'll forgive me ...
I think you were crazy! How difficult is it to find a place there?
Barlas was hurt.
I ate the meat off my head.
What am I going to say now? Isn't Yasemin's state of mind correct?
So ... this is also an option.
No ma'am! There is no such option. Get it out of your mind!
Yasemin! Coal coal.
Let go of your recipe. Live in the moment, honey!
You are completely trapped at home! You have reached the domestic feminine mode, Bravo!
I am very elegant.
I'm thinking of shining, honey.
Don't use anything simple there! Please don't make me like that please!
No Sitare. Whatever you wear, it stays with you.
I love this. Well.
I will give Aydan an ultimatum.
Let's close it. Do not be late.
Come on, I kissed. Goodbye. Goodbye.
I swelled up.
Well ...
... are you enjoying yourself?
- Shall we go to the meeting? - I don't understand dad.
You do not understand! They have all spread it!
The company has left the company! Discipline, etc.
... Do it well!
We meet according to the pleasure of the nation, according to the appointment of the nation!
We were finally able to meet today!
If we believe that yesterday I waited for you for hours ...
.... thank God. Damn, I'm an old man!
Do I have to wait for you here? What's that?
We have given our work to our children ...
...... we will be comfortable. Listen to it, don't believe it! Look at this!
Misfortune!
You're absolutely right, Grandpa. There is a great misfortune!
And it is clear from whom.
What does that mean?
Namely, I came to the company yesterday.
But meeting in an empty room for hours ...
... wait.
One minute! I don't understand anything. What's going on here?
Brother Murat, how do you care about the company now.
- You have no idea. - Yes darling? - When your mind is elsewhere.
- What does Sadri Bey say this boy? - Murat, Murat.
OK, calm down, calm down. Onur.
Be careful with your words! Your brother Murat is not your friend!
Because I have no idea that I came ...
Good. Understood. Barlas.
- You said he didn't come to me. - It's late, dad.
You were outside.
We will talk about them later. Yes. Schedule?
Not! Let's talk now, grandpa.
Because you don't know what's going on here.
My dad ...
... put me in a room for a meeting yesterday ...
... lots of old reports piled up in front of me.
I was like an idiot for hours ... I went through those reports.
It will keep me entertained and out of the game!
This is the agenda.
Mr. Sadri.
I sent those reports to your desk.
To have information.
Those who don't know last year can't understand this year ...
... I sent those reports just because he didn't know.
Onur well, shut up Onur, shut up.
Yes. Understood.
You dealt with the problems between you first ...
... call me at the meeting after that.
My time is precious!
We can't do business with the bad boy, Sadri Bey.
Speaks!
What do you mean, Onur, huh?
what do you mean?
It had nothing to do with the company!
My mind was elsewhere. Tell me where my mind is.
Tell me, let's find out, bro.
Good Murat. Here's the boy. Do not do anything.
Are we going to work with the child?
Sorry about the report, little one! I am sorry!
What things do you like from now on, tell me!
I will send them to you. I will even install some games on your computer!
Hang out with them! Get!
Don't go back to the meeting without reading them!
Everything is for you!
I didn't even open my mouth, you saw it yourself.
Welcome to the first league, son!
- Welcome! - Thanks.
There were pumpkins for the night. Should I do it? Murat Bey likes it.
There's no need.
My lamb. But we weren't running. We've alredy talk about that.
Mrs. Filiz, we're going to dinner tonight with Murat. That's why.
So there is no need, I said.
The game is very boring without running!
.. then the mother gets very angry, dear. You know it.
Mrs. Filiz?
So I wonder if you spend the night ...
It is possible. So with Ece.
- Derin but you know. - Of course I'm staying.
Do not worry.
Aunt Filiz. Shall we play with my babies?
But Aunt Filiz can't play with you.
- He has jobs. - Yes. I am ...
I'll tell the people in the house, okay?
- Then you play. - Mommy, I have a job too.
But you have become a great girl now.
You can play alone.
When will Sister Bahar finish? When will it come?
Then go to dinner with my aunt Filiz.
Why?
Let my father come. Let Sister Bahar come too. The three of us play.
Don't be silly, Ece! Do not be ridiculous!
Your mother is me. Did you understand?
Your mother is me.
I am sorry. I'm so sorry, my dear.
So sorry!
However, you squeezed my arm.
I know it darling. It happened by mistake. So sorry!
I'm really sorry. Let's do something, come on.
Then let's do something. Let's go to my room.
Let's prepare my clothes together. Will it be my darling?
Okay dear.
My Ece.
Come.
Come dear.
We chose this dress, right, mom?
Yes mom.
I'm going to dress Yasemin baby.
Well. Here you have. Dresses.
Without running, slowly.
For my husband's money, his location ...
... you're trying to take advantage of it.
Why should I trust you?
Because Yasemin ...
... I think your friends are not trustworthy.
What does that mean?
It means paying attention to your friends.
what do you mean?
Maybe they know everything.
But they are hiding from you, Yasemin.
What are you talking about? Who is that?
You better ask them.
After all, nobody likes snipers.
You are lying.
Could be.
This is also a possibility.
I'm going to say something. Are you broken?
But you are very right!
If I find out that my friends stab me in the back ...
... I will break too.
Where are you darling We will say the dishes.
Are you still freshening up your lipstick?
Well. It's over.
What are you doing girls
I tell that boy. I can not tell.
It looks oily.
What are you doing girls
- Why did you come Aydan? - So what should I do, sugar? I am bored.
- They always talk business. - Would it be, darling?
We have you watched with them. Men ...
... don't come to leave you alone.
Not! So while we were in the bathroom ...
... even if they find someone, Sitare.
There's nothing to do.
Yasemin, what happened?
Nothing. Well, come close. You are beautiful, okay.
He has worked very hard to reserve a place here. Go.
Go Go! Go.
The boy from yesterday is shaking my seat.
What? But this is normal, Barlas. So ...
... the horn will pass the ear eventually.
But the energy of the young man really ...
is another.
What are you talking about? Who is he?
Air sugar, water. Our youth. Our youth.
But! It's not that far ...
... honey?
Oh, you're going to say it for Barlas.
Did you say something? What did you do?
We did it while you were distracted.
Isn't it aga? Yes. Murat said the dishes.
I trust Murat's taste.
What did you say, Murat?
We thought everyone would eat fish.
Ah, there are crunchy calamari, butter shrimp, ...
... grilled octopus.
Everything else.
Bravo. You are not showing anything blessed! You ate the worlds.
Take a break.
Murat is such a person, but Barlas.
Take the worlds, nobody knows.
Actually, I wasn't expecting it either. Really.
Do you not eat such food at home?
But the man is right, honey. Everything ...
... so delicious. It is not?
Yasemin, I'm sorry dear. You're a great cook, but ...
... the taste of the outside is always more appealing.
There's nothing to do.
Is that so?
People get bored of eating the same food all the time.
He wants to eat something from time to time.
Whatever you do, keep doing the same thing. Dig in! Dig in!
Yes honey. Of course.
.. must try different things outside.
Isn't that right, Murat?
Well, I don't like it very much, but ...
... the food here was really great.
- Oh, don't let Yasemin listen! - Why my dear? You listened.
It is always good to increase competition.
Are you okay, Yasemin?
I think your friends are not trustworthy.
what do you mean?
They may know everything and keep it from you, Yasemin.
Yasemin?
Are you okay?
No. I am not.
As long as you continue to act like this ...
... it won't be good.
Yasemin, what is happening?
What happened my Aydan ...
Murat is cheating on me.
And everyone knows it.