Are you okay, Yasemin?
Yasemin?
Are you okay?
No I'm not.
As long as you continue to act like this ...
I'm not going to be okay.
What's going on Yasemin?
What happened, Aydan.
Murat is cheating on me.
And everyone knows it.
How, Yasemin?
Don't be silly, what do you say?
Yasemin.
What's going on, Yasemin?
Simply amazing.
An Oscar-winning performance.
Don't pretend you don't know.
What should we do, Yasemin?
We do not know. We do not know.
What does Murat ağa say about this woman? Look at Yasemin ...
... from everyone at this table.
This is not from this man.
I have worked at the fund for forty years.
If you say something, Ruhi.
What should i say
Let's ask a friend if you want, let's see.
It's possible. It is not?
What will he say?
If Murat.
Ağa, four-place bomber. Say something. Defend yourself.
Stop Barlas.
Sükut, it came from confession, isn't that Murat?
You have no face to speak.
Is it just Murat?
You do not have any.
I met you, my friend.
How did you hide this misfortune, this joke?
How did you digest it?
What kind of people are you?
I mean, Ay Yasemin.
Say ah.
You are also numbering without shame.
Are you crossing the wave behind me?
...I wonder.
Does that happen, Yasemin?
Done.
I won't be able to take this nonsense anymore.
Enough. Enough, Yasemin. Just one stop.
Why Murat?
We were going to express our feelings.
Sight. Now we do what you want.
I am boldly expressing my feelings in front of everyone.
What happened? You do not like?
Is this here?
Is it your turn to speak here now?
I have said that?
My Yasemin, my sugar. Sight. Calm down. Sit down.
Your blood pressure will go out. Come.
What should I calm down, Sitare?
What will I calm down?
Or you are one and you brought me to the clamp.
I know like my name.
You have already arranged this plate to cover it.
No looting. The game is over here.
I know. I know.
You are all in this business one by one.
I also met you, my friend.
But it's my fault. Should I say something? It's my fault.
I would never come here.
It would not be part of this misfortune.
But Yasemin.
What are you saying?
Sit down.
In disgrace to the nation.
Yasemin, calm down.
Not Murat yet? Yet.
God damn you all.
Yasemin.
I am shocked.
I can not believe.
I am in shock right now. Pain came to my head.
Open that phone.
Open up now, Murat. Just turn that phone on.
Yes it is ...
... something else ...
... I don't know, one of you knows.
You have the mic, Ruhi.
But you don't have beans in your mouth.
Aydan ...
... you can't stop either, you ask your husband.
You're talking nonsense, Barlas.
Oh Barlas. What are you saying? With Yasemin ...
... Murat's marriage turns silver, my brother.
What is this talking about?
Don't make the man sick. We'll get mad ...
... he yelled, you know.
Who knows?
Nobody knows.
Yasemin has officially made paranoia.
You did not see it? The woman exploded like a volcano.
This burned the coatings completely.
In fact, I've never seen Yasemin like this.
Where is that cold-blooded woman?
I understand, of course.
It is not an easy thing.
What I don't understand ..
What Aydan don't you understand?
Here is the mode of woman accompanying her husband.
She kidnapped the goats, she brushed the woman.
What do not you understand?
Well why did he stop us?
Isn't it ridiculous to be suspicious of you and me?
How do we know, dear?
Can we keep it if we know?
Isn't it, Ruhi?
Then.
Yes, but.
This is sugar for women, you say.
Men know such things, but they hide them.
Joins the crime.
Like a black box.
What is there, what is a secret registry. Snatching.
What door?
Why did the incident turn to us, friend?
The wounded man is comfortable. What is it for me?
Perhaps Murat opened up to one of his friends.
Whatever happens, maybe one was spilled.
Yasemin is screaming about it.
No Ruhi ...
... don't be the black box. Don't say I know everything.
Aydan ...
... What are you saying?
Unfortunately, you are the only suspect, honey.
It is obvious that Barlas is news of the world.
Look, tell me if you know something.
Don't tire me. I got nervous.
Do not tire.
Barlas ...
... don't.
Did Murat tell you something?
What did he say?
Look, if you know something, say it, we will get very angry.
I say Aydan.
Brother, can we have our car?
Immediately Mr.
You're officially paranoid, Yasemin.
Where did you get that everyone knows?
Not paranoia.
I'm sure.
How are you sure?
Because Bahar said.
Yes?
Besides that.
Don't trust your friends, Yasemin said.
Everyone is aware of the situation.
But nobody makes noise. He said.
It wasn't a lie, Murat. I'm sure.
Why are you going to Bahar, Yasemin?
Why?
I do not know.
You're thoroughly mixing things up Yasemin.
Yasemin ...
... I am your interlocutor.
I am married to you. We need to talk.
I'm glad you remember.
Yes, Murat, we are married.
You cheated on me too. I'm going too and ...
I wanted to talk. This.
This attitude is of no use to anyone, Yasemin.
And no one.
Yahu's house is our house.
Both of us. We're on it.
Every mallet, every pick you hit hurt us ...
Yasemin.
If we fix this, we will. Nobody else.
We can? I don't know him either.
But we have to do something.
At least we have to talk.
What did you do?
They shouldn't be fighting.
Are you looking, Sitare?
I don't know, honey.
What should Aydan look for?
As if Murat fell in love with the other woman ...
... he will take him to the wedding ...
Husband and wife are not allowed.
Leave these jobs.
Yes.
Excuse me guys.
We are very tired.
We couldn't find the perpetrator for a minute, where are you going?
Much work is waiting, Barlas. Add yours ...
... you know, for example, that the company has food products.
You have to deal. You know. Go.
Let's talk, sugar.
We will call you sugar. I will see.
I will see.
Goodbye.
This is every time.
Getting angry.
I will call. Who are you looking for?
Maybe they kiss and smell after a fight.
What it is for you?
What? Is a lie?
Barlas.
I will call.
Who are you looking for?
Are we going to keep quiet like this?
Are we not talking again?
No.
Not now.
We always delay.
We always ignore.
We will talk about that at the end.
How far will we escape Yasemin?
Oh please.
I am not in a position to have anyone at this time.
I'm tired. I have no power. Please.
Look Yasemin.
I really care what you say in psychiatry.
I always think.
I don't want you to be sad, Yasemin.
Never.
Let's do something. Please.
Your phone is ringing ...
... and we both know who the caller is.
I also don't think it's time to talk.
Nor is it time for therapy.
I agree.
How beautiful it was.
For the first time in a long time ...
... we both agree.
Your vehicle is ready, sir.
Thank you.
You have to get rid of these suckers first.
But do not worry.
I'll take care.
You ...
... I ...
... just the two of us ...
I know you love me.
Because I love you too.
Yasemin, just a second.
Mrs. Yasemin ...
Murat Bey came back early.
I hope nothing bad happened.
Nerd.
My head hurts a little. I guess the migraine ...
... Mrs. Filiz. I do not know.
I couldn't get to the noise or something there.
I'll take a pain reliever and go to bed.
I worked like crazy.
We put the boys together. We made a reservation.
We pay so much truck.
Let the woman come. Don't leave stones on stone.
Look at you, Sitare.
Grief, darling.
Are you saying for three cents?
I am not in money. You know.
It comes from our mouth and our nose, my dear wife.
If we had known who would Murat take?
There's no space.
So it was inefficient. In my opinion.
If you don't touch my mother ...
... I don't have to talk to your son.
Don't pretend Barlas.
What number?
I didn't say anything, it's not there.
But you already know who you are.
If you knew why you would ask?
I swear I don't know.
One minute.
You know someone like you say.
Look, tell me, let me love your eyes. This torture is over.
Sitos ...
... Don't eat me.
You officially wrote the conspiracy theory, Barlas.
I don't know who I should know.
How many times am I going to say?
Like you don't know Yasemin.
The husband and wife say nothing.
My secret sugar is reserved.
Where?
I'm going to sleep.
Don't let my face fall into my eyes tomorrow.
The stress mites are already ruined.
Botox melted and my fillers melted.
Lay down.
Onur.
You are early.
Do not ask.
Events. Events ...
Well, we'll talk later. Berkaylar is waiting.
Is it the tribe of this?
Don't start Barlas again, please.
You will not play if you are offended, champion!
I haven't started playing yet. You will know when you play!
Look ...
The artist keeps his tail straight.
Your son is the artist Sitoş.
Artist ... Artist ...
I remind you who you call an artist in our son, my sweet.
What do you think you're doing?
Didn't I call myself at night?
Don't call me at night. We've alredy talk about that.
Well.
Mrs. Yasemin, I'm going.
Mrs. Filiz, would you wait a minute?
I separated them and I will give it to you.
These are for those in the neighborhood. I have reserved them for you.
There are some from Ece that shrink before use.
They will also be in Gülsüm.
It will be highly appreciated. Mine will be happy. Thanks.
Meaning.
Mrs. Yasemin, Ece's baby Bahar.
Ah, he must have entered by mistake.
I'd take it home if we didn't find out.
No, Filiz doesn't exist. There is no mistake. I also put it on.
But Mrs. Yasemin, Ece, you shouldn't be upset, you love it.
Ece has many more toys.
Do not worry. Let this go to other children.
Let them play too.
Well. If you say it.
Come back again.
I will see.
Well.
Okay, Asim Bey, I'm not sending to school then.
Yes, yes, so I was worried that she had a fever.
Of course, I know, that's how it is ...
I know it doesn't matter.
I'm giving antipyretics.
It's okay, Asim Bey is okay.
If there is any improvement, I will let you know. Thanks.
The eggs are boiled. I also made the tea.
I did not produce fruit either. Nobody is eating.
I see everyone has a surprise today.
I thought you would be happy mom.
Run girl! Run baby Runs!
Don't run, don't run! Running is prohibited.
What kind of table is this?
I prepared. Come on, sit down.
Thanks girl.
Enjoy your meal. Come on. Come on mom.
We could not talk. How was your dinner?
It was a very modern place. Everyone says so.
Fabulous.
It was very revealing, Mom.
So I'm asking for details. For example, your boss was very good.
What was their food like?
Well it's great. Okay, let's not do anything. This ...
Let's enjoy the beautiful table. Go.
Cheers to my daughter's hands.
The man eats from the daughter's hand is another.
Enjoy your food, daddy. I want everyone to think like you.
I think like my father.
By the way, don't look at Derin, my head is very busy.
It was very nice, everything.
It was very nice.
Ece, I spoke to your doctor, my lamb ...
We will rest you today. You're not going to school ...
... sit down with your aunt Filiz. Very good honey?
I'll take care of my work and come to you right away.
I'm Murat, and you're dropping Derin at school.
I will not go to school.
So ...
I say if I haven't been in that crowd for a while.
It would be better for me to stay home for a few more days.
I work here.
Derin no. As you know, there is very little left for the exam.
I don't want you to miss a lesson.
Absenteeism will also be a problem.
Look how beautiful your father will leave you at school.
I am a super mother.
You already thought of everything for me.
You have no right to speak to me anyway.
If you did something, mom. Give us a chip for all of us.
You control us all from where you sit. You work, you go to school ...
You don't have to get so tired.
When I make that breakfast or something ...
I thought my daughter grew up all of a sudden, but ...
I mean ...
The sane movements also had an end.
You proved to be a true teenager. I swear ...
... Thank you.
My daughter ...
... we'll be late let's go.
All right, dad
... take my bag and come. Inevitable ...
... orders from great place.
Enjoy your meal.
I also go out.
I will let you go.
I'll be a little late if you want to go to the company today.
Let's sit down and chat?
Nerd.
Let's not interrupt the order of the children. Don't be surprised by your routines for now.
What routine?
What routine? Don't you care about our experience?
What?
Are you not aware of what we live for the love of God?
What order? Is there a request?
Derin is right. It really uses a chip on us ...
... to relax. Get rid.
Murat, I am aware, of course, of what is happening.
As a result, I am not the lover.
I'm ready. Lets go dad.
Here you have. I see you in the evening.
Won't you open it?
This is Aydan.
She will be gossiping now. I'll call you later.
Well, bye, bye.
It does not open, it does not open.
He never did that.
What happened, Ruhi? The fight shouldn't have grown.
Do not worry. There is nothing.
Why don't you open it?
Today ...
... I'm going to stop by Murat. I learn from him.
I don't have that much time, Ruhi.
Besides, if our work is left to Murat ...
He will tell you something. You will accept.
What a question, nothing. It is not my concern, my life.
In your calm, in your comfort.
Why don't you take care of your own business?
What does that mean?
Leave people alone.
Yasemin is my friend. I am in support.
Their problem is not supporting Aydan.
What was I going to say?
Confusion.
Chaos.
Sadness. Tears.
You officially love them.
Also...
... this is how you go about collecting gossip. I know.
Officially sad ...
... you're a nourished person, Aydan. What else can I tell you?
I wanted to.
I didn't even know they were upset.
But apparently there is something you know.
Maybe if you tell me, I can act like you, Ruhi.
I don't know anything, Aydan.
I'll be ready and out. I have a job.
The coffee is good too.
Sitare, good morning darling.
I called Yasemin but she is not answering now.
Really?
I didn't speak either.
Yasemin's phone ...
... if it didn't open, my sweet. We have to confiscate.
Do we jump in and go? What are you saying?
You may really need our support right now.
Okay sugar, okay. I am preparing immediately.
I'll call when I leave.
What's that? You got to the bottom of the conspiracy and diabetes again.
I think the agenda is hot.
What happened, Sitare.
Yasemin wasn't on her phone.
The woman does not open the phone, does not open it.
You are crazy?
Are you done with that now?
Everyone like you, darling?
It's not in Yasemin's story.
Zero mistake woman. Next.
Next. Yesterday it failed but next.
It does not work.
Speaking of malfunction, Onur Bey doesn't exist?
Aren't they up yet?
He is up.
He made his breakfast.
He went to work early, honey.
Look to you.
Your mind is with me ...
... as high as leg ...
... I'll tell you something Sitare. Please don't be.
You made this boy, but you couldn't.
Ah Barlas, ah Barlas.
Maybe it's trying to get into your eyes.
Have you ever thought honey?
No. Because there is no such thing.
Where are you?
Sitare work.
As I do every day.
Did it seem strange to you?
I do this every day.
I am a businessman. I have a white collar.
I'm going to work, I'm coming home. I'm going to work, I'm coming home.
Moron.
They are all unstable.
You are competing with him because he is a kid like a leg.
Who is a teenager and who is an adult is not known.
I swelled up.
Finally.
I'm a little mad at you but ...
... how many days have you neglected me, love?
Listen carefully. The situation is urgent.
Now go straight to Onur.
Sadri Bey is you ...
... you say he named me as his new assistant, Onur bey.
Did you get it so far?
I understand.
What is Onur? What did he drink?
Who came? Who did not come? What did he do? What did he not do?
You report everything to me.
How to spy?
It's like spying.
Don't wake the bird, it's okay.
Well.
Let's look at peanuts. Let me see. Let me see.
Will the sparse brain do this?
Are you going to buy coffee? Bring it to me.
I have another job. Take it honey.
Surprise.
Not a pleasant surprise at all.
What are you doing here?
Can you come without such notice?
They all have limits.
Everything has a routine, Bahar.
You have reached that roof door. This is the workplace.
Sit well.
Look Bahar.
You are challenging me.
Come on, that's enough.
Turn on the phone when it doesn't.
I'm not hungry. Then you break. If I don't, I can't.
I do not speak.
Why do you make me in such difficult situations?
Am I pushing you?
Yes, you are defiant. You are looking for me when it is not possible.
I don't pick up the phone it's breaking.
Bahar, if I don't, I can't.
Then I can't speak.
Why do you make me in such difficult situations?
Why is that?
I'm going then darling.
It does not work well.
Your wife was resting at my door.
I came to report it.
Being caught unprepared.
Oh, that's another matter.
What are you trying to do?
You said ridiculous things to Yasemin.
Did I say stupid things?
Yes.
What is happening?
You must have gone crazy.
His wife comes to my door.
Damn it. You are not, not this.
I told him ...
... it would be better if you spoke to Murat.
What else did I say?
Does he also say he's walking on me?
Yasemin is cold blooded.
Does not do that. Why are you laughing?
I know Yasemin. Does not do that.
Yasemin.
Yes.
Cold blood.
By God, it wasn't like that, dear.
Approached.
He walked a lot on me.
It is what it is ...
... I'm already talking about these things and I'm choking you ...
I didn't come here.
I came to inform you.
Because I think about you.
So you don't get in trouble.
Seeing Yasemin like this ...
... I was naturally afraid.
It attacks you, it does something.
I wish I hadn't come.
Because the power of your husbands is enough for me.
I'll say something ...
... that you're going to be able to draw me like this ...
... if you join in and talk like that?
Maybe you can solve your problems.
Come on thanks.
Well well. I am sorry.
Sorry to yell, Bahar.
Sit down, Bahar.
Okay, I shouldn't be yelling. Excuse me.
I am nervous.
You are right.
Nor should it have come like this.
Yes.
But what should I do, Murat?
So I was worried about you.
You didn't open my phone.
Yasemin is going crazy.
I have my mind. I was wondering about you. It's a crime?
So I have no choice.
Anyway early ...
... I left because there is no one in the company.
I enter as a shadow.
So I thought I'd leave when I got there.
Well well.
Don't drop your face right away.
If anyone sees ...
I thought you'd say I came to speak ...
No one knows anyway.
However, you didn't tell Yasemin like that.
Your friends know.
You said things like they were cheating on you.
Because it is.
I guess I don't have a lie.
Who knows?
He said. Who knows, Bahar?
Sitare.
Yes.
How do you know?
How do I know you know, Murat.
How do you know what it knows?
It occurred to me because ...
He said publicly, you are the lover.
It came to you.
He told me that I seduce you.
If I don't match my foot ...
... I knew you would. He threatened such threats.
But it's funny. Of course, I didn't take it seriously.
He has no way of doing anything to me.
So sure.
It is not like this?
Maybe as you say, you are right.
Tried to dump it empty and keep it full.
I also dug, I ate. How pure.
Not important.
Somehow soon everyone will learn Bahar.
How is that?
Get it going.
I'll talk to Yasemin.
Our marriage is not working. I will say that we part.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going to say something.
You're not doing this for me, are you?
No.
Our marriage is over, Bahar.
We were just playing. For false ...
... we are with everyone.
I did not see it.
But now I see it.
Look, we can't even talk.
Will we have dinner at night?
You thought, Murat.
I swear I have no secret purpose.
As such primitive people ...
... we will just feed it.
I make meatballs for you.
We put two wafers on top.
It's actually a good idea.
Great on wafers.
But no, Bahar.
Without speaking freely with Yasemin.
I know it's okay.
You are right. I'm not saying anything.
But at least let's have a coffee.
So we can do that too.
Well.
Okay, deal done.
How do you say.
But I think Yasemin won't talk to you today.
Sadly, I think so too. But ...
... that day will finally come and we'll talk.
For some reason, it seems like that day will never come to me. You know?
I'll talk to Yasemin.
Good luck.
Well then I'm running away.
But I also trust the universe. It's true?
Maybe a miracle will bring you to me.
That's what I say for coffee.
Maybe your talk will end early.
Perhaps.
Good luck.
Look what I'm going to say.
What are you doing here?
As I said Murat bey ...
I received a job offer that I cannot refuse.
So please don't look at my fault.
Are you sure.
Good, Bahar. You already decided. Goodbye.
You have a good day.
Goodbye.
Ağa ...
... Sadri asked for reports.
Wait a second, I'll be back.
What reports?
Exporting is one thing. I'll be here for a minute.
Why did you come this morning?
He came to say that he was going to quit and found a better job.
You listened.
How gorgeous.
Why does it come to you? If so, let it go.
Oh I called.
I said continue until I find someone, but he said no.
It does not matter and ağa is unemployed.
You will find better. I did not watch this woman.
Don't say that, Barlas. Good girl.
Ece loves him very much.
When things are like this, I don't want any other problems. Well.
That's the thing.
What did you do tonight Did your wife hit you?
Barlas worse than hitting.
What are you looking at?
Won't you tell me which wife you took?
What are you looking me?
Nonsense, Barlas.
Reports.
Have.
Where?
I'm upset, I'm not talking to you.
Where are you going?
Leave it alone.
Barlas.
I swear it was super. Very cool.
But you must take it by my arm and bring it ...
... not so much ...
... it didn't fit the big boss like you.
Pray, I'm not mad.
Don't confuse the words.
Look, I'm asking you for the last time. Why did you come?
I came to talk to my father.
What?
Joke.
Murat called, so I came.
He was going to tell me something.
That I have to do?
Look, you're trying to waste time, but it will be bad.
Bahar explodes in you.
Will my father yell at you?
Do you think it will be like this?
Actually, I saw my father in Murat's room.
But I didn't say anything. Do not worry.
I have no confusion.
You are lying.
My father does not come to work at this time of life.
Is here. How can I know.
Even let me get away.
More than you can see.
Now he sees something with you.
You suspect it well, right?
As you can see my brother ...
I still think about you.
By the way, your room was really cool.
The office chair is legendary.
It fits you well.
It would be a shame to take it off, right?
We both don't want that.
Sorry, well ...
I guess I misspelled your name on the quote.
What is the name? I do not leave the record incomplete.
I didn't tell you my name, honey.
But ...
Onur Bey's dates ...
I wasn't on a date with Onur Bey.
As you can see, exactly ...
... from here. We come together before your eyes.
We went into the room together. But congratulations.
It was not good, if not intelligent.
Who is this?
Who is this girl?
Is it order now, sugar?
She is not a girl for us. Yasemin worries.
You're right, honey, but ...
... if we find the girl, maybe we'll squeeze her out.
We will let him go after you.
I don't know Aydan. No matter.
I did stupid things. I'm already embarrassed.
Okay, Yasemin, okay. He went away.
Gone, okay.
Let's look forward now, okay?
You are very hurtful when you want it alone. Let me tell you that too.
You're telling the truth, but I really got lost.
You won't lose, darling. You will not do it.
You have lost yourself, you lose the war. Next.
It is clear that.
You couldn't handle the crisis, honey.
You fell with crazy movements.
You showed how weak your nerves are.
No. He
'll be calm ...
... that he will follow his cunning plan ...
... you yelled at the man.
Also with us.
I was very surprised, Yasemin. I've never seen you like this.
Yes. I was in disgrace.
Don't be ridiculous, Yasemin. Lift your head.
Yasemin, look at me.
Do you want this man? You do not want.
I do not know. I swear I don't know.
He says I don't know yet. He keeps thinking.
It broke.
Your marriage, Yasemin.
Of course you want.
So you have children, Yasemin.
Yeah but I ... I
really don't know what to do.
Look Yasemin.
Open your ear, listen to me.
Men do such things.
They get someone as young or something.
But they eventually return to their wives.
Point.
When we say young ...
... that friend from Derin ...
... would come in and out of your house.
Don't let it be.
Oh, Yasemin.
Your work is very hard.
His daughter is one year old.
No, it's not. Not that.
It's not that, don't be silly. It is not another.
So Who?
I don't know who exactly. Murat ...
... phone on ...
... when you get the message ...
... Murat had to admit it.
Oh who is it darling.
Nobody, it doesn't matter. One of the girls is here.
God.
Look Yasemin.
Now with the right tactic ...
You shake them all up.
What are you doing?
Peace with your husband in no time.
Go to your water. Behave before work, honey.
Well.
I'll say something, really ...
They know that Murat is cheating on me ...
Is Yasemin the same again?
The same again? You took it, honey.
Who told you this?
No one.
Nobody, I think he was crazy.
When we listen, we are in shock. Look, I swear.
How do we know, sugar?
But you were so sure ...
... I even suspect myself, so sometime.
Is your meeting over?
Well done.
It is quite complicated here.
My father officially opened the war, I'm dealing with it.
Why is that?
You don't want me to be in the company.
Trying to slide my foot.
Of course, I get even more ambitious when he attacks. No news.
How is that?
Well ...
... the company will remain for you. You are not a stranger.
Be it the long story, I'll tell you later.
Where are you?
I am by the sea.
Why aren't you in school?
Mine is a long story.
Did something happen Derin?
Your hands again?
No worries, I'm fine.
I'll tell you later.
Okay, so the message has been received.
See you after work at night?
Could be.
Okay, I'll call you.
I will see.
Thanks Yasin.
I think there is a Bahar sister party.
I hope, Yasin.
My daughter, are you kidding me?
...Are you kidding me?
What are you doing?
I'm not kidding. What joke?
What were you doing with Murat in the morning?
You don't really understand the words.
Don't move around me. Didn't I tell you?
I am doing it too.
Didn't you hear it with your ear? I came to say that I quit my job.
I won't see you with Murat again.
My beautiful girl I will not see her.
That I have to do?
That I have to do? Should I disappear to the point where I stopped?
I did it cleanly.
Well. I'm not very curious about your work either.
I do not come. Done.
Done.
God willing.
Don't bring me here again.
You understand.
Don't ever bring me here again.
You will pay.
Are you available?
Yasemin ...
... of course I'm available. Come.
I said pass while you pass
You did well, Yasemin. You take?
I don't drink anything Murat.
I thought ...
Here you go.
Because of my behavior last night ...
... then ...
I am aware that it has exceeded its purpose. Look, I couldn't quite reach it ...
... the difference.
Because I am very angry.
I acted like this.
This is ...
... this is not an excuse. I am aware of that as well.
But ...
I also lost my balance.
Anyway, I accused you but ...
I'm sorry.
You are going to break.
I am sorry. Two words.
You will say that I am sorry. Yasemin will be finished.
Why are you squirming?
No.
So ...
I'm sorry, of course.
Of course I am sorry. Then I was wrong.
But ...
... what is this?
A telephone rings.
From here.
Mio is here.
There is a phone here.
Mine is here but.
It is from Barlas or Onur.
Or Ruhi.
Give.
Murat, did I become Alzheimer's?
I forgot my phone.
Would you bring it to me at night?
So, of course, it doesn't bother.
You're going to have coffee, you know.
I'm waiting for you. Hello?
Murat didn't hear you, hi.
Yasemin.
I just sat here ...
I'm trying to apologize to you, Murat.
Lo, maybe something ...
... I'm trying to talk about how we can fix it.
That girl was here.
So all you say is brag.
Bragging. What I said.
You don't want to save our marriage, Murat.
It's very obvious.
Where are you taking it from, Yasemin?
Can we ever talk?
I can not believe you. You are so selfish.
So even say a situation ...
Excuse me ...
... you think I'm not you.
No, curiously ...
... you expect me to believe it too and ...
... you make me believe it.
I am sitting here with regret.
I hate you so much now.
Yasemin, you misunderstand everything.
I can't stop here.
Yasemin, he won't go.
I ask you not to go to Bahar.
One minute.
What happened?
Complain about me, what happened to your lover?
Look at you, Yasemin.
You cannot think correctly. Yasemin.
Could you put down that phone?
Please don't disturb people.
Please, we have no right to do this.
No problem.
Are you going to drop that?
Have.
You have a new one for your lover.
We are talking to you very often these days, my dear Yasemin.
The conversation with you is great.
But I think I'm very busy right now.
Are you continuing your relationship with Murat?
You should ask no to me, Yasemin.
I can not say anything.
You said your friends had the news.
Who knows?
Everyone.
All your friends.
You are lying.
Nobody knows.
Ask them these questions, not me, Yasemin.
But you can't ask, can you?
This is your whole problem.
You cannot speak anything openly.
No husband, no friends, no one.
Is there any news from Derin?
I do not believe it.
The door stayed open, Bahar.
Your phone is also off. Are you running out of charge?
Mom, what are you doing here?
I think ...
Honey, he came to call me to work.
He made an offer that I can't refuse. I also confirmed it.
Isn't that right, Yasemin?
Yes, of course.
This is great news! That's all!
And they call you cruel, mom.
You are a wonderful person. I'm so happy.
Yes. Anyway, I'll go.
There is a lot of work. I will see.
Of course.
Goodbye.
See you tomorrow.
I'm not too late.
We will talk in the afternoon.
I'm so happy.
I have something to tell you.
Honey, close the door.
What are you saying? They tightened up nicely after you left.
I hope you didn't say that.
Can you say, will I tell you Murat?
But I mean, cold sweat didn't flow down my back.
Sitare is also a friend. It keeps coming to me.
On the one hand Aydan. No ...
... all apart ...
... my explosion for Yasemin.
If Yasemin finds out ...
... I can't look at his face embarrassed.
I think he heard you. Looking for him.
Let me come out and talk.
No need to open the phone.
I can't handle another fight now.
The girl is going to be very angry.
After what happened this morning ...
... she can't be angry anymore. Do not worry.
Damn!
God damn you!
Damn! God ...
damn it! God damn you all ...
... Damn.
I would appreciate if you call when appropriate. Important.
A lot of.
Calm down.
Relax, relax.
The coffees have arrived.
I'm listening.
I made my decision. I leave the school.
So I will never go there again.
You were right. Now I have to show that I am growing.
Life is mine and I make the decisions.
You're super.
So did you think what to do?
I do not know.
So I don't know yet.
But there is something I know. I definitely don't want to be a pianist.
Then maybe I'll be a waitress for a while.
If I were you ...
... I would make this decision immediately tonight.
I'm home tomorrow.
I will support you. I will stand behind you.
Don't delay, don't give up.
So ...
... the later I say it will be more difficult ...
... isn't it?
Exactly.
I think tonight is delicious for this news.
This is the situation.
Brother Murat.
Welcome brother Ruhi.
Hello everybody.
Which client did my father go to?
He told you for sure.
Sorry guys, I stepped in but ...
Excuse me. Murat to see you.
Say hi to your dad.
I'll say it if I find it.
I don't know, Onur.
He came to my office ...
... said he would go to the client, but which one ...
... I don't remember. He said, but I don't remember.
If there's anything, tell me I'll help you.
No brother asked. So.
Hello everybody.
Welcome Aunt Yasemin.
I hope I didn't break it.
No no no, come on.
I have some jobs.
Excuse me.
You are welcome, brother.
Here you have.
No, I will not sit.
Why don't you pick up your phone?
I do not want to fight with you. That's why.
We are not going. Why did you come? Which is the topic. Tell me.
The theme is the same.
The subject is Bahar. This Bahar ...
... we have problems for you, Murat. Well.
To go home again ...
... he threatened me along with Derin.
She will come home tomorrow.
Can you understand what I am saying?
I don't know, maybe you would be much happier.
So you can gather much more comfortably.
Wait a minute, a minute, I didn't understand anything.
How did he threaten you?
Where did you see Bahar?
I went to Bahar.
You went.
Yes, I went to Bahar.
Yasemin.
That's not the point, Murat.
You will understand if you listen to me.
While I was there, Derin came to Bahar's house. Well?
Of course he didn't know what to say.
And Bahar, just to leave me in trouble ...
Your mother came to call me to get back to work, she said.
Good to Derin.
Can you take a look at the trap he dropped me, Murat?
If I said no, I would say everything. To Derin.
I was going to tell Derin.
Not know what to do.
Had to say yes. So as a result.
Look, that girl is a demon Murat.
Yasemin.
You went there on your own foot.
Didn't we talk to you?
Didn't I tell you not to go, Yasemin? Why are you going?
Why do you face a girl in two?
The ones between you and me have nothing to do with it.
No.
I can't believe.
I can not believe that?
I can't believe Murat, he's great.
So beautiful. This little devil ...
... can do whatever he wants. But after all ...
... Yasemin will be charged again.
It is this? Is that so?
Amazing. You are so noble, Murat ...
... you are protecting your love right now and your wife ...
... you throw him off the cliff. Bravo.
What does it have to do with it?
What you have to do?
Why did you go there? I am asking you a clear question.
Why ...
... did you go?
Because ...
... in my husband's office ...
... he's reckless enough to put down his phone ...
I wanted to go and ask him.
What Yasemin? Complete your sentence.
What did you want to ask?
I can not do it.
What Derin? Are you okay?
I'm good. You?
What happened?
Nothing.
I said, let me take a look when my work clears up.
How are the situations at home?
I mean, we have a little fight with my mother but ...
... that's normal to look at.
What happened?
Nothing nothing. I was just asking.
Onur, while calling ...
... or ...
... I know we have contracted, but with my parents at night ...
I have to eat.
If we do it later, will it?
Of course.
It gets even better. Because me too ...
I have a dinner plan with ours.
Long story. So you say we'll talk later.
Yes.
As soon as possible.
Well. I will see.
Welcome.
Thanks.
I am sorry.
You've been in trouble, right?
But what should I do? I never realized that I dropped the phone.
I left you in a difficult situation.
Something.
I do not worry.
The phone.
But this.
Yours is not in use.
Yasemin?
I already guessed it. He was very angry when he came to me.
Fortunately, she broke the phone, not me.
Yasemin, Bahar is out of control.
It is unclear where the tramp will explode like a mine.
Anyway.
Come on.
Don't let me come. What happens.
One coffee, five minutes.
I promise I'll fire you for the sixth minute, really.
A coffee.
You sit. I fill the cafes and come.
Thanks.
Enjoy your meal.
Know your worth. Latest.
If it's the last one, stay with you.
You need more today.
You are right.
Are you not going to ask anything?
No.
We are both very tired.
They both know it.
I promised that I would wait.
Then there is no doubt.
No wonder if I run out of it.
You will come to us tomorrow.
Oh yeah.
Derin ...
... As soon as Yasemin screamed, I was surprised what to say.
It just came out of my mouth.
No, he looked like an idol in Yasemin. The pause.
Thanks.
It was a ridiculous situation.
But I'll handle it.
So a day or two without hitting the girls like that.
With an excuse, lick it again, don't worry.
Nice ...
... Yasemin didn't kill me tomorrow.
Yasemin ...
... says she did it to put him in a difficult situation.
You got it trapped.
What?
That is good.
I'm the one in trouble.
When it comes to Derin ...
... Derin ...
... what would I do when my mom said what are you doing here?
I said the first thing that came to mind.
No, the weather is nice for me. I say the truth.
She is the one hiding.
Because of this, he was in a difficult situation.
I fell into a false state.
Just because I'm going to save him.
Well well.
You are right. Well.
But come tell this to Yasemin.
Really ...
... I don't want to say anything bad anyway.
Or I want to say it.
I swear.
I mean ungrateful. Ungrateful.
Yes doughter?
Hello Dad. Where are you?
I'm out, dear, did something happen?
I waited for you to set the table, I said, let me know.
Okay, okay.
You begin.
I will catch up. I will arrive a little late.
See you later, my daughter.
I couldn't have my coffee either. I have to go.
Do not go.
Stay here.
I can not jump. I can not do it.
Actually, the truth is Bahar ...
... I'd rather stay with you here.
But I can't do this to you.
I can not do it.
Murat.
I know.
If we only hug once.
One time.
See you later.
Excuse me.
To the most beautiful woman in the world.
Thanks Barlas.
No one can afford it like you, darling.
Sitoş can't understand it.
Hi dear.
We found it good, mom.
A drink before eating.
Let's prepare your father. The closure is very beautiful.
No, I'm not taking it, Mom.
Today the company ...
... it was pretty intense. If I drink it now, I love it without eating.
And Onur Bey ...
business world ...
... is not like studying in private schools.
My sugar gets used to that. If you help too ...
... learn the job. It is not?
I know ...
Onur Efendi.
From his father ...
... he won't help you.
...in my opinion.
No dad.
Actually, I needed your help on an issue today ...
... I couldn't find you.
If you went to Murat, my partner.
If you go to brother Murat.
I went, I went.
Aunt Yasemin also came.
He was in no condition to speak.
I asked him where he was. Said it went to the customer.
Which one did I say?
The head of a man of the world. He couldn't answer me.
What client did you go to, dad?
You will know if I say it.
I also worked on this issue.
I examined all the clients one by one all day.
Well, we need to know who we work with, right?
Look how beautiful. You learn it like this. It is bad?
You still haven't told me who you're going to.
Are you boiling?
What will I boil? I went to Kemal.
To Kemal Bey, Kemal Gürses.
You know?
Kemal.
I didn't read such a name, dad.
So you have to work harder. You saw it?
If you look at the letter K.
Kamuran, Kamil, Kemal.
You will call, you will find.
Are both ...
... where did you get this love for the customer?
I think we are curious.
No. I just want to deal with clients. All this.
Let me take the load off your shoulder. It is not?
At the beginning of this, my son. First you get the inside of the company.
Dominate there.
Then chase customers outside.
Then. There is more time for him.
Okay, let's go.
Let's get ready to eat. Here you have.
Go.
Dad, look what I'm going to say.
I think this is the right decision for the client's business.
Let's ask my grandfather.
We understand.
Great place torpedin, great boss.
But do not forget. I'm not a kettle, son.
Just enough sugar.
The job remained with the company.
Working at dinner, with the client ...
... on the file ...
I don't want to hear a word. Well?
It's fine?
Okay, okay.
What's for dinner?
Mom ...
... my baby Bahar ...
Do you know where?
Today I searched with Aunt Filiz but I couldn't find him.
I have not seen one. Get it out of a place.
But I was going to play with it.
You have a lot of babies, my dear. You play with them.
How are we going to deal with food now?
I do not want.
I want baby Bahar.
I love her very much.
Let's call.
Not before you finish your meal.
How is school going?
Well. My mom.
School is like always.
Dad, why didn't you come yet?
The income was now at work. What happened?
Do you have a job with your father?
Dad, my dad came.
I came, my dear.
Welcome.
Hello.
Welcome dad.
My only.
Welcome father.
Thanks. You are not in your fire, I hope.
Oh. My beautiful daughter.
Enjoy your meal. Hi Yasemin.
Hello.
I can't find my baby Bahar.
Do we look for it together?
Well, daughter.
But first, let's eat our food. It's okay?
Do you drink soup?
I go. Let me wash my hands.
Sitare doesn't open his knife.
There is nothing new? Conspiracy theory.
Gossip.
Nothing different, honey. What they know.
Didn't Yasemin say anything?
What the hell do you want, Barlas?
I call it reserved, sugar, discreet.
I also squeezed Murat. He said nothing.
He is blessed as a spy.
What's going on?
Son, you don't know about the world.
It is a great scandal.
Brother Murat is playing with Aunt Yasemin.
Wait a minute.
We are eating and Aunt Yasemin was screaming.
There is misfortune, great misfortune.
You're exaggerating, Barlas.
What am I exaggerating?
What am I exaggerating? Didn't that happen?
No, tell me if you know something. If a man's head burns ...
... the tip touches us.
That's why I say, if not ...
... what will I care? He does what he wants.
You probably don't think I'll buy those numbers, honey.
Son, I'll train you to deal with me.
Brother Murat dealing with his burned head.
Go deal with it.
Let's not have a goal there.
It's beautiful, Yasemin. Health to your hands.
Enjoy your meal.
I did it however you want, without frying.
Thanks.
How was your day?
Not bad.
My day was also very good.
Because my sister Bahar is coming tomorrow.
Mom ...
... wanted bread. You can bring?
Bread for you, sweet for you.
Forgiveness.
I spoke to Bahar, Yasemin.
It will keep coming and going for a few days.
So that Derin doesn't suspect something. Then you will find an excuse.
He will get off work.
Does it seem reasonable to you?
It doesn't really seem reasonable to me.
I tell everything and ...
... It seems reasonable to me to put an end to these antics.
Don't worry Derin. Let's go inside.
Are you going to open the door?
Sorry Sorry. A cup fell. There is nothing.
Come.
Well. Not important.
Take it, honey.
I have to tell you something.
Tell me dear.
I left school.
What?
What does that mean? What happened Girl? Why are you leaving school?
Did something happen, dear?
Derin'cig.
I am sorry.
This will never happen.
I never allow it.
My mom ...
... I don't want your permission anyway, I say my ...
... decision.
Well my daughter. But why? Can you tell me why?
Daddy, I don't want to go to school anymore.
Okay, why girl? You say something serious.
Why?
There is no yelling at the table.
You are quite right, my dear.
Derin'cig ...
... sorry. What you say will not happen.
It's not possible.
The topic has been closed.
The subject was not closed.
Derin.
Yasemin.
Can we talk about this later?
What are we going to talk about? There is nothing to talk about.
What do you mean by nothing to talk about?
This means that you will not say, Derin'ci.
Everything.
Dessert.
Dessert?
Mom, aren't you listening to me?
Or do you not want to understand?
I'm trying to explain a decision to you here.
I say I won't go to school either. You understand?
Done. I don't go to school or something like that.
I am not a child now I understand this.
I am tired of your behavior.
My daughter.
Please, dad.
Did my sister get into mischief, Mom?
Something like that happened, honey.
In other words, without speaking, listening ...
... why did you do it again?
Again.
What am I going to listen to this nonsense?
Can you tell me?
So I can't believe it.
Five months to finish school.
Are we going to let him throw his years away?
We will not overlook Yasemin. Of course, let's not overlook.
But why do you want this? Let's try to understand it.
We knew that if you don't make it to the door.
In the middle of the night
I'm curious about that too. Wherever he went ...
Well, I guess, of course.
Where did she go ...
All these exploits ...
... because she was a prophet after meeting Bahar.
So did the word get out?
Did he turn around and go back to Bahar?
He turned around and got there. Because ...
... Derin went to Bahar today.
He went to Bahar.
Then he came home and said he dropped out of school.
What that demon did to get back home ...
I'm not even saying.
Yasemin.
Can you be sick?
I'm going crazy.
I wonder, once.
Just once.
Do you think I have a chance to be right?
One time.
Just once.
You are always right, Yasemin.
All the time.
You are always right.
Don't yell at mom.
I don't scream, daughter.
I'm not yelling at myself.
Your father was joking ...
... my lamb. We were playing games.
Your father was joking. I'm one. Come.
My daughter is not screaming. Do not worry dear.
Bahar, if Derin calls, can you inform me?
It means that the apocalypse is broken.
Handsome.
This will distract you a bit, Ms. Yasemin.
Of course.
Is there a problem?
Hello.
What is it?
Derin left the house and left.
We had a little fight.
Why is that?
I'll tell you Bahar. Then I'll tell it. Long story.
Alone, can you tell me if it comes to you?
Of course.
I must notify it.
If you want, I'll call you and find out where it is.
No no no no.
Now you understand what we are looking for. Everything becomes more complicated.
If you come, give him the news. Thanks.
Well.
Not important.
So ...
... if it's about me, if you call ...
... I'll definitely let you know.
Well.
Well. Thanks. Thanks.
Murat.
If you get news, please let me know, okay?
Well well. I will see.
I will see.
Where did you stay I froze.
Take it. Why did you come out like this? What happened?
I left school.
I told my mom at night.
My mother started talking foolishly at that moment.
No, I do not allow it.
I am trying to explain something there.
He tells my father if he wants dessert.
The woman has no respect for a gram.
Or one gram has led me to a fortress.
Well, bravo, well done, I say you did well ...
... of course I don't wait.
But he doesn't even listen to me. He does not listen.
She acts like I'm not there.
Okay, then let's do it like this ...
Let me notify your mother. Do not worry.
No. You are not looking for my mother Onur.
I no longer have anybody in mind.
Especially that woman.
I don't want a permit or something.
Do not be silly.
I didn't say we got permission anyway.
Let us notify. I said don't worry.
Would you be calm?
Please ok.
Derin is with me, don't worry.
I will leave her safely at her home.
Okay now ...
... let's go to a better place.
Let's discuss this great decision.
Well.
Derin reported.
I was with a friend.
So it's good. He gave notice.
Ece how?
Asleep
I am there then.
I'll take Ece then.
No, it is not necessary.
Yasemin.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
Well.
Yes.
I am listening to you.
There is not much to tell.
It was not exactly like that.
I left school.
I mentioned it to my mother at dinner.
But they both fell on me.
Nice, I can't eat my father's right. I wonder why.
But my mother ...
... said the topic is closed and clicked all the words in my mouth.
Why am I surprised?
Here's my regular mom.
No, to make my own decisions ...
... he never allows it.
Why is that?
What? Why?
So why do you want to quit school?
Because I don't feel like I belong there.
I don't want to be a pianist or something like that.
Well.
I understand you.
But look, that's half a period left.
Then school is over.
Wouldn't it be a bit silly if you quit now?
The year you read so much will be wasted.
These are just the words of Yasemin Düdenli.
Well, Onur.
What I feel?
Do you think they don't matter?
Of course there is.
But your school ..
OK, let me ask you then.
What do you want to do after school is over?
So what do you really want to do?
I do not know.
We thought she might be a waitress for a while.
We think.
Who did you think with?
I was going to say I thought.
You thought with Bahar, right?
Onur, I just checked.
God.
Let Bahar draw his own life first.
Then he comes to advise you.
Waitress.
What do you understand as a waitress?
Thanks.
Thanks. Because you trusted me so much.
You're all the same, right?
I did not mean that.
But you said it.
Where are you going, Derin? Stop.
Onur ...
... if I wanted to make this speech ...
... I would talk to my mother at home.
Don't come after me.
Derin.
Dear.
What's up mom
Well.
I think you were late at night, I didn't hear you.
Enough, enough.
He is holding a coffee in two. Sugar flutter.
I was a little late. Yes.
Nothing bad, Onur?
Like what?
What do i need to know?
Suddenly the phone came. I'm asking you out.
Nerd. I met a friend, mom.
How is that friend?
Mommy.
I'm asking if I can prepare, dear. What is wrong with that?
What type of preparation are we talking about?
Depression with Derin.
Why is that?
Because I'll be old that second.
A complete disgrace.
Next.
Mom, you look great. Don't worry about them at all.
It's not what you look like.
Who are you?
The moment I was in the mother-in-law ...
... will be the moment I finish.
Because when it's valid ...
... something old automatically.
I will be ten years old at a time.
Do not laugh.
And can you believe it?
No doctor can cure this, my sugar. Next.
Laughter.
Look at me, you laugh, but that's what's going to happen.
Because of this ...
... just because of my nerves ...
... note that something lousy will be validated.
Look what I'm going to say.
In my opinion...
... you are in the world ...
... the most beautiful.
But of course you have more, you have a little more time.
Have more?
That's.
That's all. Onur, I love you so much baby.
I love you very much. That's. I think there is more.
There is more time. I agree.
There is no need, dear.
Of course. There is more. Then there is more.
Whenever you want?
I agree.
We are like friends with you.
Yes.
Isn't it?
What you say.
Mrs. Filiz will come to Ece every fifteen minutes.
Pay attention to that.
...runny nose. Sometimes we miss him.
What happens. It's okay?
So if something urgent happens, please call.
Well.
OKAY. Wait if you want.
If it is fifteen minutes.
Here if I don't hurry.
You know.
Let me use this.
Let me help.
Well well. It was.
In his room, Derin.
Receive your news.
OK Do not worry. I'll let myself know if something happens.
It happened, Mrs. Filiz. Thank you.
Don't leave your eyes behind.
Well.
Brother Murat.
I know.
You came for the pay table.
I will send it to you shortly. Do not worry.
There isn't, brother. Actually, I didn't come for him.
Why did you come, Onur?
Well ...
do you know about Derin? I can not reach.
Derin ...
... is the school. It is in class.
I know I quit school, bro.
You fought yesterday.
My name is. We were together yesterday.
I even texted Aunt Yasemin so she wouldn't worry.
Yasemin ...
He never informed me. He said nothing.
Oh Yasemin.
Said with a friend, but ...
... I didn't say it was you. I couldn't guess either.
I understand.
Yesterday everyone was probably nervous.
Onur.
Derin locked himself in his room.
He does not speak to any of us. Just for your information.
Well. Thanks brother.
Onur'cug.
This situation.
Brother ...
... I just wanted to know that Derin went home safely.
I was curious about it.
Thanks.
Yasemin, Yasemin.
It is always a mystery. Always a ...
Everything around ...
It's broken for you to understand.
It's not very good if you leave home.
But I think yours reacted a lot too.
Then.
No, what bothers me, you know?
Take a decision. But nobody respects.
Nobody said it would be easy, honey.
So you have to show them that you are growing.
I'm trying.
Since the morning ...
... no job vacancies remain.
But there isn't even a waitress ad.
Other than that, what work will I do? I do not know that.
No. How serious if I have a job ...?
... they will understand that I am ...
It is very difficult to find a waitress without warning.
So you have to go to the cafes one by one and talk.
Actually, there are some places that I know.
So if you call and give my name, they will help you.
I'm going to say something. Come on, get dressed.
I'll call a Gökhan too.
Thanks.
I'll go out then.
Because I have to go back before my mother comes back.
Why are you forbidden to leave the house?
No.
I don't want to meet at the door.
Do not be silly.
You are a young adult.
Then your mom will have to accept it later.
You are right. Here are old habits.
Go.
How good that you are here.
What's going on honey
From Sitare, I'm miserable.
As he stood still last night, Derin ...
"I'm quitting school," he snapped.
We try to talk but what is possible.
Then he knocked on the door, got out, and left.
You will understand that we have deeply entered each other.
God ...
... called Onur.
Thanks. He also called and reported.
However, he was a bit relieved. Terrible. I am miserable.
Finally, the owner of the mysterious phone became apparent.
Mister?
Onur is for you to know. He loves Derin like his brother.
Is his brother?
Oh. Don't worry, sugar.
The issue of descent never ends.
He says I left this day. It starts again tomorrow.
You will be left with so much pain.
Just drop it ...
How are you with Murat?
That's bad.
So while you're trying to pack ...
... I rub my face.
Yasemin, I know.
Girls.
Aydan'cıg.
Yasemin, how are you?
Here it is the same.
I was telling you when you came, honey.
Look, I know.
I know it is very difficult.
But somehow you have to look ahead.
Your husband, the children have a wonderful home, honey.
The female bird makes the nest. Well.
But it doesn't end with doing.
You have to protect it. You have to fight if necessary.
Isn't that right, Aydan?
Exactly.
So who is it?
Haven't you learned who you are yet?
If it was, it was cracked by curiosity.
Me too, sugar. I also broke curiosity.
So it is difficult to fight without knowing who your enemy is.
It is not?
I do not know, I do not know. I do not know yet.
Mommy!
What are you doing there?
Well ...
I was going to buy ...
I couldn't sit on the list in my head.
What are you doing?
Was outside.
Derin ...
what?
We need to talk.
Are we going to talk mom? What are you doing to me?
... are you going to tell me what I can and cannot do?
No, so don't get tired ...
... you write a list. Give to me. I read.
Derin ...
Mom. Look, you won't be able to talk here anyway ...
... someone will see. You'll come back as you stretch.
Let's go home and talk there, okay?
Well.
Come on.
Come on, won't you come?
Welcome.
Mommy!
How are you honey?
We do watercolor.
Go.
Well dear, let me change a top.
Dear.
Finish the clouds until your mother arrives.
I'm going too. Well?
Here you have.
How did it go?
It is not very bright.
I met many places. Bahar has not worked.
My feet exploded all day.
My love, from day one. One thing is certain.
Actually there is something.
So your friend can configure something.
What a beautiful thing.
Bahar is on the boat and for a long time. This means that I don't have much.
Super!
Super too ...
I'm ready to take a big step ...
I don't know if ...
Derin will be a very good surprise.
It's a complete shock.
To who?
I mean it will be an adventure.
It will be a strange adventure.
Say yes ...
Don't be silly.
Think of it like this, a long vacation.
Then. That's.
You haven't come yet. Sister Bahar.
We need to speak confidently.
Okay, but look at us for now. Well?
OK Do not worry.
Sister Bahar.
It will be beautiful.
I left you the salad dressing.
I washed the vegetables, but dried them.
No more rice.
Well, you're great, Mrs. Filiz.
After that, I have it.
Maybe you are interested in something else.
Look Mom.
It is very beautiful darling.
There is also my sister Bahar.
I see.
Let me see.
This is great.
Shall we paint the tree together?
Of course. What color is it?
I do not know. What do you want?
Let my sister Bahar choose.
It is purple?
Your mother had a very nice dress. It was also purple.
Oh yeah. You were dressed for my father's birthday.
No way.
I mean, there is no purple tree.
I am sorry.
I forgot it.
Let's make another color.
Let's not make it purple. It will not be purple.
Oh why not dear?
There are many purple-flowered trees, right?
It was unanimously accepted at the time.
Take it.
Mother, is my sister Bahar going to eat?
Yes. This is a great idea.
Yes. Great idea!
I said that, lamb.
Bahar, stay for lunch.
Yes Yes Yes!
Mom, say something.
Mom, what happened? Let me see.
Ok nothing nothing nothing nothing.
Chopped up.
Ok, I'm fine. There is nothing.
Does it hurt mom?
It does not hurt. I do not have anything.
What happened so suddenly?
Evil eye for sure.
Girls, by the way, you're so cute, but ...
... I have a very important job tonight.
Maybe I'll stay another night.
Well.
Let me wash it there.
Yes please.
Oh God. Here they are ...
I don't think there are any fish.
Let. There is hope.
You fell early today, boy.
I'm confused, dad.
My dear never wanted to go home. I came here.
If you need to make up your mind about e ...
... confused of course.
Because every choice leaves one ...
... didn't they say it in vain?
Nothing is under my control. Nothing.
Don't check it then.
Let everyone act as you know.
You did not tell me?
I want to fly. Just because I want to be myself.
Let them live as they want.
So why do you think everything has happened?
Where did I go wrong with this job?
What have I done?
There is a story about Prometheus.
Steal the fire of the gods ...
... give it to the people. When people see the fire ...
... they ignited. This is not liked by the gods at all.
They punish Prometheus.
Actually, that story doesn't end like this. There is more.
The main god Zeus was so angry that ...
... he wants people to be punished too.
They create a woman from the earth and the water.
Pandora ...
They adorn this woman. They dress very well.
Whatever your own beauty ...
... they equip it and send it to earth.
Why is that?
To match the brother of Prometheus.
Epimetheus.
All the gifts and most importantly ...
... Zeus urges him to open up ...
... match the box with Epimetheus Pandora.
Come on, now, husband and wife ...
... well okay, they say okay.
They wonder what's in this box.
Epimetheus first ...
... does not want to open the box, afraid that they will come out, but ...
Is Pandora like that?
... inside out of curiosity.
Later ...
... can't stand the charm of Pandora's beauty ...
... Epimetheus.
He says ok.
Let's open the box.
Tell me, how does it look from the edge?
Husband and wife open the box.
A lie ...
Anger, jealousy, envy ...
In other words, whatever is bad distributes to the earth.
Husband and wife ...
... want to avoid it, but fail.
Pandora's box ...
... opened once.
The husband and wife repent. They close the box but ...
Box in ...
... nothing but hope.
Oh our boy ...
That's your story.
But you did, but you opened the box like this.
There is no cure.
You cannot go back.
Like Epimetheus.
Do you know what Epimetheus means?
It means thinking later.
I mean who thinks what I did.
Just like me.
I have nothing but hope.
It is like our child.
Like that ...
Let's talk at night, okay?
Do not worry. We should talk about it.
Well.
Come on, don't get cold.
Ok come on kiss I see you ..
Goodbye.
You're going?
How are you?
I do not know.
Little strange, of course. Everything.
The girls were very happy because I came.
Yasemin is also nervous.
He looks at me like he's killing me.
I don't know Murat ...
On the one hand ...
I think excuse for the girls.
It is a ridiculous situation.
You fell into this situation because of me, Bahar.
I'm sorry but ...
You see, I have nothing to do.
Whatever, no matter.
You don't have a crime either.
No, do you know what is bad?
I love Derin and Ece.
It's good for me to spend time with them.
Now to take it off ...
... to be an excuse ...
... it goes to my strength. Do you get it?
I don't want to lie to you.
I don't want to lie to anyone, Bahar.
No one.
I even want to hug you now ...
... I mean everything will be fine, but ...
... I can't say.
I know.
Look girl, this photo is beautiful.
Oh dad, this Bahar is crazy.
If you see him today, he handled Ece that way.
Kuzum couldn't cry to cry. I looked like this.
Tell me, miss ...
what is this? I'm going to quit school, nonsense.
My mom.
Sight. I thought a lot. My classes ...
I find it difficult to adapt to my classes.
I said why.
"Why?" I asked him. Why don't I want to go to school?
I don't want to be a pianist.
My daughter ...
... finishes your school. Don't be a pianist if you want.
You will be what you want to be.
Officially nonsense.
He didn't have to be a pianist.
Derin'ci, are you going to throw away ten whole years?
I'm wrong?
Mom, I say I don't want to be a pianist.
You don't understand what this is.
Look Derin. Look ...
... when you choose this ...
... we had the same discussions with you.
I don't want it because I don't want it.
... you opposed me. You threw yourself there. Look ...
... I was finally right. Turns out ...
... you don't want to be a pianist.
Mother, are you kidding me?
I was twelve or twelve.
Don't yell Derin.
Deep.
My daughter.
First of all, speak calmly.
You too, Yasemin.
Look ... I couldn't understand ...
Finish your school. Why don't you finish your school?
You don't have to be a pianist, honey.
There is half a semester here.
Are you going to waste them all?
Finish it. Don't be a pianist.
Daddy, I can't touch.
My daughter, what is that? Why is that?
What should I tell you?
This means that it could not be sufficiently prepared. Well?
As a result, why are we experiencing this crisis now?
Why do we live?
Because the final exam is coming up, either ...
Isn't this a regular crisis that we experience every year?
I know wrong?
Now he leaves school without wanting to leave.
Then he regrets it.
He tries to go back.
I'm not going!
Mom, my decision is final.
So what did you think for so many years my dear?
When you put the egg in the door, you are standing in front of us.
Did you think about that now?
Yasemin.
Do we listen to our son? Are we going to understand if you want?
What are we going to hear exactly?
As if these teenage crises were personality ...
... I really can't believe I ate it.
Teen crisis?
If it is. That is exactly Derin.
Who wants to go to that school instead of you ...
... do you know how many people want to be in your place?
They are dying to be in your place.
What's up mom?
What about me?
Don't yell Derin.
That's what I'm talking about.
My daughter!
Don't yell at your mother.
Whatever you say, please tell me correctly.
Pay attention to the tone of your voice for God's sake, Derin.
Recently, we have been infamous enough with the neighbors.
Isn't that you, mom?
Who thinks what the real world says, right?
Trying to put us all in the picture he drew ...
... but what we want ...
... you don't care how we feel, do you?
But how do we see ourselves from the outside?
Look, it's very important to you.
For example, being a pianist is very important.
Because you can show off like that to your friends, right?
You couldn't even finish that stupid school.
But the girl finished that big greenhouse.
The conservatory you haven't even gotten into ...
... are you going to feel good because you're done, mom?
What you don't understand is that this is my life.
For your life and I have my own life ...
... I want to live as I want. Well?
Derin ...
... if you want to make your own decisions ...
... then you have to stand on your own two feet.
Here we are mom.
I agree.
Is this a word to say to the boy for crying out loud, Yasemin?
Why are you doing like this?
I really wonder why you are doing it.
I hate her.
Bahar, I made up my mind. I go.
I also called Gökhan.
Oh, that was very bad. So in which pattern are you right?
But whatever. I think it will be good for all of you to escape.
I will miss you a little.
Thanks.
Why is that? I did not do anything.
It's okay? Did you hear me. You were with me.
I couldn't have done any of this without you.
We are friends.
They do.
Maybe it would be a little later, but you would.
I'm very curious about my mother's face when I say I'll go.
It's not like a very good idea, Derin.
Why is that?
Think about it, when you say it now ...
... it will say that you are threatening me with this.
You'll get on your nerves.
If you go, he will say it was my stubbornness.
But if you don't get advertised ...
... then exactly how you want it ...
... the shape of your face will be worth seeing.
Just think.
They won't even scream in front of you.
You are right.
You are right. It is better to go without telling anyone.
Exactly.
Welcome.
Where did you stay, darling?
My makeup is on, Sitare.
But you are beautiful, Ağa.
Thanks.
Everything looks great. Bless your hands.
Thanks, sweetie.
I hope they're all Aydan ...
... you didn't bother to go it alone.
Of course I didn't bother.
Possible, dear?
My wife helped a lot in the preparation.
What kind of man are you?
Didn't you just say that I organized everything?
Look at ağa. You make jokes like this.
They will think the truth.
Oh dear, I'm not taking Barlas seriously ...
... I learned that years ago.
My wife puts it in her mouth too.
Look, the little prince came too.
Thanks. Good night.
Hi dear.
We found it good, mom.
Hi handsome.
Hello Brother.
What are you doing, brother, are you okay?
Exactly brother. How are you?
Well.
Isn't Derin here?
Derin's head hurts a little. He stayed at home.
Yasemin, do you drink anything? What are we seeing as a movie?
Go.
Let's gossip. Let's do it.
Will you sit?
I'm good.
I will have something to drink.
Well darling.
Come on and sit down.
Excuse me ...
Yes guys.
Finished ...
Welcome to the 20th anniversary.
I'm going to give you drinks, right?
I am a host.
I can give.
You are not a stranger, Barlas.
Are you tired.
Come honey
You are drinking?
Onur. Handsome, are you going to drink?
No brother. I'm not going to drink. Thank you.
Play sweetly. Well? Go Go.
Really, why didn't Derin come?
It doesn't feel good at all.
Same story again, darling?
Sitare is not talking to me.
I swear.
No.
One, two again with his father ...
... he talks.
He's very angry with me.
School.
My life is not going, nor is it going to school.
So I spoke to management. What can we do, what can we do?
I don't know how long they will succeed.
God.
Sometimes I am glad that we really did not have children.
Where did that come from out of nowhere?
What are you doing at home all day?
What does my life do at home all day?
He's doing nothing but pouting.
It's not going to work, honey.
Both with the caretaker.
She's so bad.
Of course, Hilal is destroyed.
The woman stopped crying.
Pity.
You?
It's me?
What did you do?
So ...
... Growing to ...
... I'm so sorry to say my sweet ...
... you come and tell us here, right?
I understand it well.
What does that mean, Yasemin?
No. I wonder, so you ...
I wonder ...
... you know me too ...
... here and there ...
Ay Yasemin is really enough.
Your setup played well.
Your ear doesn't hear your mouth, sugar.
No. What do I have to do with Hilal?
Out of your mouth.
Of course I will come and tell it.
You said it like a child.
I'm going to have something to eat.
You broke my way.
Aydan, I'm talking nonsense, right?
So what you have to do with Hilal is really.
Certain.
The woman mounted her husband with a babysitter at the hotel.
He is deluded.
Horn.
Let's close.
Let's close the topic.
How do you do this to yourself?
Mom, I'm going.
Where my dear?
So ...
Are you going to a special place?
I will meet with friends. No extension.
I didn't say anything right, my dear Onur.
Come on, have fun. Goodbye.
Come on, Ece. Come beautiful girl.
Come and sit.
Let's shoot a little.
Let's sit like this.
Good for you.
Sitare ...
You say auntie. Sitare aunt.
Ay Barlas, don't interfere.
I don't like it anyway, Aunt Meyze.
Sitare is sugar.
I'm hungry.
Well.
Let's prepare something for you. Eat.
Can you eat it alone?
Take your fork.
Which one do you want?
From this.
Well.
Anyway, think no more.
It is happening.
I put.
Other.
From this.
White? It is black?
Black.
Ay Barlas, your grandfather likes this too. It is not?
Other.
And this.
It doesn't happen, but it's sauce.
Then don't be mad at us.
Not angry, not angry.
Sister Bahar is giving me at home.
Who is Bahar's sister?
He comes to play with me.
A very sweet sister.
The caregiver is safe.
I suppose.
He is not a caregiver.
He is my friend.
He bought me a baby.
If you come tomorrow, we will play with you.
It's okay anyway, sugar. Come on, like this ...
... I put. You eat it here.
Come on, eat. I have a bit of work.
Slow. Be careful.
What happened?
I do not know.
Derin'cig ...
... I don't know what it means?
You probably won't say that I gave up.
No no ..
I'm scared, Bahar.
So, in a small boat, with a lot of people ...
... if I fail.
Honey ...
What's going to go wrong?
You will make tea and coffee at the bottom.
What happens if you fail?
I guess they can't throw you into the sea.
Without telling my mom and dad ...
... do you think it's okay to go?
At least I was calling my father.
No way.
Derin, no.
He goes and tells your mother. Everything is ruined.
You can't go anywhere.
So ...
... give up, don't go.
But I think it will be a huge failure if you give up.
Are you saying that?
It would be great for you to embark on this adventure, darling.
Looking for Onur.
Normal, phones are for this. Here you have.
In ...
... we're still mad at it.
So we never talk.
After talking to someone ...
I didn't talk either.
I think you did your best.
So let's think a bit in your mind.
No, I'll call Onur.
You're going to ruin all of Derin.
So darling
Look, if you leave now without warning ...
... it comes to Onur's mind.
After all, it means I'm going ...
... take it and go to the suitcase.
Do you forget what you told yourself?
You told me I was judging you.
Please soften so fast.
Like I said, if you leave now ...
Onur will come to his mind. I'm sure.
You will understand what you have lost.
Are you sure?
Jump with surprise maybe to the plane ...
... it arrives at one of the cities that you anchored.
This is not a difficult thing for him.
Wouldn't it be more romantic like this?
Then.
I also believe it. Believe me
Go.
You put me a little again.
Are you crazy?
Why do you keep bringing that girl home?
Which girl? What are you saying Sitare?
Don't fake Yasemin.
You know who I'm talking about.
Ece, when Bahar said sister, I got a shot from my brain.
I guess you were crazy.
There is no other explanation for this.
You are either manic or very pure.
Was you.
It was you who knew everything.
You know Bahar.
This is not our topic, Yasemin.
And you didn't tell me.
I didn't say anything to anyone.
Sitare could at least have warned me.
I can not believe.
That's why you interrogated this girl at our house.
And then he looked me in the eye ...
... you lied Sitare.
I can not believe you.
Did you tell Aydan?
No, sugar.
Of course I didn't say it.
How can I know ...
... honey, you'll act like that stupid.
I didn't tell anyone so it wouldn't spill.
Look at me, Yasemin. Meet yourself.
You need to send that girl away from home immediately.
Otherwise, you will completely lose your husband.
Well.
Well enough now.
You will make me cry too.
Well well. I go.
Bahar ...
... will be the craziest thing I've ever done in my life.
Honey, this ...
... will be the first crazy thing I ever do in your life.
Yes.
Right.
I go.
I will see.
Welcome.
Hello everybody.
We are waiting for someone. We will get up soon.
Do you want me to take your suitcase to the ship?
It would be great. Thanks.
Bahar.
We were waiting for someone. If you want to go wait.
Very good honey.
Take care, okay?
Equally.
Thanks again.
I will see.
Come on girl.
Are you waiting in the hall?
Let me put Ece to bed. Let's talk.
Well.
I guess you're not worried about the kids being home this time.
We have to talk about this now.
My lamb.
Come.
Go to sleep.
Good night my princess, my dear.
Onur.
Hello.
I know you will be mad when you see this video.
Maybe even a little broken.
You are also right.
But ...
I ...
... to give up, tell my mother ...
I was afraid you would stop me.
But...
I didn't want to go without saying goodbye.
So ...
... Take care.
Goodbye.
I'm a little scared.
Actually because ...
... with people I've never met ...
I'm going on a time adventure.
I'm scared but ...
... I have to do this too.
Because to my mother otherwise ...
I can't prove I'm an adult.
Anyway ...
... let me show you a bit of our ship.
Such.
This is also the case.
Her name is Tiririme.
I think it meant a ship in very absurd Greek.
Eccentric types that you will understand.
So ...
... they're a bit strange.
I don't know how to deal, but ...
... somehow I'll get along.
Anyway, with this output, the video will be one hour long.
Let me not stretch anymore.
I'd be glad if you call me from time to time.
Well ...
... if you're still not mad at me.
Here you have. Sleep beautifully.
Story.
It is a tale?
It is too late for the story.
It is a party or a fairy tale.
Why did you organize your babies like this?
We played a new game ...
... with my sister Bahar.
Tell me, what kind of game is this?
Ece baby is sleeping with Bahar baby.
What is Murat doing baby there?
He waits.
You're waiting for me.
What is Yasemin doing baby?
He is always in the kitchen.
She cooks in the kitchen.
Could you take a look at the problems you opened for us?
What would you say?
Bahar, of course.
So this girl has a mental illness.
I don't know if it's crazy.
Are we going to talk about her again?
Why can't we talk about both of them?
Look, I'll tell you.
Look, do you know what this is?
This is me. Yasemin baby. Well?
I am standing in the kitchen.
Where are you. You know?
In Ece's room ...
... with Bahar ...
... at the head of the sleeping Ece.
Do you get it?
Look at the game he had with the boy.
Can you believe it?
So he wants to send me out of this house.
He wants to replace me.
Yasemin ...
... are you aware of what you're saying?
A toy in your hand.
Ece's toy ...
The boy is playing with it.
Murat, you are naive.
Or are you doing the naive trick.
Or I do not know. Maybe you two are close.
That's enough. Enough is enough, Yasemin.
Enough. I'm coming.
You started to go crazy.
I think the best way is to leave Murat's house.
Yes?
In my opinion ...
... you better get out of the house.
Gather your luggage.
Go home.
If your wife ...
... don't worry if she fired him from home.
You've been waiting for someone else, right?
But I'm here, daddy.
You are also your mother's daughter.
You are looking for troubles.
Yes. You better get out of this house.
Because unless you get out of this house ...
... we will never get rid of this girl. Well?
This girl won't leave us alone.
I am not your problem.
I am an extra in your war.
You haven't thought of me.
It is not mine. But you are that girl's problem, Murat.
And it will never leave us alone.
Take a look at what I am right now?
You even turned your back on me.
You just fired me from the house. Are you warned?
I think you wanted to go.
I gave you an excuse.
Now go comfortably.
Well.
Let it be what you want.
As you want it ...
... so be it.
But know that this is not my wish.
I wouldn't want to leave this house like this, Yasemin.
It never is.
It shouldn't have been like that.
It is too late to do what we want now.
I'm telling you ...
... let me help you pack your things.
I said you would do what I tell you.
I said you won't get off my word
Don't bring me here again.
I said you would stay in my hand
I said life *** to ruin my life.
You tried to hit the man without the genie.
Does it work like this?
It doesn't have to be this way, Yasemin.
Goodbye Murat.
Look, there is no going back.