I said you would love my surprise.
Yasemin ...
... you ...
... I have to tell you something.
Very important.
I'm listening.
I'll tell you clearly, Yasemin.
Everything happened suddenly, Yasemin.
Something happened.
What could we do with love?
Even the music must be silent sometimes in love.
You have to fall in love.
Applaud our composer Derin Düdenli.
Are you okay?
Thanks for everything.
You were very good.
What would you say?
Mom, I'm going to sing.
Darling of course.
Do you want to sing too?
I think there is a little princess among us who wants to celebrate her father's birthday.
With your permission.
Let's run.
Happy Birthday Dad.
Happy birthday, happy birthday ...
... happy birthday dad.
My dear well done, how beautiful you said.
With your permission.
Are you okay?
Not bad.
Bahar has recovered so well that it would have disgraced me.
Don't worry, nobody understood anything.
How are your hands?
As if I didn't feel anything.
Look ...
... we're leaving tomorrow, okay?
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I have never seen anything so beautiful.
Especially that trip you took at the end ...
... No matter how proud Yasemin is with you.
Thanks.
With your permission ...
I'll come soon, okay.
I admire the color of your voice.
Thank you.
Sorry, I'm taking Bahar for two minutes.
Where?
Great date.
But.
Look who I brought you.
I want to introduce you to Bahar.
Your voice is tremendous miss.
Thank you.
No, no seriously, they all passed out.
You have become the surprise of the night. It is not?
Sorry, I got together, but ...
... Ma'am, what a beautiful voice this is.
I mean, I was surprised, you are great.
Thank you.
One minute.
But I know you from somewhere, but I couldn't get it out.
I do not know.
It could be from anywhere, right?
No, no, I do not forget the face that I saw again, but.
Maybe somewhere you sing.
Possible ...
... I have a small fan base.
Could be.
What do you put on the man Ruhir?
Now, if you'll excuse me, I want to speak to our people.
OK.
What are you doing?
We are fine, we were talking about life.
Where are you? I could not see you.
Cemil and his wife came and hung them up a bit, they sold the house in Sapanca.
Sapanca ...
... if we say Sapanca, are we going somewhere on the weekend?
Wait a minute, I was going to talk something.
If I want your permission?
I don't feel very good either.
Are you okay?
My stomach got a little sick but it happens when I rest.
Are we going to look for something like a drug?
Don't bother, thank you.
Good night.
Good night Miss.
I say Sapanca, let's go somewhere.
I think it's a great idea.
How much did they sell?
I don't know, I didn't ask him.
What are you doing here?
You're invited.
Didn't you text me like my birthday?
Look, what kind of game is this, I say I don't like it at all.
Surprise.
What?
There is no game Murat.
The surprise is a surprise that your wife made you.
So sorry.
What?
Ain't it funny how your wife's surprise is me
I'm surprised by this surprise ...
... I didn't like it at all.
And your own home too?
You missed me so much.
Go.
Ah Baharcım ...
Congratulations on how good you were or we love the voice in the last part, right?
We love the final vocal part, right?
Yes.
Husband and wife are very nice.
Murat Bey liked it too.
He also loved your surprise.
Isn't that right, Murat Bey?
Very nice song.
I am very happy with your liking.
With your permission, I ...
... will use the sink upstairs.
Of course.
Very sweet girl.
He was going to say something that he was looking at Derin. You tried to say something.
Yasemin ...
... I ...
... let's talk now, not the time ...
... at the first opportunity.
Well.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
What are you doing?
My job.
Your work?
How much do you care about yourself?
Have you been taken?
Are you using my son to approach me with two grams of your brain?
I resolved the situation, parenting ...
... I have no business with you after this time.
As for her son ...
... it was because you threatened my mother ...
... you can think of as insurance.
If you don't touch my mom ...
I don't have to talk to your son.
Meanwhile ...
... keep in mind that I'm not like Sema.
Well ...
well, little devil.
Since the bathroom is full downstairs, it must have been empty here.
I will update my makeup my photos should be nice, right?
It is.
What happened dear, what happened?
Should we be long or delayed?
No sugar, it would be a shame if the cake has not been cut yet.
Oh yeah.
We will go to the exit.
You find Onur disappeared again.
It's fine. Sitare.
Where can I find Onur?
This is not something to be neglected.
We go to the doctor first thing in the morning, I don't want any objection, okay?
Well.
Okay, let's go.
Did you see Bahar?
No, you didn't speak the last one?
Where did this girl go?
As he is the star of the night, Onur accepts the celebrations.
I am arriving right now.
Bahar.
Brother Murat.
Um ...
... I looked.
It was a beautiful song, I said thank you. Did you see Bahar Hanım?
No, i have not seen it.
What are you doing here?
I was going to bring a cardigan for Derin.
Do not go cold my beautiful daughter.
Thanks brother.
Tonight would never have been so beautiful if her soul hadn't worked so hard to spy on us like this.
Yasemin with pleasure.
He is the man of spiritual details, he can help you whenever you want.
Murat ...
... We are here.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, the hero of the night has arrived too.
You're very lucky Murat, this whole team has officially destroyed them for you.
Thanks to my wife every year.
Yasemin, I'll have you a drink.
No.
What would you drink please?
Water.
I am reaching the water.
My life ...
... Is there a problem?
No, I'm looking at it.
Yasemin.
Thank you.
Please enjoy your food.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
Isn't that my cardigan?
Yes, the air got cold, don't you put it on?
Look at the cake, come on.
Now tonight ...
... Murat ...
... complete ...
... no no, I won't say exactly how old you were.
Of course, no one here tonight will know how old Murat is.
But all of you ...
... there is something I really want you to learn ...
... because we have it ...
... this is what keeps us alive ...
... for incredible years ...
... because he's so skinny, he's very attentive, so as a family ...
... we want to thank him very much.
Muratcığım cut the cake.
Pie.
Here you have.
Ruhi ...
... this is not cherry.
Muratcığım you don't like cherries.
Me?
I don't like cherries.
I don't like tart cherry friends.
Maybe I was going to have cherry this year.
How do you know?
My daughter, I don't like cherry.
Girl, I don't like cherries.
What if we can come get this cake and get it out?
Yasemin ...
Why isn't the cake cherry?
Murat doesn't like a fruit cake, Ruhi made it to sabotage, I guess you can eat it.
My wife, maybe you wanted to eat cherries this year, my wife, you ...
... right?
Doesn't your soul want to have cherry once in your life?
I don't understand why this cherry is a question and why they laughed so hard.
I'll tell you later, dear.
What can Murat tell you about this cherry joke?
With my wife between us.
I'll explain, I'll explain
Well.
Let's have a lot of fun, eat the cake, and go to bed right away.
But today is my father's birthday.
That's right, my daughter, sleep late tonight.
Mrs. Filiz.
It's not possible, you know Murat.
We are going to bring them here.
Oh God, I'm so sorry.
Nothing daughter.
I Sitareci.
Thanks, sweetie.
Did you take my soul?
Thanks Yasemin.
I raise the glass to my dear wife, my friends first ...
... thank you all very much, you bothered to come to this surprise party.
My dear wife is good.
Who thinks what to eat for us ...
... who decides when to go to bed, who thinks more of us than we do? ...
... I am drinking for my dear wife. It is good that you are my wife. What would we do without you?
Enough, Yasemin ...
... that's enough ...
When will this torture end?
Look, today is my birthday.
My birthday is mine today.
Isn't there a kiss?
My gift was there ...
... but ...
... you're mad at something again ...
... and you're going to punish me again, right?
I did not do this.
What is this enough? What is this for the love of God?
My husband, I want to kiss you or what is in you?
What is it and why are you doing this to me and why?
I'm so tired, Murat, let me be alone.
You are always tired.
You are tired...
... you are always far away.
You laugh alongside people with your laughter and have fun while you are alone ...
... wall ...
... you are like a wall.
What do you expect me to do?
Did I scold you in people, Murat?
Did I just talk like you?
I don't understand why you are drinking so much.
Look at you, you can't stand.
Murat you have children ...
... you have a wife Murat ...
... your dignity is important to me.
I want to protect my dignity, I cannot be a mask on people like you.
Be our friend, what if we had a little drink?
Is that a little bit?
Yes small.
Murat stand up ...
... you smell like carrion.
Please see what happens.
Get away from me.
You can't treat me like that, Yasemin, your husband, I am.
Please let's go.
Drop it.
It's enough or enough, enough Yasemin is enough, what stupidity is enough or ...
... what did I do to you? When will your eyes clear me, when, why are you doing this to us? Why?
Leave me alone.
Well.
- Come, that's enough. - Leave me alone.
God.
What happened? Something happened?
Leave me alone.
Leave it alone.
Let me see this.
Derin ...
Didn't you go to bed?
Mom, are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine, my feet got stuck, I hit my head against the wall, my lamb.
I'm fine, I'll look at Ece.
Okay, I'll take care of Ece.
I'll take care.
Hello daughter.
Come on, go to bed, dear.
Take it dear.
Thanks.
Good morning daughter, these cheeses will be finished.
My life ...
... everything was great last night ...
... thanks for everything.
You are very tired for me.
No, I didn't do it alone, the girls also helped a lot.
But if Derin isn't deep, it wouldn't be so beautiful if he didn't write that song.
Thanks daughter.
Oh, take this.
What to your head mother?
Nothing.
I accidentally hit my life.
I have to go out, a request?
No dad.
See you later.
See you honey.
I forgot what to say to these guys ...
... folding the ornaments ...
... removing them.
You officially destroyed the plan.
No, I don't understand why you ran after me now, why are you giving up?
And what is the disappearance? How did I call? Why don't you open your phone?
Don't you understand that my stomach was wrong?
What kind of liar are you?
... What disease did you invent to escape from there?
Well, I made it up, I made it up, and I went home.
It's good because?
What would happen when he explained?
... your mother never gives up on your father.
Especially for a juvenile bug like me.
Since the party made such an exit, we were going to be in a small state, something would not change for me.
Then they would throw me in the corner again.
Yes, you are right.
Do you have any suggestion?
We need to get into the vein.
We can't get anywhere with such naive movements, do we understand that we have to suffer this man?
We need to get your money, power, everything, so I don't know, you don't want it anyway?
Ay Şekerim officially stretched the woman like a drum, I have not seen such a bad operation.
It was so bad that I didn't really know what to say or what to do, the woman flowed at some point.
Her husband went to the Maldives with his secretary, or the rest of the woman was shocked.
Meanwhile, Sitareci were amazing, thank you so much so they officially saved the night.
I would like my sweet.
What did you do then?
What?
What will it be, Yasemin?
... flowers, strawberries at night.
Yes, tell me, you have the real news.
I ...
... We now ...
... sorry, the door knocked.
Here you are.
Hello.
I brought Ms. Yasemin's dress.
He's at home?
Here you are.
Bahar has arrived.
Hello everybody.
Sorry I forgot to leave the dress when I got sick early last night.
Yes, yes, we have seen that it was bad, we will be angry.
It doesn't matter now, are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine, thank you.
Not at all, he was in no rush. Filiz Hanımcığım, can you take this and go up?
We were going to have tea now.
I am not upset.
Oh by the way, I forgot to give this in a hurry for Murat Bey's birthday.
It's so kind, Bahar, I insist, come on, come and sit with us.
Come on, please sit down.
Hurry?
How good we were boiling, we know them both.
Well.
If you insist.
Alo and what did you think again?
Nothing at all.
Come on, Figen Hodja says he doesn't take the rest.
The woman put me on the head, I have no fingers, and while I was working the other day, my hand was officially closed.
But at the prom I had such a seat that the bottom of the woman will fall off.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
I am not going to class.
Why is that?
My stomach is nauseous or I'm not feeling very well, so I can go home and get some rest.
Okay, you know, I'm running away.
What a pretty surprise.
It's not a surprise or something, you know that very well, we're going to the hospital.
Well, I have a lesson.
Derin ...
... I even got the appointment, it's too late for you to sneak out of this job.
Come on, never put on your beautiful face.
Ms. Filiz is not the same team with these tea spoons and cutlery alone.
I am sorry, I mistook.
Okay, it doesn't matter, and if you fold these napkins like this, not a triangle, but a square.
Well.
Really? Where are you sitting
Kadikoy.
Isn't it difficult for the woman?
I don't ...
... handle it.
Yes, everything is ready. Let's go to the table.
So how do you know Barlas?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I couldn't understand, who is Barlas?
My husband.
I think we met him but couldn't remember him.
I did not understand well, I suppose you think you will find me immediately.
Then I would like the teas.
Can we have some Filiz Hanımcığım tea?
Sitareci, my dear, Aydancığım, Bahar sit down and you.
Look over there, you're crazy.
You became an astronaut.
Come on.
No, I was going to make an announcement at some point not to burn it with fire.
The exaggeration is not so much.
Caramba.
No, I saw this girl somewhere, but where I saw her.
Who found this?
Let me know, brother, surprise.
What's going on?
... okay brother ...
... left, it's over.
He went away.
You know, Sitareci? Onur, introduced us to Bahar.
You meet Onur, am I right?
Is that so?
We are going to the same gym with Onur. Actually, when he met Derin from school, he noticed.
School finished yet?
Unfortunately.
Since he had to earn money, he had to take a break from time to time.
It is very difficult, both school and work are difficult.
Mommy.
My angel.
My dear woke up, do you come and come to see?
You want to paint?
Okay, let's find something else, sit down a bit.
Do you want to eat these?
Well ...
... are you working at the nightclub, honey?
In other words, I don't realize that I also do a lot of bar shows.
It must be difficult to work at night.
But I got used to it.
Should I play in my room?
I think it's a great idea.
Look, I had nothing.
It seems that way.
What happened?
You seem sad ...
We will go to another doctor.
We need to cook fast.
Bahar ...
... come on, you're not playing games.
Oh I'm very sorry.
So ...
... let this mother be a baby ...
... this is daddy baby.
No, this mother, this father.
This is Ececik and this is his older sister.
So what is Bahar?
Let this be Bahar.
It is so beautiful this Bahar baby.
So ...
... baby father and baby mother sleep there.
No way.
Why?
Because Ece is sick, Murat, you do not understand that this boy is responsible for everything because of you, you are going to sleep alone. With the mother, Ece baby will lie down.
Bahar.
Yes Dear.
Should they cook?
Let them do it.
Look.
I opened it.
Hello my daughter, good night.
Hi Dad, Bahar you remember my friend from school, right?
I remember, of course, hello.
Welcome dad.
Princess.
Darling, what's up, darling?
How are you?
Dad, how are you, how are you so formal?
I'm fine you?
Thanks.
Okay, I'll change my clothes, okay?
Welcome Dear.
Hello dear, hello.
Let me shower and come.
Okay, but we have guests, get it quickly.
Quick, I'm coming.
Okay, why are you sweating so much?
I wonder if I am sick.
Come on, it's not hot either.
Come on, I don't understand.
His ring, I'll say something, came.
Well.
Go.
Is the table okay girls?
Okay, mom is ready.
Come on, let's see.
Mom ...
... you're so beautiful again.
One drink before eating so many liars?
It would be very good.
I saw your friend today ...
... he said hello.
Which one of my friend?
Bahar.
Is that so?
Where did you meet?
She brought Yasemin's dress back.
She is a pretty girl.
This.
What did he say?
We have never talked about air to water.
Why is that?
Is there something I should know, honey?
I understand now.
It's not a problem like you guessed, mom.
What does it mean?
I'm hungry like a wolf.
Go.
Come honey
Welcome back.
So I don't think I'm putting too much pressure on you. Bahar, after all, Ece also has a school.
It's actually a great idea.
What is a great idea?
I hired Bahar.
Like Ece's gaming sister.
Well, Yasemin ...
There is no objection.
Hurrah!
Thank you Mrs. Yasemin.
No problem.
Oh, I was just forgetting, dad ...
... look Bahar is very polite who bought you a present?
Thanks.
Blue.
Is there a problem?
No, no ...
... no problem, how do you know, of course Murat doesn't like blue very much ...
... not much of its color, no Murat ...
... it doesn't suit ...
... but you are very elegant, thank you very much.
Is that so?
Fits my daughter.
But since this is your gift, I will give it to you because it suits you better.
My dear.
How is your school going?
Good mommy, as always.
I'll say something ...
... I love your composition, so I think it's a very different and very powerful composition.
It is not like this?
Composite ...
... isn't it good?
Yes. Yes.
I think the idea of ​​stopping at a time is very creative.
A tremendous idea was drawn in that section at a very different time.
It is not like this?
How was everyone scared, but suddenly there was something wrong?
You are a genius, Derinci.
Thanks.
Actually, I said not to blow up, but you found such a good idea, Derin.
Meanwhile, words are breaking, congratulations Murat Bey.
Thanks.
Anyway, I said let's sing ...
... come and say love ...
I'll come if he says come.
... I will run for your love.
Where do you know this girl?
I do not know it very well.
Why did you ask?
His voice was good.
The food is great ...
Let's tell Leman Hanım to do it frequently.
Did you like it too?
Well ...
Give me the salad.
Did you know that Brother Ruhi said I know her?
Father.
Yes son.
Brother Ruhi said I know her.
What should I know, boy? I don't care about Bahar, but it's in your head.
Can I have some meat?
Thank you.
Why are you angry?
... we are talking here.
Well.
Let's talk.
What are we going to talk about?
We are chatting, why are you nervous now?
Why do you also know Bahar?
I don't know, where will I know about Bahar?
Enough ...
... close this matter.
Let's have a comfortable meal.
Let me kiss your mouth.
Come on, kiss me.
Barlas.
Yasemin ...
... about last night ...
... I want to talk.
Let's talk ...
... let's talk about our responsibilities?
OR...
... we can't do it according to our heads, for example.
Here you have.
Murat, we have two children at home.
... we must be aware of this ...
... yes boring yes difficult ...
... but unfortunately being a father is something like this.
I know that.
Is that so?
So why don't you think it does that to me?
Because ...
... you ...
... have a bad mood to look at everything from your own perspective because ...
You Everything ...
... you look through your own eyes and interpret.
Murat, you attacked me last night.
I said no, but you didn't even listen to me ...
... how do you think I can interpret this?
We need to act a bit mentally now.
Well?
I want the children to understand nothing. Derin is already very shocked.
I don't want them to be sadder.
Tonight ...
... how it's supposed to be ...
... we're going to sleep together in our room.
This issue is now closed here.
In the meantime, I don't want you to interpret this offer in any other way, so you shouldn't think of anything else.
I only got you ...
... I didn't forgive him.
Understood.
You speak, I will go out.
No, no, it's not necessary, honey.
I will not speak now.
Of course, you wondered when you left the party early and even asked me if you saw it.
I don't know if we didn't talk or when I had to leave so early, I'll probably ask you what you did, like you said, you wonder.
You were right, my mother will never give up on my father.
From the orchestra.
I'm late like this, but is there no problem?
No, honey, no, ours are comfortable, and now you are counted as family.
You are Ece's older sister.
I am aware of what they offer me forever.
You are very lucky. Very good people.
They are not bad.
I guess they get along so well?
They adapt well.
It seems to me an ideal couple.
Yeah yeah, they get along really well ...
... they're even like a team that always complement each other, they're still so in love that they can never give up.
Thank you very much for everything.
You're going?
Let me get up now.
Let's call a cab right now.
My mother called, but they said there was no taxi.
Don't bother, I'll run away.
No, this is not the case at this time. Murat, will you leave her?
Do not bother yourself.
No dear, what a hassle.
How is this bad Turkish movie?
What did my friend do?
What?
I tell you?
... you are the one who lied to me, you say you get out of the car and you are my head, and now you also offend me as if I did something.
What do I say I did?
No, I mean, I'm not going to explode, I'm not going to fail, but you are irritating.
What are you doing?
This is bad.
What?
What wrong, what happens?
What's wrong with this, or I don't see anything wrong with that, Murat ...
... so we both feel good about each other, we have a good time, we have fun together, which could be wrong with that ...
... who says I don't understand either, or what could be wrong to be happy.
We are both grown up and free.
It happens ...
... it's debatable how free you are, of course I forgot.
What does that mean now?
Even your wife decides what color you like.
Who are you?
Is he the person that Yasemin wants you to be ...
... otherwise I know, I know, love ...
... but it's obvious that Murat, whom Yasemin never met, or rather, he doesn't even want to know ?
Anyway ...
... why am I talking about that?
Don't be afraid not to bother you ...
... I'm not going to tell your wife what happened ...
... well, there's nothing to tell.
I'll call you tomorrow and tell you that I don't take the job ...
... this problem goes away.
But I must tell you something ...
... if you want to think about what I said ...
... I don't know how long you can go on like this.
Good night.
Idiot, I'm still thinking ...
I can't.
What can't I do?
You're right ...
... I can't do this.
I can't be that Murat anyway.
I don't want to upset anyone ...
... anyone ...
What am I going to do?
Don't worry then.
I do not bother.
Come on.
Welcome our boy.
Thanks.
Welcome.
Wait, what are you doing, what are you doing?
Don't worry ...
... this fortune in me, this wish is a great income, he puts his mouth on the hook.
Although he doesn't want to be caught, no son of Adam can take him and put him in this bucket.
But ...
... love is here.
Even a bucket of water can make it look like water.
Can I sit?
Of course, it is late.
Should I tell you something, boy?
Here you are.
You will leave it all to yourself ...
... current.
Does it happen when I say I quit?
Even if you don't let go, our boy cuts off love.
You are trapped, now ...
... a curtain is pulled over your eye ...
... everything I say is empty ...
... wherever your heart takes you, there is no other solution.
What are you looking for?
... our boy is in vain, I tell you ...
... when I see myself like this, I'm reading one by one ...
Yes, tell me to relax.
I'm confused ...
... am I in love or am I happy?
... What do I want ...
... I don't know ...
... mixed.
You will fly, our boy will fly, you will risk falling before flying.
If he won't be able to move ...
... why did he put this wing on my heart?
... I remember correct why to fly, where to put it ...
... takes off and turns around to find me saved and find me in a bucket.
I am in such a place ...
... what is possible to go ...
what is possible to stay ...
... I am somewhere ...
... between surrendering and resisting ...
... I am in the middle of the earth with ...
... on the eve of losing ...
... I am on the brink of a new life ...
... it will hurt if I stay ...
... I go .. .
... my life.
I know you don't sleep, Yasemin.
Don't worry, I won't touch you.
Good night.
If there is a happy night, be yours.
Your suit is ready.
Breakfast is also ready in ten minutes.
Good Morning.
Come on, Murat, what are you doing?
You are like a child.
No, I can't say I was wrong ...
You have to see, I'm trying to rotate, I can't rotate. The man is looking at me like this, if I see my soul, my soul left my body.
What happened?
This bothers me, Bahar.
About what?
So ...
... this thing between us ...
... let's say friendship.
Will we come back to the head again?
You know what I think sometimes ...
... you're the one who doesn't want to be happy.
What does this mean, where do you get it from now?
You never leave yourself in the moment, you don't know how to be happy with Murat, you don't know how to be happy.
I don't know ...
... maybe you don't know you're right.
By looking at these latest tests and evaluating the opinions of my other colleagues, I can say that ...
... the cause of your discomfort is not physical.
We believe this is for psychosomatic reasons.
Then?
Therefore, I recommend that you meet with a psychiatrist, even if you want to have Ayşegül Hanım in our hospital, you can contact her immediately.
... the room is already aware of this situation.
But look how on this side ...
as if it had made a difference.
I said it, I said it ...
... said it will be the same for a few days, is there a difference?
So there is a little difference.
Didn't you just make Sitare?
Look, this is between these eyebrows, look here, so there are no wrinkles when you frown.
HE.
I understand that you don't need sugar, you don't care, your husband admires you, but don't be so indifferent to us mortals.
Speaking of mortal, there was a young woman working with you. What was Bade's name?
Bahar isn't happening that morning, but she's going to school ...
... she's not working the toilet anyway, playing with Ece.
He imagined he was playing the game.
Yasemin ...
... young girl ...
... don't you hesitate?
Murat?
... nonsense, Derin friend, these are things that are not Murat's style.
I swear whatever it is that I should lie.
Don't you think so?
If my sweet, Yasemin does not bother, I think there is no problem.
The woman is confident, my dear.
But they are right, they are very sweet.
I don't know, sugar, I only know one thing. One day if your husband gives you flowers, there is something behind it.
I'm out of work, I'm out ...
... I'll come to you in a few hours and let you know if the caller is asking.
Thanks.
Which one are you looking at?
These earrings ...
Aren't they so beautiful?
I think, is it a seahorse?
Yes, yes, I looked like that.
We are going to buy, do you want them?
How it is not necessary is expensive.
Couldn't you be the one who told me to live in the moment?
Please I am asking you.
Hello everybody.
Hello and welcome.
There is a seahorse in the window, can we get the earrings?
I'm sorry Mr.
... the earring was sold out, more precisely, one of our clients set it aside for his wife.
Do you want anything else?
Will you stop Bahar, please?
What happened? Why are you doing this?
I am not your lover, nor am I closing.
Never again, don't leave me like this.
I can't understand, so I said something wrong, I said, let's buy another, what's up?
The gift is something taken from the heart, Murat, you could think of me and buy it in the trash ...
... I liked those earrings, but I would not like a gold bracelet.
I'm fine, I'm not taking the medicine.
Yes, but you're stressed, you heard what the psychiatrist said.
What happened now, whoever said to see another doctor, were you immediately convinced by what this woman said?
Okay, they couldn't find anything.
Well then I have nothing and I'm fine.
I'm just trying to help you.
Let me tell you, what you did is not helping me.
Don't behave like a child.
Like a child?
What do you think you are?
I'm just trying to help you.
No Onur, you won't help me, okay?
Where are you going?
What do you care
Still not here? This Murat Effendi.
You've done a rush job, we'll hold the meeting and I'll pass the information on to you, Dad.
What do you know about it, what information will you pass on?
Speak before, let Onur come.
I'm talking, I'm already saying dad.
I know very well what he did and what he wanted to do.
Look at me, Barlas, I don't want to break your heart, but if I get involved, you hurt yourself.
Competition with your child.
You lose.
Very good, Mr. Sadri.
What?
Where are you?
What do you care
If my son responded as a man, there is something to consult, I would say that if you are looking for it, come soon.
I wasn't around you, weren't you saying to get involved in company business?
Your configuration breaks again, you are surprised, come back, let's talk, we come, you come.
I will come, we will talk, we will solve everything.
Then you will see what the settings are.
I apologize, are you still going to pout?
I'm not a money fool to be affected when he says he likes me when he puts me in the jewelry box.
You understand me?
The whole neighborhood understood.
What does that mean?
So you said so loud that everyone understood.
I get mad about those things.
You are right, I sincerely tell you that you are right.
I mean, after that I'll buy you junk as a gift.
You have one.
I swear I didn't know what you said.
Come on, I'm gone.
Well.
I am sorry.
Not important.
What are you trying to do?
I know what to say honey, but if you want to come tell me, don't stay there.
Sorry, I'll pack a little house, but if you want a lot, I can make you a coffee.
What are you trying to do?
Make it enough, no intimidation, we love each other with murat.
Bahar come to you, the man is married.
Well ...
... what if he's married?
What happened?
... I think your ears can't hear, I say the man is married.
No ...
... hears great ...
... but I can't see a problem with that ...
... let me give you an example if you understand better ...
... for example, your dad.
Because of someone like you, I was breaking up a bit more with my father and you are the only kind of opportunist who looks like your mother.
Is that so?
Then you will be happy with your mother and father in life, now, get out of my house, get out of my house, don't interfere with my work or my life.
Also ...
... we both know that you don't think of me as darling, you just try to punish him because your father didn't give you the right ...
... don't eat me, but if you want more air, come out now.
I'm coming partner.
Calm down, I took care that the meeting is over now.
Don't joke, I'm ten minutes late.
No, what about this girl?
What a Girl?
Or Murat Düdenli ...
... you are not the man who will forget the meeting time.
The meeting, which ended an hour ago, is for a reason, you are generally in love.
Do not be silly.
Look, don't eat me, don't eat me for the love of God, Ruhi muhi is cheating on you.
I'm the master of this business, don't eat me from the master league.
There is no such thing Barlas.
Hay, I understand you ...
... your lord is trapped in your life now you can't feed yourself but don't eat me.
There's no such thing.
Look ...
... you don't care about me, you can do whatever you want, even if you ask me, keep doing the same.
Because I haven't seen you so energetic and full of life for a long time.
Here you are.
Thanks.
No, he treats me like a child, I'm at an age where I can take my own responsibility ...
... but sometimes he behaves so much that even my own anger feels like a whim after a while.
He changes the subject in such a way that he jumps, so that someone will fight you, then you yell at him, so why are you angry?
... I was so mad at you, who am I mad at?
Moron.
You like this Onur, I get it.
Is it too obvious?
Then.
Did you understand that you did not understand or did not understand?
Honey ...
... men don't understand anything you don't say, sometimes even when they say it.
So I think you talk to Onur.
No.
Don't be silly Bahar, I can't talk about it, so my hand goes around my feet.
Even now I am glowing red.
It wouldn't be bad if we had a few glasses or something and you would be relieved.
I mean ...
... I don't have much to drink ...
... I'm not so used to it.
Honey, there's nothing to get used to, we'll drink two glasses of something at the bottom.
I don't know sugar. If your husband brings flowers, there is something behind.
Where are the garden shears?
These draw the car, I'm pruning.
Wait, I put them on this thing.
Bahar give me one too.
It fell out of his pocket.
You like me?
I liked.
So it's not my style, but ...
... gift is a gift ...
I don't know, maybe I'll change.
Thank you.
Murat, I know you want to make amends ...
... I am also aware that you are trying to change something ...
... this is a great start, but ...
... don't expect high expectations because ... .
... some injuries ...
... it's taking too long to repair.
Yasemin ...
... I have to tell you ...
Father.
My dear.
My daughter.
The babies were awake.
When he woke up, okay, let's go right now.
The food will be ready for half an hour, according to him, an early completion game.
But we had just started.
But you will continue after lunch, come on.
Hello Mrs. Yasemin, hello, we are with Derin and I called him to inform him.
She drank a little, I don't want to send her home like this.
Just tell me this ... I
should worry ...
No, don't worry, don't worry, everything is under control.
I'll sober her up and put him in a cab, don't worry, okay?
No, no, no, no, his father can't see him, it bothers me that he makes up a lie. Don't send Murat to you before he's sober.
Ok, ok, don't worry, then good night.
Are you okay?
Come on, get up and let's go home.
Who were you talking to?
With Derin ...
... I was talking to Derin, they were trying to rehearse, they were trying to tell him that he was going to be late.
Are we not exaggerating this test topic a bit?
Why should I exaggerate my dear?
My Ece, lamb, come on, we wash your hands right before, mom.
But it is not dirty.
But look, I don't want to appeal. Go.
Come on girl come on baby come quick
Without running.
Do you think it's okay to stress so much?
So I don't like to get tired like that.
But if Murat depends on you, there is no difficulty.
I did not mean that.
I'm afraid she will be ill.
You are exaggerating, but why is she sick, is she not the first pianist?
Also, when it comes to this stress problem, I don't think it's that bad, so a little stress is quite motivating on the exam.
You were going to the company, what happened to report my limit?
I do not want to talk.
Wait a minute, wait a minute under your tongue.
Is there a girl thing?
Talk to me son, whatever you're going to talk about, don't trust that, is it convenient for your father?
Ok let me tell you then ...
I want my right in the company.
What does that mean?
I want to get into my job.
You say my job.
Exactly, won't they leave it to me in the end?
What are you talking about here father and son?
No mother ...
... my father wanted me to work in the company, he was telling her, he insisted, he insisted that he couldn't break it, right?
Well that's good news.
He will ask when and when your grandfather will be very happy.
Okay you know.
Don't leave one day tomorrow.
Don't worry, father.
I've run out of milk.
Well done.
Good Morning.
Where is Derin?
He left early.
Yasemin, I think this question of exams.
Let's not talk about it Murat right now.
Come on mom.
Stop, let me see.
Sick?
He started school.
What does that mean?
So there is a pandemic.
I'm fine mom.
Get up girl get up
Where?
I'll take you to school today.
Hurrah!
Come on, grab your bag, run, run, run.
What are you doing Murat?
As a precaution, I only measured.
Yasemin ...
... I think you should see a doctor.
So as a precaution.
My daughter.
Bahar.
Derin.
Good Morning.
Are you okay?
My head hurts so much, look, oh, I can't do it like this.
But I'll tell you something, I feel great.
Don't worry my dear, it was the same when I was your age, and then I'll give it to you and you'll come yourself.
Meanwhile, my mother called five hundred times and informed the police what should I do?
I informed him last night, by the way.
Really.
I'll see, my mother has come, I tell you, nothing will escape from you.
Who is it?
Dad, why did you come?
I called Derin, to find out.
What a good father you are, Murat Bey.
Yes, Bahar called.
Why is that?
When I couldn't reach Yasemin, I had to call Derinci, your father last night.
Murat Bey, I hope you didn't tell Yasemin Hanım that you know that Derin is here.
Say no ...
... I don't say.
Anyway ...
... this is our little secret.
Derin.
Good morning mom.
My God, where are you, my daughter?
I'm going to school, I'm fine, don't worry.
I told your father that he left early in the morning, okay?
Fine, thanks.
I will see.
What happened, my daughter told me that you are lying?
Isn't it a very bad thing to lie?
This is Murat's gift, papa. Always very polite the day we had a little disagreement ...
I think he was broken and seemed upset the next day he came in with this gift.
He is trying to fix us.
Sometimes we break up involuntarily ...
sometimes we don't get along ...
but trying to carry on ...
... if I step into myself ...
... what do you say?
For example, if I give a gift ...
... a shirt, a tie.
Yasemin.
Yes Dad.
Who is your husband?
Murat dad, don't you remember?
We need to talk.
I have you.
I'm kidding.
What does that mean, brother?
Either I'm kidding or how long haven't you been in the office.
Look at me, are you okay?
I'm fine, fine.
I am not Ruhi.
What happens? What happened?
I have to tell someone.
Are you ready?
Yes tell me.
There is a girl.
When did you get married?
Twenty years ago, you were, my mother was there.
Twenty years ...
... already has it.
Twenty years later ...
... people don't have much to share.
When I say a child ...
... there is no time to be alone.
How ...
... are you happy?
So ...
... maybe.
... Yes ...
... as you say ...
... after a while ...
... you're married.
Then.
Are you married, is there more?
But I knew I told you that I saw this girl somewhere.
Where did you see where you see for the love of God or is the world little brother?
Does Barlas know?
No, I just told you.
Brother, you know something like putting a bomb under your marriage, so you need to stop talking to this girl.
I'm happy Ruhi, what will happen now?
Not happy, you have to be married, brother, do you care, or will you make it clean like Barlas?
Then you will never be involved in such things.
What is the cleanliness of this job or how does Barlas clean this job? What are you saying?
Either look here or not, I don't care ...
... and you took the girl home.
My son, you will get in trouble, the girl is already playing with you.
I didn't know that I was going there in the morning or that no one had sin.
I'd go there in the morning ...
... purity, this is yours, purity, girl, it has made you an idiot, it has made you a fool.
Thank you or you have been a great help, what happened to what you said?
What happened, Ruhi? Listen to the sound of your heart, wherever your emotions take you.
Believe me, this is not the happiness you are feeling right now, that girl is not a solid shoe.
Look, Murat, if you lose Yasemin, you will be very unhappy, so don't tell me.
As a joke.
I am sorry.
So at least we agree on this.
Sorry, I shouldn't have insisted.
So this is a decision you made, it should have given you time.
I thought you were right, I'll take the drugs.
I was a little nervous when I said home school stress or something.
What happened at home?
What about my mom and dad?
... they fight all the time ...
... so they try not to be sure, but there is one thing, there is something like electric current in the house.
Why is that?
I do not know.
Another ...
Could there be another woman?
No, what more woman.
Therefore, they don't seem to get along with each other as if they have a problem.
Why did you ask it like that?
Why are you asking another woman?
Usually I don't know if I said it.
But of course it was illogical to think about yours, you're right.
Anyway, let's take these drugs.
No matter what we talk about, I don't have much time anymore, I'm working.
Are you playing with me, Bahar?
What game?
What was Derin doing in your house?
What is this?
The girl had problems, she asked me that my mind was a bit wrong, I didn't want to leave it that simple.
It's great to fool yourself all around.
Unfortunately, Muratcığım has nothing to do with you, sorry, but the world does not revolve around you.
What happened to him?
What do you care
If you are very curious, you may wonder if you want to learn.
I guess I'm not going to stand here and throw you off Derin.
Okay, sorry, you're saying it right.
I don't think so, right, don't tell me what's between you and Derin.
Apologize ...
maybe better if you pay attention to their behavior.
I'm thinking of talking to Yasemin.
What?
This.
Why is that?
I don't know, I know I don't like to tell those lies.
There is a big problem with Yasemin, right ...
... I have to talk about it and solve it, not with such lies.
I think such injustice is a great thing.
But I don't know how to tell Yasemin how to do it.
I do not know.
Listen here.
Long live Sister Bahar.
I installed a little peanut.
How was school today?
Look, the teacher gave me a dog sticker today, she actually wanted a cat.
But this is also very good.
Isn't your mother here?
Baharcığım we are in the kitchen.
Come on, let's say hello to your mother.
Excellent.
Good luck with.
Welcome Bahar.
I found it cute.
Let me help you, if you want, I'm not very good at a nice kitchen.
It is the greatest help to you to watch Ece right now.
I'll ask you at the last minute too, but is it possible you're staying a little late tonight?
Of course.
Are you looking at the earring?
Yes.
They were very beautiful.
It's a gift from Murat, I mean, I'm not very elegant, but ...
... what we do is very careful and I use it because it has a very special meaning.
I understand.
But it looks good.
Thanks.
Come on, Ececim.
Go to your room now, get your toys ready, I'm coming.
Let's see what this particular problem is.
Can I make something with a cup of tea or coffee?
Of course, we don't ask when you came, look at the cups.
Filiz Hanımcığım these are fine ...
... take out a china now and it would be great if you clean the silverware.
Sorry, I can't get the earrings that are so beautiful.
Thanks.
Is it a thank you for your birthday surprise?
Really ...
... How can I say to have more heart?
Romance is at its peak.
Actually, it can be answered by a romantic meal.
Marriage needs things like this from time to time.
Well, you know, you had the last fan of these songs.
What did he gain her heart?
No.
Let's say he stabbed me in the back.
Derincig.
My mom.
You look so beautiful.
I told everyone that I would play for us at night.
Mom, if I don't play tonight.
Why does that happen? Or everyone is looking forward to this and there is some practice before the exam.
Sight.
You are very beautiful but if you apply a little more mascara.
Well.
Go.
You are ready?
My angel, how beautiful you are, wait, let's use it.
Come here.
But we choose them.
They are at least dear, they never look, did you ever see the color of your outfit?
But now how nice it will be to wear these whites now.
Look now look.
Let's take a walk.
Ms. Yasemin, I'm sorry if I don't attend dinner, right?
Oh!, why?
So I'm on your side now in these clothes.
You are so Beautiful?
Your friends are full of people and now there is no need, please, Ms. Yasemin.
Don't be silly Bahar, you weren't that wild and go to Ece. Help me with the table.
Here you have.
Come on.
Yes ...
... our princess has also arrived.
Show me your clothes.
Let's go back.
Marvelous.
Goodnight everyone.
You know Bahar.
Yes yes, hello.
JeFiliz Hanimcığım, let's go to the table.
Yes, my Ruhi, my Sitareci, come like this.
Aydancıg ...
... with Barlas's son.
It's me.
Come on son.
Look at me ...
... are you messing with these export reports?
Don't be stupid, what does that mean?
No ...
... those values ​​can't be real.
Nothing to do. We are number one, we crush what we find.
Except you.
Is that so?
What did you put on him, Yasemin?
I put gooseberries instead of carrots, I have such a special recipe.
He is very wise.
Girls, you never see my nails.
Let me see.
Where did you do that?
Ay Derin, if you give it to Onur, the boy could not find something to eat.
Thanks.
I feel honored?
I'll take it too.
Dad, can I have it too?
Well, my exam was very good to celebrate.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
Thanks.
What proof was it?
Harmony.
My daughter put a little.
Thanks Dad.
How did you get used to home?
Yes, not bad.
Ece's bedtime has come, isn't it Ececim?
Will you deposit me today, Sister Bahar?
Of course.
With your permission.
Good night.
My daughter good night.
I know you don't sleep, baby.
I am aware of this little trick you did.
These coincidences ...
... but I should tell you something ...
... eventually you will be a victim of damage.
Trust me, I know that man very well.
What he wanted to say?
Well, let me take this from two doors.
A matter of taste, Aydan.
But isn't the engine of this more powerful?
Well, the normal sports model will be like this.
I can't use it to be able to escape.
That is why they are doing a young Aydancığç job, so that he can run away.
I won't stop crashing.
Actually, if you ask Onur, he knows better. Look, Onur, Aunt Aydan is consulting something.
Wait a minute dad.
Did you take the medicine?
I will start tomorrow.
Well, look, please don't interrupt.
You sit at the same table and eat ...
... what are you doing? Are you scared?
Did I call my friend here or what did I do to do?
Finish Murat, finish this job.
And they call the women gossip ...
... Barlas, shall we get up?
Let me kiss your mouth.
The fresh air that misunderstood Aydan was reduced.
I have learned that I will learn but I will not forget this word.
You burned, I tell you, you burned, baby, let's go.
Where are you, Yasemin?
You're going?
Thank you.
Come on, let's see your health.
Ruhicig.
Health to your hands.
See you, cheers to your feet.
Yo Derincig ...
... can you help me?
Dad, did you say you came to Bahar in the morning?
No girl.
So what is this?
I do not know.
You learn to go.
I'm over here.
Derin.
Interested in this drinking problem ...
should I be concerned?
Not.
My mom, of course, no.
Look, I had a bad day yesterday, so you know, school, exams or something ...
... but my harmony exam was really good, so I was relieved today.
Come sit down.
You don't have to do anything Derin, bother you, you don't have to do anything, okay?
Really.
You are very important to us.
Above all, I don't want you to feel bad about your health.
But, dear sacrifice your future for a small problem, a stress.
Look, life requires some struggle, a little effort ...
... so how can you be successful if you escape on the first difficulty?
Let me give you a secret ...
... these problems, these tensions and all of this is flying away.
But your success leads to a completely different life.
Mom ...
... the only reason I'm worried isn't my exams.
I know, I know, I know, look, you misunderstood what happened between your father and us that night.
Look, we just lifted something small that night.
But my foot joined and I fell.
Really ...
... we couldn't tell you in that anger, but the exact situation.
But now we have tied it to dessert.
We are good.
Look what it got me.
Peace gift.
Now I'm also thinking ...
... if I do something romantic.
Like what?
I do not know that.
Maybe we will organize a hotel on the weekend and make a reservation online.
All weekend?
Yes.
You didn't like it.
Great, great, great.
So let me make a great organization for you this time.
Well.
Good night mom.
Good night, lamb.
What are you doing here?
At home?
Or in the kitchen?
I'm drinking water.
Are you okay?
I'm thinking.
What?
All men came and spent my life ...
... not all mean my loved ones, so my mother's dear husbands ...
... my friends' spouses ...
... I always thought it was so smart you couldn't get caught up in these stupid traps with the kid.
I am not.
It was not necessary to speak big.
I'm drinking a glass of cold water on you, Murat.
what do you mean?
Speak clearly.
I'll talk to Yasemin ...
... great injustice to you ...
Why did you tell these lies?
I didn't want such a thing from you.
I didn't lie to you.
You are lying.
No.
I don't say.
When I said let me explain everything, I wanted to tell you that I was thinking about you, I was worried about you, I don't want to be unfair to you.
How did you give those earrings to Yasemin or how would you do such a thing?
I'm sorry ok.
Dad.
I came to this place, is there something? Can you look at Murat Bey?
Does something appear?
No, nothing, girl, can you take a look? Maybe I saw it wrong.
What happened, why did you get up?
Does your head hurt?
Yes a little, but it's over now.
We sleep, is it too late?
We slept.
OK.
Good night father.
Good night, my daughter.
Get better, Bahar.
Thanks good night.
Good night.
Let's see the princess in the right bed.
Won't you come?
No, but I'll wait at the door until you sleep.
Come on, good night, I'm here, I'll leave the door ajar, okay?
Ok, good night.
Good night.
What are you doing?
You have busted the Bahar Prize.
Enjoy your meal.
A glass of something would go so well now Derin.
Come on.
Keep.
What are you looking for?
Hotels.
A romantic weekend getaway with Onur Bey?
Of course, it's a lot of fun for my mom and dad, whether these peaceful gestures are flying in the air these days.
That is good.
So what are you going to pay with?
I promised I would do it with my mother's credit card organization, but there are so many hotels that I was officially bloated.
I'll help you.
Really?
Of course.
Let's prepare a big surprise for them.
Good Morning.
Where are the girls?
I woke up.
Oh did you wake up?
Good morning, let me be the victim of my life.
Derin comes, Bahar not when I woke up.
Well.
I'm leaving, girl, see you.
I will see.
Where are you?
This will be over.
What did I tell you?
Didn't I say to keep you away from me and the people around me?
What do we do now, what do we do now?
Now you will call those people and say that you will not work with them again.
Get it now?
Well.
Call.
I will listen out loud.
Hello.
Thank you Yasemin for everything ...
... I called to say that I can't work with you.
What happened? Is there a problem?
No, no problem, I received a new job offer and I have to prefer it better.
Sorry, so I'm happy for you, of course ...
... you know, what should we do with the weekly job?
Someday I will get income, thank you very much.
No problem, I'm going to ask something, right?
I'm fine, I'm fine, no problem.
OK see you.
Don't ever bring me here again.
Or do you understand that I don't just squeeze your throat?
Suburban pink.
What happened to this girl while she was still.
Youth is here and there.
17:00 Hotel Gama.
Oh stay the day Bahar.
Come on, those cheeses will run out.
Turn on the phone once or once.
I assumed you were here.
Did you take your medicine?
Yes, I drank now.
Sister.
Where are you, sister?
Wake up sister.
Sister awake.
Sister.
Room service came for sure.
Orange juice ...
Yasemin?
Well ...