I came.
You're late.
My work is long, my dear, the whole house smells of broccoli.
I made you meat with puree.
My dear wife was also thinking about her husband.
What was this now?
What was it?
I stayed like that, Yasemin, I wanted to kiss you, you left.
I didn't see it, honey.
That's all?
How much, what are you saying, Murat, I don't understand what you want, what are you saying?
I want my wife, Yasemin, my wife.
I have a job, can't you see Murat?
I see it, I see it fine, but there is a problem.
You can't see that you haven't looked me in the face since I came here. Yasemin.
What do you want, Murat, am I cooking? You can see?
Mrs. Filiz couldn't come, I cleaned all the windows in the house, then Ece came, there was a fever at school ...
1 hour I tried to lower her fever an hour later ...
I got deep, I want broccoli.
Ece can't eat broccoli, he doesn't eat potatoes like Derin Ece loves.
You don't like French fries the way Ece likes meat ...
he doesn't mash how you want, Murat cooked for all of you and all of this ..
If I can't finish in half an hour, you'll start telling you.
Look, I burned my finger, meanwhile my back hurt, but did I have a cold or will you stop and understand?
I didn't even have a minute and if I couldn't entertain you in all of this.
Sorry, Murat, don't look at my fault.
It's over, I didn't ask you to entertain me, Yasemin, I didn't ask you for anything.
But you are right, I have the irregularity, because when you are in this state I came to help you.
I'm trying to support you, I'm trying to hold you, my gratitude to you.
I'm trying to prove that I'm Yasemin, I'm trying to love you.
But you are right God, damn it, Yasemin, may Allah be my misery.
So, even in this case, I can't believe there is Murat fad, you do.
What will happen? Will everything be corrected? Come on, let's hug, okay, okay, or are we happy?
We are happy, we are happy.
Come here, mommy, a little like your fever's down.
Hurrah!
But it can reappear, so what are we not doing?
We don't jump.
We don't jump, yeah mom.
So can I go to school?
36.6 very good, lamb.
School ...
One more day but I need a lot of help at home, you see that they still wake up.
I wake up.
Let's go then my lamb, without running.
Where did a fairy come from in the morning?
Heaven.
The air fairy came here or waited, let me look at that fairy, let me look good then; Let me kiss ...
I'm better.
Then I can kiss one more time, this bed is very comfortable, after that I will sleep here.
No father.
Why not?
You did not have your feet come out.
But it is very airy, very beautiful. There will be a lot of fairy air. Go.
1, 2, 3 flew flew flew flew flew.
Derin. You have to get up, my dear lamb.
My mom says I'm going to sleep in the afternoon.
Okay, so you can study the exam, let's see laziness. There is very little left for the exam.
Thanks mom or if you don't remind me of the morning and morning exam.
Actually it will happen, but my mother who says "you are not" eating the meat of my head to go to work?
How's it going?
It's almost finished.
Your father will love this surprise, you know?
Let's see 15 minutes or that breakfast will be ready, let's see.
He flew, he flew, he flew, my daughter flew.
Ece, Ece.
Mom, I'm flying.
Look Yasemin.
Murat, that's enough.
My daughter, did you wash your face, darling, are we going to run?
Please don't yell at me next to the kids again.
Murat, Ece ill; Ece has a problem with his heart, okay ...
If you act on this situation, I don't have to yell.
I know I am aware that my daughter is ill, Yasemin, my daughter too ...
... but we can't end like this.
However, I can make him sicker.
But I can not provide, I am a father, I can not put my son?
For this, you must first be aware of the situation.
What situation.
This situation also requires some responsibility, these are the things that Murat does not like.
Do you know what Yasemin's real pain is?
What?
You feed on this, yes, you feed on this disease.
I didn't hear anything stupid, stupid in my life.
Look very smart, very smart Yasemin looks at Ece playing with these babies and you are playing with Ece ..
The disease is also an excuse because it does not tolerate that he separates from you and is independent.
Because you do not tolerate anything that is out of your control.
Nothing nothing. Ece he's sick of nothing, nothing, nothing, you.
Breakfast is ready for 15 minutes and is announced to those who want to eat their hot bread.
Damn.
Stay, let's see, the young people are in the hands of cotton, wake up, today I am going to meet a gentleman.
Take a cab and check it out.
Bahar, the man hasn't called you in years.
Does your father know?
Exactly, dear. Come on, let me see, cotton hands. Go Go.
My daughter is going like this, does the man not even know?
What I am going to do? I'll send a letter from the front.
My daughter put your head on the man, what you know is your father.
Look what you know, look what you see, you see the photo; my dad in this photo ..
Next to me is my mother, and me her belly.
Do you understand me, this man is my father?
Look, this man is my father, this man will find me today.
Take it, I'll tell you how many times or not I want a tablet phone on this breakfast table.
Mom, how much fun did you have? I wish it was a great celebration.
No, it was not a fun party as it appeared in the photos.
Our party will be more fun, isn't it mom?
Yes, mom, but we are not breaking the surprise.
What surprise is that?
Nothing.
Good morning my daughter.
Good morning Dad.
I think I am faced with a treacherous conspiracy of three women.
Could be.
Thanks .
Nice don't know who drew.
Sitare put it.
Can you send me this dear?
You can get it from its own page.
I said deep now, I don't want this, I don't want a laptop.
Mom, we were looking.
My daughter says that your mother is right, the rule is my daughter, everything has a correct time ...
I'm going for half an hour, my daughter, I'll leave you if you want.
Ok dad.
Quick recovery, do I have a meeting?
OK Daddy.
I told you to give your ring to Murat or to give it to your ring.
Yasemin falls just off my finger, you're weakened, I guess they should catch her.
Not because of that, there is no need to shrink from the air, it gets boring in hot weather ...
I'll take it and it will disappear here now.
Ağa I dropped a girl, there are Turkish delight.
Barlas, brother, let me know that one day you will be in very bad trouble.
No, Ağa, nothing will happen to you.
Of course, your situation is different, it is normal that the diapers do not have diapers.
I say how it goes, I say the traditional surprise birthday preparations.
Don't ask, Barlas, the whispers started behind me, a whisper at home and I'm going to go crazy.
I swear I'm overwhelmed.
Well, you say I got stuck, tell me Yasemin, if we are not surprised this year, what about the boss?
He passed, that's his thing, Barlas, don't you know Yasemin?
Made him a joy for life, I'm afraid he will destroy himself every year, regret.
Women have toys Ağa she likes how Antin Kuntin works.
Look what I'll say, when the meeting is over, I run away. You accompany me today, then whatever language you want from me.
What about the Barlas reports?
You say the reports, the girl said: «Come on», says Barlas, isn't it said that she will come now?
I will say that you do not understand anything of such situations, of course, the hungry does not understand.
Yours is always the same menu, I always say you have to cry, you are a handsome man ...
You need to learn to fish.
What was this fish?
Daddy client, he told Murat. Connecting customers is like fishing.
Hey, don't believe.
Come easy, I was going to meet with Barlas Pusat.
Sure, did you have a date?
It was fine, but there was no meeting ...
Unfortunately.
But I have to find myself.
So what should I say?
Also for the blind of your hand.
Ercan.
Forgiveness.
Oh sorry, I think he seemed like a friend to me.
Well, we compare it to Kıvanç Tatlıtuğ or something like that.
You are working here.
Yes.
It was cool, by the way, how cool a card is or was it, I always wondered ...
Can I do it once, how was it done?
That's.
It's amazing, can you do it again or stop it this time?
It always seemed strange to me.
It actually has a very easy mechanism.
By the way, do you know Barlas Bey?
What happened to the export reports for the last three years, Barlas?
I don't know, Murat was the last to look, dad.
Why is that?
When I was dealing with stocks, I transferred Murat to that business so he wouldn't be delayed.
Don't worry, I'm getting ready.
Fine fine fine if you mind
Dad, if you have nothing to say to me, I will not go out ...
Leave it at that, how is Sitare?
Good dad is great, he misses you, of course, because you are staying in a country house.
Barlas, I say what we are going to do Sitare because you are working hard on my site.
Will these reports be ready for tomorrow now, Murat?
We can do it.
Well.
Dad, if you have nothing to say to me, I will go to a client I have to go to.
You need to catch new fish.
Why isn't this Honor coming to you, isn't it over yet, or is school over?
Months have passed from America.
You're right, I'm telling you dad, but it looks good on me ...
It's his job, he'll be the boss of this place.
You're right, I'm talking again daddy, I try to convince.
Speak up, don't confront me with these problems, or everyone will be heartbroken.
Ok dad I got it, then I went out, anyway I let the report work easily.
What are we going to do and what are we not going to do? Is there nothing for you? And it works because he works hard.
Getting ready, don't worry, it will be ready tomorrow.
Let me tell you, Murat, I trust you, son, look at the whole initiative.
I'll be out soon, is there anything you can tell me?
No, just don't worry, I'll prepare everything.
Well okay, easy.
If your phone.
They closed the reports on me again, I'll come late at night, don't wait for dinner.
Ok honey.
Does anyone ask?
You have a guest inside.
Who?
Honestly, I don't know, Barlas Bey was a lady.
I don't know, Barlas Bey, what exactly do you do in this company?
I tried to avoid it, but I sat down.
Sit down.
Finally welcome.
When you say welcome, we are in my office; I'll essentially say welcome, we meet somewhere ...
I think I'd remember if we met from the ground.
True, but I'm not a foreigner, dear, don't be afraid of Ümraniye.
We can also say that the daughter of Semos, the girl of Sema.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry, I should say something; dad?
How is your mother?
Well.
Are you still doing it?
What work?
Prostitute.
You do it when you leave him out with the boy like a bastard, what do you do?
I know this game.
Is that so?
Can you tell me?
Let me explain, your mother sent you here.
No, now I can move on my own, I grew up, I became a big girl.
However, these tricks are a little out of the year 2020, you have to be a little more creative.
Your mother sent you here.
Let.
What happened, you were so cool.
I said let it go
Scream and call and don't break my irritation, now go back to that hole no matter which hole you came from.
Otherwise, I will burn you and your mother.
What the hell are you looking at?
The number you are calling is not used.
You don't say that Yasemin is searching, but she brings water from a thousand streams, Ruhi.
My brother will not be a messenger, said Yasemin, shake his mouth and I will check; now meat or fish.
What should I know when I have such a problem?
Look at me, Yasemin won't know I'm asking this question like that, right?
Or the same thing every year is Ruhi the same thing every year my brother ..
Is this a surprise, or are you a maniac or are you trying to drive me crazy?
The meat is not bad, but I think it can be fish.
God what is this, I did not tell you moment.
Come on, make up your mind bro.
Everything will happen, everything will be spiritual.
But which?
Spiritual. I'll call you later, bro, it's okay or something important.
I am asking a simple question, which one?
It doesn't matter if you choose the spirit, I'll call you, Ruhi.
Meat is not bad meat, okay, I know what if it's fish?
Mr. Murat.
Then please.
Stop, please.
What should I not do?
Don't move, I'll come to you slowly.
Why are you a cop or something?
No I'm not a cop, but will you keep jumping?
Look what you have experienced is not a problem, suicide is not a solution.
Turns out, you mean it because of the shoes, but don't be afraid.
I won't kill myself, my shoes just fell off.
Are you sure?
Absolutely, even let me tell you this. If I found my father here today ...
If he makes fun of me, I still don't throw myself, why am I going to throw myself?
Oh, anyway, it doesn't matter.
Are you afraid of heights?
Let's not say that, let's say I don't feel safe. You are obviously not afraid.
No, I am not afraid, I have my shoes back with my prince.
Yes.
Thank you, by the way, you two are excellent.
I mean, if I throw myself, you'll catch me.
Probably.
Don't be afraid, don't worry, I won't kill myself, at least not today.
Okay, okay, will you come back for me a little, please?
If you're not going to jump, what are you doing here?
Ask a question, why?
Why?
That is why I am treating my inferiority complex.
How?
Sight.
I'm really scared, don't do it.
Look at these people, they are smaller, the higher you go, the smaller they are.
Stupid problems, both themselves and their created ones, fall apart.
Ay Şeker, my doctor's job. I went back five years in five minutes.
What did you say?
Coffee, stop, I'll tell you too.
Let me see.
It seems there is no difference when I look.
Ay Yasemin, you do not understand these works, look alive, his skin officially glowed.
It seems a bit bloated to me.
As it is the first day, it lasts a few days.
We're making an appointment for me right away, Sitare.
That job is my sweet, come on, don't worry about the date.
Let Yasemin do it too, her skin glows, vitamin, this is nothing ...
Let's get botox there and there, they will be very beautiful balls, very pretty.
There is no need, I am so good, I am peaceful with my age, wrinkle.
Honey, the important thing is that you don't like it. Whether your husband likes it or not, they don't like it, of course.
It is true, the young woman is full, they give her the husband.
Aa, I don't think Murat likes it very much.
Yasemin says that men love naturally but for some reason they always go for hormones.
There is no sugar, these are love events, but if they have those sweets, I love them.
Where do they come from?
Bag.
Take it.
You say that coffee is good for all kinds of breakdowns.
Yes, it is better to go up the mountain and to the roof when you feel depressed.
What am I supposed to do?
For example, the wind that disperses your hair is probably.
There is also that, but more than anything the feeling of escape.
So let's call me freedom, in short, so that no one can touch me here.
Freedom, as I know, is unlikely in this world, so it doesn't matter how free you want to be.
True, how could anyone know who worked in the possession of a three-cent salary day and night?
Well, what kind of freedom does this freedom look at?
Freedom, freedom, that's it, look at this ...
Freedom to fly like this kite, no one can reach it, looking from the sky.
Think about it, what would you feel when you fly a kite?
I don't know, how would I feel? Have I never made a kite?
What, in childhood? Are you honestly a person who doesn't fly a kite?
You need an ultimate kite, add it to your to-do list before you die.
Look, I cannot explain this feeling to you, it is such a thing, it is experienced as soon as it is told.
Can I give you another little secret?
I do not receive three cents of salary, I am one of the bosses of this place.
Wow, the second boss I met today was fine.
Actually, your songwriting is really great, but it didn't work, it doesn't suit my voice, it's strident.
If I transpose, even though all the air in the song will disappear, I can't change it.
What am I going to do now?
I wanted to help, but unfortunately, I need to catch up with the class now, and shall we talk?
OK thank you.
Onur, what is it, what are you doing?
Derin, what happened, why is your voice bad?
I'm in big trouble, I don't know what to do with this song.
Are you at school?
Yes, and I'm about to freak out.
Okay, calm down, we'll solve the problem, I'm coming.
Were you really in business?
I said I'm coming.
OK thank you.
What did you do with my candy birthday organization? Are you working with the same company again?
They made me very sad last year.
I say I'll handle it on my own this year.
Oh, you're crazy, how will you catch up?
Let me give you the number of my company, call and speak, my sweet is clear.
Are you saying that, is it a great idea at the same time ...?
No, how Murat wants cake now, what color do you want on the tablecloths?
Love is such, what are you doing, in the night of sleep, you ask the man what to eat, what to drink?
Thanks to Ruhi.
What did you do with the gift business? Did you call Murat's mouth?
No, but I know what to do. I found a very romantic idea.
What is it?
Now there is a poem that Murat wrote to me, twenty years ago, when we met.
Derin composed in song, he will play at the party, he found a friend from school, he works.
What's so romantic about this?
Isn't it romantic?
It's not romance, not passionate sugar, I need a little passion.
That's right, you have to think of something for the night. What a fiery thing.
After all, we're not sixteen, are we?
Well.
Terrible, I have to take a break more often.
I think you are not only tired, but also sad, what happened?
Nothing happened.
It's true, I feel more like mine, yours is a bit more like more unhappiness.
As if there is a deep void in your heart, they are covered everywhere with dark clouds.
There is no such thing, where do you get it from?
It is not so important that you lie to me, you are lying to yourself, it is a little bad.
I'm not unhappy, where do you get it from?
So you are an unhappy guy, so we say boring.
So much.
How could you not breathe through those dark clouds?
But you cannot realize that your soul is withdrawn.
I realized when you said it.
Well, well, this is something too.
Well, is there a cure for this, so can I recover?
Actually there is, but can you do it a bit?
You underestimate me, look, I brought your shoes from below and almost with you, despite everything ...
I'm sitting here, don't underestimate me.
That's right, you're right, then let's plan.
Okay, let's go.
If we forget everything.
What?
Past future. If we don't think anything, just feel the moment in which we live,
If we go out the moment we breathe, let us flow. Let's see what happens to us.
At this time?
It's ridiculous to be the boss if we can't go out anytime you want.
You're right, you're right, let's go out.
I think it's time to get rid of this damn place.
The song is fine, I wrote it, but nobody can sing or maybe I have the problem, I couldn't do it.
Sure it can be.
What a pity.
Of course I'm kidding, I'm sure you did a great songwriting, ..
As for the say part, stop, we thought about it, we'll find someone, of course.
What is born before the day comes, right?
Also that girl will regret doing this, when you become a famous songwriter in the future ...
Since she lost the opportunity to work with you, she will hit her head from wall to wall.
Thank you, the problem is not that important when you are here.
It's not because you've been eating me in vain, since you've been trying to take advantage of me until now ...
You're going to buy me coffee because it's not the coffee I drink.
Well, soon we have a good place, let's go there.
Well okay.
Everything should be perfect, I do not tolerate the slightest mistake.
Don't worry, I'm sure she'll please you like Ms. Sitare.
The moon eased, I was so tired of running.
Did you pick something from the catalog for decorations, Mrs. Yasemin?
Your options are vast but they are still items that I couldn't decide.
Let me help you, how do you think this is?
This will not happen, Murat hates blue, please take this to your notes please.
I think it is beautiful.
I don't like blue at all.
So does blue know about this?
I think it looks good on him.
Well, let's drink.
How much, sister?
Fifty pounds.
Thanks.
Well, do you want to have fun or not?
I want to, I'm not used to vacations in the middle of the day.
Wow well it was an honor to have a half day vacation with me.
Thanks to you too.
Let out.
What?
Before you can be free, you must get rid of your handcuffs because ...
everything that chains you to the imperative, everything.
So how do I learn time?
One, this will stay with me, but don't worry, I'll give it back to you.
Well.
Now you can learn the weather by looking at the sun.
And you haven't looked at it in a long time, get a bonus from me.
Take it, wafers are good for depression.
The bottomless pit in this bag is blessed.
But I told you, I love being a nomad.
When I'm so impressed, I like to go where I want to, do the things I want to do.
And to eat wafers contrary to this point of view, you are not aware, but ...
We are looking at the most expensive vision in the world right now.
Take it with courtesy.
You say this view will suit wafers, right?
It fits everything, so you can think like a miracle.
Let's see.
What happened? Didn't you eat the wafers when you were a kid?
Look, this is bad.
What are you doing?
If you don't take advantage of the opportunities that are offered to you in life, it will be taken away.
Then.
So they eat the goods of not eating.
Well.
It's okay. Thanks.
Why, because I bought the wafer?
No, I have been in this city for forty-five years and I have never seen this face.
That is good.
Istanbul was truly the most beautiful city in the world, thank you.
Thanks.
Can I look at the clock now?
What happened now?
Come on, let me drop you at home, there's work tomorrow.
Okay, accept, but finish your wafer first.
Take it, my phone number is; you call when you need it.
Yes, or, yes what, do you have two names?
So you don't know him, SOS is help. You can think of it as a cry for help.
Well.
Call when I die of boredom.
There is much more beauty to see in this city.
Won't you say your name?
I won't say, if you call, you learn, if you don't call, it doesn't matter anyway.
If you can't take it, why are you stumbling? And that?
Let's be.
Bahar.
Mom, what happened to you?
My daughter.
Come on in, damn it, or Veysel don't repeat, okay, calm down, sit down and let me look at you, stop.
Veysel, his hands are broken, he's purple.
Mom, how do you give permission or do you keep doing this, how?
Let's see what time it is, boy.
Yes.
I said what time.
19:00.
That means you are in the air.
You left the night happy because I was smiling like a baked head.
They say there is a place to go, so it means you have to go.
When you look at it, it is obvious that you are not going to work.
How is that?
Time, as precious as time, now does not want people to pass ...
you cannot step on your feet, nor can you step on. So what should we do in this situation, our boy?
I do not know.
You need to drink coffee.
You need to drink coffee, sit and think, come and sit down.
Thanks.
I set it on fire, I was waiting for his share, it is not possible to have coffee alone. The smallest team is for two.
So what would happen if it didn't come?
It will be difficult for you to decide the answer, since you are always looking for it.
Now, if we doubt your decision, I will pour the coffee into the cup.
Hop, it will happen, but not your wish.
Enjoy your meal.
It looked really good, you're actually telling the truth.
It's about being in the limel, so here I am like a limbo in hand.
The idea of ​​going home is really like hell.
So when you say come, love is such people.
The man is the son of Adam that you call, he seeks heaven on earth but does not know that he is looking for himself.
The sky is not where you find it, but where it is located, maybe you know ...
One day, Harun Reşit is so cold in the forest that Behlül asks Dana for a fire and says "Go away!"
Bring fire, Behlül Dana is a married man, he goes to hell but remains empty ... He
says, there was no fire in hell, everyone would take fire there ...
Maybe this is your account, how about our boy?
I am doing my best.
Sure it is, but the story is not over yet.
When Harun Reşit can't find fire in hell, Behlül tells Dana and enters paradise, let's see if there is one.
Behlül Dana goes to heaven and her hand becomes empty again, neither does it say in heaven or fire ...
yes, sir, yes, but they don't give it to everyone, you and me ..
Harun Reşit doesn't understand, he asks ; why is that?
Lord says, do not give fire to those who are not willing to burn in the fire.
There is no fire for you, our boy, who looks at the fire, who does not dare to burn in the fire.
It stands just like you, somewhere in between, no burning, no burning, you are not ready to burn ..
You cannot go to hell, you are not ready to burn, you cannot go to heaven.
Nice, I think I found paradise in love and living hell. You looked at what you thought was hell.
Another kingdom you call heaven, I mean human beings. I can't get up without falling down, this is an exam ...
Let no one know that they are innocent without being proven, no one is innocent of a love that has not been proven.
Murat, don't touch me.
Yasemin, you didn't miss me too, why is it Yasemin?
Why do you think?
I am sorry.
There's no need.
I could come early last night, sorry.
It is not necessary, I do not want your apology, it is not necessary.
Do you hate me so much?
I have a job, I'll make breakfast, will you?
Wouldn't you wait for breakfast?
I can not wait.
Let's make love hungry immediately, what happens without breakfast, children will not starve.
Nonsense.
After we love each other, what time and place matter, my dear if we love each other.
It exists for me, everything has a place and a time, this is the rule of life.
If I was early last night, would everything be in line with your rules?
Maybe I don't know, but we'll never know because of you.
This is not a matter of last night or today, but you know it.
Ece has been like this since he was born, I'm sure it would have been an excuse if I was early last night.
Can't you see, can't you stand to touch me?
I can't forgive you inside of me, okay, okay, did you want to hear this?
I'm struggling, struggling but not happening, I'll change my clothes now ...
then I have to make breakfast.
Breakfast is important, breakfast is very important.
Good morning darling.
Good morning mom, isn't there grandpa?
He would stay at the farm.
What diet are you doing this time?
I think of death.
Come on, put some more.
Thanks love.
Mom, what happened to your lips?
Nothing major, it will take a few days because of the procedure I had yesterday, the doctor said, but it's not a big deal.
Come on mom, you're already beautiful, you don't need needles, botox ...
You're in vain, doctor, doctor.
Yes, you are right, honey.
I'm beautiful but it's okay to be a little more beautiful, right?
My father hadn't woken up yet?
He arrived late at night, his work was a bit long.
Of course, he is working hard these days.
Good morning, the most beautiful woman in the world.
Good Morning.
What's up, lion?
Onur, Onur.
Mister.
I'm calling you, you don't listen, baby, what happened?
Nothing happened.
This woman is not an old friend either, she is older than me.
Stop, don't turn around, don't look.
Aa comes to our Ömer Bey for a vitamin needle. What did he do?
Stretched it out, look.
Let's be.
Look, it's not one, it's not two, what do you expect me to do?
I don't know, Bahar.
I don't know what it means, I don't know what it means. You give it to the court is gone.
I am tired, believe me, I am tired, may Allah dispose of my life now.
Look at the maniac, do not talk foolishly, you put the kick, you collect your mind and you come to me ...
I will take care of you, we are enough for each other, we do not need anyone.
How do we do that in our muscles?
It would be such a thing.
After the beating, it becomes like cotton, it does.
His torment does not end, of course. You are right, of course, I will stay in this man's days.
Oh, you already knew.
Semos, there is no other man in your care Veysel, okay, we will move the world with you.
We, right?
We also make a joke.
Come on, let's have a hot soup and let me get you a cup of tea.
Well.
What are you laughing at, tell me I'm laughing?
You tied it up to the high school teacher again.
I think it would be useful for me to start working in the company.
Look, you're working hard, maybe it'll help you.
Don't worry, son, look at your details and your book.
Why were you saying the other day that the documents were drowned and you couldn't go home?
It is not necessary, there is no position for you in the company, boy.
Are you making this decision?
Yes, because I put the money in your pocket. Two ... I'm your father, you're not mine.
Dad, you look more like eighteen teenagers right now.
Your only strength is money. You're trying to scare me with this, I don't need this, but if you lose your money ...
you will be nothing, while the true power of man is family, right?
Oh, what is the trip in the morning and in the morning, what kind of attitude is this, if you finish, I will be late for work?
Maybe you need to lose everything to understand the value of family, what do you say, dad?
Bahar, can we talk?
Mr. Onur, could you call me? Last time it hung in my face.
I don't have brothers like you, my father doesn't do anything like that, what happened?
Please listen to me, okay, I didn't take you seriously at first, but decided to give you a chance.
God, what is it, you fell on your head or something. What happened suddenly you decided to believe me.
You can say it, Bahar, I'll give you the chance of a lifetime.
Tell me what that opportunity is and I will know.
Wait for news from me, find me where I will write you the place and time today, you will learn ...
I have a great plan, I think you are right, it is time for my father to pay the price for what he did.
This is great news, a great burden has been lifted and we will see you, thank you.
What was the burden of this?
Is my father away?
Is the output about the song?
Yes, my friend from school yesterday stopped singing the song.
I was saying we were screwed, but Onur's friend will sing the song.
The girl is called Bahar, and I will go to see her because of her voice.
This is wonderful, great news, and yesterday I signed up with the Sitare organizing company.
We will celebrate for a long time.
Or everyone will be fascinated.
I'll go on stage too, sing with the singing sister.
You are going to give us a special concert.
Derin, I don't understand these musical works, but if you want, let me talk to the girl about money.
It would be great or I don't understand money.
Let me go today, speak first, then speak after you speak.
Be careful not to press fast, fast, don't you take with your hand, Derin take your sister?
Come on, okay, okay, you should pay attention to your hand before the test.
Girl are you leaving?
I have a small job, Semos.
You're not too late, are you?
- Do I ever stay, girl? Don't worry, I'm with you as soon as I'm done. - Well.
You go to sleep, rest now.
Now you will sing your normal song at the party and do your job as if nothing happened after the song.
First I will introduce you to my mother and then I will explode the bomb, look, my grandfather and my mother ... will
you be there when you tell the situation besides them ...
Will everyone hug me and suddenly praise me?
At least we will put an end to my father's deception, the facts will have been revealed.
What happened?
I do not understand.
I was running after him trying to tell you ...
I went to the gym to get closer, I went to the gym and did the abdominal muscle ...
And you have not believed me for months, then you open the phone one morning and you tell me that you will have a winged arm .
I also ask what happened naturally.
Whatever happens, are you with me or not? Tell me.
I don't know, if you are sincere when you say that you are with me ... be sure ...
What did Sema do to his wife?
No, the wife is in the middle, brother, they have moved, they say nobody knows.
You will find, I give you tons of money, no matter what hole it enters.
It looks very good, if it says come, if it says love, come, I will come to your love.
I will die if you say die, die for your love.
You even did a duet.
You probably forgot that Master Muhammer left my classroom as soon as he heard my voice.
I think it was unfair.
Which Muammer, by the way, is your left key Muammer?
What are you up to? He called me crows or something. Do not worry about it.
Are you in our school? It was awesome. Why haven't I seen you before?
I haven't been visiting for two years, so there wasn't much time for extras; if you just entered.
Yeah, never mind, they don't teach anything properly anyway, and I say if I quit.
Are you serious why?
Yes.
Oh dear, don't rush, maybe I'll go back to school ...
Is it okay if I already have a friend?
So you are thinking of going back.
So there is a little money problem that I have to deal with, even if I solve it, I will even do it to the doctor.
How beautiful, my dear, don't get bored then.
Super, your composition, I help you at that moment ..
We read the left key of Muhammer.
Yes, Yasemin.
Murat, we left the doctor, Ece's test results are fine, we're comfortable for now ...
So I wanted to let you know.
Oh, I'm so happy, okay, let's celebrate, let's go to dinner together.
Nerd. Let's not break Ece's sleep pattern now, let's do it some other time.
You are two steps away.
Let's go to my father.
We talk, we look, we look at the flowers.
Ece wants too, look, I'll come.
No, don't do it now, don't insist today.
You're punishing me, is it morning Yasemin?
Don't be silly Murat, what does he have to do?
How and what has to do, I know you, you get to the bottom ...
But I'm mad at you, you say I don't want to be side by side, Yasemin ...
You're taking revenge on me, don't do it.
No, I just wanted to tell you that I called him.
Of course, if you say so.
Now we have a lot of work and I will not interrupt the program.
Okay Yasemin, okay.
Let's go with daddy, mommy.
We can't go, honey, your father has a lot of work to do.
My handsome partner, I should take it, where did you put the reports?
Sorry, I couldn't prepare it yet.
What happened to my workaholic Murat, what did you do?
What do you have to do, brother? Can't I breathe, brother?
Alright mate, we're not used to it now, so I asked him, are you okay, huh?
I'm a little tired, Barlas.
Brother, what are you sitting on? Get up, go home, get up at your home.
Look at the reports later, rest at home; what will you do here.
I'm at the company, I'm looking at work, don't worry about that health, you need us, my handsome brother.
Thanks.
Bahar is cute, where do you meet?
From there, a friend of a friend actually called our organization, but then it didn't happen.
Fortunately it was our job.
I'm so glad you got along, why did you mention dropping out of school?
So I don't know, I'm not sure I want to play the piano.
So it seems that being a pianist in this country is too much.
Yes, I heard your lies, Mrs. Now tell me what really happened.
Because something very specific has happened, you are not telling me.
I don't know if this is a problem, but my hands have been numb for a while.
Your hand is numb, did you tell your mother?
No, my mother is broke, panic attack environment at home or something.
You went to the doctor?
Stop now, the doctor is not an important thing, and I am so tired of the exams.
Maybe that's why.
Don't be silly, let's take a look, we won't tell your mother.
Ok, let me rest a bit, if it doesn't go away, we'll go.
Please.
Okay, but I'm on follow-up.
Semoş Semoş Semoş, look what I bought you, I even found a pumpkin, that Veysel, also a candle for you.
Where are you, let's be?
Veysel brother came, he begged a lot, we will return to the house that he will not do it again.
Ah, I know Semos, why did you go to that shove again? I would protect you, why did you leave me again?
Sal, the idiot woman, she likes to hit or beloved, girl you, beloved, you deserve it ...
Insert them in the bottom of the boy, break his nose. You are right, I am a greeting.
Thank you very much, Mrs. Filiz.
Wait, let's see, wash your hands and then look at your room.
But I'll go out into the garden.
Ece, dear, please, whatever I say you will do, don't bother me.
Don't make me sad, Mom, don't make me sad.
Let's do this, grab the new crayons, paint well behaved.
We will play runner.
No mother, no Ece, no, you know.
No, the doctor said no, I always paint, I always play with the baby, I want to run.
But Ece'ci ...
You do n't allow anything, mother, you always say well.
Be nice and be mad at you, don't come to my room. It is forbidden for you.
Here you are.
They left you a package, Murat Bey.
God, what is this?
I don't know, they said it was SOS. I think the company.
What did they say?
SOS.
Well.
You can fly this yourself if you want, you can fly with me on Caddebostan beach at 4 o'clock.
But definitely fly, don't miss your childhood.
You are punishing me well, Yasemin, for what happened in the morning, don't make me sad, mother, don't make me sad.
Ms. Yasemin, did something happen or did you cut yourself?
I'm fine, Filiz, I'm going to look at Ece, can you continue?
Yes.
Ece is mad at me, how can I make it up to my daughter?
But I never wanted to upset him, I love him so much.
His name is not Feride, this is Feride.
Excuse me, should we make amends?
My Feride, I thought something like this. I actually have a great idea to make amends, should I say?
I'm saying it's okay, now I'm saying let's make a great meal.
Let's celebrate the good news from your uncle doctor.
I also say, let's let Ece let her cook.
Don't break the eggs.
Of course, you can knead. What do you say, will Feride accept?
Peace is then.
Shall we make amends, my Ece, my Ece?
My dad likes it too, right mom?
Of course he will like it, will he ever like it from your hands? Come hug me here come here?
We go faster, you have to take the wind back, just like that.
Is that so?
A) Yes.
It was.
How?
So beautiful.
I did it.
This is a wonderful thing, thank you.
I told you, there is still a lot to do.
What?
I will tell you sometime.
Why haven't I done this before, what?
Excellent.
What are you doing, why did you do it?
I released it.
Gone.
I know, the life lesson is one. You can't keep everything forever.
Come on, what are we going to do now?
We also release other kites.
Okay, let's go.
I did the dishes, you know, sister?
You will be the chef with this game. Little mouse, my father will love it too.
Cheers girls in your hands, the dishes have been wonderful.
Should we see a movie after dinner, did Onur suggest a very nice movie?
We will see that.
Long live the food from the movie.
Long live the celebrations.
Olley.
Thanks.
At least I know what it's for this time.
Don't you want to enter?
I can not come.
Why, I thought you liked it?
That's why I can't go, I don't want to be unfair to you.
It is unfair, how good you are, how naive you are, you are a very sweet person.
There aren't many of you married ones.
Okay, I agree, let's not rush.
Hey, hey, what's your name?
You would learn if you called me next time.
Dad, my dad came.
Without running.
My daughter.
Hello, what happened, what happened to God?
Look, I did the dishes.
Great, there's a surprise for you here.
Kite.
Dad, you bought a kite.
Darling yeah do you like it girl?
It's mine?
Of course, let's get one of you.
Comet Comet Comet, hooray.
Slow down, what is this?
Comet dear, we will fly together, come on you come too.
Girls, go fill in the deficiencies of the table, I'll talk to your father.
Comet, come on now.
But mom.
I was so hungry, first kiss and cheek. Who is this mouse?
Murat, you're crazy, what do you want with getting a kite for Ece, do you want to attack?
You said the doctor said it was fine.
The doctor said it was good, but did not say it was completely healthy.
The doctor's word or yours?
I am responsible for the child, not the doctor. I know what I'm doing.
Of course you know what you are doing, Yasemin, you do the best of everything, you know the best of everything ...
The blade cannot move without being aware of you, it does not move because if it does move ...
Yasemin, tell it why you are a controller.
Am I a controller, Murat? I am trying to protect ourselves.
You are not protecting us, you are strangling us all. What's going on?
Let go a little, much less relax, something is not under your control, Yasemin ..
A kite above six, you magnified when you magnified.
A kite up or down?
Yes.
Murat, I'm not like you, I'm not irresponsible like you ...
Ece happened because of you, because of your thoughtlessness.
Because you took the future away from our daughter.
Aren't you tired of guilt, will this conversation ever end?
It will never end, it will never end.
I remember that day every time I look at Ece.
I don't think I'm going to forget that you caused our daughter's illness, Murat.
What I do is empty, what I do is empty, can't I fix my mistake?
Then God curse me, Yasemin ..
God give me my pain, Yasemin, God give me my pain, Yasemin, God give me my pain, Yasemin ...
- - you too relax, relax.
Girl, your uncle Barlas called your father had to go to work in a hurry, what should we do?
Ece happened because of you, because of your thoughtlessness, because you took the future away from our daughter ...
I remember that day every time I look at Ece ...
Murat, because I couldn't talk to you, our best effort to talk is that we blame each other.
I am writing this letter because it turned into a fight.
At least this way you judge me, I get mad at you ...
Without these fights like I never said the things I never wanted.
I can express myself, I do not know if it is possible to repair the damage, but I will try.
We are not new lovers, after all, we have been married for many years, we have children,
Yes, marriage is not an amusement park, it is a refuge in war.
I have no one else to take refuge in.
I know you are the one I fight from time to time, this has exhausted us.
Our excitement may have diminished, we are going through difficult times.
They are normal. I know we will throw them all away, we must be together, we must make our decisions together.
I have no other wish.
All we need is to hold on to our marriage, I believe in us.
You are awake, mine does not make sense, you are in front of me.
I already woke up.
Good Morning.
Please, I'll just look, come on, but I'm wearing a white collar.
Keep in mind that one day I will save you from this captivity.
It is a little difficult.
Yes, I have some time before I go to work.
Really, it's super, it's okay, let's plan right now, let's go have breakfast, I'm already hungry as a wolf.
I'm sure I'll take you to a very beautiful place, you haven't had breakfast like this before.
Well well.
This will stay with me.
You are the boss, what are we going to eat?
I'm not surprised.
I don't eat everything.
No mischief, Murat Bey, you will eat.
Ece'ci, finish playing with your plate.
Good Morning.
Where is my dad?
Left early, my Ece'li olives, come on.
Well, I already have a job and I'll go myself.
What are you doing? Derin, what are you doing I say?
Mom, I said I have a job, we will meet Bahar and review the song.
Tell me that, look at me, are you excited?
Mom, my heart will go out for two days or I hope my father is happy, but it is worth all this.
It will.
I don't know, if you don't like it, or you might find it silly.
Look, I know your father very well, dear, believe me, he will love our surprise.
The message I was waiting for arrived, mom, I left, I kiss you, I am leaving, peanut.
Now I was going to say eat the tomato.
Who are you texting with?
I will meet a friend for work and I communicate with him.
Is that?
Exactly.
It doesn't seem like a scary place at all.
If you want to decide without seeing the inside.
Then I won't go in.
You enter.
Forgiveness.
I didn't tell the kids that you didn't come home at night.
Who bothered him?
What else could work? You will be two minutes late. I'm going.
Okay, but I'm late so hungry I'll eat whatever comes to the table, let me know.
Hello.
Yes?
I stayed in the office last night.
Stay home tonight, please.
How are you?
I say let me go today.
Why can't we talk, Yasemin?
Yes?
Not good, well say hi, say hi.
Murat go and see, Yasemin kills me hour after hour.
I got there too early to get some work done, but when you got there early, plans fell into the water.
What happens, my dear, you can enjoy it and I already have breakfast with my friend ...
What happened?
My father, Bahar my father, all the surprise will be ruined here, he has seen us now, are you okay?
My daughter.
Dad.
Girl, what are you doing here my dear?
What are you doing? I was sitting with my friend.
Hi, I'm Bahar. Then you are Derin's father.
Yes, Murat, Bahar.
Girl I'm going to the meeting for coffee, do you need one?
No dad, thanks, easy.
I'm glad again, maybe we'll see each other again.
Maybe, come on, see you.
See you.
It was so bad, are you looking here right now?
Do not worry.
Come on, what did you want?
An American.
I was so terrified, don't you think?
Derin didn't understand, could you calm down?
OK.
When he's alone, definitely call, we need to talk.
Ruhi, you know, if I ask Murat now, he will understand why I asked him, so I told you.
Last year he did not like his cake, he does not say that I will not be sad ..
Anyway, what happens, my Ruhi, you go in and out of your nose, you find out what kind of cake he wants.
Okay, okay, my dear Yasemin, calm down, don't worry about it.
You're great, Ruhi, okay, let's help out a bit, let's go.
Well.
Mommy.
My dear.
What happened?
Are you mad at my dad?
Baby why are you so fatherly?
He didn't kiss me when I went in the morning, he always kissed me and never forgot.
Now your father was going to kiss you completely this morning, when your uncle Barlas came, your father told me ...
This morning, go and kiss me, I forgot.
It's OK now?
He also said something. He said if we had a barbecue in the evening.
Get meatballs?
Of course I'm my lamb, I'll do it to you right away.
Hurrah!
Without running, shirt, shirt.
I love that those who have a sterile life like you buy these motors.
I do not understand.
So I say you will do a maximum of 90, a little too much. How many do you really do?
300.
Wow, it's good, if you give it your right.
How do you know it didn't come out of 300?
Of type.
If you want, I can show you how wrong you are.
Why not? Show me
Are you married? I'm not married, anyway, I don't think I'm going to believe the pattern.
But not me.
My father.
He is your father?
What happened, are you scared? Let's get out of here before we meet.
Come on fly with me.
A cake is important brother, everyone has a taste.
I don't know, for example, I like chocolate, you.
Didn't you get tired in this game? Leave me alone, brother, leave me alone.
Okay, I want cherry, okay cherry.
Wait a minute, why is it a cake underneath now, doesn't it happen every year, Murat ...?
I'm asking, you're saying, I'm asking, you're saying So what happened now?
So aren't you bored with this nonsense, Ruhi?
We know why we come to the party for not knowing, isn't it always the same terane?
What do you do or don't you do what you do? We lie to each other what surprises this ..
We all know that we are not surprised, we know like ice, we lie, we ignore.
But then ..
What, Ruhi, is there a dead man there, we see the corpse lying there, but we ignore it, Ruhi, why?
Murat, brother, are you okay?
I'm good.
So what is this death, dead, so nothing from this birthday in this house?
I'm overwhelmed, I'm overwhelmed, brother, I'm overwhelmed by this meaningless life ...
Or it affects me, it collapses like a nightmare, I can't breathe.
Wow, now I get it.
It's normal, but boy, you went to the andrope but you say it?
I told you a lot, do you understand that?
So what, don't spoil my son, don't spoil yourself!
Yasemin breaks to make you happy girl.
Yasemin, are you tearing up for me?
Let it be for the love of God, everything is doing by itself, what do you have to do? I have something to ask
myself ... Look, there are cards in my hand, I have to choose one of those cards ...
What does it matter to me, what does it matter?
She does it herself, to show her friends how perfect she is.
What does that have to do with me? I do not care?
I'm sorry, Ruhi, it's okay, I'm sorry.
Tevfik Bey, let's clarify this detail tomorrow, okay, okay ...
An important phone arrived, okay, I'll call you.
Yes Ruhi, what did he say quickly?
He wanted cherry.
Cherry, are you sure?
Yes because?
Not at all, he doesn't normally like cherries.
I don't know, so she started loving the cherry. This is what I understand.
Okay, okay, if you're that cool, Ruhi, you saved my life.
What are you going to do this year? Is your program ready?
This year I'm going to set off a strange bomb, but I wouldn't even tell you.
Thanks.
Yasemin will ask you something, did you fight with Murat?
Not because?
It's not that important, I was a bit frustrated, so something happened at the company.
I guess it's very stressful these days.
Alright, see you later.
Why don't you pick up the phone?
I had some work.
OK, we need to talk.
I think we also need to talk, I'm downstairs.
Where is it down Okay, I see you, I see you,
Wait, I'm not going, you don't need to come, I'm coming, wait, I'm coming.
Father.
Enters.
I thought I was a stranger and I was scared.
What happened? Did you start kidnapping?
My daughter, don't you understand the word? Didn't I tell you to move out?
I do not understand, I am scarce, my head does not buy. What are you doing or are you crazy?
Now listen to me well, if I see you again about 50 meters from the company, I will not look at your tears.
Put it in that bird's brain, okay, girl, get out of my car and my life now!
Let.
I can't see you, where are you?
I'm close, wait, I'm coming.
No, you are not coming, I am going.
You were right in front of the company, what are you doing here?
You asked me.
Can I have my watch?
Well. Turns out it was a gift from your wife, let's see.
Where do you meet Derin, Bahar, what did you talk to?
I am being interrogated, it is not an important thing, it is air to water.
We will not meet, we will not meet again, this is not true Bahar, the latter is each other ..
May this be the end, we will not see each other again.
Why is that?
Because I am married.
We already understood that, am I not aware that friendship is forbidden in married people?
We are not friends?
It would be wrong, this is wrong for you and me, okay, this is the last time, could you make it easier?
Please im sorry.
You say it's over, okay, Murat, we haven't started yet.
Please let's go.
Well then, goodbye then.
Stop, Murat Efendi, I haven't started yet, we haven't started yet.
Hello sir, my dear Derin, say it dear.
Okay, I'm coming.
Sema, look at me Sema, take care of your daughter.
I swear ...
Fulfill our agreement, shut up, or complete the unfinished business?
Don't bother, how did you find me?
Say hello to that little demon like you're putting it with my hand! There is no escape from me. Be smart Sema be smart.
Murat, I can't tell you how excited, if you saw a birthday, like a child all day ...
She asks me all kinds of questions about surprise ...
But if I screw it up, I don't open my mouth, of course, a sweet excitement surrounded us all ...
If you could come, dad, maybe we will get permission.
Anyway, I'll tell you for a long time. It is very difficult for you to know the details.
I agree with the company Sitare works for.
Murat wanted cherry too, you know dad yeah I know I don't normally like it.
But I don't understand, maybe it will change but I didn't say the real bomb ...
I won't tell you, will you miss it?
Yasemin.
Yes Dad.
When is my birthday?
5th of April.
I couldn't suddenly remember.
Dear Dad.
Daddy, I'm coming.
I didn't know you were coming.
I decided so suddenly, Yasemin, that I told you to look at you and let me see your father for a long time.
You did well, I called you that you were busy today, is everything okay at work?
Account, as always, how is your father?
Well.
Come come ..
Bahar, my daughter, you must come here immediately.
What happened to Semoş? Isn't it Veysel meat again?
No, it's not about him, we can't talk on the phone.
Well.
Ediz Bey's medication time has come, I'll give him his meds and deposit it.
Okay, we were getting up, my father is entrusted to you.
Don't worry, Mrs. Yasemin.
My daddy dear, we're leaving now, rest well, take your medicine, it's okay, dear.
Lets go dad.
I'll come again, okay, dad?
Ediz Bey, we have to go take your meds, come on.
Let.
What happened now, sorry about last night, sorry, what can I do?
When you apologize, it doesn't end, they both apologize and push me behind me.
About what I'm throwing, I said what I feel, what should I say more.
Are you sad, are you really sad?
Yes.
I don't think you are even aware of what you are doing.
Speak clearly what you want to say.
I promised Ece, your father will come at night, I said we will have a barbecue.
Well, we do, we do.
Semos girl scared me as the fuss manager, what's going on again?
You walk in, you walk in quick, what are you doing in your head, huh?
Why am I getting confused? Tell me and I'll find out.
Look at me, I know you're going to Barlas, Bahar.
The point is that, no where did you know I went?
This problem does not lift the water, do not mess with Barlas, he is a very bad guy.
Look at Semoş, girl, are you watching this? Why did not you tell me.
Let Satan see his face, what will I meet him? How beautiful I had lost my mark.
But thanks to you, they chased him again, look at me, look at my neck.
Warned, never mind Barlas ..
Wherever he has a hand, he pushes us all, and if there is anything left of us.
Wow wow, who came, hello, not welcome girl?
Welcome.
Welcome my lion, are you tired?
Where Bahar? Stay for lunch, we'll break the back of two words.
I have a job, Brother Veysel.
Eat my work, look at me, does this moment tell me something behind my back? The language of husband and wife does not stop.
Look girl, are you saying something bad behind me?
No, Veysel, is that so? Bahar, of course, my daughter, we haven't been doing anything together for dinner.
Come on, set the table, Sema, and don't machine the girl.
Sit down let's go.
Not alone for a minute.
When I run, it flies really fast, right dad?
Yes girl, well done, well done to you.
Well done, didn't I say Ece, won't you play with this?
But mother.
Why aren't you listening?
But mom.
Mrs. Filiz, Mrs. Filiz.
But I didn't do anything wrong.
You didn't, you didn't, I know, my dear.
If it's up to you anyway, good time, Filiz.
Can I ask Ece why he's not looking, Mrs. Filiz?
Excuse me, ma'am, I just wanted some air.
I will never argue about this with you, blood sweat boy ...
Whatever happens, take it and change it.
But mom.
You destroy it, it has opened up enough trouble for us.
Let me help my mother.
It is not necessary, sit down. You have reached the beginning of forty years.
As much as you forgive in the kitchen. Tell me what are you doing, do you sing songs in the pavilion?
I'm not working on the ward.
Of course, the pavilion, the cafeteria, of course it is not them, but your voice is also burned.
Take your hand, put your hand on your arm.
What would you do if I am not?
Pray, I would know what to do if my mother is not there.
What the hell are you doing, are you holding my head?
What do you think you are I gave you your bread, thank you ungrateful.
Veysel, don't be a victim, I apologize for what you did, please.
I'm running away, Semos, you're happy with your husband.
Leave my hand.
Bahar, my daughter, I will tell you not to go, but every time we arrive, our peace fades.
Semoş, the guy tried to touch me.
No, it's not, you like her daughter, when drunk, is a bit silly, but in essence ...
In essence, it is good in its essence, look what I say, hang out or hang ...
. ..watch your wave, eat these rhythms, sit down, choose this life ...
You choose to live this unpleasant life, so you deserve all the beatings you've eaten ...
But I can't bear this unpleasant life, I don't have to live with you.
Happiness for you in this life is miserable.
Bahar, Barlas is a matter of ...
Don't ever call me Barlas again, you know that guy will pay me the penalty for what he did.
I'll pay one for one, I won't stop until your happy little family falls apart and the flour is small.
You can't help it, I'll take revenge, you can't help it when you're done.
It will be so regrettable if you have an idea, don't tell me Barlas again ...
Don't try to intervene, I don't look at your tears.
Sema, come on.
What happened?
Fortunately, he did not have a fever.
You got it all in vain again, boy, what is it?
Let's not talk here, come.
I know Murat, it's a boy, but Ece is sick, what you don't understand is that.
Well, this is not a matter of understanding, I also know that our daughter is ill.
But I'm trying to keep experiencing this, Yasemin ...
... you never let us forget this, you don't.
I don't forget because the day you had that accident, listening to you, trusting you ...
I can't forgive myself for getting in your car ...
I can't forgive myself for letting my daughter do this.
It was an accident Yasemin, you know it was an accident or did you see the man come and hit me, I did nothing.
You drank Murat, you drank.
Again, how many times are we going to discuss this? I had a glass, this accident is not my fault.
Yasemin, it's not my fault that the car came and hit me, Ece was born prematurely.
It's not my fault that her heart was born sick, we had an accident, that's all ...
Ece is not only your daughter, but also my daughter.
Dad.
My daughter.
Are you going somewhere?
No girl, I forgot my phone in the car, I thought it was here.
Well, I'm in my room.
My beautiful daughter, my dear daughter.
Look, if you want.
No need to wait a bit, I wonder, right? If you can't find it, my value goes up.
I have been married for 20 years, of course I forgot these games.
So 20, congratulations, it's not easy.
Thanks .
You were telling the scene.
Now our garden is big enough that there is no problem with setting up a scene.
Actually, I thought it would be better to see the Yasemin Hanım place, so how much acoustics or something like that ...
Where to put a column, how to choose a microphone, these are important details.
Of course it would be, but I didn't know how to do it because Murat surprised me.
If he sees you home now, his surprise will disappear.
Of course, you are telling the truth, let's not break the surprise.
Let me meet up and ask where it is.
I think you're right, I guess the chase got away.
Certainly your spouse must have been after you as well.
Murat is not really that kind of man, come on.
I can swear that men come out of a single pattern, frankly, I think they are all the same.
We have a different relationship with dynamics.
I understand, your husband is very lucky, Mrs. Yasemin, he obviously knew what he wanted, he ran after him.
I say let's put it on the open buffet, the tables will be in the middle.
We will set the scene here.
Could be.
We will make a place for children here.
Everything is fine but I need 1-2 more hours Ruhi, yeah what's up a little more distraction.
Okay see you all.
I arrived just in time Bahar, but now we have to hide you ...
Because you are the surprise of the night.
Wherever you look, we are here for 2 more hours.
This will be a two hour zoom, how do we take it, with the saddlebag?
Guys, something came to my mind.
I'm not going to this birthday, look good idea, be really surprised.
What are you saying? Yasemin kills me.
No, forget it, Sitare divides me into fourteen, you lost one out of two.
Either he will go or he will go.
Exactly.
Friends or is this woman crazy?
Why.
Or do you think he wants me crazy?
If you quit smoking, you drank enough, you'll drink where we go, let's spend that night.
Today is my birthday, the relationship will give me a drink.
I forget that everything is really a surprise.
My soul has shrunk my soul, brother, I'll be wandering.
Let me tell you a coffee, that birthday boy.
Two things put something into it.
Of course, would you throw this away? Even if you make a black coffee, even double.
I know you won't open it, but today is my birthday, I wanted you to know.
You can easily prepare here.
Thank you Mrs. Yasemin.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Sure, can I order a juice if Ms. Yasemin doesn't mind?
Sure sure.
I would be very happy if they have cherry.
Fine, I'm shipping right away.
Thanks.
I got to the room.
Let us begin.
Derin, are you okay?
Onur, I'm a little excited, I don't think I can breathe a little.
Okay, calm down, take a deep breath, take it now, let it go slowly, well, calm down, okay?
Okay, okay, I'll be fine, I'll be fine.
You didn't go to the doctor for your hand, we talked a lot. Why are you doing this?
Onur was cured, cured, but now he's completely stunned, I can't touch, I'll be in disgrace, what do I do?
Okay okay, calm down, you're going to play it wonderfully.
It was very nice.
Sorry, look, forgive. Excuse me?
Here you are.
Could you call me Mrs. Yasemin, very urgent but really urgent?
Of course.
We are broke, Mrs. Yasemin. What are we going to do now? No, I didn't bring any other clothes like me.
Okay, don't be mad, we'll have something for me in my clothes.
Really, I was afraid that I will not be able to go on stage, the surprise will be broken.
Nothing, let's find something.
Yes.
This is a very nice dress, can I wear it?
I mean, of course, but this is a very old dress.
What matters, you know, retro things like that are all the rage right now.
Well, take it then.
You are so lovely Ms. Yasemin, a wonderful piece.
What kind of car is this?
Come.
I swear my foot is kicking back, am I obligated to join this party?
Don't be silly, son, we've already arrived.
I don't want to go in and do something wrong again, I swear I'm going.
Ağa is enough. We have been a babysitter for you since morning, come back to yourself, what is this?
What do you say, my son? You don't feel sorry for us.
Wrench.
Open the door.
What were these?
Stop it, calm down.
I'm not going to do anything, my birthday is mine today.
Welcome Murat.
Thanks.
Good night.
Welcome.
Thanks. Hello.
What nonsense is this Sitare, hello, how are you?
Hello welcome.
I'm waiting at the company, okay?
Yasemin, thank you honey.
Murat.
Happy birthday, Mr. Murat.
Divine Murat Bey, you must be the husband of Mrs. Yasemin, we actually met, more precisely, we were deeply caught.
When Yasemin said, it was as if she understood.
I almost caused the marriage to end in my awkwardness.
Yasemin, I thought you were.
I gave him my dress.
Of the.
Happy birthday, by the way.
Good evening everyone, welcome back. My dear husband Murat 20 years ago.
She wrote me a poem to tell her love, she was pregnant with my daughter, now our daughter has grown up.
And his poetry compositions written by his father, Derin ...
... but don't worry, I won't read. Someone who can do this job much better than me right now ...
Bahar is my gift to Murat. Bahar will tell us about love tonight and say ...
... love, Murat is for you, happy birthday darling.
I said you would love my surprise.
Yasemin, I have to tell you something.
I'm listening.
I'll tell you everything clearly, Yasemin.