Over here!
I'm afraid it's true.
His Royal Highness has struggled.
And whilst Her Majesty's desire to have
her son be the first heir to the throne
to attend a normal school is laudable,
and we were delighted
to have His Royal Highness at Cheam...
we should not delude ourselves...
that it has been entirely successful.
Thank you.
The press run stories
about him almost daily.
The other boys read about him
in the newspapers.
They see his detective.
We do what we can, but...
boys that age can be cruel.
The fact is, His Royal
Highness is different.
And not just because of who he is,
who his parents are.
He's uncommonly shy.
Sensitive.
Delicate.
So, if you're asking me where,
in my professional opinion,
he should go to senior school...
Yes, I am.
I would say that in Eton College,
you have the perfect solution.
Right on your doorstep.
Look, Charles!
Look, you'll be so much closer to us.
The weekends, you can just run up
the hill and you'll be with us all.
And you can sleep in your own bed.
I have to ask Daddy,
but I'm sure he'll agree.
Dear Uncle Dickie,
Mommy told me that she had chosen Eton
College for me for senior school.
I must say, I was very relieved
and now find myself very excited.
Being at Eton makes so much sense.
Am I right in thinking
that you went there, too?
I was never at Eton.
I was tormented by a
particularly dull tutor at home.
Then I was sent to the
Naval College in Osborne.
So, I'm very envious of Eton.
What great fun you'll have there.
And may I suggest a gentleman's
outing to meet Arthur Cunningham,
head cutter of the finest House
in Savile Row?
- Sir.
- Is that a two in the hand?
- Yes, sir.
- Also known as?
- The Eton knot.
And shoot the cuffs.
I think slightly higher on the shoulder.
Yes, sir. Quarter of an inch.
And we position the hat with the thumbs.
The Eton suit.
- Next size up?
- Five, sir.
Five?
- Five.
Whites.
Breathe in.
Good.
Thank you.
- Now, doesn't that lift the spirits?
- Yes, it does!
Finishing touch.
Oh, yes!
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*
Congratulations, sir!
- Well done, you!
- Thank you!
We won by half a length, which
is the nautical equivalent of a nose.
- Ah. Neck! You've burnt your forehead.
- You should see my legs.
Oh, thank you.
We left it rather late admittedly.
But came good at the last marker.
Which is the nautical equivalent
of the final furlock.
Furlong!
After dinner you should
look in on Charles.
To show him the trophy? Good idea.
No. I thought to compliment
him on his uniforms.
- What uniforms?
- His uniforms for Eton.
What are you talking about?
Charles is going to Gordonstoun.
- Not necessarily.
- Yes, necessarily.
- It's not set in stone.
- Give me a hammer and chisel
and watch me carve it into one.
Philip.
Gordonstoun is the right place for him.
It's no exaggeration to say that school
made me, and it can make Charles.
He won't learn a thing
about himself at Eton.
Yes, but he might just
survive or flourish.
Or he might just become
another wet, namby-pamby,
mollycoddled twit like the rest
of the British upper classes.
Your Majesty, Your Royal Highness.
Well, Dickie thinks it's
the right school for him.
- It's none of Dickie's business.
- He's got a soft spot for Charles.
- They write to one another.
- Since when?
- He heard how unhappy Charles was.
- I wish he'd stop meddling.
Well, meddling is what Dickie does.
We would be betraying our son
if we let Eton have him.
He's going to Gordonstoun,
and that's the end of it.
All right, fine, if you feel
that strongly about it.
- I do.
- We'll return the uniforms.
You can burn them for all I care.
But you can break it to Charles, not me.
- Fine.
- Your Majesty.
Thank you, James.
I do like Scotland,
but isn't it a long way from home?
- No.
- And a terrible inconvenience
- for you to come and visit me there?
- No. Not at all.
I've already decided to fly you
up there myself as a special treat.
But...
I won't lie to you.
When I heard I was going to Gordonstoun,
I felt exactly as you do now.
Wretched.
I wanted to stay at home
with my dear, favorite sister.
I wanted the easier, softer way.
But in order to grow up properly,
you need to get away
from all this nonsense.
Would you like me to let you into
a big secret?
Please.
This... is not the real world.
John. Get rid of those.
You can have my old jumper.
The uniform hasn't changed a bit.
Pop your head through.
That's the first lesson.
Who we are is not what we
wear or what glitters.
It's the spirit that defines us.
In here.
Philip?
You're not really
going to fly him to school
dressed for a funeral?
Of course.
One might as well be dressed
for the inevitable.
If we land safely, I'll change.
She's your sister!
See you soon.
Uh, yes, I'm Greek.
Come along. Let's get this over with.
Ja.
Why did we do this? I hate flying.
We should have gone by train.
Give me your hand.
It's fine. Look at me.
- It's all right. It's just air.
- Yes.
- It's beautiful!
- It's freezing!
Why couldn't I have stayed in Germany...
and gone to school there?
Because Father thought it very important
that you be educated by a genius.
And since Dr. Hahn is a Jew,
staying in Germany was impossible.
Fine.
But why did the genius choose Scotland?
Your Royal Highness.
- Who's that?
- Some foreigner.
- What's your name?
- Philip.
Philip what?
It's just Philip.
Hey. Back to work.
Philip! Come along!
Your Royal Highness!
The big day began at London Airport,
where the Duke of Edinburgh
surprised Prince Charles
with the decision to fly him to school.
This is the really modern
way to go to school.
By airplane, piloted by your father,
on this most important
day for our future king.
- Welcome!
- My dear Dr. Hahn.
- Welcome home, sir.
- It's good to be back.
Mr. Tennant, the head of Charles's year.
- Your Royal Highness.
- Pleasure.
- Good morning, boys!
- Good morning, sir.
- Your Royal Highness. Welcome.
- Thank you.
You know this school runs
in your father's blood.
He was one of the first pupils here.
- He helped build the place.
- I did, I built that wall.
Yes. Things have changed
a little since your father's time.
But not the important things.
The principles remain unchanged.
- Yeah, good. You haven't gone soft.
- No.
Don't want him mollycoddled
in some luxury hotel.
This way, Prince Charles!
Are you ready for how tough it is?
How do you feel being far away, sir?
All right. Good. Thank you.
Is this good for him, sir?
Is this the right school for him?
This was your father's dormitory.
We've even given you his old bed.
- Hello, boys.
- Morning, sir.
Simon Harper, sir, dormitory guardian.
Simon will teach you the
rules and look after you.
We've given you the window,
Your Royal Highness.
No, no. Don't call him that.
It's just Charles.
Yes, sir. Charles.
Thank you. That's awfully kind.
This is Geddes.
Charles.
This is Gilkinson.
Memories flooding back, sir?
Yes.
Happy ones, I hope.
This is Griffiths.
The happiest. Who's that?
The royal detective.
The palace insisted.
In case of press intrusion.
The whole point is the boy
learns to fend for himself.
Don't worry. We know
what's expected of us.
The Duke wasted no time
before signing Prince Charles up
to Gordonstoun's infamous
Annual Challenge,
notorious for testing
endurance and determination
in the inhospitable Scottish Highlands.
At Gordonstoun, fitness is valued just
as highly as academic excellence.
The prince is sure to be put
through his paces
by their grueling physical regime.
This is surely the place
to make our young prince
into a man ready to serve his country.
It doesn't close. The thing's broken.
- The rain's getting in.
- The frame's broken, idiot.
- Now what are you doing?
- Moving the bed.
- Put it back!
- But the sheets are getting wet.
Put it back or I'll put you on report.
Lights out!
Come on, we're going to be late.
Faster!
Come on, lads.
- Push out.
- Hurry up! Let's get it over with!
- Out of my way.
- Let's go!
Hurry up!
Get up! Your Royal Highness.
Move.
What's wrong?
It's freezing.
Wait until you've had
your cold shower! Come on!
One more lap. Come on!
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
Right. Come on then!
Move!
Come on.
Oi.
Hey! Get down here!
This isn't optional.
It's your assigned work project.
It's manual labor.
If Hahn wants this place rebuilt,
he ought to pay the staff to do it.
Staff...
Do you think you're better than us?
Actually, I know I am.
- Keep a lookout. Oi. This will be good.
- Will do.
Some mongrel European count?
It's prince, actually.
We know all about your lot.
Your sisters are all Nazis.
And your father's
washed his hands of you
so he can be with his whore in Paris.
Uh... It's Monaco.
Your mother's a mental defective,
locked away in some asylum.
You're no one,
and you're going to do the work.
Why? Because I bloody well say so.
Get off!
Here!
Sit yourself down.
Jim threw the first punch.
Mnh-mnh. I understand injustice.
We're both exiles.
Both victims and I
understand your anger.
But on its current path,
the world will fill with anger
and soon will be destroyed.
So here, away from the madness,
we must build a new way.
A new school. A new philosophy.
A new ethos.
The world needs saviors.
A generation of remarkable young men
who have put fury behind them,
who embrace their pain
and their struggle.
All men must step into the unknown.
There, only there,
in the annihilation of hate and anger,
and ego, is our salvation.
Hmm?
I can't stay here. They're all mad.
Completely mad.
Cousin Louis' wedding falls
in your half-term.
Don wants to fly.
I'll tell him I won't go and you can
come and stay with me, in Germany.
- Just the two of us?
- Probably.
What does that mean?
I didn't tell you. I'm expecting.
Expecting what?
- A little one.
- A-again?
Don't be like that.
Castles need to be filled.
And Herr Hitler is
encouraging us to have
as many children as we can.
As Germany grows,
she will need more soldiers.
Hello?
Idiot!
I thought I would come up here
and see how you were settling in.
Have you made friends?
One. I think.
Although, it's quite hard to understand
what he says sometimes.
Yes, I hear they've
let some local boys in.
Charles.
Even though I am close to your father,
I am not your father.
Things you feel you cannot
show him or tell him
because you feel they might upset him...
- Yes, sir.
- Or even disappoint him...
Those are the things you can say to me,
safe in the knowledge that they will
never be repeated to anyone else.
Anyone else on earth.
Yes, sir.
Charles, if you're not happy
here, you must tell me
and I will take care of it.
Dumbo!
What are you doing in here?
Why aren't you dressed for dinner?
- I need to talk to you.
- What about?
Could you close the door?
I've made the decision to take Charles
out of Gordonstoun and bring him home.
Decide what you like.
He's staying there.
Dickie's just reported
his unhappiness to me.
Dickie's a meddling, interfering
fool who knows nothing.
Well, he knows an unhappy
child when he sees one.
And by all accounts,
Charles is wretched.
He's tormented from the
moment that he wakes up
to the moment that he goes to sleep.
Do you know what he calls the place?
"Hell on earth, Colditz with kilts."
- I don't want to debate this.
- Well, you have to.
And not just because he's your son.
Because he's the future king.
Bullied children are scarred for life.
And scarred children
make destroyed adults.
You and I had an agreement.
A deal that ensured there would be
some level of equality
between us in the marriage.
It's my decision Charles go
to Gordonstoun... not now!
And that would be fine,
for all our other children.
But Charles is the future of the Crown.
And in the name of the
Crown and as his mother,
I have decided to take him out
of Gordonstoun and bring him home,
to Eton, to Windsor, where he belongs.
You can't always fall back on the Crown.
Oh, yes, I can. And I will.
Then you would do well to remember
the promises you made to me.
And the consequence breaking those
might have on the Crown.
Charles's education...
is my responsibility.
Yours is to honor your word...
and keep your husband.
- Charles.
- Hello, sir.
Are you preparing
for the Annual Challenge?
I am.
The Duke of Edinburgh
is giving the prize this year.
I know.
He's spoken to me a great deal about
the significance of the Challenge.
The Challenge is one of this school's
great traditions, but it is arduous.
You don't think I'm up to it.
Physical endurance is only one path
to self-determination.
You have your own particular challenge
here at this school given who you are.
Your father struggled, too.
He had difficulties of a different kind.
Great difficulties, great pain.
But he never gave up, and then,
with help, he prevailed.
I think I would still like
to do the Challenge, sir.
I think my father expects it.
Move!
- Come on, boys! Let's go!
- Give me a hand up!
- Come on!
- Go on!
- Pull up!
- Almost there.
Come on. Help me up!
Get up here!
Did you think I was going to let it go?
- Help me up!
- Philip!
- Are you all right, Jim?
- Serves him right!
I don't expect you
to get on with everyone.
What I do expect of all my pupils is
to conform with Platonic ideals...
to argue without quarreling,
to quarrel without suspecting,
- to suspect without slandering.
- Sir...
You and James will have
extra building duties.
You can work on the main gate together.
Look, in my defense...
I think we've all seen how you act
in your defense.
Thank you.
...and as a punishment we have to
build a gate together over half-term,
- instead of coming to see you.
- Dr. Hahn telephoned me yesterday.
He's going to keep you
at school over the holidays,
to help you settle. I'm afraid I agreed.
- Are you going to be long?
- Piss off! You did what?
Which leaves me obliged
to fly to the wedding.
But that's in London.
Yes. We're at the airfield now.
Sorry, but I've got to go.
Now you just settle and behave well.
That'll cheer me up.
Oi!
Prick!
Yeah.
Philip!
Hahn wants you!
Hurry up!
After takeoff from Cologne,
bad weather meant
they couldn't land at Brussels.
While attempting to land in Ostend...
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid all 12 souls were lost.
Twelve.
Including the four crew.
But with four crew, plus Cecile, Don,
Ludwig and Alexander, that's eight.
Also the Grand Duke's mother,
a nurse, Joachim Freiherr von Riedesel.
Eleven.
And your sister Cecile must have gone
into labor
on the flight.
A newborn was found in the wreckage.
Arrangements...
Where is he?
- Philip!
- Philip, where are you?
Philip!
- Come on, Philip!
- Philip!
Philip! Come on!
Philip!
- Philip!
- Over here! Dr. Hahn!
- He's in the lake!
Come on!
Sir!
Go home!
Back to the school!
Give me the lantern.
You too.
The milk train will leave
Inverness station
at 4:45 tomorrow morning.
You will be on it.
From London, you will fly to Berlin and
then on to Darmstadt with your uncle,
to attend the funeral
of your brother-in-law,
your nephews and your sister.
It will not be easy.
But when you return,
we will be your family.
This school will be your home.
Now come!
Be strong!
Philip!
Philip.
Go on.
Philip, come.
Mama. It's Philip.
Your son.
I'm surprised he dare show himself here.
Papa!
Had it not been for Philip
and his indiscipline...
she would never have taken that flight.
It's true.
Isn't it, boy?
You're the reason we're all here
burying my favorite child.
- Papa.
- Get him out of here.
You may hate him now,
but one day, God willing,
you will be a father yourself.
And you will fall short,
as all parents do.
And be hated.
And you will know what it is to pray
for the forgiveness from your own son.
Philip. Where are you going?
Get inside.
I think he needs help, sir.
Not until he's asked for it. Come.
- Sir?
- Move on!
He's here.
Help.
Speak up.
I... I need help.
So...
Now we go.
Boys.
Come on, boys.
- Three, two...
- Hands on.
- One.
- Lift up!
- Steady.
- Careful.
Stop. Pull back. Back.
- Yeah.
Good. Well done, boys.
You too, Philip.
The challenge ahead is one
that faces every Gordonstounian.
Your route is 18-miles long.
Torch.
You are Gordonstounians,
and you are expected
to rise to the challenge.
Plus est en vous, gentlemen.
There is more in each of you.
Plus est en vous.
Hurry up!
- Go on!
- What?
Go on!
Get a move on, Charlie! Hurry up!
Charles!
Catch them up! Quick! Go on!
- Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Just leave it. Keep going.
Hello, sir! It's good to have you back!
It's my absolute pleasure.
How's he doing?
Well... they should all
be back at two o'clock.
- Grater. Hadden. Cann.
- Sorry, sir.
Never mind. And Pickering. Griffiths.
- Is Charles here?
- Let me have a look.
- Where's Charles?
- We lost him, quite early on.
Geddes. Right, everyone,
get changed quick as you can!
Thank you.
Mr. Peacock, the head of our studies.
How do you do? Good to see you.
Ah!
And finally, Team B.
Well, I think we should start
the presentation.
Ten more minutes.
Of course.
Charles?
Right! That's it. Let's begin.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much!
Well, it's a great joy to be here
and a great pleasure to see
so many happy, healthy, handsome faces.
The Annual Challenge is a unique test.
In completing it, all participants will
have shown great character, stamina,
and most of all...
It's him. Where's he been?
...and most of all, courage.
The ethos at Gordonstoun
is to embrace the community
over the individual,
the team over the star.
And so it gives me great pleasure
to present this wonderful trophy,
the Duke of Edinburgh Cup,
to the winning team,
which I believe is Team C.
Led by Simon Harper.
Well, don't just sit there, boy!
Come and collect it!
Congratulations. Good work.
Well done! Good lad! Well done!
I want you to know,
if you're feeling bad
about where you finished
in that challenge today...
it's of no consequence to me.
I understand that these
sorts of physical
tests don't come naturally to you.
But you showed great courage
and determination.
Don't worry about it.
Whatever shame you may or may not
be feeling, I can assure you
it's nothing compared to the
shame I felt at your age,
over something I did.
- To my favorite sister.
- Oh!
Cecile. She hated flying.
Loathed it, terrified of it.
She always dressed in black
when she flew, for her own funeral.
Anyway, the point is that Kurt Hahn
and that school put me back together,
toughened me up. Charles...
The pain...
The struggle is a gift, Charles.
This is the moment you have to dig deep.
You put the work in now
and you won't struggle in the future.
But you've got to toughen up a little,
boy, for what is ahead of you.
Don't worry about it! It's just air!
I know there's more in you, Charles.
You've got to be strong,
and you've got to find it.
It's just air!
- Get him back here!
- Don't be so weak!
Don't be so bloody weak!
Charles, it's all right.
- Out! Get out!
- Charles!
It's all right.
Winds are picking up...
Daddy!
Darling Anne!
How's my favorite little girl?
- Faster, Daddy!
- I'm coming, I'm coming!
Thank you.
You must be hungry.
Like me to make you a sandwich?
Yes, please. Hello, Martin!
synced and corrected by susinz
*www.addic7ed.com*