Now, Anne, what's this?
- A penguin.
- Very good.
And, Charles, who do you suppose
is surrounded by penguins at the moment?
- Daddy.
- Yes, that's right.
That's because he's in the
Antarctic, and from there,
he goes to the South Shetland Islands,
then he goes on to the Falkland Islands.
And then he goes all the way
up here, to Ascension Island.
All these are British
Overseas Territories,
and they have to be visited
every once in a while,
so they don't feel
neglected or forgotten,
and don't get any silly ideas
like becoming independent.
- Right, brushed your teeth?
- Yes.
- Good. Have you said your prayers?
- Jolly good. Right. Night-night.
- Night-night, Mommy.
Come along, children.
Oh, we might put a picture
of the Duke of Edinburgh
by the children's bed, so they
recognize him when he gets back.
Five months is a long time at that age.
Yes, ma'am.
- Oh, what's that?
- From His Royal Highness, ma'am.
Footage from the Royal Tour.
How nice.
We might watch that
instead of our next film.
Kensington 3742.
Tommy.
The Prime Minister returns
after three weeks in Jamaica.
And here he is now!
Thank you. Thank you. It's
wonderful to be back amongst you.
As you know, I, uh... I went away
to concentrate on my health.
I'm now fully fit to resume my duties.
Thank you.
Quiet, everyone. Sit down you two.
- It's starting.
- Charles, come on, darling.
Now, he's sent some notes to accompany
the footage, so I'll read aloud.
"Hello, all of you!"
Hello!
- "Hello, Daddy!"
- Hello, Daddy!
"I can picture you all perfectly,
sitting there wishing it was
Creature from the Black Lagoon.
But instead, this is just
boring old me arriving..."
- Penguins!
- That's not Daddy, is it?
"At King George Island..."
Look!
"A hundred miles off the
coast of Antarctica..."
- There's your daddy.
- Is that Daddy?
"And nestled between the white
bones of ancient whales.
Here we've made some new friends,
and Mike was rather smitten."
- Look how tame they are.
- He's got a beard!
Yes, yes. They're all growing beards.
It makes them look a bit shifty.
Oh, no, don't say that. It makes
him look like an explorer.
- What's that?
- This is very funny, Mommy.
Um, "We've even installed some signage
so we can find our way home."
Oh, Buckingham Palace! Oh,
that's good. I like that.
"It's a bit of a commute
to the office, though."
"Luckily, we found some
friends for company,
the British Hunting
Aerosurvey teams, who make
excellent tennis companions." Oh, look.
They're all playing
tennis. Isn't that silly?
Goodness me!
"Now, some things about
huskies that you never knew.
They have eyes of different colors."
- Oh, like the Kaiser.
- Oh, Mommy.
"But most of all, they really,
really like tennis balls."
Yes, we can see that.
"And they have claws to ensure
they don't slip on the ice."
Oh, look, now, Philip's on one.
"Joining our family of
animals are the penguins...
and seals, who send
their love to you all.
As do I.
Your loving papa...
and husband.
Philip."
Good morning.
Tommy?
Your Majesty.
I thought you were supposed
to be in happy retirement.
- I am, ma'am.
- Then what on earth are you doing here?
Oh, dear. Either you missed the
place more than you could bear,
which would be...
- Tragic.
- Yes.
Or there's a serious problem, and
you've been called in to help.
Yep. Just a routine matter
with Colonel Adeane, ma'am.
It's hardly routine if he
sent one of the royal cars.
Well, in actual fact, that's my car.
We gave you a car?
You did, ma'am. As part
of the farewell package.
Not the driver too, surely?
The driver too.
- Was that me?
- I believe so.
Well, you've always held
a very special place
in all of our hearts, Tommy.
Anyway, I must go.
Windsor, ma'am?
No, Sandringham.
Michael's re-arranged things to
give me a couple of days off.
Quite right.
You did well to bring
this to me, Michael.
I've served three generations of
the royal family, four monarchs...
and done a good many things to protect
them, mostly from themselves,
but this is the first
time I shall endeavor
to save someone else's marriage
in order to safeguard the Crown.
Not that we give a fig about the Parkers
or their happiness, you understand.
Not a fig, Tommy.
Dear Philip...
I cannot tell you how much we
enjoyed watching the film you sent.
It was lovely to set eyes on you again.
And the children were very impressed
by the whales and penguins.
You looked very handsome, I thought,
in your whaling outfit,
and hirsute, too.
"And I can never forget what
my grandmother said to me
about being married to
a man with a beard."
She goes on, but actually no,
I'm not going to repeat that bit.
Oh, come on. Don't be a spoilsport.
- Come on!
- Ah!
Bloody hell!
I think we can safely say
a very, very warm welcome
awaits His Royal Highness's return.
Good morning.
Morning.
First of all, I must thank you
for the way in which you have
all carried on without me...
and for the manner in which
Rab has very competently
stood in for me in my absence.
You've kept me informed of
all the major decisions
that had to be taken.
In all these months, we have
been a united government.
And we shall remain a united government.
But we're not a united government,
are we, Anthony?
The war you insisted on has left
us as divided as Caesar and Pompey
and the country in chaos.
There is no petrol in the pumps.
There are no tins on the shelves.
Our allies are aligned against us.
Our international
reputation is in tatters.
How adroitly your weather
vane spins, Harold.
You were for the war... as I remember.
Only as long as it was legal.
You...
liar!
Liar!
You wanted it every
bit as much as I did!
You'd have torn off Nasser's scalp
with your own fingernails
given the chance,
taken the oil from that canal
and set the Middle East ablaze!
You've lost the trust of the
people and of the party.
It's the end of the road.
A road which you willingly led me down!
And would you abandon me?
Here?
Hmm?
All of you.
Come now, Anthony...
you know as well as I...
there is no justice in politics.
Captain Lascelles?
Mrs. Parker.
- What brings you here?
- Oh.
A retired man must make friends
with all the good reading
spots in London.
What are you reading, may I ask?
Tell me that it's romantic poetry.
Military history.
The campaigns of Napoleon.
- Your son?
- Yes.
Lieutenant Commander
Parker must be very proud.
He might be. If he knew what
the children looked like.
He's away again. On tour.
You have my sympathy.
I know from my own wife how
difficult that can be.
Being left alone with
the children for days,
sometimes weeks on end.
Well, I'm sure that strong
marriages find a way through it.
I'm afraid it's broken ours.
I am sad to hear that.
Might I ask if you'll hold off on any
instruction or public announcement
just a little while longer?
As we both know, the Duke of Edinburgh
is performing important
royal duties on this tour,
and we wouldn't want any story
breaking in the newspapers
that might undermine his efforts.
Or impugn the royal marriage.
That's what you came here for, isn't it?
This wasn't a coincidence at all.
You came here because you
knew it's where I'd be,
and you wanted to put in a word
on their behalf. It's pathetic.
Still their round-the-clock
lackey, even in retirement.
Sorry to disturb you, ma'am.
I've just had a call
from Downing Street.
The Prime Minister has
requested an audience,
as a matter of urgency.
He's on the train and will
be with us by three p.m.
Platform one, London train.
Please stand back from the edge.
Eden! Eden!
Thank you.
Eden must go!
Of course, I asked for second opinions.
I asked for third opinions.
I implored them to let me carry on.
But I'm afraid the doctors
were of one voice, one mind.
The time has come to put my
health above the country...
and to...
Uh...
To offer you my resignation.
I'm sorry if I, uh...
disappointed you.
Did I suggest that you had?
No, but I...
I think you thought it.
I...
I did think that the decision
to go to war was rushed.
And I was sorry to see you lie
to the House, when you told them
that you had no prior knowledge
of the Israelis' intentions.
We both know that to be untrue.
But, wrong though it was...
I did have sympathy for you.
To have waited in the wings for so long
and to have supported a great man
like Winston so patiently, so loyally.
And then to finally
have your opportunity
to measure yourself against him.
To do nothing is
often the best course of action...
but I know from personal experience
how frustrating it can be.
History was not made by
those who did nothing.
So, I suppose it's only natural
that ambitious men, driven men...
want to go down in history.
Or make history by going down.
I do think the time has come
where we have no option
but to tell Her Majesty
about the Parker divorce,
and to warn her
that regardless of how blameless
the Duke of Edinburgh is
or isn't in the matter,
that newspapers will be newspapers,
and questions will now
inevitably be asked about the
state of the royal marriage.
Hmm.
I sense trepidation, Michael.
If you'd rather, I can
always handle it myself.
No, I'll take care of this...
and try to find a moment on the
train to mention it to Her Majesty.
Good luck, Michael.
Sorry to disturb you, ma'am.
A telegram arrived from Lord Salisbury,
and the recommendation is
that Sir Anthony's successor
should be Mr. Macmillan.
Of course. Thank you.
- Yes, what is it, Michael?
- Uh, it's just to say...
and we could, of course,
discuss this on our return
to the palace if Her Majesty prefers.
No. Do sit down, Michael.
Thank you, ma'am.
Um, but it seems that...
Mrs. Parker, uh, who is the wife
of Lieutenant Commander Parker...
Yes, I know who Eileen is.
Um, she has decided to sue
her husband for divorce.
Goodness. Is that what you
wanted to talk to me about?
Yes. Um...
And that while, of course, there
is no suggestion whatsoever
of any impropriety on the
part of His Royal Highness,
the Duke of Edinburgh, we should
perhaps be bracing ourselves
for one or two irritating headlines.
Why? Whatever for?
What is it that she's alleging?
Cruelty, unlawful desertion and, uh...
Uh, adultery, ma'am.
We're just aware of the fact
that Lieutenant Commander Parker
is His Royal Highness's private
secretary, he's a close friend,
and there is this letter, I believe.
A letter?
Written by Lieutenant Commander Parker
to his fellow members of the lunch club,
bragging about exploits
on the royal tour.
What sort of exploits?
- Uh...
- No...
I don't need an answer to that
question. Thank you, Michael.
Thank you, ma'am.
Mr. Macmillan, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I gather soundings have been taken,
and that you have been
chosen by your colleagues
as the man most able to unite the
government and lead this country
following Sir Anthony's resignation.
Yes, ma'am.
Congratulations.
Although I fear you've inherited
something of a poisoned chalice.
It's true. The storm is
now raging against us.
With Eden's war, we've
discarded the moral advantage
or any goodwill we once held.
Not to mention the dire
economic situation.
It's really been quite ruinous.
But it wasn't just Eden's war, was it?
It was a war prosecuted by a government
of which you, as chancellor,
were a major constituent part.
I also seem to remember that you
were one of the loudest voices
in support of the war in the beginning.
One always has to accept
one's own part, I believe...
in any mess.
Prime Minister.
Your Majesty.
Michael, could you ask them to
send 'round one of the cars?
Bridge receiving. Go ahead.
D-Watch requests permission to leave.
Granted. Affirmative.
Ship's communication to bridge.
Bridge receiving. Go ahead.
Do you have a moment?
What were you thinking?
You know the rules.
No letters to anyone.
I told Baron to be discreet.
But somehow the letter
got back to Eileen.
And now she has written to the palace...
to give notice of her intention
to sue me for divorce.
Which means it's got
back to you-know-who.
Yes.
I think we have to assume so.
Don't tease me like that.
- Good morning.
I remember how we used
to do this in Malta.
Go grocery shopping together.
Feels like a long time ago.
Yes.
The reason I came here today is, uh...
because I heard, with great sadness,
that there are difficulties
in your marriage.
And I would like to know if
there's anything that I or...
anyone else can do to help.
My marriage to Mike is beyond help.
I see.
Our separation has been
inevitable for some time.
I had intended to
divorce Mike years ago,
but because of the attention
surrounding Group Captain Townsend
and Princess Margaret...
I decided to hold back.
Thank you.
But that was then. This is now.
What's changed?
Nothing has changed. That's the problem.
It just got worse.
And while some women may elect
to put up with this sort of humiliation,
I simply have too much
respect for myself
and my children to bear it.
I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
Then read this.
Hmm.
Don't bury it, ma'am...
or sweep it away.
It's there, in black and white.
Might I ask you a favor?
That you hold off your announcement,
just while we work out what to do,
in light of this?
I've had enough of favors to you people.
My entire adult life has
been favors to you.
You people aren't even remotely aware
of the cost of the damage to families
and marriages in your service.
I've instructed a solicitor.
That's my decision.
Gentlemen,
I would like to make a brief
statement on behalf of my client,
Mrs. Eileen Parker.
"Having endured an unhappy
marriage for some years now,
I have come to the sad conclusion
that a formal separation is
the best option for us both.
My husband has shown no
inclination or enthusiasm
for the responsibilities of
parenthood or marriage...
and divorce remains the only solution."
Thank you.
Mr. Lewis!
Duke's best friend and wife
separate, read all about it!
Read all about it!
No.
Sir.
Uh...
Telegram from my lawyer in London.
His view is that, yes, the
newspaper coverage is bad,
but it's not disastrous,
and he feels confident it'll
all die down in 48 hours.
He thinks we can ride it out.
You and I both know
that's wishful thinking.
I've had my own telegram from London.
I...
I hope you're not going to make
this next step difficult for me.
No.
You'll have my resignation first thing.
I'll need it now.
I hereby offer my resignation...
as Principal Private Secretary
to the Duke of Edinburgh.
Effective immediately.
Accepted.
You've worked for me for long
enough. You know the rules.
Who we are. How it works.
There is no room for mistakes.
There is no room for scandal.
There is no room for humanity.
I think you should probably
leave us in Gibraltar.
Might I suggest a policy of
"no comment" on all counts,
and especially no letters?
Yes, of course.
Commander Parker!
Did the Duke fire you, sir?
Just a few words? Just a few words, sir?
Piss off.
Go on, piss off.
Go on now. Go on! Go on, I've
got nothing to say. Piss off!
Following the resignation
of Lieutenant Commander Parker,
the British press have fallen into line
and been overwhelmingly supportive.
But?
I'm afraid the foreign
newspapers have not been so kind.
Yesterday, a story broke
in the Baltimore Sun...
- Where?
- Baltimore, Mommy.
Claiming that the capital
was awash with rumor
that the Duke of Edinburgh
was romantically involved
with an unnamed woman whom
he met on a regular basis
in the West End apartment of a
society photographer, Baron Nahum.
Nahum is also president of
the Thursday Club in Soho,
of which the Duke of Edinburgh
is a founder member.
Anyway, that story has
rather lit the touch paper.
The British press has caught on,
with The Manchester Guardian reporting,
"Not since the first rumors of a romance
between the former King Edward
VIII and Mrs. Ernest Simpson
have Americans gobbled up the
London dispatches so avidly."
Go on.
The Sunday Pictorial, on its front page,
reminds its readers
that the royal family
"is loved and envied throughout the
world because it is a family."
Time magazine has a headline:
"Too Much Thursdaying."
It goes on to say, "Not
since Wallis Simpson
stalked the corridors
of Buckingham Palace
have the eyes of the world
been turned so beadily towards
those chintz drapes."
I say we fly the Duke of
Edinburgh back straight away.
That's one thought, Your
Majesty. And it's a good one.
The devil's advocate might argue,
and I'd be interested to hear
Michael's thoughts on this,
that the Duke's early return, obviously
stage-managed by the palace,
might appear too much of a
concession to the newspapers
and pour even more petrol on the flames.
I would agree.
And we don't want that.
No.
So, what then?
What?
Yes?
The Admiral would like a word, sir.
That's fine. Tell him he can come.
As a matter of fact, he suggested
you go to see him, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
- Sir.
But if something
has to attack Chinese
currents in a Flycatcher
and then put down on the
deck of a Hermes...
Admiral.
Oh, do come in, commander.
Thank you.
Buckingham Palace has been in touch
regarding your reunion photo-call
with Her Majesty the Queen.
With you? Not me?
I am in command of this ship.
I am her husband.
It's been agreed that Her
Majesty will fly out to Lisbon
a day ahead of schedule.
- As I see it, your instructions...
- Instructions?
Are to meet her at the airfield.
They've been quite specific for
how the reunion is to be managed.
Thank you.
Tie.
Not that one. One that's
fit for an adult.
Those were the instructions.
For God's sake. It has hearts on it.
And the hat, too?
- Yes, sir.
- I hate hats.
I believe its value on this occasion
is not in its being worn,
but in its being removed.
Ah.
"In a gesture of
chivalry and deference."
Before I enter the aircraft.
Before you reach the
stairs of the aircraft.
Michael.
Your hat, sir.
Yes, perhaps it would be prudent
to postpone the civic lunches...
Darling.
We'll talk later.
Shall we?
Your Majesty!
And here they are. Reunited
at last, but for how long?
Your Royal Highness!
Have you missed her?
...and display a united
front to the world.
This will do little to
quell rumors of a rift.
Unprecedented scenes here
as photographers from
all over the world...
The Queen and the Duke of Edinburgh
hide from the world's eyes
on board the Royal Yacht.
Now the eyes of the world
turn towards the Royal Yacht,
on which they have sought shelter.
No, no. No, I see.
Thank you.
That was the palace press secretary.
In his view, the steps we've taken...
The show we've put on.
The steps that we've taken
haven't quite done the trick.
The rumors still haven't gone away.
I think we both agree it
can't go on like this.
No.
So I thought we might
take this opportunity...
without the children,
without distraction...
to lay our cards on the table...
and talk frankly for once...
about what needs to change
to make this marriage work.
All right. Who goes first?
Stupid question. If I've
learned one thing by now,
it's that I go second.
If I am to go first,
that's where I'd start.
Your complaining.
- My complaining?
- It's incessant.
Whining and whingeing like a child.
Are you surprised?
The way those god-awful mustaches
that run the palace continue
to infantilize me.
If you weren't behaving
like an infant...
Giving me lists, instructions.
"Do this, don't do that,
wear this, don't wear that,
say this, not that."
Can you imagine anything
more humiliating?
Yes. As a matter of fact, I can.
I've learned more about
humiliation in the past few weeks
than I hoped I would in a lifetime.
I've never felt more alone than
I have in the past five months.
And why do you think that was?
- Because of your behavior.
- Because you sent me away.
- Yes. And why do you think that was?
- I don't know. You tell me.
Because you're lost.
You're lost in your role, and
you're lost in yourself.
Christ!
Look...
I realize
this marriage has turned out to
be something quite different
- to what we both imagined.
- Understatement.
And that we both find ourselves in a...
Prison?
In a situation that is unique.
Our marriage is different to any
other in the country because
the exit route which is
open to everyone else...
Divorce?
Yes, divorce.
It's not an option for us.
Ever.
No.
This... This restlessness of yours,
it has to be a thing of the past.
It's what I need.
And it's what our family needs.
The monarchy's too fragile.
You keep telling me
yourself, one more scandal,
one more national embarrassment
and it would all be over.
So, what would make it easier on you?
To be in, not out.
What will it take?
You're asking my price?
I'm asking... what it will take.
All right.
To make it work... to
make it bearable...
I'll need the respect and acknowledgment
of the dreaded mustaches.
Please stop calling them that.
I'll stop calling them that
when they don't all have one.
An end to their snobbery and
prejudice, no more being sniffed at
for being a foreigner with a
background nobody understands.
You will earn their respect
with your behavior.
No. No. No.
I will earn their respect
with the only thing those
creatures understand,
a gesture, a statement.
Something irrefutable that shuts
them up and commands their respect.
Right now, I am currently outranked
by my eight-year-old son!
Well, yes, of course. He's
the heir to the throne.
I am his father, Elizabeth.
Her Majesty the Queen
has been pleased by Letters Patent
under the Great Seal of the Realm
bearing the date the
22nd of February, 1957,
to give and to grant
unto his Royal Highness,
the Duke of Edinburgh,
the style and titular
dignity of a prince
of the United Kingdom of Great
Britain and Northern Ireland.
The Duke of Edinburgh
shall henceforth be known
as His Royal Highness, the Prince
Philip, Duke of Edinburgh.
"O, famous son of England, this is he.
Great by land and great by sea.
Thine island loves thee well,
thou greatest sailor
since our world began."
Quite marvelous, sir. Thank you.
"Now to the roll of muffled drums,
to thee the greatest soldier comes.
For this is he, O give him welcome.
This is he, England's greatest son.
He that gained a hundred fights,
nor ever lost an English gun."
Quite magnificent, sir.
Quite marvelous.
Michael? Do you have a moment?
Of course, ma'am.
Sorry it's a bit gloomy.
A bit?
I was never much good around
the house without Eileen.
You could have at least put the fire on.
Hey. I've provided whiskey, all right?
I've burnt some sausages. Who
do you think you are, royalty?
Here you are.
- To our wives and sweethearts.
- May they never meet.
What will you do now?
Go back to the Navy?
No. I'm going back home.
The Navy is home.
My other home.
Australia.
Oh.
Can I come?
And I thought everything was
all sorted in your world.
Well, as sorted as it can
be. When you sell yourself.
- She wants more children.
- Ouch!
I told her the last
thing the world needs
is more royal mouths to feed.
She said, "You should think
of it as a second act."
Of what? A Greek tragedy?
Of her life as a mother.
That makes sense, from her perspective.
Hmm.
Charles isn't a child to her, is he?
He's also the Crown.
A living embodiment of who will
replace her. Supersede her.
Loving a child who, through
no fault of his own,
represents your own death can't be easy.
- No.
- Because she's a little cold with him.
She tries her best.
Might be nice to have a couple
of kids that are just kids.
Not mortal threats.
Who she can actually love.
Ah.
It's the airport driver.
What will I do without you?
I'm always at the end of a telephone.
That's it then?
End of an era.
Thank you for that era.
No. No, Mike.
Thank you.
- Sir.
- Philip.
Sir.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com