Previously, on The Shield.
You need help.
I can't...
.. be helped.
This is how serious I am!
Calm down.
Jesus Christ!
What's the matter with you?
I'm your Landlord, Rondell.
And you can't follow by my rules,
I'll find someone who can?
Rondell's out. I'm making the change.
He's working for a drug dealer?
The drug dealer was
working for Mackey.
I want you to help him prove it.
We killed a cop!
Get over it. Don't bring it up again.
You accused Big Mackey
working with a drug dealer.
- Who's your witness?
- Anonymous tip.
Anyone who can corrobrate it?
Call me anytime...
Jesus Christ! What did you do?
Nothing you haven't done.
You've been manipulating
police resources...
...to crash land value
in this neighborhood?
The facts will show that
Assistant Chief Gilroy...
...chose a path that led to tragic
circumstances fro this city.
(14 months earlier)
Store owner says he heard the shots.
He didn't come out to take a look.
That make him gutless or smart?
Probably a little of both.
The D.M.V. says she had a '96
Ford Escort registered to her.
You think driving with an escort will
disqualify you from being car-jacked.
Where the hell are the tech guys?
A knife fight over on Stanton.
Hurry up and wait time.
No. I'm gonna try the gum again.
You'll be back
on the tar in a week.
Thanks for your support.
Christ almighty, my
whole life is going by.
Vic.
Gilroy's in the house.
Hey. What brings you
to the front line?
A car jacking at 2:00
in the afternoon.
Yeah, well. Business
as usual on the Farm.
Look, I wanted
to talk to you in person.
The command of this new Strike Team.
I'm having a hard time
selling you to the chief.
Balls!
I know the area. I know the players.
No one can do this better than me.
The chief's not looking
for somebody better.
He's looking for somebody more...
What? What's the problem?
He's worried about all
your run-ins with Plotkin.
- Plotkin was an asshole.
- He was your superior.
Yeah, and I've done my penance
for a year and a half because of him.
I'm never gonna get another shot?
Not this one, Vic. I'm sorry.
No. I need to get out
on the street, cleaning it up.
I mean,
you gotta talk to the chief again.
- What?
- You can make it happen.
Pull a favour.
Just get me the assignment.
Get me Shane on the Strike Team.
That's another one
with a spotty jacket.
Shane's a good cop.
And he works well with me.
You can fill the rest of the team
with whoever you like.
Ben, I need this.
I've only got one marker
to use with the chief.
If it use it, I need results.
I need them quick...
...or we're both out of a job.
Just give me the chance.
The unit's anti-gang, anti-drug.
- Your own team, wow.
- I just can't blow it.
- You won't.
- A lot of O. T.
It's more money, but
it's less time with you and the kids.
We'll manage.
You have to do this.
- Ben picked you, didn't he?
- Yeah.
After looking
for any reason not to.
And he couldn't find one,
so show him.
Can I help you?
I'm Detective Mackey.
I'm running the Strike Team.
We're still interviewing
for that position.
I hope not.
Assistant Chief Gilroy
told me I start tomorrow.
I figured I'd settle in early.
Hit the ground running.
Gilroy told you that?
I'm Captain David Aceveda.
You said your name was Mackey, right?
Yeah.
I read your file.
We have a chance to
do something real special here.
Well, you let me know
how I can help.
I don't care how you
did it in the past.
But in this house, we're
gonna work together.
Special squads, detectives,
uniformed police officers.
We'll help each other
and share information,...
...however and whenever we can.
It's the only way that this
satellite precinct can work.
I'd like to thank the man
responsible for our new jobs,...
...Assistant Chief Ben Gilroy.
Thank you, Captain.
You all know this unit
is a trial squad.
An expensive one.
People say it's a waste
of time and tax dollars.
I don't believe that.
Let's prove them wrong.
- Thanks, Big Ben.
- Good luck, Vic.
Come on, Brent.
I remember you.
Sofer, you did your P-2
over at Central?
- Yeah.
- Who sucked you into this hellhole?
I couldn't pass up the long hours
and the low pay.
- You ready, boot?
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Don't ever call me "ma'am."
- Yes, sir.
Just Danny, okay?
All right, Danny.
I know you two haven't
worked Farmington...
...as much as Shane and I have,...
...so I want you to get out
on the street, cultivate C.I.s...
...find out who's
hating, who's mating.
- Knowledge is power.
- Cool. When do we get started?
Already have.
I put a list together of the
neighborhood dickheads.
We're gonna make some house calls.
Let them know who's new in town.
This is gonna rock, man.
Thanks for letting me join the band.
Shane vouched for you.
In spite of that, I figured what the hell.
Might have been a mistake.
Oh, yeah? Who let the guy
with the mustache in?
- The ladies love the 'stache.
- Listen, guys.
Trust isn't something
that happens overnight.
And trust me, where we're going,
we're gonna need it.
Yeah.
Sorry.
We have a drive-by,
gang-related, one fatality.
That's you.
- We're on.
- Let's do it.
- What happened?
- Yo, man, they killed Wanda.
They took Jolene off in an ambulance.
- Polly's shot somewhere.
- Looks like you got off easy.
- Who did it?
- Yo, man, I didn't see him.
- What's your name?
- Ringo.
Parents didn't like you enough
to name you after John or Paul?
No, I know a Ringo.
- Oh, yeah?
- Small-time pimp daddy.
Who'd you piss off?
Yo, man, I was just walkin' with my
girls, mindin' the store. That's all.
I mean in the last couple of days.
No one.
Someone's trying
to mark their territory.
Who's the lion?
See what you can
drum up out of Ringo.
I know one of the girls
that works for him. Owes me.
- I'll see if she can help.
- Okay.
The classroom's where you learn the
rules, but 70% of the job is instinct.
Morning, Jules. Black tea, please.
You want anything?
Orange juice
and a breakfast burrito.
- I'll take care of that.
- That's okay, man. On the house.
I appreciate that, but I have to pay.
Regulations.
- Five bucks.
- There you go.
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
Vic.
Can I come in?
Sure, yeah.
You taking care of Brian now?
He stays with my mom
most of the time.
Sometimes she's got this thing
like three, four hours though.
And then you're alone with him?
He's fine. I don't fix
while I'm watchin' him.
One of Ringo's girls
was killed today.
Another one got shot.
I heard about Wanda.
She was okay.
Any idea who might have done it?
Well, you heard it
from somewhere else?
- Lionel Phipps or his guys.
- Who is he?
From the neighborhood.
Got his hands in drugs.
Decided he wanted to get
a piece of our asses.
Ringo didn't wanna pay the tax.
Next thing you know...
Stay away from Ringo.
He's a walking target right now.
That's my mom.
Time for me to get to work.
If Lionel is the Lion, then what does
that make you, his wives or his cubs?
Who wants to tell us
about the drive-bys this morning?
- Stop feeling me up, faggot.
- You getting a hard-on, faggot?
Bitch ass!
Hey, hey, hey!
Against the wall!
Up against the wall!
Man, he's the asshole
who started it, man.
There's also about a dozen
citizens watching us, man.
Just one mistake,
that's all it takes.
Look, he's the cocksucker...
Who just put
himself on our list.
But when the time
is right, understood?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
All right. Let's wrap them up
and take them home.
Get your ass up!
- Wagenbach?
- Yeah. Hi, I'm Dutch...
- You're two hours late.
- What?
- At Sunset, detectives start at 9:00.
- You start here at 7:00.
- Yes, sir. I didn't...
- You're lucky there's a desk left.
That's by the kitchen
and the women's restroom.
Is there anything else?
There was at 7:00.
You might as well
make yourself useful.
A rape victim led us back to the
vacant building she was held in.
Detectives Gannon and Wyms
are headed there now.
- Tom Gannon?
- Do you know him?
Not personally. Everyone knows
he solved Beachwood Canyon.
- I hear he's great.
- He's punctual.
Managed to loose the ropes,...
...punch out the window with
her bare hands to get out.
There have been other women here.
Vacant building, quiet street.
Not much chance of witnesses.
Dutch Wagenbach,
Farmington Division.
Over here, we just call it
the Farm. Tom Gannon.
I know. Beachwood Canyon Slasher.
- Claudette Wyms.
- Wyms?
- You been on the force long?
- Long enough.
I'm sorry. I just
haven't heard of you.
Why would you?
I like to keep up on my colleagues.
Follow the bigger cases.
- So, Butch...
- Dutch.
We got a Salvadorean illegal,
doesn't speak English,...
...won't give her name,
her parents, just her story.
- Which is?
- She was kidnapped.
Held here by three cholos.
They called somebody for ransom.
Threatened to rape her
if they didn't pay.
Called back later, family
didn't have the money yet,...
...so they went to town on her.
After they were done,
they tied her up, left.
She managed to escape.
First one to roll
on Lionel gets a free pass.
The rest don't.
So who's talking?
You don't think I'm gonna get
Lionel with or without you?
Okay.
I'll be back in an hour.
See who changes his mind.
Screw you!
I don't think we're
looking at typical rapists.
Sexual predators are antisocial.
They're driven by
inadequacy, not money.
Our three will have rap sheets, but
for violent crimes other than rape.
The sexual assault was a punishment
to them, not a proclivity.
Best desk in the house.
Right here by the
kitchen, the men's room.
We lucked out.
This isn't an isolated case.
Seems like a lot of
illegal immigrants...
...have been getting
snatched up on the Farm.
Our stats don't show that.
The families don't report it.
They just pay.
Several people said I should talk
to someone named Jesus Latigo.
Who's he?
Well, I don't know, but
I got him coming in.
Great.
That's good work, Wyms,
but I got you beat.
I dug up a witness.
Says she saw three guys driving
off from the crime scene.
So I'm running a partial plate.
I'll fill in the boss.
So, Tom, when you broke Beachwood,
what made you think the stepbrother?
Something just wasn't
right about that kid.
His stepsister was all cut up,...
...but he didn't even seem worried...
...about his mother's safety
or his two real sisters.
You see, he loved them.
Anyone know what the partner
situation is around here?
Captain's still working on it.
Maybe we could work together.
I could learn a lot from you.
Yeah. Well...
...maybe it'll end up like that.
When I heard what had
happened to Anabel, I was sick.
- How did you know her family?
- I'm a friend.
Well, we have to talk to them.
See what the kidnappers said to them.
They won't come in.
My clients are illegals.
You know how it is.
I thought you were a
friend of the family.
I am.
Are they also your clients?
Are you a lawyer?
No, no. I'm just a friend.
Everyone I talked to said that...
...you're the man to see about
dealing with kidnappers.
What does that mean?
I've really said too much.
No, you haven't.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Goddamn it. I didn't mean that.
I was told this is the ladies room.
I guess it is.
Gannon, you creaky old sack of shit.
What are you doing?
Gilroy asked me to do him a favour...
...and bring a little credibility
to this old barn.
Barn. I like that.
I heard you're running
the Strike Team.
- Yeah. They're giving me the shot.
- That's good.
Plotkin's probably pissing
blood just thinking about it.
Have you talked to Joe Clarke lately?
He's enjoying his retirement.
I'm looking forward to it myself.
These are my guys now.
This is Curtis,
Shane and Ronnie.
- Good, as always.
- Hey.
What are you working on now?
Some illegal got gang-banged.
The victim's more concerned with
Mommy and Daddy's I.N.S. status...
...than catching the pricks
that spooned her.
Who are you partnered up with?
That black girl and some Dutch guy.
- Who?
- Come here.
Come take a look.
I keep hiding his chair on him.
You're starting already?
Every house needs a rube.
And you're anointing this guy?
Oh, yeah. I got the
scoop from Sunset.
His wife was a big boozer,...
...so he puts her in A.A.,
thinking he's getting her help.
And she ends up getting
shtupped by her sponsor.
And the kicker is she finally tells
him not only is she leaving him,...
...she's having this other guy's kid.
Oh, no, no.
Maybe we should
cut him a break then.
Nah.
My guy says that Dutch-boy
is just a big windbag,...
...needs his sails trimmed.
- Doesn't anyone knock?
- This one's Wyms.
- Hello.
I got someone in interrogation.
Who?
Why don't you come
upstairs and find out?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
All business.
She'll never last around here.
- This ain't gonna work.
- What do you mean?
There's not enough oxygen
in there for the three of us.
- Fletch, you hang back.
- We'll tell you how it goes.
- Sure.
Mr. Latigo, this is
my partner, Tom Gannon.
There's just one
cage here, right?
Excuse me. Where did
our prisoners go?
- The captain released them.
- Why?
Ask him.
- Captain, I have a question.
- Yes?
Well, I was just wondering...
...why you cut my prisoners loose
without checking with me.
I saw the paperwork.
It was a mess.
There was no probable cause.
The D.A. wouldn't have taken
the case, so I let them go.
Maybe you'll remember this...
...the next time you turn in
such sloppy paperwork.
I wasn't looking for a conviction.
I was just sweatin' them.
It's a holding cell,
Detective, not a sauna.
It's reserved for
legitimate, actual arrests.
They were part of my
murder investigation.
What investigation?
I haven't seen anything of merit.
Where are the suspects?
Where are the leads?
You sent them off packing.
Commanding the Strike Team
is a prized position.
We had a lot of candidates
just as qualified, if not more.
So get your act together,
or I'll find someone else.
Are we clear?
Yes, sir.
How's the first day going?
A few bugs,
but I'm working them out.
Anything I should know about?
Your guy Mackey, he's not off
to a very impressive start.
- He'll get results.
- Maybe.
But I'd like to put a
backup plan in place.
Fill the last open slot
with a guy who could...
...run the Strike Team
if Mackey flunked out.
Give the man a chance,
David. It's day one.
I've read his file,
called around.
A lot of people
won't work with him.
It's a crucial slot.
We can do better.
I need this experiment
to be successful.
So do you.
Then we need someone who can deliver.
He will.
Come up with some candidates
though, just in case.
I'll pick somebody personally.
No, come up with a few guys,
run them through my office.
- You shouldn't have to be bothered.
- It's too important.
I'm making all personnel
decisions around here.
Just keep an eye on things.
I'll be in touch later.
Hey.
Heard about your spat
with Aceveda.
Aw, we're just getting
used to each other.
No time for a learning curve, Vic.
The chief gave me
everything I wanted here,...
...but I had to take on Aceveda.
He's not going anywhere.
Now, do you have leads
on this drive-by or not?
Hell, yeah. We think this street thug
named Lionel is behind it.
Then make your case, and put
the Strike Team on the map.
We will. Just might need
a little more time.
The chief's not gonna
have any patience.
Which means I don't either.
We clear?
The people I've talked to
say you're a ransom broker.
Detaining someone is a heinous crime,
but very lucrative in Latin America.
Detain, my ass. You're
a goddamn kidnapper.
I'm a consultant.
The kidnappers demand a ransom.
The families hire me
to broker the deal,...
...get their loved ones back safely.
And you do this out of the
goodness of your heart?
I charge a commission.
I have a 100% recovery rate.
'Cause your buddies are the
ones doing the kidnapping.
No. Because I understand how to
negotiate with these people.
The Salvadoreans do not.
Negotiate with what people?
Mexicans.
They see the Salvadoreans
as lower class.
They target them.
- And what are you?
- Honduran.
So, look, where are
these kidnappers now?
I've never met them.
We arrange a drop.
How do you contact them?
They page me to a pay phone.
Next time they page you, you tell us.
Look.
I'm successful because the families
and the kidnappers both trust me.
I lead you to these men. All the
others will never work with me again.
If there were no more brokers,
it would be harder to do business...
...and maybe the
kidnappings would stop.
Oh, no.
There'll always be kidnappings.
And the families will hire
other brokers who don't care.
Brokers who take
the money and keep it.
And the kidnappers
will kill the victims.
And the broker says,
"That's just the way it goes."
Well, I care. I pay the money.
I get people back alive.
Look, are you gonna lead us
to these guys or not?
I can't.
Talk to me.
We wait a couple of weeks.
We wait till one of Lionel's
guys slips up on some felony.
And then we flip him.
We don't have a couple of weeks.
Lem and I spoke
to Narcotics and Vice.
They've been trying to make a
case against Lionel for months.
They're at a dead end.
- They have nothing for us?
- That's what they said.
God!
We gotta nail him,
like right now.
Okay, so we keep at him.
We hit him long enough and hard
enough, he'll get the message.
You an expert on making
guys long and hard?
Hey, this isn't funny.
I mean, it's the goddamn first day,...
...and the bosses are already
talking about making changes.
Anybody here feel like
going back to their old post?
Look, I hate
to say this, but...
...I think we need a shortcut.
Like what?
Maybe we need to squeeze a
guy in Lionel's outfit.
Make him produce some
evidence for us.
That'd speed things up a bit.
Produce as in plant?
Hey, we all know that this guy's
an asshole in the first degree.
It's for goddamn sure this isn't
the first body he's responsible for.
- I don't know, man.
- You just hear me out.
A high-profile bust
gets us credibility...
...out on the street and
with the bosses.
Once we get our feet
on solid ground,...
...get a couple of wins
under our belt,...
...we go back to doing it
the right way.
Hey, we need this.
Just this once.
Hey, where we goin'?
Ain't no police station this way.
Yeah, well, we a mobile unit.
Why you in such a hurry
to go to jail anyway?
Bringin' me in for a
couple of joints, man?
I ain't doin' time
for no three sticks of chronic.
With your record,
I wouldn't be too sure.
You're gonna help us
build a case against Lionel.
Are you on the pipe?
You see that?
We had our own tagger do some work.
We're the new king of this jungle.
You think paintin'a snake on
the wall makes you top dog?
Wanna go back for possession?
You guys may be the cops,
but Lionel's the law around here.
You gotta bring it a lot heavier
than this to change people's minds.
- I don't think he's gonna cooperate.
- Give it time.
- If he doesn't?
- I'm thinking.
You know what? Screw Rondell.
We'll just try another homie.
- Lionel will catch wind of it.
- Can't stake him out.
He's smart.
If we bring him in for piddley shit,
Captain Ass will just kick him.
Why don't we get a warrant based
on suspicion of the shooting?
We drop the evidence ourselves.
Lionel will scream "setup." And that's
exactly what it will look like.
It can't even remotely appear
like we brought the shit in.
No, we've gotta have
another cop find it.
How about planting it in his car?
Crib's the best bet.
When's it empty?
It isn't. He's got girls streaming
in and out of there day and night.
We don't need you
to tell us when they call.
We'll just wait, get
the page ourselves.
No, they use a code.
Without me, the number
won't make any sense.
I tried to interrogate our victim
again. She still won't talk.
They don't trust the police.
That's why they come to me for help.
I do this community a service.
It's not just about the money.
I help families pro bono...
Cut the champion
of the people crap.
- So what happened?
- Mayfield Duffy...
...pushed a cart full of groceries
out of the store without paying.
When my husband went to
stop him, he got attacked.
- What did he hit you with?
- A bag of ice.
- Go call the paramedics.
- Mayfield is okay.
He just had a bad run.
No work.
He said he will pay
for the stuff later.
I told him we don't do that.
No money, no groceries.
Look, I don't wanna get
Mayfield in no trouble.
I just want the money
or the groceries back.
Well, sir, he committed a felony.
We're gonna have to arrest him.
Well, then go do it.
He took perishables.
- Yeah?
- Step out of the apartment, please.
- You Mayfield Duffy?
- Yeah.
Step down, please, sir.
Hands out of your pockets,
sir, and behind your head.
- What's the beef?
- Turn around.
- I told him I'd pay him.
- Before or after you struck him?
Is Otto okay? I didn't
mean to hit him hard.
Yeah, he's okay.
Second set of cuffs.
You know there are places where
you can go for aid, sir.
- I got aid. Then I got robbed.
- Robbed?
I get food stamps twice a month.
That punk gangster in 29...
...keeps breaking into the mailbox
and stealing everybody's food stamps.
It will be days before
I can get some more.
Meanwhile, my family's starving.
What am I supposed to do?
Not commit a felony.
Use this purse.
It's got a false bottom
and a remote mike inside.
- What's that, coke?
- Crack.
The sentencing is more severe.
Give me your purse.
Come on.
I want you to go inside
Lionel's apartment.
You tell him that you're willing
to pay a street tax...
...to stay out
working and stay safe.
I don't even know this guy.
He knows about you.
You hide the crack in his bathroom,
under the sink or something.
This is the guy who shot up Wanda?
It'll be a pleasure then.
Hey, hey. You're miked.
We can hear everything.
If at any time the mike fails,
we'll be in there, okay?
- Okay.
- Listen.
This guy is bad.
If it seems dangerous, you
just say the word "gringo."
Then we come
riding to the rescue.
- Gringo?
- Yeah.
Right.
Hey. I mean it.
Any sign of worry, you say the word.
You Happy Sandez?
Yeah, that's me. What of it?
You the same Happy Sandez...
...that's been breaking into
people's mailboxes...
- stealing their food stamps?
- Food stamps?
I don't need no ghetto coupons.
Happy, we got your sheet, man.
You got three priors
for theft and no job.
Why don't you give those people their
food stamps back so they can eat?
I'm missing the game.
I tell you what, Happy.
My partner and I are gonna go around
the corner for exactly two minutes.
And when we come back,...
...either the food stamps you took
are sitting on that bottom step,...
...or I'm gonna call
some detectives down here...
...and they're gonna turn
your life upside down.
You got it?
You got two minutes.
Screw Ringo. I'm willing to pay you.
I don't wanna get shot up.
Smart thinkin', sweet pea.
- So are we cool then?
- Nah, not quite.
See, I like to know what I'm
puttin' on the streets.
Come here. Right here.
- He wants to taste the kitty.
- Sure.
- Just let me run to the bathroom.
- What for?
To pop in my diaphragm.
No need, baby girl.
I ain't hitting that raw.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, God.
The broker is a pipeline,
but he's decent.
If we talk to him
the right way, he'll talk.
That broker is a dead end.
I got my witness coming in.
I think she's our best bet.
You know, I got
30 years experience says...
...if we slap this broker
with obstruction of justice,...
...he misses one home-cooked meal,
he'll talk.
Tom's got seniority. Follow his lead.
The witness is here.
- Hi. I'm Detective Gannon.
- Carry on.
So, hypothetically,...
...how would you go
after the broker?
The boss wants to do it
Gannon's way.
And he's going his way.
Doesn't mean we can't go ours.
They teach you that in the classroom?
Goddamn, you're tight.
Oh, God.
- You ain't gonna dis me again, right?
- No, I swear.
Right?
- I'm going in.
- Hey, hey, hey.
She didn't say gringo.
- I'm going.
- Hey! We don't have a warrant.
And we're only gonna get
one shot at this. All right?
I don't care.
Hey, god-goddamn it!
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on, man. Hey.
She's a pro.
This is what she does for a living.
We gotta make this case, right?
Right?
Oh, for God's sake.
Hey, Vic. Come here.
Hey, look. We're almost there
now, right? All right?
It's in the bathroom,
under the sink.
God.
Vic, I'm okay.
Vic.
I need to score
before you take me home.
- Nice digs, David.
- Nice enough.
You don't sound too excited.
No, I am.
It's just...
Gilroy's stocked the pond
with his own fish.
I'm still figuring out
what waters are safe to swim in.
I could use
a friendly face working here.
Is this gonna be like
the time you tried...
...to get me to work
Narcotics in the Valley?
- It'll be different.
- How?
You'll say yes.
I'm happy in Robbery.
This is more money,
more action, more fun.
So what's the job?
Gilroy's pick for the
Strike Team, Vic Mackey.
There's a spot on the team.
Take it.
If Mackey doesn't work out,...
...you'll take his place.
Run the Strike Team?
Even if he does work out,
it's still a great gig.
Come on. It's a no-lose
situation for you.
Your boy's going down tonight.
The question is
are you going down with him?
Lionel's got drugs in his crib.
- Lionel don't keep drugs at his crib.
- I guess he got sloppy.
Makes me wonder.
You ever get sloppy?
You wouldn't.
Aw, shit!
So we busted Rondell here
on possession for distribution.
- He wants to deal now.
- What can you offer us?
My boss, Lionel.
We think he did the drive-bys.
I made deliveries to his house.
He's got product there. You gotta
move on him right away though.
And you're willing to swear
to this in an affidavit?
Sure.
Whatever it takes.
Detective Vendrell,
let's take his statement.
Call for a warrant.
- Impressive.
- Thanks.
Getting him to roll
on a heavy hitter...
...for a misdemeanor
marijuana charge.
I can't take all the credit.
I don't think he fully grasps...
...the distinction between
felony and misdemeanor.
When that paperwork comes in,...
...I'd like to go
on that bust with you.
See you in action.
Sure thing.
Your pager just went off.
I know we don't have much time.
Sorry. I'm bound by tradition.
This tradition does it always
include multiple rape?
No, that was wrong of them.
What if the kidnappers decide
the family owes them money?
They could go after her again.
They probably will.
I see how you're being honorable.
You tell me how they're
being honorable.
Look, if you helped us though,
if you led us to them,...
...it would be a message to them...
...that the brokers are not the only
ones who have to follow the rules.
So do the kidnappers.
Your community
would understand that.
They could appreciate
the honor in it.
Informant? Yo, who the hell
told you I got drugs?
That's confidential
for security reasons.
I'm sure you understand.
Yo, don't play me, dog.
I've got a right to face my accuser.
You can mention that at trial.
Hey, yo, man.
Take it easy over there.
Hey, you heard the man.
Respect the property.
Got something.
Whoa. How many years
of experience in this room...
...and the goddamn rookie finds
the brick on his first day.
- Let me see that, man.
- Nice.
Yeah, damn straight.
The kid's a natural.
- I taught him everything he knows.
- I'll bet you did.
Yo, that ain't mine, man.
This is a stone-cold setup.
- You put it there.
- Found it under your sink, sir.
Well, this is a goddamn setup, man.
Vic, Vic.
- Check this shit out.
- That's a TAC-9.
It's the same kind of gun
used in the drive-by.
We plant this too?
Yo, look.
I didn't shoot nobody.
Is that what ballistics is gonna
tell us about that dead hooker?
I didn't think so.
- I have 10 minutes to get there.
- We better hurry.
Just get in the cage.
Good work, Vic.
You know, you really
pulled it together.
- Thanks.
- The chief's happy.
He wants another press conference
to trumpet the quick results.
I'll do most of the talking,
but he wants you there too.
Sure.
Detective. We got a call
from our kidnappers.
We set up a drop.
You mind getting our backs?
The captain said we could
help each other out.
Hey, my day's
just getting started.
Shut up!
Get down. Stop!
Get back here!
Stop, goddamn it!
- Down. Hands behind your back.
- Where do you think you're going?
You got him cuffed?
I said stop!
Goddamn it!
All right, we're secure here.
- You all right?
- I got him.
Keep looking.
- That's them.
- Which ones?
Those ones.
Hey, what happened?
Latigo had a change of heart.
- You didn't tell me that.
- It happened quickly.
I've been sitting right here.
Those our kidnappers?
Well,...
...our broker cooperated,
led us to them.
Well done.
Thanks.
You didn't have to do that.
Credit's overrated.
Tangible results.
Nice goddamn job.
Both of you, really.
I told you he'd deliver.
I just didn't think
twice on the first day.
What did you expect?
The whole team worked well together.
Some things could have been
smoother, but we'll get there.
I'm sure his public defender
will have some questions.
It's just a few scratches.
From being dragged
through barbed wire.
I told him to stop.
Bet you next time he listens.
Come on, fellas.
The job's hard enough without
tension between the walls.
We should be celebrating.
Yeah.
Nathan, you gotta be kidding me.
What am I supposed to do now?
- Use the ladies room.
- Jesus Christ.
Relax. The plumber promised
me he'd get to it tomorrow.
Try not to destroy that one too.
The obvious thing would have
been to go Gannon's way.
Instead, you got Latigo to do...
...exactly what he didn't wanna
do and feel good doing it.
Some cases you get an instinct.
I don't get it. How come
I haven't heard of you?
It's a mystery.
I was thinking maybe we could
serve as partners again.
You know, on a permanent basis.
Wherever I'm needed.
So, if I spoke to Aceveda, asked him
to put us together, you wouldn't mind?
No, I wouldn't mind.
Okay, who took my chair?
Hey, Lem and Ronnie are psyched.
We're gonna go get a beer.
Start without me.
I gotta take care of something first.
Look, I talked to both of them,
and they're cool about what went down.
- Good.
- We got Lionel.
- Got us a little breathing room.
- Yeah.
- It was easy, wasn't it?
It was a little too easy.
My church conducts monthly food drives
in Farmington to help feed families.
I don't need the gospel.
I need work.
My pastor knows a lot of people.
I'll ask him if someone's hiring.
Next time, find some help
before you do something stupid.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
I'm just letting him know where
his family could get some help.
If you're gonna get emotionally
involved with every collar,...
...get off the streets
and into social work.
You don't have to tell
me about the streets.
I grew up on them.
Living in them and working in them
are two different things.
Look, I know I got a lot
to learn about police work.
And you've got your way
that works for you.
But I got a way
I wanna try for me.
Hey. Oh, Jesus.
I didn't know we're coed.
Welcome to the experiment.
- I'll be out in a sec.
- All right. Cool.
All right. I'll see you tomorrow.
It was a good day today.
Hey, man.
So how was it out there?
Fine.
Yeah. There's nothing
like your first time.
I didn't think Gilroy was
ever gonna sign off on me.
Don't take it personally.
- He was just busy.
- Well, I'm glad to be here.
You'll like it.
The john's still broke.
I'm working on it.
- You ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready for anything.
Good, 'cause we get
everything down here.
Starting to get a rep
out on the street.
Bad guys don't like seeing us.
It's starting to get fun.
Hey, hey.
This here is Terry.
- He comes to us from Robbery.
- Robbery?
We love you, pretty
boys from Robbery.
How you doing?