Previously on The Shield.
Before you got hurt, you...
...you said you'd leave the house.
- I know.
- As soon as you can find a place.
I need a room.
I do things that can't be forgiven.
You're gay, okay?
I'm getting married.
- Married? To who?
- Vanessa.
I'm happy to help you
if you're helping me.
- Are you?
- I have been.
But I'm just about through.
- Hi, Vic
- You're clean.
Yes.
This is a C.I. contract.
You'll be required
to provide four tips every month.
Tips that lead to arrests.
- And I get paid?
- Two thousand a month.
Drop the gun now!
I'll never forget what you do.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Justice will find you.
I come out to go to work,
and I find my car like this.
The widow did this.
She knows where I live.
Tell me you're leaving!
Say it!
You work with a Detective Mackey?
The guy he's looking
for...
And I'm afraid if Vic isn't careful,
he might start talking.
Means he's going to explain
the grill marks on his face.
Talk about how we were
protecting his drug competition.
If somebody else finds
him before us...
Can't happen. We have
to find him first.
You've been greenlit.
Detective Mackey.
Weren't you supposed
to meet me here to suck my xxxx?
I hope you all made it.
I wanted to speak to
you one last time.
You better talk to your brother
before you start making death threats.
I've already taken
care of my brother.
And now you've been greenlit.
Department of Corrections
just sent this over.
When were you planning on telling me
about Armadillo's death threat?
Relax. Cops get
greenlit all the time.
It's just talk.
Nothing ever happens.
Armadillo had his
own brother killed.
If there's one guy who'd be
the exception, it's him.
Look at the
bright side.
This tape serves up Armadillo
for accessory to murder...
...and conspiracy to kill
a police officer.
- All we got to do is find him.
- Before he finds you.
Not a problem.
About the minority
on the Strike Team, Vic.
I've got a candidate
I want you to meet.
Sure. Send him by anytime.
Vic. Make sure you
and your guys watch your backs.
Yes.
Why does Aceveda want to
bring on another guy?
It's a quota thing.
We need color on the team,
so the brass can feel better...
...about underpaying
their Mexican gardeners.
Taking on a new guy...
This means one of us gets booted?
No. It means we go from four to five.
Have a seat.
I...
I'm sorry about this
Armadillo heat.
It's my shit.
It should be on me.
I never meant to get
you guys on a hit list.
We're a team, right?
- Yes, right.
- Right.
So, Armadillo's saying
you're greenlit.
Is that like you in a plural sense
or you in a singular sense?
No. It's just... I was on
the porch the whole time.
I mean, he didn't
really see me.
Don't worry about it.
We'll find him before
he gets to any of us.
What about this new team member?
Someone who doesn't understand
how we do things...
...could throw a wrench
into how we do things.
I'm not bringing anyone on
unless they understand.
How are the wedding plans
coming along?
Good.
Look, I'm not going to say
anything to Vanessa...
...you know, about things.
It's not my place.
Thank you.
It's just that if she hears from
somebody else though, you know,...
...or if you
slip...
she's going to be hurt
really bad.
I'm not going to slip.
That's us.
Washburn Terrace.
- What's the call?
- 911 hang-up.
Some three year old probably just
learned how to use the speed dial.
What's up?
I need you to put guys
on my wife and kids 24/7.
You think she's seeing someone?
It's not about that.
But if she is seeing someone,
you want to know about it, right?
Look, I've been putting a dent
in this Mexican banger's drug trade.
He made a threat. I got to make sure
he stays away from my wife and kids.
I'll put my best guys on it.
And one more thing. Corrine
can't know you're watching.
You're invisible. You got it?
Got it.
Julien.
One-Tango-13 requesting backup.
We have a forced entry.
Roger that, One-Tango-13.
Jesus.
One-Tango-13.
We have a 187.
Requesting additional
backup and an R.A.
Roger, One- Tango-13.
Sending additional units and an R.A.
God.
It's a battered woman's shelter.
Go to the other side.
It's okay. Come here.
It's okay. Come to me.
It's okay.
- You got everything you need?
- Yes.
- Stop it!
- Let me see it.
- No, I like that open.
- Stop it!
Cassidy. You still
locking up at night?
- Of course.
- Cassidy, stop!
Okay!
I'm putting a new alarm
system in the house.
- Why now?
- 'Cause with me not here...
...it's the only way you and the kids
are going to feel safe.
Yes. Where is it?
Private shelter for battered women.
They decide to leave their abuser.
They call a 1-800 number.
Get picked up, brought here.
Location's never given out.
Looks like the wrong person found it.
As far as I'm concerned,
there's only six suspects.
- A boyfriend or a husband.
- Yes.
No I.D.'s anywhere in the house.
These places usually issue aliases,
collect the women's wallets.
- Looks like he found them.
- He spent time in the house after.
Cut the power.
Snatched the closed-circuit videotape.
This is more premeditated
than blackout rage.
Any of the kids talk?
The child psychologist will
let us know when they're ready.
Ma'am, you can't go in there.
I'm Emma Prince, director
of this shelter.
- Step back!
- Can I help?
I live here. I run this shelter.
- I'm sorry.
- I have to get inside.
It's pretty bad.
I left for a few hours to pick
up some clothing donations.
They're all dead?
- What about the children?
- They're okay.
We're going to need some help
identifying the women.
We couldn't find their I.D.'s.
I only know their aliases.
Who would know
their real names?
Ms. Henry. She keeps
all that info in her computer.
Where is she?
She was in there when I left.
We're going to need
that information.
Her computer is password protected.
- Who else would know it?
- Our assistant, Julie.
She was also...
All seven of them?
- We only found six bodies.
- Six?
There should be seven.
We take a picture when they
arrive to document the abuse.
- And she arrived?
- Today. A prostitute.
Said her pimp had beaten her.
We usually don't take them in, but
if she went back on the street,...
...he'd kill her.
You were right
to help her, then.
I got two more women
coming in tomorrow.
I can't send them back
to their abusers.
Where am I supposed to take them?
Maybe the city has room for them.
If the city had room, I wouldn't have
had to start my own shelter.
Hold on.
Yes, that's her.
Walt. This is our missing woman.
Get her face and name out to everyone.
You got it.
It's password protected.
I know. That's why I called you.
You're the computer guy, right?
Yes, Police Information
Systems. P.I.S.
"Piss?"
We don't call it that.
I don't have any suspects
until I get the real names.
- Can you get 'em out?
- I'm not cleared to work on...
...non-departmental computers.
It's an emergency.
- Danny.
- Yes?
Yassirah Al-Thani just filed
another complaint against you.
She claims you made a threatening
phone call to her.
I didn't threaten her.
So you did
call her then? Why?
I just told her I knew what she was
doing, and I told her to stop.
Just please tell me you did
not call her from your house.
There will be a record of it then.
What were you thinking?
She destroyed my car. She called
here saying that my mom died.
We can't prove any of that.
Please! Jesus!
She is trying to ruin my life!
We just ducked a major lawsuit...
...and you have just given her
a valid claim for harassment.
You're going to make
a formal apology.
How's it coming?
It's complicated.
What's going on?
Our "PIS" guy's incontinent.
Mind if I take a look?
No.
Emma I.D.'d our
missing woman.
Dorea Pinchuk. Five
priors for solicitation.
She's either a
witness or a victim.
Or an accomplice.
Emma says her pimp was beating her.
That's our guy.
We'll find out who he is.
No, I'll
find him.
If this guy's behind the shelter
slaughter, he won't go down easy.
Thanks. We'll run down other leads.
How are you doing
with I.D. 'ing the victims?
- Your boy know what he's doing?
- Better than this PIS-poor pud.
Her name is Dorea Pinchuk.
She's a pro.
We think she was kidnapped
from the shelter this morning.
Might still be alive.
Don't recognize her.
Who decorated her face?
Her pimp. I want him.
You find out who he is. Ask around.
- See if anyone's spotted her.
- Okay.
Vic...
...this is kind of
a big thing, isn't it?
High profile. A lot of press.
- A lot of work.
- Help me find her.
I'll make sure that it counts
as two of your C.I. tips.
Yes. I was thinking
more like a bonus.
I'm trying to get
a decent place to live.
Maybe show I can
take care of Brian.
Find the pimp.
I'll see about your bonus.
She didn't firewall her backdoor.
- Most people don't.
- I can route around her password...
...by changing the operations
post back to default.
I tried that.
There. What do you want to know?
Fantastic! I need the real names
of those women and kids.
Along with a formal apology
from this department...
...Officer Sofer would like
to address your client personally.
Mrs. Al-Thani, I apologize...
...for the phone call in which
I accused you of harassment.
I had no proof
to support such a claim...
...and I am very sorry
if it caused you any undue stress.
That's all good and well.
But we are still filing...
...a temporary restraining order
against Officer Sofer.
- On what grounds?
- For what?
Mrs. Al-Thani fears for her safety.
You didn't shoot
and kill my husband?
You'll be receiving our
paperwork by the end of the day.
Stay put!
- What's this about?
- It's about her!
Do you know where she is?
Dorea? I wish I knew.
Get up here! You think
I'm screwing around, man?
Man! I haven't
seen her in a week, okay!
Who did that
to her face?
Her pimp! Yes, that's right.
That's you.
Man, I never put my hand
on any of my employees!
That's some old
school bullshit.
They can't go down if
their lips are busted up.
You call me if you hear from Dorea...
...and I don't haul
the rest of your stable in.
They can't go down
if they're locked up.
No, they can't.
Our pimp's a dead end.
You guys got anything?
According to shelter
records,...
...three of our victims checked
in with a total of five children.
- Hold on. We only found four.
- I know. We're a kid short.
There's a seven-year-old
boy missing.
The missing hooker's son?
No. His dad's the one guy we
haven't been able to locate.
His mom's one of our bodies.
Looks like we
got a suspect.
If it is him, he left his
two-year-old daughter behind.
A two year old's
harder to travel with.
Maybe he just doesn't like women.
I'll call back.
Who's our father of the year, and why
would he take a hooker with him?
Name's Mike Holden.
He's a firefighter.
He's got a thing for hookers.
Three priors for solicitation.
Any connection to Dorea?
She lied. The pimp never beat her.
He hasn't seen her in a week.
How much do you want to bet we find
her sliding down our fireman's pole?
All right. Okay. Settle down.
Brass finally get wise?
The new chief wants every captain in
blues and on the street once a month.
A sort of keeping-it-real thing.
Yes. Keeping it real funny.
I'd let you try out for the Strike
Team, but, you know, very competitive.
- Ready?
- Sure.
Let's roll.
It was black and yellow.
Brand-new, with a black seat.
- A Street jammer.
- One of those new sleek things...
...with the 18 speeds.
Eighteen speeds.
Got it.
- Where was it stolen from?
- Our yard.
- Was it locked?
- Yes,...
...but I told him not
to leave it out.
$300, and I just bought it
two days ago.
We'll try to get it back.
Emma, hi.
These are the two women
I mentioned.
- Hello.
- I couldn't believe your message.
You really have a place
I can use temporarily?
The city has a few
apartments,...
...houses they use to stash
witnesses during trials.
I fudged the paperwork, got it
signed out for a few days.
This isn't going to get you
into trouble, is it?
It's as white as a lie gets.
- I just hope it helps.
- You don't know how much.
Here's the address, the keys.
Call me if you need anything.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Emma...
...you're doing a good
thing for these women.
Well...
...someone did it for me once.
You get my wedding invitation?
Yes. Moving pretty fast.
Yes. Vanessa and I are excited.
How long you been married?
Eight years this June.
Anything I should know going in?
Secrets.
Don't have any.
Tell her everything.
Because the one thing you think
she can't possibly know about...
...that's the one thing that
will come back to haunt you.
Good to know.
That stolen bike. Black
and yellow Street jammer, right?
Yes.
- Is that your bike?
- Yes.
It's kind of small
for you, isn't it?
It rides, don't it?
We got a report of a stolen bike.
Brand-new. It looks
just like this one.
I didn't
steal it!
You may be young, but I will
arrest you. Give me the bike.
- But I...
- Do you want me to take you in,...
...book you?
No.
Run home.
Go on.
Don't let me catch you
out here again.
Two hours on the street.
Already cracked a case.
Well, you know.
Once you got it, you never lose it.
Have pimp daddy
get these to his girls.
Five grand? That's like
a hundred hand job reward.
Vic, that guy was the pimp
you were looking for, right?
- That was good, right?
- Yes, that was good.
I'm working on that
bonus for you.
In the meantime,
I got something else.
We think this is our shooter.
Judging from his rap sheet,
he's a regular john.
Hand 'em out to the girls,
see if anybody knows him.
Five thousand dollars? That how
much my bonus is going to be?
No. That goes to whoever gives
us direct information...
...that leads to the
arrest of the guy...
...or the safe return of the kid.
- Just get 'em out on the street.
- Yes, okay.
Want to tell me
why I'm here?
- You know Mike Holden?
- Yes. He's a friend.
You're more than
just friends.
Weren't you best man at
each other's weddings?
Yes.
Bailed him out of
trouble a few times?
Arrest for soliciting prostitutes.
A drunk and disorderly.
Each time, the charge
was dropped on a technicality.
Officers make mistakes.
And sometimes cops
help out their friends.
Is there anything
wrong with that?
Maybe not at Western division.
But here it's a different story.
That's not what I hear.
Six women were murdered
last night at a place...
...where their husbands shouldn't
have been able to find them.
That's Mike's wife Julie.
What... What happened?
Don't tell us you didn't hear.
Someone broke into a woman's shelter
and killed them. We think Mike did it.
- No way.
- There were five children...
...staying at the shelter.
Only Mike's son was taken.
Mike wouldn't do that. Mike loved
Julie. He wouldn't kill her.
He's violent enough
to beat her regularly, isn't he?
She knew how to push
his buttons...
...but it was never as black and white
as she made it out to be.
Why am I here?
I think you got the
address of the shelter.
It's secret to the public,
but a cop could get it.
You told him
where she was.
Then he sent his hooker
girlfriend over there...
...to make sure, and then
he killed those women...
...and disappeared
with the hooker and his kid.
Any idea where your
best man is now, Lou?
If I knew, that would make me
an accomplice after the fact.
No. We just want to find Mike.
I need, like, 20 minutes
to think about some things.
We don't have 20 minutes.
Then I can't say anything.
Tecks got a hit.
I talked to one
of my girls.
Seems your fireman had
a thing for Dorea.
He started seeing her regularly
and then off the books.
Started playing Jack and Jill
on my goddamn dime.
- Anyone seen him?
- No.
And the girl won't
return my pages.
Screw her.
You hear something, you call us.
- I can't believe it.
- Sometimes we're good.
Sometimes we're lucky.
Sometimes we're both.
- This is not mine.
- What?
This is not my bike. I scratched
my initials under the seat. See?
J.D. It's not there.
You didn't tell us that.
Well, can I keep it anyways?
I'm afraid not.
Sorry.
I just stole a kid's bike.
Time's up.
I hope you used it
as wisely as we did.
Your bank says you withdrew
$400 today.
While you were on duty.
You mind if we look in your wallet?
Where's the cash?
You got a call on your
cell from a pay phone...
...10 minutes before you
made this withdrawal.
That money was for Mike, wasn't it?
You saw him after these murders.
Look, I can't lose my job.
This isn't about
your job.
- Yes, it is!
- It's about a child's life!
You know how many of these
things end in murder/suicide?
Look...
I'm not going to sit here
and tell you something...
...and make me lose my job at 32.
I'm not even sniffing a pension yet.
You knew Mike, Jr.
You've been to his birthday parties.
Believe me, I want this
thing to end well. I do.
But I got my own kid
to worry about.
He's not going
to talk.
He knows talking helps us
more than it helps him.
He's not going to break
unless we give him a reason to.
The fact that he's a cop helps us.
He may not like being unemployed,
but he'll like prison even less.
It could take us all day to make a
deal with him. The kid could be dead.
Let's throw him a lifeline, give him
a free pass for the information.
Just 'cause he's a cop doesn't
mean he gets a free pass. Not from me.
- Dutch is right.
- I'm not talking to you.
- I'm talking about saving a kid.
- Don't act like I'm not.
- I vote he gets a pass.
- Who says your vote counts?
I've been chasing down leads
all over this goddamn city.
Better believe my vote counts.
- This isn't your call. It's ours.
- I think he's right.
How old did you say
your daughter was, Lou?
- Three.
- I got two little girls of my own.
- Family's good.
- And expensive.
- No kidding.
- Yes.
But, see, I understand
what your problem is, Lou.
You got to keep your job,
got to keep providing for them.
I'm in a real tough spot here.
Yes. Except
Mike's still out there.
We think he has the kid.
We don't think he's
in the best frame of mind.
For Christ's sake, you think
I don't realize that?
I don't know what to do here.
I mean, I'm... I'm
in an impossible position.
Well, I think there's a way
we can both get what we need.
How?
You a smoker, Lou?
Are you jonesing for
a smoke about now?
Yes.
How's about you and me head
down to the motor pool,...
...you grab that smoke...
...make an anonymous phone call,
tell me where Mike might've gone.
I don't know.
That's too risky.
You find him, you can make me an
accomplice after the fact. No way.
- Come on, Lou.
- Look, you know I want to help.
I just can't.
You son of a bitch.
For the record, I have
no useful information.
You know he's out there!
You know he's got the kid!
All you can think about
is saving your own ass!
What are you doing?
Look. It's the po-po
who stole my bike.
There seems to have been
a misunderstanding.
- I told you I didn't steal it.
- Yes, you did.
- And you didn't believe me.
- Well, we had a report.
- The description matched.
- Description?
My parents said
that's racial profiling.
No, look. That's
not what happened here.
They said if I ever get profiled,
be polite, respect the officer...
but get a badge number.
- Look, here's your bike back.
- Is that a eight or a three?
I'm sorry about
the mix-up.
It's his first day on the job.
He's still learning.
What do you say
we just forget about it?
I'll make sure
it doesn't happen again.
And I'll owe you one.
All right. But
better not happen again.
Thanks.
Better not happen again.
I hear Aceveda's putting
a new member on your team.
No. He's jamming affirmative action
down our throats.
Looking at any women?
Yes. We're bringing in
Batgirl and Charlie's Angels.
I see. 'Cause someone like me could
never run with the real cops, right?
No. I mean, you know, we're going to
look at all viable candidates.
- Asshole.
- What?
Come on! I didn't know
you were being serious.
Three years on Vice,
a year on Narcotics.
- Any gang time?
- Just what I saw in Vice.
A little undercover
when I first got my shield.
- I'm a fast learner though.
- We're a tight team.
Trust and brotherhood
keep us alive.
Well, I'm looking
to be part of a team.
I see that.
Decorated marine.
You see any action?
Short tour in Bosnia.
Marines saved my ass.
I used to be a hell-raiser.
Needed the discipline.
- You know how to follow the rules.
- Yes, sir.
And I'm a guy who likes
busting people who break them.
Good.
- I see you got a wife and kid.
- My boy'll be four next month.
Brave guy.
Must've been a tough decision
to join my crew right now...
...especially with people
you love at home.
Yes. What do you mean?
Didn't Aceveda tell you?
We pissed off a serious
Mexican player.
The whole team's been greenlit.
- Greenlit?
- Yes.
Hits out on all of us.
What did you say to Villanueva?
He withdrew his application.
That's too bad. He had promise.
You scared
him off.
Better in here than
out on the street.
Look, the field is only
going to get thinner.
The choices don't get
much better than Robbie.
Maybe the next guy'll feel right.
Don't think these stall
tactics are going to work.
We're going to hire a
minority and soon.
Yes, Officer.
Carla here says that fireman
picked her up...
...with another girl
a couple of times lately, weekends.
For a threesome?
To baby-sit. She'd watch his kid
while he banged the other one.
Sometimes the other way around.
Jesus. Why isn't she
telling me this?
She just don't trust cops.
Or maybe you just forgot
to tell her about the reward.
Whatever.
- He come around lately?
- A couple of weeks ago.
Okay. Well, he's got
the kid back.
You tell her to call me if he comes
around looking to play nasty nanny.
- Don't worry. I'll call.
- Connie.
Thanks for your help.
We know if our hooker's got a car?
- None that's registered.
- That means he's driving his own.
Or he stole one. Get me
a list of every car stolen...
...within a five-mile radius
of the shelter last night.
Yes, ma'am.
Maybe you should go in,
try your way.
If Lou knows we've got nothing on him,
what am I going to use for leverage?
Yes. I don't know.
Well, I'll try, but
it's a waste of time now.
I checked the arrest reports.
You guys have been on the street seven
hours, haven't made a single collar.
- We're working a robbery.
- How's that going?
- It's progressing.
- From the donut shop,...
...to the sports bar,
to the strip club.
Absolutely not.
- Cute.
- The captain does not like excuses.
He just likes results.
You want to get the paperwork
on this bicycle thing, or should I?
I'll do it tomorrow.
We need to complete
our reports the same day.
I'll let myself slide.
The guys are here
putting in the alarm.
Good.
Vic, this isn't some
simple keypad by the door.
They're wiring the windows,...
...putting in timed lights outside,
setting up motion detectors.
Is there something
that I need to know?
Know that you have
nothing to worry about.
It just seems a bit much.
It seems a little complicated at
first, but you'll get used to it.
- Okay.
Followed Corrine all day.
No problems.
- Same with the kids.
- Good.
- They're beautiful children.
- Yes. Thanks.
Listen. This
protection...
I can cut you a deal, but it's
still going to cost a bundle.
- I know.
- I'd welcome the windfall.
But paying to watch
your kids at recess?
Let me just stick a couple of
guys on the house at night.
That plus the alarm.
I don't want to take
any chances right now. Stay on them.
Sure. Okay, Vic.
Good news is you're right.
She's not seeing anyone.
At least not yet.
You're a lucky man.
I'd leave the house to get milk...
...my ex would be balling some other
guy before I got to the 7-11.
I got to take this.
Yes, sure.
I'll talk to you later.
- Yes.
- It's me.
Connie, where
are you?
I'm in an apartment.
I'm with the kid.
- What are you doing?
- I was with Carla...
...when Dorea came looking
for a baby-sitter.
- I figured it was for him.
- Where are you?
1530 Los Prisa, number 24,
right next to the 101 on-ramp.
This'll get me the five grand,
right, Vic?
Get the kid
and get out of there right now!
I can't. I'm in the bedroom. I got
to go past them to get to the door.
Is there a window or a fire escape?
- Who are you talking to?
- Connie!
Setting up my next date.
You're still mine
for another 20 minutes.
Come join us.
Shouldn't someone stay with him?
No. He sleeps through anything.
Okay. Let's set up a containment.
Ronnie, you take the rear.
Lem, you take starboard.
- You take port.
- Where are you going?
Through the front door, as soon
as the department snipers get here.
Shit!
We're supposed to be
non-code.
Nobody told the ambulances.
Goddamn it!
- You called the cops.
- No. I swear!
- Drop the
gun, Mike!
- Put the gun down, Mike!
- Call 'em off!
Take that gun
away from her!
Otherwise, you might as well be
putting a bullet into your head!
- I want 'em gone!
- Okay.
Back off! Everybody, back off!
Mike, I'm coming in to talk.
- I don't need to talk!
- Two hostages are better than one!
Gun stays outside!
Throw down piece two! Come on!
You think I don't know cops?
Okay, Dorea, get the door.
Come on!
Shut the door! Lock it!
Lock it!
Shut the blinds!
Goddamn snipers, right?
You okay?
You need a plan.
I'm the man
that can make it happen.
Cut the negotiator
101 crap!
You're going to do what I tell
you, or I'll kill you both!
Fine. Take me.
Let the girl and the kid go.
I already have what I want!
Call your buddies!
Tell 'em you're in here if
they're thinking of using gas...
...or knocking
down the door!
It's not going to matter
to them that I'm in here.
They're not going to do the risky
stuff with one of their own!
- Do it! Do it!
- Okay. Okay.
- What's going on?
- Mackey's inside.
So... Why don't you
let him go? The kid.
He's been
through enough.
I didn't go through all this
just to lose him again.
- He's mine.
- He's your son.
- He's not your property.
- You don't know anything about it!
The hell I don't!
I got a boy. I had a boy.
My wife has him now.
She left me. Made me leave.
Then she took my son
and my little girls.
- They always take everything.
- Everything except advice.
That's why I like whores.
You know what you're buying.
We never had a
problem, did we, baby?
It's not even like I feel alone.
I just feel abandoned.
- Pissed off?
- Yes. Hell, Yes, pissed off.
I tried with Julie.
I didn't want... I didn't...
It's all right. I've had
the same thoughts...
...go through my mind
that you've had.
You're not the only guy
who's been used.
Most of all, I just miss my kids.
I can feel myself becoming
a stranger to 'em, you know?
- You're so full of shit.
- No.
You're going to sit there and
pretend to understand me,...
...what I'm going through?
- I'm telling you the truth.
- You think I'm going to believe...
...a bullshit story like that?
- Calm down!
- What, it's going to make me...
...associate with you?
- Calm down!
- I'm going to give you this gun?
You think I'm some kind of idiot
that you don't have to take seriously?
- Of course I do.
- This is how serious I am!
- Don't move! Don't move! Don't move!
- No!
Suspect is wearing a gray T-shirt.
- She's dying.
- You're going to be dead too...
...if you move.
- You didn't need to do that.
- Shut up.
Jesus! What the hell
is the matter with you?
- Shut up!
- You stupid piece of shit!
Dad, what's wrong?
Mikey, it's all right.
Stay in there, okay? Shut up.
Dad?
I can't think when
you're talking.
It's okay. It's okay. Just go inside.
Christ!
Vic, I'm...
- Officer Sofer.
- Yes?
Detectives Branning and Simpkins.
- I.A.D.
- Yes?
We need to search your vehicle.
- Why?
- We got an anonymous call.
Someone claims you're dealing
marijuana out of your car.
Okay, look. I was involved
in an on-duty shooting last month.
That guy's wife has it out for me.
This is another bullshit
prank of hers.
Either way, new regulations say we
have to investigate every complaint.
No matter how bogus.
Where's your car?
Got something.
Wait a minute. That's not mine.
I told you, this Arab woman.
She wants my job!
She's the one that
vandalized my car.
She must've put the pot
in at the same time.
We'll look into that, but we're also
going to have some questions.
What sort of questions? Dust
the bag for fingerprints.
You're not going to find mine.
Let's talk inside.
Please! What do you think I am,
some big-time drug dealer?
I just happen to keep my pot all four
ounces of it in an unlocked car...
...in the middle
of a police station?
It's a setup.
Mike's been shot. He's dead.
Jesus!
He also managed to take
another woman's life before he died.
Eight people dead.
But you saved your job.
Listen. I never wanted
any of this to happen.
Good for you.
Now get the hell out of my sight.
Okay, your system's running fine.
Well, it should.
They told me it cost $2,000.
I got a deal from a guy I know.
Sort of a barter thing.
What's wrong?
- What?
- Did something happen?
It's just work.
Just make sure you
turn it on when I leave.
I will. Are you...
Are you sure you're all right?
Yes.
I'll see you and the kids
tomorrow for dinner.
Okay.
Here you go.
They found it, Mama.
Put this on, little man.
State law.
Okay. Go, go!
Go! Thank you.
We're here to serve.
$300 for a bike!
Lucky this uniform thing
is only once a month.
Any more crying kids,
I'd be broke.
I thought I'd stop by
and check out the new digs.
Nice.
What's this?
Donation.
Thank you.
Things we do to each other.
- Maybe someday I'll understand.
- I doubt it.
Thanks for the food.