Previously on The Shield.
This isn't about me, Vic. It's about
our kids, about them being safe.
I'll move out if I have to,
if that's what it takes.
Manny Sandoval skated
two murders I should have had him for.
I've wanted this bastard for a year.
Drop the gun now!
I do nothing wrong!
Zayed!
I've got a problem
on this Tio murder.
The more I look into it,
the more Vic Mackey's name pops up.
I'm going to find the truth.
And if I have to go
through both of you... I'll get it.
Tell me right now! Where is she?
I don't know!
- She's dead.
- She was in the trunk?
The whole time? Marcy,
why didn't you tell me?
Sorry, daddy.
You know what I get for those
on the street? Fully automatic.
Drop it!
When we retire...
...we're going to play golf
together every day.
I'd really like that.
For his selfless action off-duty
sustaining a gunshot wound...
...during the apprehension
of a major gun-running ring...
...and for exhibiting the type
of individual awareness, initiative...
...and resourcefulness that serves
as an inspiration for all officers...
I'm proud to hereby present
Detective Vic Mackey...
...with the department's highest honor
for valor and courage under fire.
Everybody here deserves one of these.
I was just the guy holding onto it
when the music stopped.
Thank you.
Don't think this means you
get a free pass around here.
- Of course not.
- Congratulations, Vic.
It was Lanie's idea to
recommend you for the medal.
Really? I didn't know that.
Thank you.
It's important
that the...
...public knows about our successes
as well as our failures.
We're running your
Toys for Guns drive tomorrow.
That's where people trade in
their guns to the cops?
Yes. While, Vic was
laid out in the hospital.
He came up with this
great twist for us.
Yes. They get to fill
out raffle tickets...
...for a big prize when
they trade in their guns.
Which gives us their name and address.
We run the gun for ballistics.
If they were used in a crime,
we know where to find them.
You thought of that while
you were on a morphine drip?
Well, stolen guns
put me there.
I had three weeks to figure out
how to get them off the street.
I'm impressed.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Enjoy the toy.
- Next.
- Have a nice day.
- What's your name?
- Patty Ann Hinkle.
- That's a pretty name.
- Thanks.
Where'd you get the gun?
Home. I don't like it.
Do I get a toy?
You sure do.
Gimme your
address.
Starting me off with a bang?
A robbery. Ended badly.
One dead.
Witnesses said the shooter gained
entry using a police badge.
Number 714. That's your number.
Where were you two hours ago?
With me.
Let me see your badge.
- This is a fake.
- I got mugged.
I lost my badge in Tijuana. I never
thought it'd end up back in L.A.
An L.A. cop badge
sold on the black market.
Where the hell else
would you expect it...
- ...to be used?
- Let's all calm down.
- Did you know about this?
- No. No, he didn't.
Where'd you
get this one?
This, Serbian guy in Rosehill.
- It's just like the real thing.
- No. No, Officer Vendrell.
It's not. The real thing got used
in an armed robbery and a killing.
I'm going to clear this whole
thing up. Let me get into it.
I'm sorry, man.
- Where were you two hours ago?
- I was sleeping.
Aceveda seems
pissed, doesn't he?
It's just like old times.
- Who's the dead guy?
- He worked here...
...along with our witness,
who isn't saying much.
You saw this go down?
Is the shooter white? Black?
He had a mask. Happened quick.
What'd he take?
- Nothing.
- So he used the cop's badge...
...to get you to
unlock the place.
He murders a guy for no reason,
steals nothing and leaves?
This guy definitely
knew what he was after.
Whatever it was, it wasn't supposed
to be here. Am I right?
What if I told you my buddy and I here
have a little side business...
...helps victims
get their stuff back.
You offered to get his stolen
merchandise back for a fee?
He was hiding something
he wasn't going to tell a clean cop.
- You thought this would work?
- It already has. He's cooperating.
The store is a front for
an Armenian mob diamond chop shop.
- He told you this?
- He wants his diamonds back.
They fence hot ice. Recut the gems,
put 'em in different mountings
...so they can't be ID'd...
then they resell them.
This is what our shooter stole.
This is
entrapment.
Just for the jeweler...
and he's a guppy.
We're hunting a whale here.
You want us to catch
this killer or not?
Going undercover as dirty cops.
You think you can pull that off?
We can try.
You know, being crooked cops when
it's my ass and badge on the line...
- It's not as fun.
- Yes, well,...
...we're only pretending
to be crooked cops.
So we're not really
taking a cut of the jewelry?
Well, it's always an option,
but today I'm feeling good.
Flip that right there. Yes.
That's got a little thing right there.
I got some stuff too,
in the back.
Man! You havin' a sidewalk sale
and you didn't invite us, Taylor?
I thought we was on
your mailing list.
This has a remote, right?
Okay. Listen. I gave you Fleetwood,
okay? I'm free and clear.
Just one more favor...
swear to God.
You know who might be movin'
this kinda stuff?
No. No. I don't usually
travel in those circles.
Find out who does and then buzz me.
Look, man. You know, CIs are supposed
to be registered and paid, man.
Tell you what. Here's a fin.
Go buy yourself a taco.
That's a $50 box.
Thank you.
I can't believe this.
It was a clean shoot.
I know. I was hoping lawyers
wouldn't get involved.
Let's just hear
what they have to say.
Five million makes this go away.
Well, five million makes me laugh.
I didn't do
anything wrong.
Your officers improperly
entered the Al-Thani home...
...establishing a pattern of racial
insensitivity and abusive behavior.
He gave us
permission to enter.
Only after you threatened
to bring in the F.B.I.
You treated him
like a criminal,...
...which escalated the
dispute with the neighbor.
She felt she
could attack him.
- He needed to defend his life.
- This is ridiculous!
The search was legal.
The shooting, by the book.
We don't agree.
I'll be expecting your counteroffer
by the end of the day.
I wouldn't hold my breath.
Did I mention we're
also naming you...
...as well as Officer
Sofer in the civil suit?
Think it over.
You Tike?
He'll be back later.
What do you want?
How 'bout an
honest answer.
A friend of mine says you're
trying to move some hot rocks.
Man. What the hell you doing, man?
- We're cops.
- It's him.
Give me the keys.
I'd like to see
a warrant.
I'd like to see Anna Kournikova
naked on a water bed.
- I'm calling 911.
- Go ahead.
We'll come back in five minutes
and take your report.
I'll start with possession
of stolen property.
It's an exact match
to our crime scene.
Who sold you this stuff?
I'll tell you what. You get the guy
who sold you these down here...
...and I'll give you
a third of them to keep.
You'll let me keep a third?
Hell of a deal.
What kinda cops are you?
Ballistics just got a hit
on one of Vic's Toys for Guns.
Well, maybe they'll
give him a second medal.
Slug from a test-fire matches up
to an unsolved murder from last year.
One of yours.
Richard Cummings. Yes.
Who's Richard Cummings?
This is a guy who took a loan from
a shark named Manny Sandoval.
Couldn't pay the money back,
ended up dead.
It's obvious Manny killed him.
So why does somebody else
have the murder weapon?
Find out.
Yes.
- He's talking to his old lady.
- He's not going to show.
Coffee, cigarettes, and too much
joviality. Smells like a 12-step.
Excuse me.
What program is this?
- Gamblers Anonymous.
- Thanks.
It's that time of year...
Two days after the Super Bowl...
...everybody finds a higher power
when they lose their shirts.
I lost 100 bucks on
the goddamn Raiders.
- I'll be damned.
- What?
That's Manny Sandoval.
The loan shark? Where?
In the alley.
So your suspect is hanging
outside the meeting...
...where the guy who owns
the murder weapon is?
- Some coincidence.
- Hell of one.
You want to take him in?
Manny doesn't crack easy.
And he won't sweat unless I'm packing
a lot more info than I got now.
Let's wait and talk
to the gun owner first.
So what's so important?
Hope you hocked enough for bail.
Where's my badge,
you dumb ass?
Work with me here, all right?
I need a deal.
We don't. We have you
for robbery and homicide...
...and being dumb enough to sell
the jewelry that ties you to both.
Look, I needed the money, all right?
But you don't have everything.
- Alex Eznik.
- Alex who?
He runs the Zeroun family
for the Armenian mob. What about him?
I give you Alex, you
shave some years, right?
Convince me.
I work protection for him.
He owns that jewelry shop I hit.
And you robbed
your own boss?
I was taking back something
that didn't belong to him.
- That's all.
- Well, why'd you kill the guy?
'Cause he was a thief of Alex's...
...who stole some jewelry from
a store I provided protection over.
What? Wait a minute.
You work for Alex. The
dead guy worked for Alex.
He robbed from you.
You robbed back and killed him?
Doesn't sound like a
very happy family.
No. It's not.
Yes. And Alex
encourages competition...
...especially between Russian
Armenians like him...
...and Lebanese
Armenians like me.
That's why I didn't
mind ripping Alex off.
What else can you
tell me about Alex?
Everything.
Gambling. Hijacking.
You ever heard a rumor
about a money train?
What's a money train?
Story goes it's like a
rolling bank vault.
Supersecret.
Supposedly runs out of L.A.
every couple of months...
...to clean their
dirty money overseas.
How much money
are we talking about here?
I hear it's big.
So who do I make a deal with?
- No.
- Why not?
Because we've already got the killer.
This is where it ends.
We got a line on the biggest
Armenian mobster in L.A.
I'm not running a
mob task force.
- You don't have to.
- You just have to watch.
Let me return the jewels to Alex...
...see if he wants to buy a dirty cop.
You're having too much fun
playing this.
Well, inside I'm a sad clown.
What about the jewels?
You already gave a third
to the pawnbroker.
You want to give the
rest to the mob boss?
Well, that's the deal I made.
If I want them to think
that I'm a corrupt cop,...
...I at least got to
be honest about it.
I don't like it.
And I especially don't like
you in the middle of it.
You know how Giuliani
became the mayor of New York?
He brought down the mob.
I want to know
every move you make.
Absolutely.
There he is.
Mr. Hinkle.
Detectives Wyms and Wagenbach.
We'd like to speak with you.
Is everything okay?
- I wouldn't bet on it.
- Come on.
That's Richard Cummings...
...a man who lost a lot of money
in a restaurant.
He's also a guy who was
into Manny Sandoval for $50,000.
Your gun
killed him,...
...so don't bother wasting our
time with a bullshit excuse.
Where'd you get
my gun from?
Your daughter traded it in
during a toys for guns drive.
How much did Manny pay you to use your
weapon... Or did you do it for him?
What?
We also checked your phone records.
You seem to call
phone booths a lot.
Is that your bookie
or your loan shark?
Certainly wasn't your sponsor.
Where's my daughter?
A complaint has been lodged against
you by a man named Abu Ibish.
- Who?
- Six months ago.
Some bar fight you broke up.
- I don't remember.
- At the Lakeside Tavern.
I get a lot of calls there.
What was the complaint?
This guy says that you used racial
epithets prior to arresting him...
...derogatory comments
referring to his Arab ethnicity.
This is bullshit.
Well, how would
you know?
You don't even
remember the arrest.
I'd remember
that.
Danny...
...if you made any
anti-Arab comments...
I didn't.
Even in the heat of the moment.
I need to know now.
I didn't.
My name's on that lawsuit too.
- What the hell is that?
- I don't know, but buy me a ticket.
Yes.
Hold it.
He's expecting us.
Mr. Eznik.
I believe these are yours.
Some are missing.
That's right. A third.
That's the deal I made with your boy
over at the jewelry store.
You made that deal with him.
You didn't make it with me.
A third is a lot of money.
It was a lot of work.
I don't like cops in my social club.
Fine. Then we'll leave.
You have an auto shop
over on Waverly, right?
Yes. From what we hear,
it's filled with stolen car parts.
Police are going to raid it
in about three hours.
Why are you telling me this?
Shane and I here are
looking to moonlight.
First tip's a freebie.
Next one will cost ya.
Now we're waiting for
the Armenian to call back.
- I said keep this simple.
- It is simple.
I need a raiding party
at this address in two hours.
Not a moment
sooner.
- To find what?
- Nothing.
It'll be cleared out by
the time they get there.
Look. I know it's your world, but I'm
the one who lets you work in it.
Clear this with me before
next time.
I would have.
I just didn't have a chance.
What about this money train?
If it exists, we'll get to it.
- When?
- Soon.
I'm transferring Shane
off the Strike Team.
- What?
- I see you're listening to me now.
Shane is my partner.
I'm thinking Vice might be
a more appropriate assignment for him.
Where does this bullshit come from?
An all-white team
knocking down doors...
...in an 83% minority
neighborhood is bad policy.
We had a deal.
I keep my nose clean
You keep your nose outta my business.
Well, Shane didn't
keep his nose clean, did he?
So we're going to
find somebody who can...
...either a black or a Latino.
Feeling okay?
Fine. Just a little
office politics.
What's the issue?
Actually, it's something you
might be able to help me with.
Aceveda's trying to ram something
down my throat.
You mean adding a minority
to your Strike Team?
- Yes. That's right.
- That was my idea.
And it's a good one, in theory...
...but I don't have another spot open
on my squad.
David told me
he was opening up a spot.
He was mistaken.
Look. An all-white unit...
...smashing down doors
in a heavily minority neighborhood...
It's just bad policy.
You'll get used to the idea.
That's it exactly.
Appreciate your tip.
My men were able to clear
everything out just in time.
- Here you are, gentlemen.
- How did the police know about it?
Seems like you pissed off the
wrong Lebanese Armenian.
Hrach?
Once he killed the jewel thief,
I guess he felt compelled to open up.
How do I shut him up?
While he's in custody, you can't.
Shit.
How much to have him taken out?
- How you doing?
- What, killed?
No. It's not possible.
Not killed. Not killed.
Just taken out of jail.
I'll deal with him myself.
That'll cost you more than you have.
Yes, but, it can be done.
- It's possible.
- He's in custody for murder.
Well, I am
the arresting officer.
I suppose if I made a
technical error...
...violated his rights somehow.
Yes, Yes.
How much to violate his rights?
You want me to release a murderer
so that his mob boss can kill him?
It sounded better the way
Vic explained it to me.
We're not going to
let Alex kill Hrach.
- Well, that's a relief.
- We're going to do it ourselves...
...or at least provide
a reasonable facsimile.
All we need is a body.
What do you want now, the keys to the
morgue? When does this stop?
When we take
Alex down.
Look, the only way
to nail him...
...is to catch him
paying us off for the hit.
I'm pulling the plug.
Alex needs to see a body.
I mean, showing him a picture of
some uni in Halloween makeup...
...isn't going to cut it.
If this ends in anything
but total success...
...you can join him on Vice.
What the hell's
he talking about?
Who knows?
It's a little
clammy in here.
- You'll get used to it, Manny.
- I won't need to.
You fronted Richard Cummings
money for a restaurant...
...that closed after two weeks, right?
I don't lend money.
I'm not a loan shark.
Cummings never paid you back.
Why would he? I never
lent him a dime.
Lance Hinkle also owed you money...
A fortune.
Don't know a Hinkle.
You clear his debt.
He helps you kill Cummings.
Sell it to the Grimms Brothers.
I've got your lies on record.
Now sit there...
...while I prove them wrong.
Take Bob and Marcy.
They lived next door to the victim.
He had a prior for kidnapping, liked
young women. I should have seen it.
Could you concentrate
on this case, please?
I'm using it to illuminate this case.
Excuse me.
It was Hinkle's gun.
Hinkle doesn't have an alibi.
It should
be Hinkle.
Hinkle's got nothing to do with
Cummings or the restaurant.
What about the dead guy's wife?
Maybe she and Hinkle, having an
affair, want the husband dead.
The widow's got no insurance money.
She's not involved.
It's worth
checking out.
Look... I've got a suspect.
His name is Manny Sandoval.
And I'm bringing him in.
I'm having a hard time explaining why
we're backing you for city council...
...when you seem to be
wholly unconcerned...
...with our community's needs.
What are we talking
about here?
A gang member died in a
drive-by shooting this week.
His gang has demanded a funeral mass
at his family's church...
...but our new reverend
refused on principle.
Since then, the church
has been vandalized...
...and he has received death threats.
That's unacceptable.
A community's strength
stems from its leaders...
...especially its spiritual ones.
I'll assign a protection detail
immediately.
Just got a suicide call. White
male, 20s, just blew his head off.
Perfect. I'm going to need
your clothes and your wallet.
What the hell is this?
We found our candidate.
- Who?
- Some guy.
What guy? Where?
Dead guy. No face, no
relatives, no problem.
- I'm coming with.
- Sure. We'll meet you there.
- What's the address?
- I think Cacuzza's got it.
They're setting up.
All right.
Set the camera up in here.
Alex is on his way.
We got 15 minutes, tops.
You know what? We'll...
We'll take it from here.
Yes. We're not done
with the investigation.
Time to swap out the clothes.
- You said he blew his face off!
- That's what I was told!
What did he do, miss?
He's totally recognizable!
Jesus Christ.
He's going to be here any minute.
God.
All right. Go... Go to my car
and get my shotgun.
- What?
- Just do it!
Don't worry.
You won't feel a thing.
- I'll walk the neighborhood.
- What should I do?
Stop anyone
from killing the reverend.
Try to keep me in sight.
Excuse me. What are you doing?
- Hi, Officer.
- Hi.
- What are you doing?
- I know this looks weird...
...but I'm a volunteer coach
for a kids' soccer team.
- Yes. I see that.
- Well...
One of them found a squirrel
by the side of the road.
It was the only way
to get him to stop crying.
I promised to send it
to squirrel heaven.
Okay. Well, that's not really legal.
Well, I didn't know
what else to do.
I just wanted Jordan
to feel better.
Well, that's sweet. Okay.
Bury it deep.
Thanks.
You want to give
him the face-lift?
I'll pass.
Pussy.
You're not here to realize it...
...but you're doing a good thing.
Yes. That's better.
Okay. Camera's got signal.
- God.
- Where've you been?
He gives you the money.
You give the signal. You get out.
And hear me... this is it.
Understand?
Sure.
When he gets the money, we go...
On my mark.
Got it.
- We got to go.
- Thank you, sir.
One of them yours?
No. I used to play.
Bye.
No. Most of these kids
don't have fathers.
That's very nice.
We have a game on Sunday.
Maybe if you're not working
you could stop by.
Yes, I'm free on Sunday.
Great.
You killed him yourself.
Yes. He got a little squirrelly.
We're going to have to
charge you extra...
...for saving
you the trouble.
All right. Here we go.
How much do you
think he told them?
We can find out.
He was very involved
in a lot of my businesses.
He knew a lot of things.
Perhaps you can help
with some protection.
Get ready.
- Hold! Hold! Don't do this to me.
- Holding.
Like with what?
Let's talk someplace else.
I'd like to know if any more
of my places are going to be raided.
Give me the addresses.
I'll check 'em out at my station.
It'll take a couple hours.
That's delicate information to give to
a police officer that I barely know.
Fine.
If you need me some other time,
give me a call.
Wait.
Hagop.
Hagop knows the addresses.
He'll go with you.
- Works for me.
- And he'll stay here.
It's insurance, you know? You have
one of my men. I have one of your men.
Make sure he doesn't catch anything.
- See you soon.
- Yes.
We believe one of these men
killed Richard.
Claudette, I didn't see his face.
He was running.
Take a look.
I'm sorry. I just...
I didn't see a face.
- It was nine months ago.
- It's okay.
There's one thing I don't understand.
The night your husband was killed,
you were home alone with him?
That's right.
You have two small children.
It was a Wednesday night,
middle of the school week.
Why weren't they in the house?
Their grandmother takes them
ice-skating on Wednesday nights.
They sleep over,
and then she drops them at school.
It would be interesting
if the killer...
...knew the kids wouldn't
be in the house.
Fewer possible
witnesses...
Or maybe to spare
them the trauma...
...which is odd unless the
killer knew them personally.
- Are you saying that I...
- Excuse me.
Come here.
What the hell are you doing?
Pursuing an angle
of investigation.
By attacking my witness?
She's not much
of a witness.
That's right. She's the victim.
I cleared her nine months ago.
You cleared her of any connection
to Manny. What about Hinkle?
She's not in this.
- Maybe it's just that simple.
- Goddamn it.
She's not Marcy.
Now, you screwed up your case.
Fine. It happens.
But don't screw up mine.
Take that back.
Later.
Right now, I'm handling this case.
Alone.
Cummings's wife saw you
outside the house...
...the night you
killed her husband.
She just positively ID'd you.
You're done.
Hinkle spilled his guts
like a cheap pinata.
How you'd excuse the vig on his loan
in exchange for killing Cummings.
Not the principle, though.
You're a piece of work.
It's his word against mine.
Believe me. When he's on that stand,
and his little girl's there...
...and he's bawling like a baby...
...they're going to believe
every word he says.
I don't need a confession.
Take him.
Let's go.
They could still be undercover.
They could be doing God knows...
Never mind.
Nothing. I guess he didn't
squeal on that one.
What's the next address?
4103 Merrick.
And this is?
Cigarettes, tax-free.
Well, your smokers can cough up
their lungs in peace. Next address.
This one's not really anything...
...but since we're here,
check it anyway.
Sure. Give
it to me.
9210 Escovida.
And this is?
Not sure. Storage or something.
- It's clear.
- Where the hell you been?
I'm working on another case.
What'd you expect?
You disappeared.
Where's Shane?
He's working on that hooker
sting I told you about.
Hooker sting? What do they have you
doing now, entrapping johns?
He's just talking with them.
Might bring in a few of them later.
Well, you're supposed to
check in every two hours.
Make sure you do.
Asshole's just trying to keep his job.
It's pathetic. Next?
Hrach?
- Hagop?
- Shit.
You're alive.
- What's going on?
- You need help here?
All right. Let's go.
What time were you supposed
to check in with Alex?
What happens to Shane if you don't?
I'm out. I'm out.
I beat him anyway.
Instead of playing poker,
we should be playing poke her.
- Want to play another one?
- Yes.
In exactly 10 seconds
go to the john.
Now say, "wrong
number" and hang up.
Wrong number.
Tell you what. This gypsy swill
just goes right through me.
Be right back.
Stay still.
Everybody down! Come on! Everybody!
Down! On the floor!
- Get down on the ground!
- You get on the floor! Get down!
- You too!
- Get your hands up!
Lace your hands, put your palms
on top of your head. Do it!
Alex Eznik, you're under arrest.
Shane! Take him. Shane!
- Shane!
- Yes.
How 'bout next time I save your ass?
That's a date.
- Anything I need to know?
- Nothing at all.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Hi. I'm burying a hamster.
Did you just pay that kid for it?
No. I gave him some money
so that he could go buy a new one.
Okay. You know what? I'm going to
have to write you up for this.
- No. You don't.
- Yes. I do.
- Look. It's really not...
- Shut up.
Jesus Christ.
All right, ladies.
Move it along. Come on. Let's go.
- Nice bust.
- It's not over yet.
Once these goons lawyer up,
the word'll get out...
...and those places will be cleared
out before we can hit 'em.
So let's move now. Give me the
specifics. I'll send units.
We got a chop
shop on Newman.
Cigarette stash on Merrick.
A few others.
Something mysterious
on Escovida.
We'll check
that out.
Something to do with
the money train?
It's probably just a jerk-off.
We'll let you know.
Do you think
that's the money train?
I got a pretty good feeling.
So it is real.
What do you want to do?
At the bar, when I didn't answer her
questions, she called me names.
Why didn't you report this earlier?
I don't know.
I didn't know my rights.
But you do now.
Mr. Ibish, do you remember
Officer Lowe?
- Yes.
- I remember you too.
My first week on the job.
He resisted arrest, became violent.
My partner exercised
great restraint.
- Did Danny use any racial epithets?
- No, sir.
But Mr. Ibish used one or two
towards me.
He's lying. He's covering for her.
You all do that.
What did Mr. Hamad offer you
to come forward with this story?
If he's retracting his statements now,
it's a surprise to me.
You told him that if he
filed a complaint,...
...you'd represent him for
free in his own civil suit.
That was predicated on
his story being true.
There was no quid pro
quo for him to lie.
Well, either way,
your case ends here.
Our case doesn't
depend on him.
I'm here to discuss
your counteroffer.
Well, here it is. Nothing.
Her own partner won't
corroborate her story.
He doesn't contradict
it either.
We have a wrongful entry...
...an innocent man,
and a grieving widow.
And I've got a
decorated officer...
...who's fighting to keep this city
safe during very troubled times.
I look forward to a jury
settling this.
We'll be in touch.
Washington, Oregon,
Arizona, Nevada.
This isn't just L.A. money.
This is the whole goddamn West Coast.
Holy shit.
First the head of the Zeroun family,
then this.
Aceveda's going to be
licking our scrotums for weeks.
I'll call... I'll call for backup.
- No.
- What?
- We're going to let it go.
- Why?
We're going to let it go.
Get over here.
- Tell that bitch you lied.
- What?
Tell her you made it up because
you owed me money, wanted to get even.
I can't lie anymore.
I got you to take
out Cummings.
You don't think I can arrange
to have your daughter be next?
Use your head.
I didn't need a confession.
But it doesn't hurt.
Vic. We hit the mother lode.
Credit cards, digital cameras,
phony passports.
- What did you find?
- Nothing.
You're the only one
who came up empty?
A case of frostbite,
but, no money train.
You think he gave you
the wrong information?
Either that or it never existed.
What's the matter?
Cage not full enough for you?
So you won't mind
if I check it out.
Why would I mind?
Good work today.
Good enough to get
a chit with you?
What kind
of chit?
I'll take a minority onto my team,
but I get to keep Shane.
He's suspended for a week...
...and I get approval
of the new team member.
And I get to approve your approval.
I can live with that.
Then I guess we start lookin'.
I take it back.
No need to. You were right.
Let me buy you a little dinner.
A detective can't personalize
his investigations.
I'm... I'm not really very hungry.
Hrach says the money train
moves every couple of months.
Where does it go?
Next time?
Right into our pockets.
There's a lot of unknowns.
Well, we can do it right...
Be extra careful...
Take our time.
You can't really be talkin'
about making off...
...with the Armenian mob's
entire Western U.S. kitty.
Goddamn Eastern Euros can't
keep track of their own plutonium.
You think I'm going to trust 'em
with our cold hard cash?
Mr. Hamad dropped my case.
One big city against just me now.
Mrs. Al-Thani, please. I don't want to
have to put you under arrest.
You! Zayed was a good man!
He would never shoot you!
And we sympathize
with your loss.
If you did, you would have
signed those papers...
...and given me peace
and a chance for my baby.
Come. Come here.
He will never know his father
because of you.
I'll never forget what you do.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Justice will find you.
Now, you have a king.
She only has a four...
...which means you can take her cards.
See? These cards go over here.
Go ahead.
Move these cards over here.
- Matthew?
- You just have to show him, Dad.
Here.
Birthday cake? Vic.
Well, it's somebody's
birthday... somewhere.
It's time to get ready for bed.
Come on.
Go brush your teeth,
put on your p.j's.
I'm not tired.
You heard your mom. I'll be in
in a second to read you a story.
Go on.
Megan went right to sleep.
No problem.
How are you
feeling?
A little stiff. I'm
okay, not too bad.
First day back at work was good.
It's a little early, isn't it?
These doctors. If they could,
they'd put you on bed rest...
...until you got something else
they could charge you for.
You seemed pretty anxious
to get back.
- I have a lot to do.
- It's just that...
...before you got hurt, you...
...you said you'd leave the house.
You promised.
I know.
If you're good enough
to go back to work...
Soon as you can find a place.
What can I do for ya?
- I need a room.
- Yes.
You know what? That's fine.
Here, just write your name
and your police division.
Is this about
the people across the street?
- I can't say.
- Okay. Yes. That's...
I understand.
I tell ya. The things
he does to her...
It's a sin.
Why don't you give me a room
with a view across the street?
You know, I might be staying awhile.