Last season on The Shield:
Your turn to play bad cop?
Good cop and bad cop
left for the day.
I'm a different kinda cop.
You're the police!
What's your take
on Vic Mackey?
I don't judge other cops.
Mackey's not a cop.
He's Al Capone with a badge.
You suggestin' Mackey's
working for a drug dealer?
I'm suggesting the drug
dealer's working for Mackey...
...and I want you to
help me prove it.
What are you gettting
out of this?
I just want a dirty
cop off the street.
You wanna be mayor some day,...
...you better learn how to lie a hell
of a lot better than that.
Terry was gonna turn you in,
so Vic wanted him dead.
-Vic needed him dead.
-No!
We killed a cop.
Until now I've tolerated you.
Come near my men again...
I'm gonna lose patience.
I know what you did.
You're not gonna believe what just
went down between Aceveda and Mackey.
Anyone gets between those two...
...is just gonna end up with a hose
full of piss running down his leg.
After all the problems we had...
...I thought the one thing that...
...I could count on was the fact
that you had a good heart.
-I'm not gay.
-Julien...
I push it down it goes away,
but it comes back stronger.
Why are you a better deal
for me than Rondell?
I don't use my own product.
Rondell does, more and more.
If I'm done fillin' out
the job application,...
...let's talk about how
much rent's gonna be.
50 grand lets you move in right away.
-Some leaked the 911 tapes.
-Shit.
We got a situation brewing.
Pack bags for you and the kids now.
You're not staying here.
What are you talking about?
This is our house.
It isn't safe.
-What are you mixed up in?
-Corrine...
This doesn't happen to other cops'
families. Tell me the truth.
What are you doing that's worth
making us go into hiding?
I went by the hotel.
Your family's gone, man.
Corrine! Cassidy!
I know you'll wanna find us.
If you still have love for me,
you won't, you won't try.
No!
I sent Corrine's picture to hotels
with weekly and monthly rates.
Night manager called
when he got the fax.
Said she checked in about a week ago
as a... Jan Murphy?
Which room?
She's not alone up there, Vic.
-I know. She's got my kids with her.
-No kids.
There's someone else.
Ran the plates.
Guy's name is Steven Linfield.
He owns a yoga studio.
She's probably takin'
classes with him.
When my gash of an ex-wife
ditched me, first thing she did...
...was got that ass real tight.
Manager said the guy's
been up there every night.
Which room?
It's 209. Vic, wait.
Wait.
Vic, don't... don't do this.
What the...
What do you want?
Who are you?
I'm s...
I don't know. I...
Manager confirmed two different
photos, swore it was her.
You've been on this
thing for a month.
You can't find three
kids and a housewife?
No money trail.
The kids haven't been in school.
She's not with friends
or relatives.
Look, if we don't expand
our search beyond So. Cal.
You know, maybe I should...
...check hospitals, accident
reports...
Look, they're alive.
Just find them.
Come on. Hurry up.
Fresh from Mexico.
Still has its cherry.
Crack the seal.
Two shipments in a week.
That's not bad.
-We're pregnant.
-Beautiful.
Wrap it up.
We'll follow you home.
You know, when we
double up on shipments,...
...sooner or later
someone's gonna notice.
Hey, Vic put me in charge, all right?
It's working, okay?
So just roll with it.
Christ. Couple of salties.
-They're gonna roust 'em.
-What do we do if they find that coke?
That's 50 grand each, gone.
Three black guys with a
trunk full of cocaine...
...can't drive the
goddamn speed limit?
Great.
-I knew this was a mistake.
-Shut up. Let me think.
Hey, you're in charge.
Hey, we're in this together.
Hey, lookee here, Clark.
Don't shoot!
-Keep your hands where I can see 'em.
-I'm a brother cop.
It's all right.
It's cool. We're cops.
Here you go.
Look, you're not
gonna believe this,...
...but you just nailed
my informant.
We're on our way to a bust.
That's our coke.
-Who's in charge of the sting?
-Mackey's our team leader.
I'll give him a call
and get him down here.
-Who's your C.O.?
-Aceveda.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna call him too.
Sure, if you don't mind
waking up a captain.
I don't mind.
Burning necklaces
have been gaining popularity...
...in Central and South American
drug cartels.
Only a matter of time
before se mueve al Norte.
South Africa's A.N.C. also
used tire necklaces...
...to torture and kill impimpi.
-Impimpi?
-Police informants.
-And since when do you speak Spanish?
-I'm taking a class.
I work in Los Angeles.
Not knowing the language
was limiting me...
...from being the best
detective I could be.
Hiya. I'm Detective Vic Mackey.
-These your men?
-Depends.
What'd they do?
We pulled over these guys,
found some weapons...
...and a sizable amount of cocaine.
-These guys say it's for a buy-bust.
-That's right.
They were supposed to
meet me over in Farmington.
Nobody notified our department.
We're waiting on a Captain Aceveda
to clear things up.
It's not necessary. We're
late as it is. By the time...
Aceveda shows up...
What's going on?
We pulled over these men
with several kilos of cocaine.
I was gonna give you a heads-up.
They claim they're on
their way to a bust...
...you authorized in Farmington.
I didn't forward the C-90.
I take responsibility.
Apologize to your C.O. for me.
I guarantee it won't happen again.
Sure. Sorry to hold you guys up.
No, no. You were right to call me.
Look, I'm sorry about...
-You're on your way to a bust, right?
-Yes, sir.
-Then go arrest someone.
You and I need to talk...
...now.
Hey, thanks for cutting us some slack
on that little paperwork snafu.
You've been logging less hours.
Arrests are way down.
Bad guys must be hibernating.
-Is everything okay with you?
-Sure.
Because you're a lot of things,
but sloppy isn't one of them.
Why don't you just give me
a demerit and call it a night?
A civilian auditor's
been assigned to the barn.
She gets a whiff
of what I've been smelling lately...
...she's gonna slam a lid
on this whole place.
Well, that's your problem.
I don't think she'll
be as understanding...
...of your paperwork snafus as I am
which makes it our problem.
This drug business tonight...
Shane and the boys are out
making arrests as we speak.
You better find your game,
and you better find it quick.
I never lost it.
The two victims have been I.D.'d as
Pablo Fernando and Christopher Reyes.
Street names are
Bang Bang and Cuca.
We got two dead bangers,
two different gang affiliations.
A Los Mag and a Toro.
Both high-level lieutenants
in the drug racket.
You can understand why they'd
want to kill each other.
Who'd want to kill 'em both?
-Well, that's the mystery, isn't it?
-Keep an eye out for the tag.
Talk to your contacts.
Find out what's brewing.
Maybe it would help
to recreate the crime.
Dios mio! I'm burning!
Hey, hey, Smitty.
Get these two to the morgue A.S.A.P.
Just a reminder: Lanie
Kellis will begin...
...observing activities
today in the barn.
She's a civilian auditor.
I know, but there was a riot...
the whole Gilroy scandal.
You can't expect the city council
to do nothing.
Say hello to fall guy number one
and fall guy number two.
Hey, why are you
turning in Tio's stash?
It's not Tio's coke.
-It's theirs.
-They had that much blow on 'em?
-I thought they were small-time.
-They were until tonight.
I see you've made some arrests.
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
Finish the paperwork, return
the coke to Property,...
...and move on to your next case.
Yes, sir.
That's a ton of weight.
Did he say who's running 'em?
-Alvarez.
-Well, we better go talk to him...
...find out why he's moving
from the minors to the majors.
Goddamn it. What now? Yeah?
Tio, I don't like being here.
What's the problem?
That.
He's puking up blood, man.
What the hell did you call us for?
Like I'm gonna call a bunch
of paramedics to my drug crib.
-Jesus Christ.
-What the hell's wrong with him?
I don't know, man.
He looks like he's gonna die.
Well, did he eat something?
He snuck a few lines
just to check the stuff out.
Snuck a few lines?
What did I say about that?
Is he allergic?
Man, he's going
into cardiac arrest.
Shit. Get me a towel.
Towel, towel!
Shit.
Come on.
God, it's beating.
We gotta get him to a hospital quick.
Drop him off.
Don't answer any questions.
Just get the hell out of there.
-Move.
-Hurry up.
Jesus...
How much did he do?
Just a couple lines.
He's not allergic.
Was he mixing?
Maybe the coke's bad.
The coke is not bad.
It's fine.
Tio just needs to step
on it a little more.
You're so sure. Do a line.
Have the lab run a sample.
See if someone spiked it.
Yeah.
Who's gonna mess with my stash?
Somebody with enough product
to step in.
Asshole, 12:00.
Hey, Alvarez.
-You're out early.
-What do you want, man?
Tell me something.
How does a pissant
crack dealer like you...
...suddenly start carrying heavy
weights of high-grade coke?
-I'm clean, brother.
-We picked up a couple of your guys.
Who gave you the coke?
Who's trying to push their way in?
I don't know what
you're talkin' about, man.
Let's see if a car ride
jogs your memory.
I guess you don't get to visit
One-niner territory that often...
you being natural enemies and all.
Hey, Mo!
Your sister's ass really taste as
sweet as Alvarez here says it does?
He wants to know what your mama's
putting in the corn muffins.
Excuse me?
-You messing with Tio's coke shipment?
-What? No.
Who gave you the drugs?
You don't help me out, you're
gonna have to find another ride.
Hope those $ 100 pair of
Cortezes help him run faster.
-All right. The Quintero brothers.
-Never heard of'em.
Armadillo and Navaro.
They're from Tijuana.
They told me to get ready
to flood the streets with blow.
They think they can just come
into Farmington and take over?
-I guess so.
-Guessed wrong.
Hey, get me out of here, man.
Get out of the way!
Claudette? Your dead guys
may have been cooked up...
-...by a couple of Mexican nationals.
-You got some names?
One. Quintero.
They're brothers...
Navaro and Armadillo.
-See that guy with Vic?
-Yeah.
He's been in a few times lately.
Any idea who he is?
Nope.
He had to sign in at
the front desk, right?
-That's the policy.
-You wanna check the log?
Love to.
I'm part of a network
of private investigators.
For a fee, I can get
your wife's info out...
...to over 200 P.I.s
throughout the U.S.
How much?
For 20 grand,
I can get to half the agencies.
It's good coverage, but less bodies.
Things are gonna move slower.
How much to make things
move faster?
50 grand will cover
the entire network.
If she's anywhere in the free 52,
we'll find her fast.
-Do it.
-They don't get started...
...unless they have half
the fee up front.
I need 25K, like, now.
You'll have your money in an hour.
Who would have wanted
to kill your brother?
-You know who Cuca was?
-Drug lieutenant for the Toros.
He was killed along with his
counterpart from Los Mags.
-Were they doing business together?
-Don't know.
Your brother was
burned to death.
Is there anything you do
know that can help us?
-Nope.
-Mrs. Reyes?
Does the name Armadillo
or Navaro mean anything?
Armadillo?
Mayda doesn't know
anything about this.
None of us do.
Again...
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Hey, what's up?
I need to make an emergency withdrawal
from our retirement fund.
You got the key, right?
Vic, there's nothing in there.
-You gotta be joking me.
-No, we took it.
Me, Lemon and Ronnie,
we took it to invest.
Without telling me?
You put me in charge while
you were taking time off.
A quarter of that stash is mine.
And I'm in the process
of tripling it for you.
It was... It was
gonna be a surprise.
It is. A bad one.
Look, I've been giving this thing
a lot of thought.
Yeah? And what's your plan, exactly?
I've been stepping up shipments.
I've been overseeing distribution.
Distribution?
We're middlemen
keeping the peace,...
...not drug dealers.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm not doing anything
that we weren't doing before.
-I'm just bumping things up a level.
-Well, what level is that?
Prison?
All right.
Where's my investment now?
It's all tied up in the coke shipment.
That coke that had Tio's guy
bleeding from every orifice?
-We don't know that that was the coke.
-I need that money.
Yeah?
Well, we all do.
No, I need it now
to get back my kids.
-What are you talking about?
-They're gone, Shane!
Corrine took 'em and disappeared.
What? When?
-Five weeks ago. God.
-Jesus.
And I need 25 grand right now
to find them.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-You screwed me!
I didn't...
I didn't screw you.
I was just trying to
make things up to you.
Goddamn it!
I didn't know!
-I lose my family, and now this?
-I didn't know.
-What am I supposed to do now?
-If I'd known, I'd never...
What am I supposed to do?
Cuca's friends say
you were his girlfriend.
You left him for Armadillo?
No.
Jessica Hintel...
...senior at the Wedney
School for Girls.
Father's chiropractor
to the stars in Bel Air.
How does your father feel about you...
...trading down from
Westside cheerleader...
-...to barrio gang babe?
-That angel tattoo on your face...
He must love seeing that
in the family Christmas cards.
It's a dove.
Two weeks ago...
Cuca and I were
walking down Olympic.
Armadillo and a few of his guys
came up to us...
...and asked Cuca
if he had changed his mind...
...and Cuca said no.
Armadillo took me...
...away from Cuca...
...to his house.
He told me to take my clothes off.
When he'd finished with me...
...he held me down
while another one gave me this tattoo.
A dove...
...to remember him by, he said.
When I went back to Cuca...
...and he saw the tattoo...
...he called me puta.
He wouldn't touch me anymore.
Can you have my dad
pick me up, please?
God. I fell asleep.
Yeah.
What are you gonna tell your wife?
She's out of town.
This is, like, the
fifth time this month.
Is it?
We're not wrecking something
that's working, are we?
Nah. We won't let it
turn into a thing.
Good, 'cause
I don't mind a thing. I just...
I just don't want a thing.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, sure.
Hey.
I'll see you around.
Sit down.
The coke's worthless. It's got
rosary pea mixed in it. It's poison.
-Well, he tested it.
-For coke.
Not if it was any good.
If this shit hit the street...
God knows how many bodies
we'd be picking up.
I'm telling you, man. That seal
was intact. These guys saw it.
-You messed with it beforehand.
-I'm a customs guy, for Chrissake.
I was making money
off this stuff too.
If somebody screwed with it,
it happened on the Mexican side.
Well, who handles things
on the Mexican side?
It's, Rosalina Imports in Tijuana.
It's a front for some
guy named Navaro.
Navaro Quintero?
Yeah, yeah. That's him.
Jesus Christ.
These guys are up my ass.
Better come out here!
I got the other P.I.s started on it.
You got the dough?
Not yet.
There's a problem.
These guys only started
without the deposit as a favor to me.
You gotta front me.
You'll have the money soon.
-It doesn't work like that.
-You make it work.
Just keep 'em looking.
I don't have that
kind of cash on hand.
Gordie.
These are my kids, man.
Please.
I'll tell 'em the
money's coming tonight.
Thank you.
But this is my reputation, Vic.
You don't have that cash
in my hands by 10:00 tonight...
I'm pulling them off the case,
and I'm off it too.
Ditch your weapons. We're headed south
to get our money back from Navaro.
-What?
-Just do as I say... for once!
Vic, we've been looking for you.
I'd like to introduce you
to Lanie Kellis.
-I'm a little busy right now.
-Miss Kellis is our civilian auditor.
There's some things I'd like
to talk to you about.
I gotta go.
Don't worry.
I'll handle this.
What the hell are you doing?
-I don't have time for this.
-Why? And where are you going?
-Tijuana.
-Mexico? What for?
Someone's putting poisoned
coke out on our streets.
I'm gonna stop 'em.
Well, you don't have
jurisdiction across the border.
-Well, I'm taking the day off.
-I'm not authorizing it.
Well, if you want dozens of potential
voters keeling over dead...
...so be it,
but I'm taking the day off.
Hi. What's the nature
of your visit to Mexico?
Little bit of everything.
Go ahead.
Welcome to Mexico.
Okay, get out.
Go find some guns.
-They got gun stores?
-It's Tijuana. Use your imagination.
Got it.
If we find him, we'll call you up.
Where the hell is Calle Mar Campio?
Come on. Nice girls.
Come on. Come on.
Come in, inside, with girls, nice.
Nice ones. Come on.
-Come over here please.
-Let's go.
Rosalina Imports.
It might as well read "dead end."
-Now what?
-Goddamn it!
Police.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. We're just
looking for someone.
We're police too, from L.A.
You should be more careful.
This part of town isn't
so tourist-friendly.
-A lot of muggings.
-Yeah. Kidnappings too.
A friend of mine's sister
got nabbed here two days ago.
I am sorry to hear that.
Did your friend file a report?
We'd rather pay the ransom
and get her back.
We're looking for
a Navaro Quintero.
Navaro.
I'm not surprised.
He and his brother
are our biggest problem.
Your own government has
a federal warrant for Navaro.
But as long as he's on
our side of the border...
Look, you know where
we can find him?
-Where are we goin'?
-To get your guns.
Keep following.
You know, this place could
be nothing but casinos...
...and poontang,
and white-sand beaches.
Instead, look at it. It's the
goddamn asshole of South America.
Mexico's in Central America.
Hey, man, where the hell
are these guns?
Right here.
Where is your money?
Yeah! Your money!
Come on.
This is bullshit.
Shit, man. Goddamn it.
Give it.
Come on! Give it!
Come on.
Now get out.
Get out!
-Detective Wagonback?
-Wagenbach.
Sorry.
Lanie Kellis, civilian auditor.
Right. Hi.
I understand that you were
the lead detective...
...in Assistant Chief Gilroy's case.
Yes, I was.
The hit-and-run or the
land fraud scheme?
Knee-deep in both.
Could I get a look
at your personal notes on that case?
His bail hearing's
coming in a few weeks,...
...and I want to make sure...
-...that nothing surprises us.
-I'm certainly the man...
...to, get you that file.
I'll get it to you as soon as I can.
-Thanks. I appreciate the help.
-Mayda.
You forgot your notebook.
-Thank you.
-Did you catch him?
-Who?
-Armadillo.
He's the one who
killed my brother.
Armadillo,
he came to the house one day.
He told Cuca
he could join him, or he could die.
He said that with you in the room?
He kept looking at me,
like he was trying to scare me...
...but I'm not afraid
of him like Topo is.
Hey, sweetie, how you doin'?
-Dutch.
-Be right back.
-What's she doing here?
-She came in on her own.
Where's the mother?
The brother?
You're interviewing a minor
without a guardian present.
She implicates Armadillo directly.
He made threats to Cuca
right in front of her.
What exactly are we supposed to do
with all that information?
Put her in front of a grand jury,
arrest this guy.
If she can lead us
in the right direction, great.
But her family doesn't
want her to testify.
She wants to testify.
-And her family doesn't.
-So?
So if you had kids,
you'd understand.
-Mayda?
-Yes?
Hey, come with me, baby.
I'm gonna take you home.
I lost my barrette.
I'll get you a new one.
-Is something wrong?
-No. I'm gonna take you home.
Are you going to arrest Armadillo?
We are gonna try.
You're a brave girl for helping us.
I know.
Only two guys. You'd think he'd have
more firepower around him.
Probably thinks no one's
crazy enough to mess with him.
Great. We're after
the ugly one up high.
Give me a piece.
We had a little
problem with the guns.
-What kind of problem?
-Montezuma's revenge.
Shit. They're leaving.
We gotta go.
What? They're packin'!
-Boss, this is nuts, man.
-Ronnie, go get the car.
Shane, Lem, you take the two big guys.
Take their guns.
I'll take el feo.
Easy, easy.
Hey, can you tell me where
the donkey shows are around here?
Up against the wall!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
-He's here! Come on!
-Don't even think about it.
-Come on!
-Okay.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
-Here you go.
-You got my boy in here?
-Randall?
-Are you his mother?
-Yes. Why is he locked up?
-Buzz her in, John.
-What did he do?
-A hardware store owner...
...caught him shoplifting
some spray paint.
No.
He says he's seen
him and his friends...
...tagging other buildings
in the neighborhood.
Is that true?
Did you steal?
You vandalizing now?
We don't usually bring
them in this young,...
...but we couldn't get
ahold of you...
...and this guy's pretty adamant
about pressing charges.
Look, I cut back on my hours,
so I could be home nights.
I am active in his school.
We go to church...
...and still he does this.
What else can I do?
Let me see if I can help.
-She's pretty upset.
-She should be.
He's only ten, and already
he's racking and tagging.
Next, it'll be armed robbery.
Before you know it, we'll be
mopping him off a sidewalk.
The mother's doing the
best that she can.
I think I can make a difference here.
Julien, come on. You want me
to tell you how this story ends?
Okay, fine.
Knock yourself out.
Who knows?
Maybe it could do some good.
I ain't payin'you nothin', ese.
-Really?
-You let me go right now...
I'll let you get back
across that border alive.
Toss me one of them.
This what your brother Armadillo
does to people who don't cooperate?
You're not cooperating!
Douse him.
Last chance.
How much money are
we talking about, man?
Three-fifty, American.
I can do that.
-Plus 50 for ruining my day.
-Come on, Vic. Don't push it.
Shut the hell up!
Armadillo Quintero?
Yes?
You're a hard man to find.
We'd like to talk to you.
What are you doing
in Los Angeles, Armando?
You mind if I call you Armando?
I have a hard time...
...keeping a straight face when I hear
the name "Armadillo."
I'm looking for
new opportunities.
Those opportunities include...
...moving the Toros and the Los Mags
out of the drug business?
It's a little early
in the interrogation...
...to be showing all your cards.
Where do you go now
when I say...
"I don't know who the Toros
or Los Mags are"?
Our house, our rules.
This hasn't always
been your house.
This used to be Mexico.
And I've been reading
about your rules.
Yes, we saw the law
books at your place.
You could only keep me
here for six hours...
...without charging me with a crime.
You're a prime suspect in the fire
murders of two men last night.
-We can hold you for 24 hours.
-And I can provide many people...
...who will be happy to say
I was with them...
...when this awful crime took place.
Six hours.
You're not here to fight
the Toros and the Los Mags.
You're here to unite 'em.
One gang, one leader: you.
Uniting the Toros and the Los Mags?
Come on. Think about it.
They stop pissing
on each other...
...and turn their guns on everyday
folks... it's not good.
-So how do we keep him here?
-The girlfriend won't testify.
Mayda will.
I'm not putting a 12-year-old
girl in the middle of this.
Not with him involved.
We'll find another way.
Here, man.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Keep it to yourself.
All right. No guns, no games.
Drop your guns on the ground!
Okay.
What are you doing?
Jesus Christ!
Let's toss him!
-Anybody hit?
-No, man.
Holy shit.
I just leased this car!
What are we doin'?
He's got a federal warrant.
If the feds want him,
I say we let him start doin' his time.
We can't make arrests in Mexico.
Once we get him back home,
won't matter how he got there.
This is insane! His buddies are
out looking for us right now!
We got our money.
Let's just dump him and go.
This prick was willing
to poison dozens of strangers.
If we leave him here, you think
he won't come lookin' for payback?
How we supposed to get
him across the border?
In the trunk.
Same as the money.
That's if we even make it to
the border! Look at the car!
How am I gonna pay for this?
He'll be kicking and
screaming the whole way.
There's 20 farmacias on every block.
We'll go and get a bottle of roofies.
What, the date rape drug?
Don't pretend like you don't
know what they look like.
We're gettin' 'em.
Armando was an orphan,
lived on the streets.
I spoke to a woman who
was a social worker years ago.
On a hunch, she gave him
an I.Q. test at age 11.
Score off the charts.
She managed to get him into a
school for gifted children.
-He lasted a week and a half.
-Didn't fit in?
He raped and beat his teacher.
When he was 11?
Two years in Sinaloa juvie,
back on the street after that.
If he hasn't been caught since,
he's gotten a lot smarter.
I'll call I.N.S., see if the rape's
a violation of his visa requirements.
-Do you have that file for me?
-I'll get it to you soon.
When I ask for something, I ask
politely because that's my nature.
But when you make me ask a
second time, I lose my patience.
This squad has been the epicenter
of police corruption...
...civil lawsuits,
and most recently a riot.
The people I work for want answers.
They expect me to get them.
I have the power to recommend changes,
get people fired...
...even shut down this entire building
if it's warranted.
Do you understand
what I'm saying, Detective?
Yes, ma'am.
Good. If you could
get me the Gilroy file...
-...I would really appreciate it.
-Sure.
Thank you.
-Man.
-Shut up.
How do we explain
400 grand in cash...
...and a doped-out
drug lord in our trunk?
Nobody breaks a sweat,
we won't have to.
Come on, boy. Search.
Any sign of Detective Mackey?
He's still in the field.
"In the field."
Is that code for "He
pretty much goes...
...wherever he wants without
any supervision"?
You're not after Mackey, are you?
You're after me.
I'm not after anyone.
-You have enemies on the city council.
-Who?
They're not thrilled that you
parlayed a scandal and a riot...
...into a 15-point lead
over Karen Mitchell.
17-point lead.
They take the heat.
They get bashed in the press.
While you come out
looking like a reformer?
-I'm gonna be a reformer.
-Not if you don't get elected.
I have a 17-point lead.
They're hoping I'll find
something that will change that.
They know I'll be fair,
but they also know...
...that if there's something to find,
I'll find it.
I'm glad you know.
Randall. The owner
left it up to me.
He won't press charges if I
vouch for you. Let's go.
Okay, tell me why
I should let you go.
I don't want to go to jail!
-I don't believe you.
-Henry and I needed some cans.
Henry? Henry who? Do I need to
arrest him too for coercion?
-No. I won't do it again.
-Are you sure?
Okay. I tell you what.
I'm gonna give you this one.
But remember, I'm vouching.
And if this happens again, you will
have to answer to your mother...
...and you will
have to answer to me!
-You got it?
-Yes, sir.
Go sit over there a minute.
-Is he gonna be okay?
-He'll think twice next time.
Thank you.
I'm so worried about him.
You are doing your best.
It's tough these days.
What church do you take him to?
-Faith Temple.
-I've heard good things about them.
I go to Covenant.
That's Reverend Cook.
Bad smoker, good man.
Yeah, that's him.
So, you gonna be home tonight?
I don't know. Why?
Because I'm not allowed to ask someone
out on a date while I'm on duty and...
Come by.
Maybe I'll be home.
Here you go.
Thanks.
-What's so funny?
-Nothing.
It's been six hours.
You're free to go.
I guess what I did
when I was 11...
...doesn't stop me from
visiting your country.
-Okay, stop right there.
-Okay, work it.
Come on, boy. Work it.
I.D.s, please, and can you
pop the trunk for me.
Sure. Busy day
for you guys?
Work it. Come on.
-You boys are cops?
-Farmington Division, L.A.
You guys have a rough
time on the other side?
Bachelor party.
Can barely remember
the last few days.
Pop the trunk for me, please.
Sure. The trunk latch is broke.
Sir, stay in the car, please.
-I will take the keys.
-Sure.
What happened back here?
We were in Rosarita.
Madame Marie introduced us
to some of her friends.
Came out this morning,
and it looked like that.
You boys are lucky
you got off with just a few stickers.
Yeah. Hey, you need
some help back there?
You're gonna need to
get rid of that wire.
I think I got some pliers
in here somewhere.
No, that's all right.
You guys have anything to declare?
Just that it's great
to be back in the States.
Welcome home.
-Get in there.
-Give me the Polaroid.
Quesadilla!
Just wanted to give your little
brother something to remember you by.
-It was creepy.
-How?
The way he laughed to himself,
like something happened.
He was sitting alone for an hour.
What could have happened?
-I don't know.
-Maybe he's just creepy.
No, he was reacting
to something.
-Ms. Kellis.
-Detective Mackey.
I'm really sorry about
hustling out on you earlier.
It did seem very abrupt.
Well, we had a tip about a
Mexican drug lord being in town.
Anyway, we just brought him in.
Got him just as he was about
to head back across the border.
Wanted by the feds on about 15
different counts. Pretty bad guy.
But I just wanted to sit with you
and answer a few of your questions.
It can wait until tomorrow.
Congratulations on the arrest.
-It's a team thing.
-So, we'll talk tomorrow.
I look forward to it,
Ms. Kellis.
Me too. And call me Lanie.
Unbelievable.
-Did anyone talk to him?
-Who?
Armadillo, when
he was in interrogation.
-Nobody was supposed to.
-You check the tapes?
What was that?
What is that?
It's Mayda's barrette.
God. He knows.
Tio found someone with
an emergency supply.
Enough to get him by till
the next shipment comes in.
-Give me the leftover cash.
-Here you go.
You know, even after
writing off the car,...
...we still come out
ahead on this deal.
Asking for 50 grand
for ruining your day was sweet, man.
-Give me your keys.
-What?
I can't trust you with them anymore,
so give 'em to me.
Come on.
Here you go.
-Where's Mayda?
-A friend's house. Why?
Call and check.
-Mayda came to talk to us.
-What?
-She told us about Armadillo.
-No. I told her not to!
We think he knows she spoke to us.
She never what?
She never showed up.
I'll make the call.
Where is she?
-He's gonna kill her!
-We'll find her.
Hey. You okay?
-Mayda...
-No!
-I'm here. It's okay.
-Topo, let us get her to a doctor!
Stop!
-Stay away from us!
-Stop!
Topo! Please!
Let us help her!
Topo, let us help her!
My guy in Denver got a hit
on Corrine's driver's license.
She got a warning
for rolling a stop sign last week.
-In Denver?
-Colorado Springs.
He tracked the license plate,
the address she gave.
Long story short...
...he took this photo
about three hours ago.
That's them, isn't it?
Yeah, that's them.
My guy lost 'em in traffic...
...but if they're shopping
for groceries there,...
...they gotta be close by.
We're gonna get 'em, Vic.
-Can I keep this?
-Yeah, sure.
I'll call you in a few.
Hey. I didn't know
you made house calls.
This P.I. you've been meeting with,
has he found them?
-Found who?
-Your family.
I assume if they were
here, your place...
...would be in a slightly
better condition.
At least now I know
what's been making you so sloppy.
By this time next year,
I'm gonna be on the city council.
In six years,
I'm gonna be mayor.
By then, I'll have
much bigger problems than you.
In the meantime,
how do we solve this problem?
-I don't see a problem.
-I do.
Her name's Lanie Kellis.
And as much as I'd love
to see her take you down,...
...I don't need a scandal right now.
So you and I need
to come to an understanding.
You and me? Right.
I don't see how
you have much choice.
You don't want her and me
gunning for you, right?
You're smart enough
to know that.
-You're gonna watch my back.
-Until the election.
In exchange for what?
You get your head
back in the game.
Get your boys under control,
and don't do anything to embarrass me.
How do I know I can trust you?
I guess we have a deal.
Fine.
This doesn't mean I like you.
Try to screw me on this...
I'll bury you.