Tonight, James gets wet.
An actual or spin
doctor on our track.
And the Stig laps a Reliant Robin.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE Hello.
Hello. Good evening. Hello.
Now...
Now, as we know, as we know, track
days these days are very popular.
The idea is that you drive
your own car to a race circuit,
wearing some horrible
branded shirt...
LAUGHTER
Like, for example, this one.
And then you drive around as fast as
possible all day and then you go home.
Today, track days are
such big business
you can even buy specialised track
day cars like this KTM Crossbow.
Thing is, this costs
L45,000, which is a lot,
especially as you can't exactly
take the kids to school in it.
No, so, to address this, the producers gave
us each a budget of L5,000, and they told
us to buy
four-door saloons that could be used every
day but that would also be good on a track
day.
And because the challenges they
had in mind were quite serious,
they told us to meet up in the
world's the least amusing city.
Yup, it was Berlin.
I was the first to arrive
and as you would imagine,
I had done everything properly.
This is a Mercedes 190 Cosworth
and Martin Brundle, the
former Formula One driver,
said that this car had one of the best
chassis ever fitted to a four-door saloon.
It is, if you like, the
thinking man's BMW M3.
Talking of which...
Hammond. Oh, yeah. Take a look.
Yes. BMW M3, 3.2 litres.
So you've bought the wrong one.
No, I haven't, because the original
one is now considered a classic.
So you can't get a good
one for less than 15,000.
This, the series two of the M3,
is bigger, faster and better.
So this is the famous
Mercedes 190. It is. 2.3.
Cosworth. Known for being the
slowest performance car of all time.
At that moment we were interrupted
by the arrival of Clarkson.
Predictable, predictable...
For good reason.
The only reason you two didn't buy a Ford
Sierra Sapphire Cosworth is cos you forgot
about it.
No. It's because when you think of
high-performance four-door saloons you
naturally think of Germany.
It's what they do here. Exactly.
And where was yours made?
Well, it was designed by a man
called Uwe Bahnsen, who is German.
And where was it built? Belgium.
Ah, Belgium, the meccafor the
performance motorist. Yeah.
Belgium is home to everything.
Tennis players, chips...
It's not the first place you think of
going for a performance saloon car!
You two are going to lose his and
you will end up in ze cooler...
'At that moment, a
challenge arrived. '
Oh, hello. Thank you.
"You will now leave Berlin, and head
down an unrestricted autobahn. " Good.
"Points will be awarded for every mph more
than 130 that you can or, should we say,
dare achieve. "
Still won't be out of second
gear when they're going down...
What's the top speed?
Top speed of that? Yeah.
151.
Mine had to be LIMITED to 155.
This is when they
introduced limiting.
They realised it's too fast.
It's a monster.
Fair enough, becausethis had the six
cylinder engine,3.2 litre. It did.
James, I seem to remember
this was not that fast. No.
What was its top speed? 143. 143?!
So not really a performance car.
But I reckon mine will still do
that because it is a Mercedes...
What? Oh, my God!
Ah, the interior, yeah.
Have you seen the inside of his car?
Toffee and caramel, that interior is.
It's not! Oh, and he's gone
for the fake wood door-pull.
That's a quality touch.
Right,we've got to get out of Berlin. OK.
What's that?
I don't know.
Wasn't there this morning.
You don't think it fell out
of James' luggage, do you?
HE LAUGHS Fell out of my what?
I missed that.
Ooh, yes. Straight six.
That's a proper engine.
This is the Wall.
What this car has, that the other two cars
don't have, is a dog-leg first gear. I
should explain this.
Normally, first gear is
away from you and forwards
but here it is away
from you and backwards.
That means that second and third and then
fourth and fifth are in straight lines,
which is what you want for racing,
so that is a sign that this car
has a proper motor sport pedigree.
You have to remember that in
the late '80s, early '90s,
the Germans were all drunk, running around
celebrating the fall of the Berlin Wall.
And that showed in the sloppiness
of the cars they were making.
The Belgians, on the other hand, they
never have anything to celebrate.
They just get up, go to work and
do a good job, as we can see here.
Those are his reversing lights.
Oh, BLEEP!
James, what was that?
Er, nothing.
Look, I've had 30 years of
it being left and forward.
It's a difficult
habit to get out of.
HE CHUCKLES
On the outskirts of Berlin, we pulled
over so our cars could be fitted
with super-accurate speedometers.
And then we hit the autobahn, to
see which one was the fastest.
Right, for Belgium!
Two-litre. 16 valve. Massive turbo.
5,000rpm.
5,500. Into fifth.
120.
Come on, come on!
125.
6, 7...
Ooh, it's pulling to the right.
Gone floaty.
128... 9.
Come on, let's have 130!
Traffic.
Lot of trucks. A lot of trucks.
117.
121.
Feeling good.
128...
132.
135. Traffic.
Oh, God!
Clocked now at 114.
Concentrate.
122. A bit of a weave.
Oh, bloody lorry.
Achtung! Schnell! Schnell!
It turned out that while you're allowed
to reach the top speed of your car
on the autobahn, it's not easy.
You get these German trucks...
Yes, look, he's doing it. He's doing it.
You just get these East German trucks and
they just pull out when they want to pull
out.
Eventually, though,
the traffic did thin.
So we went for another run.
Here we go, again!
Don't pull out.
Do not pull out.
132...
3, 4, 5...
Go! Come on!
136.
Smelling pretty bad.
138... 9...
140 miles an hour!
Oh, yes!
Engine temperature's shooting up.
Well, that was 142mph.
'Not bad for a 21 year-old Ford. '
Woo!
135, yes!
Give me 140! Give me 140!
There it is.
'Just three more miles per hour and the
German Cosworth would beat the Belgian
Cosworth. '
Come on, come, come on.
It's not going to do it. Sorry.
I did my best.
'Now, watch and learn. '
Come on now, come
on now, come on now.
138.
144...
47. 48...
49.
50...
152!
Traffic. Slowing.
This thing will do 155 pretty easily
I've just hit traffic every time.
Yeah, yeah... This will do 180.
It will!
'With round one going to the BMW, we pulled
over in the next town and were given
another challenge. '
"So far, we've established
the speed your cars can go.
"To see how practical they are,
for the next bit of the journey,
"you'll take it in turns
to carry some passengers. "
That's all right.
As it turned out,
it wasn't all right.
OOMPAH BAND PLAYS
If we do crash, it will
take some explaining.
Come on. I'm the
tallest thing here.
It's not as bad as
you'd think, actually.
I'm trying to bekilled
by lightning. What?
by lightning. Sorry?
Are you deaf? Sorry?
In you go.
'Sadly, I wasn't killed by
lightning, so I went next. '
Oh... I might just move these.
It's my light reading over here.
OOMPAH BAND PLAYS
'Almost immediately, I realised that
there WAS enough space in the back
'and that the rear
suspension was coping fine.
'So, I decided to pull over
as quickly as possible... '
Kill me.
'.. and handed the
band over to James. '
Ready, James? Ja.
Forwards!
Scheisse. HE LAUGHS
'After a while, it became apparent
James wasn't coming back. '
BAND CONTINUES PLAYING
Oh, hello.
This looks like trouble.
'While waiting for the
Mercedes to cool down,
'we asked the oompah band which car
they thought was the most spacious. '
Is it the Mercedes? No.
Definitely not the Mercedes.
What about the BMW?
It's the best.
Ha-ha! You see? You see?
It's our favourite.
Why?! It's smaller than the Ford.
It's coming from Bavaria, like us.
It isn't the test of
where are they from!
This is just racism
against the Belgians.
Listen, their decision is final.
They decide it won the... What are
we calling it - the oompah test?
The oompah test.
It won fair and square.
Because it's Bavarian. It won!
OOMPAH BAND RESUMES PLAYING
Thank you for nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
That's ridiculous.
The judges' decision
is final. Saying...
Saying the BMW's the most spacious
because it was made in Bavaria...
that's like saying, "Who's the
tallest Top Gear presenter?"
"It's Richard Hammond cos he'sfrom
Birmingham. " No, it's not!
"Who's the fastest driver of the three?
It's James May because he's wearing his
mum's curtains. "
It really is the most spacious car. That's
a fact and that's the judges' decision.
Live with it.
Stop bleating, let us do the news.
Yeah. Actually, I want to starton a serious
note, if I may,with the news, because, as
we know,
for many years, we've been told that Wayne
Rooney is the light and the path to
righteousness,
and we must emulate his lifestyle, and
indeed the lifestyle of his lovely wife,
Coleen.
Now of course, we realise he is a
lazy, talentless jug-eared oaf.
AUDIENCE CHEERS
APPLAUSE Well, he is.
That's quite strong.
Strong but true.
I'm now hoping this means an end
to the Rooney-fication of Britain.
Exhibit A, the Range Rover, OK?
This was the old model.
Note the plain, sensible front end,
just some headlights to see where
you're going. Its noble. It's noble.
As dignified as a rolled umbrella.
Now look what they've done to it.
Look at this. Honest.
This is the new one. What is it?
How much bling can you
get on the front...?
Look at all the fiddly headlamps
and all this business going on!
I'm surprised it doesn't
have studs in its ears, here.
They have literally ruined it.
Now, listen, I am aware, of course,
that there is a demand for a car
that looks like this, because I know
there's such a place as Cheshire.
And I don't mind if they make this...
Range Rover Rooney edition.
They could just call
it the Range Rooney.
No, no - the Wayne Wover.
LAUGHTER These are good names.
These are good names.
But all I'm asking is
please can everybody else,
ordinary decent people, have
the old one back, please?
I have to say I agree with you.
There needs to be a version
of the new Range Rover
that isn't for people who want to celebrate
the life and work of a potato-faced
shopping enthusiast.
We want the old one back.
We really do. We do.
Now, there aren't very many things
that we all agree on, except this.
We all think that the best small car that
you can buy at the moment is the Citroen
DS3.
Now, we're not joking about this.
That is a genuinely brilliant littlecar.
There's something about it.
It's like a Mini that smokes Gauloises.
It is. It's fantastic.
The weird thing is, it's got exactly
the same engine as the Mini,
the Mini Cooper. But it just feels better.
It does. It's great.
They're bringing out a
new hot version of this.
I've got the picture of it here.
It's called the Racing. OK? Yeah!
200 horsepower. The only think is Citroen
will not... They refuse to tell us how much
it's going to cost.
I'm just going to make it up.
50 quid. There you go.
It's L50. That's fantastic.
And the thing is, who in their
life wouldn't want orange wheels?
Seriously. Anyone with red hair,
I imagine. It would clash.
Red squirrels.
They'd look terrible.
The Duchess of York.
Anne Robinson. Yes.
The Pope. What's he called,th
e Pope bloke? Well, the Pope.
Silence, you two.
They're are only making 1,000 of them,
because they're French and therefore idle
Communists.
It's because nobody wants
orange wheels, obviously!
I can't wait to get a go in that. It looks
brilliant. And I do like the wheels.
Hey! Good news. LAUGHTER
I have secured some top-secret film taken
inside the factory of the new Dacia Duster
being made.
Ooh! Excellent.
Excellent. Anyway...
LAUGHTER The end of...
I'm sure you have. Thank you.
At the end of last week's programme, this
appeared. This is called the end board.
This is what you see
every single week
at the end of every
single programme.
Except for Top Gear. Look -
MMXX.
That's 2020.
This is the only programme coming
from ten years in the future.
Anyway, the point is, OK,
there's a new car come out.
It's called the Night XV.
I've got a picture of it here. OK, now...
XV. What's that?
That's 207, in Roman numerals.
No... 93. Yeah,
something like that.
No, it's 207, definitely.
Let me talk you through it, OK?
L650,000.
For that you get internet connectivity,
you get DVD, TV, a cigar humidor...
And according to one report, it
can resist gunfire for 24 hours.
LAUGHTER
Do you know what? I think if I was shooting
at someone, I'd get sort of bored after
about four hours.
I think the police would havearrived by
four hours, personally. But, forgive me, it
is a car.
You'd kind of drive
off before then.
After an hour, you'd think, "They're
not changing their minds. I'm going. "
He is still shooting at me.
And the other thing, as well,
is it's made in Canada.
Who in Canada could do...
? Are you Canadian?
Yeah! Yeah!
Whatever happens in Canada
that would cause somebody
to shoot at somebody
else for 24 hours?
The other thing as well is if you are
shooting at it, it's not likely you're
going to miss,
because here's a picture
of it next to a Hummer.
Look at the size of it! It is massive.
Absolutely unbelievable.
So that's Canada's answer
to the motor industry there.
Now, I don't know if any of
you were watching last week,
but I had several accidents
in a Reliant Robin.
Which has generated
a sizable postbag.
I've got some of the letters here. Lots of
them. Let me just read you this one, OK?
It says, "Dear Top Gear, the only reason
why Mr So-called Clarkson was killed
"is because he wasn't
driving it properly.
"I bet if the Stig drove
it, he'd be fine. "
Tell you what, let's find out.
I'm betting he rolls that over.
No, this is the Stig.
The only thing that's
ever defeated him was...
He will not be able to do a lap in that
car without rolling over. I guarantee it.
He'll use his special
Stiggy powers.
Coming up to the first corner now.
Perfect. Absolutely fine.
And... So he's made...
Oh no, he hasn't.
AUDIENCE GROANS
Told you. I told you.
There are more letters.
Here's one that caught my eye.
"Dear Top so-called Gear, why didn't
you use a Isetta Bubble Car instead?"
It's a good point. Why didn't you?
I've got one here - one wheel
at the back, two at the front.
It's a more stable
three-wheeler configuration.
Yeah. But this has another problem.
What problem? Well, why
don't you fire it up, mate?
The 300cc engine
bursting into life.
Now, if you could drive into our imaginary
garage over here, that would be lovely.
Oh, look. He hasn't fallen over.
Still hasn't fallen over.
It's much better already.
Just wait, Hammond. Here we go.
OK, all the way into the garage,
please, mate. All the way in.
You've got a foot to go. Six inches.
There you go. Marvellous.
It hasn't fallen over.
It's much better.
OK. Now, if you'd
like to get out...
LAUGHTER
Oh, yeah. I see your point.
The door's at the front.
You'll have to back it up, mate. Yeah, go
on - reverse. OK. Where is reverse?
Hasn't got one.
LAUGHTER Really? No.
So how does he get out?
Well, this is the thing.
Honestly, if you think about it...
If you don't listen...
James, stop fingering the studio.
The thing is, OK, that if
you had one of these cars,
you got home like this, you got stuck
in your garage, there were two problems.
You couldn't call inside your
house for your wife or girlfriend
to come and rescue you, because it was the
1950s and the mobile telephone hadn't been
invented.
And of course, if you had a car like this,
you wouldn't have a wife or a girlfriend.
Very funny. Could you
push me out now, please?
What? Would you give me a push?
Me push you out? Push you out...
Er... Can we...?
Sorry, what was the question? We could
either push him out or... Not do that. Not
do that.
Can we push him out? Ah...
I think no.
I'm coming down in favour
of no as well. Sorry, James.
It's a no, sorry. It's aunanimous no.
See you, mate. Sorry.
Right, well, let's
move it on, to this.
To that, actually, over there.
That is a Porsche 911.
And one way or another, that has
been with us for about 1,000 years.
Now, though, they've brought out
a sort of greatest hits version.
Here it is.
Porsche call is the Sport Classic.
But I prefer to think of it as "Now That's
What I Call The Best Of The 911...
"Volume One. "
These duck-tail spoiler was originally
a hit for the 1973 Carrera 2.7 RS.
The black headlamp surrounds were
first recorded by the 1974 Turbo RSR.
The Fuchs alloys are a cover version
of the ones first seen on the 1966911S.
And the wide-body rear arches
are from today's Carrera 4.
Anyway, that's enough
band analogies.
Let's see if this thing is as good as it
was before Peter Gabriel left Genesis.
Starting, if we must,
with how fast it will go.
You get 22 more horsepower than
you do in a standard Carrera S.
That means 0-60 in 4.6 seconds.
Top speed 188.
And I suppose that means
I've got to go and do it.
Argh!
So, it's very fast,
very good looking,
and surprisingly
soft and comfortable,
but there is a problem.
It's L140,000-
twice what a normal
Carrera S costs.
And they've only made 250 of them.
And you can't buy one, because
they've all been sold.
So let's move on to a
Porsche you can buy...
.. the new Boxster Spyder.
Porsche say this harks back
to the lightweight models
James Dean was driving in the '50s.
But frankly, that's a bit
of marketing cobblers.
He was a rebel without an airbag.
This does have an airbag.
But that's about it.
It's 80kg lighter than the standard
Boxster, thanks to aluminium doors,
aluminium engine cover, super-light
wheels and carbon-fibre seats.
There's more, or rather, less.
There is no standard air-con.
The door handles have been replaced
by these little bits of rag
and they've even ditched the piece of
plastic that goes on top of the instruments.
What Porsche do is, they leave a lot of
things that you should get on a Boxster on
a shelf in the factory
and then they charge you more
for not giving them to you.
This car costs L46,000.
That's 5,000 more
than the standard car
and you get less in return.
Or do you?
The 3.4 litre flat 6 now has 320
horsepower, 10 more than the standard
Boxsters.
And because it's lighter, 0-60
is done in just five seconds.
Top speed?
166.
I've owned the standard Boxster
S for the last four years
and I can promise
you, this is better.
It's more eager.
It's bloody excellent.
Hee-hee-hee!
But all this stripped back Spyder
stuff does have its drawbacks.
What if you're driving along with the roof
down and, suddenly, it starts to rain?
Exactly. What a
remarkable coincidence.
Oh no, I need to
erect the top tent.
What you do is, you open the boot.
You take out this piece, which
is called the sun shield.
You get in the car, you
attach it at the front first.
Ah!
Like that...
Then... You get
that bit behind you.
Hang on.
And then the other end of the same
wire goes on this special clamp
and then these two bits
clip on to there...
Oh, sh...
'It was a nightmare. But I got it
finished just as the "rain" stopped.
Top speed is now
reduced from 166 to 126
because any faster than that
and the sky tent blows off.
Frankly, I couldn't care less.
Because the way this car feels is so
much more important than the top speed.
This is a really happy car.
It's full of vibrant
energy and enthusiasm.
It's a bit like one of
those really stupid dogs.
I bet if you threw a ball
it would chase after it.
And it's having a bit of an
effect on me because to be honest,
I have started behaving a bit
like the other two idiots.
The really amazing thing is, in a car
as lithe and nimble as this, I can.
I've said before that some cars give me a
strange fizzing sensation inside and this
one really does.
I'm fizzing massively here.
I'm fizzing fit to burst. Nurse!
That's actually a
spin, but never mind.
Never mind, indeed.
What Porsche has done is take one of the
most practical everyday sports cars you can
buy
and turned it into a
simple indulgence.
And by making it simple they've
made it simply brilliant.
APPLAUSE
He will be disappointed.
It is a shame James isn't here because I
didn't agree with everything he said then.
It's a shame he's not here to stand up,
but never mind, will carry on without him.
Start with this, the Sport Classic.
It's a fabulous looking thing.
It's a fabulous car, actually.
But the price! What I think happened here
is, they started off with a price and then
tried to justify it.
No, I'm sorry, it is a pretty
thing, but this is worse.
This really is worse.
An umbrella, no door handles.
Honestly.
So, I guess there's no point putting that
round the track because you can't buy it.
We'll just put this
stupid thing round.
I'll have to do the
commentary, obviously. Oi!
While it's driven by
our tame racing driver.
Some say there are 17 different
reasons why he's banned
from the Northampton
branch of Little Chef.
LAUGHTER
And that his favourite
airline pilot is Mark Webber.
LAUGHTER
Me too, actually. All we know,
of course, it's the Stig!
Oh no, he's facing
the wrong direction.
Of course, it's a Boxster -
both ends look exactly the same.
Off now, slowly, to
the first corner.
Just slowly driving
through it really,
in a not very interesting way.
Nothing interesting at
all to report there.
Stig, still enjoying his
new CD, Vuvuzela Moods.
I should add that
this is made possible
because Porsche has very kindly reinstated
the stereo they normally charge you L5,000
to remove.
Plodding through the Hammerhead now in the
manner of a car that only a complete idiot
would like.
Oh, dear. Bored.
Little known fact, this is also the noise
Stig makes when he wants to attract a mate.
Follow through, past some tyres.
Wish I'd brought a magazine to read while
waiting for this stupid thing to haul its
way round.
Not very interesting there, sort of
sliding there, and across the finish.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
I don't mind that. don't like that.
I have the time here
for a Boxster Spyder
and it did it in
1:24.9 which actually
isn't bad at all.
That puts it right up there.
No, notinterested in that at all. Let's put
a star in our brand new
reasonably priced car.
Now, my guest tonight
began his career
writing pornographic stories
for a gentlemen's magazine.
He then went on to be communications
director for Tony Blair
and Gordon Brown, so he spent most
of his adult life working with...
penises.
LAUGHTER
Ladies and gentlemen,
Alastair Campbell!
How are you? All right.
BOOING
Go on then, go on then!
Two of the best people.
Well, you've come in to the den
oflions here. Yeah, they're all right!
You don't know yet.
It is tricky, I have to be honest,
thinking about how this
interview might go.
Me, you... Yeah... left, right.
Not necessarily right.
Wrong.
LAUGHTER The thing
is, I don't believe
what I write any more than
you believe what you say.
So... LAUGHTER
.. interesting sitting here.
We've got to do this interview
and, at some point, we've
got to get to the lap
which is all cheery.
I prepared some questions that
I hope aren't too contentious.
OK, I thought you would.
A lot of work gone into these.
Good.
What is your favourite colour?
LAUGHTER
I've got two. Claret and blue.
Blue? I wasn't expecting blue.
Burnley Football Club.
Burnley? I'm fascinated by your
love of, erm, football. Mm-hm.
Because you're a Yorkshireman
but you support Burnley. Yup.
Isn't that a bit
like, I don't know,
going to an Oxbridge college and
then joining the Labour Party?
LAUGHTER AND GASPS
Lots did and lots have.
But Burnley back then were one
of the biggest and best teams
in the country and they were 20
miles away from where I lived.
What star sign are you? Gemini.
I don't know anything about
Gemini, except my wife's one.
LAUGHTER
D'you want to marry me?
No?! No. I'm going to get
political now. Go on, then.
Here we go. So you
started out writing porn.
I mean that was Forum magazine.
Was that right? Yeah.
And then you became Blair's.
You were communications director.
There was a gap.
There was a gap but eventually...
So you did something
noble and then ended up
sort of prostituting yourself
which I think is a weird way round.
I want to move on to Gordon Brown,
who lost the general election
and has now disappeared.
CHUCKLING
Two-part question,
and a serious one.
You were obviously in
charge of the image
and how the election was
presented to the people.
Two parts. Who was it that
told him that he had to smile,
and then why did no-one
tell him to stop?
LAUGHTER
Well, I wasn't in charge.
I would have been in charge if we won,
but we didn't win.
So I wasn't in charge at all.
LAUGHTER
I don't think you can
tell anybody to smile.
But I think it was
possibly his misfortune
that he followed a Prime Minister
who does smile a lot
very, very naturally.
Not like that. He did.
He's got nicer teeth than you,Jeremy.
He looks after them. Yes,
he probably used taxpayers'...
Did they go on expenses, his teeth?
No. No, they didn't.
Don't applaud. APPLAUSE
It just occurred to me...
Don't applaud that. If I may,
if I may, OK, I have
some footage here.
I just want to see
Gordon Brown here, OK?
Here he is. And ready, steady...
LAUGHTER
But look - he lightened up the
room, didn't he? That was nice.
Was it done with
electricity, or...?LAUGHTER
Fzzzzcrrkkk!
LAUGHTER
The thing is, you did
Tweet, I believe,
earlier this week saying, "How do I
handle Clarkson, any suggestions?"
I got a lot. Really? Yeah.
Murder, kill...
Some of those.
"Kick him in the nuts. "
Mm-hm. Yeah.
"Ask him how he voted. "
Do you know, I think it
is none of your business.
OK, fair enough.
INDISTINCT RESPONSE I'm
going to make a guess.
Go on then. Tory.
That would mean voting for
my next door neighbour.
Anyway, they didn't win.
Cameron? No, he did win.
Well, he didn't really.
Well, he's the Prime Minister.
He's the Prime Minister but he
needs little Cleggo, doesn't he?
He needs the tea boy, I agree.
LAUGHTER
HE SNORTS
I... I...
Anyway, when do we see the lap?
No, not yet, not yet
because I want to talk about
your books. Do you? Yeah. OK.
You say that you get
inspiration for writing them
when you are driving along.
Is that a distraction for your driver, or?
LAUGHTER
Honestly, in your book... OK.
.. Prelude to Power, which is your
diaries, pretty much in detail.
That's, how many pages?
744 pages and it only gets us up to 1997.
So, the actual "Prelude to Power".
That's five times longer
than War and Peace.
I write a diary every day. You do?
You really do write every day?
You will be in there tonight.
The chat we have outside about the
director general will be in there...
Oh, bloody hell! It was as well.
I do a diary. I said that he wasa
very well-endowed man. Yes, yes.
Now, there is a lot about Clause
Four, and all of the things
that were being changed prior
to His Tony-ness's appointment.
I couldn't find a single reference
to the most important thing
that happened when he became Prime
Minister which was the M4 bus lane.
Hmm.
Was that just a whim then?
Was it not planned?
No, the thing is, Jeremy, as you
rightly say, it goes up to 1997.
Mm-hm. Volume two
is subtitled "The M4 bus lane.
In full. " I was terrified
that John Prescott had
walked in one day and gone,
"Hey, I tell you what, let's paint
outside lane on t'motorway red
"and make it a bus lane. " Aye.
And that's not what happened? No.
There was a thought that it might
alleviate some of the congestion
and, according to the
statistical analysis
thereafter, it kind of worked.
But YOU can't accept that
because you want to cover
the whole country in concrete
and drive in big cars.
Yeah. Yeah.
LAUGHTER
The other thing as well,
what did you think of our
new reasonably priced car?
Because you're the first person to
drive it in this proper situation.
I quite liked it. Once I'd got
into really kind of leathering it,
it didn't have a lot of oomph.
I think The Stig was really patient,
he really was. Top man. Really?
I was kind of half hoping
it would be a woman.
Some say he's
fanatically right wing.
No, he told me he's not.
Really? He says you are.
SCOFFS
See? You're just believing what
it says in the papers again.
No, I know you're a
reasonable, fair-minded chap.
No!
LAUGHTER
Anyway, who wants
to see the lap?I do.
You do. Let's play the tape.
Let's have a look.
WHEELSPIN SCREECH
'Here we are.
That wasn't me, was it?'
'Not bad. Was it all right?
'Dunno, actually.
'Come on, concentrate.
Remember everything he said.
'Let's have a look through the first corner.
I'm going to see this car...
'Well, going to see it going
all round the track. '
Nick Clegg should do this cos he
hasn't got an awful lot to do.
'Now, you've got to stay right here.
Oh, no, you've veered left.
'There's a surprise
'On your way down
to the hammerhead.
'It understeers more than
the old Chevrolet, this car.
'Doesn't look like it's going
as fast as I thought it was.
'Everyone says that.
But you keep... '
You ARE veering to the left!
Oh God, yeah.
'No, here we go. This is flat out.
Were you flat-out from your...?
'Felt flat-out, yeah. ' BLEEP!
'Are you competitive? Very. '
I just want to beat
Nick Robinson tonight.
'Yes, that's nicely done through
there, you cut the corner very well.
'I had real trouble down there.
'I kept going into 5th.
That's bang...
'Not quite fast enough.
'You were in 5th?
At one point, yeah. Wrong!
'And there we are.
And boing! Across the line!'
So...
where do you think
you've come there?
I'm quite keen to beatNick Robinson.
There's a surprise,
the BBC political editor.
You did it,
Alastair Campbell, in one minute...
That's good... 40...
So bearing in mind he was at 49.9,
you would have a job squeaking
in after him. I'm doing well...
1:47 dead.
Oooh...
That puts you as
our second fastest.
CHEERING
That's OK.
Well done. No, that's very good.
My name fell down.
That's very good.
It fell down.
Your name's fell down?
Yeah. LAUGHTER
Can we do that bit again?
It can stay there.
Why have you lost the magnetism?
Because we don't get
enough licence fee,
thanks to you lot. There you are.
So I beat Al Murray.
You're faster than Al Murray.
And aPage Three girl. Peta, 23, Essex.
And Nick Robinson. Nick Robinson.
Next time he interviews
you, you can go,
"I'm faster than you. I'm faster than you.
I'm faster than you. "
And then hit him. LAUGHTER
You're a huge sport
for coming down here.
Best of luck. I enjoyed it.
Alastair Campbell! Thank you.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Marvellous.
Now, now, earlier on, we proved
that this BMW M3 is better
in pretty much every way than
this Mercedes and this Ford.
Because of racism...
Yeah, whatever.
Now it's time to go back
to Germany so that the BMW
can win all the
other tests as well.
We begin with Jeremy,
predictably, moaning.
This part of the world was ruined
first of all by Hitler then Stalin
and now Jonathan Porridge with
his windmills. I like 'em.
They're noisy, they're pointless.
Oh, hello. Right.
"Your cars will now
be tested for faults
"by ADAC, Germany's
equivalent of the AA."
We test them now, after we've maxed
them on the autobahn, brilliant
It won't hurt them.
Apparently "one of ADAC's mobile
patrols will arrive shortly".
So we're looking for a van.
It'll be a van of some sort.
That's all right.
'It was a van,
'but this being Germany... '
It's got a reception, look.
Look, it has.
'The ADAC men took
charge of James's Merc. '
Guten tag, Klaus. Hi.
Fortschritt.
JEREMY CHUCKLES
What's wrong with the car?
His racing gearbox is going well.
'The equipment they had in
the van was extraordinary
'and the tests were very thorough.
'They used a computer to
measure the boiling point
'of the Merc's brake fluid
'and a gizmo to check the
roundness of its tyres. '
There's a laser and everything.
'It was doing quite
well, but then... '
Oh, dear.
Scheisse!
What a load of rubbish!
'After this, things got worse. '
CLUNKING JEREMY HOOTS
I did 140 miles an hour.
You did 140 miles an hour,
and your wheels... nicht gut.
.. Are very bad, you
have let them rust.
'It was time I put these German
chappies straight on a few things. '
Martin Brundle was
sehr gut uber dem auto.
What was that you just
said about Martin Brundle?
I was just saying
how Martin Brundle said
that this was the finest rear-drive
chassis he'd ever driven.
He never said any...
He did! He had one.
He did not say...
Unluckily for you, mate, I
have Martin Brundle's number
on my telephone.
He will confirm that he said that
and that he had one.
This, he claimed, was the best?
! And famously said that.
'Hello?' Martin?
I'll talk to him. No, get off.
Martin? Let me talk to him.
Martin, morning, it's James
from Top Gear. Hi, how are you?
'Yeah, good, are you
somewhere exciting?'
I'm underneath a Mercedes
190 Cosworth, actually,
and the other two won't believe
me when I say that you said
quite categorically
that this was the finest
rear-drive chassis of
any car in the world
and the best you'd ever driven.
'When did I say that?
'I've had a few knocks on the head
but I don't remember saying that.
'It's not a bad engine
'but, no, it's
really not that good.
'You need the M3 for
the best chassis
'from around that time,
I would have thought. '
That was always my belief that
people believed the M3 was better
and it had got this
folkloric reputation
but anybody who knew what they
were talking about, ie you,
Ayrton Senna, knew that
actually the Mercedes
was the superior car.
'I don't remember Ayrton getting out
'and saying, "That is the best rear
drive chassis I've ever been in. "
'I think he got out and said,
'"I'm pleased it thrashed Lauda
and Prost and all those guys. "'
Niki Lauda and Alain Prost as well?
I didn't know that.
You don't need to speak to him...
I do need to speak to him.
Martin? You've turned it off.
He's catching an aeroplaneto his
second home. What did he say?
He confirmed everything I
said about him. He also said,
"The engine is excellent
"and the M3 was a mere shadow
of what this car was. "
Did he? That's what he said?
Yes he did.
That's what he said? Yes.
That'swhat he said? Right, lower the car.
'Next it was the turn
of my Cosworth. '
Mein auto ist die einzige mit...
TRANSLATION FROM GERMAN:
Mein auto ist designen
von eine Deutsche. Yah!
Good. OK.
Just making it plain.
I don't want him to mark it
down because it's Belgian.
As it happens the ADAC man
was impressed with my car.
Good?
All good! All good!
Ha-ha-ha-ha! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
'But it would now be humiliated
by the much younger M3.'
I hate to say this
because it's verging on
complementing you but your car
is now quite cool and
collectible whereas that is
just something driven by...
Imbeciles.
TRANSLATED FROM GERMAN:
Best car? Sehr gut.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yes. It is.
'As it turned out, it wasn't. '
Crikey, look at that.
That's the anti-roll bar, isn't it?
It had an accident... Kaput.
JEREMY CACKLES
That's why you got a
different shock absorber.
It's been botched together.
It has clearly had
a crash, hasn't it?
'Soon it was time
to get our scores. '
And that's your Ford.
The Ford. And the BMW. Thank you.
What would be a good score on this?
A new car would
score, a good car...
150 points. I will go first
with my score. Are we ready?
58. 58? That's good.
...19.
19?! Mmm.
That's not so good. No.
Hammond? Six.
He's not serious?! Six?
Six, yes.
Six?! That's right.
Bu...? The Ford!
How have I only got six?
The back is very bad. Yeah.
58- that's a pass.
Six?! You might as
well have gotnought.
Would you say the BMW
is dangerous?Yes.
This had a dramatic effect
on the way Hammond drove.
Six.
I don't know how it
could score less.
It would have to have,
like, wheels missing
or a tiger in it.
Tonight on First Gear,
Richard Hammond drives across
Germany in a death trap.
'Hammond's mood wasn't
improved when he found out
'where we'd be staying the night. '
You've got to be kidding.
'Yup! Colditz is now a hotel. '
OK.
'The next morning, James
and Richard checked out
'in the traditional fashion. '
"Colditz Theme"
Where have you two been?
How did you get out? I used
mycredit card at the reception desk.
I don't know why we
all didn't do that.
It wouldn't make for a
good TV series, would it?
It wouldn't have had 28 episodes.
Next, Major Pat Reid denies watching
the movie that was on his bill.
'To Richard's consternation, it
was then time for our track day.
'The producers insisted we stuck
to track day etiquette by wearing
'clothing from the catalogues of
the companies that made our cars. '
Holy
Moly! Ooh, that's daddy's.
That's not a good look.
It says a lot about people
who drive Mercedes Benz.
It does, and do you know, as
of Monday morning, I don't,
any more!
If there was a fire around here,
imagine the melting...! Ah!
Now, the most important challenge -
"Which of you has the
fastest track day car?
"To make sure this test is fair,
"each of your cars will be
drivenby the same driver. " Yes!
I don't have to go out there in
the death trap... Oh, yes, you do.
"You will be in the passenger seat
"while the car is driven
by a tame racing driver. "
What, the Stig?
No, he's not the Stig.
He's the Stig's German cousin.
Looks like the Stig to me.
Still the Stig. Still the St...
It is the Stig! No, hang on.
Oh, my giddy aunt. Mullet.
I think it might be
Stiggy Ray Cyrus.
First up for Herr Stig
was the Mercedes.
Go!
ROUGH ENGINE ROAR
That doesn't sound good.
You've got to remember that in
the ADAC tests, they revealed
that the steering was a bit loose.
There's a lot of play in the rack,
so just don't overdo it, OK?
Bloody hell!
'To compensate for the
Merc's lack of power,
'German Stig was on
maximum attack. '
So this is bigger than the
Nurburgring, right, this track?
Must be, cos of the amount of time
it's taken. Must be 35 miles. Yeah.
You can feel the multi-link,
Martin Brundle-approved,
rear suspension hunkering down...
Get a grip, man!
It's 2 mins 19.3, and we've
no idea what that means.
'But we'd soon find out,
'because it was time
to lap the Ford. '
And the muscles from
Brussels is under way!
The Jean-Claude Van Damme-anator!
That rear suspension is collapsed.
This is... pure track day magic.
1,250 kilograms, that's all
it weighs, the same as a Mini.
But it has 200 horsepower!
So, this German Stig fella...
will he take well to Jeremy shouting
at him and stuff, do you think?
He didn't take any notice of me
when I told him which gearto
change into. Who would?
This is the car which has won
the British Touring
Car Championship,
the World Touring Car Championship,
the British Rally Championship!
Das Stig is a maniac!
Here he comes.
Wall, wall, wall.
This is going to be close.
12, 13, 14.
Come on, let's have it.
Two... Yep. 14. Ooh-hoo-hoo!
Five seconds faster!
'All that remained was to lap
Hammond's crash-damaged death trap. '
There are quite a lot of right
hand turns, aren't there,
in that first bit? Yeah.
You're really putting a lot of
stress on the front left suspension.
Exactly. If your car had
had, let's say, an accident,
and had been mended cheaply
on the front left corner...
Stop talking.
Now, Herr Stig, there's one
important thing I have to tell you
about this car before we set off...
No, I didn't mean set off!
I haven't told you the thing!
What about the thing?
Are you cold? No.
Go right. Go right.
D'you know what I'm
expecting to see? Er...
Just the front wheel coming across
the line in about two minutes' time.
I'm just waiting to hear
the unmistakable sound
of metal snapping.
And the... of arterial blood.
Wall!
110 miles an hour in
a car that scored 6.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
The board. The points.
Here we go.
Yes. What?
Oh, come on, then, what was the time
for the BM, what was the lap time?
I've forgotten.
The time, what was it, come on?
Seriously.
What did he do it in? 2.06.
Yes! Thank you very much,
I win that. So, yeah,
you get one point for every
second underneath three minutes,
so 2.06...
54 points... Oh, yeah... for you.
Why is that 3.14?
What?
Well, I did the lap
in 2 minutes 14.
But, you see, the
producer disagrees.
Why? Well,
it was that new producer we've
got, the one from Uruguay.
Sorry, mate, he's right, he
didn't see one of those minutes,
so you can't have it.
It was on television!
That'sinadmissible. It doesn't count.
This is ridiculous. Bad luck.
Moving on. So that means my BMW
was the fastest on the autobahn,
it was the most
spacious in that test,
and then it put in the fastest lap.
Well, I will now garner
back some points,
because it's the YouTube section.
As we know, people
who go to track days,
they put a camera on the dashboard,
they record their lap, they
put that lap on YouTube.
And we were told to
do the same thing, OK?
And then there would be one
point for every hit we got.
James, I believe now we have a
clip from your Mercedes lap?
Let's have a look at that now.
'And we're off. A little bit of
tramping from the axle there.
'Then I'm going to
select fourth as we come
'up to the end of the straight,
and we go in to turn one.
'As we go round turn one... Oh...
'Oh, cock. As you can see,
'there are bollards on
the circuit, which is not
'what I was expecting, and must
mean I've gone the wrong way. '
How can you get lost on a
racetrack, mate? I don't...
I don't... It's one way.
I know, I don't understan
d it,I'm sorry. All right.
Let's have a look at a
clip from Jeremy's video.
'Coming up now to the end of a lap.
'I'm doing 195 miles an hour,
'200, 210 miles an hour now, 220...
'And I cross the line. '
What? You just lied and then
sped up the film. A bit.
A lot! A bit. Let's have a look
atyour lap in the death trap.
All right. Here we go.
Vroom! Vroom! Vroom!
And listen to that straight six!
Brvoom!
You didn't take it out.
No, I did, the camera broke.
I did it properly...
Cluck! Cluck!Stop doing that.
That's very annoying.
You chicken. No, I wasn't.
I did do a lap, the camera
broke, it just recorded sound.
OK, we've had those clips up
for a week? Yeah. How many
hits did you get? I got...
71.
CHEERING
Are you seriously suggesting
71 people...? Why would
theydo that? Why would
71...? Why are people compelled
toput themselves on it? 71 points.
OK. I got 137. Wow!
Hammond?
Seven.
LAUGHTER
Seven? Seven, yeah.
Seven. That was pathetic.
Thinking back,
I should have misspelled M3
in the tag line bit on
the Internet. What, 3M?
No, if I'd spelled it
"Angelina Jolie topless",
I'd have got more hits than both
of you, but I didn't. Anyway,
we then did an economy run,
from Germany into Poland.
Sadly there isn't time
tonight to show you that.
The upshot was, though,
James ran out of petrol.
Therefore, you get
minus 141.Hang on.
What? I've got minus
exactly what I already had. Yes.
That's the rules - it
happened to him once. It did.
That is the rules. You're minus 141,
so you're currently on... nought.
Er... I get 10 for
that, because I won
in the Ford, thanks to
its two-litre engine,
and you get five for coming second.
Which means,
we have just one final challenge,
something to do with price -
I have it here.
So it's a two-horse race.
Either you or me will win.
He's out. Absolutely.
He is completely out. He's on nought.
OK. So, here we go.
You get one point for every pound
your car was under
the L5,000 budget.
So, hang on, mine cost L3,990,
so I get 1,010 points there!
Look at that.
I like that. Go on then,
how much did yours cost? 4,999.
So you get one point!
Which means, clearly, I win that!
Thank you very much. I may as
wellhave just bought a toy car.
I was going to get the prize.
I would have got...
Those are the rules,
and I win! Thank you!
Delighted. And rightly so. CHEERING
No!
I'm sorry.
If I may just take that from you
and ask you to stand to one side,
because my car was L2,990,
meaning I have 2,010 points
straightaway there, which I think
you will find makes me...
the winner.
CHEERING
That's just silly.
That's just ridiculous.
Oi! Are we honestly going to say,
on the world's biggest
motoring show,
to 350 million people,
that the best track day car
is a slow, rusty,
wobbly wheeled,
small, uneconomical piece of junk?
Yes. And on that bombshell, it's
time to say goodnight. Goodbye.
Oh, this is just ridiculous!
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E- mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk