We will anger the Americans
slipping out like this.
If your son
was a student
at one of the greatest
universities in the world...
So make him
come to you.
We are protected
near the UN.
But once we cross
42nd Street...
As always, I appreciate
your caution, Joseph.
But as always, you
have far too much of it.
Stay down, sir.
Get on the ground!
I'm just
serving process!
Your boss is being sued
under Title 18
of the United States Code,
section 1350,
for genocide, crimes against
humanity, and torture.
Mr. President, this is
only a civil lawsuit.
We can ignore it.
Mr. President.
You want us
to work for Foreman?
Not permanently.
He is setting up
interviews
to replace Taub
and Thirteen,
but it might take
a couple of weeks.
Well, what happened
to them?
He quit, and I had to let her go.
You actually fired
your girlfriend?
Yes.
You two are
both competent,
and I know I can
work with you.
You really do know
how to woo.
I need you.
It would be interesting.
And we could
work together.
Did you see who
the patient is?
That's one of the reasons
it'll be interesting.
Dibala is one of the most
repressive dictators in the world.
You had no problem
treating a guy on death row.
Who was still in prison
after we patched him up.
We fix Dibala,
he gets on a plane
and executes
half his country.
He's been repressing an
ethnic rebellion in the south,
the Sitibi people.
It's getting worse.
Dibala is a guest
of the US government,
and he's been invited
to speak at the UN.
I'm not asking
you to love him,
I'm asking you
to do your job.
Utterly incomprehensible.
And, of course, I'm talking
about you firing your girlfriend.
We weren't getting along
with her working under me.
This'll help. Cameron
and I worked together.
But you weren't
her boss,
and you stopped
working together.
Why don't you just tell her
you were wrong and...
Because I wasn't.
I know how
this looks.
I know it might
break us up.
But that's better than
definitely breaking us up,
which is what would've
happened otherwise.
Hemorrhagic
ulcers in the lungs.
Oh, my God,
it's three years ago.
Does that mean
I'm still crazy?
You're back?
You look good.
We're just helping
out because... I know.
I just ran
into Thirteen
while she was
clearing out her locker.
My condolences.
Although it's not like she's
the hottest woman in the world.
We haven't broken up.
Are you back?
Sort of. You get your license back?
Not for a month or so.
So you'll be in charge, I'm
just gonna pitch in a little.
Dibala thinks it was
an assassination attempt.
Polonium, like the
Russian guy in London.
FBI checked the service of
process forms and his hotel room.
No radioactivity trails.
Acid reflux?
No history of
asthma or heartburn.
He has a bug bite
on his hands.
Malaria's endemic
in his country.
Let's start him
on Coartem.
I don't want to step
on any toes,
but I guess I do have a
higher duty to the patient.
If you have something
to say, say it.
You're rushing
to a diagnosis
because you're
rushing out of this room
rightly upset with me.
Although I wasn't the one who
made that asinine decision to...
Do you have anything
medical to say?
Poison fits better
because of the vomiting.
Bug bite might
not be a bite,
it might be
the start of chloracne.
Assassination attempt
through dioxin poisoning.
It's hard to detect.
Fits.
Start him on olestra.
You couldn't have just
said dioxin up front?
I was hoping you'd
get there on your own.
So, I guess we
should talk to Cuddy.
You are sure
it is dioxin?
Nope.
It's our best guess. The
olestra here binds to the poison,
flushes it out
of your system.
Where are you from,
doctor?
I'm Australian.
Do I hear a bit
of British?
Most people
don't notice it.
Yeah, I kicked
around there for a while.
You went to
medical school there?
Actually,
a year of seminary.
And you left.
Uh-huh.
There was a Catholic mission
near my childhood village.
I liked the priests.
They were good people.
But when my two younger sisters
were dying from consumption,
it wasn't more priests
we wanted.
I fired my girlfriend because
he said he was gone for good.
I need this in my life.
A week ago, it was the
last thing you needed.
It's a process.
I'm learning.
And screwing me over
as you go.
Yeah,
that's why I did it.
Sorry.
If you want, I'll
explain it to Thirteen.
He's not ready.
He doesn't have his license.
Then he can't practice. But we'd
be idiots not to listen to him.
You're in charge. He sits
in on all the differentials.
Until you get your license
back, this is all unofficial.
No procedures,
no patient contact.
I think I can probably deal
with that last one.
The only reason
I let you go
is because our relationship
wouldn't work
if I was in charge.
But I won't be
in charge soon
so I came to offer
your old job back.
I know I look bad, but
circumstances have changed.
I don't want the job.
Why not?
Because there's a much simpler
explanation for you firing me.
You wanted to
break up with me,
but you were too weak
to do it yourself.
Then why would I try
to hire you back?
Can we please get
some dinner tonight?
I'm sorry.
Uh...
You're a follow-up?
You must not treat him.
Dibala killed my wife.
She was a trade unionist.
They took her from our
home while I was at work.
Who took her?
Dibala's Youth
Labor League.
He pretends it's to get
young people off the street,
but he takes teenage boys
from the provinces
and feeds them
drugs and alcohol
and teaches them
how to torture.
They dumped her body in
my yard two weeks later.
They raped her.
They carved "inyenzi",
cockroach,
onto her stomach
because she's Sitibi.
I'm very sorry, but I can't
discuss other patients.
You should talk to a
lawyer, talk to the UN...
So they can sit and watch
like they did in Rwanda?
There are
two million Sitibi.
He is planning to
massacre them all.
His radio stations
are talking about
a final war to
exterminate the cockroaches.
He can't recover.
I'm sorry.
How was your
first day of school?
Didn't pee once
in the sandbox.
How was it with Cuddy?
What did you think
I was talking about?
Hmm.
You didn't use garlic. You
didn't use it last night either.
We always use garlic
on Chicken Florentine.
It tastes fine
this way.
You seem to be losing
your sense of smell.
I think you're losing
your sense of mind.
I can check right now
if you pull my finger.
No, it's the...
Are you inventing some
big medical mystery here?
Because if you're
imagining things again...
You weren't wearing shoes
last night either.
Yes, shoes, garlic,
I am vampire, Sookie.
I told you to get
that echo fixed.
My downstairs neighbor,
after you moved in,
started complaining about the
extra noise and the cooking smells.
What's his name?
I don't want you
making things worse.
He's on the condo board,
and I'm trying to get
the back garden renovated.
The white coats
taught me a whole bunch
of fun coping
and relating skills.
He's not only
a total jerk,
he's a decorated war hero
who lost an arm in Vietnam.
I mean, there's no
winning with this guy.
Coping skill number one,
complete avoidance.
You happy?
Booty call? Give me 20
minutes to not shower.
Patient's having
a heart attack.
Mask and 15 liters.
Just thought
you'd like to know.
Streptokinase. Heparin.
Lassa fever.
You were mad that
I withheld it last time,
so I'm saying it
right up front.
He's already stabilized,
so 40ccs of ribavirin,
and we're home
in time for Ellen.
I checked. There's no
Lassa in Dibala's country.
Oh.
The rash is gone.
It rules out
your dioxin theory.
He's running
a slight fever,
which we can add to the
heart, plus the lung ulcers.
Ebola? Marburg?
Too long
an incubation period and...
Yes?
Don't people sometimes travel
to places that have, you know,
a fever that originated in
the Nigerian town of Lassa?
He's been to three other
countries in the last two years.
Here, Zimbabwe and Sharm el-Sheikh,
Egypt. No Lassa there either.
Oh. Again.
Trypanosomiasis?
No sleep disturbances, but
it fits best with his symptoms
and it's geographically
the most... What?
The Egypt visit was for
the African Union meeting,
where I'm guessing he was
"meeting" people from "Africa",
which includes Liberia,
which sent some members
of their foreign ministry
which has itself just been hit
by an outbreak of jock itch.
No, wait, not jock itch.
Lassa fever.
I'll start the ribavirin.
I did say it up front.
It's great to have the old
team back together again, huh?
Yesterday,
it's poisoning,
today, Lassa fever.
Maybe a specialist...
Joseph, leave him alone.
These people know
what they are doing.
Are you married, doctor?
No.
You have a girlfriend?
Yes.
Judging by your
tentative answer
and the complicated
expression on her face,
I believe that is she
standing in the hallway.
I got a call from Douglas'
department at Princeton General.
They want me to
interview with them.
Which is weird because
when I called last week,
they said they had
nothing available,
so I never sent in
my resume.
Douglas owes me a favor.
Most people
send chocolates.
And I'd stand outside your apartment
all night holding up a boom box
except you told me
you hate '80s music.
So about dinner,
I'm free tomorrow night.
I was wondering what that
noise was. It's the damn cane.
And I'm Greg.
And I can't sleep with you
banging around with that thing.
You're not actually saying
that I have too loud a cane?
Is that hard for you
to understand?
Well, only in the sense
that it has a rubber tip
on the end,
not a tap shoe.
Now you're
getting cute with me.
Okay, we started badly.
I apologize for the noise
and we will try to figure
out a way to be quieter.
And a thousand other things
I don't give a crap about.
Now you keep it down or
we're going to have trouble.
Wow.
You paged me?
This is Ama. She is from our
country, but she lives here now.
We'd like you
to use her blood.
For what?
She recovered from Lassa
fever two years ago.
Our Health Minister
has advised us
that plasma from one
who has the antibodies
is much more effective
than ribavirin.
This is
a signed consent form.
Will you take
her blood, please?
No.
I want to do this.
You understand that we
will be using your blood
to cure
President Dibala.
I know.
Are you from
the Sitibi people?
I am Sitibi.
Did they threaten you
in some way?
Your family members
back home?
Please let me
give the blood. Please.
Do it.
She's being coerced.
If she is,
I'd rather have a needle
prick on my conscience
than the death of
her family members.
Hey!
Don't let him in there!
That's enough,
we got him.
Hey.
You all right?
Who is that man?
He shot him?
No.
You need a lawyer.
You can get
a court-appointed.
I can help you.
I can't be helped.
You did a stupid,
terrible thing.
But given the circumstances
with your wife,
you could get
a reduced sentence.
She wasn't my wife.
Well, who was she?
They never
told us her name.
What his men made us do
to that woman,
he is now going to do
to all the Sitibi.
You could have
gotten killed.
He wasn't
going to hurt me.
He fired a gun
in the hospital.
Come here.
Maybe next time, don't
yell out that warning.
The bloody eye was from an enlarged
lymph node blocking the retinal vein.
We restored
circulation,
but it means we've got
to add lymph involvement
to the heart and lungs,
and rising fever.
I'm just going to
sit here quietly.
Why?
I feel like I've been inadvertently
undermining your authority.
So I'm just gonna observe.
I'm not gonna say a word.
The heart could point
to sarcoidosis.
I'm thinking the X-rays indicate
a lack of hilar adenopathy,
which rules it out.
Staph aureus?
No.
Because he smokes?
He's miming
a thermometer.
He says the fever's
not high enough.
So some other infection.
He's wrong.
The fever could be misleading
us into thinking infection.
Talk.
It could all fit
with lymphoma.
I need you to spread your
legs so I can do an "H".
Can't be lymphoma.
LDH is normal.
He's got good
liver function,
it's masking
the elevated levels.
Biopsy the lymph node.
Check it out.
Makes sense.
Guess you don't need me.
Oh. By the way, you might
want to close the blinds.
It's really bright
in here.
It's just
a wild coincidence
that he thought
you were a rude jerk.
Come on, give me
the benefit of the doubt.
You said he's a jerk.
I barely talked.
You talked!
All I wanted was to
sip morning espresso
next to a peaceful,
burbling fountain.
You could be
sipping Courvoisier
next to a replica
of the Playboy grotto
if you tell him
what you got on him.
I don't have
anything on him.
I don't want
Closest he's been
to Vietnam,
ordering the Mee Krob
at that place on the corner.
Mee Krob is
from Thailand.
Exactly.
What did you do? Why do
you think he's faking?
I saw his mail.
You broke in?
No. He was holding it. Private
medical insurance, not from the VA.
Plus he's gotta
be early 50s.
He's too young to be a
vet. So, I looked further.
You did break in.
Online.
There's no reference to him
in any of the vet records.
Why would he fake
being a veteran?
Well, just look
how you're acting.
People have been tiptoeing
around this jerk for years.
Normally, we'd all tell the
amputee to go screw himself.
Victims get pity. Heroes get
adulation. It's way better.
Thank you for trying to
help me out with my neighbor.
Now forget
the Vietnam stuff.
I could prove this.
But you won't because
you'll be too busy
writing him
a letter of apology
and dropping it at his door,
without knocking at his door.
I didn't do anything.
That guy's a total ass.
Which is the point. It's easy
to be nice to people you like,
but being nice to people you
hate, that's a skill. Do it.
Thank you
for saving my life.
The man that
tried to kill you,
he said that you were
preparing a massacre.
The Sitibi are
my countrymen.
I am fighting
a guerrilla war.
In a way that's
being called genocide.
Twenty years ago, these same
Sitibi rebels took over the south.
They massacred
tens of thousands,
and they would
happily do it again.
I'm trying to impose order.
I'm trying to prevent
a genocide. Genocide.
My own son, my youngest,
he is a student here.
He hasn't
spoken to me in years
because of what he read
in your newspapers.
But what he read
is not true.
What about your
Youth Labor League?
There, I was at fault.
I hired men who, in their
zeal, stepped over the line,
and there were abuses.
But that will
not happen again.
Hello?
How's it going?
Normal-looking nucleus.
How's it going
with you?
It worried me
when you joked
about letting that man
shoot Dibala.
I wasn't joking.
You can't want
to kill anyone,
especially not
your own patient.
It's only natural
to feel...
No, it's completely
unnatural.
Only psychopaths
can kill other people
without having some
sort of breakdown.
Not when it's justified.
Look at soldiers.
Even when
it's justified.
Am I trying to kill our
patient? Of course not.
But if he died, am I
supposed to just pretend
that wouldn't be good
for the world?
The cells are neatly
differentiated. This isn't lymphoma.
I thought I had detected the
sickly sweet smell of maple syrup
and socialized medicine.
It smells like victory.
That big flag in your place prompted
me to chat with your housekeeper.
Turns out you're a citizen
of the Great White North.
You broke into
my apartment?
Technically, no.
Well, technically, yeah,
but two steps,
hardly...
You're going to jail.
Speaking of, you know what can get you
six months and
a $100,000 fine?
Falsely claiming that you
won a medal in Vietnam.
You think I'm faking?
Canada did not send troops to
fight in Vietnam, you idiot.
They sent troops to reinforce
the '73 Peace Accords,
which is where I tried
to free a 12-year-old boy
who stepped
on a land mine.
Thirty-six years later, every
second I feel pain in my hand
like I'm still grabbing
that boy's arm
even though
my arm isn't there.
So, no, I'm not faking.
Oh.
On a related note,
go Maple Leafs.
Did you get
the biopsy results?
Is it lymphoma?
No.
So we have to move on.
Infection,
perhaps autoimmune...
Did you get
the biopsy results?
Yes, I just told you.
Is it lymphoma?
Cameron and Chase?
They both really
like diagnostics,
and I think they both really
like watching House torture me.
Anyway, thank you for
understanding about the job.
I had two really
crappy alternatives.
There was a third.
What's that?
You could have
stepped aside.
We both would
have lost our jobs.
You could have asked Cameron
or Chase to take your place.
They wouldn't
have wanted to.
You just said they both
really like diagnostics.
You want to
go back in time?
I want to
make this work.
I want to understand you. I mean,
you know how you made me feel.
If you could
do it again...
I made the right decision.
I need your confidential
medical opinion.
Is the President capable
of thinking clearly?
Obviously not right now.
Will he ever be?
I think...
Neurons don't grow back, and
he's already in his decline.
Anything he tells you, any command
he gives, how will you ever know
it's not just the delusions
of a sick, mad, dying, old man?
He just started
spiking a fever.
It's scleroderma.
You don't have some clever
way of telling me this time?
Patient's dying.
I'm done with clever.
Look at his skin. It's
tight for a 75-year-old.
Based on his admission
photo? Bit subjective.
Fever points
to infection.
And now he's got nodules on his
fingers. That's blastomycosis.
Nodules? You're calling
tight skin subjective?
I'm with Foreman.
We would have seen fungus
balls on the head CT.
Fungal lesions
can be missed.
We could
settle this with a test.
Anticentromere antibodies
would point to scleroderma.
Point to, not prove. And his fever's
too high. We have to treat him now.
If we treat wrong, we could
send this disease into overdrive.
You're with me on
the scleroderma?
I guess. I just don't care
enough about the patient
to waste my time trying to
convince anyone. We get it.
You don't like the guy, you
don't want to work on this case.
And yet
you're still here.
Why don't you
take a stand?
Either do something
about it or shut up.
Treat him for blasto
if you want.
I'll get Cuddy.
I can convince her to...
This isn't a democracy.
I don't care who you get.
At least for right now,
this is my department.
We're treating
him for blasto.
Start him
on amphotericin B.
Inject my IV
with an air bubble.
What are you doing?
I will have
another heart attack.
No one will know.
Let her go.
You tell my colonel I'm a sick,
dying old man who can't be trusted.
I didn't say...
You were trying to
put a gun in his hand
and point it at my head.
The gun is now in your hand.
That is a practical
difference, not a moral one.
If you want me dead,
then pull the trigger.
It is not so easy when
you have to do it yourself.
Allison.
I guess I didn't
want you dead.
If you touch
my wife again,
I'll kick your ass
out onto the street.
I don't care
who you are.
I did her a favor. I showed
her her true character.
She's a better person
than you are.
She is too weak to
act on her beliefs.
But that is not her fault.
Almost everyone is.
Even my own advisers,
my own colonel.
All they do is negotiate
and debate and sign treaties.
They are appeasers.
All the while, we are beset by
assassins and traitors, the scum...
Cockroaches?
What are you gonna
do about them?
What is an enemy to you?
Some younger physician
who covets your office?
In my world, there are dangers
and bloodshed and death,
and that makes you a man.
And men make choices.
And your choice is to send
bands of drunk, crazed children
to massacre
an entire people?
Don't ask me questions you
don't want to know the answer to.
I saved your life. I deserve to
know what you're planning to do.
Whatever it takes to
protect my country.
You broke
into his apartment?
I didn't break in.
I wish I believed you.
I can fix this.
I already did.
He was gonna
press charges,
but I promised him
you'd leave.
You're kicking me out?
I'll explain it
to your psychiatrist,
but, yeah, you gotta
go somewhere else.
House, I know
when things go wrong,
usually you just double down
and get more involved.
But here,
you could go to jail.
And I truly believe
that you've changed enough to
know this is the right thing.
We need
a blood sample.
We gotta do the
anticentromere antibody test.
It'll show House is right.
It's scleroderma.
Why are you
doing this now?
Because I didn't
want to kill him.
And you're right.
I have to take a side.
So I'm gonna do what I
can to keep him alive.
I'll get you the blood.
Positive for
anticentromere antibodies.
We gotta get him
off the anti-fungals
and onto steroids
immediately.
I told you before.
This only points to
scleroderma. It doesn't prove it.
You're just gonna
ignore the test?
Blasto still fits best.
I know it's not conclusive,
but when you put it
with all
the other evidence...
I've made my decision.
Have you told Thirteen
you were wrong to fire her?
What does that have
to do with anything?
I've worked with you long
enough to know you're reasonable.
You can usually admit
when you're wrong.
But there's some
deep part of you
that when you find
you're wrong about
the most important
decisions you've made,
you get insecure
and you just retrench.
If you wanna mess up your
relationship that's your right,
but you mess this up,
our patient dies.
Switch him to steroids.
Hi, honey.
How was your day?
Morning.
First of all, my bad.
I've gone through this whole thing
recently. I don't want to bore you.
Short version, I'm really
trying to do work on some stuff.
This is a definite setback.
Although, in fairness, you
really did make it tough.
Phantom pain in
your missing arm,
the five different kinds of
painkiller in your medicine cabinet,
that's what this magic box of
neurological trickery is for.
This'll be a lot easier if you do what
the crazy guy who tied you up says.
Put your hand in there.
Now look.
Mirror magic.
Your arm is back.
Now clench both your
fists at the same time.
Clench. Real hard.
If you believe in God,
pray that
this is gonna work.
You might also want to ask
him why he blew off your arm.
Ready?
Now let go.
Oh, my God.
You relaxed it.
For 36 years I've been in
pain, and it's finally gone.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
O2 sat's down to 88.
Going through the main stem
bronchus into the right upper lobe.
Get them out of here!
No!
It's okay.
Bleeder.
Cauterizing.
Got it?
Yeah.
Get the paddles.
I'm going back in.
What is happening?
He's bleeding into his lungs. Charging.
Another bleeder.
I can get it.
Hold on.
There's a third.
God, there's a dozen.
Shock him.
Clear.
Charging. Clear.
You want to
curl up and cry,
the lounge chair's
a little more comfy.
I switched his meds.
I thought I was wrong, so I
took him off the antifungals,
put him on steroids
like you said.
You know what
that means.
I was too late or I was
right in the first place.
So, either you
killed him
by not having confidence
in your opinion
or you killed him by being
too attached to your opinion.
If you're anything like me,
and by the way, you are,
you need to know which.
He's under lock and key
in the morgue.
His government wants their
own doctors to do the autopsy.
They're taking his body
out tomorrow.
There's a reason
I hired you.
You used to know what
to do with a locked door.
I went down to the morgue
to rerun the antibodies test.
You ran it twice.
Turns out,
I couldn't get in.
They had
an armed guard.
But I saw this.
It's a sign-in sheet
from the morgue.
Your signature,
9:45 this morning.
That's right before
you guys ran the test.
What were you
doing there?
Follow-up on
a clinic case.
What case?
You think this is
really important?
One of the patients
in the morgue
was a 70-year-old woman
who had scleroderma.
You and Cameron, if you
took that woman's blood,
you could have
messed up the test results
so we treated Dibala
for the wrong disease.
Cameron had nothing
to do with it.
You son of a bitch!
He was going to
kill the Sitibi,
every last one of them.
I don't care what
he was gonna do.
He came to us and put
his life in our hands.
All the good we've done,
every life we've saved,
it would have meant nothing
if we just sent him off to kill
hundreds of thousands of people.
Look at the news.
The moderates
are taking over.
There's hope
for peace talks.
You tell the world
that I faked this test,
Dibala becomes a martyr.
The massacres begin.
I cover this up,
I become your accomplice.
You think you can
guilt me into that?
If the cops are
going to come for me,
please warn me
so that I can
tell my wife first.
Chase,
you really think you can
kill another human being
without any consequences
to yourself?
No.
My neighbor called.
He sounded happy.
That's nice.
Even nicer, he's approving
the garden expansion.
Huh.
And even more nicer,
he's not going
to press charges,
even if you
don't move out.
What did you do to him?
I was nice.
You really want
to know?
I think I want to give you
the benefit of the doubt.
Alligators' main
prey is smaller animals
that they can kill and
eat with a single bite.
Oh!