How about
the name Brooke?
She just doesn't
seem like a Brooke anymore.
Brooklyn?
She's a baby,
not a city.
What do you think, bud?
Got any suggestions?
Toadette.
I'm hungry.
I'll get you guys
something to eat.
You're okay.
Okay.
I was paged?
What are you
doing here?
Can we talk
somewhere?
I was thinking...
Sarah?
Yeah.
Where's the baby?
No one saw
anyone go in or out,
and the baby's
not in the nursery.
What was her condition?
Five weeks pre-term.
C- section because
of mom's preeclampsia.
Is that the father?
Mr. Lozinski, I'm Dr. Lisa
Cuddy, Dean of Medicine.
How long were you
out of the room?
Fifteen,
20 minutes, tops.
Was there
a proximity alarm?
No alarms.
What's that?
The bracelet on your baby's ankle has
a microchip that would set off alarms
if she were carried
through an exit.
Call the police, shut down all
the exits. We're on lockdown.
Nobody moves until
we find that baby.
Why won't you
sign the divorce papers?
It's been on my
to-do list, sorry.
Will you sign them?
Not until we have a real
conversation about our marriage.
Okay, I made a mistake
coming here. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna leave
this copy here.
Code Seven. Code Seven.
All non-essential
personnel and guests,
please remain
where you are.
Security personnel should
report to their staging areas
and await
further instructions.
All patients, please
remain in your rooms
and use call buttons if
you need medical assistance.
Please remain calm and wait for
hospital personnel to come to you.
Do not try to leave your
room until the Code Seven...
It's clear all the way
down. Nurse, just leave it.
But it's...
Leave it.
You need to get
into the room now.
Please notify hospital
personnel or police immediately
if you see anything
suspicious.
We cannot allow anyone to
leave the hospital at this time.
All personnel should remain
in their staging areas
unless otherwise
instructed by security.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gotta clear the...
Thank you for your
patience and cooperation.
And did anyone other than your nurses
ever come by asking about your daughter?
No. No,
just those two.
I'll check in soon.
Wait. Hon, what are you doing?
No, I need
to help them look.
You have
to stay in bed.
You pulled a stitch,
lay back down.
I've got it.
Why don't I give you
something to help you relax?
No, no. I don't want to
relax. I want to find my baby.
The police are searching room by room.
Who would take her? What
if she needs to be fed?
We're gonna find her.
Why aren't the police
talking to our nurse?
What now?
Truth or Dare?
Oh, no, you don't
want to mess with me.
Truth or Dare queen
at Newton North.
I was kidding.
I'm sure we can find something
interesting to talk about
without relying on some juvenile game.
Sure.
Truth.
They think I took the kid? Do
you think I would do something...
I'm just asking questions.
The dad let the older brother
hold the baby for the first time,
so I put her in his lap. After
a few seconds, she shrieked.
I'm pretty sure
he pinched her.
I need to know this stuff,
anything out of the ordinary.
It was sibling rivalry. I
thought it was kind of ordinary.
Hey.
What are you
doing down here?
I was looking for
McKenna's patient file.
Oh. You mean this file?
The one I said I'd get?
Two hours ago.
Seriously,
you don't trust me
with the immense responsibility
of fetching a file?
If you already found it, what
are you looking through those for?
Do you know
what these are?
The staff credentials files.
Those should
all be in HR.
Down here
to be digitized.
And we're locked in, and whoever's
supposed to be watching them is locked out.
We could look up
anything on anyone.
Malpractice records,
felony histories...
Put them away.
Come on.
We have a tiny window of opportunity to
gain some insight into our colleagues.
Okay. What if we just snoop on our boss?
I think I can
live with that.
You're on two milligrams
of morphine an hour.
How the hell are
you still awake?
No, don't tell me.
Ischemic cardiomyopathy.
If the blood's not
reaching your gut,
you'd have intestinal
hypoperfusion,
that'd be stronger
than the narcotics.
The nurse said I might
only have a day or two left.
She was being kind.
You're Dr. House,
aren't you?
Oh, God, don't tell me we used to date.
The limp, yeah, I read about
you. I sent you a letter.
Before they knew
what was wrong,
I tried to get you
to take my case.
Yeah, well, you should
have kept reading.
Heart disease is kind
of below my pay grade.
It started
as tooth pain.
No one got it that
it was a heart problem
until I had a series
of massive heart attacks.
This doesn't bother you?
You talking with your
mouth full? A little.
I meant the fact that you're
standing in here watching me die
because my file bored you.
I take maybe
one in 20 cases.
A lot of the people
I turn down end up dying.
It's really a good argument for
there being more than one me,
when you think about it.
Truth.
All right.
Have you ever
had a threesome?
No.
You haven't?
What, just because
I'm bisexual?
Well, yeah.
Do you understand
what bisexual means?
It doesn't mean you have
sex with two people at once.
And by the way, you didn't
ask me if I'd had a foursome.
Truth or dare?
Wait, you've had a foursome? No.
But now you've asked me two
questions so I get to ask you two.
You see why I was the queen.
Walker wouldn't do anything,
he's my son, too.
I don't mean to sound cold,
but he's your stepson.
We can't ignore
any possibility.
Walker's been getting in
fights a lot at school, lately.
Last week, he hit another kid with
a book, hard enough to draw blood.
If he did something
to the baby...
We were working on it.
We failed.
No. You had a conversation with House,
then came back, informed me
I'd been forever poisoned by him
and started packing.
It's interesting how your
story leaves out the part
where you murdered
another human being.
A dictator who was
committing genocide.
You thought about
doing it yourself.
But I didn't.
Right, because you're
not toxic like I am.
What do you think
is gonna happen here?
You're going to logic
me into coming back?
There must be over 30
malpractice settlements in here.
He did a brain biopsy
without CT mapping
"causing brain herniation
and death. "
Look at this one.
"Patient lost four liters of
blood from a botched penisectomy. "
On a patient
named Lisa Cuddy?
Damn it, they're all named Lisa Cuddy!
He's not even here and
he's screwing with us.
Where's the joy
in that?
You really wanna
get into his head?
Yeah, but I decided against
stabbing myself in the leg
or getting addicted
to pain pills.
You can skip
the stabbing.
Where did you...
Confiscated them
from a drug seeker in the clinic.
Didn't get a chance to turn them in.
It is after-hours.
I'll take one.
Walk in House's
shoes for a night.
One? I believe
he wears a larger size.
No cards, no flowers,
not even a phone call.
Let me guess,
lighthouse keeper?
I was a classics professor
at Princeton for 26 years.
Mostly research.
So, your closest colleagues died
2,000 years ago, that must be it.
Not that you have no friends because,
say, you're a miserable bastard.
What do you care?
The next few hours
are gonna be grim.
There'll be nausea, pain, no company
as soon as I get myself out of here.
I can unlock the regulator, you can
put yourself into a narcotic haze,
sleep blissfully
to the end.
Is that a favor
to me or to you?
Win-win.
No, thanks.
You're trying to guilt me
for not taking your case?
You think a classicist
doesn't believe in fate?
You think Odysseus would lie whimpering
like a loser in a hospital bed?
Come on,
take my offer.
Take the drug holiday,
numb yourself out.
I think you're the one
who wants to numb himself out.
Truth.
How did your dad react
when you came out to him?
He made me tea.
Seriously. Doesn't matter what I tell
him, he smiles, tells me he supports me,
and makes me some
peppermint tea.
Truth or dare?
Truth.
Are you dating anyone?
Now? No.
Interesting, you added
a modifier. Truth.
When you were dating
Foreman... No, no, no.
What?
If it was something
personal about him or us,
I just don't think that's right
to answer. We all work together.
That's the whole point of
this game, something personal,
preferably embarrassing.
Just pick something else.
You see,
this is your problem.
You act like you're
so liberal and open,
but you are the least...
I changed my mind.
Dare. Just no nudity.
Yes, nudity. I want
you to show your breasts
to Taub.
That is the most
idiotic dare ever.
Have you ever
played this game?
Well, I thought showing me your
breasts would be a little exploitative.
Your dare is in
the future, genius.
Hey, if you're saying
you won't do it...
No, no, no, no.
Of course I'll show my breasts to Taub,
tomorrow, perhaps, or
maybe sometime next year,
you know, because
I'm honor-bound.
Truth or dare?
It's understandable that you
wouldn't be happy right now.
Your world is changing.
Are you scared?
And how do you feel
about your sister?
I hate her.
Walker, this is important. Did
you do anything to the baby?
Did you move her somewhere? Hide her?
No.
Nobody'll be mad at you.
I said no,
so stop asking me.
Bad pain day?
Bad pain month.
And since
I'm not using it...
If you don't
want the morphine,
you must have
something of your own.
I was in rehab.
Had a little problem with
the "something of my own. "
Now all I take is ibuprofen,
and that's two flights up.
For the whole month?
The pain's migrated, I think
the arterial wall is damaged.
And what?
You don't know?
I haven't had
an arteriogram yet.
You don't want the test in
case the arterial wall is fine,
which would mean that the pain
is coming from something else.
What's her name?
Interesting that you'd jump from
physical pain to long-lost love.
You're projecting.
So, what's her name?
What time is it?
What does it matter to you?
It's T-minus four hours.
8:20. Now tell me
who she is,
and what are the pathetically long
odds that she's gonna visit or call.
Only that's a reason
not to take the morphine.
Dude.
Is the room
still spinning?
Mine is.
Maybe we shouldn't
have taken so many?
I'm gonna try
to stand up.
You be careful.
Oh, yeah,
that's working.
I can't feel my face.
No way.
Way. Hit me.
What?
Hit me in the face.
Seriously?
You know you've always
wanted to. Now's your chance.
That's a great idea. We can
start a fight club, maybe we...
Oh, my God, you're
right. That is so cool.
Okay, I'll even...
I can still feel my hand.
I wasn't ready.
What were you gonna do,
flex your goatee muscle?
Wait a minute.
This is your
credentials file?
Give me that.
That's why you came down
here, not for the patient file.
You wanted...
Okay, Robert. I will answer
whatever questions you want.
But then you're gonna
have to sign the papers.
Did you ever love me?
How can you
even ask that?
The first time you slept with me
was because you were on crystal meth.
I was on the drugs
because I was emotional.
It was the emotions that led
to the sex, not the drugs.
Not true.
After that, you refused to let
it go further than just sex.
Because I knew I was falling
for you and I didn't want to.
And that never changed.
You broke off our vacation
because I bought you a ring.
I got cold feet,
I'm not proud of it.
And then you almost
called off our wedding
because you couldn't
give up the idea... No.
Don't. ... of having
your dead husband's baby.
Don't bring him up.
Because even then
you weren't
sure about me.
Maybe if I was dying
when you married me,
it would've been
a bit different.
That's not fair.
It's not only fair,
it's exactly the point.
He was dying when you met him and he
was gone just a year into the marriage.
So, it was all
a honeymoon with him,
and I could never
match up to that.
The first time reality
intruded on... Stop this.
Just tell me the truth.
About what?
Did you ever love me?
I don't know!
Thank you for finally
telling me.
Truth.
You said you weren't
dating anyone now.
Does that mean you recently
were or soon will be?
Oh. Look who's
guarded now.
You had no problem talking about
your sex life, but your love life...
Fine, dare it is.
No nudity.
Now or in the future.
You're too much of
a nice boy, Wilson.
Let's let the bad boy
out for a bit.
You have to go steal
one dollar, right now.
From who?
Oh, come on.
"Interned at Hopkins,"
old news.
Here we go!
"Academic probation. "
I'm asking you
to please stop reading.
I'm afraid
I can't do that.
"Faked a lab result. "
Very wrong.
And you came down to destroy the
record before it gets digitized.
Permanentized.
Even wronger.
I...
I needed to beat all those
elite, spoiled kids around me.
To show no weakness,
to win at everything.
Why'd I just
tell you that?
I always talk too much
when I'm stoned.
Why'd I just tell you that?
It was stupid.
You had great grades. One lab
result shouldn't have mattered.
Except I didn't
think I deserved
to be at a top med school
in the first place.
Again.
Faking a lab result
is one thing,
but you needing to come down
here to destroy the records
12 years after the fact...
This isn't about
med school.
You don't think you belong
here at the hospital.
"Dr. Taub, comma,
Christopher Michael. "
So, this is what it comes
down to in the final hours.
Deifying some lost love.
Hoping to get her on the phone
and make everything perfect.
It's pathetic.
Either you left her for a reason
or she left you for a reason.
A phone call
is not gonna...
It's my daughter.
So, why isn't she here?
I left my family
when Gracie was six.
I was sort of
forced out, actually,
after I had had an affair
with a student.
For sex or love?
Neither.
I'd only married Gracie's
mother because of the baby.
But I didn't think I could
handle the commitment,
and just like any decent
academic, I proved myself right.
And what time it is
matters because...
She's a dance
teacher in Atlanta,
she gets home
from work at 9:00,
and I just wanted to
speak to her one more time.
That's my story.
What's yours?
Same thing,
pretty much.
I'm gonna be dead
in a few hours,
your secrets
couldn't be safer,
unless you're keeping
them from yourself.
I like being alone.
At least I convinced myself
that I'm better off that way.
And then I met someone in a
psychiatric hospital of all places.
She changed me.
And then she left.
We're better off alone. We
suffer alone, we die alone.
Doesn't matter if you're a model
husband or father of the year,
tomorrow will be
the same for you.
But yesterday
would've been different.
Hey, Daria.
Dr. Wilson.
Could you cook me up
a chicken sandwich?
Grill's closed.
It's important, medically.
Dr. Hadley needs a
high-protein meal right now.
She doesn't like to talk about
it but she has hypoproteinemia.
We got chicken salad.
Yeah, that's cold.
She needs to eat warm
protein for this disease?
Well, we could
give her cold protein
whose uptake enzymes
haven't been activated,
as long as you don't mind her risking
liver and kidney failure and eventual death.
But, hey, it's worth it so you
don't have to flip on the grill.
You don't have to be
obnoxious about it.
How do you look so okay?
I spent months wondering
how I made it go bad.
If you never loved me, then
I didn't do anything wrong.
Hey.
Allison, come on.
It's all right.
Still don't know
why I said that.
It's not even true.
I did love you.
Just not in a way that
would have ever worked.
Why not?
Because everything
you said is true.
I'm a mess.
I married a man
I knew was dying,
so God knows how
screwed up I already was.
Him dying messed
me up even more.
I pushed you
out of my life.
And I'm unfixable.
Not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Truth.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
No, I didn't
even play fair.
You asked me how my dad reacted
when I told him I was bisexual.
And the Huntington's.
No tea party?
I never told him.
He's been through enough.
So, he just visits his
heterosexual, healthy daughter,
and you go out to dinner and a
movie and talk about your garden?
I work late. He's staying at my house.
It's easier if I stay
elsewhere as much as I can.
You can't suppress your life
for his convenience.
You don't see
a little irony in that?
That's exactly what
you do for House.
When he moved in with you, you
bought a bigger place for him.
No wonder you're
not dating anyone.
You're right.
That woman, the woman
I'm not involved with,
her name is Sam Carr. But in
1990 and 1991, it was Sam Wilson.
Your ex-wife?
No, my mother.
Yes, my ex-wife.
Ex number one. She
friended me a few weeks ago.
We started e-mailing, turns
out she's recently divorced,
and I wanted
to ask her out.
You can't take
a woman to dinner
or else House will go running
straight back to the loony bin?
You're not worried about House,
you're worried about yourself
because she's an ex,
so even dinner will mean
it's immediately serious.
What are your favorite
parts that you remember?
I liked how, when I'd wake
up in the middle of the night,
you'd put your arm around me
and you wouldn't even wake up.
I liked watching you stand up to your dad
at Christmas when he yelled at your mom.
How you didn't even know you
were strong, but you were.
What do you miss?
I miss a lot.
But when I think
about missing you,
I think about that dance class
that we took, for our wedding.
It's weird.
I think, "He's never going
to hold me like that again. "
Oh, God.
Come on.
I'm gonna miss this, too.
"Published in The New
England Journal at 26"?
I finished all the lab
work a year earlier.
"Led a group of surgeons to fix
cleft palates in Bangladesh"?
What can I say? That concert
was very moving to me.
I have to take a knee.
I don't get it. This has gotta be
the most spectacular file down here.
Why are you pretending
to be ashamed?
I'd trade mine for
yours in a second.
When I was in med school, I
thought I'd be House someday.
Instead, I'm a fellow,
working with...
Working for people
years younger than me.
So, we both have
a few regrets.
You should be proud of yours.
Your life's been trending up.
No news.
How you holding up?
You let them sedate you.
Yeah.
Do you have kids?
A little girl.
I adopted her last year.
I adopted Walker right after
Donald and I got married.
What if I can never love Walker
the way I love my daughter?
Does that make me
a horrible person?
Let me get you
some tissues.
Did you request
some extra towels?
No. What? Why?
There are eight towels
in Sarah's room.
Okay.
There should only be four.
Housekeeping handles towels.
I need you to track
down their logs.
Figure out who was
up there and when.
Because they
got extra towels?
Just find the logs. Now.
Adrienne, you okay?
Sure.
What's wrong?
Adrienne,
give me your arm.
The hair on her left arm
is standing up.
Asymmetric
neurological function.
She's having
a pilomotor seizure.
She seemed fine
a minute ago.
She was, she's probably been
having complex seizures all day.
She'd be basically
functional,
but more or less
acting on autopilot.
She probably dropped
the towels off twice.
She could have
taken the baby.
We never really did
have a proper goodbye.
It's 9:00.
It's Gracie, I can't come to the
phone, so please leave a message.
I guess she's running late.
You don't seem
that surprised.
That's what you
expected to get.
You waited until
you knew she'd be out.
Her aunt said that
she starts work late.
Every now and then, I just call
to hear her voice on the machine.
I was never there
when she needed me.
What right do I have
to need her now?
None.
Which just means you're a
hypocrite. Because apparently you do.
Forget about rights. Just tell
her what you need to tell her.
It's Gracie, I can't come to the
phone, so please leave a message.
Gracie?
This is
your father.
I love you.
Anything?
We've covered every room
on Maldonado's logs.
Been everywhere she's been.
Where's the other cart? Isn't
there usually another cart in here?
Hey.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Hi.
Anyone in there?
Lockdown's over.
I should go.
Yeah.
I just asked
Sam to dinner.
Little baby's
all growed-up.
You gonna
tell your dad?
I'll stop by his hotel,
talk to him.
Hotel? You said he was
staying at your apartment.
Was there any truth
in anything you said?
The part about it being a good idea
for you to call Sam. That was true.
Good night, Remy.
Good night, James.
Code Seven has
been lifted.
Repeat. Code Seven
has been lifted.
You want your file?
Nah.
All hospital personnel
can leave their staging
areas... Good for you.
...and report back
to their department.
Thank you for
your cooperation.
We don't have to tell anybody what we...
Mmm-mmm.
You got the patient file?
I'll grab it.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
I think I'm ready to
take you up on your offer.
Dr. House? Lockdown
ended a few minutes ago.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry I didn't
take your case.
Me, too.
Gracie was the cutest
six-year-old you ever saw.
Interesting night, huh?
Interesting night.