Who is it?
It's Tom.
Tom, your husband?
What's he doing here?
Uh, what's going on?
I'm sorry. I know I'm
not supposed to be here.
But Evelyn's school
contract is due tomorrow.
I knew I was forgetting
something. Let me find a pen.
Hey.
Not quite sure what
Emily Post recommends
in this situation,
but I'm Tom.
Damien. Hi.
Sorry to intrude, I just... I wasn't
quite sure when she'd be coming home.
No problem.
Thank you so much
for catching this.
Yeah.
I'll get out of your way.
It was good to meet you,
and I'll see you
later, hon.
Bye.
So, he seems
like a nice guy.
Ooh.
Jules, you okay?
No, my stomach...
Here, lie down.
Ow!
Try to...
Get Tom.
Okay.
Ow!
Tom!
You know what
would be perfect?
Hmm.
French Toast Tower.
You still go to Mickey's?
What's your cholesterol?
It's my one vice.
I'm keeping it.
As much as I would love
to clog my arteries,
I have a 10:00 CT, and I still
have to race home, get changed.
Maybe you could keep
some clothes here.
Maybe I could.
He's just trying to
get into your skirts,
and I don't mean
metaphorically.
Well, he's got
the legs for it.
So, I will
see you tonight?
Yeah.
Bye, House.
Have a nice day.
"Have a nice day"?
How civilized.
I said I'd
stay out of it.
What?
Nothing.
Clearly something.
Nope.
House, on a list
of your attributes,
there's nothing that
even rhymes with "coy. "
Okay, I may have seen
something in the fridge.
Like the end of
your relationship.
She put the milk in the
door and not on the shelf.
It's not a big deal.
You hate that she did that,
but you didn't say anything.
You're trying to
get us to fight.
No, I'm trying to help. If
you got an issue, let her know.
I should've known that you
weren't done sabotaging this.
Fine.
Stew in your irritation.
Sure, last time it bubbled
over into resentment and rage,
leading ultimately
to a painful divorce
that neither of you have
ever really recovered from,
but I'm sure this time,
it'll be great.
Interesting case,
35-year-old woman
with fever and
abdominal pain.
ER ruled out all
the usual suspects.
Stop before you
interest me to death.
And she's in
an open marriage.
That's not interesting.
It's just weird.
Know what's weirder?
That other humans are
monogamous in the first place.
No other species on the
planet mates for life,
and if you're
gonna bring up swans,
they cheat like
everybody else.
They just have better
PR than rabbits.
Animals also eat their young
and kill their rivals.
That make it weird
that most of us don't?
Says the guy
whose opposable thumbs
have been all over how many
women who aren't his wife?
A functional open marriage
is like a unicorn.
It's a mythical creature
that doesn't exist.
Someone always
ends up unhappy.
Our patient's unhappy because she's
suffering from an intestinal blockage.
Boring. Now, I'm gonna have to
find a reason to rule it out.
What about
herpes colitis?
She picks up the infection
from one of her partners.
It takes root
in her colon.
STD panel was clean.
Chances are this couple was
unhappy in the first place.
This is their attempt to
save something that never...
Go on.
Herpes might not register if she
was exposed in the last six weeks.
But it would show up
on a barium enema.
Wait.
You're going to do it?
Gotta see if our patient is a
unicorn or just a slutty horse.
Think how much fun
Taub could be having.
Barium coats the inner
lining of your colon,
lets us get a good
look at it on the X-ray.
I can get somebody else
to pick up Evelyn.
I feel like I'm
abandoning you.
I'm on painkillers.
I'd rather this not be
what you think of
every time you
look at my butt.
Okay,
roll onto your side.
It's fill 'er up time.
So, is Evelyn
his new squeeze?
She's our daughter.
Must be interesting, growing up
in a production of Oh! Calcutta!
She's six.
She knows as much about our sex
life as any other kid her age.
You can explain
that she's the reason
the two of you
stayed married.
You've been in the room
five minutes.
You got us
all figured out.
Of course, you left out the
part where we love each other,
and we wanna
grow old together.
But you just don't
wanna be young together.
Look, when you
think about it,
tons of couples
do what we do.
It's just that
with most of them,
one spouse doesn't
know about it.
We decided
things work better
when people tell
each other the truth.
Tank's full.
I'll page
the radiology elves.
I'm not saying I hate it. It
just doesn't go with your eyes.
You hate it.
Little bit.
Any more heartless critiques
of my general appearance?
Nope. All done.
So, is she
as bendy as she looks?
Maya and I
are just friends.
No, you and I
are friends.
And you don't have coffee
with me three times a week.
She's an
interesting person.
She grew up in Ohio.
She has three brothers.
Fascinating. Last week that
Cambodian lab tech was telling us
how he survived
the Killing Fields,
and you left to
go get a donut.
So we flirt.
It's fun.
It's dangerous.
That woman would
totally do you.
You think?
Nothing is gonna happen.
All I'm saying is, if
you want to be on a diet,
you might want to stop hanging
out by the dessert cart.
X
- ray was clean. She doesn't have herpes colitis.
Or abdominal pain.
It stopped hurting
during the X-ray,
which means it was just an
intestinal blockage that passed.
We should
discharge her.
Absolutely, there's no need
to find any underlying cause.
These things
never happen twice.
Take her digestive system
for a test drive.
Give her
a radio-opaque milkshake.
X- ray every 15 minutes
to see if it makes
any unscheduled stops
on the way through.
We'll be here all night.
No, Taub will
be here all night.
Go talk to the unicorn, then
tell me you don't believe.
I did an abdominal CT
on a kid today,
and found a six-inch bezoar
made entirely of gum.
I mean, who gives a three-year-old
an endless supply of gum...
You okay?
Yeah.
I mean, there was hair in it
and maybe a piece of paper.
So, how long have
you been married?
One of the few drawbacks
of having an open marriage.
Nobody ever asks me about
current events or the weather.
The Yankees look
good this season.
Seven years.
And how long have you,
you know...
After three years,
we realized
that traditional marriage
was making us both miserable.
Most people get divorced
at that point.
Yeah, we didn't want
to get divorced.
We still loved
each other.
We just realized that
expecting one person
to fulfill all of your
needs forever is unrealistic.
There are happy monogamous
couples out there.
Sure, one or two have
the perfect marriage.
Everybody else has figured
out how to settle for less.
I don't want to settle and
end up resenting my husband.
I'd rather get the 10% he
doesn't give me somewhere else
so that I can really appreciate
him for the 90% he does.
I think something's wrong.
With your stomach?
My heart is racing.
Try to take deep breaths. I'm
gonna try to slow your heart down.
Is this because
of the blockage?
No. It's not working.
Need a crash cart
in here!
I need a list of all your sexual
partners from the last six months.
Why?
Your wife had
an arrhythmia.
The progression of
symptoms from bowel to heart
makes a parasitic
infection most likely.
Since Julia hasn't been
out of the country...
The only place that
I've been recently
is a business trip
to Nebraska.
But either of you could
have picked up a bug
from one
of your partners.
It's kind of complicated.
How many partners are we
talking about? Ballpark.
None.
None?
We have a great sex life.
I don't need anyone else.
So why not
just tell her that
and close this
whole thing up?
You married?
I was.
Did you ever agree to go see
a chick flick with your wife
or pretend to
enjoy classical music?
Stravinsky never groped my
wife in a Midtown hotel room.
She needs this.
I don't, but I don't want
her to feel bad about that.
He's lying.
Guy's got
a license to drill.
Why would he lie
about not using it?
That's not the lie.
The lie is that he gives
a crap how his wife feels.
If they're both screwing
around, that's one thing.
But she has a piece on
the side, and he doesn't?
The only way he'd
be okay with that
is if he's betraying her
in some other way.
Then in his mind,
it makes them even.
My unicorn isn't a unicorn.
It's a donkey with a
plunger stuck to its face.
Right, even a guy
who's not cheating
is doing it for
underhanded reasons.
No, no, no,
he's not being cynical.
He's assuming the husband is
doing something to even the score.
Which means he thinks
there is a score.
Which means,
cheating swans aside,
House believes
in monogamy.
He's being romantic.
What I believe is that men are
genetically engineered to be jealous.
Doesn't matter if I think there's
a score. I guarantee you he does.
Any of the wife's
partners pan out?
She's been with two people other
than Tom in the last six months.
Neither of them have been
outside the Tri-State area.
So we're back
to the husband.
You just said you
believed he wasn't...
He's doing something
behind her back.
What better cover than a
business trip to Nebraska?
Like that's
really a place.
Let's find his travel
records and get back to work.
You seem pretty mellow
about this couple's deal.
Thought you'd be first
in line to shake a finger.
They're still married.
I'm not.
Not that I could
ever do it.
I was jealous of House, and
Cameron never touched him.
Not counting the emotional fondling.
When my mom was dying,
my dad had an affair.
He told you this?
I'd seen them
get out of his car.
Two years after Mom died,
they got married.
Must've sucked.
At the time, yeah,
but looking back,
it makes sense.
My mom never
knew about it,
and he needed someone
to make him feel less alone.
He took care of my mom,
day in and day out,
for two and a half years
before she died.
He was devoted to her. Loving
someone else didn't change that.
So loving two people
at once is fine
as long as
one of them is dying?
Whoever's taking care
of me when I get sick,
I hope they've got someone
else to take care of them.
Tom was
telling the truth.
He really did go
to Nebraska.
Plane ticket and
restaurant receipts.
Forget Nebraska.
Maybe they just bought
their parasites at the mall.
You know, we should really
throw away that loofah.
They're imported. Sometimes
they're not sterilized.
We think our patient got
amoebiasis from hers.
She going to be okay?
We're treating now.
She should be fine.
It's actually
kind of bizarre.
She and her husband
have an open marriage.
They sleep
with other people?
Well, she does. Her husband's
totally fine with it.
That's crazy, right?
And you're bringing
this up because...
I thought
it was interesting.
More interesting than
your other cases, I guess.
You talk about your colleagues.
You rant about House.
You don't usually
mention your patients.
Is open marriage
something you want?
No. I mean...
I know you'd never...
All this time and
energy you spent
convincing me
you weren't cheating.
And there's
somebody else.
I'm not... Would you
like some more water, sir?
Okay.
There's a woman at work. People
say she's attracted to me.
But nothing's happened.
Nothing's going to happen.
I'm not having an affair.
But you want to.
No, honey,
I'm trying to be honest.
I don't want to make
the same mistakes.
Be honest then.
Are you attracted to her?
Look, she's attractive.
There's an attraction.
Aren't there men who
make you feel that way?
Of course, there are.
But it never occurs to me to
act on it, because I'm married.
To you.
And that's enough for me.
Aren't I enough for you?
Of course, you are.
Our patient's lost
all movement in her legs.
There are other doctors,
Chris. We're talking.
I'm sorry.
The woman's paralyzed.
I'll get a cab.
Tests show
no spinal cord injury,
no cerebral lesions,
no hemorrhage.
We finally got a stool
sample. The loofah's innocent.
No sign of amoebas
or any other parasite.
So paralysis, arrhythmia,
intermittent abdominal pain.
And he nicked
himself shaving.
Sorry, that was Taub. But
it was easier to solve.
Means he used the crappy
razor in his locker,
which means
he slept here.
Thanks to you.
I brought up open marriage
with Rachel.
It was a disaster.
On the medical front, we've
knocked out sex and foreign travel.
Could be
an electrolyte imbalance.
So the only time
you're not interested
in my marriage is
after you blow it up?
You were the moron who took
marital advice from Tila Tequila.
You pushed me
into this.
Figured it would either blow up
your marriage or make it more honest.
Either way, you win.
What about sex?
I'm talking
about the patient.
Is that cool
with everybody?
We ruled out sex.
We ruled out sex
with other people.
Tom said he and Julia have been
doing it three or four times a week.
And she's got
boys on the side.
Increased libido can be a symptom
of adrenocortical carcinoma,
which also explains
her other symptoms.
A woman who likes sex
must be sick?
Just because
everybody in this room
wishes that all women were horny
all the time doesn't make it so.
Get an MRI of
her adrenal glands.
Hi.
Okay if I take
the sports page?
Sure.
Would you mind
using a coaster?
Oh. Sure. Sorry.
It's okay.
Also, it'd be great
if you'd replace
the toilet paper
when you finish a roll.
And when you load
the dishwasher,
you can't put a big,
flat bowl on the bottom.
It traps the water so
nothing on the top gets clean.
And please don't throw banana
peels in the bedroom trash...
I haven't done
any of those things.
You're probably
not even aware...
I hate bananas.
Oh, my God.
It was House.
I'm sorry. He's been
trying to get us to fight.
Why would he think that
stuff would make us fight?
Because of the milk.
You put it in the door.
The body of the refrigerator
is the coldest part.
The temperature in
the door fluctuates,
which decreases
shelf life...
Wow. When did
you get all OCD?
I just want clean dishes
and unspoiled milk
so we can all
stay healthy.
Oh. It's about health?
What about the coaster? Does that
replenish my B12 or something?
Can we just drop it?
Sure.
You have this
list of annoyances
the entire time
we were married?
Get better, Mommy.
I love you, rabbit.
Julia, you have a guest.
Hi.
This isn't a good time.
Dr. Hadley, did you say there
was a video game in the playroom?
Maybe you can teach me
how to play one of them?
See you in Radiology.
Get out of
my wife's room.
Your relationship with her
stays out of our space.
I was worried about her.
Tom's right.
You should go.
So it's fine
if we have sex,
but if I drop by
to see if you're okay...
This is our family.
Sorry.
I spent two years
of residency
wearing shirts that
were a size too small.
How hard is it to ask me
not to put them in the dryer?
And I only did your laundry
because you were never home.
I didn't ask you to.
Of course you didn't.
You just got annoyed
whenever you didn't
have clean underwear.
I never said
I was annoyed.
That's the point.
You didn't say anything.
So I'm getting a lecture
on communication
from someone who had her lawyer
inform me our marriage was over.
Asking for an open marriage.
You got stones.
Conversation sort of got away
from me. It was a train wreck.
I think it's good
you brought it up.
I read a study that found
men who have multiple copies
of a certain
vasopressin receptor
are twice as likely
to be unfaithful.
Maybe you're just
one of those guys.
So my cheating is biologically
predetermined. Fantastic.
Multiply times five. We need
a better look at the medulla.
I thought
you'd be relieved.
This gets you off the
hook. It's just genetics.
I'm 5'6" and have
a receding hairline.
I hate genetics.
Medulla's clean.
I don't see you wearing
lifts or hair plugs.
That's because being short
and bald doesn't hurt anybody.
The only thing hurtful about
your other genetic predisposition
is that you keep
denying it.
It's not good
for you or Rachel.
There's nothing there.
It's not adrenal cancer.
And maybe you're
right about me,
but I'm not going
to stop trying.
Rachel's worth it.
Look up there. The lung. What is that?
You served me
with divorce papers
in the middle of a medical
conference in New Orleans!
I threw a bottle
into an antique mirror.
You exhibited an emotion. I
wish I'd known you were capable.
I loved you.
I thought I was gonna be following
you to Baltimore, remember?
I called about apartments.
I set up interviews.
How could you think that we
still had a real marriage?
We hadn't had
a conversation in months.
Maybe because I was working
two jobs to support us.
No! No, it's because
when you were home,
it was like talking
to a block of ice.
You were obviously
so pissed off at me...
I was killing myself so that you
could take that non-paying internship.
That you said
that I should take.
I was trying to
be supportive!
Why do I have to
be the bad guy?
Expressing yourself does
not make you the bad guy.
Okay, then, you were
being a selfish bitch.
VIQ scan confirmed the spot
on Julia's lung was a clot.
Think there's a chance
the husband's a plushie?
If he has a secret, I highly doubt
it's more relevant than the clot.
Clotting disorder
would explain everything.
Question is, which one?
Do you read any of
your departmental memos?
Only the ones
labeled NSFW.
Accounting notified you two days
ago about your patient's insurance.
Sorry. That's NNSFW.
Here. He doesn't have any.
Try not to bankrupt them.
I'm long past the number of
procedures that'll bankrupt them.
Julia's got insurance. I saw
the policy number on the forms.
The policy lapsed
due to non-payment.
I already made
three calls about this.
She should have
been aware of that.
No, that's just
a mistake.
Of course we have
health insurance.
We're actually a little
behind on the premiums.
But I pulled money out of my
retirement account to cover it.
They said that we'll be fine in a few...
Why the retirement account?
We'll just give you
a few minutes to...
By "we,"
she means "she. "
I lost all of
our savings.
Sounds like
a secret to me.
I started her on heparin
to prevent further clots,
but we still don't know
what's going on.
Of course the husband's
secret was money.
If it's not sex,
it's always money.
Unless it's sex
for money.
How did he lose it
anyway?
It's not medically relevant.
You're not going to care.
Wilson's been teaching me
how to care. Try me.
He builds wind turbines and leases
them out to local power companies...
You're right.
I don't care.
Clotting disorder. DIC, Factor V
Leiden, Antiphospholipid syndrome.
Vitamin K deficiency
also fits,
causes thrombophilia and is
consistent with abdominal pain.
Congratulations, House.
Sam ended it.
What happened?
Go test
our patient's blood.
It can wait
five minutes.
For everything
we discussed.
I'm sorry.
Well, at least you're actually taking
responsibility for once in your life.
I'm sorry that she left,
but it's not my fault.
I didn't even want
to get involved.
You dragged it
out of me.
What about the dishwasher
and the banana?
Yeah, she left
because of the banana.
I just wanted you to stand up for
yourself, tell her what you want.
If doing that causes her to
walk out for the second time,
well, then your relationship
wasn't going to last anyway.
Or you could've
stayed out of it.
I could've kept
my mouth shut,
been annoyed sometimes,
but I'd be happy,
because I'd
still be with her.
Now all I have
is cold milk.
As long as you're free,
you want to grab some dinner?
Did Tom go home
for the night?
For starters. I told him to
leave. I don't want him here.
Money is
a complicated subject.
Yeah, it's not the money.
I mean,
the money is bad, but...
When we first
opened our marriage,
I got involved with a guy
who lied about being single.
And one day,
his wife calls me.
She's crying, and screaming,
and totally out of control.
And I felt
superior.
I thought, "I don't ever have
to worry about feeling this way,
"because Tom and I are
honest with each other. "
Well, here I am.
Hi.
Sorry I didn't make it
home last night.
I needed to
run some tests.
You know what the worst part
was when you had your affair?
It wasn't the sex.
It was the lies.
Realizing that the narrative
of my life was totally wrong.
You weren't
stuck in surgery.
out of town.
I don't wanna go
through that again.
I told you,
nothing's going...
Thursday nights.
You have to be home
by midnight.
You don't bring her here, you
don't talk to her about me,
and I don't want to meet
her ever in any context.
Are you giving me permission
to sleep with other women?
It's what you want,
isn't it?
I want you.
No, you want
more than me.
You want that thrill.
But I love you, and I really
believe that you love me.
And we have
a good life together.
And at this point,
either I walk away,
or I try to accept
who you really are.
Tomorrow's Thursday.
Yes, it is.
All our tests
came back negative.
It's not
a clotting disorder.
Which means we need to
come up with a better idea.
So what causes problems in
the stomach, heart, nerves...
Oh, my God.
You know what it is?
Taub's wife gave the green
light for an open marriage.
He's wearing cologne
but not the stink of shame.
You've got a date?
I am going out with Maya
tonight with Rachel's blessing.
Mazel tov?
Maybe the problem
isn't her blood.
Maybe it's the vessels
carrying the blood.
No sign of schistocytes
or hemolysis.
So you're actually going
to sleep with another woman,
then go home
to your wife?
Thank God someone's keeping us
focused on what's really important.
Taub was going to do
all of that anyway.
Pulmonary
arterial hypertension?
Imaging showed normal diameter
in her pulmonary artery.
Here's a thought. Taub's wife
is now totally on the market.
Mind hitting me
with her digits?
She would love that,
but duty calls.
What's the matter?
My stomach.
Same pain as before?
Yeah. Worse.
Get the portable
ultrasound in here.
We need to get
a look at her belly.
Help me.
Pain, pain went away,
came back another day.
Question is,
what brought it back?
Physical exam was unrevealing.
Ultrasound was clean.
So afterwards,
you gonna shower
at your girlfriend's
or at home?
Patient. Abdominal pain.
Yeah, he's right. Let's get
this wrapped up before 6:00.
Taub turns back into a
faithful pumpkin at midnight.
The patient was out with her
boy-toy before she came in.
Maybe the pain was triggered
by sexual excitement.
Because lying alone
in a hospital bed,
contemplating
bankruptcy? Hot.
My point was that
arousal is a function
of the parasympathetic
nervous system.
If that's where
the problem is,
the pain could be triggered
by crying, which seems...
PNS also controls digestion,
which she's been doing
without screaming her head
off since she's been here.
What if what matters isn't when the
pain started, but when it stopped?
It was during an X-ray.
You think that cured her?
No, but House prepped her for
the X-ray with a barium enema.
That wouldn't treat
anything except...
Go.
You're in pain because part of
your intestine folded in on itself.
It's called
an intussusception.
It's cutting off blood flow.
We need to fix it
before your bowel
gets necrotic and dies.
Once you do that,
will I get better?
When this happens
in adults,
it's usually a sign
of abdominal cancer.
We'll fix the overlap, and then
search your intestine for tumors.
Foam?
I have a bad feeling
about this.
A friend can't
spontaneously buy
an overpriced Italian espresso
machine for another friend?
What did you do?
Nothing,
that's the beauty.
I genuinely tried
to help Wilson.
I told him to
stand up for himself,
which you know is
legitimate advice.
And his relationship
blew up.
Is he okay?
He'll be fine.
Point is,
I realized something.
I do nice things, nice things
happen to me. Karma works.
So you're
paying it forward?
If this should somehow lead
to Lucas dying or oral sex,
so be it.
You think I should
wear a tie tonight?
This isn't weird at all.
I mean, where's Rachel eating tonight?
Home.
What if she's
going out, too?
She's allowed to, right?
Of course,
it's only fair.
But I don't think
she will.
Your wife only
eats dinner at home?
If she did go out,
that'd be tough.
But I think
I can handle it.
Don't do it
unless you're sure.
I know I'd rather be
jealous than a liar.
Got something here.
Kelly clamp and scalpel.
Biopsy showed
non-specific inflammation,
which suggests IBD.
Only that doesn't explain
the cardiac problems.
Or her declining
kidney function.
We ran panels
during surgery.
Actually,
IBD does make sense,
'cause it can trigger
ankylosing spondylitis,
which would explain the
heart and the kidneys.
Start her on sulfasalazine
and TNF-inhibitors.
And Taub,
I'm not gonna see you
before you head off
for Gomorrah.
Just remember,
if you get disoriented,
Breathe through your nose
and look for the horizon.
I can't.
I really thought
I could do this.
Logically,
it makes perfect sense.
But all afternoon,
all I kept thinking about
was the two of you together,
and you touching her...
Nothing's happened.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
'Cause I really wanted...
No.
I've been an idiot. I don't need
anything else. I just need you.
You mean that?
I do.
I love you, Rachel.
I love you, too.
Let's go home.
Is that okay?
There are other doctors.
The treatment's
not working.
Her left kidney
failed last night.
The other one's
right behind it.
It's not
ankylosing spondylitis.
Kidney biopsy showed
she had IgA nephropathy,
which could be caused by or associated
with any of these conditions.
We've gone from too
few ideas to too many,
and our patient is
running out of time.
Why the lack
of afterglow?
Physio girl not as freaky
as you'd hoped?
I went home with my wife.
After all that?
You chickened out.
I can't hurt
Rachel like that.
Sickle cell anemia would've
shown on blood tests.
No flattened intestinal
villi rules out celiac...
Seriously?
Our patient is dying, and we
can't move past my sex life?
Seriously?
You think it'd kill her
if we spent 15 seconds
mocking you?
Time's up.
Normal liver enzymes
rules out Hep B and cirrhosis.
Alport and Anti-GBM antibody
are both untreatable,
so if she has them,
we can't help her.
And it can't be
Henoch-Schonlein purpura.
No inciting respiratory
infection and no rash.
I don't care
what it's not.
I wanna know
what it could be.
Well, everything
left on the list.
The list was
not created equal.
Neither was man,
by the way.
Hemochromatosis is a possibility.
Excess iron builds up,
causes problems
throughout the body.
Weil's Syndrome also affects
multiple organ systems.
And it wouldn't
have been treated
by the antibiotic
the ER gave her.
Sarcoidosis
makes sense, too.
Good.
Treat for those three.
I think
you should call Tom.
Am I going to die?
I don't know.
If he walked in here
right now,
I'd look at his face, and
all I would think is "liar. "
Don't you think
that's kind of unfair?
You say honesty
is all-important,
but you conveniently
ignore the truth
that some truths
hurt people.
Tom lied to protect you.
He was covering his ass.
I'm not talking
about the money.
Tom hasn't slept with
anyone else in over a year.
He told you that?
So my entire marriage
is a sham.
No.
Your husband,
who only wants you,
lied so that
you could be happy.
That seems
pretty real to me.
Yeah?
Hey.
Listen, I'm sorry.
Me, too.
I shouldn't have said...
No. You were right.
I was selfish back then.
I'm trying to change.
And I don't know if
it's House or what,
but you're different, too.
I'm trying.
I always thought that
I was keeping the peace.
But I was just
resenting you
and giving you
a reason to leave.
I wish we had this fight
10 years ago.
Is it okay if we don't
give House the credit?
I recommend it.
0- for-3, her kidney
function is still declining.
We're going to need
to start dialysis.
Glad
the husband's back.
After missing
so many little deaths,
he should be here
for the big one.
Top six, anyone?
Polyarteritis Nodosa?
We would've seen some
improvement on prednisone.
Guy's wife is dying.
He stops to buy flowers.
They're from his garden.
Mercury poisoning fits.
Those are lilacs.
My mom used
to grow lilacs.
My dad made her
get rid of them
'cause there were
too many bees.
We ruled out HSP because there was
no inciting respiratory infection.
But in rare cases, it can also
be triggered by a bee sting.
We also ruled it out
because there's no rash.
Maybe we just
didn't see it.
Have you been stung
by a bee recently?
About a month ago.
What's going on?
I think your wife has
Henoch-Schonlein purpura,
systemic vasculitis
that can cause lesions
and inflammation
throughout the body.
It's pretty awful,
which explains why it was named
after a German. Actually, two Germans.
Lesions can pop up
in the heart,
sometimes
in the kidneys.
But always on the skin. Means
you'd have a rash somewhere.
I don't.
Not that you know of.
Okay, I'm going to have to check
your holes. I'll start with the mouth.
If there's nothing there, then
things might have to get kinky.
Say "ah. "
Ah.
I was kind of
hoping for kinky.
Is that good or bad?
We'll treat her with high-dose
IVIg and cyclophosphamide.
You should be fine.
I'm going to be okay.
I love you.
That is adorable.
Other than you still wanting
to have sex with other dudes
and him bankrupting
your family,
I think you kids are
pretty much home free.
And...
You two made up?
No.
You can
thank me later.
I'm all in.
All right.
Fold.
Jesus.
Nervous?
I'm getting there. I'm
getting some nervousness.
You need a hand?
Thanks.
Sorry about canceling
the other night.
Me, too.
You wanna
go somewhere?