Help!
Help me!
Dry heaves are
gone, so am I.
I'll check with the doctor.
No, no, no. I'm here voluntarily.
Just got to check with me.
I'm sorry. Dr. Nolan left
specific instructions.
She's not sick, she's
scared. So tell her to tell...
Wow.
And he's black.
Thought you'd be a little more
sensitive on the slavery issue.
You can't keep me.
Dr. House,
you look a lot better.
I am a lot better.
No painkillers,
no hallucinations.
Leg hurts,
but it's manageable.
Great job.
Gonna miss you.
Want to start missing you
as soon as possible.
Well, legally, you're free to go
whenever you want, but I suggest you stay.
I'll take it
under advisement.
If you thought the hallucinations
were from your Vicodin problem,
why didn't you just check
yourself into a rehab facility?
I was deluded into
thinking I might be crazy.
But you have been
abusing Vicodin for years.
Never had delusions,
never had trouble sleeping,
never had any problems, other than
narcissism and anti-social behavior,
until two colleagues
died, your father died.
Your issues run
deeper than Vicodin.
That's not gonna
cheer me up, is it?
You need to be transferred
to our long-term ward,
started on medication,
talk therapy...
Yeah. I get it.
Just one thing I'm getting hung
up on. I can leave whenever I want.
How about I start with that?
You can't go back
to practicing medicine.
I don't want
to practice medicine.
I've decided I want
to be an astronaut.
Well, if you want your
state astronaut's license,
you're gonna need
my recommendation.
Is that a popular
new treatment, blackmail?
You need to get better.
Welcome to Ward Six.
So, brass tacks.
What do I have to do and
how long do I have to be here?
Depends on you.
Process is pretty basic.
If you follow the schedule,
agree to take meds,
participate in group and individual
therapy, we can work on goals...
I set a goal.
Excellent.
What is it?
My goal is to get your boss to write
the letter that I want him to write.
Now let's talk process.
I can smile through
gritted teeth and play nice,
but there are serious risks of
violence involved in that choice.
So I'm going with turning
this ward upside down,
making you and your boss'
job and life so unmanageable
that he'll write whatever he
has to write to get rid of me.
He's all set.
Thanks.
Yo, I don't need
an escort. Get off me.
Who are you?
You believe these guys?
Lecturing me on manic depression,
like I couldn't write a book or two.
I stopped taking my meds because
I want to stop taking my meds,
because nothing is wrong with me. No
reason to keep dragging me back here.
When I'm on them, everything slows
down, that's when the problem is.
Hey, nice to see you.
My roomie last time
couldn't stand me.
Really?
I'm Juan Alvarez.
J.A.'s my stage name,
but Alvie's what everybody
around here calls me.
Like the Woody Allen
character in Annie Hall,
but the Puerto Rican version
and not as neurotic.
So, what do I call you?
You're actually waiting
for an answer this time?
You can call me House.
He's a brick house
Hey, wait up.
I've already got the whole place
wired, so I'll give you the rundown.
Yo, everybody, this is
my new roomie House, y'all.
Main thing you gotta know...
Is this a line?
Hey, Gabby, meet my
new roommate, House.
You can call him Hizzy.
No, you can't.
Don't worry, she won't
call you anything.
She hasn't talked in like
10 years or something.
Good you came here. You need
to know the lay of the land.
I need to request a new room.
You're funny.
You're also gonna come
here to get your meds.
I'm not on any meds.
You either?
Good for you.
Tell me my mind
works too fast,
probably tell Usain Bolt
he runs too fast.
Excuse me. I know you're busy
ignoring me, but my mini-bar is empty.
You think Bolt could
do the long jump?
That sport
needs to evolve,
had the same world record
for like 20 years.
I think if one guy
launched himself head first
and right before he hits the
ground does a front flip instead,
get three extra feet
out of that, easy.
Go be that man.
My head!
You're not getting
any Haldol. Sorry.
That's Hal. His real name is Connor,
but we call him Hal because...
Yeah. I got it.
We can't play that.
They keep it locked up.
I wish we could,
but at the same time,
you can imagine
how annoying that could be.
Crazy people playing
on it all the time.
We'd never
get any peace.
Come on, I want to
introduce you to everybody.
You think
he's serious?
He's a doctor. He knows that acting
out will only reinforce our diagnosis.
Or it'll work.
You actually think this is something
we should be concerned about?
A patient makes a threat, you
should always be concerned.
There are two new additions to
our ward. You all know Alvie.
Thank you.
Hold your applause. It's great
to be back here in Mayfield.
Not just for the food,
not just for the ladies...
Well, okay, maybe
just for the ladies.
And you should also
welcome Greg to the floor.
Don't worry about the name.
Just passing through.
I don't want to
break any hearts.
Can we go outside now?
Not now, Jay.
So he's claustrophobic, right?
You're claustrophobic.
Can I get a pen
to write this stuff down?
Where are you going?
Where's he going?
It's okay.
Paranoid. Check.
Dr. Beasley, I'm having
an issue with the food.
What's the problem?
I swear I'm eating
less and less
and I just keep getting
bigger and bigger.
A crayon, anybody?
We'll talk about it
another time.
I understand you all had
art therapy yesterday.
Maybe we can hang some of
the new pieces on the wall.
Cut your wrists, huh?
Greg, there are
certain topics...
Oh. I'm sorry,
is suicide taboo?
Gosh, if I've broken a rule on
my first day, I will kill myself.
Group's over.
That flew by.
You realize you're not the first
uncooperative patient on this floor?
Really? Is there a club?
Yes. Come with me
to the clubhouse.
That didn't take long.
I'm that good.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, Alvie,
let's see some action.
Me! Me! Me!
Pass. Pass. Pass.
Good!
Come on, guys.
Ready to play nice?
Would you believe me
if I said yes?
No.
Then yes.
You do know
I'm trying to help you.
I also know you're trying to
be sweet, caring and effective.
You're just not.
You want out.
Just talk, be honest,
try to work with people,
try to deal with people.
Okay.
House! House!
He's on my team.
Shut up.
Nobody likes you.
Hey. Am I crowding you?
What?
Can't see the sun?
Oh, no.
Everything's closing in.
Okay. Okay.
He's the claustrophobic one,
right?
Because I'm doing
this from memory.
You have to dribble.
Why?
CIA satellites aren't watching
me, they're watching you
'cause you're
wearing green.
That one was
just too easy.
Seriously, anorexia? Were
you supposed to be a girl?
And in answer to
your implicit question,
yes, those pants
do make you look fat.
How upset were you
when you woke up in the ER
and you were still
alive and a failure?
Two-nothing,
good guys.
You're right. It is
rewarding to reach out.
You can't go up there.
It's yard time right now.
Put it on my tab.
I think you'll find music
therapy is more effective
if the patients are
inside to hear it.
Where'd you get the key?
They gave it to me.
So, if she ever talks, are
we gonna get a German accent?
No. She's my
husband's sister.
So let him come
play the piano.
He doesn't
know how to play.
Nice. A little heavy
on the right foot, though.
See her head?
It bobs to the music.
It's the only real reaction
I'm getting from her.
Feels like we're talking.
You're not talking.
Her head is bobbing
to her pulse.
Are you a new doctor
on the ward?
Technically, yes.
Can I lead this time?
Come on.
Leave the lid unlocked
when you're done.
Can you close the door? You're
letting all the cool air out.
If you keep up this
scorched earth policy,
you're gonna end up
living in this room.
Are you ready
to try another strategy
or do you want me
to leave you in here?
Twenty-one. Two-one. That's
game. Hey, House is back.
I'll get the ball.
Come on. I need some meat.
I got no one left to play.
I'll play you.
Pssh, girl. Come on,
House. You can serve.
I had some time to think about
the approach I've been taking.
I'm new, I'm unhappy here, and
I've been taking it out on you guys.
Unfairly.
It was misdirected anger.
'Cause when you think about it,
the real jerks here are the doctors.
House.
You see how they give
you a ping-pong table,
but no paddles, no net.
It's like they're mocking you.
Preach.
The game is called table
tennis not table volleyball.
Greg, you know where
this is gonna end.
Whoever saw a tennis
court without a net?
A little run-down park across
from my apartment, growing up.
Three courts, no nets,
no one ever used it.
No one's gonna try to hang
themselves with a ping-pong net.
Of course not.
That's ridiculous.
It ain't right, Doc. You
treat us like little kids.
Little kids are allowed to play
ping-pong, they can play the piano.
Yeah, worse
than little kids.
All right. Why don't we just
go and sit down and discuss it?
No, no, no! No! I want
to discuss it right here!
Guys.
Guys!
We want...
House is right. I think
everyone here can handle these.
Seriously?
Is that your strategy? Give
everybody what they want, except me?
You're a natural leader.
You could do something
useful down here.
For them.
Definitely for you.
Or we could keep fighting.
If you think
you can break me,
if you think I'm not every
bit as stubborn as you.
He came to fight the Man
And he had the master plan
But it started to unravel Nolan
smashed him with his gavel like...
Shut up.
So, you're gonna keep trying
to make them miserable?
No.
New plan?
Yep.
What is it?
I don't know yet.
His mind is burning
The wheels are turning
The butter is churning
You think Nolan can keep
House from strolling?
You know, it's easier to come
up with a new plan in silence.
Right. Cool.
Can I hum?
I'd like you all to welcome another
new addition to our ward. Steve.
Freedom Master.
Steve Elkerton's
just a cover.
It's like Clark Kent or
Bruce Wayne or Peter Parker.
Cool, we get more Jesuses
than superheroes.
Well, I try to blend in,
in the outside world,
but I figure in here
everybody gets it.
Hey, we're living
in the Ward of Justice.
Alvie.
Can you explain a little more
about what you think everybody gets?
That there's good
and evil in the world.
And some people
are special,
and they're chosen to help
keep evil forces at bay.
You don't think
you can stop bullets, do you?
I move out of their way.
Can you read minds?
No.
Group time, Greg.
Why isn't she talking?
She needs help. She needs
somebody to save her.
That's what we're
all trying to do.
Let's take five minutes.
Everybody get to know Steve.
I can fly.
I know you're scheming,
working on your next elaborate
plan to get out of here.
Why don't you put the plan on hold
for a few days, see what happens?
Just let me do my job.
If you prefer private to group, we
can do that, maybe try some SSRIs.
If you think nothing's working, you
can always go back to your schemes.
God, if only you'd said
that two minutes ago,
before I came up with my new
scheme. Now I'm committed.
Get it?
Shaq up in my area
I'm a better baller
and a better rapper, what?
And I'm good
at basketball, too!
Do you have
third-floor privileges?
Ever since I shared in group
about my uncle fondling me.
Is that true?
Yeah.
And now I can use the
third-floor vending machines.
Do you eat sour cream
and onion chips?
I mean, the whole point is the dipping.
Sure, we save
time by not adding
the mix to the sour cream,
but you're missing out...
I need you to break
into Nolan's office.
Commando style.
I want you to focus.
You want me
to mess him up?
Go into Nolan's office,
look at his calendar.
I need the name of the woman
he met with at 11:00 today.
No problem. And I'll get
you some old-school chips.
If they have them,
I'll get you some dip,
but I've never seen dip
in the vending machine...
Yes, get me chips
and dip. What else?
I get it, I get it.
Plan B.
"B" is for blackmail.
I got you covered.
Commando style.
Let me go! I just wanted a
little snack. That ain't right.
Yo, I didn't know the machine
was moved. I want some Ritz Bits.
Yo, I might be pregnant.
I get these cravings.
You get the name?
Nolan's schedule book just has a big "X"
marking out the whole middle of the day.
Then we can assume the girl
he's with is called "Nooner. "
Nooner, nooner
Nolan's gonna spoon her
He's gonna fork her.
And then he's
gonna knife her
I didn't get a chance to check
the phone or anything else.
That's okay.
I got her license plate.
I call my friend,
he gets the name,
I get the letter that
gets me out of here.
You got phone privileges?
I'm on level minus four. I'm
still writing with a crayon.
You?
You gotta be a level five.
That's like the top
of the Space Needle.
Hal's the only one
that's up that high.
Hal's a level five?
They give him a point every
time he clears his plate.
I've been eating
his potatoes.
Will he sell you
some minutes?
No, I pay two cigarettes
for the potatoes.
Phone's worth a lot more.
Can you cheek a pill?
No.
That's too bad for you.
You sure
you're good with this?
Yeah, yeah.
Gotta be done.
So, how do we start?
I think we just start.
Make it good. Make it real.
Just do it already.
Code Gray!
Give me
five milligrams of Haldol!
Get him off me! Hey!
Give it to him.
Dude, that was awesome.
You think Hal will
mind if they're wet?
House?
No, it's your other
friend at the asylum.
How's it going?
Hallucinations are gone,
so is the Vicodin.
How's the leg?
How's the pain?
They got me on
some non-narcotic.
I'm dealing. I need you
to run a license plate.
Was there a hit-and-run
on your floor?
House, just do
what you're supposed to do,
listen to the doctors, and
I'll be able to visit soon.
Track down the owner of this car and I'll be
able to visit you. In your office. Tomorrow.
My doctor's too smart, too old, and too
well-dressed to only be running one ward.
He screwed up
something in his life,
and I think
he's doing it again.
I need her name, so I can
blackmail the blackmailer.
House, he called me.
What did he want to know?
He wanted to know about you.
He wanted to warn me that
you'd be calling for something,
and he told me if I wanted to help you
get better, I had to let him do his job.
Yeah, well, now I'm calling you
to tell you that if he calls you...
House, I'm so sorry.
I wish I could help you.
You can.
Turns out,
You're my only friend.
House ain't a newbie
Now he's living on this floor
And I hate you.
I'm gonna cooperate.
That's not much of a plan.
That's actually their plan.
No. I'm pretty sure their plan is
for me to actually swallow the pills,
to actually cooperate.
I'm so proud
of my little roomie.
I only taught him
everything he knows.
One, two, three.
Okay, Stomp, you start the
betting. Highest card wins.
That's probably
a fold. Richter?
Two cigarettes.
He's not confident, Alvie.
You can crush him. In the
form of a rhyme if you wanted.
No regrets
Raise 10 cigarettes
Whoa. That's a lot of nerve for
someone with a two on their head.
You're messing with me.
You can't raise 10,
I only have five.
Throw in your phone card.
I'm not gonna throw
in my phone card.
Can I play?
Come here.
Why?
I want to see if you've
got what it takes.
Give me your best poker face.
Too rich for my blood.
You can take my seat.
Med time!
How are you
feeling today?
Better than yesterday,
not as good as tomorrow.
I've been humming to her.
She sways.
Might be significant.
Are you ignoring me or are you
just letting my charm wash over you?
Kind of tough
to play and chat.
Couple of weeks ago,
you told me
playing to her was
a complete waste of time.
You're right. Your playing
does get worse when you talk.
I assume she loved music.
She played for the Philadelphia
Philharmonic. Cello.
If she responded to the piano, she
might respond even better to the cello.
I play a little.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll bring one
in Tuesday. Thank you.
Different desk.
Different doctor.
You've been on meds
for a while now.
I'll be checking in with you periodically
to see if we need to adjust your dose.
Any dry mouth?
Trouble sleeping?
No.
Can I go now?
There's a manic out there
with a fresh carton of cigarettes
and he's a terrible bluffer.
It's nice to see that you
and Alvie are friends again.
Tell me about your fight.
He hit me, I hit him back.
Repeat until pulpy.
Alvie told me you
instigated the thing.
That tends to be
the way fights work.
Different interpretations
of the same circumstances.
Very understanding attitude.
There's that tone again.
You're smart.
How come every time you compliment
me, it sounds like an accusation?
You're not having any side-effects
from your meds, which is unusual.
It's not that unusual.
The story about the fight
isn't adding up.
Why don't you stop pretending that
you haven't reached a conclusion?
You don't trust me. Actually,
it's more fundamental than that.
You don't like me.
I didn't say that.
You think I'm not
taking my meds.
Are you?
Yes.
So, what do you want me to do?
Want me to take a urine test?
Will that earn your trust?
Actually, yeah.
Have at it.
A little dignity, please.
You know the rules.
I have to watch.
Yes, but you don't have to have court
side seats. Can I at least use a stall?
For he himself has said it
And it's greatly to his credit
That he is an Englishman
He is
An Englishman
Get it while it's hot.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Freedom Master, think
you could help me out?
You need help?
Of course. That's what I do.
Great. Could you move
the piano for me?
Five hundred pounds
is not too much, is it?
Is there something
trapped underneath or...
No, I just want to move
it away from the window.
I'm sorry, my powers
aren't for frivolous...
Just one quick lift.
Why are you doing that?
House, it's none
of your business.
I'm just curious, as a
doctor. What are you doing?
Either he is Freedom Master
and he shouldn't be here
or else he's suffering from a
serious and dangerous delusion
that he needs
to deal with.
So legit medical reasons.
You're not just trying to break the
guy because he's a little different.
He's not different,
he's delusional.
Can you help me out?
What is she looking at?
You're not
a superhero, Steven.
You're just a regular person,
that's okay. I can save her.
We're all just regular people.
It's what we do with that...
They stole her voice box.
They have it in there.
That's what she's staring at.
She's always staring at...
Your wife is dead.
Good can defeat evil.
Not every time. Evil people killed
a lot of good people that day.
You couldn't save her.
No one could save her.
It's in there. Her voice is in
there. Her voice is in there.
Code Gray.
Her voice is in...
Her voice is in there!
Don't do it.
I'm not doing anything.
You're thinking.
Things go from thinking to
doing way too fast in this place.
Keep thinking, you're gonna
wind up with no mo in your mojo.
I'm thinking
of hitting you again.
You hate Medina, you hate all
of them, you want to hurt them.
You gotta keep pretending.
Step away from the hate.
What's the difference between
pretending to cooperate and cooperating?
Pretending is pretending. It's
not real, you don't mean it.
I sat and watched while he did
something stupid and pointless.
I cooperated.
In a few days, you won't have to
watch because you're going home.
You'll be getting
your job back.
Everybody, inside.
Closing ceremonies, everyone
attends. One of you is going home.
It's been a great week.
A number of you have made
tremendous strides.
But today we're here
to congratulate Susan.
We are proud of her. We
wish her well and we hope
to never see her again.
To never see her again.
Isn't it pretty?
Where's Freedom Master?
He isn't able to take part.
Get out there. He said
everybody has to get out there.
Talk. Say something.
Dr. House,
leave him alone.
Did you drug him?
Of course
I didn't drug him.
He's in flat affect.
He's practically catatonic.
Hey, we got cake.
He's fine.
Double chocolate.
Yummy, yummy.
Don't tell me that
he's fine! You did this!
He was functioning.
He was happy.
He was delusional.
Yeah. He's way better off now.
Dr. House.
Let's talk.
Thinking sucks.
I'm not allowed to get
angry? They screwed him up.
And for the record,
I am two privilege
levels above Susan.
I got the same
depression scale score.
Every patient is different. It's
not about scores and levels and...
Happiness is happiness, the test
is the test, coping is coping.
And you think you're...
Absolutely!
I need to address
some deeper issues,
which I could do on
an outpatient basis.
Three hours a week?
That's just my opening offer. If you
want to counter, I'll likely fold.
No.
"No" is not an argument.
You trying to frustrate me?
No.
"No" again?
I can cope. I'm coping.
In fact, I'm coping
better than you think.
I've not been taking
my meds. Not one.
And yet I still scored a
"high-functioning" on your depression test.
So your proof of your
well-being is that you lied?
Manipulated.
My proof is that I can fool
the test, I can fool you,
which means
I am high-functioning.
I'm sane, rational, capable.
I should not be here.
These are your
pills from today?
I'm not gonna take it.
I'll just cheek it again.
Lick it.
You want me
to lick your hand.
I washed.
It's sugar.
Your test results were improving
too regularly and too quickly.
I was concerned that you
weren't taking your pills,
that it was all an act. So
I switched you to a placebo
to see if your improvements
would continue.
Your psych tests
told me nothing,
but your urine tests
told me you were faking.
You need to stop
fighting the system.
You need to let me
do my job.
So, what's the next plan?
There is no new plan.
I'm out of plans.
So, what do we do?
We stop talking.
I see you got some
cello in your trunk.
No, it's not a euphemism.
Are you spying on me?
I'm living in
a psychiatric hospital.
Staring out of the window
is what we do.
I assume you'll need
help carrying it up.
I still got
grounds privileges.
And who's going to carry you
when you're carrying the cello?
Yes, cast aside the useless
cripple. How very German of you.
Seriously. The thing weighs a ton with
that case. I think I'll need a dolly.
Or we could ask
Clark Kent to pitch in.
The dolly's
probably easier.
The dolly already
feels good about itself.
He was a happy-go-lucky superhero
until they told him he has no powers.
You let him help out,
he feels good about himself,
might be less depressed.
So, why do you
put your life on hold
to visit your sister-in-law
five times a week?
Am I somehow a bad person
for showing compassion?
No. You're not even a bad person
for lying about why you're doing it.
Oh, that is impressive.
That is a superhuman feat.
Why don't you take a rest before
you fly that thing up to the ward?
He's still depressed.
Give me your car keys.
You gonna dangle them in
front of him to entertain him?
I'm gonna make him
feel like he's flying.
I'll just drive him around the
grounds, top down, wind in his hair.
Seriously? You're
gonna say no to that?
Why are you
so nice to me?
I think you have
a good heart.
Would you still be nice to
me if I told you that I lied?
I'm not just driving around
the grounds in your convertible.
I'm kidnapping him
and stealing your car.
You sure?
I was just starting to feel
a little heat between us.
Thought we had kind of a Bonnie
and Clyde thing going there.
Bonnie and Clyde
get shot to pieces.
Hmm. See you.
You can do this. And if you
hold my hand, I can do it, too.
Don't let go!
Going up!
Freedom Master is back!
Keep it down, Freedom Master,
you're scaring the good citizens.
That was the coolest
moment of my life.
It was fun.
You can repay me by
telling Nolan he's an idiot.
Smell that fresh air. And
the warmth of your yellow sun.
We do enjoy it.
Careful of the traffic. Don't
want to go damaging any fenders.
Hey! Hey!
Come on. Get down.
There's no cry for help.
There's no cat in a tree.
Thank you, Greg.
No!
He's lucky to be alive.
He's got a lacerated spleen,
rotational pelvic fracture,
compound break
of the femur and humerus.
Everything in your life has
been about finding the truth,
but suddenly, with this guy, you decide
to reinforce a sick man's delusions.
You just wanted to take
a swing at me. Hmm?
You don't care about getting
out, you don't care about him.
You don't even
care about the truth.
You don't care
about anything, House.
I'm transferring you
to Winslow Psychiatric.
You'll have better luck pulling
the wool over their eyes. I'm done.
Don't.
I need help.
So, how is this
supposed to work?
You sit. I sit. We talk.
About what?
About whatever you want.
You want me to whine
about my mother?
Do you want to whine
about your mother?
I could tell you about the time
I was five and my goldfish died.
If that's where
you'd like to start.
I've had a billion things
happen to me in my life,
how am I supposed to know
which ones are relevant?
As far as I'm concerned,
they're all relevant.
Well, we better get moving 'cause
this session could take 50 years.
Yes, you are the sum of
everything that's happened to you,
and, yes, some events are
more relevant than others,
but the only way we can figure
out which ones are is to talk.
So, tell me,
what's on your mind?
What do you want?
I want to get better.
Whatever the hell that means.
I'm sick of being miserable.
So you'd like to be happy?
Again with the reflecting.
Yes, I'd like to be happy.
Being happy is
an excellent goal.
Not many patients
can crystallize
exactly what they're
hoping to get out of this.
Well, bully for me.
So, now all
we have to do
is figure out how to get
you from here to happy.
SSRIs? That's your
genius technique?
I don't think we should
ignore any tools that can help.
I know you don't have
a problem taking drugs.
For my leg. For pain.
Well, think of this
as being for psychic pain.
I don't want to
change who I am.
Miserable?
You think that by taking
meds you'll lose your edge?
Stop making the unique connections
that make you a successful doctor?
If Van Gogh
was your patient,
he'd be satisfied painting houses
instead of the Starry Night.
Van Gogh would still be making
inspired paintings of the night sky,
just maybe not from
the room of his asylum.
You don't know that.
I know both his ears
would be intact.
And I know his life
would be better.
I know this doesn't
come naturally to you,
but you want my help, which
means you need to trust me.
Hmm.
Delicious.
Why are you here?
Waiting for my
communion wafer.
You're cheeking it, right?
Nope.
Tell me you're
cheeking it.
I swallowed it.
No, you didn't.
We don't take meds.
You don't take meds, Alvie.
I decided to get sane.
You're scamming again.
You can tell me.
I'm not scamming, Alvie.
They broke you.
They didn't break me.
I am broken.
And stop worshipping me and go
worry about your own loser life.
I hate you.
Prom?
Got an assignment for you.
Role playing?
I'm not sure how pretending
to be a businessman
with a foot fetish is
going to help, but I'm game.
Have you connected with
any of the other patients?
You've been here
four weeks.
Tell me about your relationships
with the other patients.
Diane is convinced
that Silent Girl hates her.
Richter is not as
paranoid as you think,
he just likes
that you think that,
and my roommate hates me.
Only one of the
things you said
indicated how somebody else
feels about you. So...
I'm sure they've done some form
of rudimentary analysis on me,
concluded that I'm a jerk.
You know, there is a way for
them to find out things about you
without deductive reasoning.
I have had relationships.
You've screwed up
relationships.
Every one of them.
Almost like that was the goal.
I want you to trust people.
Try.
Get dressed.
Just open up?
Just open up. Trust.
Strangers?
We'll start with strangers,
then work our way up.
If it helps, I find "Hello"
to be an excellent ice breaker.
Hi.
It's like hello,
only shorter.
Yes.
Glad we were able
to save that time.
Judging by the fancy suit,
I'd say you were a donor,
but the nervous demeanor says
maybe you've had issues,
probably that's why this
place has personal meaning.
But this is supposed
to be about me.
I take advantage
of my friends.
Friend, really.
I've only got one.
It can be tough sometimes.
I'm not gay.
Neither am I.
Actually, I am.
See that guy over there?
He's my lover.
He's also my psychiatrist.
Which some would argue
is a little inappropriate,
but they just don't know
what love is. Am I right?
You're not gay.
No.
But I have to tell
intimate secrets to people.
Maybe they should be true.
Hadn't thought of that.
To be on the safe side,
I should probably do both.
Starting with the fun ones.
Come on, let's get me better.
Hi.
I'm a philanderer.
Oh.
Philanderer doesn't mean
that I give a lot to charity,
it means...
I know what it means.
You were asking me if there were
any nuts in the hors d'oeuvres.
What?
Honey.
What did my husband
just say to you?
I was asking him if there were
nuts in the hors d'oeuvres.
Then where
is your EpiPen?
My what?
No one with an allergy would
walk around without an EpiPen.
Give me your purse.
No.
Stop. No.
What really
happened is...
I thought he was cute.
I hit on him.
We're going.
You having fun?
I did connect with one guy,
but then my propensity for
screwing things up overtook me.
Then my desire to have fun
overcame my propensity.
You didn't screw it up.
The assignment wasn't to get you to
trust people with a piece of your soul,
the assignment was to teach
you that you can trust.
Did any of these people rat you
out as the obnoxious womanizer
or the porn producer
that they think you are?
Why do you think that people would
treat you worse if they knew the truth?
Good night, Doctor.
Are you in trouble?
Apparently not.
So, what's next?
You wanna be my pimp?
Why don't we just talk?
Okay.
How come you weren't pissed
at me for stealing your car?
It was a nice thing to do.
Hmm. I'm not sure about the
German-English translation of "nice. "
The stealing was nice or the
ruining of Freedom Master's life?
What you did was misguided
and irresponsible,
but it was also nice.
You gave him a moment
of pure happiness.
You asked me why I come
here so often to visit Annie.
She was my best friend.
Then she started pulling
away from everybody.
The doctors don't know why.
I think
I married her brother
because he was the only other one
who was going through the same thing.
But he stopped visiting
after a couple of years.
I just couldn't stop.
I miss her.
I should go.
Good night.
So, what happened?
You're talking to me now.
No.
Was it fun?
Yeah.
She kissed me.
Don't read into the phrasing.
We kissed each other.
And how do you
feel about that?
How do I feel about that? It was
a kiss. Kisses are good things.
Okay.
That was a loaded "okay. "
Not at all.
Why would you assume that?
You're being judgmental.
If I'd said that I had some delicious
Chilean sea bass for dinner last night,
would you say, "And how
do you feel about that?"
If the sea bass
was married, I might.
See,
you're being judgmental.
Isn't that against
your code or something?
I'm simply
stating the obvious.
It's complicated, not
just because she's married
and not just because
you're institutionalized.
I know you spent the last 12 hours
trying to figure out what that kiss means.
Who was that woman you were
with in the parking lot?
When you deflect,
it's more effective when
you're not that transparent.
Obviously you have
no problem with infidelity.
You're trying to rationalize that if
it's okay for your doctor, it's okay.
But just for the record,
I am not having an affair.
Then who is she? Why do you
think you're working so hard
to figure out the details
of my personal life?
Might not have to work so hard if
there were some personal items in here.
You've got one number
on speed dial, it says "Dad. "
Come on,
how old are you?
Why are you so afraid
to talk about this?
I want to talk about you. I want
to know who I'm taking advice from.
I'm not giving you advice,
I'm asking you questions.
I think that kiss meant a
lot. I think that scares you.
I think there are
no personal items in here
because you have
no personal life.
How do you think
you and Lydia will end?
You are a lonely man.
You've screwed up every
opportunity you've had in life.
What's the ending
to this story?
I don't know.
Visiting time.
Why did you kiss me?
How many
reasons are there?
I like you. It felt like a
nice way of showing you that.
How'd it
go with Lydia?
I found out she can only be happy
so long before the catatonic guy
with two broken limbs rolls off the
elevator. Philosophically speaking.
Why do you value your failures
more than your successes?
My mother caught me masturbating
to pictures of her mother.
Can we get past
these cute deflections?
Successes only last until someone
screws them up. Failures are forever.
So you accept that fact?
You accept that there's
nothing you can do?
Okay. I accept the fact
that there's nothing I can do.
Now what can I do?
You acknowledge failure
and you move past it.
You apologize.
Wow.
Powerful things,
these apologies.
You get someone
to jump off a building,
you say two words and you
move on with your life.
Hardly seems fair.
Is that the issue?
You caused him pain.
If the world is just,
you have to suffer equally?
You're not God, House.
You're just another screwed-up
human being who needs to move on.
Apologize to him.
Let yourself feel better.
Then you can learn to let
yourself keep feeling better.
Hey.
Dr. House.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Time for group.
Group time, everybody.
I have a surprise.
Two weeks from today, we're going
to have the Mayfield Talent Show.
Talent show?
Who's in it?
I'd really love it if everybody
here could participate.
But then
who's gonna watch?
The staff will come.
Friends and family.
Are you going to tape this?
No, it's just for us.
Well, if it's just for us,
I vote we don't do it.
Think of it as a fun way to
work on our therapeutic issues.
Alvie, maybe you could
sing one of your songs.
I don't sing, I rap.
Okay. Well, you can write
something just for us.
I don't write.
I just do. Freestyle style.
I think you're gonna
wanna be prepared.
Make something special.
Always special.
How about you, Diane? Is there
something you'd like to do?
I don't have any talents.
Sure, you do.
You all do.
Steve, don't you think that
Diane has hidden talent
that we'd all like
to see come out?
You really think
he's going to answer?
Eventually.
Why?
Because things pass.
Things change,
doesn't mean they get better.
You gotta make
things better,
you can't just keep talking
and hope for the best.
Diane, maybe you and I can work
together and figure something out.
I can save him.
"They stole her voice box. "
That's what he said.
That's what
she was staring at.
That's why he's staring.
Dr. House, please.
Because there's
a music box in there.
Orderly.
Come on,
just give it to me. I can...
I'm not having
a psychotic break.
I promise you this will work.
It's that blue box
on the top shelf.
This is what you wanted. This
is what you needed. A voice.
You thought you could cure
Silent Girl with this.
So by your own rationale,
it should cure you.
There's nothing wrong
with you. You're healing.
All the parts work.
Just speak.
Come on. Speak.
Say something.
I think maybe everyone
should take a break now.
You're trying to fix,
instead of moving on.
I brought Dvork.
Four hands.
What?
I need to know
what this is.
It's sheet music.
I told you. It's just
two people having fun.
There's two possible outcomes.
It ends, someone gets hurt, or it
doesn't end and someone gets hurt.
So the end sucks, it doesn't
mean the beginning has to.
Everything ends, life ends. It
doesn't mean that we can't enjoy it.
I can't...
I can't do this.
All I know is I was happy five
minutes ago, and now I'm not.
How is that better?
Goodbye, Lydia.
I'm really worried
about ECT.
Apprehension's normal.
Has anyone else had it?
They shocked me, man.
Thanks, that's
very reassuring.
I don't know if
I should do it.
Just do the treatment
or shut up.
Greg, there's a process.
Yes, a process. Wouldn't want to
disrupt the process with results.
Hizzy had a rough
night last night.
Guess he decided to go back to
being an ass instead of a hypocrite.
Let's move on.
Alvie, are you making any
progress writing your rap?
Yeah. But really, no. I just
don't want to write my songs down,
it takes all the spontaneity out
of it, it's not of the moment.
Alvie, if you
write things down...
When the time comes, my rhyme
comes When my spotlight shines...
Yeah. You're a genius.
Rhymes with penius.
Sorry to interrupt, Dr. Beasley.
Dr. Nolan asked me to give you this.
Is this a day pass?
He'd like to see you.
Thanks for coming.
I was hoping you could take
a look at my dad's chart.
A consult?
What happened?
You went through every
sane doctor in town?
I thought you wouldn't
mind getting off the ward.
The cleaning lady found
him on the kitchen floor.
Doctors here don't think that he'll
recover. That I should pull the plug.
I want a second opinion, so I
thought I'd be a fool not to call you.
Lacunar infarct converted
to hemorrhagic stroke.
He squashed his brain.
They didn't miss anything.
That's what I thought.
That's what you knew.
His brain has been
replaced by blood.
It's over, and it's obvious to any doctor
who looked at that scan. Even a shrink.
You want someone to tell you
that what you need to do is okay.
You need permission.
Absolution.
Not now, House.
You have
no friends, no family.
At some point, you made a
mistake, you lost everything.
And now I'm the closest
thing you got to a friend.
Just shut up.
I don't need you here
to play this game.
I'm sorry
I pushed you away.
It's what I do
when I'm afraid.
Again, the German-English
translation may be a little off.
I'm not crying
because of you.
I'm crying because
I'm pathetic.
I brought her cello. In case she
magically wakes up for the show.
Well, then I take
the apology back.
We're all pathetic. It's what
makes everything interesting.
I'm sick of life
being interesting.
You're nobody
'til somebody loves you
'til somebody cares
Ladies and gentlemen, the
one, the only, Juan Alvarez!
Yo, yo, what's up? Ward Six is
jumping off, y'all.
Give it up for DJ Richter
on the ones and twos.
Yo, DJ Richter, spin that.
Welcome to Mayfield
Where the day feels long
We act strong But there's
got to be something wrong
See, we got hidden talents
You don't see hidden secrets
If we could show you those...
Then we wouldn't
have no regrets
Wanna know my secret?
Sit back and let me explain it
My Pop split, Momma got sick
Clich, ain't it?
Now I'm a manic Hispanic
I'm trying to make it work
But the doctors
think I'm lazy...
And my roommate is a jerk
Dr. House is
in the house, y'all
Give it up for Dr. House
to the stage, y'all
Paging Dr. House
Are you there, Dr. House?
It's on, bring it on, on
Oh, yo, he's coming
to the stage, y'all
It's Dr. House on the remix
Dr. House on the remix
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
They say to take their pills
They say don't be a creep
But how can I get better...
If I can't get no sleep
You gotta think before you act
in order to progress
If you don't make connections
then your whole life is a mess
Yeah, so tell me, Doctor
what I really gotta know
How do I get better?
Just do a talent show!
Oh, well, I guess I'm just a
mess, yes! Preach it to me, brother
A life of restlessness
But at least
we have each other!
We got each other!
Like two brothers
from another mother
Duck and run for cover
Ward Six
How are you doing?
You hanging in there?
Usually, I open with that.
Thanks for staying.
So, what do you
want to talk about?
Things are actually...
Actually good.
You're not just saying that
because you don't want to complain
in front of the guy
who just lost his father?
I'm not that cured.
I still got stuff to do,
but I'm good.
I'm sorry.
I was trying
to prove a point.
I was trying to be right.
I ended up putting you
in a dangerous situation,
and I was not equipped
to handle it.
And you got hurt,
and it's my fault.
And I'm sorry.
Med time.
I'm going to try one of
those pink ones today. You?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Got a surprise.
Today we're here
to congratulate Annie.
We are proud of her, we
wish her well, and we hope to
never see her again.
Never see her again.
If you go silent
for over a decade,
you don't just get to slide
right back into society.
She's going to a rehab
facility first. In Arizona.
Her family's moving there.
I'm sorry, House.
I just found out myself.
I want an overnight pass.
I can help you with this.
I've earned it.
You have, but...
Isn't extending trust part of the
whole "getting me better" thing?
If you insist on a pass,
I'll give it to you.
But I know where you're going and I
know you haven't thought it through.
We need to sit down
and talk about this.
Please give me the pass.
Hi.
Hello. Who are you?
I'm...
Ben, go inside, okay?
You didn't say anything.
And now Annie's leaving, and
I hear you're going to Arizona.
My husband travels
to Phoenix a lot,
his corporate
headquarters are there.
We've been wanting
to move for years,
but we've been
tethered here.
Now we're not.
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to go.
But I can't break up
my family.
I can't leave my children.
I just don't
want it to change.
I'm sorry that I didn't
come to say goodbye.
I thought it ended
kind of perfect.
I have to go.
Not the most exciting use of the
overnight pass I've ever seen.
She left.
And
I'm lost.
I'm gonna
write your letter,
to the medical board,
recommending that
they give your license back.
You can't just console me by giving
me a lollipop when I skin my knee.
Two things
just happened.
You got hurt, which means
you connected to someone else
strongly enough to miss them.
And more important,
you recognized the pain
and came to talk to me, instead of
hiding from it in a Vicodin bottle.
The fact that you're
hurting and you came here,
the fact that you're taking your
meds, and we're talking right now.
Come inside and
get some sleep.
Tomorrow, you can start
saying your goodbyes.
Today we're here
to congratulate Greg.
We are proud of him, we
wish him well, and we hope to
never see him again.
Never see him again.
House.
Back off. People
already think we're gay.
What do you need, Alvie?
My meds.
I want to get better.