Are you ever
coming to bed?
I still say
I'm a vegetarian.
You can say that
you're an astronaut,
but that doesn't
make it true.
A salmon is not
a vegetable, Frankie.
Well, apparently eight out of
10 commenters agree with you,
except for the part
where you said,
"I believe what
I want to believe. "
That, they found
a little judgmental.
You blogged
our argument?
I asked you to quit
talking about me.
I don't want a bunch of
people that I don't know
hearing stuff that's meant
to be between me and you.
I write
about my life,
and you're
a big part of that.
That's great. I want to
be a big part of your life,
but I don't want to be
a big part of their lives.
Take it down. Erase it,
delete it, make it go away.
Come on, man,
it's 2:00 in the morning,
these walls are made
of tissue paper.
I gotta be up in three hours to
do a wiring job out in Edison.
Sorry, we'll try
to hold it down.
Sorry.
Frankie, what happened?
No, no, that's not what you
think. Something's wrong.
We need a police
car at 152 Haverhill.
What are you two
talking about?
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
I think it's coming from my gums.
What are you
doing tonight?
Masturbating.
I'd invite you, but
people are already talking.
It's pathetic. You divide your nights
between porn and the Discovery Channel.
Right, playing Dance Dance
Revolution is a much better choice.
Okay, that was a gift from a patient,
and it happens to be great exercise.
I mean, who rents
porn anymore?
Can't you get that
stuff on the Internet?
You can, but you can't get disk
two with the director's commentary.
Come out with me tonight.
I'm going speed dating.
If you mean you're dating
on meth, count me in.
You need to
meet somebody.
This way, you meet
20 somebodies.
Over a five-minute
discussion of Proust?
Speed dating's
a meat market.
Yeah, dozens of women,
just waiting to be hit on.
Your odds of a happy ending are nearly
as good as staying home and watching porn.
You plan on doing
any work today?
I thought I might do a little
light doctoring in the afternoon.
Twenty-eight-year-old female,
sudden unexplained coagulopathy.
Could be congenital
thrombocytopenia.
Platelets look normal.
The patient makes money
doing freelance photography.
Some photographic processes
produce toxic gases.
She's a blogger. I can't see her
photos being anything but digital.
What does she blog? Politics?
Dominatrix? Cooking? I need recipes.
It's a personal journal. I don't
get putting your whole life online.
It's not that crazy. Privacy's
basically a modern invention.
Towns used to be too small for
anybody to keep any secrets.
What if it's not the platelets, but
the glue that holds them together?
No, thrombin and von
Willebrand factor are normal.
And knowing too much
about each other
is exactly why people leave
small towns and move to the city.
And a lot of people
choose to stay
because in return for zero privacy,
you get community, connection...
Big, red A's
for our tunics.
Connections are
for airports.
For people, we have
over 300 cable channels.
Her photos
may be digital,
doesn't mean she couldn't have
been exposed to some other toxin.
We should search
the apartment.
Eenie, meenie, minie,
Thirteen and Tiny.
This one's locked.
I'm surprised you took
the pro-community position.
I have friends,
I like people.
You also like secrets.
You deny it, that sort
of proves my point.
When we're left to our own
devices, we make lousy choices.
Ignore it.
I can hear you in there. Open
the door or I'm calling the cops.
We're four stories up, but there's
a fire escape on the other wall.
The ledge might
be wide enough...
We're doctors. We
aren't stealing anything.
We are collecting
samples.
Who are you?
The neighbor.
Did they say that you
could come in here?
Yep. What do you know
about Frankie and Taylor?
Not much. The guy works a
lot, but I see Frankie around.
We argue a few times a week, and
then we go back about our business.
What do you argue about?
Frankie's got some
strong opinions.
Wants to recycle
every molecule of trash.
You take the anti-recycling position?
Trash piling up for composting is
attracting every rat in the neighborhood.
I had to put down poison.
That's her private drawer,
what are you doing over there?
She says she doesn't have any
secrets, I'm taking her at her word.
Is there any chance Frankie
touched the rat poison?
Touched it?
She grabbed a chunk of it
right out of the mouth of the
schnauzer from down the hall.
Now every time I put the stuff
down, she picks it back up.
You brought a date?
Wilson seemed to think
it was a good idea.
You need to dive
back into the pool.
And he has
to swim in ours?
You go to a bar, you
bring your ugly friends.
It's not
a beauty pageant.
Life is a beauty pageant.
Little girls who kiss frogs
expect them to turn into you.
Come on, I'm not that good-looking.
Yeah, you are.
You kind of are.
So you attribute
every relationship
I've ever had to the
height of my cheekbones?
Not the whole relationship,
just the beginning.
The rest is your hair.
This is ridiculous.
Women aren't as distracted
by appearances as we are.
They look deeper.
You wanna bet?
You can't tell anyone you're
a doctor. You're unemployed.
You're also a little slow.
Misunderstand everything they say.
And lose the accent.
A hundred bucks says you still
walk out of here with a dozen names.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the fun is about to start.
When I strike this gong,
each man should sit at the
table you've been assigned.
When I strike it again,
date's over, move on.
I'm an oncologist.
My aunt and my grandma, they
both died from breast cancer.
Do you want
to talk about it?
I'm a diagnostician.
I find out what's wrong
with people and I fix it.
Don't all doctors do that?
Yeah, but they can't
dance like I can.
I play video games.
Oh, professionally?
I wish, bro.
After six months of chemo, we
thought he was out of the woods.
I don't want kids.
Check.
I'm thinking about
going from a C to a D.
Quadruple check.
And I'm on fire
for the Lord.
I'm a chocolatier.
I could tell
by your hips.
Yeah, I guess I could
afford to lose a few pounds.
I don't think I know
anybody who died of cancer.
Thank God. For you, I mean. Obviously.
Except my cat.
She died a few months ago.
I hate these things.
You here at gunpoint?
Need me to call 911?
Friend dragged me. She
keeps trying to fix my life,
which, admittedly, could
use it, but still, annoying.
You like puzzles.
I hoped my job would let me
play with puzzles all day long,
but it didn't work
out that way.
Police detective. Turns
out criminals are idiots.
If they're not gonna bother to
challenge you, what's the point?
Is there a fire alarm
we could pull?
Maybe get out of here.
Except maybe
you're just too swoft.
I beg your pardon?
Swoft. It's one of
your crossword answers.
I believe it means,
"Lying manipulator
"who tells men anything
they want to hear. "
You brought a prop
as a conversation starter,
folded the paper to make it look
read, filled in some answers,
but you couldn't be
bothered to work at it,
so you just put in
random letters.
You have some natural talent as a liar,
but not enough brains
to see it through.
I'm gonna assume
you're not a cop.
Are the five minutes up?
These women would
welcome a call from you.
And these women would
My.
It's nice to
have visitors.
I'm updating my blog.
And I'm reading it.
You realize you're
in the same room.
Sorry.
So I've been thinking
about what you said,
and I'm sure I washed my hands
after I threw out the rat poison.
Apparently you did it multiple
times, over a course of days.
Can't be too certain.
You must be
Dr. Foreman.
Gotta get back to work.
Okay.
Take it easy.
What? She
reads my blog.
Personally, I don't think
you're condescending at all.
That's not what I wrote. When
you were taking my history,
I told you I went white-water
rafting six months ago,
and you said it was
"unlikely to be related. "
I was just
giving information.
Let's face it,
you got a little snarky.
You can't convey a tone
of voice in writing.
I just put
what you said.
If you don't want people
to think you're condescending,
maybe you shouldn't say
condescending things.
Can this wait a second?
'Cause I have to pee.
I think people behave badly because
there are no records of what we say or do,
and nobody believes anymore
that God's watching.
Well, God's not,
but I am.
Everything is on the record,
including everything I do.
I don't think my pee is
supposed to be mud-colored.
We were wrong
about the rat poison.
Coagulopathy plus
kidney equals what?
Hemolytic
uremic syndrome.
Normal creatinine levels.
She has elevated
cholesterol.
Hey, Wilson!
I can't find my pornos.
Have you tried
offering a reward?
Gaucher's Disease. It would affect
her ability to synthesize Vitamin K.
She's on a semi-
vegetarian diet.
Means she gets
plenty of Vitamin K.
Sjogrens is more likely.
I assume you moved them
while you were dusting.
I checked the drawers, window
sill, the DVD player in your room.
The quiet ones are
always deeply repressed.
I returned them
to the store.
She had a fish dinner
a couple of nights ago.
Could be Haff Disease
causing rhabdo.
What? Why did you return
them to the store?
It's no trouble, I had to stop next
door for my dry cleaning anyway.
Sjogrens would inhibit the clotting
enzymes, infiltrate the kidneys,
explains everything.
So does Haff Disease.
I'm not thanking you,
I'm asking you why.
Because if I did happen to
bring a woman home last night,
I wanted it to be
a porn-free zone.
You do realize things don't have to
be socks to go into a sock drawer.
I'm sorry.
Horribly, horribly sorry.
I thought you'd
watched them all.
You completely
ruined my morning.
I had to pull out your
old family photos.
Your mom was pretty hot.
Haff Disease fits
the timing best.
Start her on saline
and Mannitol.
You reading your
patient's blog?
No.
You should.
Could be some clues.
Too many. It'd be like
doing a whole body scan,
send us up eight
blind alleys.
That's why
Chase is doing it.
She mentions you.
She's never met me.
You're an unseen presence,
like the Wizard of Oz.
He was a fraud. She couldn't
have gone with Keyser Söze?
Speaking of movies
that don't make any sense,
I stopped at the rental store
to get those pornos back.
I told the guy at the counter I was
so grateful that you'd returned them,
but I wanted them, and guess
what? You only returned two.
You lost the third.
Decent of you to pay for it,
not let them put it on my bill.
You know...
I can explain
what happened.
I'm sure you could,
but rather than listen to your
lies, I thought it'd be more fun
to drive all over town
and get another copy.
You have it here?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Okay, first,
that's not me.
It's not... Mostly not...
I was in college! I don't... My
roommate was minoring in film.
Are you
hyperventilating?
Remember that covering your
mouth and one nostril can help.
He had to get this in for some
grade, and he was desperate.
And the only reason I did it was
because no one would ever see it.
Who knew he'd become
an actual director?
He's not a director,
he's an artist.
The way he plays with light
and darkness and boobs.
Look,
that's not me.
What are you?
Where are you taking me?
Be not afraid.
The forest nymphs have taught
me how to please a woman.
That's not me! It's not me.
You can see it's not me!
He added extra scenes so he
could release it as a porno.
Be not afraid, Wilson. You
took risks for your art.
Oh, boy.
No one... Hey, look at me.
No one can know about this.
From this moment on,
my lips are sealed.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Be not afraid.
Find anything?
Relevant? No.
Interesting? I guess.
There's nothing she doesn't
share. "Angry sex is overrated.
"How can he expect me to be
aroused when I'm so pissed at him?"
Revelations like that might
just earn her a new kidney.
An hour after she blogged
about her kidney failure,
the hospital got
a call from Singapore.
One of Frankie's readers asking
how hard it would be to donate.
How good-looking am I?
I'm not asking
if you're attracted to me,
I'm looking for
an objective answer.
Oh, okay, then it's an
appropriate question.
Last night I acted like a
complete tosser to prove to House
that women don't go out
with me for my looks.
Cost me 100 bucks and my
definition of myself. And women.
So date men, they're not shallow at all.
Everything's physical.
Yes,
we are physical beings.
Some more than others.
Please don't define my entire
gender based on one night.
No. What if the patient's
problem is a physical reaction,
not an emotional one?
What if her lack of arousal had
nothing to do with their fight?
Sjogrens would inhibit
her normal secretions.
Sorry for keeping you up. I thought
it better not to wait till morning.
Oh, it's no problem,
I'm a night owl.
So you think I might have this Sjogrens
because of my lack of discharge?
Yes. It's lucky
you wrote about that.
And a little crazy, you're
thinking, to share that much.
Not crazy, unusual, to be so
intimate with people you don't know.
But I do know them. They read
my blog, I comment on theirs.
Just because you haven't
met someone physically
doesn't mean you
don't know them.
What about you?
Are you in a relationship?
It recently ended.
Oh, sorry.
Lie flat on your back,
all the way.
But you saw each other
every day, right?
How much did you tell her
about what you were thinking?
Or did you just end up talking
about where you were going to dinner
and who needed
to do the laundry?
Is that what your relationship
with Taylor is like?
No.
Well, maybe a little.
He's great,
but sometimes
it's easier to open up to
people who aren't looking at you.
You need to lie flat
for us to get the x-ray.
I'm actually not comfortable on
my back. Can't we do it this way?
Did you strain a muscle?
No.
What's wrong?
I've booked our patient
in for heart surgery.
I was doing a sialogram on her, and
she didn't want to lie on her back.
That's a complaint you hear from
people with heart valve issues.
It fits. Sjogrens
damaged her heart,
causing her clotting problems,
causing her kidneys to fail.
You based all that on the fact
that she didn't want to lie down?
That, and the cardiac echo I performed
after she didn't want to lie down.
Her mitral valve
is nearly gone,
which means
she's nearly gone.
God, you're pretty.
So we can replace the mitral valve
with a pig valve or with a plastic one.
From an actual pig?
It's the better choice if you
want to have children someday.
The plastic valve requires
you to be on anticoagulants,
which are known
to cause birth defects.
On the other hand, the pig
valve wears out quickly,
so you'd need to have heart
surgery again in 10 years.
I know that you're on the fence about
having kids, but Taylor really wants them.
It's in the blog.
I'm afraid you two will need to agree
on that decision earlier than planned.
It's your call.
Can you pass me
my laptop?
Seriously?
I want to get some feedback.
You really think that
asking strangers
for some off-the-top-of- their-head
response is gonna be helpful here?
A lot of your readers
are into animal rights.
They've got you two-thirds
of the way to vegan,
what are they gonna say about you
buying your life with the life of a pig?
Whatever they say,
I don't have to do it.
It won't work
out that way,
and we're the ones that are
gonna have to live with this.
Please, Frankie.
Don't tell them.
If I start picking and
choosing, I'm being dishonest.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Though I guess I should thank whoever
taught you how to please a woman.
Maybe it was the
forest nymphs.
Get my Vertigo
poster back.
Be not afraid,
it's exact change.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm looking to get
something on House.
Couldn't you just ask the
love-nymphs for the secret?
Don't.
My mission is to find something that
House would not like to see made public,
and make it public.
In.
But you know him better than
anyone, why do you need my help?
House would never leave
anything secret around the condo.
But you've worked in the same office
with him, on and off, for years.
Think back. Were there ever any odd
phone calls or visitors from the past?
He openly brings prostitutes
into the hospital,
and he gambles with bookies because
he's too lazy to go to the OTB,
and you're asking for...
What? What? What?
He's reading
The Golden Bowl.
By Henry James?
Yeah. No, he's not
really reading it.
Okay. I don't understand.
That book's at least
400 pages long,
whatever he's reading
is only half that thick.
Maybe he's reading a version
with a smaller font.
He's not using
his reading glasses.
That's a good point.
He took the cover off The Golden
Bowl and put it onto this other book,
so no one would know
what he was reading.
Whatever it is,
he's ashamed of it.
Huh.
I'm going with plastic.
It just makes more sense.
I don't want another
operation later.
That's not why
you're doing this.
Look, when you were first telling
me about why you love the Internet,
you said that no one
has to be alone again.
Whoever you are, whatever you
love, you can connect with someone.
If you want to recreate
the Boston Tea Party,
while dressed as
Imperial Stormtroopers,
you can find the 10 other people in the
world that have always wanted to do that.
That hasn't changed.
But you have.
This thing that you do, it's
not about connection anymore.
It's about an audience.
It's a performance,
and you've got one eye
on the number of hits.
You've turned our lives
into their entertainment.
You're smart, you're fun
to read, it's okay.
But don't give them this.
Or if you do,
don't expect me to be here.
It's a good cover choice. It's
not like anyone would pick it up.
It's Cameron's
favorite book.
I don't even know
what it's about.
Don't do that to yourself.
What the hell?
Giving him a computer is like
giving plutonium to Dr. No.
Got it.
Sermons
for Everyday Life"?
These are literal sermons,
written by a minister.
"Loving thy neighbor even
when thy neighbor's stereo
"is keeping you up at night. "
Why would he read this?
Why would he hide it?
He reads the Bible,
he reads the Koran.
He says he likes to know what
mistakes people are making.
You think he's sincere?
You think that he's actually
getting something out of this?
I don't know.
What a hypocrite.
How can we use this
in a cruel yet funny way?
You know what?
Don't mention
this to anyone.
So what was the point?
Are you going to be
here when I wake up?
I hate that you
don't have a blog,
I hate that I don't know
what you're thinking.
Let's not get
into it right now.
We need to get you
through surgery.
I don't want to go in there knowing
you'll stick with me through surgery
'cause that's what
good guys do,
but once I'm better,
you'll be gone.
Let's not get into it now.
It hurts.
Is it her heart?
No, it's here. Here.
Get her inside.
Your appendix burst.
We had to remove it.
And the biopsy confirms it was full of
abnormal cells consistent with lymphoma.
I have cancer?
We've postponed
putting in the new valve.
So, I mean, I guess we do,
what, chemo and all that stuff?
Yes, but apparently you've
had this for some time.
When your appendix burst,
it was like a dam giving way.
Those cells went streaming
throughout your body.
So you're saying you'll treat,
but you don't expect it to work.
That's why no valve.
It's pointless.
Our Dean of Medicine has approved
an experimental treatment.
We use your unique cancer cell signature
to create a targeted lymphoma vaccine.
Okay. So that'll
cure me?
Well, we're not actually
sure what it'll do,
but the intention is to
train your immune system
to recognize and kill cells bearing
the same malignant signature,
while leaving
healthy cells alone.
But, as Dr. Foreman says,
it's experimental.
I see.
Without it, what kind of
time are we talking about?
An exact prognosis
is impossible.
How about a guess?
Something, please.
Based on people in situations
like yours, maybe a year.
Baby, whatever we have to do, we'll do.
I can take care of you.
I can work from home.
Sounds good. Thank you
for letting me know.
We'll start with the
treatment whenever it's ready.
Is she being a good
soldier or is she in denial?
Denial's not unusual
for a first reaction.
Or it could be a symptom. Some
lymphomas affect cognition.
If it is denial, she
needs time to process.
If it's a symptom, hopefully
treatment with the vaccine will help.
Hey, Sandy.
Can I borrow your car?
She gave me the keys.
You're a doctor, she
was doing you a favor.
She barely knows me.
I've been deluding myself that I'm
actually connecting with people.
The first person I ever fell in love
with turned out to be a total tool.
He came across all funny
and charming and thoughtful,
but it was an act.
He saw something
he wanted
and he knew he had to behave
a certain way to get it.
In retrospect, the fact that I was 17
and he was 30 should've been a clue.
Figuring out who people are takes time.
And it takes twice as much time
if they're trying to impress you.
Now, I could take from this that
anyone who loans me their car
has an ulterior motive,
or I can accept that it's
just a nice thing to do,
and take people
as they come.
You wanna do
the first injection?
Why are you reading a book
by a Unitarian minister?
Book club. Oprah was going on and on...
I'm serious.
This is messed up.
A patient wrote it.
No.
You've never treated a patient
with this name, I looked it up.
It's an assignment
from my therapist.
No, it wasn't.
No one you respect would give you
this and expect it to be helpful.
It's a book!
Of sermons!
For anyone else,
spiritually enlightening.
For you, it's practically
a psychotic break.
I know that you have trouble, sometimes,
with the pain
without the Vicodin.
Is that it? Are you so out of options
you're looking for answers in
what you consider irrationality?
I'm all right. Trust me.
Are you all right because
you're back on Vicodin?
I said trust me.
I know this
means something.
You mind?
I haven't finished it yet.
Thanks for the gift.
Obviously differs from
my own personal beliefs,
but if these stories have helped
you through some spiritual turmoil...
Read chapter six,
entitled "Shut the hell up. "
I appreciated
the inscription
about the benefits of prayer
before medical treatments,
and I think it's great that you have
been called to witness by the Lord.
Chapter two, "Bite me. "
Hi.
Thirteen's giving our patient
her third vaccine injection.
She's responding
well so far.
How did you get all these
copies? It's out of print.
I called the author. He's got
cartons of the thing in his basement.
You called him?
What did you say?
That I knew some people who could
benefit spiritually from the book.
Did you mention me?
No, but...
Fever's at 104.
The antibodies tripped
her autoimmune response.
The vaccine
is killing her.
Well, clearly
it's not working.
You have to stop
the vaccine.
Sure. Give up and let
her die on schedule.
It's better than
speeding up the schedule.
How quickly did
this come on?
She was all right when I woke her this
afternoon for the second injection.
Of the stimulating agent, which
added to the first injection,
switched her immune reaction
into overdrive.
Why was she sleeping?
Who can sleep in a
hospital, during the daytime?
I'm not surprised
she's tired.
She's always
been a night owl.
Just by treating her, we've
completely disrupted her schedule.
Is that what her blog says?
She's a night owl?
No, she told me.
In what tense? Is? Was? Will have been?
I'm not sure.
What are you onto?
Look at the time-stamp
on this post.
2:30 a. m. Here's one at 4:00 a. m.
Whatever he's onto doesn't change
the fact that she has lymphoma
and we gave her a dangerous
vaccine. We need to...
Six months ago, she's
posting in the daytime.
Two years ago, daytime.
That's her natural rhythm.
Day-night reversal.
Sign of liver disease?
Which
doesn't fit lymphoma.
But we know
she has lymphoma.
We know she has the cell
atypia that indicates lymphoma.
Biopsy her liver.
That was pretty cool,
what I did, right?
You wanna make out?
You don't have lymphoma.
But you said my appendix
was full of cancer cells.
Your appendix was full of cells
that showed a lymphocytic atypia.
We now think they were a granulomatous
build-up from some unknown cause.
So I'm not dying?
You're actually dying
more quickly than we thought.
Unless we figure out what's
causing your liver failure.
You have three or four days.
What the hell do you mean
I have three or four days?
Well, we're past denial.
Maybe we didn't
cause the fever.
We gave her the vaccine and
her fever spiked, seems to me...
Yes, but it persisted after
we took her off the vaccine.
What if it's
a new symptom?
Okay, so we add
fever to cell atypia,
coagulopathy, kidney, heart, liver...
It has to be an infection.
But which one?
No one she knows is sick.
She hasn't travelled anywhere.
There's nothing in the history
she gave us, nothing in her blog.
There has to be something
unique to this infection,
something about its transmission,
the way it manifests.
There has to be something
she's not telling us.
There isn't. She's told us,
and everyone else, everything.
Start her on broad-
spectrum antibiotics.
Since we know everything, we
might as well treat for everything.
I picked up one of the copies of the
book that Chase left in the lounge.
If you're going
to be this way,
I'm not going to invite
you to my baptism.
The first time I'd seen
the real dust jacket.
The inside back flap, there's
a picture of the author.
Imagine how surprised I was
when I recognized him.
Your biological father
is a minister?
Natural selection
is not an infallible force.
I don't get it.
Okay, he was
a friend of the family,
you'd only known him
when you were a kid.
But if you wanted
to meet him now,
get an idea of what he's like,
why not just go talk to him?
"Hi, it's Greg.
You slept with my mother. "
You're capable of it.
I was mildly curious.
Enough to read a book, not
enough to make a phone call.
Please. You didn't read
this, you studied it. Why?
All your life you've
thought this was crap.
You can't
suddenly turn around
and build a whole new
world-view based on crap.
Crap.
You better not be faking this just
to get out of a tough conversation.
Do you poop?
Come on. Everybody poops. I
read the book in medical school.
Sinkers or floaters?
This is the Wizard.
Greasy and soft,
or hard and pellet-like?
Floaters and the first one.
You just had
to be so swoft.
You're a hypocrite,
no lies, no secrets,
but everything stops
at your colon.
Four thousand pages,
not one word about BMs.
And I bet yours
don't smell at all.
Nobody wants to hear about
that stuff. Readers don't.
People who don't really care
about you don't, but doctors might.
The icky stuff changed,
right? A few months ago.
Well, I became
a vegetarian.
A lot of people misunderstand
how a vegetarian diet works.
You take in less unusable material,
and your waste gets more efficient,
harder and rounder. Just
look at the feces of rabbits.
Seriously, I think I might
have some. Malabsorption.
Her system's not retaining
the necessary nutrients.
A GI infection that
causes malabsorption,
granulamatous
build-up of cells.
It's not contagious, 'cause
no one around her got sick.
Whipple's Disease.
Let's split the credit.
Start her on cotrimoxazole.
We all need some secrets.
So long as they don't kill us,
they keep us safe and warm.
I'm...
I'm gonna be okay?
You'll still need
a new heart valve,
and you'll be on meds for a few years,
but basically, yeah, your odds are good.
Thank God.
I think I wanna go
with the pig valve.
I know you'll go crazy
if you don't tell people.
Thank God
you're an enabler.
Do you think people can
actually know each other better
on the Internet
than face-to-face?
Faces can be
distracting,
but there's nothing better
than looking into someone's eyes
and everything
that goes with that.
I don't know. People meet,
they like something superficial,
and then they fill in the blanks
with whatever they want to believe.
Why are you
so hung up on this?
I refuse to believe it's all because
you just noticed you have a nice face.
I mean, you just
came off a relationship,
you know things
go deeper than...
Is that what this is
about? You and Cameron?
I was the one
that pursued her.
Maybe I was just filling
in the blanks, maybe...
Maybe her first
reaction was right.
We were just two people
who were in proximity
and found each other attractive,
and I never should have...
Paranoia. You felt
something real. So did she.
Don't try to take
it back now.
Can I borrow your car?
No.
Why would it make more sense for
you to read your father's book
than to go talk with him?
Can you write a book, so
I can stop talking to you?
You weren't looking
for some big catharsis,
you didn't want
to hug the guy.
You just wanted to know how
his head works, how he thinks.
Because I'm fascinated
with how ministers think.
Because you're not
ordinary, House.
You're way out there
on the fringe somewhere.
I'm your best friend, and half
the time I don't understand you.
You're alone, you've been
alone your whole life.
When you read that book you
were hoping that somewhere,
underneath all that talk of God,
there would be a way of thinking,
a mind that you
could recognize.
You wanted
what we all want.
The power to transform
into any water-based object?
To look across the gulf and know
there's someone else like you.
At least tell me this, did
you find something there?
Underneath the God stuff,
more God stuff.
Get maintenance
to take that down.