Hey.
Hey, I'll be right there.
Take your time.
You mind if I get
a drink of water?
No, no. Not at all,
help yourself.
Not exactly
beach reading, huh?
Do you understand
any of that stuff?
Well, most of these
I can get through.
But that one, I can't
get past the dust jacket.
Where's Ted?
Laid off.
Company's going
with per diem workers.
You don't have to pay
overtime, health insurance.
Wow, that sucks.
I don't mind. Really. I'm not
a 40-hour-a-week kind of guy.
Uh, if I could just
get you to sign...
Right. Um...
Hang on one second.
I wanna show you something.
You're gonna laugh,
but I swear this guy, James
Sidas, looks exactly like you.
Wait, hang on a second.
This guy is you. I saw a
profile Nova did on you.
You're like the youngest
guy to ever graduate MIT.
Standards were
lower back then.
You got an IQ of 178.
Published three books
and 35 papers,
all before
the age of 18?
Yeah.
Sorry, I really
need to get going,
so if I could just
get you to sign off...
All right. I'll trade you.
I'll sign if you'll sign.
I'm not that guy
any more.
Come on, man. This is
the most exciting thing
that's happened
in this place in years.
Come on,
don't be like that.
I'm paying you
a compliment.
It's not that. I'm...
My hand's not working.
Hey, hey.
Whoa, whoa. You okay?
No.
$2.32. Put it on Dr. Wilson's tab.
I don't know who Dr. Wilson
is, and we don't have tabs.
Do you know who I am?
No.
Good.
But, sir...
I got it.
It's all right.
Thanks.
Although, I should make it
clear that for two bucks,
all you get is top half,
over the clothes.
Any plans
for turkey day?
Going to my sister's
for dinner. Why?
Just making
pleasant conversation.
I heard tell of
folks doing such.
How about we
talk about this?
Fifteen-year-old, recurring
migraines and blurred vision.
Great.
Really?
Sure. There's no point
putting a band together
if we're not
gonna play any gigs.
Hold on.
Take this instead.
I was expecting
more resistance.
That was the old me. New me is
static guarded and friction free.
Enjoy your drumstick.
Ready to
save some lives?
Thirty-two-year-old courier,
ataxia, anemia, mild cough.
CT was clear,
tox screen negative.
What are you
so excited about?
Why wouldn't I be?
Got all my starters back,
plus a couple of first-class free
agents. I feel like Mike Tomlin.
Probably not as much as you
do, but you get the idea.
Ataxia and anemia, could
be viral, maybe West Nile.
No fever, lymph glands were
normal. Anybody seen Wilson?
Hyperbilirubinemia?
Yeah, like that's
a real thing.
Meningitis.
Anemia's a stretch.
Page Dr. James Wilson
at 558.
What about
sickle cell?
The guy's white.
Whites can get it.
Come on. We get the tennis
elbow and all the money,
let them have
sickle cell.
TTP is a better fit.
He's right.
What, you thought I wouldn't
agree with him? Ever?
Well, you didn't
agree with him.
That's why he dumped you.
Oh, sorry, it was mutual.
We're cool, okay? Nobody's
angry, nobody's hurt.
Sounds passionate.
TTP makes sense to me.
Not to me.
What if he had
a history of...
One big happy family.
TTP it is.
Confirm with a blood smear
and ADAMTS13 antibodies.
Dr. James Wilson,
please dial 558.
Can you cure it?
TTP isn't
completely curable,
but the symptoms are manageable
with the proper treatment.
Is this the treatment?
No. First we need to do a blood
test to confirm the diagnosis.
But he's gonna
get better?
Honey,
that's what she's saying.
I'm gonna be okay.
Don't worry.
How can't I worry?
You're in the hospital.
I'm gonna be fine.
Are you sure everything
was fine before?
I mean, given your
educational background,
you'd think you could at least
find a job with a medical plan.
We have money.
Don't worry.
It's not that.
It's just I want
to make sure
we have all
the information we should.
My husband wouldn't lie.
It's okay, baby.
He's just doing his job.
He just wants to make sure I'm not
a secret drug addict or an alcoholic.
Or hiding a history
of mental illness.
I work as a courier
because I want to.
It's easy.
I don't have to think.
It's too hard to think?
No. Just unpleasant.
No matter what I did, it
really wasn't good enough.
Then I met Dara.
She didn't care
how smart I was,
or what I might accomplish
in the future.
It was the first time in my
life that I was really happy.
So I decided I would
rather be happy than smart.
You all right?
Sorry. I know you're
not okay. I mean...
She left.
Went back to Chicago.
Any chance of
reconciliation?
No.
You sure you don't wanna
grab a drink after work?
I figured we could talk about
the perils of dating doctors.
I wasn't dating Cameron.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
I know what you're doing,
and I appreciate it.
But I've got it
under control.
That's what you said
about the Dibala incident,
and obviously you didn't.
And talking about it obviously
made things so much better.
Didn't you think there was
something weird about that guy?
Not really. In fact,
he seemed pretty normal.
That's my point.
Guys with IQs
off the chart
are usually
completely abnormal.
Speaking of House,
why did you come back?
I mean, you must have
taken a major pay cut.
Life's too short
to worry about money.
Your wife feel
the same way?
She's happy to cut back
on some things.
Like sex.
Why'd you come back?
Why wouldn't I?
Like Foreman said, nobody's
angry, nobody's hurt.
Schistocytes.
That means TTP.
Which is what we thought it'd be,
remember? This is a good thing.
This is an easy thing, and House
doesn't take cases that are easy,
which means
it's not TTP.
And he wants to see how long
it takes us to catch up to him.
Schistocytes
suggest TTP.
Good, now what?
Normally we'd try
plasmapheresis,
but the patient has an
albumin colloid allergy.
So?
So that means we have to
give him a splenectomy.
Yes, it does.
Wilson?
No.
Do you know
where he is?
Not in here.
You're sure you want us
to take out his spleen?
Is that what
a splenectomy is?
I thought it was an
ice cream treat. Yuck.
So you do really
think he has TTP.
You're not
just testing us.
Yeah. Like I have
time for games.
So, why did you
really take this case?
Isn't it obvious? I'm
fishing for a dinner invite.
Missed you
at breakfast this morning.
And lunch.
I had
a dentist appointment.
You know where
Cuddy's sister lives?
You see, this is why I don't
answer your urgent pages,
because they're
not urgent pages.
I've decided what I'm gonna
do about Cuddy and Lucas.
I'm going to
break them up.
Of course. It's given
me a purpose in life,
a goal,
a raison d'être.
Albeit a selfish,
mean-spirited, childish raison.
I think of it
more as benevolent.
There's only two possible
outcomes for their relationship,
they split or they
stay together forever.
If it's split, then the sooner it
happens, the better for everyone.
If it's stay, then my
meddling won't matter.
In fact,
if they survive it,
it might even make
their bond stronger.
How you manage to
elevate your narcissism
to beneficence
is masterful.
And I've decided to do it
at Thanksgiving dinner,
just 'cause
I'm sentimental.
Dinner's at Cuddy's sister's,
which brings us back to...
House, don't.
I fished for an invite. Cuddy
wasn't biting, so I'll have to crash.
I have no idea where
Cuddy's sister lives.
Ask and thou
shalt receive.
You can't honestly think
I would help you with this.
Not help me,
help Cuddy, remember?
If you don't get it, I'll be forced
to use more nefarious methods.
Happy holidays.
Ah.
Looks great.
So, he's all better?
Probably be on
some long-term meds,
and he's about
10 ounces lighter,
other than that, he
won't even know it's gone.
Did you hear that, honey?
You're gonna be just fine.
When can I get out
of here?
If everything checks out,
less than a week.
Good. 'Cause those boxes
aren't gonna deliver colors.
Colors?
Green and orange
and ceiling.
Mr. Sidas, do you know
where you are? Chewing.
Jimmy?
Shirt.
He's stroking.
Call the cath lab, now!
Oh, my God.
Blood flow's restored, appears
to be no permanent damage.
Good news is it turns
out to be an exciting,
action-packed thrill ride
of a case after all.
Bad news is we took out
his spleen for nothing.
Thank God he's still got
his appendix and tonsils.
So what looks like TTP,
acts like TTP,
Tests like TTP,
but isn't TTP?
CNS Vasculitis,
explains the ataxia
and anemia,
maybe the stroke.
CT would have
picked up something.
Hi, I'm Greg House. I'm a
friend of your sister, Lisa.
Could be DIC.
Lisa Cuddy.
Sorry, wrong number. You gonna ask?
I'm sure he's got a
perfectly logical explanation.
Can't be DIC,
no hemorrhaging.
And I'm calling all 12 Julia
Cuddys within 100-mile radius.
See? Completely reasonable.
Acquired pancytopenia?
WBC's normal.
Hey, Julia. You're
Lisa's sister, right?
Are you sure?
You are number 12.
Maybe she got married
and changed her name.
Otis Campbell.
Probably kept
her first name.
The mnemonic for toxins.
"O" for organophosphates, "T"
for tricyclics, "I" for insulin...
Or as I remember it,
"Moist Place. "
That's "Place" spelled with
two "L"s and a silent "B."
Except the tox screen
was negative.
Standard tox screen. Unstandard
toxins don't show up on it.
Well, you two do an unstandard tox
screen. You two search his home.
Otis Campbell's gotta
be hiding somewhere.
Smartest guy
in the world
and this is
the best he can do?
Maybe he's doing
what he loves.
Delivering boxes
was a childhood dream.
Soda, processed cheese,
marshmallow spread.
Nothing in here is
capable of going bad.
Ibuprofen, eye drops,
cough syrup.
You want to come over
for Thanksgiving dinner?
You never asked me
over before, why now?
Just never thought of it. But
now that we're both on the team...
And my wife left me?
Is that a bad reason?
No, but I'm okay.
On both the food
and friends.
Mice.
Leptospirosis could explain
the ataxia and the anemia.
But not
without a fever.
You have someone
to talk to?
Yeah.
Who?
What, you want names?
Look, you lost a friend,
I get it.
But I'm not Kutner.
Good. 'Cause Kutner never
used to come over for dinner.
I'm going to pretend there's
something interesting over here,
so you'll shut up.
Actually, there is. He's got
sketches of atomic structure.
This one is full
of math proofs.
They're all old.
Nothing since '96.
This isn't some
homework assignment
his parents
forced on him,
this is passion. Why would
he want to stop doing this?
Marriage destroyed
his soul?
Ooh.
Or maybe it was
just the booze.
Thank you, Doctor.
You've been wonderful.
As have you, Diana.
Be well.
Thank you.
You're helping.
Voluntarily.
He's done six already.
I figured you might
be getting backed up
with the holiday season
and all.
So which one of us slipped through the
wormhole into an alternate dimension?
I have always loved
to travel. And paint.
Lucky number seven.
House, I know you're trying to be nice.
But I also know you're doing
it because you have an agenda.
Wow. Sexy and smart.
Lucas is a lucky guy.
The question is, is this
a bad agenda or a good one?
Either you're trying
to screw with me,
or you're trying to show me
that you've really changed.
So which is it?
I'm dying to know.
What are you doing
for Thanksgiving dinner?
Peace in our time!
Only cost me 45 minutes
of clinic duty.
This is a three-hour drive.
Have you considered the possibility
that this is a fake address?
You think she'd send me to a
vacant lot for Thanksgiving dinner?
If she's smart.
She is.
That's why I ran it through
Motor Vehicles. Good as gold.
This cannot end well.
Don't want it to end well.
You should come as my date.
You're not gonna want
to miss this.
The unstandard
tox screen
was as clean
as the standard one.
But we found vodka
stashed away in his place.
What's with the ties?
Makes me look adorably
non-threatening. Party or party-hearty?
Liver failure would
explain all the symptoms.
Party.
So, the guy's a brainiac and his
secret drug of choice is booze?
It's kind of pedestrian,
don't you think?
Talk to him,
he's a pedestrian guy.
With pedestrian alcoholism. Liver
biopsy can wait until after Thanksgiving.
Yes, assuming the biopsy
is going to tell us exactly
what we expect it to tell us,
it can wait till
after New Years.
On the other hand, Taub and Thirteen
can do the liver biopsy today.
Why us?
Juniority.
Welcome back.
What do you
want us to do?
Same as me.
Have a happy Thanksgiving.
I'm not an alcoholic.
Yes, you just hide vodka
around the house for fun.
I drink,
just not a lot.
Since when do you
drink at all?
I have one shot when I get
home from work, baby. That's it.
So why lie to
your wife about it?
Because
it's not important.
What difference
does it make?
That you drink every day,
by yourself?
I have one lousy drink,
okay?
Have you ever
seen me drunk? Ever?
No, but you've obviously been
drinking enough to hurt your liver.
My liver is fine.
Hold still.
There we go.
This test is
a waste of time.
Hey.
This wine?
All right. Very good.
There, we got this...
String beans?
Julia?
No, I'm the house sitter.
They're in Hawaii
for the week.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Happy Thanksgiving,
you guys.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Cheers. Cheers.
You must be Dr. House.
I was told I should offer
you a turkey sandwich.
Tuna salad. Closest
thing they had to turkey.
Thanks. But I'm hoping I
can still get out of here
and catch the tail end
of dinner with my wife.
Anything?
No cirrhosis, no scarring,
no infection.
Blood panel?
Elevated albumin, 7.2.
That's it?
Everything else is fine.
So it was
a waste of time.
Unless,
it's not his liver
that's elevating his
albumin, it's his kidneys.
Renal failure.
Explains the anemia.
If he developed
hyperkalemia,
that would explain the
ataxia, but the stroke...
Ischemic encephalopathy.
Nice.
Except now we have to stay
and test his kidneys.
Key under the mat.
There's no key
under the mat.
Oh, right.
You need to replace one
of your kitchen windows.
I helped myself to
your wine cellar.
I'll leave a buck
on the way out.
You're not right for her.
And you are?
Less wrong.
Ah.
But then
I started thinking...
What was I saying?
You were saying
it's late and...
She invited me. She
didn't know if she should.
She was trying to figure out
if I really have changed
or if I'm still the same
old SOB I've always been.
But she always
gave me a chance.
Eight hundred and
thirty-two chances,
and I used up
every one of them.
Eight hundred and thirty-two's
her limit, make a note.
How about
a cup of coffee?
It's just instant, but...
I'm pathetic.
I don't deserve her.
Okay. Okay.
All right.
Here.
Maybe you should
crash here.
It's a sofa bed.
I love her.
Patient's liver is fine, it's
his kidneys that are shot.
And where the hell
is House?
He left a message on the
machine. He's not coming in today.
So what causes
kidney failure?
Rhabdomyolysis.
No edema.
I trust you had
a wonderful Thanksgiving.
I don't remember.
So I guess I did.
Multiple myeloma.
No bone pain.
You got drunk alone?
No. That would
be a sign
that I need to talk
to you about this.
Polycystic kidney disease.
No UTIs or flank pain.
Well, what if his cough
is more than just a cold?
He hasn't been coughing.
It's in his history,
and we found a new bottle of cough
syrup in his medicine cabinet.
Cough could mean
Goodpasture Syndrome,
affects kidneys
and lungs.
Start him on
immunosuppressors and dialysis.
We'll do it right after
we run it by House.
He's not
answering his pager.
Looks like he's
leaving it up to us.
Us. Not you.
And since
we don't disagree,
you can save your fight
for another case.
How long do I have
to be hooked up for?
Four to six
hours a day
until we see an improvement.
What if you don't?
Then we keep doing it
until he gets a transplant.
You were sure
it was his spleen,
and then you were sure
it was his liver,
which he told you
it wasn't,
and now you're sure
it's his kidneys.
It's
definitely his kidneys.
We just don't know
why it's his kidneys.
Any word
from Cameron?
Nope.
I started seeing a
counselor after my diagnosis.
She's really good.
Why does everyone assume that
everyone works in the exact same way?
We pretty much do.
Our egos want us to think we're
all snowflakes, no two alike,
but really, we all want
the same things,
love, forgiveness,
chocolate.
Well, what I want is for
everyone to leave me alone.
How do I get that?
What did you say
to Lucas last night?
I know there were
a lot of consonants.
I don't remember how I got
here, never mind what I said.
Well, I just
talked to him.
And he said he thought
it'd be better
if we stopped
seeing each other.
Said he didn't
realize how much
there still was
between you and me.
And he didn't want to get
caught in the middle of us.
I was drunk.
Whatever I said,
he can't really...
I've had enough, House.
I actually felt bad
about scamming you,
but then you lived down to my
expectations, and then some.
There is no us.
There never will be.
It worked.
Please tell me you're talking
about a medical procedure.
They split up
this morning.
You're the very first
one I've told.
And you think she'll start dating
you? I'm sure she hates you.
But her eyes say,
"How will I ever pay you
for that tennis lesson?"
What a shame.
They'll get over it.
I meant for you. I'll get
over it faster than they do.
I can't believe
that Lucas fell for my
"I'd never say this
because it's so personal
"except that I'm drunk"
profession of love.
Second oldest trick
in the book.
You're right. It's his
fault because he's stupid.
He certainly is.
You're stupid.
Well, I'm rubber
and you're glue...
He's not pedestrian,
he's stupid.
Or at least stupider than he
should be. He's a DXM junkie.
Dextromethorphan.
As in cough syrup?
He wasn't taking it
for his cough.
It's cheap, available
at your corner drugstore,
and taken in high doses,
it's a dumb drug.
Dumb drug?
He obviously hasn't...
He's smart
compared to you,
he's a moron compared
to what he was.
Robotripping lowers the IQ,
it also causes brain damage.
Unless taken with the
proper amount of ethanol,
about one drink per day.
He wasn't
abusing the booze
and taking the cough
remedy medicinally,
he was abusing the cough meds
and taking the booze medicinally.
Bravo.
Why would you do that?
If you had a gift, why
would you just throw it away?
I didn't throw it away. I
just turned it down a little.
When my brain was on low, everything
didn't seem so miserable any more.
Life was bearable.
I thought that
I did that.
You do.
Long-term abuse of DXM
explains all your symptoms.
Even, oh, sweet irony,
your cough.
Whole bowel lavage,
activated charcoal.
We get all traces of it
out of your system,
you'll be the unhappiest
little courier in no time.
I don't think
I can live without it.
You'd be surprised
what you can live without.
Make him a genius.
I can't believe it. He
looks so much better already.
We were thinking
about calling GQ.
Lavage has removed all
traces of DXM from his body.
You're drawing again.
What is it?
Just doodles.
No, it's not. Come on,
Jimmy, I want to know.
This is a toroidal
helicon plasma device.
It determines
the amount of energy
expended by
the subatomic particles.
I'm thirsty. Could you get
me a juice or something?
Yeah. Of course.
I'm so happy, Jimmy.
I told you.
You know what the difference
between her IQ and mine is?
91 points.
In relation, she's closer to
a gibbon than she is to me.
Having sex with her would
be an act of bestiality.
I assume
you didn't marry her
for her skill in
Applied Physics.
I just wish
she could spell it.
You really think
you'd be happier
with someone who
could spell better?
No.
That's the problem.
I'm the one who's a jerk.
But I owe her everything.
I want to want
to be with her.
And when I'm clear, I...
I can't.
Fainting, dizziness,
shortness of breath?
Sometimes.
Is the wait
always this long?
Only on days that end in
"day. " Diarrhea, weight loss?
A bit.
Don't you ever shave?
Yeah, once a week.
How about you?
Stomach pain, tenderness?
Every now and then. Are you
this rude to all your patients?
Oh, yes, don't think
you're special.
So we got a lot of vague,
unverifiable symptoms,
yet all the physical signs
are perfectly normal.
What do you think I have? I'm not sure,
but I think
it's a lame job.
What?
You're a rat. Insurance
company sends you out
to check on the quality
of medical care.
That's ridiculous.
Is it really?
'Cause you seem
a lot more interested
in asking questions
than answering them.
Handwriting in your medical
records is obviously not a doctor's,
'cause I can
almost read it.
And when you went out for a urine
sample, I looked in your purse.
Found the list of questions
you were supposed to memorize
before you came to the
clinic. I was looking for gum.
You're an ass.
Put it in your report.
I'll tell you what.
I'll give you 20 bucks
if you'll pretend
that I'm not
when we leave this room.
Remember,
first ice, then heat.
If you have any problems,
don't hesitate to call me.
Thank you,
Dr. House.
Wait a second.
Where's Cuddy?
Gone for the day.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Sorry, can't remember if I've mocked
you yet for being a male nurse.
I think this counts.
Fair enough.
That isn't
the man I married.
Yes, he is. He's just
smarter. Give him some time.
I'm sure...
He hates me.
His body is going through
withdrawal. He's adjusting.
Maybe he never loved me.
Not really.
Maybe we never really
had anything at all.
Somebody help!
I can't feel my legs.
Anywhere. Nothing.
We have to talk
about this.
It's late. I'm tired.
I know it's
a big pay cut,
but I'll always have
the chance to make money.
I won't always have the
chance to do this job.
That's what you think?
That it's about the money?
So it's that I didn't consult
you before I took the job?
That was offensive, but
it's not about that either.
So then...
Can you give me
the first letter?
When we got married,
you were an intern working
30-hour shifts, doing grunt work,
and we both put up
with it because we knew
that it was leading
to something better.
In your private practice, you
are the boss. You call the shots.
But now,
you're 40 years old,
you're still
doing grunt work.
That's what this is about?
You think I'm a wuss?
He made you miss
Thanksgiving dinner.
Vitamin B12 deficiency
gives us anemia, numbness...
Not a stroke.
If he has
a vascular malformation...
Anemia's not macrocytic.
Sorry to
inconvenience you.
Dying patients can
be so thoughtless.
Don't.
Great comeback. Is that
Oscar Wilde? Come on, people.
Bone marrow malignancy.
Wouldn't produce
schistocytes.
Lupus. Gee, thanks for coming in.
ANA was negative.
What about you?
You got any predictable
drivel you'd like to add?
I think they've given
you enough already.
At least they're trying, not
just sitting there like roadkill.
Give me something!
Give me something or I'll
get your ex-smarter half
on the phone and ask her.
House...
You're going to be
pressing charges?
Against the ottoman
I tripped over?
Against Chase.
I'm pretty sure the
ottoman was acting alone.
You free for dinner
this weekend?
At least three other
people saw him do it.
Mass hysteria.
Either night?
I can't have doctors
punching each other out.
Oh, my God,
who got punched?
And more importantly,
for Chase's sake,
I need to know if he's
able to handle himself
or if I should be
getting him some help.
Chase couldn't
have punched anyone.
He was with me when I
tripped over the ottoman.
If you're not planning on eating
this weekend, maybe a movie?
I'm not doing this,
House.
It's not fun any more.
Just do your job.
I need your help.
What happened
to your face?
I was mowing the lawn
when the phone rang.
You're a computer. I'm gonna
feed you data, and you analyze it.
What are you
gonna feed me,
20 years of
medical knowledge, too?
It's not gonna work.
I know. But I don't
have anyone else to ask.
It's lonely, isn't it?
It's not that bad.
Then you're not
that smart.
You ever try
to kill yourself?
Not quickly.
I did.
Twelve years ago, I jumped off
the top of my eight-story building
into a dumpster bin
the day before pick-up.
I broke my collar bone,
my leg and three ribs.
When I was in the hospital,
they put me on narcotics
and suddenly
everything was just better.
I didn't feel
isolated or lonely.
That's where
I met my wife.
She was so happy
and dumb.
And I was
smart and miserable.
You tell me who
the genius is.
I fell in love with her
buzzed out of my head
and I knew I wanted to
stay that way forever.
Enjoy.
Easier on your conscience
if I die an idiot?
What's a conscience?
Which ribs did you break in
the fall? Down the left side?
Yeah, bottom three.
But that was 12 years ago.
This probably cost me my
marriage, so it better be awesome.
Ferrous oxide
contrast?
It gets absorbed
by the spleen,
unless he doesn't
have one,
in which case it's absorbed
by the liver and fries that.
You're killing him?
You think I opened him up and
didn't take out his spleen?
All organs do look kind of
the same, red and squishy.
Oh, my God.
Accessory spleens.
Okay, that is amazing.
Twelve years, eight
stories and a dumpster ago,
he broke three ribs,
damaged his spleen.
Bits of it split off, circulated
through his blood stream
until they landed and
attached somewhere else.
So, it is TTP.
I just didn't remove
all of his spleens.
Sixteen splenectomies,
pretty sure he gets a set
of steak knives with that.
I can outrun you.
Sorry about the nose. And
the eye. And the eyebrow.
Guess I deserved it.
Well, if I thought that,
I wouldn't be apologizing.
Your fist slipped?
Everybody kept bugging me,
asking if I was okay.
So you bust my nose to
keep people off your back?
Pretty much.
Making people even more
worried about you.
Maybe. But at least they're
not talking to me about it.
Fair enough.
Cheers.
Thank you.
Don't be so grateful.
You'll be delivering packages
for 70 years to pay for it.
Well, thanks for our talk.
It's been a while since I had
a stimulating conversation.
So what are you
going to do?
Go back to my life.
Which one?
The one that
has my wife in it.
Robotripping.
How does she feel
about that?
Well, she doesn't have to
know. It's worked for 12 years.
Tell your brain
I said goodbye.
Einstein's giving
himself a lobotomy,
and you're cool
with that?
Ignorance is bliss.
Hold that pose.
I'll start with t
- shirts and mugs and see how it goes.
Home early.
What happened to him?
You beat up House?
Just one right hook.
Why? What happened?
You were right.
I told him we need to lay down some
ground rules, it got a little heated.
That's not what I meant.
Is he okay?
Are you going to
be fired? Arrested?
Everything's fine.
Wow.
Dr. Cuddy.
Can we at least be civil?
How's your nose?
It's okay.
Does your kid
like animals?
I got tickets to
that holiday carnival.
I hear they have
a nice petting zoo.
I think I was
pretty clear before.
I don't mean with me.
Here. Take them.
Enjoy.
No, thanks.
They're not fake.
I didn't steal them.
One of the nurses was selling
them for her kid's scout troop.
I know it doesn't make
things right between us,
but I just wanted
to do something nice.
I don't want them.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
They didn't split up.
She wouldn't
take the tickets.
Of course. Windtalker code
for "we never split up. "
House, she told you
multiple times
she wants nothing
to do with you.
I wasn't gonna be there.
She just felt guilty that I felt
guilty, so she couldn't take them.
Either that or she didn't
want to appease you.
These weren't reparations,
just a simple gesture of
remorse, and she slapped it down.
They didn't break up.
She just wanted me to
think that, so I'd back off.
Dare I ask what
you're gonna do?
Nothing.
I said they'd either break
up or they'd stay together.
They didn't break up.
And you're okay
with that?
It is what it is.
Good for you.
House knows I lied.
Why? What did he say?
Nothing.
I could just tell.
You gonna stage
another breakup?
No.
Oh.
Hi.
It seems like he's
going to leave us alone.
Mmm. Why would he do that?
I'm not completely sure.
So, we have his blessing?
I guess so.
I made you some
eggplant Parmesan.
And maybe House
isn't so bad after all.
That would be nice,
wouldn't it?