We will anger the americans,
slipping out like this.
If your son was a student
At one of the greatest
universities in the world...
So make him come
to you.
you're protected
near the u.n.
Once we cross 42nd street...
As always, i appreciate
your caution, joseph,
But, as always, you have
far too much of it.
Stay down, sir.
Get on the ground.
I'm just serving process.
your boss is being sued
Under title 18
of the united states code,
section 1350, for genocide,
Crimes against humanity,
And torture.
[tires squeal]
Mr. president.
this is only a civil lawsuit.
we can ignore it.
Mr. president.
[massive attack's teardrop]
* *
You want us
to work for foreman?
(cuddy)
not permanently.
He is setting up interviews
to replace taub and thirteen,
But it might take
a couple of weeks.
What happened to them?
He quit,
and i had to let her go.
(chase)
you actually fired
Your girlfriend?
yes.
You two are both competent,
and i know i can work with you.
You really do know
how to woo.
I need you.
It would be interesting.
We could work together.
Did you see
who the patient is?
That's one of the reasons
it'll be interesting.
Dibala is one
Of the most repressive dictators
in the world.
You had no problem treating
a guy on death row.
Who was still in prison
after we patched him up.
We fix dibala,
he gets on a plane
And executes half his country.
He's been repressing
an ethnic rebellion
In the south,
the sitibi people.
It's getting worse.
Dibala is a guest
of the u.s. government.
and he's been invited
to speak at the u.n.
i'm not asking you
to love him.
I'm asking you
to do your job.
Utterly incomprehensible.
And, of course, i'm talking
About you firing
your girlfriend.
We weren't getting along
with her working under me.
This'll help.
Cameron and i work together.
But you weren't
her boss.
And you stopped
working together.
Why don't you just tell her
you were wrong?
'cause i wasn't.
I know how this looks.
I know
it might break us up.
But that's better
than definitely breaking us up,
Which is what would
have happened otherwise.
Hemorrhagic ulcers
in the lungs.
Oh, my god,
It's three years ago.
Does that mean
i'm still crazy?
You're back?
you look good.
We're just helping out
because...
I know.
i just ran into thirteen
while she was clearing out
her locker.
my condolences.
Although it's not like she's
the hottest woman in the world.
We haven't broken up.
Are you back?
sort of.
Did you get your license back?
Not for a month
or so.
So you'll be in charge.
I'm just gonna pitch in
a little.
(chase)
dibala thinks
It was an assassination attempt.
Polonium,
like the russian guy in london.
Fbi checked the service
of process forms
And his hotel room.
No radioactivity trails.
Acid reflux?
No history of asthma
or heartburn.
(foreman)
he has a bug bite on his hands.
Malaria's endemic
in his country.
Let's start him
on coartem.
[clears throat]
I don't want
to step on any toes,
But i guess i do have
a higher duty to the patient.
If you have something to say,
say it.
You're rushing
to a diagnosis
Because you're rushing out
of this room
Because you're rightly upset
with me.
Although i wasn't the one
Who made that asinine decision.
Do you have anything medical
to say?
Poison fits better
Because of the vomiting.
Bug bite might not be
a bite.
It might be the start
of chloracne.
Assassination attempt
through dioxin poisoning.
It's hard to detect.
fits.
Start him on olestra.
You couldn't have just said
dioxin up front?
I was hoping you'd get there
on your own.
So i guess we should talk
to cuddy.
It is dioxin?
No.
It's our best guess.
the olestra here binds
to the poison
And flushes it
out of your system.
Where are you from,
doctor?
I'm australian.
Do i hear a bit
of the british?
Most people don't notice it.
Yeah, i kicked
around there for a while.
You went
to medical school there?
Actually a year
of seminary.
and you left.
uh-huh.
There was a catholic mission
near my childhood village.
I liked the priests.
They were good people.
but when
my two younger sisters
Were dying
from consumption,
It wasn't more priests
we wanted.
I fired my girlfriend
Because he said he was gone
for good.
I need this
in my life.
A week ago, it was
the last thing you needed.
It's a process.
I'm learning.
And screwing me over
as you go.
Yeah, that's why i did it.
Sorry.
If you want,
i'll explain it to thirteen.
He's not ready.
He doesn't have
his license.
Then he can't practice.
But we'd be idiots
not to listen to him.
you're in charge,
he sits in
on all the differentials.
Until you get
your license back,
This is all unofficial.
No procedures,
no patient contact.
Think i can probably deal
with that last one.
[knock at door]
The only reason
i let you go
Is because our relationship
wouldn't work
If i was in charge.
But i won't be
in charge soon, so...
I came to offer you
your old job back.
I know.
i look bad.
But circumstances
have changed.
I don't want the job.
Why not?
Because there's a much simpler
explanation for you firing me.
You wanted to break up with me,
but you were too weak
To do it yourself.
Then why would i try
to hire you back?
Can we please get
some dinner tonight?
I'm sorry.
Uh, you're a follow-up?
You must not treat him.
Dibala killed my wife.
She was a trade unionist.
He took her
From our home
While i was at work.
Who took her?
Dibala's youth labor league.
He pretends it's to get
young people off the street.
But he takes teenage boys
from the provinces
And feeds them drugs
and alcohol
And teaches them
how to torture.
They dumped her body in my yard
two weeks later.
They raped her.
they carved inyenzi, cockroach,
onto her stomach
Because she's sitibi.
I'm very sorry, but i can't
discuss other patients.
You should talk
to a lawyer,
Talk to the u.n...
So they can sit and watch,
Like they did in rwanda?
There are 2 million sitibi.
he's planning
to massacre them all.
His radio stations are talking
about a final war
To exterminate
the cockroaches.
He can't recover.
I'm sorry.
How was your first day
of school?
Didn't pee once
in the sandbox.
How was it
with cuddy?
What did you think
i was talking about?
Hmm.
you didn't use garlic.
You didn't use it
last night either.
We always use garlic
on chicken florentine.
It tastes fine
this way.
You seem to be losing
your sense of smell.
I think you're losing
your sense of mind.
I can check right now
if you pull my finger.
No, it's the--
are you inventing
some big medical mystery here?
Because if you're imagining
things again...
You weren't wearing shoes
last night either.
[sighs]
Yes, shoes, garlic--
I am vampire, sookie.
[bangs loudly]
[responsive banging]
I told you to get
that echo fixed.
My downstairs neighbor,
after you moved in,
Started complaining
about the extra noise
And the cooking smells.
What's his name?
I don't want you
making things worse.
He's on the condo board,
And i'm trying to get
the back garden renovated.
The white coats taught me
a whole bunch
Of fun coping
and relating skills.
He's not only a total jerk,
He's a decorated war hero
Who lost an arm
in vietnam.
I mean, there's no winning
with this guy.
Coping skill number one...
[cell phone rings]
Complete avoidance.
You happy?
Booty call?
Give me 20 minutes
to not shower.
Patient's having
a heart attack.
Mask at 15 liters.
just thought you'd like
to know.
Lassa fever.
You were mad
that i withheld it last time,
So i'm saying it
right up front.
He's already stabilized,
So 40 ccs
Of ribavirin,
and we're home
in time for ellen.
I checked. there's no lassa
in dibala's country.
Oh.
the rash is gone.
It rules out
your dioxin theory.
He's running a slight fever,
which we can add
To the heart,
plus the lung ulcers.
(chase)
ebola? marburg?
Too long
an incubation period.
Yes?
don't people sometimes travel?
To places that have,
you know, a fever
That originated
in the nigerian town of lassa?
He's been to three other
countries in the last two years:
Here, zimbabwe, and
sharm el-sheikh, egypt.
No lassa there either.
Oh.
Again.
Trypanosomiasis?
No sleep disturbances.
But fits best
with the symptoms.
And it's geographically
the most--
What?
The egypt visit
Was for the african union
meeting,
Where i'm guessing he was
meeting people
From africa.
Which includes liberia,
Which sent some members
of their foreign ministry,
Which has itself
just been hit by an outbreak
Of jock itch.
No, wait.
not jock itch.
Lassa fever.
I'll start the ribavirin.
I did say it up front.
It's great to have the old team
back together again, huh?
(ntila)
yesterday,
It's poisoning.
today, lassa fever.
maybe a specialist--
(dibala)
joseph!
Leave him alone.
These people know
what they are doing.
Are you married,
doctor?
No.
you have a girlfriend.
Yes.
Judging
by your tentative answer
And the complicated expression
on her face,
I believe that is she,
standing in the hallway.
I got a call
from douglas' department
At princeton general.
They want me
to interview with them.
Which is weird,
because when i called
Last week, they said
they had nothing available.
So i never sent in my resume.
Douglas owes me a favor.
Most people send chocolates.
I'd stand outside your apartment
all night
Holding up a boom box,
except you told me
You hate '80s music.
I'm free tomorrow night.
[keys jangle]
I was wondering
what that noise was.
It's the damn cane.
And i'm greg.
And i can't sleep
With you banging around
with that thing.
You're not actually saying
That i have too loud
a cane?
Is that hard
for you to understand?
Only in the sense that it has
a rubber tip on the end
And not a tap shoe.
Now you're getting cute
with me.
Okay, we started badly.
I apologize
for the noise,
And we will try to figure out
a way to be quieter--
And a thousand other things
i don't give a crap about.
Now you keep it down,
Or we're gonna have trouble.
Wow.
[door slams]
(cameron)
you paged me?
This is ama.
she is from our country,
but she lives here now.
We'd like you
to use her blood.
For what?
She recovered
from lassa fever
Two years ago.
our health minister
has advised us that plasma
from one who has
the antibodies
Is much more effective
Than ribavirin.
This is a signed consent form.
Will you take her blood, please?
No.
I want to do this.
(cuddy)
you understand
that we would be using
Your blood
to cure president dibala.
I know.
Are you
from the sitibi people?
I am sitibi.
Did they threaten you
in some way?
your family members
back home?
Please let me
give the blood.
Please.
Do it.
She's being coerced.
If she is, i'd rather have
a needle prick
On my conscience than the death
of her family members.
Hey!
Don't let him in there!
[gunshots]
[beating
and gasping]
(bass)
hey!
That's enough!
we got him.
Hey!
[shouts]
you all right?
Who is that man?
He shot him?
No.
(chase)
you need a lawyer.
You can get
a court-appointed.
They can help you.
I can't be helped.
You did a stupid,
terrible thing.
But given the circumstances
with your wife,
You could get
a reduced sentence.
She wasn't my wife.
Then who was she?
They never told us
her name.
What his men made us do
To that woman...
He is now going to do
To all the sitibi.
(cameron)
you could have gotten killed.
He wasn't going
to hurt me.
He fired a gun
in the hospital.
Come here.
Maybe next time
don't yell out that warning.
The bloody eye was
from an enlarged lymph node
Blocking the retinal vein.
We restored circulation,
But it means we've got
to add lymph involvement
To the heart, lungs,
and rising fever.
I'm just gonna sit here
quietly.
Why?
I feel like i've been
inadvertently undermining
Your authority,
so i'm just gonna observe.
Not gonna say a word.
The heart could point
to sarcoidosis.
[clears throat loudly]
I'm thinking
the x-rays indicate
A lack of hilar adenopathy,
Which rules it out.
Staph aureus?
(chase)
no.
Because...
He...
Smokes?
He's miming a thermometer.
He says the fever's
not high enough.
So some other infection.
(foreman)
he's wrong.
The fever could be misleading us
Into thinking infection.
Talk.
It could all fit
with lymphoma.
Um, i need you to spread
your legs so i can do an h.
Can't be lymphoma.
Ldh is normal.
He's got good liver function.
It's masking
the elevated levels.
Biopsy the lymph node.
check it out.
Makes sense.
I guess you don't need me.
Oh, by the way,
You might want
to close the blinds.
A little bright in here.
It's just a wild coincidence
that he thought
You were a rude jerk.
Come on. give me
the benefit of the doubt.
You said he's a jerk.
i barely talked.
You talked!
All i wanted was to sip
morning espresso
Next to a peaceful,
burbling fountain.
You could be sipping courvoisier
Next to a replica
of the playboy grotto
If you tell him
what you got on him.
I don't have anything
on him.
I don't want anything
The closest he's been
to vietnam?
Ordering the mee krob
at that place on the corner.
Mee krob
is from thailand.
Exactly.
What did you do?
Why do you think he's faking?
I saw his mail.
your broke in?
No.
he was holding it.
private medical insurance.
Not from the v.a.
Plus, he's got
to be early 50s.
He's too young
to be a vet.
So i looked further.
You did break in.
Online.
There's no reference to him
in any of the vet records.
Why would he fake
being a veteran?
Just look
how you're acting.
People have been tiptoeing
around this jerk for years.
Normally, we'd all tell
the amputee to go screw himself.
Victims get pity,
heroes get adulation.
It's way better.
Thank you for trying
to help me out
With my neighbor.
Now forget the vietnam stuff.
I could prove this.
But you won't
because you'll be too busy
Writing him a letter
of apology
And dropping it
at his door
Without knocking
at his door.
I dil ass.
Which is the point.
It's easy to be nice
to people you like.
But being nice
to people you hate,
That's a skill.
Do it.
Thank you
for saving my life.
The man
that tried to kill you,
he said that you were
preparing a massacre.
The sitibi are my countrymen.
I am fighting
a guerilla war.
In a way that's
being called genocide.
20 years ago,
These same sitibi rebels
took over the south,
They massacred
tens of thousands,
And they would happily do it
again.
I'm trying
to impose order.
I'm trying to prevent
a genocide.
Genocide.
my own son,
My youngest,
He is a student here.
He hasn't spoken
to me in years
Because of what he read
in your newspapers.
But what he read
is not true.
What about
your youth labor league?
[sighs]
There i was at fault.
I hired men, who,
in their zeal,
Stepped over the line,
And there were abuses.
But that will not happen again.
Hello?
How's it going?
Normal-looking nucleus.
How's it going
with you?
it worried me
when you joked
About letting
that man shoot dibala.
I wasn't joking.
You can't want
to kill anyone,
Especially not
your own patient.
It's only natural
to feel he should--
No, it's completely unnatural.
Only psychopaths can kill
other people
without having some sort
of breakdown.
Not when it's justified.
look at soldiers.
Even when it's justified.
Am i trying
to kill our patient?
Of course not.
But if he died, am i supposed
to just pretend
That wouldn't be good
for the world?
The cells
are neatly differentiated.
This isn't lymphoma.
(house)
thought i had detected
The sickly sweet smell
of maple syrup
And socialized medicine.
It smells like...
Victory.
That big flag
in your place
Prompted me to chat
with your housekeeper.
Turns out you're a citizen
of the great white north.
You broke
into my apartment?
Technically, no.
Well, technically, yeah,
But two steps.
Hardly--
you're going to jail.
Speaking of,
You know what can get you
six months
And a $100,000 fine?
Falsely claiming that you won
a medal in vietnam.
You think i'm faking?
Canada did not send troops
to fight in vietnam, you idiot.
They sent troops to reinforce
the '73 peace accords,
Which is where i tried
to free a 12-year-old boy
Who stepped
on a land mine.
36 years later, every second,
i feel the pain in my hand
Like i'm still grabbing
that boy's arm,
Even though my arm
isn't there.
So, no,
i'm not faking.
Oh.
On a related note,
Go maple leafs.
Did you get
the biopsy results?
Is it lymphoma?
No.
So we have to move on.
Infection,
perhaps autoimmune.
Did you get the biopsy results?
Yes, i just told you.
Is it lymphoma?
Cameron and chase?
They both really like
diagnostics,
And i think they both really
like watching house torture me.
Anyway, thank you
for understanding
About the job.
I had two really
crappy alternatives.
There was a third.
What's that?
You could have stepped aside.
We both would have lost
our jobs.
You could have asked cameron
or chase to take your place.
They wouldn't have wanted to.
You just said they both
really like diagnostics.
You want to go back
in time?
I want to make this work.
I want to understand you.
I mean, you know
how you made me feel.
If you could do it again...
I made
the right decision.
I need your confidential
medical opinion.
Is the president capable
of thinking clearly?
Obviously not,
right now.
Will he ever be?
I think...
Neurons don't grow back,
and he's already in his decline.
Anything he tells you,
any command he gives,
How will you ever know
It's not just the delusions
Of a sick, mad,
dying old man?
He just started
spiking a fever.
It's scleroderma.
You don't have
some clever way
Of telling me
this time?
Patient's dying.
I'm done with clever.
Look at his skin.
It's tight
for a 75-year-old.
Based on his admission photo?
Bit subjective.
Fever points
to infection.
And now he's got nodules
on his fingers.
That's blastomycosis.
Nodules?
And you're calling tight skin
subjective?
(chase)
i'm with foreman.
We would have seen
fungus balls on the head ct.
Fungal lesions
can be missed.
(cameron)
we could settle this
with a test.
Point to,
not prove.
And his fever's too high.
We have to treat him now.
We treat wrong,
We could send this disease
into overdrive.
You're with me
on the scleroderma.
I guess.
I just don't care enough
about the patient
To waste my time trying to
convince anyone.
We get it.
you don't like the guy,
You didn't want
to work on this case.
And yet you're still here.
Why don't you take a stand?
Either do something about it
or shut up.
Treat him for blasto
if you want.
I'll get cuddy.
i can convince her--
(foreman)
this isn't a democracy.
I don't care
who you get.
At least for right now,
this is my department.
We're treating him
for blasto.
Start him
on amphotericin b.
If you inject my i.v.
with an air bubble...
What are you doing?
I will have
another heart attack.
No one will know.
Let her go.
you tell my colonel
I'm a sick, dying old man
Who can't be trusted.
I didn't say...
You were trying to put
a gun in his hand
And point it
at my head.
The gun is now
in your hand.
That is a practical difference,
not a moral one.
If you want me dead,
then pull the trigger.
It is not so easy when you have
to do it yourself.
Allison.
I guess
i didn't want you dead.
You touch my wife again,
I'll kick your ass out
into the street.
I don't care
who you are.
I did her a favor.
I showed her
her true character.
She's a better person
than you are.
She is too weak to act
on her beliefs.
But that is not her fault.
Most everyone is.
Even my own advisors.
My own colonel.
All they do is negotiate
and debate
And sign treaties.
They are appeasers.
And all the while,
we are beset by assassins
And traitors,
the scum--
Cockroaches?
What are you going
to do about them?
What is an enemy
to you?
Some younger physician
who covets your office?
In my world, there are dangers
and bloodshed and death.
And that makes you a man.
And men make choices.
And your choice
is to send bands
Of drunk, crazed children
To massacre
an entire people?
Don't ask me questions you don't
want to know the answer to.
i saved your life.
I deserve to know
What you're planning--
Whatever it takes
to protect my country.
You broke
into his apartment?
I didn't break in.
I wish i believed you.
I can fix this.
I already did.
He was going
to press charges.
but...
I promised him
you'd leave.
You're kicking me out?
I'll explain it
to your psychiatrist,
But...yeah.
You got to go somewhere else.
house, i know
When things go wrong,
Usually you just double down
And get more involved,
But here you could go to jail.
and i truly believe
That you've changed enough
To know this is the right thing.
We need a blood sample.
We got to do the anticentromere
antibody test.
It'll show house is right.
it's scleroderma.
Why are you doing this now?
And you're right.
I have to take a side.
So i'm going to do what i can
to keep him alive.
I'll get you the blood.
positive
For anticentromere antibodies.
Better get him
off the antifungals
And onto steroids
immediately.
I told you before,
This only points
to scleroderma.
It doesn't prove it.
You're just gonna ignore
the test?
Blasto still fits best.
I know
it's not conclusive,
But when you put it
with all the other evidence--
I've made
my decision.
Have you told thirteen
you were wrong to fire her?
What does that have to do
with anything?
I've worked with you
long enough to know
You're reasonable.
You can usually admit
when you're wrong.
But there's some deep part
of you,
That when you find you're wrong
About the most important
decisions you've made,
You get insecure
and you just retrench.
If you want to mess up your
relationship, that's your right,
But you mess this up,
our patient dies.
Switch him to steroids.
Hi, honey.
How was your day?
Morning.
First of all, my bad.
I've gone through
this whole thing recently.
I don't want to bore you.
Short version: i'm really trying
to work on some stuff.
This is a definite setback.
Although, in fairness,
you really did
Make it tough.
Phantom pain
in your missing arm?
five different kinds
of painkiller
In your medicine cabinet.
That's what this
Magic box
of neurological trickery is for.
[groans]
this would be a lot easier
If you do what the crazy guy
who tied you up says.
Put your hand in there.
put your hand in there.
It's mirror magic.
Your arm is back.
Now clench both your fists
at the same time.
Clench.
real hard.
If you believe in god,
Pray that this is gonna work.
You might also want to ask him
why he blew off your arm.
Ready?
Now let go.
Oh, my god.
It relaxed.
For 36 years,
i've been in pain.
And it's finally gone.
Oh, my god.
[weeps]
thank you.
[monitor alarms blare]
O2 sat's down to 88.
Going through
the main stem bronchus.
Into the right upper lobe.
get them out of here.
No!
Bleeder.
Cauterizing.
Got it?
yeah.
[alarms stop]
[another alarm beeps]
Get the paddles!
I'm going back in.
what is happening?
(foreman)
he's bleeding into his lungs.
Charging.
Another bleeder.
i can get it.
Hold on.
there's a third.
God, there's a dozen.
Shock him.
Clear.
[paddle charges]
(cameron)
charging. clear.
[shocks dibala]
Call it.
You want to curl up and cry,
The lounge chair's
a little more comfy.
I switched his meds.
I thought I was wrong, so I took
him off the antifungals.
Put him on steroids
like you said.
You know what that means.
I was too late.
Or I was right
in the first place.
So either you killed him
By not having confidence
In your opinion,
Or you killed him by being
too attached to your opinion.
If you're anything like me--
And, by the way,
you are--
You need to know which.
He's under lock and key
in the morgue.
His government wants
their own doctors
To do the autopsy.
They're taking his body out
tomorrow.
There's a reason
I hired you.
You used to know
what to do with a locked door.
[footsteps]
I went down to the morgue
to rerun the antibodies test.
We ran it twice.
Turns out I couldn't get in.
They had an armed guard.
But i saw is.
It's a sign-in sheet
from the morgue.
Your signature.
9:45 this morning.
That's right before
you guys ran the test.
What were you doing there?
Follow-up
on a clinic case.
What case?
You think
this is really important--
One of the patients
in the morgue
Was a 70-year-old woman
who had scleroderma.
You and cameron,
If you took
that woman's blood,
You could have messed up
the test results
So we treated dibala
for the wrong disease.
Cameron had nothing
to do with it.
You son of a bitch.
He was going
to kill the sitibi.
Every last one of them.
I don't care
what he was going to do.
He came to us
and put his life
In our hands.
All the good we've done...
Every life we've saved...
It would have meant nothing
If we just sent him off
to kill hundreds
Of thousands of people.
Look at the news.
The moderates are taking over.
There's hope
for peace talks.
You tell the world
that i faked this test,
Dibala becomes a martyr.
The massacres begin.
I cover this up,
i become your accomplice.
You think you can guilt me
into that?
If the cops are going
to come for me,
Please warn me...
So that i can tell
my wife first.
Chase...
You really think
you can kill another human being
Without any consequences
to yourself?
No.
(male narrator on tv)
american alligators
are mostly found
In the southeastern
united states.
My neighbor called.
He sounded...
Happy.
(narrator)
and west to the southern tip
of texas.
That's nice.
Even nicer,
he's approving
The garden expansion.
Huh.
And even more nicer,
He's not going
to press charges
What did you do
to him?
I was nice.
You really want
to know?
I think...
I want to give you
the benefit of the doubt.
(narrator)
alligators eat
Fish, birds, turtles,
Snakes, mammals,
and amphibians.
Both: oh!