Hey.
(beringer)
hey, i'll be
right there.
Take your time.
you mind if i get
a drink of water?
no, not at all.
help yourself.
[water pouring]
[chuckles]
Not exactly
beach reading, huh?
Do you understand
any of that stuff?
Well, most of these
i can get through,
But, uh, that one?
can't get past
the dust jacket.
where's ted?
laid off.
Company's going with per diem
workers, you know.
You don't have to pay overtime,
health insurance.
Wow. that sucks.
I don't mind. really, i'm not
a 40-hour-a-week kind of guy.
Uh...
if i could just
get you to sign.
Right. um...
Hang on one second.
i want to show you something.
[chuckles]
(sidas)
[coughs]
You're gonna laugh,
but, uh,
i swear, this guy james sidas
looks exactly like you.
Wait, hang on a second.
This guy is you.
i saw a profile
nova did on you.
you're, like, the youngest guy
to ever graduate mit?
Standards were lower
back then.
You got an iq of 178.
published three books
and 35 papers
all before
the age of 18?
Yeah, uh, sorry,
i really need to get going.
So if i could just
get you to sign off.
All right. i'll trade you.
i'll sign if you'll sign.
i'm not that guy
anymore.
come on, man.
This is the most
exciting thing
That's happened
in this place in years.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
come on.
don't be like that.
i'm paying you a compliment.
It's...
It's not that, um...
My hand's not working.
Hey, hey. whoa, whoa.
You okay?
No.
[massive attack's teardrop]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
$2.32.
put it on
dr. wilson's tab.
I don't know who dr. wilson is,
and we don't have tabs.
Do you know who i am?
No.
good.
But, sir--
I got it. it's all right.
Thanks.
Although i should
make it clear
That for two bucks all you get
is top half, over the clothes.
Any plans for turkey day?
Go to my sister's
for dinner. why?
Just making pleasant
conversation.
I've heard tell
of folks doing such.
How 'bout we
talk about this?
15-year-old.
Recurring migraines
and blurred vision.
Great.
Really?
sure.
There's no point
in putting a band together
If we're not gonna
play any gigs.
Hold on.
take this instead.
I was expecting
more resistance.
That was the old me.
New me is static-guarded
and friction-free.
Enjoy your drumstick.
Ready to save some lives?
32-year-old courier.
Ataxia, anemia,
mild cough.
Ct was clear.
tox screen negative.
What're you
so excited about?
Why wouldn't i be?
got all my starters back,
plus a couple of first-class
free agents.
I feel like mike tomlin.
probably not
as much as you do,
But you get the idea.
Ataxia and anemia
could be viral. maybe west nile?
No fever,
lymph glands were normal.
Anybody seen wilson?
Hyperbilirubinemia?
Yeah, like that's
a real thing.
Meningitis.
Anemia's a stretch.
page dr. james wilson
at 558.
(taub)
what about
sickle cell?
Guy's white.
Whites can get it.
Come on. we get the tennis elbow
and all the money.
Let them have
sickle cell.
Ttp's a better fit.
he's right.
What, you thought i wouldn't
agree with him? ever?
You didn't agree with him.
that's why he dumped you.
Oh, sorry. it was mutual.
We're cool, okay?
nobody's angry, nobody's hurt.
(house)
sounds passionate.
Ttp makes sense to me.
Not to me.
what if he had
a history of--
One big, happy family.
Ttp it is.
Confirm with
a blood smear
And adamts13 antibodies.
(voice on pa)
dr. james wilson,
please dial 558.
Can you cure it?
Ttp isn't
completely curable,
But the symptoms are manageable
with the proper treatment.
Is this the treatment?
No, first we need to do a blood
test to confirm the diagnosis.
But he's gonna
get better.
honey, that's what
she's saying.
I'm gonna be okay.
don't worry.
How can't i worry?
you're in the hospital.
I'm gonna be fine.
(taub)
you're sure everything
was fine before?
Given your
educational background,
You'd think you could at least
find a job with a medical plan.
(sidas)
we have money.
don't worry.
(taub)
it's not that,
it's just--
I want to make sure we have
all the information we should.
My husband wouldn't lie.
It's okay, baby.
he's just doing his job.
He just wants
to make sure i'm not
A secret drug addict
or an alcoholic.
Or hiding a history
of mental illness?
I work as a courier
because i want to.
it's easy.
i don't have to think.
It's too hard to think.
No, just unpleasant.
no matter what i did,
it really wasn't good enough.
then i met dara.
She didn't care
how smart i was
Or what i might accomplish
in the future.
it was the first time
in my life
that i was really happy.
So i decided i would
rather be happy than smart.
[door opens]
You all right?
Sorry. i know you're not okay.
i mean...
She left.
went back to chicago.
Any chance
of reconciliation?
Nope.
Sure you don't want
to grab a drink after work?
Figured we could talk about
the perils of dating doctors.
I wasn't dating cameron.
I'm sorry.
i didn't mean to--
I know what you're doing
and i appreciate it,
But i've got it
under control.
that's what you said
about the dibala incident.
And obviously you didn't.
And talking about it obviously
made things so much better.
Didn't you think there was
something weird about that guy?
Not really. in fact,
he seemed pretty normal.
That's my point.
Guys with iqs off the chart
are usually completely...
abnormal.
Speaking of house,
why'd you come back?
I mean, you must've
taken a major pay cut.
Life's too short
to worry about money.
Your wife feel
the same way?
She's happy to cut back
on some things...
Like sex.
Why'd you come back?
why wouldn't i?
Like foreman said,
nobody's angry.
nobody's hurt.
Schistocytes.
That means ttp.
which is what
we thought it'd be.
Remember?
this is a good thing.
this is an easy thing.
And house doesn't take
cases that are easy,
which means
it's not ttp,
And he wants to see how long
it takes us to catch up to him.
Schistocytes suggest ttp.
Good. now what?
Normally, we'd
try plasmapheresis,
But the patient has
an albumin colloid allergy.
So?
So that means we have to
give him a splenectomy.
Yes, it does.
wilson?
(man)
no.
do you know where he is?
not in here.
(thirteen)
you're sure you want us
to take out his spleen.
(house)
is that what
a "splenectomy" is?
I thought it was
an ice cream treat.
Yuck.
So you do really
think he has ttp?
you're not
just testing us.
Yeah, like i have
time for games.
So why did you really
take this case?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm fishing
for a dinner invite.
[toilet flushes]
Missed you at
breakfast this morning.
And lunch.
I had a dentist
appointment.
you know where
cuddy's sister lives?
You see, this is why i don't
answer your urgent pages.
Because they're
not urgent pages.
I've decided what i'm gonna do
about cuddy and lucas.
I'm going to
break them up.
of course.
it's given me a purpose in life,
a goal, a raison d'etre.
albeit a selfish,
mean-spirited, childish raison.
I think of it more
as benevolent.
There's only two possible
outcomes for their relationship.
They split, or they stay
together forever.
If it's split,
Then the sooner it happens
the better for everyone.
If it's stay,
then my meddling won't matter.
[elevator bell dings]
In fact,
if they survive it,
It might even make
their bond stronger.
How you manage
to elevate your narcissism
To beneficence
is masterful.
Indinner.
Just 'cause
i'm sentimental.
Dinner is at cuddy's sister's,
which brings us back--
House, don't.
I fished for an invite.
cuddy wasn't biting,
So i'll have to crash.
I have no idea where
cuddy's sister lives.
Ask and thou
shalt receive.
You can't honestly think
i would help you with this.
Not help me, help cuddy.
remember?
If you don't get it,
I'll be forced to use
more nefarious methods.
Happy holidays.
Huh. looks great.
So he's all better?
Probably be on
some long-term meds,
And he's about
ten ounces lighter.
Other than that,
won't even know it's gone.
Did you hear that, honey?
you're gonna be just fine.
When can i get
out of here?
Everything checks out,
less than a week.
good, 'cause those boxes
Aren't gonna
deliver colors.
Colors?
green...
And orange...
And ceiling.
Mr. sidas, do you know
where you are?
Chewing.
Jimmy?
[monitor beeps]
Shirt...
He's stroking.
call the cath lab now.
Oh, my god.
Blood flow's restored.
there appears to be
no permanent damage.
Good news is it turns out
to be an exciting, action-packed
Thrill ride
of a case after all.
Bad news is we took out
his spleen for nothing.
Thank god he's still got
his appendix and tonsils.
so what looks like ttp,
acts like ttp,
Tests like ttp,
but isn't ttp?
Cns vasculitis explains ataxia,
and anemia, maybe the stroke.
Ct would've
picked up something.
Hi, i'm greg house,
a friend of your sister lisa.
Could be dic.
Lisa cuddy.
sorry. wrong number.
You gonna ask?
I'm sure he's got a perfectly
logical explanation.
Can't be dic.
no hemorrhaging.
And i'm calling
all 12 julia cuddys
Within a 100-mile radius.
See?
completely reasonable.
acquired
pancytopenia.
wbc's normal.
Hey, julia.
you're, uh--
you're lisa's sister, right?
You sure?
'cause you are number 12.
Maybe she got married
and changed her name.
Otis campbell.
Probably kept
her first name.
(foreman)
the mnemonic for toxins.
O for organophosphates,
t for tricyclics, i for insulin.
Or as i remember it,
"moist place."
That's "place" spelled
with two "l"s and a silent "b."
Except the tox screen
was negative.
Standard tox screen--unstandard
toxins don't show up on it.
You two do an
unstandard tox screen,
You two search his home.
Otis campbell's
got to be hiding somewhere.
Smartest guy in the world,
and this is the best he can do.
(chase)
maybe he's doing
what he loves.
Delivering boxes
was a childhood dream.
Soda, processed cheese,
Marshmallow spread.
Nothing in here
is capable of going bad.
Ibuprofen, eye drops,
cough syrup.
You want to come over
for thanksgiving dinner?
You never asked me
over before. why now?
I just never
thought of it.
But now that we're
both on the team...
And my wife left me?
Is that a bad reason?
No. but, uh, i'm okay.
on both the food and friends.
(taub)
mice.
Leptospirosis could explain
the ataxia and the anemia.
But not without a fever.
You have someone
to talk to?
Yeah.
who?
What, you want names?
look, you lost a friend.
i get it.
But i'm not kutner.
Good, 'cause kutner never
used to come over for dinner.
I'm gonna pretend there's
something interesting over here
So you'll shut up.
Actually, there is.
He's got sketches
of atomic structure,
this one's full
of math proofs.
They're all old.
nothing since '96.
this isn't some
homework assignment
his parents
forced on him.
This is passion.
why would he want
to stop doing this?
Marriage destroyed
his soul.
Ooh.
Or maybe it was
just the booze.
Thank you, doctor,
you've been wonderful.
As have you, diana.
be well.
(diana)
thank you.
You're helping.
Voluntarily.
He's done six already.
(house)
figured you might
be getting backed up.
The holiday season
and all.
So which one of us slipped
through the wormhole
Into an alternate
dimension?
I have always loved to travel.
and paint.
Lucky number seven.
House...
I know you're
trying to be nice,
But i also know you're doing it
because you have an agenda.
Wow. sexy and smart.
lucas is a lucky guy.
The question is, is this
a bad agenda or a good one?
either you're trying
to screw with me,
Or you're trying to show me
that you've really changed.
So which is it?
i'm dying to know.
What are you doing
for thanksgiving dinner?
Peace in our time.
It cost me 45 minutes
of clinic duty.
This is
a three-hour drive.
have you considered
the possibility
That this is
a fake address?
You think she'd send me
to a vacant lot
For thanksgiving dinner?
If she's smart.
She is.
That's why i ran it
through motor vehicles.
Good as gold.
This cannot end well.
I don't want it
to end well.
you should
come as my date.
You're not gonna
want to miss this.
The unstandard tox screen was
as clean as the standard one.
But we found vodka
stashed away in his place.
What's with the ties?
Makes me look adorably
non-threatening.
Party or party hearty?
Liver failure would
explain all the symptoms.
Party.
So guy's a brainiac, and his
secret drug of choice is booze?
That's kind of pedestrian,
don't you think?
Talk to him.
he's a pedestrian guy.
(foreman)
with pedestrian
alcoholism.
Liver biopsy can wait
until after thanksgiving.
Yes, assuming
the biopsy's gonna tell us
Exactly what we
expect it to tell us,
It can wait till
after new year's.
on the other hand,
taub and thirteen
can do the liver
biopsy today.
Why us?
Juniority.
welcome back.
What do you
want us to do?
Same as me.
have a happy thanksgiving.
I'm not an alcoholic.
Yes, you just hide vodka
around the house for fun.
I drink, just not a lot.
Since when do you
drink at all?
I have one shot when i get home
from work, baby, that's it.
So why lie
to your wife about it?
(sidas)
because it's
not important.
What difference
does it make?
That you drink every day
by yourself?
I have one
lousy drink, okay?
Have you ever
seen me drunk? ever?
No, but you've
obviously been
Drinking enough
to hurt your liver.
my liver is fine.
hold still.
There we go.
This test is
a waste of time.
[james taylor's
games people play]
¶ ¶
[sings fanfare]
Hey.
want some wine?
¶ ¶
All right. very good.
here, we got this.
string beans?
¶ la-la, la, la-la,
la, la-la ¶
¶ la-la, la, la, la ¶
¶ la-la, la, la-la, la ¶
¶ ¶
Julia?
no, i'm
the house sitter.
They're in hawaii
for the week.
¶ oh, the games people play ¶
¶ every night and every day ¶
¶ never meaning
what they say... ¶
Happy thanksgiving.
Happy thanksgiving,
you guys.
You must be dr. house.
I was told i should offer you
a turkey sandwich.
¶ talkin' 'bout
you and me ¶
¶ and the games
people play ¶
¶ oh, now ¶
¶ la-la, la, la-la,
la, la-la ¶
la, la-la... ¶
Tuna salad. closest thing
they had to turkey.
Thanks.
But i'm hoping i can
still get out of here
To catch the tail end
of dinner with my wife.
anything?
No cirrhosis, no scarring,
no infection.
Blood panel?
Elevated albumen: 7.2.
That's it?
Everything else is fine.
So it was
a waste of time.
unless it's not his liver
that's elevating his albumen.
it's his kidneys.
renal failure.
explains the anemia.
If he developed hyperkalemia,
that would explain the ataxia.
but the stroke...
Ischemic encephalopathy.
Nice.
Except now we have to stay
and test his kidneys.
Key under the mat.
There's no key
under the mat.
oh, right.
You need to replace
one of your kitchen windows.
i helped myself
to your wine cellar.
I'll leave a buck
on the way out.
you're not
right for her.
And you are?
Less wrong.
Ah.
Then i started
thinking...
What was i saying?
You were saying
it's late, and...
She invited me.
she didn't know
if she should.
She was trying to figure out
if i really have changed or...
If i'm just the same old s.o.b.
i've always been.
But she always
gave me a chance.
832 chances.
and i used up
every one of them.
832's her limit.
Make a note.
How 'bout
a cup of coffee?
It's just instant, but...
I'm pathetic.
I don't deserve her.
Okay, okay, all right.
Uh, here.
[exhales]
Maybe you should
crash here.
It's a sofa bed.
I love her.
Rhabdomyolysis.
No edema.
I trust you had
a wonderful thanksgiving?
I don't remember.
So i guess i did.
Multiple myeloma.
No bone pain.
You got drunk alone?
No.
That would be a sign that i need
to talk to you about this.
Polycystic
kidney disease?
(thirteen)
no utis or flank pain.
Well, what if his cough
is more than just a cold?
He hasn't been coughing.
It's in his history,
and we found
A new bottle of cough syrup
in his medicine cabinet.
Cough could mean
goodpasture syndrome.
Affects kidneys
and lungs.
Start him on immunosuppressors
and dialysis.
We'll do it after
we run it by house.
(foreman)
he's not answering
his pager.
Looks like he's
leaving it up to us.
Us, not you.
(taub)
and since we
don't disagree,
You can save your fight
for another case.
How long do i have to
be hooked up for?
Four to six hours a day
until we see an improvement.
What if you don't?
Then we keep doing it until
he gets a transplant.
you were sure
it was his spleen,
And then you were sure
it was his liver,
which he told you
it wasn't,
and now you're sure
it's his kidneys.
(thirteen)
it's definitely
his kidneys.
We just don't know
why it's his kidneys.
Any word from cameron?
Nope.
I started seeing a counselor
after my diagnosis.
She's really good.
Why does everyone assume
that everyone works
In the exact same way?
We pretty much do.
Our egos want us to think
we're all snowflakes,
No two alike, but really
we all want the same things.
Love, forgiveness...
Chocolate.
Well, what i want is for
everyone to leave me alone.
[elevator bell dings]
how do i get that?
What did you say
to lucas last night?
I know there were
a lot of consonants.
I don't remember how i got here,
never mind what i said.
well, i just
talked to him.
And he said he thought
it'd be better
If we stopped
seeing each other.
Said he didn't realize
How much there still was
between you and me,
And he didn't want to get
caught in the middle of us.
I was drunk.
Whatever i said,
he can't really--
i've had enough, house.
I actually felt bad
about scamming you.
But then you lived down to
my expectations and then some.
There is no "us."
There never will be.
It worked.
Please tell me you're talking
about a medical procedure.
They split up
this morning.
You're the very first
one i've told.
And you think she'll
start dating you?
I'm sure she hates you.
But her eyes say,
"how will i ever pay you
for that tennis lesson?"
[sighs]
what a shame.
they'll get over it.
I meant for you.
I'll get over it
faster than they do.
Can't believe
that lucas fell for my
"i never say this
because it's so personal
Except that i'm drunk"
profession of love.
Second-oldest trick
in the book.
You're right. it's his fault
because he's stupid.
He certainly is.
You're stupid.
Well, i'm rubber,
and you're glue.
He's not pedestrian,
he's stupid.
At least stupider
than he should be.
He's a dxm junkie.
Dextromethorphan.
as in cough syrup?
He wasn't taking it
for his cough.
It's cheap, available
at your corner drug store,
And taken in high doses,
it's a dumb drug.
Dumb drug.
well, he obviously hasn't--
he's smart
compared to you.
He's a moron
compared to what he was.
"robotripping" lowers the iq.
it also causes brain damage.
Unless taken with the proper
amount of ethanol.
About one drink per day.
he wasn't
abusing the booze
And taking the cough remedy
medicinally.
He was abusing
the cough meds,
And taking
the booze medicinally.
Bravo.
Why would you do that?
If you had a--
A gift, why would you
just throw it away?
I didn't throw it away.
I just turned it
down a little.
When my brain
was on low,
Everything didn't seem
so miserable anymore.
Life was bearable.
I thought that
i did that.
You do.
(house)
long-term abuse of dxm
explains all your symptoms.
Even--oh, sweet irony--
your cough.
whole bowel lavage,
activated charcoal.
we get all traces of it
out of your system.
You'll be the unhappiest
little courier in no time.
I don't think i can
live without it.
You'd be surprised
what you can live without.
Make him a genius.
I can't believe it.
he looks so much better already.
we were thinking
about calling gq.
Lavage has removed all traces
of dxm from his body.
You're drawing again.
what is it?
just doodles.
no, it's not.
Come on, jimmy,
i want to know.
This is a toroidal
helicon plasma device.
It determines
the amount of energy
Expended by
the subatomic particles.
i'm thirsty. could you
get me a juice or something?
Yeah, of course.
I'm so happy, jimmy.
I told you.
Do you know what the difference
between her iq and mine is?
91 points.
In relation, she's closer
to a gibbon than she is to me.
Having sex with her would be
an act of bestiality.
I assume you
didn't marry her
for her skill
in applied physics.
I just wish
she could spell it.
You really think
you'd be happier
With someone
who could spell better?
No.
That's the problem.
i'm the one
who's a jerk.
But i owe her everything.
I want to want
to be with her.
And when i'm clear, i...
I can't.
Fainting, dizziness,
shortness of breath?
sometimes.
Is the wait
always this long?
Only on days
that end in "day."
Diarrhea, weight loss?
A bit.
Don't you ever shave?
Yeah. once a week.
how 'bout you?
Stomach pain, tenderness?
every now and then.
Are you this rude
to all your patients?
Oh, yes. don't think
you're special.
So we've got a lot of vague,
unverifiable symptoms.
Yet all the physical signs
are perfectly normal.
What do you think i have?
I'm not sure,
but i think it's...
A lame job.
What?
You're a rat.
Insurance company
sends you out
To check on the quality
of medical care.
that's ridiculous.
Is it really?
'cause you seem
a lot more interested
In asking questions
than answering them.
Handwriting on your
medical records is obviously
Not a doctor's 'cause
i can almost read it.
And when you went out
for a urine sample,
I looked in your purse.
Found the list of questions
you were supposed to memorize
Before you came
to the clinic.
I was looking for gum.
You're an ass.
Put it in your report.
I tell you what.
I'll give you 20 bucks
if you'll pretend that i'm not
When we leave this room.
Remember,
first ice, then heat.
If you have any problems,
don't hesitate to call me.
Thank you, dr. house.
Wait a second.
where's cuddy?
Gone for the day.
(house)
hey, hey, hey!
Sorry.
I can't remember
if i've mocked you yet
For being a male nurse.
I think this counts.
Fair enough.
That isn't
the man i married.
Yes, he is.
He's just smarter.
give him some time.
i'm sure--
He hates me.
his body is going
through withdrawal.
He's adjusting.
maybe he never loved me.
not really.
Maybe we never really
had anything at all.
(sidas)
somebody help!
I can't feel my legs.
i can't feel my legs.
Anywhere.
Nothing.
We have to talk
about this.
It's late. i'm tired.
I know it's
a big pay cut,
Bubut i'll always have
the chance to make money.
i won't always have
the chance to do this job.
That's what you think?
that it's about
the money?
So it's that
i didn't consult you
before i took the job?
That was offensive,
but it's not about that either.
so then...
Can you give me
the first letter?
When we got married,
You were an intern working
30-hour shifts doing grunt work.
and we both
put up with it
because we knew that it was
leading to something better.
in your private practice,
you are the boss.
You call the shots,
But now you're 40 years old,
you're still doing grunt work.
That's what this is about?
you think i'm a wuss?
He made you miss
thanksgiving dinner.
[pager beeps]
(thirteen)
vitamin b12 deficiency?
Gives us anemia,
numbness.
(house)
not a stroke.
if he has
a vascular malformation--
Anemia's not macrocytic.
Sorry to
inconvenience you.
dying patients
can be so thoughtless.
Don't.
Great comeback.
is that oscar wilde?
come on, people.
bone marrow
malignancy.
Wouldn't produce
schistocytes.
Lupus.
Gee, thanks for coming in.
ana was negative.
what about you?
got any predictable drivel
you'd like to add?
I think they've
given you enough already.
(house)
well, at least
they're trying.
They're not just sitting there
like roadkill.
give me something.
Give me something,
or i'll get your ex-smarter half
on the phone
and ask her.
house.
You're gonna be
pressing charges?
Against the ottoman
i tripped over?
against chase.
I'm pretty sure the ottoman
was acting alone.
You free for dinner
this weekend?
At least three other people
saw him do it.
Mass hysteria.
either night?
I can't have doctors
punching each other out.
Oh, my god,
who got punched?
And more importantly,
for chase's sake,
I need to know if he's
able to handle himself
or if i should be
getting him some help.
Chase couldn't have
punched anyone.
he was with me when
i tripped over the ottoman.
If you're not planning on eating
this weekend, maybe a movie?
I'm not doing this,
house.
it's not fun anymore.
Just do your job.
[door closes]
I need your help.
What happened
to your face?
I was mowing the lawn
when the phone rang.
you're a computer.
i'm gonna feed you data,
And you analyze it.
What, are you
gonna feed me
20 years of medical
knowledge too?
It's not gonna work.
I know.
But i don't have
anyone else to ask.
It's lonely, isn't it?
It's not that bad.
Then you're not that smart.
You ever tried
to kill yourself?
Not quickly.
i did.
12 years ago i jumped off
The top of
my eight-story building
Into a dumpster bin
the day before pickup.
i broke my collarbone,
my leg, and three ribs.
When i was in the hospital
they put me on narcotics
And suddenly everything
was just better.
i didn't feel
isolated or lonely.
that's where
i met my wife.
She was so happy.
And dumb.
And i was...
Smart...
and miserable.
you tell me
who the genius is.
i fell in love with her
buzzed out of my head,
And i knew i wanted
to stay that way forever.
enjoy.
[chuckles]
Easier on your conscience
if i die an idiot?
What's a conscience?
Which ribs...
did you break
in the fall?
They on the left side?
Yeah, bottom three.
that was 12 years ago.
This probably
cost me my marriage,
So it better be awesome.
Ferrous oxide contrast?
(house)
gets absorbed
by the spleen.
Unless he doesn't
have one.
In which case it's absorbed
by the liver, and fries that.
You're killing him?
You think i opened him up
and didn't take out his spleen?
All organs do look kind of
the same--red and squishy.
Oh, my god.
Accessory spleens.
Okay, that is amazing.
12 years, eight stories,
and a dumpster ago,
he broke three ribs,
Damaged his spleen.
Bits of it split off,
Circulated through
his bloodstream
Until they landed
and attached somewhere else.
So it is ttp.
I just didn't remove...
All of his spleens.
16 splenectomies.
Pretty sure he gets
a set of steak knives with that.
(chase)
i can outrun you.
Sorry about the nose.
and the eye. and the, uh...
Eyebrow.
Guess i deserved it.
Well, if i thought that,
i wouldn't be apologizing.
Your fist slipped?
Everybody kept bugging me,
asking if i was okay.
So you busted my nose
to keep people off your back.
Pretty much.
Making people even more
worried about you.
maybe.
But at least they're not
talking to me about it.
Fair enough.
Cheers.
Thank you.
Don't be so grateful.
You'll be delivering packages
for 70 years to pay for it.
Well, uh,
thanks for our talk.
it's been a while
since i had
a stimulating conversation.
So what're you gonna do?
Go back to my life.
Which one?
The one that has
my wife in it.
(taub)
robotripping.
How's she feel
about that?
well, she doesn't
have to know.
It's worked for 12 years.
Tell your brain
i said good-bye.
Einstein's giving
himself a lobotomy,
And you're
cool with that?
Ignorance is bliss.
Hold that pose.
[beeps, clicks]
I'll start with
t-shirts and mugs,
And see how it goes.
Home early.
(rachel)
what happened to him?
You beat up house?
Just one right hook.
Why? what happened?
you were right.
I told him we need
to lay down some ground rules,
got a little heated.
That's not what i meant.
Is he okay?
are you gonna be fired?
arrested?
Everything's fine.
Wow.
Dr. cuddy.
Can we at least be civil?
How's your nose?
It's okay.
Does your kid
like animals?
I got tickets to
that holiday carnival.
I hear they have
a nice petting zoo.
I think i was
pretty clear before.
I don't mean with me.
Here. take 'em. enjoy.
No, thanks.
They're not fake.
i didn't steal them.
One of the nurses was selling
'em for her kid's scout trip.
I know it doesn't make
things right between us,
But i just wanted
to do something nice.
I don't want them.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
They didn't split up.
She wouldn't
take the tickets.
Of course.
Windtalker code for
"we never split up."
House, she told you
multiple times
She wants nothing
to do with you.
I wasn't gonna be there.
She just felt guilty
that i felt guilty,
so she couldn't
take them.
Either that or she didn't
want to appease you.
These weren't
reparations.
Just a simple
gesture of remorse,
And she slapped it down.
They didn't break up.
She just wanted me
to think that so i'd back off.
Dare i ask
what you're gonna do?
Nothing.
I said they'd either break up
or they'd stay together.
They didn't break up.
And you're
okay with that?
It is what it is.
Good for you.
Aah.
[james taylor's enditol]
¶ ¶
House knows i lied.
Why? what'd he say?
Nothing.
i could just tell.
You want to stage
another breakup?
No.
Oh, hi.
It seems like he's
gonna leave us alone.
Why would he do that?
I'm not completely sure.
So, we have his blessing?
I guess so.
Maybe House isn't so bad after all.
That would be nice, wouldn't it?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com