My lords and ladies!
Today, your Queen
will choose her champion.
Here he will battle
for not only her honor,
but for a title
of his own.
But only if he can defeat
the Captain of my Guard,
Sir Horace the Black!
Sir William, wouldst
thou fight for my honor?
To the death,
Your Majesty.
Let's hope it does not
come to that, eh?
I choose Sir William
as my champion.
Attack from
his left side.
I saw his squire bandaging
that shoulder this morning.
I wish thee
luck and strength.
I fear I shall need
all I can get.
The Captain of my Guard,
Sir Horace the Black!
Are you sure you wouldn't like to
reconsider your choice, my Queen?
I believe I chose rightly, my King.
Brave knights, in the honored
tradition of our land, have at ye!
I fear you chose
most poorly, my love.
William! William!
William?
What is it?
Your eyes.
William.
We need an ambulance
at the Camden Fairgrounds.
You're new.
You're naked.
And for the record,
a little bit cold.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
that anyone was home.
James had an early call,
and I was just leaving.
Without breakfast?
I'm fine, thanks.
I'm Sam, by the way.
House. Nice to meet you.
It'd be nicer
if you put this on.
So you and Wilson...
Thought you were staying
in New York last night.
Sorry, must have missed the "if this trailer be a
- rocking" sign out front.
I'm really late, so...
If there's any chance that we
can pretend this never happened,
I'd be completely
fine with that.
An eight-year-old
with bleeding ears.
I'll see your bleeding ears and raise
you a total muscular degeneration.
What the hell?
I had a dream like this
once. It didn't end well.
Huzzah,
my loyal peasants.
House,
what are you doing?
Filling in for Rabbi Shmuhl
at the Goldstein Bris.
While I'm busy, you all can check
out the knight down in the ER,
who instead of seizing
the throne, just seized.
He works at
a Renaissance festival?
Doesn't work there,
he lives there.
He's part of a wonderful little troupe
who spend their weekends
re-enacting a nobler age
when people crapped in the streets and
Thirteen would've been a grandmother.
Weeks, not weekends. Says here
he's been camping out for a month.
Try doing that
with a pen.
Why don't you put that down
before you kill one of us?
Better idea. Why don't you
give me something I can use
so I won't feel
the need to?
Seizure right after a fight
obviously suggests concussion.
Obviously it isn't, or the
ER wouldn't have called House.
A full suit of armor would
protect against visible trauma,
but not transmitted
concussive force.
Could be a subdural
hematoma.
You're forgetting
to demonize.
An evil, satanic
subdural hematoma.
No, two demon eyes.
Hemorrhaging in the sclerae.
Could be an allergic reaction to
something from the Renaissance fair.
Which is why we need to
check out Middle Earth.
Foreman, take Frodo and
break bread with the Hobbits.
I still think a hematoma is more likely.
That's why you and Chase
are gonna get an MRI.
But you just...
I said Frodo,
not Gollum.
Is he saying I have
short legs or hairy feet?
I don't even know
who Frodo is.
Who's the chick, and
why are you hiding her?
You were home
last night?
And this morning. I bumped
into your babe naked.
I told you to stay
out of my bathroom.
I was in the kitchen.
She was naked in the
kitchen? I was naked.
Why were you naked
in the kitchen?
That's not important
right now.
What is, is why you didn't want
me to meet her in the first place.
Is she married?
No.
Patient?
I don't have time
for this.
She used to be a man.
House!
She wants to be a man.
Sam is a man's name,
short for...
Samantha.
The soulless harpy you were
married to before we met.
People change, House.
Sure. They get older, their
ovaries start drying up
and nice guys like you
look attractive again.
Listen, I know that in
your own demented way,
you think you're looking
out for me. But I have this.
By "this" you mean a sinking
feeling in the pit of the stomach.
Fine, I get it.
It's your life, you go
screw it up. I can wait.
For what?
To tell you,
"I told you so. "
No signs of a hematoma.
Brain looks completely normal.
Normal, except for the fact
that he likes to play dress-up.
My uncle used to pretend
that he was King Leopold.
I'm not pretending.
Sorry about that.
But you don't really think
you're a knight, do you?
Being a knight isn't a
game, it's a lifestyle,
and we do it every day, not
just when we play dress-up.
We live by a code, and uphold ideals
like loyalty, courage, humility.
And the part where you beat the
crap out of each other in armor?
That we do for fun. At least
it was up until yesterday.
Are we almost done?
I'm feeling...
Let's get him out of there
before he aspirates.
Anything abnormal
on the MRI?
God's teeth! What strange
manner of garments be these?
Okay. We'll be back soon.
He consorts with tiny demons in
his hand. 'Tis witchcraft, I say.
Do I look like I'm here
to play pretend with you?
Relax.
It's not personal.
Just tell them you're a
time traveler or something.
Well, if we're gonna be here,
we might as well enjoy it.
Our knight just vomited
inside the MRI.
Taub thinks it might
be food poisoning.
Which shouldn't
be surprising.
Outdoor latrines, food prep
going on next to livestock.
I hear you wish to speak with
me concerning Sir William.
How faireth he?
Not well,
or we wouldn't be here.
A pox indeed is...
Miles.
We just thought
it was a concussion.
He's going to be
okay, right?
We need to look at the
area he was camping out in.
And you might want to invest into
a dental plan for the kingdom.
You sure he got sick
from something here?
I'm not sure of anything, yet, but...
What do you make of this?
Mmm.
Looks like vomit.
Means he was showing
symptoms prior to the fight.
True, but I meant this.
Oh. It's a cow eye from the
night before the tournament.
He makes the knights eat all
kinds of disgusting stuff.
Why?
Got the idea
from Fear Factor.
Why didn't he mention it when
he checked into the hospital?
I make them all take an oath
of secrecy about the ritual.
William tends to take his role
as a knight very seriously.
You think that's what
caused him to pass out?
It's not exactly sanitary.
Fun stuff never is.
Serious bacterial food poisoning
explains seizure and vomiting.
A lumbar puncture
could confirm.
Except it's not
food poisoning.
If it was, the ER would
look like Camelot right now.
All it takes is
one bad eyeball.
Or testicle, cow brain,
or my personal favorite,
pig rectum with a side
order of sphincter.
I think they call that
breakfast in Australia.
No one else was sick because
they weren't allergic like he was.
To what? That's what I
sent you to Middle Earth
to find out.
Run scratch tests with the
samples you brought back.
That's gonna take time,
and he's getting worse.
So treat him with
epinephrine, too.
This should prevent
any more symptoms
until we can figure out
what it is you're allergic to.
Thanks.
I told you, you shouldn't
have eaten all that stuff.
You know,
you don't have to stay.
I'm sure you and Miles are crazy
busy, what with the wedding and all.
Miles said we could
postpone it until...
Don't worry, I'll be fine. I'll be there.
I just hope you have a good photographer.
'Cause I don't think the standard
red-eye filter's going to work on these.
I need
your right arm.
That feels...
Feels strange.
What is it?
What's wrong?
His heart rate's
become irregular.
My chest hurts. It feels
like it's going to explode.
Tachycardia. We need to
shock him back into rhythm.
Oh, my God,
William...
I need his gown open.
What is that?
What is that stuff?
I don't know.
It's definitely
not an allergy,
or the epi would have helped
him, not made him worse.
Unless he's allergic and allergic
to the cure. Sodium bisulfite,
the preservative that keeps epi
peppy, can cause tachycardia.
So can Wolff-Parkinson-
White syndrome,
and it also causes
hemorrhaging in the eyes.
And abnormal electrical pathways in
the heart, which could cause seizures.
But not skin infections.
There is an infection that can
cause skin and neurological damage
and spreads rapidly
without treatment.
Methicillin-resistant
staphylococcus aureus?
Lord have MRSA.
You weren't wearing gloves when we
shocked his heart back into rhythm.
I'm sure you'll be fine. You two,
get a sample to the lab to confirm.
You get the knight into
isolation and on IV antibiotics.
You, stay away from me.
Need to talk.
About the MRSA?
I know. We're...
MRSA, shmrsa.
Something important.
Something you think is more important
than a potentially lethal bacteria
spreading like wildfire
through my hospital?
Well, that narrows it down to
something personal and stupid.
Wilson.
Theory confirmed.
He is dating his first wife, I know.
I don't believe it.
That he didn't ask
your permission first?
No, that he's actually capable
of keeping a secret from me.
Well, you'd be surprised how many
things Wilson doesn't tell you.
Would I? Like how you slept with
your father's best friend? Or...
I'm going to kill him.
You need to break them up.
Forget it.
So you'd rather
sit back and watch
while the evil blonde gorges
on Wilson's tender flesh
and then tosses out his bones
like she did the last time?
You remember what
he was like after that?
Yes, I do.
Well, then
do something.
God knows he's not gonna listen to me.
You, on the other hand, have
decades of experience dating
and being attracted
to losers.
Obviously I don't
include myself.
You know what happens when you interfere
in other people's relationships?
Of course,
I do it all the time.
Hmm. I see your point.
That is why
I'm staying out of this.
You force him to choose,
you might not like the answer.
He doesn't seem to be
in as much pain any more.
That's good.
But we won't be out of the woods for
sure until the blisters start to recede.
I'm really thirsty.
You mind getting me a soda?
Sure.
I'll be right back.
What's wrong?
The pain in my chest,
it's getting worse.
Just now?
No.
I didn't want
to worry her.
So how long have you
been in love with her?
What? No,
we're just friends.
Seriously.
Since the first time
I saw her.
Why don't you tell her?
She's engaged
to my friend.
The King?
Haven't seen him visiting
or sitting by your bedside.
He has responsibilities.
Yeah? I'm guessing
the Queen does, too.
What kind of knight
steals his friend's bride?
I hate that
I even think about it.
You're not a knight.
You're just a guy.
But I want to be
more than that.
Your chest?
No, my back.
Feels like there's
a knife in it.
Is the infection spreading?
It's not MRSA.
It looks like some sort
of clostridial organism.
Question is, which type of
clostridium? There's hundreds.
C. Perfringens?
Wouldn't account for his other
symptoms. C. Tetani, on the other hand?
Tetanus? He would have
been inoculated against it.
So he cut himself and
didn't get a booster shot.
The guy fights people with swords
for fun, no one said he's smart.
They don't just
fight for fun.
They fight to prove
their bravery.
You buying this honor stuff?
Fighting is not brave,
it's just stupid.
You would say that.
You think I've never
been in a fight?
No, I just think
you've never won one.
I took on three guys
in college once.
Hope they
bought you dinner first.
It's not MRSA.
I know.
It's poison ivy.
Poison ivy?
A severe reaction
could cause the blisters
and maybe irritate his eyes
enough to cause the hemorrhaging,
but the chest pain
and seizures?
They have bonfires
every night.
Burning leaves
aerosolizes the oil.
You've seen what it's done
to the outside of his body,
imagine what it's doing to
his lungs and his sinuses.
Okay, maybe
it remotely fits,
but I'd rather go with scientific
evidence than with your gut.
How about this?
Apparently,
it's all over his sword.
It's his heart rate again!
How fast is it? It's
slowing. Why aren't you...
It's not MRSA.
I'm giving him 12 cc's
of epinephrine.
He tested positive.
You'll blow his heart out.
If it slows any more,
it's going to stop.
I told you!
And I told you.
That wasn't caused
by poison ivy.
Or epinephrine.
Means the heart problem we ruled
out, we now have to rule back in.
We found clostridium
bacteria in the skin samples.
Clostridium's in dirt
and basically harmless.
But opportunistic, if his
immune system was depressed.
Leukemia?
He would've had symptoms
way before the
Renaissance festival.
Which is true of anything that
would compromise his immune system.
Which means it has to be some
other environmental toxin.
Yesterday he was a healthy
knight, today he's sleeping beauty.
Nothing else fits.
Trichinosis from
eating infected meat?
We already ruled
out food poisoning.
Both the butcher shop and the food
stands at the fair were totally clean.
Then he ate the poison
apple somewhere else,
or maybe you just missed it.
Start treatment for trichinosis
and confirm with a muscle biopsy.
Hey.
I can't believe I'm
about to say this. Sam...
Told you so.
No, she didn't dump me. She
wants to get to know you better.
Damn it! I never should
have let her see me naked.
It goes against all my
instincts, but I said all right.
Why?
She thinks I was hiding her from you.
You were.
I don't want
her to know.
You're asking me to condone a
relationship based on lies and mistrust?
Yeah.
When and where?
Tonight. Venezia. 8:00.
What am I gonna wear?
All my cereal boxes
are at the cleaners.
House, listen.
I know you're
worried about me.
And I also know that
that kind of unselfishness
doesn't come
naturally to you.
But I don't want your help.
I don't need your help.
Just come to dinner and
be your usual selfish self.
How could I say no?
Miles said
he'd stop by later.
Tell him not to.
I don't want to be
seen like this.
You're sick. That's
nothing to be ashamed of.
Unless you're saying
you want me to leave?
No, don't.
I think he's saying it's
different with you, Shannon.
It's a guy thing. They don't like
showing weakness in front of each other.
Right, William?
Right. Maybe when I'm
feeling a little better.
I'm going to take a small sample
of your muscle tissue here.
Do you mind waiting outside for this?
Don't hurt him.
He's safe with me.
I thought you were
going to tell her.
Not my call, but if you ask
me, she's waiting for you to.
Knights are supposed
to be selfless.
Right, they conquered countries
and built castles by being selfless.
Bravery and loyalty are
great qualities for soldiers.
If you want to be king, sometimes you
have to be willing to take what's yours.
She's not mine.
She's not his either.
Not yet.
It's just dinner. Relax.
Trust me, there is no "just"
when House is involved.
We're in the middle
of a restaurant.
What could he possibly do?
That.
Sorry we're late,
but you know girls.
Always fiddling with
the hair and the makeup.
James, Sam,
this is Sarah.
It's nice to meet you.
Horace has told me...
House.
House has told me
all about you.
Nice to meet you.
What's the diagnosis?
His muscle biopsy's clean.
It's not trichinosis.
House was wrong.
This is not environmental.
Or we screwed up and missed
something at the Renaissance fair.
You think we did?
No, but I think
House will think we did.
What could we
have missed?
Fungal infection?
There's nothing in his blood work
even remotely suggesting that.
But it fits
the symptoms.
You want to retest every
sample we took for spores?
We'll be here all night.
Have you noticed how much
pain he's been in lately?
And that's relevant how?
Extra pain means extra
cranky, means off his game.
He's not gonna accept
this isn't environmental
unless we give
him no choice.
I cannot believe
you're from Bloomington.
I know.
Isn't it amazing?
Yeah. Delightful.
Ignore him. He's just
upset that we're having fun.
Do you remember
that little bakery,
the one with the
amazing cupcakes?
Gino's.
Oh, yes!
First stop every
time I go home.
Me, too.
Remember
that strip club?
Girl, I used to work at that strip club.
Where does it hurt,
William?
My legs. It feels
like they're on fire.
Rhabdomyolysis
means his kidneys are failing.
Also means it's not
environmental. We need to move on.
I recommend we start with a full
cancer work-up, starting with the...
Which one of you
checked out the apartment?
House...
His symptoms fit
an environmental...
The test results
don't. We redid...
Search the apartment.
He hasn't been there
in three weeks.
Go! Now!
I liked him better
when he was on Vicodin.
You and Thirteen
check out his place.
While you're wasting your time,
we'll ultrasound the liver.
If it's cancer, it's as
good a place as any to start.
Hey.
Heard House met Sam.
The first time
he was naked.
The second time, he brought a
transvestite prostitute to dinner.
Overall,
it could've been worse.
Great.
That's your reaction?
What?
Nudity, prostitutes...
Sorry. Preoccupied.
House said something
to you, didn't he?
No. He didn't.
It is a little crazy, though.
I mean, isn't it?
I mean, things seem
to be going great,
but they seemed to be
going great 12 years ago.
The good things
are still good.
She's still smart,
funny, gets me.
And she's less competitive.
Either she's changed or I've
changed, but either way...
Am I out of my mind?
You never know
what can happen.
Might as well
give it a chance.
Yeah.
Looks
like you were right.
Tumors, dozens of them
inside and on the surface.
Pull in closer.
See that?
What is that?
I don't know, but it's
definitely not cancer.
Kitchen's clean.
Bedroom as well.
Most dangerous thing in his
medicine cabinet was dental floss.
It's locked.
Key wasn't on his ring.
You honestly
want to go back
and tell House we didn't check
every square inch of this place?
Of course not.
My hero.
What the hell is this?
Either a secret
entrance to Hogwarts
or our knight
is a witch.
Our knight is into some
seriously creepy stuff.
He claims it's
just sugar water,
but we sent the rest down
to the lab for testing.
You think
he poisoned himself?
It's not poison. We would have
picked it up in his blood work.
Not if it collected
slowly in his liver
and it all started leaking
into his system at once.
These tumors
that aren't tumors,
what if they're focal hepatic
lesions filled with blood?
Every time one explodes, it'd
be releasing another dose.
Of what?
Plumbum nigrum.
You putting a hex
on someone?
It's Latin for
black lead.
Our knightlwarlock apparently
also dabbles in alchemy.
Lead poisoning?
Seizures, paralysis, weak immune
system and eventually coma.
Biopsy the cysts,
you'll find your lead.
You think we'll
make the 7:30?
I'm sorry. If I don't change, I'm
gonna feel like I'm at work all night.
Yeah, I remember.
Is it a problem?
Not at all.
In fact, if we hurry...
We will definitely
not make the 7:30.
Well, there's
always the 9:40.
Or not.
Shouldn't you be
at the hospital?
Wouldn't need a team if I did
all the work, now, would I?
Plus, I had to
make you dinner.
We have plans.
Bet your plans
don't taste like this.
Don't!
House, whatever it is
that you're up to...
I'm trying to be nice.
What I did the other night
was juvenile. I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Soufflé was amazing.
It's my mom's recipe. Everything
else, I got off the web.
Here's to the Internet.
Where I found
the lamb ragù
and you two found
each other. Again.
Well, it wasn't
just the Internet.
Yeah, more like
divorce, depression,
therapy, more therapy,
then the Internet.
Yeah.
And here we are.
Exactly.
Well, I need to go
to the bathroom.
I think you're old enough now, but if
you'd like me to come along with you...
I mean, is it safe
to leave the two of you?
Come on, James,
enough already.
Yeah, James.
I cook in peace.
Okay. Be right back.
You're a cold-hearted bitch
who ripped his heart out.
I watched him struggle for years
to overcome the damage you did,
and there's no way I'm just
gonna let you reel him back in
so you can do it
all over again.
And all this?
Phase two of getting
to know my enemy.
You're wrong about me.
But I'm glad now I don't
have to pretend I like you,
except for when James
is standing next to me.
Same here. The only difference
is, I'll outlast you.
And scene.
Well, it's too late
for the movie.
Wanna see
what's on TV?
Absolutely.
Love to.
There wasn't any lead present in
his blood work or liver biopsy.
And his heart rate and BP
are getting even more erratic.
We had to shock it back into
rhythm twice during the night.
There's only one
thing left to do.
We're wasting our time.
Actually, I've already
gotten good value.
I told you there's nothing here that
could've caused any of his symptoms.
No, you told me that you
couldn't find anything here
that could be causing his symptoms.
And now we're gonna find something
new because we're in costume?
We looked everywhere.
Tested everything.
Just because Wilson's acting
stupid doesn't mean we are.
You think he's
making a mistake?
Of course. But he'll figure
it out sooner or later.
Hopefully after a few
weeks of great sex.
Nothing ventured,
nothing gained.
Wilson's not like us.
He cares too much about
people and their feelings.
Thanks for the compliment.
The code that our
knight claims to live by,
all that crap about honor and
chivalry, Wilson's naturally like that.
Which is why he is...
A great guy.
...a sucker and a target.
Someone's got to look out for him.
You smell that?
Yeah, it's the
apothecary shop,
and, yes, Foreman
and I already...
I cry your pardon, sir.
You know what this is?
Why, that's lavender.
Try rose hips.
Both harmless.
Who cares?
It could be cyanide,
as far as he knows.
How about this?
Be nothing but
St John's wort.
Wrong again.
Black Cohosh.
My uncle owns the shop.
I just started apprenticing.
What's the big deal?
Hey, I just
organized all that.
You know what this is?
A wild carrot?
It's hemlock,
you embossed carbuncle.
That's hemlock?
You sure?
Did you sell it
to anyone?
It's poison.
Think hard.
It was just one branch.
You sold it
to Sir William.
No. To the King.
It's the only part of the
environment you didn't check.
The people living in it.
What's going on?
Why can't we see William?
Because you poisoned him,
your royal anus, with this.
Wild carrots?
Hemlock.
I need to know how much you
used and how you prepared it.
You did something
to William?
No, of course not.
He's still alive. You want to avoid
a murder charge, start talking fast.
The apothecary's willing to testify
that you're the only one he gave it to.
Okay. Yeah, maybe I bought
it for the food challenge,
but I didn't know
that was hemlock.
If it was for
the challenge,
why is Wee Willy the
only knight who's dying?
I don't know.
I'm telling you, I didn't know.
Why would I want to hurt William?
I can think of at
least one reason.
Miles, please, whatever happened,
just tell them the truth.
I am.
I swear.
We ran a gas
chromatography on his blood,
found trace amounts
of piperidine alkaloids.
The main markers
of hemlock intoxication.
Well, the good news is, we
now know what's wrong with you.
Bad news is, your king's precious
ideals were just pretend after all.
At least when it comes to guys
who get too close to his Queen.
It's not true.
I guess you've never
heard the expression,
"Gas chromatography
machines don't lie. "
Neither does Miles.
He's the best knight
I've ever known.
That's why
he was chosen king.
Miles is a jealous idiot,
and you're just an idiot.
Something's wrong.
We performed a gastric lavage and
administered activated charcoal,
but he's getting worse,
not better.
It's been in his
system two days.
We're lucky he's
lasted this long.
If it was hemlock,
he'd either be dead already
or getting better
with treatment.
It's hemlock. We found it in his blood.
He may have had
some hemlock,
but it's not
what's killing him.
Don't do it,
whatever you're planning,
especially if you're
gonna use that thing.
It was just sitting
in a stone...
Here. It's gonna cost extra 'cause of
the level of detail that you wanted.
Anything good? And by good,
I, of course, mean bad.
Nope. Pretty much
your typical life.
Married young,
got divorced.
Married a little less
young, got divorced.
She's been pretty successful in
everything she's done except marriage.
Well, there's gotta be
something I can use.
Maybe. Didn't read her shrink's
notes. Didn't seem right.
But stealing them did?
Whoa! I didn't steal them.
I found a way to obtain them.
Excuse me. I don't mean to
interrupt, but you got a minute?
Sure.
Oh, him? Yeah.
I was just leaving.
Careful, I have a sword.
I don't agree
with what you said,
but I understand
why you said it.
We were married young.
We both made mistakes.
And, yes, I did make
most of them.
But that was almost
a decade ago.
I'm sorry, is that the statutory
period for soul sucking?
I'm not asking you
to like me, House.
To be honest,
I think you're an ass,
but we do have
one thing in common.
We care about James.
So prove it and
dump him. Again.
You're pretty much insufferable
all the time, aren't you?
Sorry. Go on. And yes.
We just reconnected, we have
no idea where we're headed.
But is it really too much to ask
that you give us a chance to find out?
I'm sure I'll be seeing you around.
We did it.
Well, I did it.
What exactly did we do?
You do?
These aren't focal hepatic
lesions on his liver.
They're peliosis
hepatis lesions,
which, in combination with an erratic
heart rate, usually indicates...
Endocarditis, an infection
on his heart valve.
Two major symptoms
of anabolic steroid abuse.
No, he wouldn't...
And the rhabdo
makes the third.
Our patient's a juicer.
The ancient poison accelerated
the damage of the modern poison.
Start treatment. Let the
king out of the tower.
How are you feeling?
Ashamed.
You should be.
You'll compromise your
ideals to win a fight,
but not to go for
the woman you love.
That was a game,
not real life.
I didn't...
Hurt anyone?
Try telling that to Shannon.
Or maybe I missed something
while she was crying by your bed.
You don't need
to win anyone's heart.
You just need
to ask for it.
Miles is a great guy.
He's rich, smart,
treats her well.
She's going to have
a great life with him.
With me?
I'd do everything
I could for her,
but even at my best,
it wouldn't be much.
And she deserves the best.
I guess I'd rather she be
happy, even if it means I'm not.
Guess House was right
about that, too.
What?
You really are an idiot.