Marina: Mr Randall?
They're here.
Pete: $52 million includes over $6 million...
already issued pursuant to
the over-allotment option.
When can we close?
It would be subject to regulatory approval...
in both Toronto and...
I didn't say, "how," Oliver.
I said, "when."
What?
You sure this is a direction?
You want to go, Roy?
This would move us from energy service into...
You don't think oil's going up?
Of course it's gonna go up.
The question is when.
The question is always when,
and if we wait...
until the deal makes sense
to everyone else...
we're gonna be waiting in line
behind everyone else.
All I'm saying is...
The same cover-your-ass crap
you always say.
We're gonna have to wrap this up.
I got to go.
Where are you going?
- Upstairs.
Get the regulators on it.
I want to close by the end of the month.
Come on, Roy.
There are ten other items on the agenda.
Which will have to wait until next week.
You can't drag us all out of the office...
get halfway through, and then
just kick us out.
Yeah, I can.
Dr Johnson: The antibiotic treatment had no effect.
Both the fever and the pain are getting worse.
Which means it's not
Clostridium difficile.
But you said that was the only
diagnosis that made sense.
It was.
We need to get him to a hospital.
Jack: Dad?
I don't want to go.
I know, buddy.
But we may need to.
Am I gonna die?
No, of course not.
How do you know?
Well, I just do.
And I'm always right, aren't I?
Yeah.
House, M.D. Season 6 Episode 4: Instant Karma
Original Airdate on FOX 4: October 12th, 2009
I want House.
I understand, but I told you...
Dr House isn't available.
Dr...
- Call him.
Tell him I'll have a private jet.
Pick him up from whatever island.
He isn't on vacation.
Dr Foreman's one of our best doctors.
Is House in jail?
No.
Foreman is currently working
with two of House's...
most veteran associates.
- Rehab?
No.
Mr Randall, your son will be in good hands.
My son, has already been in good hands...
and he's still dying.
I'm through dealing with good.
I want the best and everyone
I've asked says that's House.
So unless he's dead, comatose...
or insane, I want him treating my son today.
You could have said no
in good conscience.
Cuddy: The kid'll still be Foreman's patient...
But his dad wants you making the decisions.
Then he's not my patient.
You want to give me none
of the responsibility...
and all of the liability?
Which means I get...
Oh, cool.
Don't let him do anything crazy.
When is he getting his license back...
so we can stop playing this game?
Maybe never.
This game is fun.
You also need to prepare
President Dibala's case...
for this week's morbidity and mortality conference.
Oh, unfortunately I'm overdue
a mani-pedi appointment.
Not you.
Foreman's department.
Oh, right.
Well, he's got all the time in the world.
We made the wrong call.
He died.
There's nothing to present.
It obviously garnered a lot of curiosity.
And we don't have more
important things to do...
than satisfy everyone's idle curiosity?
It's not idle.
The question of how we deal
with two possible diagnoses...
whose treatments are contraindicated...
is worth discussing.
Abdominal pain increasing
in severity and frequency...
fever, dehydration...
diarrhoea, weight loss.
Mom died from kidney failure caused...
by Type I Diabetes, which has been ruled out.
House: 17 doctors.
Everything's been ruled out.
Which means we have to re-rule out.
Get a new history and physical.
Unless that's crazy, boss.
Cameron: You been out of the country...
or on any recent camping trips?
No camping.
But we were in Montreal back in January.
We went to see the NHL All-Star
game for my birthday.
Awesome.
Where's Dr House?
In his office.
He's really more of a decider than a doer.
He's decided we should
start over.
Never know what previous doctors
may have missed.
Like this.
Does that hurt more when I push there?
Not really.
What is it?
I'm not sure.
Just keep it clean, simple.
We did a test that called into question...
our initial diagnosis, so we
changed our mind.
And if they ask how the test was done?
Why would they do that?
It's a routine lab test.
Routine lab tests don't involve blood you stole...
from a corpse to trick me...
into giving the guy the wrong treatment.
Yes, and if you brought that up...
it'd certainly make for a lively
debate about the morality...
of murdering murderers.
But since you burned the only
evidence of that...
To cover for you, not me.
You're protected.
The decision was a coin flip.
There was no right or wrong answer.
The body's underground,
8,000 miles away.
Nobody can prove anything.
That room will be filled, not
because of the coin flip,...
not because of the patient...
but because House's department screwed up.
They're gonna be like sharks in
a chum-filled swimming pool...
and there's no way I'm jumping in...
unless I'm in a steel cage.
So what do you want?
I want to know you have everything covered.
House: Got what covered?
We're just reviewing the Dibala’s case.
Making sure we didn't miss anything.
We didn't.
Except of course the thing that killed him.
Cameron: He's constipated.
Physical revealed a mass in his abdomen...
so, I repeated the x-ray.
Old one was clean.
New one shows that his colon's
almost completely impacted.
Obstruction would explain the pain.
Think they just screwed up
the old x-ray?
Nope.
Hirschsprung's?
It's a congenital disorder of the nerves
in the colon.
Very rare in a child your son's age.
Most doctors would never think of it.
And you came up with this?
It's House's idea.
We need a barium enema
and biopsy to confirm.
Let me guess.
It tastes really bad,...
but it's gonna make me feel
a lot better.
Actually, you're not gonna taste it.
[Fanfarlo's Fire Escape]
You should try searching for
‘Misty May digs for gold.’
Make sure you put it in quotes.
I'm making travel plans.
Just need to get away.
Have some time to myself.
You getting the hint?
So that's it?
You're done with your little
experiment with Foreman?
It wasn't an experiment.
It was a relationship.
You may want to look into the difference.
I'm glad you're better, House.
I actually liked working for you.
But, I'm not coming back.
Good.
'Cause if you came back...
Foreman would try and save the relationship...
and he'd give up being the boss.
Are you here to try to save my
relationship with Foreman?
God, no.
Trying to save my relationship
with Foreman.
Right now I'm Kobe playing the game I love
However the hell I want.
Phil Jackson has to listen to
everyone else bitch about it.
Enjoy Cabo.
I'm going to Thailand.
Really?
Interesting.
Good-bye, House.
Good-bye, Thirteen.
Cameron: Last week, yesterday, today.
I can't believe it.
He's pain-free for the first time in months.
He's even hungry.
I'm starving.
Still waiting for the biopsy results...
but obviously it's a good sign.
You're gonna want to take it slow.
Don't try to regain all the lost
weight in one meal.
[Chuckles]
What's wrong?
Abdomen feels normal, but it looks bigger.
Jack, are you feeling...
Jack?
Hey, Jack. You okay?
Right eye's fixed.
Lateral rectus palsy.
[Electronic beeping]
He's seizing.
Need five milligrams of diazepam.
What's happening?
Put that on his head and
turn off the lights.
I need to see his optic disc.
Heart rate's elevated. Come on,
come on, hold his head.
I'm trying. Wait! Where's House?
Mr Randall, we need you to step back.
Foreman: His optic disc is swollen.
He's got intracranial hypertension.
Furosemide, 20 milligrams IV.
We could intubate him...
Need five more milligrams of diazepam.
DC the monitors.
Push 500 milligrams phenytoin.
We can't push that much.
We got to remove the pressure
or his brain could herniate.
Oh, my god.
50 milligrams of phenytoin in.
Page Chase. Tell him to meet us in the OR.
We need your consent.
What's happening to him?
Pressure in his skull's too high.
If we don't reduce it...
it could irrevocably damage his brain.
But he was just talking.
He was smiling.
We need to drill burr holes.
Drill into his head?
Phenytoin's not working.
Paralyze him.
Three milligrams pancuronium.
Then intubate
and hyperventilate.
Where's house?
House isn't here.
Do we have your consent?
Ready?
One, two, three.
3 milligrams pancuronium.
Look at the monitors. He's still seizing.
We need to do this now.
Go.
Electrical seizure activity's stopped.
Intracranial pressure's declining.
Come on. Keep going.
Pressure's down to eight.
I'll tell the dad.
What happened?
I have no idea.
He hasn't had any more seizures,
And cytological examination of
the subdural fluid...
showed no abnormalities.
Don't usually see brain damage
after a rectal biopsy.
He was fine after the procedure.
No headaches. No mental status change.
Wasn't anything we did.
It's not just his brain.
He's continuing to build up fluid
in his abdominal cavity...
as well as the dura.
We've inserted shunts to drain it.
Got to be some sort of systemic infection.
Not after spending the last
week getting pumped...
full of IV antibiotics.
Notice anything odd about the shape
of the fluid collection?
Oh, god. It's...
The Virgin Mary.
The edge should be tapered...
lens shaped.
Unless...
The dural layer was already
separated from the brain...
when the fluid started to build up.
Get a dural biopsy to confirm
brain cancer.
Nice catch.
Bangkok. Flight 799.
Wow. Bangkok.
That sounds awesome.
How long?
Not sure yet.
Luckily, I have a friend
Who's staying at my place
taking care of my dog.
He's really big, so he needs
a lot of exercise.
Remy Hadley.
H-A-D-L-E-Y.
What, you think I'm gonna rob the place?
No, of course not.
In case you haven't noticed,
I have a job.
Look, I'm sorry. I don't know you.
You're either honest or dishonest.
I figured the safer choice is...
is to treat a stranger like an ass.
Nice way to live your life...
Bitch.
I said I'm sorry.
Oh, hello.
I was wondering if there were any
business class seats...
open that I could use my miles to upgrade to.
I don't know you, but I assumed
I could trust you.
Welcomed you in my car.
Okay, you're a saint.
That's impossible.
I confirmed my reservation last night.
So, rebook it.
Well, obviously it was a mistake
on your end, not mine.
No, I'm on my way to the airport...
right now.
They didn't believe you, huh?
Brain cancer?
We should know for sure by the morning.
[Sighs]
Our luck just keeps getting worse, huh?
Treatment options are getting better every day.
There's no visible mass,
so even if the biopsy...
comes back positive, we've caught it early.
Oh, so you're telling me
this is good news?
I'm saying we will do whatever we can.
Right.
[Pager beeps]
Sorry.
I got to go.
Foreman needs more help
with the M&M prep.
Okay, I'll come up and help
After I finish the biopsy.
We can handle it.
I'll see you at home later.
If you're here, I might as well be.
Go home. Get some rest.
'cause I'm gonna be waking you
up as soon as I get home.
Stay out of my life.
Okay.
I know you cancelled
my reservation.
You obviously saw me log-in...
when you were spying on me
in the coffee shop.
I was talking to you.
I was spying on the Milf
in the running shorts.
I'm not coming back on the team.
I don't want you back on the team.
I cannot work for, with,
or around Foreman.
Which is why I don't want you
back on the team.
Now that you're out of the picture...
He's better than ever, which is gonna make me...
less miserable than ever, which is
why neither of us...
gives a damn how, when,
or on what island...
in the Bahamas you want
to get from it all.
The Bahamas?
[Sighs]
Costa Rica?
I told you Thailand.
I assumed you were lying.
Because it would have been idiotic
of you to tell me truth.
Yet, another reason I have
no use for you.
Foreman: We've got a problem.
When Cameron sent Dibala's
blood to the lab...
she specifically asked for the anticentromere
antibodies test.
So?
The printout they sent you included...
just the anticentromere antibodies...
but the lab also did a full blood panel.
So, I'm not an idiot.
I obviously made sure the cadaver
I got the sample from...
had the same blood type.
You apparently didn't check his cholesterol.
How far off?
20%.
Chase:
Dibala didn't die of high cholesterol.
Why would anyone even bother
to compare the two reports?
The same reason I did.
Because they're looking for anything...
we might have screwed up.
We could claim the blood analyzer broke.
We can't.
Cameron documented that
it was perfectly calibrated...
when she did the test.
So the numbers are off, it's weird.
Who cares?
If it comes up, just act surprised...
like it's some irrelevant curiosity.
I can't do this.
I can't go in there and stack lie upon lie.
You've got to figure out
a way to explain this.
Hey.
- Hey.
Missed you this morning.
Yeah, sorry.
I needed to get in early.
I didn't want to wake you.
I thought you did want to wake me.
At least that's what
you said last night.
I'm out of here.
- No, no.
I have the biopsy results.
It's not cancer.
How can so much be wrong
with nothing being wrong?
Since when has cancer been
considered nothing?
I just said it's not cancer.
The cell morphologies were all normal.
And so are the most recent CT scans.
On the other hand, andenocarcinoma
of the stomach...
would cause pain, constipation...
nutritional deficiencies...
that could cause seizures.
And wouldn't show on a CT.
You're right about the cancer.
Just wrong about the place.
Continue to say nothing if you agree.
Go scope him.
Get another set of biopsies.
I'd get cancelling her ticket...
if you then showed up...
with two more to somewhere better.
What are you talking about?
Or showed up at all.
But how does just ruining her plans...
get her to agree to yours?
You talking about Thirteen?
Where's she going?
Well, nowhere this week, thanks to you.
I didn't stop her.
I'm not gonna stop her.
I've already done all I could.
Now, all I can do is move on.
I think...
I actually believe you.
If you're telling the truth...
you're even more rational than I...
well, not more.
Then again, more sane.
You're gonna be a good boss, boss.
Chase:
I told you there's nothing wrong.
There's obviously something wrong.
And, I'm not even saying we need
to talk about it right now.
I just don't see why
you have to deny it.
I'm not.
Now, you're denying you're denying.
No, I'm denying that there's
anything to deny.
Robert, you can't do this.
You can't hide things from me.
There's a problem with the Dibala M&M.
The HDL numbers on one of
his early blood panels...
don't match a later panel.
That's weird.
Yeah.
It's no big deal.
Cholesterol didn't have anything
to do with his death...
But, you know, after being
let go from Mercy...
and then that thing with
Thirteen's drug trial...
Foreman's paranoid about people
questioning the way...
he handled the case.
That's ridiculous.
If anything, Foreman should be feeling secure.
He's the one who had
the right diagnosis.
We're the ones who
talked him out of it.
I know.
Don't tell him I told you.
He doesn't want to show
any signs of weakness...
Especially now that House is claiming...
he wants him to stay in charge.
All right.
So it's still cancer?
It's just somewhere else?
That's what we're looking for...
but it would explain all the symptoms...
and all the normal test and imaging studies.
Chase:
Got biopsies of the mucosa and the submucosa.
Moving towards the pylorus.
It's my fault.
Adenocarcinomas aren't caused by diet...
or environmental factors.
I inherited a $10 million pipeline business...
when I was 24.
By the time I was 30, it was worth over a billion.
Since then, I have been involved...
in over 50 deals that make that first one...
look like a loser.
Everything I do, everything I touch...
turns to gold...
except my family.
First, my wife.
And now, my son.
This is my fault.
It's karma.
That's obviously not true.
[Electronic beeping]
He's seizing again. Get the scope out.
5 milligrams diazepam.
How's the ICP?
It's... eight.
But the shunt's open and clear.
This isn't intracranial pressure.
Then, what the hell is it?
Chase: Seizures stopped, but he hasn't
regained consciousness.
No sign of any masses...
in his stomach or oesophageal lining...
and he's still accumulating subdural
and peritoneal fluid.
And every time we look to see
where it's coming from...
He starts seizing.
You think we're setting this off?
I think something is.
One of his stomach biopsies shows an arteriole...
partially occluded.
Cameron: But with no abnormality
in the other layers...
and no evidence of a cellular
inflammatory reaction.
It's definitely not cancer.
Then it has to be some sort of infection.
We already ruled out infection.
Only because he was treated
for it and got worse.
Seems like a sound reason.
Unless it's a drug-resistant strain.
Drug-resistant strain of what?
Bacterial cultures...
viral serologies, ANA and ANCA...
were all negative.
Everything's negative.
We obviously missed something.
Maybe the seizures aren't a new symptom.
They're an old one.
No doctor noticed a thrashing kid?
Abdominal epilepsy.
The seizures would just look like pain...
until it spread to his motor cortex.
It wouldn't explain the fevers.
Protein malnutrition can cause fevers...
and nothing causes malnutrition...
like excruciating stomach pain
that gets worse...
every time you eat.
I'd be a lot more certain
if it was my idea...
but it's the best we got.
Start him on gabapentin.
Hook him up to an intracranial EEG...
for continuous monitoring.
I gave him statins.
What?
If they ask about the cholesterol...
Just say I prescribed a statin.
and forgot to put it in the chart.
You want to solve a problem in the records...
by creating another problem
in the records?
It's not a problem with the records.
It's a problem with my record keeping.
There's no way anyone
can prove me wrong.
How'd you get access to the statins?
You gonna get someone in the pharmacy...
to confess to yet another record-keeping problem?
I saw an open cart. Just took it.
Why would you steal a drug...
you could just as easily ask for?
'Cause I'm trying to get you off the hook.
A story that raises more questions
than it answers...
only puts the hook deeper
down my throat.
It's all right. I'll handle it.
How?
By telling the truth.
The truth is I don't have the time...
I'm not in the mood, and
I don't see the point.
You don't want to do the M&M...
because you're not in the mood?
This kid is dying and I've got House...
trying to push all his responsibilities
onto me.
They're not his responsibilities.
They're yours.
You're the one who wanted
to be in charge.
I wanted to be in charge...
Not a figurehead.
Then do the M&M.
It's all yours.
You want me to get flogged?
For what?
So, you can have an academic debate...
about a diagnostic dilemma no one's
ever gonna face again?
What the hell's going on here?
I just don't want to do the M&M.
Did it work?
- Not even close.
Everything okay?
Just waiting for whatever
is about to go wrong.
Thirteen called.
She have a theory that
makes more sense...
than abdominal epilepsy?
She said someone hacked
into her e-mail account...
and cancelled an airline reservation.
I'm guessing Foreman.
Really?
You're accusing Foreman, not me?
Cool.
You really want Foreman to
stay in charge of the team?
Makes sense.
He loves power, and I love puzzles.
You love power and puzzles.
True.
When I had them both.
It wasn't Foreman.
How do you know?
He said he's moved on.
And you believe him?
I believe that he believes it.
[Pager beeps]
Looks like it's time for me
to get off the bench.
What's up?
Are you Dr House?
I understand you're a big fan.
I'll have my guy send over
a signed glossy.
Continuous EEG shows no interictal spikes.
It's not abdominal epilepsy.
You paged me to tell me what it's not?
I paged you to show you this.
That I did not expect.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Darn it.
I knew I should have stayed outside.
Fantasy's always much better
than the reality.
You think this is a joke?
That's my son; he's dying...
and not one of you seem to have
the slightest clue why.
I know.
That's why it's so interesting.
Fever, stomach pain, seizures...
peritoneal and subdural fluid collection...
and now spots.
Could be an allergic reaction
to one of his meds.
That suddenly developed eight hours...
after he started the meds?
If it's not cancer infection,
it has to be autoimmune.
Systemic lupus complicated...
by a CNS vasculitis would explain
the rash, fever...
ascites...
CNS vasculitis would cause a stiff neck...
along with a headache.
And would've showed up on
the dural biopsy.
What about polyarteritis nodosa?
It can occur in kids.
Except you can't have arteritis
without inflammation.
Okay, you come up with
something better.
Go on.
There was some inflammation
in the skin biopsy...
plus he's got elevated
diastolic pressure.
It's barely elevated, which you'd expect...
given the number of procedures
he's undergone.
Well, barely is more
than not barely.
Not my decision.
But if it was, I'd say start
him on prednisone...
and get a testicular biopsy.
If he's gonna have any
real inflammation...
it'll be down there.
Cameron and I will do it.
- Why?
It was Chase's idea.
Kid's father is not gonna be happy...
about a fourth set of biopsies...
and you've got a better rapport.
What's really going on here?
You need Chase to help you
over-prep for the M&M?
Yes.
Then say so. Don't be a child.
Is it on his penis?
Kid's rash?
Yeah, why?
Means it's most likely affecting
the small blood vessels.
That's why we didn't see any
inflammation on the biopsies.
It's not polyarteritis.
It's Degos disease.
I'll do it.
Your son has Degos disease.
Causes microblood vessels...
in the brain, skin, GI tract...
to break down, clot off.
It sometimes manifests early on...
with atrophic papules on the penis.
In your son's case, we don't know why,...
but they came much later.
What's the treatment?
There isn't one.
It's incurable.
You're wrong.
You've already been wrong a bunch of times.
We've rechecked the biopsies.
It's definitely Degos.
I'm sorry.
I wish there was something we could do.
How long?
Not much longer.
What does that mean?
Day at the most.
All right, great.
We need to talk.
Unless it's life or death,
it's gonna have to wait.
It's about Dibala.
Well, let me rephrase.
Unless it's a current life...
Foreman can't present the
case at the M&M.
I know you guys are busy,
but he's just...
gonna have to suck it up
and make the time.
It's not the time.
Then what is it?
The anticentromere antibodies test.
The test that caused us
to change the treatment...
from blastomycosis to scleroderma...
It wasn't.
Wasn't what?
Diane: Dr Cuddy?
They need you in the pediatric ICU.
Who's they?
I don't know.
But, I think they're lawyers.
If you guys screwed something
up, just come clean.
It's not gonna be that bad.
Ken:
With all due respect...
you don't know what's at stake here.
What's going on?
You need to stop him!
He's about to ruin his life.
Like you give a damn about my life.
Roy, he's right.
You're borrowing money to buy options...
that are already out of the money.
Even you won't be able
to cover the losses.
Your house, cars, bank accounts.
You'll lose everything.
House: That's the point.
The billionaire thinks that the gods...
will treat him better if he's broke.
I suggested he give it to me.
Roy: There’s got to be some sort of balance.
You can't have all the good fortune...
in just one area of your life.
It's not how the world is supposed to look.
Who said the world is supposed to work?
Don't just wipe everything out.
Put your assets in a trust.
Give it to a charity.
I can't get anything back.
He's insane.
- He's irrational.
So are most people.
Unfortunately, it doesn't
make him insane.
If he signs that paper...
He's not only gonna destroy
his own life,...
but the lives of thousands
of people who rely...
on this company to make a living.
If he is insane, we will sue this hospital...
Cuddy: Mr Randall.
I know you're upset.
You shouldn't make a decision
like this right now.
Give it some time.
My son doesn't have any time.
Your son's dying from an incurable disease...
not bad karma.
No.
He's not dying.
It's not gonna happen.
I'm not gonna let it.
Roy, please!
Roy: I'm sorry.
I can't let him die.
People don't get what they deserve.
They just get what they get.
There's nothing any of us
can do about it.
Deliver it or I'll make sure...
you end up the ones with nothing.
[ECG warning tone]
Call a code. He's flatlining.
Hadley: Thanks.
You're welcome.
For what?
For thinking I was worth...
breaking the law to keep around.
That's just the way I am...
but still don't know what
you're talking about.
Cuddy had IT trace all the IP addresses...
who've logged in to my email account.
There were two.
Mine and yours.
Obviously, House decided he needs
you more than he's...
I already asked House.
And he'd certainly never lie.
No, he'd lie.
Except he wants me gone.
And, he'd do a lot better job
of lying than you just did.
Really? It was that bad?
No, actually.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
Why?
Because of House or Foreman?
You're good for both of them...
but Foreman's not my best friend.
House will be fine.
Maybe.
But with you on the team, he'd be better.
He needs someone...
Who doesn't need him.
You're the only one...
he's never really been able to suck...
into his crazy House vortex.
Keeps him grounded.
His ego in check.
Why didn't you just
come to me?
I figured you'd only stay
if House asked
And I knew he would eventually.
Bye, Wilson.
This is a great job.
Maybe even better now that
House is at least trying...
to have real relationships with people.
I said, "trying."
It doesn't matter.
The job you love doesn't matter?
Don't throw it all away...
just because of a bad break-up.
Bye, Wilson.
[Sighs]
I just confessed.
I told Thirteen I was the one who
cancelled the plane ticket.
Why?
You mean why did I confess,
or why did I do it?
I know you didn't do it.
So, I guess the first.
You want her to stay because
you want her back...
or because Foreman does?
Why would I care what Foreman wants?
Because you're not as big
a jerk as everyone thinks.
Yes, I am.
No, you're not.
I just made a $10,000 short sale on a stock...
I know is gonna crash because of what I saw...
a grief-stricken dad do on
his son's deathbed.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
You are a jerk.
She's making a mistake.
So, you did it for her?
She's a good doctor.
So you did it for you?
I'm not the one in charge anymore.
So you did it for Foreman?
She's a smoking hot, newly single bisexual.
Why don't you just admit that
you like having her around?
She's good for you. You need her.
Because I was born with a heart
three sizes too small.
No, you weren't.
Yes, I...
What?
He's still alive?
Foreman: Yeah.
- Good.
Start him on heparin and IV immunoglobulin.
For Degos?
The cardiac arrest wasn't just a...
‘everything goes to hell in a handbasket’ arrest.
It was a coronary event.
Coronaries are large vessels.
Mean's it can't be Degos.
But the biopsies confirmed...
obstructed blood vessels.
But, they can't be obstructed
because of Degos.
Means it's primary antiphospholipid syndrome.
You sure?
Nope.
But I will be if he responds
to the heparin...
and the immunoglobulin.
By the way,...
someone screwed over
your girlfriend...
and she ran to me, Cuddy and Wilson.
Everyone but you.
She's not over you.
Or she is.
Where'd you find it?
Find what?
Niacin-bound chromium supplements.
It was right on top of the file.
You don't know about it?
No. Been here all night.
One of Dibala's previous docs was prescribing...
ultra-high doses of niacin bound
chromium to boost his HDL.
So?
So, it gives us something to point to.
We can explain the wide variation...
between the HDL numbers.
We're safe.
We're covered.
You really didn't request the info?
No.
And obviously you didn't either.
Which means...
It worked.
The medicine worked.
[Chuckles]
How'd you find it?
Fat old black guy.
Knew he had to be taking something
for his cholesterol.
And, what now?
I'm not the boss.
You don't think I should be fired?
Why?
I doubt we'll ever be treating
a genocidal dictator again.
Better a murder than a misdiagnosis.
Whether you want to be
in charge or not...
you are and you always will be.
[Ray LaMontagne's Sarah]
[Alarm buzzes]
Foreman: 75-year-old African man...
presented to our hospital following...
a rapid onset of hemoptysis.
He'd been fine prior to onset.
No chest pain, fever, coughing, or chills...
# When we first met #
# We were kids #
# We were wild #
# We were restless #
# After a while #
# I grew coarse #
# I grew cold #
# I grew reckless #
# I hold this memory #
# Hold you so close to me #
# whispered we'll be always happy #
# Now I see #
# Just how young #
# How scared I was #
# Eyes closed tight #
# Throwing punch after punch at the world #
# Sarah #
# Is it ever gonna be the same #
# Is it ever gonna be the same... #