This bagel's as hard
as a hockey puck.
Then don't eat it.
Used to be a full
breakfast service.
They're trying
to starve us.
You're worried
about the food?
No, I'm worried about
what the food represents.
I got seven scenes
to shoot today
on half of what
we used to spend.
We're going
through a recession.
It is what it is.
But nobody's
gonna bail us out.
Free content everywhere,
DVD sales in the toilet.
Now the back office
bean counters
are vetoing
half my ideas.
So we begin to make it
about the performances.
You okay?
A bit of a headache.
If you need
an ibuprofen--
I need you to put your
game face on, all right?
Screw the bagels, screw
the sets, screw the wardrobe.
Do you have any idea
how lucky we are?
We get to do
something we like,
we get to touch people's lives
and we get paid for it?
Let's make a movie!
Hey, baby.
Roll camera!
And...
Action.
Argh...
What's wrong?
Ah...
My eyes...
They feel like
they're exploding.
All right, turn off
the damn lights.
Get an ambulance.
Now!
Synced and edited by Kratingdaeng
Transcript from Addic7ed.com
We're gonna be
late for work.
Then we'll be late.
You took a patient's life.
You lied about it for weeks.
You broke who knows
how many laws and oaths
to cover it up,
but I can live with it.
We can get through it
together.
You have no idea what
I've been living with,
and what it means
to hear you say that.
But we need to get away
from Princeton-Plainsboro.
You can barely walk by the rooms
where Dibala was treated.
Why should we live with that
hanging over our heads?
If there was ever a time
to turn the page...
Three-month-old with fever,
incessant drooling,
and chronic
muscle weakness.
Or...
Porn actor Hank Hardwick,
born Henry Lefkowitz,
totally clean workup,
collapsed on the job
with extreme photophobia.
Or...
An infant as limp
as a rag doll.
Yeah. Let's wait till
Chase and Cameron get here.
I have a feeling they'll have
the good sense to side with me.
Doesn't matter
who they side with,
I'm still in charge.
We're taking the limp
three-month-old.
Oh, good!
You paged the limpness
specialist.
This envelope is oddly
medical license-shaped.
Congratulations.
House is back
in charge.
We get to treat
a porn star.
Congratulations.
Perfect timing for us.
We're leaving the team
and the hospital,
effective immediately.
That's kind of sudden.
Unless you've been circulating
your resumes for a while.
We're just starting
to think about new jobs,
where we want to live.
Moving too...
Interesting.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
Uh...
We'll miss you.
We'll miss
all of you too.
We'll start clearing
out our things.
Run an S.T.D. panel
and a tox screen.
Send a C-reactive protein
to look for inflammation
and an A.N.A. to screen
for autoimmune.
The rest of you
take a history
and do an L.P to rule out
viral encephalitis.
Oh, it's just you!
Here's hoping you're
good at multitasking.
I get tested for S.T.D.s regularly,
so does everyone I work with.
Since I'm guessing you don't
take their word for it.
All right, I'm gonna need you to
lie on your side
and put your knees
to your chest.
Any history of alcohol
or substance abuse?
My wife used to
smoke a little pot,
but I never
touched the stuff.
You're married.
Happily,
for two years now.
Is she happy you do porn?
Very, since she
does it too.
Hmm.
You ever get jealous
when your wife's working?
It's a job.
Once you start
letting your work life
rule your home life,
especially if you're
in the same line of work,
your relationship's
gonna be short.
You're gonna feel
a little pressure.
Any history
of sexual abuse?
I defy the cliche.
Have you ever suffered
depression or psychosis?
Let me save you
some time.
There's not a blotch
on my medical record.
Look...
I know most of
the people in my field
are drug addicts
with daddy issues,
but I'm a nice,
Jewish boy from the 'burbs.
I wasn't driven to this.
I chose it.
I believe in it.
I actually
think it's--oh!
My arms are killing me!
Looks like tetany.
Your muscles are contracting.
Need some
meperidine in here.
Oh, god!
Jew with megalophallus,
photophobia, and muscle spasm.
You tell me which
is the most unusual.
Four candidates,
three slots on the team.
Need to know if you've still
got your diagnostic chops.
I leave this office
by 6:00 every day,
I have my weekends again,
I recognize
my wife again.
Yeah, I agree.
Does sound pretty dull.
No wonder you want
to work for me.
Tox screen was clean.
We ruled out
viral encephalitis.
The only obstacle to you
coming back is your wife.
Which has never been that much
of an obstacle to you.
Maybe you're right.
The only link between eye
and muscle is the brain.
Tumor, seizure...
Taub seems to think
the link has to be the brain,
but eye and muscle are
governed by different parts
of the patient's
second-favorite organ.
Which means it's...
Thailand was wonderful.
Thanks for asking.
Of course! Yes!
It has to be multifocal.
I have an interview
with a community health clinic
in two hours.
Back-up plan's fine.
Taub's swinging
for the fences.
I suggest you don't
divide your attention.
Good point.
I won't divide
my attention, then.
Taub thinks it's
a brain issue,
Thirteen thinks
it's multifocal.
And neither of them
wants to work here.
Don't take
their word for it.
Taub's problem is his wife,
Thirteen's problem is you.
Chase and Cameron's problem
is the dead African dictator.
None of them has
a problem with the work.
Cerebral vasculitis
would explain
both the eye
and arm findings.
Steroids to treat,
brain angiogram to confirm,
E.M.G. and nerve biopsy
while you're at it.
I'll be at lunch.
I'd hire all four,
but a five-person team
seems unwieldy.
Who would you turn down?
I'll have whatever
he's buying.
Two cheeseburgers
and two large fries.
There are a thousand people
in the world
who want to be
on your staff,
but you're going after
the four who don't.
They don't because
their lives
are irrelevantly
and annoyingly complicated,
which makes
them confused,
which makes them
make poor decisions.
And your life is simple?
You went all the way up
to the medical conference
to cozy up to Cuddy.
Instead she's dating
one of two people in the world
you think of as a friend.
There's no way that's
not devastating.
So I had an
attraction of sorts.
Yeah, the sort in which
your imaginary tryst
landed you
in a mental hospital.
And I got help.
And she got Lucas,
who bought me a ginger ale.
It's all fine.
Which won't be true
of my department
unless I can figure out
which doctor I'm not hiring.
I suppose throwing
yourself into your work
isn't the worst thing
you could do.
What is the worst thing
I could do?
House thinks it's
cerebral vasculitis.
If you could just
do the brain angio
while I finish up
the blood work--
we're out the door.
He's got me running every test
and treatment by myself.
Which is why you should
be out the door too.
This is completely unreasonable,
even for House.
You owe me this.
Thank you.
You really believe this is
cerebral vasculitis?
Could be.
House wants to thread
a catheter through his brain,
which could cause
a vasospasm,
give steroids,
which could spread infection
all over the place,
because it could be.
Sounds like House.
It could also be a severe
Vitamin D deficiency.
He eats a restricted diet,
works long hours indoors,
became hypocalcemic,
got tetany and photophobia.
Are you saying
I shouldn't do the angio?
House ordered it,
Foreman wants it,
of course
we should do it.
I'm just saying
we're right to leave.
You sure?
Because right now I'll basically
do anything you ask me.
I'm not interested
in guilting you.
We're moving on.
Right after I take the patient
to the phototherapy suite,
blast him
in ultraviolet light,
and IV vitamins for his
severe Vitamin D deficiency.
So do you guys
actually work together?
We did at first,
but now we like to keep
our films produced separate.
So do you, uh,
watch her work?
We're both busy
with our own stuff.
Think what you want,
but we're proud
of what we do.
Divorcing sex from
all emotional content?
Emotion is emotional.
Sex is mechanical.
There doesn't really
need to be any overlap.
Certainly not
in your world.
We've helped
a lot of couples
by taking sex out
of some deep, dark dungeon.
Do what you want
without some big,
moral comeuppance.
You think you can escape
the consequences, but you can't.
You don't get to make
your own rules or morals.
Well, you're here to treat him,
not lecture us about our...
Hank!
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Just a nosebleed.
Inside his leg?
Petechial hemorrhages.
We were wrong.
So was Foreman.
Patient's blood
won't clot.
We're back to square one.
And you're back
in my office.
So much for playing
hard to get.
We're just here
to help Foreman.
Is that--
He's not without talent.
U.V. rays made the patient's
capillaries more fragile,
hastening
the onset of D.I.C.
Sounds like sepsis--
but isn't.
No sign of shock.
No drop in
blood pressure.
Can we turn that off?
Right, 'cause Cameron
thinks pornography is evil.
I don't care what he does.
I don't care what you watch.
I just think it's annoying
that he pretends
it's some beautiful life
we should all be aspiring to.
Left shift points
to bacteremia.
No fever.
Plus it wouldn't explain his
spasmodic muscle contractions.
The ball and chain
smacked you down.
But, widespread
petechial rash,
nervous system
involvement.
It's... some kind
of blood infection.
Meningococcemia.
Start the patient
on Heparin for the D.I.C.
Broad-spectrum antibiotics
for the meningococcemia.
Dr. Cameron.
Chase is relaxed, at ease,
in lockstep with you again.
I guess he finally told you
that he "iced" Idi Amin Jr.
Does that mean
he can break
the other nine
commandments too?
Taking the lord's
name in vain, sure,
but coveting
thy neighbor's wife?
Is she hot?
I've forgiven him.
Not for murder.
Not you.
Doesn't matter
how evil Dibala was.
By every
conscience-hugging,
Mother Teresa-loving
bone in your body,
you should be leaving him,
not leaving with him.
I thought your position
was our leaving is a ruse.
We're not talking
about my position.
We're talking about yours,
which doesn't add up.
Here's what
doesn't add up.
If you were serious
about staffing your team,
you would know exactly
which three fellows you wanted.
You plowed ahead
with this case,
even though you hadn't
hired new fellows
because you knew Foreman
would ask Chase and me to help.
Giving you more time
to blow up our marriage.
I don't want that.
But we'd be foolish
not to plan ahead.
A: My firing Chase was the only
reason you left two years ago,
B: When the full horror
of his homicide hits you,
your marriage
will blow up.
And Z...
The only obstacle to you
working here will be gone.
Or maybe I skipped
a couple of letters.
Meningococcemia's
spread person-to-person.
Something you
ought to think about
next time you
show up for work.
It's okay.
Your wife's not here.
I'm just
telling you what--
you have to lecture me
when she's around, I get it.
But I can tell from all
the questions you ask
that you're more like me
than you admit.
I'm a guy.
I look around every once
in a while, but I love my wife.
I love the fact
that she's the only one
that I'm intimate with.
And no part of you
wants to just
toss this rule book
everyone's forced on you?
No part of you wants a life
of actual commitment?
Is my relationship
perfect? No.
Am I ever horny when my wife
has just had sex for nine hours?
Yes.
But we are committed
to each other,
in every way
that matters.
In other words
you're committed,
except when you're
not committed.
Doesn't work so well
if you have a conscience.
Conscience.
You mean that thing
that kicks in
when there's no logical
reason to behave
the way people
want you to?
What?
You have a fever.
Means the antibiotics
aren't working.
Mr. Takayama.
Yes!
I'm really happy with what
the last guy did with my eyes.
But why would
broad-spectrum antibiotics
fail to work on
meningococcemia?
If you'll excuse me,
I've got a real patient.
Mister...
Hitler.
Really.
Had to do something to amuse
myself while your receptionist
fought with
her boyfriend.
Who's next?
A guy who needs
two decades' worth of corn chips
hoovered out of his neck,
or a guy who can't
stand daylight,
and whose blood
won't clot.
You do the triage.
Who's the jerk?
Someone with zero chance
of hiring me back.
I told you.
I'm content at home
and at work.
But you're not
content with content.
That's why you got sucked
into those stock scams,
why you cheated
on the wife you love.
At bridge.
My wife and I play
a lot of bridge.
Why you worked on a case
last time I was here.
I gave you a theory.
Just like I'd help
a guy who needs
a Heimlich
in a restaurant.
And then I shut
the door behind you.
But you'd knock over three other
doctors to give it to him.
Metaphorically speaking,
you're a Heimlich addict.
And you're an
addiction addict.
Right now your drug
of choice is your old team,
and like any addict
you're trying to solve
some other problem
and it's not gonna work.
If you'll excuse me,
I have a--
you have a tight schedule
of nose jobs and tummy tucks.
Yes. I do nose jobs.
Just like the guy who
came here after a car crash,
couldn't even
breathe... through... his...
Antibiotics wouldn't
work if his sinuses
were infected
and clogged
if there was
a pocket of bacteria
his blood vessels
couldn't reach.
You surgically drain his
sinuses, the drugs will work.
Nice.
Tell me that
didn't feel good.
See you tomorrow!
Not coming back.
Looks like quite a trip.
It was.
House send you
to talk to me?
No.
Then there's nothing
to talk about.
I don't want
to work for him.
You're a great doctor.
House is right
to want you in the mix.
Are you saying this because
you still have feelings for me
and you want me
to come back?
I'm saying that
shouldn't be an issue.
Do you have feelings
for me or not?
I don't want our work life
to have anything to do
with our personal life.
You couldn't
keep them separate.
And that's why
our personal life doesn't exist.
None of that has to--
I can't work with you.
Actually, you can.
I was the one
who had the problem.
I don't anymore.
I owe you an apology.
I was wr-rr-r...
I was wrr-r-rr...
What were you
wrong about?
You spent weeks elaborately
concealing the fact that you...
Crashed daddy's car.
and then you
just confessed.
seemed idiotic.
Certain to end in disaster.
instead you're riding off
into the sunset together.
Any theories on why?
I assume you've already
dismissed the
"she loves me" theory?
Well, it's possible.
It would require
the presupposition
that everything she's done
for the last six years
has been completely inconsistent
with her character,
but yeah, it's possible.
And as we've
already established,
it's also possible
that you're wrong.
Or there's
another explanation.
Since you don't have one,
I'm gonna keep looking for you.
Let him drain, then pack it with
anesthetics and sterile gauze.
Do you have any idea
what's going on with House?
Uh, he's trying to get
his old fellas back?
It's called stalking.
I am way too busy to play
officer of the court.
That's a shame, since you're
the one who triggered this.
What do you see
in Lucas anyway?
I don't see that it's
any of your business.
Did you think House
wouldn't find out?
You could've at least told me
so I wouldn't have coached him
on how to prove
his worthiness to you.
I know you're
upset with me
because I didn't choose
to date your best friend.
But I'm living my life.
And for the first time
I'm not gonna change that
because of how it might
affect him or you.
I feel like crap.
Yeah, look, our relationship
is gonna be about House,
or it's gonna
be about us.
I vote for it
being about us.
Well, House is gonna
make it about him for us.
This is very insulting.
You're apparently
shocked by this,
which means that you
thought that there
was some way
that we could date,
get married,
have two kids, a dog,
retire to Florida,
all without House finding out.
Or... you thought that
we wouldn't date all that long.
First means
you're delusional.
The second means
I'm delusional.
Technically
it could also mean
you thought House
had matured,
but then we're back
to your being--
Shut up.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I'm also flattered.
Yeah, 'cause you acted all cool
and everything with Wilson,
but you feel comfortable enough
with me that you can freak out.
That's cool.
His sinuses are clear.
Antibiotics should
work this time.
Why did you forgive me?
I mean, I'm--I'm glad.
I'm grateful, but I'm confused.
You've been harder
on the patient
than you've been on me.
Well, the difference
between you and the patient
is that you feel shame.
Guilt.
That's how I know
we're gonna get through this.
Oh... my stomach.
Oh... it really hurts.
His liver is failing.
His liver's failing
and his abdomen
keeps filling
with fluid, so--
it's not meningococcemia.
No matter how much you finish
each other's sentences,
don't count on being
a diagnostic package deal.
Patient's liver's
not working.
We don't have time
for your little team-stakes.
Sometimes you're
just wr-rr-r-wrong.
Something genetic,
Something in his
family history we overlooked?
History and genetics
are spotless.
Plus every time he had
a bad cough as a kid
he went to a doctor.
Klatskin tumor obstructing
his bile ducts?
No jaundice.
Wouldn't have ocular effects.
but if it's inflammation
inside the bile channels,
sclerosing cholangitis.
could've stopped
him from producing
clotting proteins,
damaged his blood cells,
causing small strokes.
Enough!
Stop pummeling
Thirteen and Taub.
It fits.
Prep the patient
for an E.R.C.P.
See if there's any hope
of opening
his blocked
bile channels.
And tell him to start looking
for a liver donor.
Dr. Chase.
Your turn.
So what'd she say?
She forgave me
because... I feel guilty.
That works too.
And now you expect me to ask you
what the "too" refers to.
Only if you're
interested.
Only if you have doubts
about her answer.
She thinks that you don't have
anything to feel guilty about,
because you didn't
kill anybody.
I did.
She blames me
for Dibala's murder, not you.
You were barely involved
in that case. She knows that.
Yeah but I created
the big, bad, evil climate
that allowed it to happen.
You're wrong.
Powerful
counter-argument.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you trying
to screw things up?
You got the tense wrong.
Things are already
screwed up.
Which is why you don't just
want to work for me,
you need to.
Cameron thinks you're
my personal sock puppet.
If you don't stay, it's gonna be
hard to prove you're not.
I have to go.
Last week, my cane could
only do ten minutes.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you to take a nap
so I can surge into the lead.
What's the best way
to restore the liver in someone
with sclerosing
cholangitis?
Not getting
drawn into this.
You already are.
Because you crashed
my workout?
You're doing
core training.
Which improves balance,
which staves off
the most debilitating
symptoms of Huntington's.
You've ended your
self-destructive streak.
Want to do
something significant,
something that'll
last longer
than the few years
you have left.
My team is your
first-best choice.
And my first choice is
the community health clinic
I interviewed
with yesterday.
Absolutely,
you should do that.
three hours a week.
Every doctor should.
'cause every doctor can.
But you don't want
to be every doctor.
Plus, on my team,
you get to screw
with Foreman.
Every way but literally.
Why are you
doing it this way?
You're pretending to assume
we're all coming back
without actually
asking us.
Why?
See, this is why
you'd be miserable
wiping noses in a clinic.
You can't ask because
you can't face the rejection.
Why not?
What's going on?
Are you asking me
to ask you?
I'm saying you shouldn't,
for your sake as well as mine.
We don't know how much
the sclerosing cholangitis
has damaged your liver.
It might be in a year,
it might be in ten.
But the odds are you're
gonna need a new one.
And you should know,
while no transplant committee
will say this openly,
they'll never
grant an organ
to someone working
in your profession.
You're saying
I have to change jobs?
You're medically
advising me to change jobs.
Hank, if you're
too sick--
she wants me to have some kind
of religious conversion.
She's practically
salivating over it.
I'm just being
candid about--
so you don't
think I'm scum.
Just some committee
thinks I'm scum.
That your
lifestyle has risks.
You work around more sick people
and germs and blood than I do.
I'm not gonna live
my life afraid
like my parents did.
Barely letting me
play outside
and god forbid
that I get a scratch.
I'll talk to him.
He'll calm down and realize
that this is the only--
No.
No, I won't.
Why does everyone want to
dictate the way I live my life?
Because the way we're living
is gonna kill you.
passing
the pancreatic duct...
Don't listen to House.
You have no idea
what he said.
I know that House
is manipulative.
I know that you're in
a vulnerable state right now,
and I know that Cameron
wants your marriage to work.
So do you.
So don't listen to House.
House doesn't
make my decisions.
We're in the
common bile duct.
What's that mass?
Gallstone?
Can we magnify
times five?
That's not a Gallstone.
His liver's completely
filled with worms.
You have strongyloides,
also known as threadworms.
They disseminated
all over your body,
causing all
your symptoms.
How'd I get a parasite?
Most likely through sexual
activity, but we can't be sure.
And what's the treatment?
Two mebendazole pills.
That's it?
You'll be fine.
Your liver too.
Go back to your lives.
You know this is
the doctor's lounge.
I know.
It seemed like the place
to read doctors' notes.
You are good at it,
by the way.
Why are you
reading my charts?
Because I'm worried
about my girlfriend.
Your girlfriend...
Is a male porn star?
Oh, no, I'm dating
Lisa Cuddy.
Seriously?
Cool, huh?
And if House doesn't
have his team,
that'll make her miserable,
which will make me miserable.
Which brings us
to the fact that
you have elevated noting
to an art form.
I see the connection.
Most doctors
write "9:00 a.m."
if they scrub in at 9:00
or anything near it.
You write 9:03,
and you make little notations
when procedures are delayed.
You're easily impressed.
Well, yeah.
I was, till I saw that you had
virtually stopped writing them
about four weeks ago.
Been busy.
Got a backlog.
Yeah...
People with
your level of precision
don't really just
"get" backlogs.
No one knows why
you're leaving P.P.T.H.
Because it's personal.
Well, if something
happened,
I mean,
if you're leaving
to get away from
something that you did,
or she did,
or both of you did.
I mean, emotionally maybe
you want to run away,
but in my experience,
if you're staring at a pit bull
in some guy's back yard,
you're better off
staying right where you are.
Face the problem.
That way it can't
bite you in the ass.
Thanks for
the folksy wisdom.
Hey, you got any, uh, dirt
on any of the other three?
It'd really help me out.
I thought you said those
two pills was all he needed!
Lungs are filling
with fluid.
Suction him
and get him on oxygen.
Patient's lungs are
severely compromised.
Liver's still failing.
Worms could easily
have been a coincidence.
Almost be surprising
if he didn't have 'em.
Which means it could be
a hematological problem
plus cardiomyopathy.
No, neck veins are flat,
precordial exam was normal.
What if it's lymphoma?
Peritoneal carcinomatosis
explains the liver failure.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
explains everything else.
Lymphoma it is.
Prep him for chemo.
Fax Taub and Thirteen
the latest update on the case.
Seriously?
They have as much right
to know as anyone on the team.
You either like
the diagnosis or you don't.
If you don't,
we need to keep talking.
If you do,
you need to shut up.
What we don't need
is this stupid game.
You're mad at House,
but you're not mad at me.
Do you want me
to be mad at you?
You blame House.
Not me.
I am mad at House
because he's an ass.
And I am mad at you,
but I don't want to leave you.
What I did may be
the worst thing I ever did.
It may be the best.
I'm either a murderer or a guy
who stopped a mass murderer,
but I did it. Me.
And even if it destroys me,
I'd do it again today.
You don't mean that.
This isn't you.
I'm not running away
from what I did
because you want to
pretend I never did it.
If that's how you feel...
Okay.
My strategy's not
completely working.
All four of them want
to work for me,
but all four of them
have reasons
why they don't
want to work for me.
How do I get them
to take one from Column A
and none from Column B?
Right.
Right, by not
saying anything,
you're saying that
the answer is inside me.
The answer has nothing
to do with the question.
Then it's not
technically the answer.
Why do you need
three of these doctors?
Because I know
they're good.
Other doctors fall into
the "might be good" category.
It has nothing to do
with them being good.
You think they're
idiots half the time,
but they're comfortable.
You feel
abandoned by Cuddy,
so you're reaching out
to people you know for comfort.
Oh, my god, you're right.
I don't need
doctors at all.
I just need
a good friend.
Cuddy's right.
Maybe, just maybe,
if I don't play along,
you'll realize
you can't solve a deeper problem
with a surface solution.
Would've been more profound
if you hadn't said anything.
You okay?
Getting through it.
Be a lot easier once
you two are away from here.
Yeah.
He's peeing blood.
BP's rising.
Heart rate's up to 250.
He's going into
cardiac arrest.
Charging.
Clear.
He's bleeding out.
His body's
completely giving out.
Charging. Clear.
We've got him
stabilized,
but no red cells,
no white cells,
practically
no platelets either.
Mebendazole can cause adverse
effects, but nothing like this.
He's been off 'em
since yesterday, anyway.
Long passes,
wild guesses, anything.
Hypopituitarism.
Could cause multi-organ
failure if--
if his thyroid hormone
wasn't completely normal.
Renal cell carcinoma.
Renal ultrasound
was clean.
I'd say
aleukemic leukemia.
Marrow's not making
enough normal cells--
Ablate the patient's
bone marrow.
Find him a donor match.
You want to nuke
the patient's marrow?
He had no evidence
of being anemic
or immune-compromised
when he was admitted.
Perfect white count
as well.
Ablation could
kill him
or leave him defenseless
against an infection that could.
Well, then come up
with something better.
He may as well die
while we're treating him.
Okay with you if I bring
the other candidates
into the loop now?
The risks are, uh,
they're really minimal.
We'll do a series
of painless injections, and--
Excuse me.
The whole thing can be
done as an outpatient.
You're leaving
at 11:00 a.m.?
Trust me,
case is almost over.
Foreman told me you're
ablating the patient's marrow,
on a non-theory that
Foreman himself withdrew.
You're gonna
kill the patient.
Is this about
me and Lucas?
I want alternatives
for the patient.
So do I.
I want to be on the team.
You think that's gonna
save your marriage?
I don't know.
Four candidates,
three spots.
I got a tough decision
ahead of me.
Hi, Remy,
this is Dr. Turner
from the Pennsauken
Free Clinic.
We all loved meeting you,
and, well, the job's yours.
Call me back.
Let's pick a start date.
I want it
to look natural.
I mean, much younger,
but natural.
Can you get rid of
the crow's feet altogether?
Or is it better
to leave a trace of them?
I don't look old enough
to have them anyway, do I?
Absolutely.
I do look old enough?
No. What?
I'm sorry.
Hang on a second.
Why are you here?
'cause I think
we're wrong.
Which means something's
gonna go wrong.
Or right.
Takayama here.
It's me and Thirteen.
Stop the ablation.
Because?
Those threadworms.
Why would his body
have gone to hell
just hours after
they were gone?
The worms weren't
hurting him.
They were helping him.
He has extraintestinal crohn's.
He got it from being
raised in a too clean,
too overprotective
of an environment.
It's the hygiene
hypothesis.
Why there's so much autoimmune
disease in the developed world,
and almost none
in the developing world.
The worms were keeping
the crohn's in check,
teaching his
immune system
what it should've learned
from eating dirt growing up.
Once you killed them,
it started killing him.
So his life of filth
wasn't the problem.
Clean living was.
Let's start him
on methylprednisolone.
And some helminths.
Worms.
Cool, huh?
Best out of three?
Have you been a bad boy?
I want to be on the team.
Good news for your wife.
Thanks for the sarcasm.
I reorganized my life
to spend more time with her,
but apparently I don't love her
as much as I thought.
Or you love her more.
This job gives you
the thrill
you used to find
through philandering.
Better to cheat
with a beaker and an M.R.I.
than one of your platinum-blonde
plastic surgery patients.
I'll let you know.
I told House I want
to work for him again.
Stay on the team.
You were always more
into it than I was,
more interested
in diagnostics.
Unless House was right
about why you want out.
Four for four.
I was in love with you.
I was an idiot.
Tried to be like you,
tried to understand you
because I thought
I could heal you.
You almost killed
that patient.
If almost not saving
his life means--
you knew the diagnosis
a long time ago.
You risked another patient's
life to bait your old team.
Another one?
You did kill Dibala.
By playing god and
teaching us to do the same.
I taught you to think
for yourselves.
You don't even think
of them as people.
They're just lab rats
for your little puzzles.
As you celebrate
their humanity,
I'd rather solve those little
puzzles and save their lives.
Motives do matter.
Lives can't come second.
The patient is alive.
That's what matters.
Not to you.
All you care about is that Taub
and Thirteen fell for your game.
You'll poison them
just like you poisoned Chase.
Your husband killed a patient
and you're breaking up with me.
You ruined him.
So he can't even
see right from wrong.
Can't even see the sanctity
of a human life anymore.
I loved you.
And I loved Chase.
I'm sorry for you both.
For what you've become.
Because...
There's no way back
for either of you.
Any idea
where I can get
a great, big
"Mission Accomplished" banner?
Got my sanity back,
my license back,
and now...
You're kidding.
All of them?
Three out of four.
Which is almost as good
as four out of five.
Who was the--
Cameron.
Wow.
I can't believe it.
I mean, really.
I can't...
Believe it.
You were right, House.
Good for you.
Yeah, it is.
She's broken up with Chase,
and she's leaving the hospital.
Still, three out
of four ain't bad.
Synced and edited by Kratingdaeng
Transcript from Addic7ed.com
# His solitary fate #
# Stop the drink
Come wrinkled chin #
# Ordinary sins #
# Think you must have
heard him wrong #
# 'Cause he wasn't
gone that long #
# Who's somebody? #
# Who's someone? #
# Where did you go? #
# Ooh #
# I don't want to know #
# Where did you go? #
# Ooh #
# I don't want to know #
# Where did you go? #