I guess
everybody else is dead.
Which means we're
totally outnumbered.
We gotta make up for
that in pure firepower.
You want to raid the
feeding area, don't you?
Two boxes of
grenades in there.
It's our only chance
at getting out.
Vince, that place
is a deathtrap.
Lucky for you I've
got the megablaster.
Lee, you go right, Roy,
straight down the middle.
I'll cover you both.
One, two, three.
Where's that
cover fire?
Megablaster, dude,
megablaster!
What the hell?
Got it.
Vince, where are you?
I can't
get them off of me.
Vince, you d-bag,
where are you?
Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it, Vince.
That blood look
funny to you?
Still working on it.
The code's a little janky.
Hey, boss, you just like watching
us get our asses shredded?
Yeah, not that
you're not hilarious,
but we hit the shelves
in three months.
Vince?
Vince, what's wrong?
My hands,
they're on fire.
Your NCV test was normal.
Rules out carpal tunnel.
No evidence of trauma,
your blood work looks normal.
Then what is it?
I don't know.
I'll arrange to have you
transferred to a neurologist.
A neurologist? Don't you have
some famous diagnostics guy?
What's he doing?
I quit.
You can't quit.
I think you're confusing me
with Jake Gyllenhaal.
House, are you okay?
Yeah. And I want
to stay that way.
I talked it over
with my therapist.
I need to change my
environment, my habits.
But he cleared you to
get your license back.
Which will help immensely
with my new job in research.
I've sent out some resumes. Research
means no patients, less pressure.
But you just got out, have you had
enough time to think this through?
I'm sorry.
I know this will
affect both of you,
and Thirteen,
and the one with the nose.
But I just can't
risk coming back here.
Okay.
That was surprising.
I want to run
the department.
You consider waiting
until House clears the lobby
before you start angling
for his job?
He's not dead
or sentimental,
and somebody
needs to do it.
Not necessarily.
Departments of diagnostic
medicine don't exist.
The only reason we have one
is because of House.
You reassigned us, kept us
on payroll for three months,
you might as well
give me a chance.
You're a great doctor,
I want you to stay on in
Neuro, but House was a genius.
House was an egotistical,
pill-popping, lawsuit magnet.
And a genius.
And I worked with him longer
than anybody else. I can do this.
You get one shot.
What's House gonna do?
No idea,
but he's gone,
so how about we focus
on the medicine?
What?
You're the boss,
it's kind of sexy.
Here I thought
it was just the pants.
Diabetic neuropathy?
HbA1c looks fine.
Could be hypothyroidism.
No fatigue
or weight gain.
What about complex
regional pain syndrome?
That's a good idea.
Let's run with it.
Look at that. No House,
the job still gets done.
And yet,
something's missing.
I'm short, he's black,
you're gay-ish.
That's it.
Treat for CRPS. Prep the
patient for spinal stimulation.
I don't buy it.
CRPS isn't that
well understood, but...
I think it's mercury
poisoning. I eat a ton of sushi.
And you're currently
getting mixed reviews
in Speed the Plow on
Broadway? Google it.
It's pretty hard to
consume enough fish
to give yourself
mercury poisoning,
and it doesn't usually
present solely with pain.
But it can. Check out the
Atlantic Medical Journal.
This guy came in
with burning pain
caused by
Erythromelalgia
mercury poisoning.
Who needs actual doctors
when you've got the Internet?
No offense,
but doctors make mistakes.
Medical errors are
up 30% this year.
You should check
the rate of patient error.
There's a ton of
information out there.
Why wouldn't I educate
myself, be my own advocate?
CRPS came up in
my search, too,
but I've never had
any skin discoloration,
and my pain is sporadic,
not constant.
It's gotta be worth
one lousy blood test.
You know how
House feels
about people
touching his ball.
No, Chase refuses
to tell me.
Right, my husband's gay.
Witty.
I hear you're
taking over for House.
You're gonna be great.
Congratulations.
Not permanent.
Yet. Taub and Thirteen
cool with it?
He's older than you.
She's seen you naked.
Not like we haven't been working
together for two years now.
Working with is different
than working for.
You saw House,
how was he?
He was good.
He was honest, took responsibility.
It was kind of weird.
Is Thirteen around? I need her
to sign off on her ER transfer.
She and Taub are doing
a spinal stimulation.
No, they're not.
I just dropped a patient
in the cath suite,
and your guys
were not in there.
You know, usually,
spinal stimulation
is done with the patient
in the room.
He asked us to test
his blood for mercury.
It's unlikely,
but not impossible.
It's also not
what we agreed on.
Testing doesn't hurt, and
it only takes 20 minutes.
I figured
it didn't matter.
I'm thinking I should
decide when it matters.
If you're done
marking your territory...
Test results. Surprise,
surprise, Marcus Webly was wrong.
I'll handle this.
You expected not to
have mixed feelings?
I know it's
the right call.
I just don't know what to
do with my time, and my leg.
Pain's flared up
since I left Mayfield.
Ibuprofen's barely
putting a dent in it.
You need a hobby.
Right. Doctors the world
over treat chronic pain
with collections
of Hummel figurines.
No, I didn't say
you need a lame hobby.
You need something to keep you
engaged, connected to other people.
You already made me
get a roommate.
Wilson's got
one bedroom.
I don't think we can get any
more connected without unzipping.
Okay. So what does
Wilson like to do?
Vince, I'm Dr. Foreman,
Head of Diagnostics.
So you must be
the genius's replacement.
I prefer to think of
myself as Genius 2.0.
Your blood test ruled
out mercury poisoning.
What was my mercury
level? Two-point-eight.
That means for every
deciliter of blood...
I know what it means. I
also know it's above normal.
I want mercury chelation.
Your level isn't elevated
enough to produce your symptoms.
You can't know that until we de-elevate
it and see if my pain improves.
It's a judgment call.
Based on 10 years
of medical training?
I think you have CRPS. I want
to try spinal stimulation.
So, basically, you want to shove a needle
in my spine based on a glorified hunch.
I'll stick with
the chelation.
If you don't want to get
better, I think we're done.
What do you mean "done"?
You're not interested
in my medical opinion.
I'll move on to
my next patient,
you'll move on
to a doctor
willing to run
all the unnecessary tests
and procedures you want. Or you
can stick around and be cured.
Makes no difference to me.
I'm glad you
changed your mind.
Don't know about that.
Dr. Foreman basically
strong-armed me.
Which is impressive.
Stimulating at 100 hertz.
Guess you found him a little more
persuasive than the two of us.
Probably the pants.
He reminds me of me.
Is it supposed to hurt?
Not if we're
in correctly.
Is it your hands?
Your back?
No, my chest.
Can't breathe.
Heart rate's 140,
climbing.
You need to hold still.
What did you do?
Deep breaths.
His lungs are
filling with fluid.
Analysis of the fluid from Vince's
lungs shows the lung problem
is really
a heart problem.
He's got a thickened
left ventricle.
When his heart sped up
during the procedure,
it jacked up the pressure in his
lungs, causing pulmonary edema.
Good thing I talked the
patient into spinal stimulation.
It did lead us to
discovering a new symptom,
and proved he was wrong
about mercury poisoning.
We lucked into
that discovery,
and we were wrong
about CRPS.
Ventricular thickening plus
neuropathy could equal Lyme disease.
Not without joint pain.
When's his new game
coming out?
Couple of months.
He's probably
working non-stop.
Might be using more than
coffee to power through.
Cocaine use
explains his symptoms.
So we search his
office for drugs.
No. We're gonna ask him.
In a lot of ways,
cooking is like music.
Different elements
combine to make a symphony.
Difference is that
Beethoven's Fifth
isn't going to
be poop tomorrow.
What was
my one condition
for allowing you
to tag along?
Try not to be a jerk.
I'm trying.
I'm just failing.
Roll your meatballs
and keep an open mind.
How hard are you trying not
to make a ball joke right now?
They're smoking.
Your balls.
Oh.
No, no. They're browning
way too fast.
Blue's the color
you gotta watch out for.
Enough.
God, they're...
They're still raw inside.
By the time they're cooked
through, the outside will be burnt.
I think there's
a medicated powder for that.
Although,
vinegar could work.
My old chem prof
talked about
theoretically
you shouldn't trust
the results of
a hemoglobin A1C test
on a chronically
acidotic patient.
The acid in the blood
slows the reaction
between the hemoglobin
protein and blood sugar.
Browning meat is the
same chemical process,
which means it should
also be slowed by acid.
That actually
makes sense.
You might have
saved my balls.
That's the spirit!
Obviously the procedure
didn't go as planned.
The heart problem
was unforeseeable,
but I still feel
responsible.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
How long have you guys
been doing it?
I think it's best if we
kept things professional.
Tough to do,
now that I've seen
you rock
a leopard-print bikini.
Congrats, by the way.
Up top.
You hacked
my profile page?
Your treatment nearly
gave me a heart attack.
Figured I'd check if you had the
credentials to go with the cojones,
one search
led to another.
Is there a shot
of just her?
I'm thinking screensaver.
We need to know if
you've been using cocaine.
Nope. Dude,
you just block everybody
or do you really
only have three friends?
We need you to be
straight with us.
We need to be
able to trust you.
I cleaned up my act
12 years ago,
after my college
roommate OD'd.
Okay.
Search his office.
You think he was lying?
No, but I'm not sure.
It was worth asking.
If he'd said yes, it
would've saved us a trip.
But he didn't.
You have to forget
about him.
The patient?
House.
First you try
acting like him,
that doesn't work, so
then you try the opposite.
Now you're mad because
you have to use his move.
I feel like
Tom Brady's backup.
Tom Brady's backup
now makes $10 million.
Stop comparing. You can
do this by being you.
We should still check out his
office, talk to his co-workers.
I'll get Taub.
And
thanks.
Oh. And dinner
tonight at 7:00.
Can we make it 8:00?
Already made
a reservation for 7:00.
Hi.
I'm making gnocchi.
Oh, I didn't mean
to intrude, I just...
Cecile's in
my cooking class.
She doesn't
speak English.
You bake the potatoes
instead of boiling.
Less moisture, fewer gluten
bonds, lighter gnocchi.
You seem good.
Feeling better.
House.
I need to talk to you about
your leaving the hospital.
I do love a good groveling,
but my decision is final.
That's fine, as long as
I'm not the reason for it.
I know that sounds
completely narcissistic.
Yeah.
But it's not. We flirted,
we kissed, I fondled.
I hallucinated
a night with you
and yelled it from
a hospital balcony.
You're not a narcissist.
So what am I?
Not the reason
I'm leaving.
House.
I'm gonna miss you.
Lady, either kiss him or
leave. We got work to do.
You just couldn't
keep your trap shut.
Make the damn gnocchi.
Bye.
I guess you're
not in a hurry
to get back
to the office.
And you are?
I'm not trying to
avoid my boyfriend.
I'm a lizard,
not an idiot.
You've been
in a crappy mood
since we got
in the car.
And you're completely okay with
being ordered around by someone
who 24 hours ago was
basically your equal?
Unlike you, I didn't
expect anything different.
The work part
I can get used to.
He didn't ask me to go to
dinner, he told me we were going.
He's never
done that before.
So even the score.
Go home tonight,
put on some heels and
break him like a pony.
You'll feel much better.
What?
That's one big-ass bird.
Wow.
That's kind of amazing,
the way the wings move,
it's so real.
Get them off me!
I know what's wrong
with the patient.
I'm going
to call Foreman.
A little help.
Your partner said
you studied birds
to improve
the game animation.
Did you touch them? Can't
dissect without touching.
It's the best way to
understand the anatomy.
It's also a good way to contract
an infection called psittacosis.
We spoke to Dr. Foreman, he
wants to start you on antibiotics.
Does that infection cause
problems in the joystick area?
Kind of stuck
in play mode.
Yes, we get it.
She's very, very pretty.
It's not her.
I mean, it was,
when she was here with her
boyfriend three hours ago.
You've had an erection
for three hours?
At first, it was
just embarrassing,
but now it's
really starting to hurt.
Will the antibiotics help?
I'm afraid not.
This isn't psittacosis.
His erection persisted
even with medication.
We had to put in
a surgical shunt
just to
drain the blood.
You missed dinner. And a shunt
doesn't require both of you.
I'm dedicated. So, the holy
trinity, heart, hands, hose.
Could be
Guillain-Barré.
Not with normal
nerve conduction.
Thrombocytosis.
His platelet count
isn't that high.
Brain tumor
makes more sense.
I'm sorry, I just realized.
Joint pain and joint pain.
Honest,
I wasn't laughing
because of the obvious
tension between the two of you.
Erection points to a circulatory
problem. I'm with Foreman.
It is possible for a
brain tumor to cause...
We're going with
thrombocytosis.
Okay.
You're mad I didn't
ask you to dinner?
How long have
we been dating?
It felt like an order.
Your tone of voice was...
My tone?
I'm under a little
pressure right now.
How about
giving me a break?
Look, this is tough
for both of us,
except I haven't
just gotten a promotion.
So, now you're jealous?
No. I'm just saying
don't complain
about the burdens of
command to your employees.
I was complaining
to my girlfriend.
Who are those guys?
I have no idea.
Meet the competition.
Steve Paulson,
Neurology, St. Mark's.
Nice to meet you.
You called
another doctor?
Lots of other doctors. I posted
my symptoms on the Internet.
You guys are 0-for-2. I thought
I'd look for some backup.
I can cure all your symptoms
with my papaya toxin cleanse.
Month's supply, $395.
Okay, that guy's an idiot.
That doesn't mean they all are.
Neither one of you have
privileges at this hospital,
please leave. Now.
Dr. Foreman,
sorry for the intrusion,
but I notice you haven't
done a head MRI yet.
Because he doesn't
need one.
I'm pretty sure
he's got a brain tumor.
We considered that and concluded
thrombocytosis is more likely.
I'm starting him
on hydroxyurea.
His platelets don't seem
anywhere near high enough.
If you took an image,
I'm sure...
There are no signs
of increased ICP.
I'm not delaying treatment.
Looks like we need a tiebreaker.
Dr. Hadley,
what do you think?
I think both theories
have merit.
So, brain tumor, otherwise
you'd back your bosslboyfriend.
I want an MRI.
Fine. I'll set it up.
Great, you're up.
I need a taster.
Ragú with pork sausage,
beef thigh, no cream.
It's a little early.
Did you even go
to bed last night?
Bed is for sissies.
Unless you're having sex,
in which case...
No, bed is still
for sissies.
Doesn't this seem
a little bit obsessive?
You should have been here
when I was butchering the ox.
What do you expect?
I'm an addict,
I turn everything
up to 11.
Yeah, I thought you were
trying to tone that down.
No, I'm just trying to find
something I can set at 11
without blowing
out my eardrums.
Star anise with
the caramelized onions,
the sulfur compounds
bring out the meat flavor.
I couldn't sleep
because of my leg.
It was either make ragù or go out
on the street looking to score.
Good choice.
So, so good.
He asked me a question,
I answered.
You told me to make
my own decisions,
I do, and you stab me
in the back.
I didn't even say
what I really thought.
I hedged, and I don't
like that I hedged.
If I have
a legitimate opinion...
You express it
in private.
In public, the team
opinion is your opinion.
Except the team opinion
is your opinion.
That's my job.
And what's mine?
To lie when I'm asked
a direct question?
You would have
done it for House.
Maybe you just don't
want me to succeed.
Maybe you just want
to kick me again
for not asking you
to dinner.
At least when House was
being an unbelievable jerk,
I could talk to
my boyfriend about it.
I may be a jerk, but
you're wrong. MRI is clean.
Treat for thrombocytosis.
You're early.
For what?
I knew you'd show up here
complaining about Foreman.
I thought you'd hold out
for another week at least.
I showed up to ask if
you've seen thromobocytosis
with a platelet
count under...
I went crazy,
not stupid.
I leave, Foreman
embraces his inner Mugabe.
What's that?
Embryonali.
Unhatched chicken egg.
I'm going to suck out some of
the yolk and replace it with ragù.
By the way, you can
tell the other lepers
that their absence
has been noted.
Cameron didn't come by?
Daddy's little co-dependent
is all grown up.
Making room for Daddy's hot
bisexual with boyfriend problems.
It's not a problem,
it's...
Okay, it's a problem.
I mean, I get it, the patient's a
nightmare. He posted his case online.
You know Foreman,
you know the situation.
How can I get him
to tone it down?
Stop being a coward,
for one thing.
He's the one who's
afraid of failure.
In a job that no one
before me has ever done.
His fears are justified.
You're just afraid of
giving him control over you.
Which might work
at home,
but makes it almost impossible
for him to do his job.
Pass me those crackers.
You're saying
this is all my fault?
I'm saying
that you would be happier if you
learned when it's okay to give in.
What?
You just suggested that I give
in so that I could be happy.
What did they do
to you in there?
Taste this.
Oh, my God.
This might be the best
thing I've ever eaten.
And, yes, I'm including
what you're thinking of now.
You're an amazing cook!
I know.
And yet, my leg hurts.
Fire her.
I'm not
gonna fire her.
Then stop being
such a wuss.
I am not being a wuss.
Challenging you
is part of her job.
But when she does it,
you take it personally.
So you're saying
this is my fault.
I was trying to bury it
a little, but, yeah.
You gotta eliminate either
the challenge or the reaction.
Or we could stick
with my original plan.
We get drunk and talk
about how girls are lame.
Yeah, this problem
will go away on its own.
It's 8:00
in the morning.
Coffee ice cream.
No frittata,
no bombolini?
Started thinking
about what you said,
about me obsessing. Started
obsessing about obsessing,
decided to take a day off.
You were
enjoying cooking.
How like a man
to think that I enjoy
slaving over
a hot stove all day
while you're off
banging secretaries.
You said it was keeping
your mind off the pain.
That was before I discovered The
Biggest Loser marathon on cable.
I like to pretend
they can see me eating.
And your leg?
It's fine.
My leg's killing me.
Cooking helped
for a while,
then I guess
I got bored.
My leg started
hurting again.
Then I got worried, and
that made the pain worse.
What are you
worried about?
That nothing's
gonna help.
That I end up in
the Very Dark Place.
I'm fine,
I'm just not happy.
I didn't let you out
because you were happy.
I let you out
because I believe
you have the skills
to cope with that.
You tried one thing, it
didn't work, so move on.
Write, play chess...
What if nothing works?
What if nothing gives me
more than a few days
before my brain starts
looking for the next fix,
before my leg feels like
someone's shoving nails into it.
What do I do then?
If nothing in the world
can hold your interest,
we'll deal with that
when we get to it.
But you have to trust me,
and you have to be patient.
I brought you a donut.
The florist was closed.
I'll get a vase
and put it in water.
You know I'm sorry,
right?
I'm sorry, too.
Do you think
we could start over?
That's a fantastic idea.
We're gonna be late.
Your boss won't mind.
No way.
His lymph nodes
blew up.
He's been treated
for thrombocytosis,
but there's been
no change.
I was wrong.
God, you are a genius.
I'm adding this
to my list of symptoms.
That didn't work
last time.
Because I didn't
think big enough.
Now I'm offering
a $25,000 reward.
Steroids reduced
his facial swelling.
Swollen lymph nodes
rule out thrombocytosis.
How did so many people
get my personal e-mail?
The Internet is
a magical place.
Lymph enlargement makes
me think polyarteritis.
You were saying?
No point in treating the
symptom and not the disease.
Your stunt generated
quite a few responses.
Let's take a look.
I'm way ahead of you.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
secondary to spinal tumor.
No. No hypercalcemia, no
muscle spasms or incontinence.
You are possessed by the
Biblical demon Legion.
No. No jumping off a cliff
in a herd of pigs.
Otherwise, it did fit.
Graves' disease.
No. Thyroid levels
are normal.
You want us to
spend next few days
shooting down every
theory in the world,
or can we do our jobs and
come up with one that works?
I want you to test me
for amyloidosis.
Is that your
professional opinion?
It's the wisdom
of crowds.
Studies show that
collective decision
of a group can be more accurate
than any individual's decision.
I went through my e-mails,
amyloidosis got the most votes.
If you had amyloidosis,
there'd be speckling
on your cardiac ultrasound.
In 100% of cases?
Fine.
I'll make you a deal.
We do a kidney biopsy
to test for amyloidosis.
When it comes back
negative,
you pull your case off of the
Internet and retract the reward.
It's either that or
I don't test you at all.
Deal.
If you wanted a quickie,
you should have called ahead.
I'm a mess.
I came home for lunch.
You have lunch with Cuddy
on Tuesdays.
She was busy.
And you're
checking up on me.
You know, you can talk to
me... Is that my laundry?
You were running out of
socks for me to borrow.
We have plenty
of underwear, though.
I'm fine.
You said that
this morning.
And consistency
proves what?
Really, I'm good. I'll
put these in your room.
You always hurt
the one you love
Biopsy showed deposits in the renal
endothelium consistent with amyloidosis.
The Internet was right.
Start him on dexamethasone.
Already done.
This may not be the best
time for this, but I quit.
I got an offer to join a
friend's surgical practice.
You don't
generally get an offer
unless you're
looking for one.
I put out some feelers when I
found out House wasn't coming back.
I lobbied to keep
the department open
so you could
keep your job.
Yes, that was incredibly
altruistic of you.
It's nothing personal. Actually,
I think you're doing pretty well.
But I came here
to work with House.
He's a jerk. We'll be fine without him.
Do you know how many
resumes we get every day
without even asking?
Might be a few less
after Cuddy shuts us down.
The case got solved
under your watch,
does it really matter
how it happened?
It matters.
What if I'm just not
ready for this job?
Okay, you're sad.
I could tell you
the story about me
and my roommate
at Sarah Lawrence.
Okay.
Her name was Lindsey, and she
was a cheerleader from Iowa.
I broke my toilet
this morning.
I'll get my tools.
I blocked the intake valve so I
could collect some of House's urine.
Cuddy,
he was barely limping.
What did the lab say?
The urine was clean
for Vicodin.
It did however contain
strange epithelial cells.
Further analysis showed they
were from a Labrador Retriever.
Damn.
He's using.
Vince, Vince.
Vince, relax.
It's Dr. Foreman.
Kill it! Kill it! No!
I don't have my blaster.
He's hallucinating
'cause he's burning up.
Amyloidosis wouldn't
do this.
Antipyretics
didn't work.
Hopefully the cold tub
will get his temp down.
Maybe we should see if
anyone's sent in other ideas.
Maybe the reward
money attracted...
No, I'm not letting
anyone else jerk us around.
The masses were wrong
about amyloidosis.
They don't know
about the fever.
I'm going with Light-Chain
Deposition Disorder.
You okay with that?
Yes.
We think you have
a disease called LCDD.
It causes proteins to
build up in your organs.
You think?
We can't definitely
confirm the diagnosis.
And our only chance
of beating this
would be to start you on
high-dose chemotherapy.
But I do have to warn you that in
your condition, it might kill you.
Do you want me to get you
some more information?
You're my doctor,
I trust you.
No, you don't.
You're scared, and you don't
want to make this decision.
My career is
riding on this case.
Nowhere near as
important as your life.
But I think the best shot for
both of us is to treat for LCDD.
Okay.
All right. Let's get you out
of this tub and into chemo.
We know you're
back on Vicodin.
No.
The only thing you know
is that I'm a genius
who got a dog to pee
in your toilet.
You don't know
how I did it,
or, more interestingly,
where I peed.
House, you've spent
the last three months...
Et tu, Butte?
You got no reason
to be here,
he's the one
I was jerking around.
Why is your leg better?
Ow! It hurts.
Please go away now.
If you really think
I'm using,
how about asking me before
taking a wrench to your plumbing?
House,
you're an addict.
You can't be surprised if we
can't take you at your word.
Fine. Let's get you some
proof. Hide your eyes, ladies.
House.
You, too.
My godson
made me that mug.
If the lab says
this is Retriever, too,
please let me
know right away.
It'd explain my
overwhelming desire
to wipe my butt
on your carpet.
Thank you for
dragging me into this.
Stop the chemo,
he's got Fabry's disease.
He was in a tub
for an hour,
his fingers should have
pruned, but they didn't.
Already stopped chemo,
and confirmed Fabry's.
I'm glad you both agree but
could somebody loop me in here?
We assumed the deposits
in your kidneys
were proteins,
but they were fats.
Fabry's makes them build up in
your organs, choke your nerves,
keep your fingers
from pruning in water.
It's chronic
but manageable.
How did you
figure it out?
lodide mumps.
His lymph nodes swelled
up after the head CT.
We thought it was a new
symptom, but it wasn't,
it was a reaction
to the contrast.
lodide mumps takes lymph
nodes off the table.
Remove that symptom...
And that just
came to you?
I looked through
the online responses again.
Someone posted it
this morning.
I heard Cuddy
made it official.
Department's yours.
Congrats.
I'm sorry.
I went behind your back.
On a scale of one to 10,
how mad are you?
A seven.
And that's stupid.
You did the right thing.
It's my fault you thought
you had to go behind my back.
I should have
stood up to you.
But you didn't 'cause you
didn't want to fight again.
It's our first case,
it'll take time to adjust.
What if by the time
we get adjusted,
we don't like
each other any more?
That's not
gonna happen.
Are you sure?
'Cause ever since
I took this job,
we've been making
each other miserable.
I really don't think
this is gonna work.
You're breaking up
with me?
No.
The other night, when I thought
I was done, you were there.
I need you.
I don't want
to lose you.
Then, why are you...
You're firing me.
I'm sorry.
I slipped.
You took Vicodin?
$25,000.
I solved
my old team's case.
I was about to take the
pills, I went online,
I found people
posting medical problems.
And my leg
stopped hurting.
Oh.
Oh?
I'm supposed to be changing
my life. This is not a change.
Maybe I was wrong.
Says the guy making
sand castles in my brain.
We need to keep you
from using.
Taking your job away,
the medical puzzles,
nearly drove you
back to it.
Maybe diagnostic medicine is
the key to keeping you clean.
So you're okay with me
going online, solving cases?
No.
You can't sit all day
in a room by yourself.
Isolation fosters
depression.
The hospital is
part of my old life.
If I go back,
I might become
who I was before,
pills and all.
That's a possibility.
But could be,
the only thing worse for you than
going back to diagnostic medicine
is not going back.
Guess we're gonna find out.