Mr. Randall?
They're here.
Fifty-two million
includes over six million
already issued pursuant to
the over-allotment option.
When can we close?
It would be subject to regulatory
approval in both Toronto...
I didn't say how,
Oliver, I said when.
What?
You sure this is a direction
you want to go, Roy?
This would move us from
energy service into energy...
You don't think
oil's going up?
Of course it's gonna go up.
The question is when.
The question
is always when.
And if we wait until the deal
makes sense to everyone else,
we're gonna be waiting in
line behind everyone else.
All I'm saying is...
The same cover-your-ass crap
you always say.
We're gonna have to
wrap this up. I gotta go.
Where are you going?
Upstairs.
Get the regulators on it. I want
to close by the end of the month.
Come on, Roy. There are 10
other items on the agenda.
Which'll have to wait
until next week.
You can't drag us
all out of the office,
get halfway through,
and then just kick us out.
Yeah, I can.
The antibiotic
treatment had no effect.
Both the fever and the
pain are getting worse,
which means it's not
Clostridium difficile.
But you said that was the
only diagnosis that made sense.
It was. We need to
get him to a hospital.
Dad.
I don't want to go.
I know, buddy.
But we may need to.
Am I gonna die?
No. Of course not.
How do you know?
Well, I just do.
And I'm always right,
aren't I?
Yeah.
I want House.
I understand, but I told you
Dr. House isn't available.
Dr...
Call him.
Tell him I'll have a private jet
pick him up from whatever island...
He isn't on vacation. Dr. Foreman
is one of our best doctors.
Is House in jail?
No. Foreman is currently working with
two of House's most veteran associates.
Rehab?
No.
Mr. Randall, your son
will be in good hands.
My son
has already been in good
hands, and he's still dying.
I'm through
dealing with good.
I want the best, and everyone
I've asked says that's House.
So unless he's dead,
comatose, or insane,
I want him treating
my son today.
You could have said no
in good conscience.
The kid'll still be
Foreman's patient,
but his dad wants you
making the decisions.
Then he's not my patient.
You want to give me none of the
responsibility and all of the liability?
Which means I get...
Oh, cool.
Don't let him do
anything crazy.
When is he getting his license back
so we can stop playing this game?
Maybe never.
This game is fun.
You also need to prepare
President Dibala's case
for this week's Morbidity
and Mortality conference.
Oh, unfortunately, I'm overdue
on a mani-pedi appointment.
Not you,
Foreman's department.
Oh, right. Well, he's got
all the time in the world.
We made the wrong call, he
died, there's nothing to present.
It obviously garnered
a lot of curiosity.
And we don't have more
important things to do
than satisfy everyone's
idle curiosity?
It's not idle.
The question of how we deal
with two possible diagnoses
whose treatments are
contraindicated is worth discussing.
Abdominal pain increasing
in severity and frequency,
fever, dehydration,
diarrhea, weight loss.
Mom died from kidney failure
caused by type 1 diabetes,
which has been ruled out.
Seventeen doctors.
Everything's been ruled out,
which means we have to re-rule out.
Get a new history and physical.
Unless that's crazy, boss.
Been out of the country or
on any recent camping trips?
No camping. But we were in
Montreal back in January.
We went to see the NHL
All-Star Game for my birthday.
Awesome.
Where's Dr. House?
In his office.
He's really more of
a decider than a doer.
He's decided we
should start over.
You never know what previous
doctors may have missed.
Like this.
Does that hurt more
when I push there?
Not really.
What is it?
I'm not sure.
Just keep it clean,
simple.
We did a test that called into
question our initial diagnosis,
so we changed our mind.
And if they ask how
the test was done?
Why would they do that?
It's a routine lab test.
Routine lab tests don't involve
blood you stole from a corpse
to trick me into giving
the guy the wrong treatment.
Yes, and if you
brought that up,
it'd certainly make
for a lively debate
about the morality
of murdering murderers.
But since you burned the
only evidence of that...
To cover for you,
not me.
You're protected. The
decision was a coin flip.
There was no right
or wrong answer.
The body's underground, 8,000 miles
away. Nobody can prove anything.
That room will be filled,
not because of a coin flip,
not because of the patient, but
because House's department screwed up.
They're gonna be like sharks
in a chum-filled swimming pool,
and there's no way I'm jumping
in unless I'm in a steel cage.
So what do you want?
I want to know you
have everything covered.
Got what covered?
We're just reviewing
the Dibala case.
Making sure we
didn't miss anything.
We didn't. Except, of course,
the thing that killed him.
He's constipated.
Physical revealed a mass in his
abdomen, so I repeated the X-ray.
Old one was clean, new one shows that
his colon is almost completely impacted.
Obstruction would
explain the pain.
You think they just
screwed up the old X-ray?
Nope.
Hirschsprung's?
It's a congenital disorder
of the nerves in the colon.
Very rare in a child
your son's age.
Most doctors would
never think of it.
And you came up
with this?
It's House's idea.
We need a barium enema
and biopsy to confirm.
Let me guess,
it tastes really bad,
but it's gonna make
me feel a lot better.
Actually, you're not
gonna taste it.
You should try searching for
"Misty May digs for gold. "
Make sure you
put it in quotes.
I'm making travel plans.
I just need to get away,
have some time to myself.
You getting the hint?
So that's it?
You're done with your little
experiment with Foreman?
It wasn't an experiment,
it was a relationship.
You may wanna look
into the difference.
I'm glad you're
better, House.
I actually liked working for
you, but I'm not coming back.
Good.
Because if you came back,
Foreman would try
and save the relationship,
and he'd give up
being the boss.
Are you here to try to save
my relationship with Foreman?
God, no. I'm trying to save
my relationship with Foreman.
Right now, I'm Kobe, playing the
game I love, however the hell I want,
and Phil Jackson has to listen
to everyone else bitch about it.
Enjoy Cabo.
I'm going to Thailand.
Really?
Interesting.
Goodbye, House.
Goodbye, Thirteen.
Last week,
yesterday, today.
I can't believe it.
He's pain-free for the first
time in months, he's even hungry.
I'm starving.
We're still waiting
for the biopsy results,
but obviously
it's a good sign.
You're gonna
want to take it slow.
Don't try to regain all
the lost weight in one meal.
What's wrong?
The abdomen feels
normal, but looks bigger.
Jack, are you feeling...
Jack? Hey, Jack, you okay?
Right eye is fixed.
Lateral rectus palsy.
He's seizing. Need five
milligrams of diazepam.
What's happening?
Hold down his head
and turn off the lights.
I need to see his optic disk.
Heart rate's elevated.
Come on, hold his head.
I'm trying.
Wait. Where's House?
Mr. Randall, we need
you to step back.
His optic disks are swollen. He's
got intracranial hypertension.
Furosemide,
20 milligrams, IV.
If we could intubate him...
Need five more
milligrams of diazepam.
DC the monitors. Push 500
milligrams of phenytoin.
You can't push that much.
We gotta relieve the pressure,
or his brain can herniate.
Oh, my God.
Fifty milligrams
of phenytoin in.
Page Chase. Tell him
to meet us in the OR.
We need your consent.
What's happening to him?
The pressure in
his skull's too high.
If we don't reduce it, it could
irrevocably damage his brain.
But he was just talking.
He was smiling.
We need to drill
burr holes.
Drill into his head?
Phenytoin's not working.
Paralyze him.
Three milligrams
of pancuronium.
Then intubate
and hyperventilate.
Where's House?
House isn't here.
Do we have your consent?
Ready? One, two, three.
Injecting three milligrams
of pancuronium.
Look at the monitors. He's still
seizing. We need to do this now.
Go!
Electrical seizure
activity's stopped.
Intracranial pressure's
declining. Come on, keep going.
Pressure's down to eight.
I'll go tell the dad.
What happened?
I have no idea.
He hasn't had
any more seizures,
and cytological examination of the
subdural fluid showed no abnormalities.
Don't usually see brain
damage after a rectal biopsy.
He was fine
after the procedure.
No headaches,
no mental status change.
It wasn't anything we did.
It's not just his brain.
He's continuing to build up fluid in
his abdominal cavity as well as the dura.
We've inserted shunts
to drain it.
It's got to be some sort
of systemic infection.
Not after spending the last week
getting pumped full of IV antibiotics.
You notice anything odd about
the shape of the fluid collection?
Oh, God.
Virgin Mary!
The edge should be
tapered, lens-shaped.
Unless the dural layer was
already separated from the brain
when the fluid
started to build up.
Get a dural biopsy
to confirm brain cancer.
Nice catch.
Bangkok. Flight 799.
Wow, Bangkok. That
sounds awesome. How long?
Not sure yet.
Luckily, I have a friend who's staying
at my place taking care of my dog.
He's really big, so he
needs a lot of exercise.
Remy Hadley.
H- A-D-L-E-Y.
What, you think
I'm gonna rob the place?
No. Of course not.
In case you haven't
noticed, I have a job.
Look, I'm sorry,
I don't know you.
You're either honest or dishonest,
I figured the safer choice is to...
Is to treat a stranger
like an ass.
Nice way to live
your life. Bitch.
I said I'm sorry.
Oh! Hello. I was wondering if there
are any Business Class seats open
that I could use
my miles to upgrade to.
I don't know you,
but I assumed I could trust
you, welcomed you into my car.
Okay, you're a saint.
That's impossible, I confirmed
my reservation last night.
So re-book it.
Well, obviously, it was a
mistake on your end, not mine.
No. I'm on my way
to the airport right now.
They didn't believe you, huh?
Brain cancer?
We should know
for sure by the morning.
Our luck just keeps
getting worse, huh?
Treatment options are
getting better every day.
There's no visible mass, so even
if the biopsy comes back positive,
we've caught it early.
Oh, so, you're telling me
this is good news?
I'm saying we will do
whatever we can.
Right.
I'm sorry.
I gotta go. Foreman needs
more help with the M&M prep.
Okay. I'll come up and help
after I finish the biopsy.
We can handle it.
I'll see you at home later.
If you're here,
I might as well be.
Go home.
Get some rest.
'Cause I'm gonna be waking
you up as soon as I get home.
Stay out of my life.
Okay.
I know you canceled
my reservation.
You obviously saw me log in when you
were spying on me in the coffee shop.
I was talking to you.
I was spying on the MILF
in the running shorts.
I'm not coming back
on the team.
I don't want you
back on the team.
I cannot work for, with,
or around Foreman.
Which is why I don't
want you back on the team.
Now that you're out of the
picture, he's better than ever,
which is gonna make me
less miserable than ever,
which is why neither
of us gives a damn
how, when, or on what island in the
Bahamas you wanna get away from it all.
The Bahamas?
Costa Rica?
I told you, Thailand.
I assumed
you were lying
because it would have been idiotic
of you to tell me the truth.
Yet another reason
I have no use for you.
We've got a problem.
When Cameron sent
Dibala's blood to the lab,
she specifically asked for the
anticentromere antibodies test.
So?
The printout they sent you included
just the anticentromere antibodies,
but the lab also did
a full blood panel.
So? I'm not an idiot.
I obviously made sure the cadaver I got
the sample from had the same blood type.
You apparently didn't
check his cholesterol.
How far off?
Twenty percent.
Dibala didn't die
of high cholesterol.
Why would anyone even bother
to compare the two reports?
The same reason I did.
Because they're looking for
anything we might've screwed up.
We could claim the blood analyzer broke.
We can't.
Cameron documented that it was perfectly
calibrated when she did the test.
So the numbers are off.
It's weird, who cares?
If it comes up,
just act surprised,
like it's some
irrelevant curiosity.
I can't do this. I can't go in
there and stack lie upon lie.
You've got to figure out
a way to explain this.
Hey.
Missed you this morning.
Yeah, sorry.
I needed to get in early.
I didn't want to wake you.
I thought you did
want to wake me.
At least that's what you said
last night. I'm out of here.
No, no. I got the biopsy
results. It's not cancer.
How can so much be wrong
with nothing being wrong?
Since when is cancer
being considered nothing?
I just said it's not cancer. The
cell morphologies were all normal.
And so are the most
recent CT scans.
On the other hand,
adenocarcinoma of the
stomach would cause pain,
constipation, and nutritional
deficiencies that could cause seizures.
And wouldn't show on a CT.
You were right about the cancer,
just wrong about the place.
Continue to say
nothing if you agree.
Go scope him, get
another set of biopsies.
I get canceling
her ticket,
if you then showed up with
two more to somewhere better.
What are you talking about?
Or showed up at all.
But how does just ruining her
plans get her to agree to yours?
You talking about Thirteen?
Where's she going?
Nowhere this week,
thanks to you.
I didn't stop her.
I'm not gonna stop her.
I've already done all I could.
Now all I can do is move on.
I think I actually
believe you.
If you're telling the truth,
you're even more
rational than I...
Well, not more.
Then again, more sane.
You're gonna be
a good boss, boss.
I told you,
there's nothing wrong.
There's obviously
something wrong,
and I'm not even saying we
need to talk about it right now.
I just don't see
why you have to deny it.
I'm not.
Now you're denying
you're denying.
No. I'm denying that
there's anything to deny.
Robert, you can't do this.
You can't hide things from me.
There's a problem
with the Dibala M&M.
The HDL numbers on one of his early
blood panels don't match a later panel.
That's weird.
Yeah.
It's no big deal.
Cholesterol didn't have
anything to do with his death,
but after being
let go from Mercy,
and then that thing
with Thirteen's drug trial,
Foreman's paranoid about people
questioning the way he handled the case.
Well, that's ridiculous. If anything,
Foreman should be feeling secure.
He's the one who had the right
diagnosis, we talked him out of it.
I know. Don't tell him I told you.
He doesn't want to show
any signs of weakness,
especially now that House is claiming
he wants him to stay in charge.
All right.
So it's still cancer.
It's just somewhere else.
That's what
we're looking for,
but it would explain
all the symptoms
and all the normal tests
and imaging studies.
Got biopsies of the
mucosa and the submucosa.
I'm moving
towards the pylorus.
It's my fault.
Adenocarcinomas aren't caused
by diet or environmental factors.
I inherited a $10 million
pipeline business when I was 24.
By the time I was 30,
it was worth over a billion.
Since then, I have been
involved in over 50 deals
that make that first one
look like a loser.
Everything I do, everything
I touch, turns to gold,
except my family.
First, my wife
and now my son.
This is my fault.
It's karma.
That's obviously not true.
He's seizing again.
Get the scope out.
We need five
milligrams diazepam.
How's the ICP?
It's eight.
But the shunt's
open and clear.
This isn't
intracranial pressure.
Then what the hell is it?
Seizure's stopped, but he
hasn't regained consciousness.
No sign of any masses in his
stomach or esophageal lining.
And he's still accumulating
subdural and peritoneal fluid.
And every time we look to see where
it's coming from, he starts seizing.
You think
we're setting this off?
I think something is.
One of his stomach biopsies shows
an arteriole partially occluded.
But with no abnormality
in the other layers,
and no evidence of a cellular
inflammatory reaction.
It's definitely not cancer.
Then it has to be
some sort of infection.
We already ruled
out infection.
Only because he was treated
for it and got worse.
Seems like a sound reason.
Unless it's a
drug-resistant strain.
Drug-resistant strain
of what?
Bacterial cultures,
viral serologies,
ANA and ANCA
were all negative.
Everything's negative.
We obviously missed something.
Maybe the seizures aren't a
new symptom, they're an old one.
No doctor noticed
a thrashing kid?
Abdominal epilepsy.
The seizures would just look like pain
until it spread to his motor cortex.
Wouldn't explain
the fevers.
Protein malnutrition
can cause fevers.
And nothing causes malnutrition
like excruciating stomach pain
that gets worse
every time you eat.
I'd be a lot more certain if it was
my idea, but it's the best we got.
Start him on gabapentin,
hook him up to an intracranial
EEG for continuous monitoring.
I gave him statins.
What?
If they ask about the cholesterol,
just say I prescribed a statin
and forgot to put it
in the chart.
You want to solve
a problem in the records
by creating another
problem in the records?
There's no problem
with the records,
there's a problem
with my recordkeeping.
There's no way anyone
can prove me wrong.
How did you get
access to the statins?
You gonna get someone
in the pharmacy to confess
to yet another
recordkeeping problem?
I saw an open cart.
I just took it.
Why would you steal a drug
you can just as easily ask for?
'Cause I'm trying
to get you off the hook.
A story that raises more
questions than it answers
only puts the hook
deeper down my throat.
It's all right.
I'll handle it.
How?
By telling the truth.
The truth is,
I don't have the time,
I'm not in the mood,
and I don't see the point.
You don't want to do the M&M
because you're not in the mood?
This kid is dying,
and I've got House trying to push
all his responsibilities onto me.
They're not his
responsibilities, they're yours.
You're the one who
wanted to be in charge.
I wanted to be in
charge, not a figurehead.
Then do the M&M,
it's all yours.
You want me to get
flogged? For what?
So you can have
an academic debate
about a diagnostic dilemma no
one's ever gonna face again?
What the hell's
going on here?
I just don't want
to do the M&M.
Did it work?
Not even close.
Everything okay?
Just waiting for whatever
is about to go wrong.
Thirteen called.
She have a theory that makes more
sense than abdominal epilepsy?
She said someone hacked
into her e-mail account
and canceled her
airline reservation.
I'm guessing Foreman.
Really?
You're accusing Foreman,
not me. Cool.
You really want Foreman to
stay in charge of the team?
Makes sense.
He loves power,
I love puzzles.
You love power
and puzzles.
True.
And when I had them both...
It wasn't Foreman.
How do you know?
He said he's moved on.
And you believe him?
I believe that
he believes him.
Looks like it's time for
me to get off the bench.
What's up?
Are you Dr. House?
I understand
you're a big fan.
I'll have my guy send
over a signed glossy.
Continuous EEG shows no interictal
spikes. It's not abdominal epilepsy.
You paged me to tell me what it's not?
I paged you
to show you this.
That, I did not expect.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Darn it. I knew
I should've stayed outside.
The fantasy is always much
better than the reality.
You think this is a joke?
That's my son.
He's dying, and not one of you
seem to have the slightest clue why.
I know. That's why
it's so interesting.
Fever, stomach pain, seizures,
peritoneal and subdural fluid
collection and now spots.
Could be an allergic
reaction to one of his meds.
That suddenly developed eight
hours after he started the meds?
If it's not cancer or infection,
it has to be autoimmune.
Systemic lupus complicated
by a CNS vasculitis
would explain the rash,
fever, ascites...
CNS vasculitis would cause a
stiff neck along with the headache.
And would've showed up
on the dural biopsy.
What about polyarteritis
nodosa? It can occur in kids.
Except you can't have
arteritis without inflammation.
Okay, you come up
with something better.
Go on.
There was some inflammation
in the skin biopsy.
Plus he's got elevated
diastolic pressure.
It's barely elevated,
which you'd expect given the
number of procedures he's undergone.
Well, barely is more
than not barely.
Not my decision.
But if it was, I'd say
start him on prednisone
and get a testicular biopsy.
If he's gonna have any real
inflammation, it'll be down there.
Cameron and I will do it.
Why? It was Chase's idea.
Kid's father is not gonna be happy
about a fourth set of biopsies,
and you've got
a better rapport.
What's really
going on here?
You need Chase to help
you over-prep for the M&M?
Yes.
Then say so,
don't be a child.
Is it on his penis?
The kid's rash?
Yeah, why?
Means it's most likely affecting
the small blood vessels.
That's why we didn't see any
inflammation on the biopsies.
It's not polyarteritis,
it's Degos disease.
I'll do it.
Your son has Degos disease.
It causes micro-blood
vessels in the brain,
skin, and GI tract to
break down, clot off.
It sometimes manifests early on
with atrophic papules on the penis.
In your son's case, we don't know
why, but they came much later.
What's the treatment?
There isn't one.
It's incurable.
You're wrong.
You've already been
wrong a bunch of times.
We rechecked the biopsies.
It's definitely Degos.
I'm sorry. I wish there
was something we could do.
How long?
Not much longer.
What does that mean?
A day at the most.
All right. Great.
We need to talk.
Unless it's life or death,
it's gonna have to wait.
It's about Dibala.
Let me rephrase,
unless it's a current...
Foreman can't present
the case at the M&M.
I know you guys are busy, but he's just
gonna have to suck it up and make the time.
It's not the time.
Then what is it?
The anticentromere
antibodies test,
the test that caused us
to change the treatment
from blastomycosis
to scleroderma, it wasn't...
It wasn't what?
Dr. Cuddy, they need
you in the Pediatric ICU.
Who's they?
I don't know,
but I think
they're lawyers.
If you guys screwed
something up, just come clean.
It's not gonna be that bad.
With all due respect, you
don't know what's at stake here.
What's going on?
You need to stop him.
He's about to
ruin his life.
Like you give a damn
about my life.
Roy, he's right.
You're borrowing money to buy options
that are already out of the money.
Even you won't be able
to cover the losses.
Your house, cars, bank
accounts, you'll lose everything.
That's the point.
The billionaire thinks that the gods
will treat him better if he's broke.
I suggested
he give it to me...
There has got to be
some sort of balance.
You can't have all the good fortune
in just one area of your life.
That's not how the
world's supposed to work.
Who said the world
was supposed to work?
Don't just wipe
everything out.
Put your assets
in a trust,
give it to a charity...
I can't get anything back.
He's insane.
He's irrational,
so are most people. Unfortunately,
it doesn't make them insane.
If he signs that paper, he's not
only gonna destroy his own life,
but the lives of thousands of people who
rely on this company to make a living.
If he is insane,
we will sue this hospital...
Mr. Randall,
I know you're upset, but you shouldn't
make a decision like this right now.
Give it some time.
My son doesn't
have any time.
Your son's dying from an
incurable disease, not bad karma.
No. He's not dying.
It's not gonna happen.
I'm not gonna let it.
Roy.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I can't let him die.
People don't get
what they deserve.
They just get what they get, and there's
nothing any of us can do about it.
Deliver it, or I'll make sure
you end up the ones with nothing.
Call a code.
He's flat-lining.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
For what?
For thinking I was worth
breaking the law to keep around.
That's just the way I am.
But still don't know
what you're talking about.
Cuddy had IT trace all the IP addresses
who've logged into my e-mail account.
There were two.
Mine and yours.
Obviously House decided he needs
you more than he's willing to...
I already asked House.
And he'd certainly
never lie.
No, he'd lie.
Except he wants me gone.
And he'd do a lot better job
of lying than you just did.
Really? It was that bad?
No, actually.
But it doesn't matter any more.
Why? Because of House or Foreman?
You're good for both of them,
but Foreman's not my best friend.
House will be fine.
Maybe.
But with you on the
team, he'd be better.
He needs someone
who doesn't need him.
You're the only one he's never really been
able to suck into his crazy House vortex.
Keeps him grounded,
his ego in check.
Why didn't you
just come to me?
I figured you'd only stay if House
asked. And I knew he would, eventually.
Bye, Wilson.
This is a great job.
Maybe even better, now that
House is at least trying
to have real relationships
with people.
I said trying.
It doesn't matter.
The job you love
doesn't matter?
Don't throw it all away just
because of a bad breakup.
Bye, Wilson.
I just confessed.
I told Thirteen I was the one
who canceled the plane ticket.
Why?
You mean why did I confess,
or why did I do it?
I know you didn't do it,
so I guess the first.
You want her to stay because you want
her back, or because Foreman does?
Why would I care
what Foreman wants?
Because you're not as big
a jerk as everyone thinks.
Yes, I am.
No, you're not.
I just made a $10,000 short sale
on a stock I know is gonna crash
because of what I saw a grief-stricken
dad do on his son's deathbed.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
You are a jerk.
She's making a mistake.
So you did it for her?
She's a good doctor.
So you did it for you?
I'm not the one
in charge any more.
So you did it for Foreman?
She's a smoking-hot,
newly-single bisexual.
Why don't you just admit that
you like having her around?
She's good for you.
You need her.
Because I was born with a
heart three sizes too small.
No, you weren't.
Yes, I...
What?
He still alive?
Yeah.
Good. Start him on heparin
and IV immunoglobulin.
For Degos?
The cardiac arrest
wasn't just an "everything goes
to hell in a hand basket" arrest.
It was a coronary event.
Coronaries are large vessels.
Means it can't be Degos.
But the biopsies
confirmed...
Obstructed
blood vessels.
They can't be obstructed
because of Degos.
Means it's primary
antiphospholipid syndrome.
Are you sure?
Nope.
But I will be if he responds to
the heparin and immunoglobulin.
By the way,
someone screwed
over your girlfriend,
and she ran to me, Cuddy,
and Wilson, everyone but you.
She's not over you.
Or she is.
Where did you find it?
Find what?
Niacin-bound
chromium supplements.
It was right on top of the
file. You don't know about it?
No, been here all night.
One of Dibala's previous docs
was prescribing ultra-high doses
of niacin-bound
chromium to boost his HDL.
So?
So, it gives us
something to point to.
We can explain the wide
variation between the HDL numbers.
We're safe. We're covered.
You really didn't
request the info?
No.
And obviously
you didn't either,
which means...
It worked.
The medicine worked.
How did you find it?
Fat, old, black guy.
I knew he had to be taking
something for his cholesterol.
And what now?
I'm not the boss.
You don't think
I should be fired?
Why?
I doubt we'll ever be treating
a genocidal dictator again.
Better a murder
than a misdiagnosis.
Whether you want to be
in charge or not,
you are.
And you always will be.
75-year-old African man
presented to our hospital
following a rapid
onset of hemoptysis.
He had been fine
prior to onset.
No chest pain, fever,
coughing or chills.
He does note a
nine-hour plane flight...