Good explosion! Drive
it, drive it, drive it!
You watching 77?
I'm watching everybody.
You don't need to watch
everybody, you need to watch 77.
You his agent?
Just an objective mom.
His explosion
is impressive.
It's not just burst,
he can pull, too.
You know, the only reason
he went to a double A school,
he was a bit of a late
bloomer, but he's a big man now.
You should be his agent.
Nice pancake,
Seven Seven.
You're moving up
those draft boards.
Thank you, sir.
01, 01, ready?
Break!
Set!
Blue 90. Hike.
Good job!
Second level, nice!
Get off my quarterback!
Play's over!
The play is over!
Save the aggression for
between the whistles!
Daryl!
All right,
back to work!
Daryl!
Daryl, stop!
What are you doing?
Canoeing, but I seem
to be taking on water.
This is not okay.
Use your own bathroom.
No canoe in my bathroom.
My leg hurts, soaking
makes it feel better.
You were the one who
had to have this condo.
Maybe next time you
should consider amenities,
like two full baths, instead of
just the joy of outbidding Cuddy.
The guy who signs the loan
gets to pick the bedrooms.
Stay out of mine.
Well, then you
owe me 35 bucks
for the grab rail
I installed.
Hit the kill screen,
boss is here.
It's not porn,
it's our new patient.
Bummer.
Twenty-two-year-old male,
6'7", 310 pounds.
Clearly has
brain involvement.
The guy has no recollection
of this entire incident.
Football player.
Those are the ones that get
hit in the head a lot, right?
ER CTed him.
No concussion, no stroke,
no cortical degeneration.
And he had a full psych
evaluation. He's not crazy.
So it's roid rage.
You don't think they grow
them that big naturally?
ER also tested for steroids,
he's clean.
Only proving that our guy got
his hands on the good stuff.
The negative test at least
means steroids is less likely.
We should discuss
other possibilities.
Why?
He injects his sore ankles
with lidocaine every game,
you think he's above
injecting steroids?
Repeated head trauma could
damage the base of the brain,
leading to a pituitary
adenoma, which leaks GnRH.
Pituitary damage wouldn't
be visible on a CT scan.
Could cause the excess hormones
that could cause the rage
and would elude
the ER's steroid test.
Fine. Bilateral venous sampling
to find the elevated GnRH,
MRI to find
the pituitary damage.
Unless, of course, there
is no pituitary damage,
in which case, our guy got
his hands on the good stuff.
Foreman. Let the peasants
handle the peasantry.
Your brother needs to get
picked up this afternoon.
From prison.
Your older brother, in case
your confusion is related...
How do you know
about that?
He left a message.
He said he couldn't get you
on your cell or at home.
I get it, you're busy,
you'll pick him up
the next time he
comes out of prison.
Is that all?
You're officially unbusy.
Family is family.
Take the rest of the day,
go see your brother.
I have work to do.
Do you feel any pain
that's deep and persistent?
Not just muscles
or joints.
Everything hurts all the
time. That's football.
It might not be
just football.
We're going to test for
damage to your pituitary.
If there is, it could
create excess hormones,
which could be
causing your pain.
It would also explain
your rage attack.
And if my pituitary
is damaged,
how long would
it take to treat?
I don't want to get
ahead of ourselves
and start promising deadlines.
I'm sorry, Doctor,
but he's playing
in front of pro scouts,
coaches and GMs
this Saturday.
This is the job interview
for the rest of his life.
If we do find
something wrong,
we can go in
through the nose
and repair the damage,
nothing too invasive.
You'll need a couple
of days of recovery,
and then we can have
you back by game time.
Thank you, Doctor.
There's nothing wrong
with your eyes.
Well, then, your gizmo's
broken. I'm seeing spots.
Or you enlisted, you got the cool
haircut and the awesome pants,
then you realized
that your plane ticket
to the Middle East
was coach,
and you decided to
rethink your promise.
No. I've already
been there.
Three deployments. Now
they want me to go again.
But my wife's pregnant.
So our Homeland
should be unsafe
because your Private
was unsafe?
Look, my wife and I
planned this perfect.
My enlistment was supposed
to be over last week,
so we got pregnant
six months ago.
Now they tell me
I'm getting stop-lossed.
Army speak for
they don't care
about the fact that I've
finished my contract.
I don't care about the
fact that they don't care.
Hey, come on, I waited an extra
hour just to make sure I got you.
Why?
I saw you limping out there.
Vietnam?
Viet...
How old do you
think I am?
I don't know.
Vietnam age?
Well, back in my day
the real dodgers had the
stones to run off to Canada
or shoot themselves
in the foot.
They didn't come to free clinics
whining for doctors' notes.
Go hug your wife, tell
her to get a babysitter,
and you'll be back in time to
video the kid's first steps.
Yeah, I don't need
to see the scan.
I can tell from your little puppy
dog eyes that his pituitary's fine.
Are you gonna say it,
or should I?
You were right
about the steroids.
You're a genius.
Next time,
with feeling.
Put the cheater on
a somatostatin analogue
to clear it out
of his system,
send him back to
his football game.
I've never done steroids.
Well, somehow your
GnRH got elevated.
This will help
get it back down.
Mom, I swear!
Who's gonna
draft you, Daryl?
You're stupid enough
to try that stuff,
especially the week you
know you're getting tested?
You guys must have
mixed up your labs
or got somebody
else's blood,
because I never...
Okay, what is that?
Tachycardia.
Lay back down, Daryl.
Why's my heart
beating like this?
It's not steroids.
I need some adenosine, and
get that crash cart over here.
House, next time...
Marcus.
Oh, right.
You two know each other.
What are you doing here?
Interviewing.
Oh.
Who are we kidding? Interview's
over, you got the job.
What job?
My new assistant.
Part of his parole,
he needs a job.
Just trying
to do my part.
You were wrong
about the steroids.
Patient had a paroxysmal tachycardia.
We cardioverted him
back to sinus rhythm.
We're going to get a EKG
and a sestamibi scan.
Marcus,
let's talk outside.
Family is family.
Hey, good to
see you, too.
Did you have
a hard stretch?
Not bad, I hardly got raped at all.
You can't work here.
But your boss
says I can.
I'm not playing.
Lighten up.
I mean, this could be fun.
I get to see your world. You
get me access to the pharmacy.
I am playing. Come
on, man. You look good.
I'd already know that, if you came
to visit every once in a while,
but whatever, I get it.
It's cool.
You don't wanna see me,
you don't wanna pick me up.
It's all justified.
I'll just have to
win you back over.
Let me explain something. This
man who's offering you the job?
He's not
a philanthropist.
He seems more
helpful than you.
He doesn't want
to help you,
he only wants to use you
to screw with me.
You know how you
can screw with him?
Act like your brother getting
a job doesn't screw with you.
Trust me, it'll be better for
both of us if you go back in there
and tell him you can't take the job.
I'm not a person who has the
luxury of turning down jobs.
Well, figure
something out
because you cannot
work here.
House!
Okay...
We spent all night, used
all the fancy machines.
Patient's heart
looks fine.
Well, if it was fine,
it wouldn't go aflutter
just because you
walked into the room.
Light whip,
two extra shots.
Thank you, sir.
Judging by the look
on your face,
I assume you're upset
that big bro
didn't take your advice
and skip town.
You told him about
our conversation?
He bought me breakfast.
It was fun. Put lunch in
the books, just you and me.
Our patient
could have a PFO.
Well, naturally you jump
right to a urinary issue.
PFO's not urinary,
it's a heart issue.
It is? Oh.
Well, naturally you think
it's not a urinary issue
because you're
so embarrassed
about your own
past urinary issues,
you don't dare
broach the subject.
Oh, come on.
You spending the night
over at Bobby Samson's?
I did not wet the bed,
I spilled a drink.
We're not buying it, Eric.
We never bought it.
Why are you telling him
these things?
What's the big deal?
It was 25 years ago.
Oxygenated and
de-oxygenated blood mix,
the rough flow causes a clot,
explains the heart and head.
Like that power forward from
Loyola Marymount when he...
Hank Gathers? That's
not what happened to him.
Whoa,
let your brother speak.
What happened
to Hank Gathers?
Conference tournament.
Alley-oop dunk,
jams it home,
then he runs up
the court and splat.
He dropped dead of a heart
thing right there on the court.
I remember that.
On autopsy they found
he had a hypertrophic
cardiomyopathy.
Rage and tachycardia
are warning signs.
Seriously?
Because my brother remembers
a basketball game?
Hey, I don't care
where an idea comes from,
as long as it makes sense
and embarrasses someone.
Are you out
of your mind?
As a former
psychiatric patient,
I take offense at
that terminology.
All I did was
ban you from my tub.
Whatever happened
to proportional response?
to coherent conversation?
That thing broke tiles, gashed
the walls, and pooped everywhere.
Expect a bill for repairs.
And payback.
What was that?
I have no idea.
Everybody else thinks hypertrophic
cardiomyopathy makes sense?
Good, stick the patient on a treadmill.
Stress his heart
until it stops.
You want to induce
cardiac arrest?
The only real treatment is for the
patient never to stress his heart again,
which means we have to tell him to
retire at the ripe old age of 21.
Stopping his heart speaks
louder than words. Go.
Maybe it's a good thing. He gave
your brother a job, responsibility.
I'm not arguing that
he shouldn't have a job,
I just don't want him
having one here.
I understand that House
did this to annoy you,
but why is
he succeeding?
You know what
my brother did
the last time
he got out of prison?
He stole money from my
parents to buy drugs.
He robbed a liquor store, then he
moved on to jacking luxury cars...
Last time.
Every time.
I've known my brother
for over 30 years.
You haven't even
known him a day.
I'm sorry.
The exterminator
charged 250
to get the opossum
out of there,
and the contractor estimates
1,500 to fix the bathroom.
And why are you
jerking Foreman around?
Because it's fun.
Maybe you should give
those bills to the guy
who left his own
bathroom window open.
Your motives always run
deeper than simple fun.
I want to learn more
about one of my employees
so that I can
manipulate him
and destroy him if and when I
choose. Information is power.
Not buying it.
Okay.
Why don't you tell me
my real evil plan?
I don't think
there is an evil plan.
You regret not having a
relationship with your own family,
and you don't want to see
Foreman go down that same path.
I think you're
actually being nice.
Oh, shut up.
You can't accuse me
of an opossum attack
and underhanded kindness
in the same visit.
Then I'll come back.
Treadmill test
was a bust.
The guy's in
unbelievable shape,
we couldn't get his
heart rate above 150.
Your boss is secretly
a very nice man.
I know.
If we can't
recreate the cardiac event,
we can't prove
hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.
Either we find
a bigger treadmill, or...
Did I miss the memo
about you being released?
I'm feeling fine.
I can't keep laying here
in this bed,
missing practices.
All excellent points.
Give me your arm.
What's in the shot?
It's a vasodilator.
Since we can't exercise your
son's heart on the treadmill,
we're gonna have
to do it chemically.
What's wrong?
You're turning white.
What does that mean?
It means he doesn't need football
to get a good job anymore.
Raynaud's Phenomenon.
Vasospasms cut off the
blood supply to his fingers,
could be early onset
rheumatoid arthritis.
His rheumatoid
factor is negative.
Arterial plaque
throwing clots
would explain the fingers,
head, heart.
You really think
a guy with stenosis
could've aced
that treadmill test?
You're kidding me.
You got him a desk?
And a nameplate. Man's got to
have a place he can call his own.
What about
Takayasu's arteritis?
Lymphoma's a better fit.
We should remove
his spleen.
Bold move to skip
straight to surgery.
His big game's coming up,
we don't have time to biopsy,
wait for the pathology report,
and resect.
Right. We should remove his
spleen without confirmation
so he won't miss
the big game.
Hang an ethanol drip.
That won't treat for either
lymphoma or Takayasu's.
If it's lymphoma, the
ethanol will make him itchy,
and Foreman can
remove his spleen.
If it's Takayasu's,
he'll lose his radial pulse,
and Chase can
start him on steroids.
Marcus!
What are you
doing here?
My new assignment is to
shadow you into enemy territory
and document your every
word to the patient.
Just don't say
anything stupid.
You're not an idiot.
Don't do this.
Come on, man.
I'm a new person now.
No more drugs,
no more lying.
And if I can't
get my own family
to give me an opportunity
to prove that,
then what's the point?
Mom and Dad
gave you a chance.
And a second.
And a third.
I'm not about to
give you a 54th.
Why isn't your minion
fetching your lunch?
He's busy spying on
his little brother.
What?
That's very demeaning.
You obviously have a theory as
to why demeaning is not demeaning.
You're escalating to prove I
was wrong about you being nice.
Which you would only do
if I was right.
Do you even listen
to yourself?
Twenty-three-year-old just came
in to the ER, asked for you.
What's her cup size?
I don't think his cup size
is relevant to his condition.
He accidentally
shot himself in the foot.
Oh, for...
Seriously?
I give you a choice
between moving to Canada
and shooting yourself
in the foot,
and you choose
the bullet?
I didn't want
to be a fugitive.
You think this is
gonna get you discharged?
We'll patch it up and
send you right back.
Well, don't patch it up.
Look, you got screwed over
by your own government
and that sucks.
But all you're going
to get out of this
is a five-day vacation
and a band-aid.
When I signed up,
I was just a guy.
Now I'm about
to be a dad.
I go back over,
there's a chance
my kid grows up
without a father.
You got a girl pregnant.
You're still just a guy.
How much longer
we have to wait?
We have to keep going until
you start feeling something.
Might help if you told me
what I'm supposed to feel.
I do that, that's all
you'll be thinking about.
Then you'll be telling me
that's what you're feeling.
Power of suggestion.
The other black dude who was in
here earlier, he your brother?
What gave it away?
The way you looked at him.
I have two older brothers, and
we always want to kill each other.
Something wrong?
Not really.
Just feels itchy.
Is that what you
were waiting for?
Means lymphoma's
most likely.
But that's
actually good news.
How can that
be good news?
Because it's treatable,
we can remove your spleen
tonight laparoscopically.
Will I be up and
around by Saturday?
We can get to the
radiation in the off-season.
Hey, Ma. Wake up.
Ma, wake up. I'm itchy.
Means I can play.
What are you
doing in the dark?
Lying in wait.
Jeez, what happened
to your face?
Right, play innocent.
Like you weren't
looking for revenge
for the prank
that I didn't pull.
It's karmic justice,
but I didn't do it.
Of course you realize,
this means war.
Isolating
the gastroepiploic artery.
Nearly there.
Foreman, come and
take a look at this.
Liver's inflamed.
So the itching wasn't
caused by his spleen.
It's not lymphoma.
What happened
to your face?
Wilson annexed
the Sudetenland.
No abnormal
T- cells or B-cells,
it's definitely
not lymphoma.
Liver biopsy only revealed
non-specific inflammation.
Kind of like the time
you took your mom's birth
control pills on a dare
and ended up with
swollen nipples.
That never happened.
Right.
And your nickname all the way up
through high school wasn't Erica.
It wasn't.
Okay, I may have
made that one up.
With the understanding that my
brother still had his sense of humor
and would figure
out to play along.
Polymyositis would
explain the head,
liver, heart,
even the white fingers.
Would also be accompanied by a
significant decrease in muscle power.
Marcus, chance to
redeem yourself.
Does our patient
look strong to you?
Sorry, Eric. Big brother
disagrees with your diagnosis.
Felty syndrome?
You said the liver was
inflamed, not the spleen.
Can you believe they let
this guy perform surgery?
What are you doing?
Requesting permission
to share my idea
without being belittled in
front of your new assistant.
Permission denied.
Continue.
Our patient has cartilage
damage in both ankles,
he gets lidocaine shots before
every game to mask the pain.
Team doctor uses the same
needle twice by accident?
Viral hepatitis.
Do you think he's an idiot, Marcus?
I don't think
he's an idiot.
Okay.
Go test his blood.
Come on. We have
a lunch scheduled.
So you jerked me around.
Your allegiance lies with your
brother. I get it. Admirable.
But here's the problem. I
hired you to tell me the truth.
If you don't do that,
you no longer have a job.
I don't know what secret
you're looking to uncover,
but my brother
is a decent guy.
He was arrested
for grand theft auto.
You're gonna
be disappointed.
Try me.
He tell you
I was with him?
Was it your idea?
We did everything
together,
I don't know
whose idea it was.
I was 16,
he was only 14.
Little punk couldn't even
see over the steering wheel,
but he was quicker
with a flathead screwdriver
than most people
with a key.
Sorry to interrupt my character
assassination with boring medical stuff,
but when we drew
the patient's blood
it clotted right there
in the vacutainer.
So the problem is not in his
blood, it's the blood itself.
He's been working out in
the cold, doing two-a-days,
it's got to be
cryoglobulinemia.
I usually love breaking bad
news, but in this case...
Start the patient
on warfarin.
I am so sorry about that.
You were saying?
We drove for
about 10 minutes
before we got caught
and that was it.
When mom came
down to the station,
she didn't say a word
the whole ride home.
She came to the driveway,
turned off the car.
We're sitting in there
in silence.
And then,
without turning around,
she said,
"I'll pray for you. "
Then she got
out of the car.
Wow. You got off easy.
Easy for you, easy for
me. Not easy for Eric.
His life mission became to never
disappoint our mother like that again.
Because he is
a good guy.
Thought he would tell
that story at the eulogy,
but I heard
he didn't give one.
Your mother's dead?
If he didn't tell you,
I'm sure he had a reason.
Look, you can mock him all
you want about peeing the bed,
but please don't
bring up our mother.
Your blood contains an abnormally
high volume of certain proteins,
called cryoglobulins.
They become thick
when it gets cold outside.
It's like a car trying to run
after the oil's turned to sludge.
We think that's what's been
causing all your problems.
So I just need a quick oil
change and I'm good to go.
This oil change
isn't so quick.
We have to put you on blood
thinners and other medications.
The process will take
two to three weeks,
but after that, you should be
able to play without a problem.
After that,
it's not gonna matter.
Doctor, if Daryl doesn't
play in front of the scouts
on Saturday,
he won't get drafted.
Can't you wait
until after the game?
If we wait
and let him play,
there's a good chance
he dies right on the field.
I had an epiphany.
Usually that precedes you
walking away with purpose, so...
Flathead screwdriver.
And then I say...
It's not a game,
it's proof
that you didn't rig the
grab rail and make me fall.
I already have
proof of that.
The fact that
I didn't do it.
I can't go on that.
But I can go
on the fact
that I had to borrow a
flathead screwdriver from Nora
to install the thing because
we only had a Phillips head.
Then, of course, I
returned it late that night
in a completely successful
effort to see her braless.
Whoa! Wait. Wait a
minute. Wait a minute.
Which means that you didn't have
the tool to sabotage the grab rail.
Braless? Under, like,
a sweater? Or, like, a...
Now I also have proof that I'm
not responsible for the opossum
because I'm absolving you of
responsibility instead of escalating,
which you know is
not in my nature.
So someone is breaking into
our place just to screw with us?
The opossum
was meant for me.
I'm so tired. It was exciting
until about 2:00 a. m.
Now it's just torture.
Did you even go
to college?
This is the escalation,
isn't it?
Keeping me up
all night.
Nothing happens, then you keep
me up all night again tomorrow.
This is your retaliation.
You see,
that's just illogical,
'cause I'm
staying up, too.
Maybe you napped all day.
I gave you empirical proof
that I did not prank you.
No. No, you did not. You
created empirical proof
that I didn't
prank you,
selling me on the notion
that you didn't prank me.
Maybe you self-pranked.
I don't masterprank.
Is that cut on
your cheek even real?
See? This is exactly what our
nemesis wants. Divide and conquer.
Can't you see that?
Okay.
I'm going to bed.
I'm telling you,
if we sleep now,
we're going to wake up
next to severed horse heads.
Or worse, the rest of it.
Oh!
House!
The flatscreen!
You would never
sacrifice the flatscreen.
Oh, this guy's good.
Is there a reason
for this?
There is a reason
for everything, mes amis.
I am troubled to report that
we have a criminal in our midst.
Guilty of what,
exactly?
Last night the fire sprinklers
flooded our apartment.
And before that, I found
an opossum in my bathtub.
You each had motive,
you each had opportunity.
This is the emergency
you paged me about?
Not so fast,
Mademoiselle Cuddy.
No one leaves here
until they can account
for their whereabouts
the evening last.
Bye.
Okay. No one who
is employed by me
leaves here until
they account
for their whereabouts
the evening last.
What about you,
Professor Chase?
Why would I?
Because you
hold me responsible
for breaking up
your marriage.
I was here all night
with Thirteen
monitoring our patient's
IV blood thinners.
Can either of you
prove that?
The patient's alive
and improving.
Is that proof enough?
For now.
What about you,
Colonel Taub?
I was out to dinner
with my wife.
Really? Your wife?
Yes, really.
Good enough. 'Cause I
had you pegged all along.
You certainly had all
the motive in the world.
First of all,
I'm not interested.
Second, I don't even know
where you guys live.
Yesterday, I confirmed
that you are a liar.
What are you
talking about?
Well, at least
a liar by omission.
House!
Don't.
Get this, class.
Foreman's mom died.
He ever tell any of you?
House, I think you're
getting off topic here.
Is he serious?
Did your mom pass away?
About three months ago.
I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you
tell anybody?
And to top it off,
he refused to say anything
nice about her at the funeral.
I didn't talk because
it isn't anyone's business.
Stop. You don't have to
explain yourself to this guy.
You want to hit me,
don't you?
Marcus, don't.
I quit.
You should stop him.
He needs this job.
Our patient
needs a fresh IV.
I don't need two
to three weeks.
See?
Got my color back.
It means you're getting
better, but it doesn't...
Means I am better. My coach
had the team doctor come by.
He cleared me to play.
Did your team doctor realize
you're on blood thinners?
I'm off them now.
You're still sick.
You're not ready
to go off your meds.
Daryl, listen to him.
It is not worth the risk...
I'll come back
on Sunday, Mom.
You guys can give me
all the meds I need then.
The treatment
doesn't work that way.
Please, go with him.
The antibiotics
aren't working.
We're going to switch you
to different ones,
but you're going
to lose your toe.
Outstanding, soldier!
As a general rule, before you
celebrate, do a little research.
The Army's Medical
Evaluation Board
is perfectly fine with
nine-toed infantrymen,
as long as they
can walk and run.
So I lost a toe
for nothing?
Afraid so.
Unless you want me to keep
you on the old antibiotics.
We can let
the infection spread,
then we can amputate
more than just a toe.
Why are you risking
your life for this?
Your mom doesn't
want you to.
My mom sacrificed
everything for me.
Her telling me
not to come here
is just another
example of that.
I do good out there,
I could take care of her
for the rest of her life.
Who am I if I don't sacrifice
for her? That's family.
You okay?
Everything's blurry.
I can't see.
Take me back
to the hospital.
The blindness means
we were wrong about...
Actually,
I'm responsible for that.
I spiked his water bottle with
nitrates. Dropped his blood pressure,
robbed oxygen rich blood from
his brain, making him blind.
I figured a temporarily blind patient
is better than
a permanently dead one.
His vision was
already coming back
by the time I dropped
him off at the hospital.
Well played. If only we could
combine your medical chicanery
with your brother's
ability to fetch me mochas,
you'd be
the perfect Foreman.
Where are you?
I'm busy.
Great, so we don't
have a new symptom.
Means we should just stick
him back on his blood thinners,
and he should be okay to
leave in a couple weeks.
Actually, we do
have a new symptom.
Any of you take a look
at his readmittance chart?
Between the time
he checked in
and the time
he re-checked in,
our patient lost
a single pound.
Patient like that would
usually shed over 10 pounds.
The obvious answer
would be steroids,
but since we've
already ruled them out...
So he's not injecting, but he
could be getting them naturally.
Paraneoplastic syndrome,
the body produces antibodies
which battle cancer,
which could also act
like growth hormone.
We've eliminated lymphoma. What
other cancers mimic growth hormone?
Lung, pancreatic,
renal, breast...
It was a rhetorical question,
I don't really care.
Go test him
for all of them.
What are you doing here?
You need a job.
Maybe I can
talk to House,
see if I can get
your job back.
As soon as he knows you're
okay with me being there,
he won't want me back.
Maybe I can help you
figure out something else.
I promise
I won't let you down.
Don't do that.
Let's just see
how it goes.
So do they mandate you to
stay here at the halfway house,
or can you come stay
with family?
It's Foreman.
Well, it should stop
now that Marcus left.
Well, that's
the whole point.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Was my leg sticking out?
I'm so distracted lately, trying
to think of something funnier
than fire sprinklers
going off
in the middle of the night.
Any ideas?
Whoa. Easy there, tiger. I know
where you live. You know how I know?
'Cause my girlfriend
and I,
we tried to buy
that very same condo.
Why don't you
leave me out of this?
Wilson was the one
who bought the place.
And you're living there. You
deserve to suffer equally.
Actually, I've suffered more
now that you just tripped me.
Hey, hey. I'm...
His suffering will equal out
because he actually feels remorse.
Why would you
out yourself?
You can't even imagine
the retribution.
There won't be any. I'm ceasing
all offensive operations.
I've both made my point and
established my superiority.
And if you even get to the
planning stages of retaliation,
I will tell Cuddy that she
lost her dream place to you two.
See, she's under
this odd impression
that you guys
are her friends.
There's no cancer.
We scanned him
head to toe,
we checked blood smears
for leukemia,
we even ultrasounded his chest
looking for breast cancer.
Maybe I was wrong
about the weight loss.
You weren't wrong. We found
blood in his catheter bag.
His kidneys are failing.
So it has to be cancer.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
is the only thing
that can link kidney,
heart and liver,
even the rage.
Then why can't
we find it?
We've looked everywhere
inside this guy.
What if it's not inside?
You know why
you're black?
'Cause God loves me
more than he loves you.
Hmm. What I was going for was
melanin. You got lots of it.
Makes your skin dark,
protects you from
the sun's harmful UV rays.
What are you doing?
Unfortunately,
it also prevents
even those with advanced
medical degrees
from considering melanoma
as a diagnosis. Other hand.
On the rare occasion that
black people do get skin cancer,
they usually get it
on their white parts,
like the palms and
soles of the feet.
But your hands and feet are
so smashed up from football
that my team would
likely have written off
any skin blemish
as a bruise.
But now that I know that melanoma
is the only thing that fits...
Come take
a look at this, Mom.
There's the thorn in the panther's
paw. Paraneoplastic syndrome.
Your body forms antibodies
to fight the tumor.
Those tiny little proteins travel
through your blood and wreak havoc.
We remove the cancerous mole,
everything should be fine.
I'll tell Dr. Chase
to schedule the surgery.
Why bother?
I missed my shot.
What kind of life
am I gonna lead now?
Did you study really,
really hard?
Then the same crappy life
that the rest of the guys you'll be
graduating with are going to lead,
minus the student loans.
Hey, you ready?
Almost.
And done.
I heard House and Wilson are
getting pranked by someone.
You wouldn't know anything
about that, would you?
No.
And why should
I believe you?
You said I had
a trusting face.
I still don't understand why you
wouldn't let me retaliate, though.
They stole your dream.
Well, that's overstating it.
It's just a condo.
It's not because you feel
guilty about hurting House?
Or guilty for
being with me?
We'll buy another one.
I just don't see the need
to make a war out of it.
Well, I think
you're rationalizing,
which a less confident man
than myself
might take as a sign that
you're second guessing...
Okay. You know what?
Forget that last part.
I heard Foreman
and his brother
are trying to
work things out.
That's nice for them.
It's nice of you.
You didn't provoke Marcus to
quit so the pranks would stop.
You were becoming the common
enemy they could bond over.
You are the diabolical,
yet benevolent puppetmaster.
I provoked Marcus to quit because
he was no longer useful to me.
I hired him to get
information, I got information.
Uh-huh.
And how are we going
to get back at Lucas?
We're not.
I win.