Previously on "The Rookie"...
Rosalind: People are gonna die,
and you can't save them.
I ate their pain
like a five-star meal.
♪
Do you want to come in?
I didn't know
that you were gonna be here.
Tim and I were ju...
No.
Have you decided
what you're gonna do
with your Golden Ticket?
So next week, you're off
to F.T.O. school.
You will officially be
a Field Training Officer.
Detective Misha Porter.
I'm here to recruit you.
When do classes start?
Next Monday.
♪ Whoo
[Funk music plays]
♪
♪ Whoo
[Siren wails]
♪
[Tires screeching]
♪ Glitter on the ceiling,
gold under our shoes ♪
♪ Yeah, we gonna
make you feel it ♪
♪ We gonna make you move
♪ Ahh, ahh, ahh,
ahh-ahh-ahh, ahh ♪
♪ I'm in a mood, yeah
♪ Ahh, ahh, ahh...
[Music stops]
Hi.
Is there a problem, Officer?
Um... where's the driver?
It's a driverless car, obviously.
My dad designs them.
He was busy,
so he told it to take me.
Okay. Well, he...
um, just ran a stop sign.
The camera must
not have seen it.
Right. But I'm gonna have to
write you a ticket.
Why? I wasn't driving.
Yeah, not...
not you, but, um...
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh *
Um...
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Both: Surprise!
[Chuckles]
Oh!
You're home from undercover
school, so, you know, mm.
I love it.
[Chuckles]
Well, mm...
I'm gonna be late for class,
but I want to hear
all about it tonight.
Okay, great.
Oh, wait.
You're...
[Door closes]
But... Yep.
[Snorts]
Oh, God.
[Keys rattle]
Mm. [Chuckles]
Ah.
Hi.
I'm so happy you're home.
How are you?
[Chuckles] Great.
Mm?
Uh, typing still
a bit of a challenge.
And forget about
opening a jar.
It hasn't been too much for you,
being back at work?
Are you kidding?
I was going out of my mind
sitting on the couch all day.
There's something else
that's been helping me more.
[Exhales sharply]
An online group
that's hunting Rosalind.
They contacted me
a few weeks ago.
They call themselves
"Dye-Hards."
Hmm. Let me guess.
"D-Y-E" as in Rosalind "Dyer"?
Exactly.
Mm-hmm.
At first I thought
they were a bunch of kooks
who just wanted to hear
about the attack.
But, you know, th-their research
is actually really impressive.
Uh, what kind of research?
What...
They...
They scour message boards,
subreddits,
and social media posts for tips,
then compile the most credible
ones in an encrypted PDF
they call
"The Mother Doc."
And they...
Well, I was hoping
you might take a look.
Chris,
I'm a patrol officer.
I-I... Um, I'm not a part
of the investigation.
But you're still a cop.
Look, I wouldn't ask,
but the task force
has been blowing me off.
You are still recovering.
You know, and it's...
it's not healthy
to be immersed in
hunting Rosalind all day long.
Just take a look.
If you think
it's worth passing on, great.
If not, totally fine.
Fine. I will look at
"The Mother Doc."
[Chuckles]
Thanks.
Sgt. Grey: Your first day
as a Training Officer.
How does it feel?
Well, considering
six weeks ago,
I thought I'd have to wait
another... two years,
pretty fantastic.
What you got there?
Nothing. Just a couple things
I didn't want to forget.
Let me see, let me see.
"How to set up a shop"?
"Processing a prisoner"?
Nolan, I sincerely hope after
two years in the department
and a month at
the F.T.O. Training Academy,
you don't need
a crib sheet.
No, sir. No, I just...
I-I've been working towards this
so long,
I just didn't want
to mess anything up.
Oh, but you will.
This is your first time training
a rookie officer from jump,
making you
a rookie yourself.
Which I'm sure you're not gonna
haze me about at all.
You're gonna stumble.
But you're a good cop
and you know how to do the job.
Thank you, sir.
I needed that.
Good, 'cause you're not
getting this back.
Now, let's go
meet your rookie, boot.
[Chuckles]
So, alright,
first things first...
So, I'd like to congratulate
Officer Lucy Chen
for successfully completing
the D.E.A. Covert Operations
Training Academy,
which is no small feat.
[Applause]
♪
Good to have you back,
Officer Chen.
Happy to be back, sir.
Also, I have the privilege
to introduce
Mid-Wilshire's newest
Training Officer, John Nolan.
[Applause]
Hey, hey, hey.
♪
Good work.
And since Harper has decided
to abandon patrol
for a cushy desk job
with the detectives,
today Nolan will take on
the responsibility
of training
his first rookie.
Officer, stand up,
state your name
and badge number.
I'm Celina Juarez,
badge number 53397.
Officer Juarez,
you have earned the right
to be in this room,
but you must
prove yourself to stay.
The way we do things matters.
Protocol and tradition
are the metal
from which every cop
in this city is forged.
You have anything
to add?
I see you got top marks
at the Academy.
Good for you.
None of that matters
when you hit the street,
so assume
you know nothing,
and you'll never be wrong.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
That's it.
Be safe out there.
Hi, I'm Celina...
your new rookie who, uh,
apparently knows nothing.
Oh, I wouldn't say
"nothing."
Dean's List, D3 soccer,
graduate classes
in criminal justice...
pretty impressive.
Thank you.
But I'm aware that
academia and street smarts
are two different things.
I like to think simple
common sense trumps them both.
But if you have any questions,
you can always come and ask me.
Yep, and me.
Hi. I'm Lucy Chen.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
May I?
Please.
Sergeant Bradford's right.
The most important thing
is to never pretend
that you know
something you don't.
Pretending is what
gets you killed out there.
You're very lucky to have
Officer Nolan as your T.O.
He's a great listener.
And if you ever want
to talk to another woman
who was in your shoes
not that long ago, um, I'm here.
Thank you.
That means a lot.
Yeah, of course.
You guys have
a great first shift.
Thank you,
Officer Chen.
Are you ready
to get started?
Yes, sir.
Congrats on making P2.
Thank you.
I heard
you're doing a great job
riding with Tim
as his Sergeant's Aide.
Thanks, but look,
I'm ready to step aside
now that you're back,
s...
Wait, Tim said
I'm doing a great job?
Uh, no. Sorry. Oh.
I-I made
that last part up.
But, you know,
he hasn't replaced you yet,
so he's happy.
You should, um,
stick with him.
Really? You sure?
Yeah.
I mean, I could...
[Cellphone chimes]
...use some quiet time
riding solo,
thinking about next steps
in my career.
You haven't heard
a word I've said.
No, sorry. Uh, yeah, I got
something I got to take care of.
Excuse me.
Good talk.
Good morning.
Thank God you're back.
But first things first...
I need to see photos
of Leah ASAP.
[Cellphone clicks]
Look.
Oh, my God.
She's gorgeous.
It must have been hard
to leave her this morning.
Yeah, it was.
You ready to think
about crime again?
Yes.
What can I help with?
[Sighs] Let's see.
Jill Baskin.
Missing now for three days.
Uh, any suspects?
The roommate says Jill's
ex-boyfriend had a nasty temper,
but I haven't been able
to find enough for a warrant.
I'd love fresh eyes.
Tyler Harvin.
Alright,
I will jump on it.
Thanks.
This is your shop.
Do not call it a car,
a cruiser,
or a black and white.
It is where you work.
Anytime you leave the shop,
your body camera
needs to be on.
[Body cam clicks]
Perfect.
First, check the exterior
of the shop for any damage.
You are looking for dents,
dings, scratches.
We're gonna check
the back seat
for anything a suspect
might have left behind...
money, weapons...
drugs.
Was someone smoking weed
in here?
I think that was me.
Excuse me?
No, it's not marijuana.
I-I saged the shop.
You...
That's unconventional.
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't think you'd notice.
It's just that
it's my first day,
and I figured I could use
all the help I could get, right?
Sure. Next time,
just check with me first.
Okay. Now, where was I?
It was...
My Rook Book says you check
the trunk for equipment.
The trunk.
We're gonna need police tape.
We're gonna need road flares.
Load up.
♪
[Cellphone ringing]
[Cellphone clicks]
Hey, you're back.
How was U.C. school?
Challenging.
How's life
working for the enemy?
Not as weird
as I thought it would be.
It's actually
pretty interesting
seeing things
from the other side.
That's great.
Um, how is Chris doing?
Yeah, he seems fine.
You know, they're starting
him off slow,
nothing too intense.
Why?
Has he talked to you
about this online community
he joined
that's hunting Rosalind?
No, but I could see
why that would worry you.
Want me to
keep an eye on him?
Yeah, I really do.
Yeah, no problem.
But, Lucy,
just give him time.
We've both been
where he is.
He'll get through it.
[Police radio chatter]
What's the name of the store
we just passed?
Huh?
Uh, it was, uh...
You have no idea because
your face has been on your phone
for the past 10 minutes.
Put it away.
Sorry, sir. It's just, um...
[Exhales sharply]
There's something going on
that I don't know how to handle.
You know the deal.
This is a personal-life
free zone.
Yes, sir. But, uh,
this is something that could,
like, derail my career.
[Sighs]
Alright.
What is it?
I'm being blackmailed.
Yeah, so, I, um...
I sent this photo
to this girl on a dating app,
you know, just shirtless,
nothing X-rated.
A thirst trap,
you know?
I wish I didn't.
Turns out it was some dude,
and I was catfished.
And now
he's blackmailing me.
With what? You said
the photo didn't show anything.
Right.
The... The original one didn't.
But then
he Photoshopped it.
Whoa.
Yeah.
What does he want?
He didn't say.
He just told me to wait
for further instructions.
Well, I mean,
it could be worse.
At least he was generous.
[Police radio chatter]
Control, 7-L-19,
I have a 10-34 at The Nautilus
near the corner
of Virgil and West Fourth.
I'm going 9-5-4
to look for squatters.
♪
[Sighs]
Control, 7-L-19, I'm code 4.
There's no one here but me
and some spiders.
♪
[Bang]
Uh...
Hey!
Control, 7-L-19,
I need backup to my last...
[Static]
Damn it!
Hey!
Can anyone hear me?
[Banging on door]
[Cellphone clicks]
[Groans]
It's not funny.
Celina: Thanks for
letting me drive.
You know,
at the Academy,
they said it would be six months
before I got the chance.
[Breathes deeply]
Sorry. The... The smell
will pass soon.
No, it's alright.
I, uh... I know plenty of cops
who wear
a St. Christopher's medal...
uh, protection.
Mm.
Police are
a superstitious bunch.
What about you?
Do you believe in
that kind of thing or...?
Superstitions?
Mm-hmm.
No, no. Not really.
In high school, I, uh, didn't
wash my hockey jersey for a year
because of
a winning streak.
Oh, see, that's gross.
[Police radio chatter]
[Siren wails]
I didn't see this vehicle
commit a violation.
Why are we
pulling them over?
Something's wrong with it.
We're gonna have to be
a little more specific.
Officer Juarez, protocol is
we call it in first.
[Police radio chatter]
Was I going too fast,
Officer?
No, ma'am.
Ask for I.D.
Ma'am, I'd like to take a look
in your trunk.
Guess that's alright.
[Sighs]
[Trunk opens]
Uh, ma'am, that won't be necessary.
Officer Juarez,
come speak with me.
What's the probable cause?
There's something dark
coming from that trunk.
Dark?
Like an aura.
Officer Juarez,
we do not pull over vehicles
because they give us
the heebie-jeebies.
And we certainly do not search
trunks without probable cause.
That is a form of profiling,
and I won't have it.
But she consented, so I...
I don't care.
She's an elderly woman
who is clearly intimidated
by police officers.
You're taking advantage
of that fear.
Just look.
No.
I'm...
♪
That's blood.
I knew it.
♪
[Police radio chatter]
Alright, ma'am.
Thank you.
How is she?
Upset.
I tried to dust her off.
She still wants to file
a formal complaint.
Look, I've never had to say this
to a rookie before,
but you cannot pull someone over
for having a dark aura...
or any kind of aura.
Nolan, how could you let
your boot make a stop like that?
I'm sorry, sir.
The situation got away from me.
Okay, but what about the blood
in the trunk?
She says she has a grandson that
sometimes borrows the car.
He... Maybe he spilled something.
Look,
we'll collect a sample.
We'll test to see
if it's human.
If it is,
then we really have a problem.
Okay, but won't that mean
I was right?
The crime was committed,
so...
Yes, probably.
But since the evidence was found
during an illegal stop,
it's inadmissible in court.
It's the fruit
of a poisonous tree.
Nolan, think you can handle
taking this back to the station?
Sir.
You ever do anything
like that again,
not only will you
be disciplined,
you'll be
out of the LAPD.
You got it?
Yes, sir.
Now go apologize to that woman
and tell her she's free to go.
[Cellphone chimes]
Well, my catfish
just messaged me.
Said he wants a PS5,
or he's gonna release the photo.
That's it?
I mean, they are
really hard to find.
Okay.
Where's the drop?
Looks like his apartment.
So he's a dumbass. Great.
Alright,
we'll pick one up on the way.
Oh, uh...
I thought you weren't supposed
to negotiate with terrorists.
Well, he's not a terrorist.
He's an idiot.
But if we arrest him,
that photo becomes evidence.
Everyone at the station
sees it.
♪
Good thing I got a gamer connect
in K-Town.
Of course you do.
Lucy: Control, 7-L-19.
Do you copy?
[Static]
Oh!
It's gonna be fine.
This is fine.
They will do a welfare check
when I don't report in,
and this is fine.
Until then, I will read,
because there is
nothing else to do.
Wesley: Morning.
Hey. Need help again
with the copier?
No, no.
I've made peace with the fact
that it's possessed.
I was just dropping by
to see how you're doing.
You talked to Lucy.
Yeah.
I think the Dye-Hards thing
has spun her out.
Yeah.
That's why I didn't tell her
about it while she was away.
Yeah, I wish she'd just
believe me that I'm fine.
You probably don't know this
about me,
but I was stabbed a few years
ago at the courthouse.
What? No, uh, I didn't.
That's awful.
I'm telling you this
so that you know
that I've been
where you are.
All I wanted was for people
to stop seeing me as a victim.
Exactly.
My friends on the message board,
they don't treat me like that.
They see me as someone with
valuable insight into Rosalind.
And that must feel great.
It's like you're back in control
of your own narrative again.
But simply saying you're okay
doesn't make it so.
Just consider it.
I will.
Hey, if you're looking for
a community that understands
what you've been through,
you got Lucy and me.
Thanks.
I appreciate that.
Okay, man.
Sgt. Grey:
So why the hell was your rookie
driving in the first place?
That's how I was taught.
It's not standard practice.
Once you've been a T.O.
for a few years,
then you can get creative
with the guidelines.
On your first day,
stick to the damn script.
Yes, sir.
Where's Juarez now?
Writing up the report.
I want you to
triple check it.
All the paperwork surrounding
this needs to be immaculate,
so make sure she specifies
that she was unable
to articulate
the reason for the stop.
Yes, sir. I'll also be writing
up a blue page on her.
In it, you need to detail how,
as Juarez's T.O.,
how you plan to correct her
moving forward.
It may have been
her mistake,
but as her supervisor,
she's your responsibility.
♪
[Chuckles]
That can't be true.
Can it? I...
♪
Now, this user is making
sense... TruthHunter184.
"Don't give Rosalind
the satisfaction.
She eats her victim's pain
like a five-star meal."
♪
"Like a five-star meal."
Rosalind said that to Nolan.
Hey!
Can anybody hear me?!
[Grunts]
Yo,
I got what you asked for.
Pavi:
Drop it and leave.
[Muffled television chatter]
[Lock clicks]
[Door opens]
Hello.
Sergeant Bradford, LAPD.
Hi, uh, O-Officers.
What's up?
You're blackmailing me.
Do you have any idea
how serious of a crime this is?
I could charge you
with a felony.
Hold on, 'kay? I-I wasn't really
gonna release the... the photo.
I-I just...
just wanted the PS5.
My mom won't get me one.
Pavi's Mom: Pavi,
are you talking to me?
No, Mom. God!
Just stay out of it.
[Breathes shakily]
Oh, I think we should
get Mom out here.
No, whoa.
That's not necessary. No.
Then delete the photo. Now.
Okay. Alright. Yeah.
Deleting the photo. Okay.
See? It's gone.
And get rid of
the dating profile, too, okay?
It's messed up,
catfishing people.
Yeah, done.
Bad behavior
does not get a reward.
You do anything like that again,
I'll make sure your phone
and laptop are collected
as evidence.
You got it?
You suck. [Scoffs]
Sweet kid.
So, what's up?
We taking this back or...
Hell no.
Taking this home.
You know how hard it is
to find one of these?
[Telephone rings]
Harper.
Are you sure?
What?
Jill's blood was swabbed
from the trunk of a car
during a traffic stop.
Whose car?
Wait. They what?
Do you know
how dead to me you are?
The blood that you found
in the car belongs to a woman
who has been missing
for three days.
It is our only lead.
And... And now I hear
that it's a bad stop?
I know. I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
I'm...
His rookie. Which means that
you are his responsibility.
Nolan, I trained you
better than this.
And now you are both
making me look bad.
Lopez: I just got off the phone
with T.I.D.
When they went
to impound the car,
they took a preliminary look
and said the blood appears to be
only 10 to 12 hours old.
Jill could still be alive.
Oh, then we gotta
move quickly.
Not so fast.
I take it
you're Officer Juarez?
Yes, sir.
Wesley Evers
from the D.A.'s office.
Since the blood evidence
you found is inadmissible,
the LAPD will have
to figure out another way
to implicate your suspect
in this crime.
So we do have
a suspect?
Our missing person's
ex-boyfriend, Tyler Harvin.
The car belongs
to his grandmother.
She confirmed that
he has regular access to it.
So to nail this guy in court,
I need something concrete
tying him
to Jill's disappearance.
Without P.C.,
Carradine won't authorize
a surveillance detail
on Harvin.
But he did agree
to let me and Lopez
run foot surveillance ourselves.
If we can catch Tyler engaging
in suspicious activity,
Carradine said
he'd approve a full team.
You're gonna try and run foot
surveillance with two officers?
No, four. You and your rookie
are gonna start
digging your way
out of my doghouse by helping.
Remember, Harvin has
a history of violence.
Don't underestimate him.
I've got Harvin heading north
down Lake.
Black pants, blue ball cap,
light-blue shirt.
Nolan: Roger that.
Standing by.
Alright. I need you to focus on
what I'm about to say.
Everything you learned
at the Academy
goes out the window
the moment the adrenaline hits.
You have to keep thinking,
remain aware of your
surroundings at all times,
and avoid
any physical contact
unless someone's life
has been threatened.
Yes, sir.
Harper: I've got him.
♪
I'll pick you up
in the alley.
♪
Continuing west on Eleventh.
He just turned onto Grandview.
He's heading north.
That's us.
♪
[The Wrecks' "Get 'Em Ready"
plays]
♪
[Horn honks, tires screech]
He's running!
Which way?
Nolan: North on Grandview,
west side of the street.
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah, ah-ah, ah,
ah-ah, ah-ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah, ah-ah
♪ Get 'em ready, get 'em ready,
come on ♪
♪ Get 'em ready, get 'em ready
♪ Are you ready? Come on
Hey!
[Horn blares]
♪ Are you ready? Come on
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah, ah-ah, ah,
ah-ah, ah-ah, ah, ah *
* Hey, hey, hey, hey
Aaron: I can't believe my career
was almost ruined by a kid
whose mom still does
his laundry.
[Police radio chatter]
When was the last time
you heard Chen on the radio?
I can't remember. It was like
an hour ago, maybe two.
♪
Dispatch,
this is 7-Adam-100.
Can you perform a security
check on Officer Chen?
Dispatch:
Hold on, 7-Adam-100.
She's not responding.
When was last contact?
According to the logs,
it was over two hours ago.
Alright, that's a problem
we're gonna talk about later.
Right now, give me
her last known address.
Chen?
Chen!
Lucy: Yeah.
[Banging on door]
Yeah, I'm in here.
[Door rattles]
Hang on.
The door is stuck.
Yeah, no kidding.
You okay?
I-I think I have a lead
on Rosalind.
- What?
- How?
Chris has been spending time
on these message boards
filled with
armchair detectives
that are trying to
track Rosalind down.
You think one of them
found her?
I think one of them
is her.
I would add that it was
an error in judgment
that you will not repeat.
And this memorandum
is going to the Watch Commander?
Yeah. And then he will run it
up the chain of command.
Are they gonna wash me out?
It's a possibility.
You can be fired
for literally anything
in your probationary period.
But, on the other hand,
it's your first day.
Your failure
is more so on me.
Are they gonna find Jill
on time?
I hope so.
But you should prepare
for the worst.
No, she's still alive.
I can feel it.
The way you felt
the bad aura?
Yes.
Look, I-I know that
in the movies,
police seem to rely on
their intuitions
all the time
about a suspect.
In reality,
this is not the case.
What you see as intuition
is actually years
of hard-won knowledge
in how to interpret things
like body language.
It's not a mystical power.
It's observation.
And even then,
cops get it wrong all the time.
With all due respect,
reading someone's
body language sounds
just as mysterious
as my feelings.
That's because you don't have
the experience to back it up.
You sound just like
the old-school instructors
at the Academy,
going on about tradition
while conveniently leaving out
the dark side of that tradition.
I thought you wanted to be
a different kind of T.O.
Why can't I be
a different kind of cop?
Maybe one day you can be.
But first, you have to learn
the fundamentals.
But I was right
about the car.
Yes, you were.
And I bet you think it's unfair
that that stop was inadmissible.
But I want you to think about
what would happen
if the police were able to stop
people based on feelings alone.
Where do we draw the line
between a dark aura
and outright prejudice?
That's why the rule exists.
To protect people.
I don't see how the rules
are protecting Jill Baskin.
[Sighs]
♪
Hey.
Lucy.
Hey, what's going on?
They won't tell me.
Sit down.
Okay, so, um, I went through
"The Mother Doc,"
and I think
I found Rosalind.
What? Where?
That sighting in Rome?
N-No. I...
Are you familiar with
the username "TruthHunter184"?
Yeah.
Uh, he lives in Atlanta.
He doesn't?
Lucy found
some irregularities
in TruthHunter's
communication style,
so she asked us
to look into it.
I reviewed all of
TruthHunter's messages,
and I agree
with Officer Chen.
The forensic linguistics
are a match to Rosalind Dyer.
But... No, that doesn't
make any sense.
Do you remember when
TruthHunter wrote
Rosalind "eats her victim's pain
like a five-star meal"?
Yeah.
I heard Rosalind
use that exact phrase
to describe the pleasure
she took at her trial
when watching the agony
of her victims' families.
♪
I told her things about me,
about the investigation.
It's okay.
You didn't know.
Uh, so what do we do?
I can message her,
try to set up a meeting.
N-No. Uh, Rosalind will
see right through that.
I agree. With this level
of intelligent psychopath,
I would advise to err
on the side of caution.
So we work with
what we've got.
We get cyber crimes involved,
and we see if we can track her
using her I.P. address.
And if we find anything,
we promise to keep you
in the loop.
Thank you.
Yeah. Uh, thanks.
♪
Hey. Are you okay?
No.
I'm really not.
♪ Got the face on
like, "Oh, yeah" ♪
♪ In the mirror, looking like,
"Mm, yeah" ♪
♪ On the run like gym shoes,
steppin' on... ♪
Officer Nolan, I-I want
to apologize for yesterday.
Look,
I was upset that my mistake
may have put Jill
in further jeopardy,
and I unfairly took it out
on you.
I promise to do better.
I appreciate that.
I also thought about
our conversation.
I want you to trust me
with your feelings.
If you had confided in me
yesterday before the car stop,
we could have avoided
this whole mess.
So next time
you have an idea,
no matter how crazy,
tell me about it.
Oh, thank God.
Because I had
the wildest dream.
Okay, that's not exactly
what I...
No, you're right. I'm sorry.
Tell me your dream.
I was up half the night doing
a deep dive on Tyler Harvin.
When I finally fell asleep,
I-I dreamt that
I was on the beach
and a body
washed up on shore.
Jill Baskin?
No. It was a man.
A giant, actually.
Wearing an old-timey armor,
holding a big wooden shield
with a crown on it.
Okay.
And you think this knight
had something to do with
Jill's abduction?
I don't know.
But it was so vivid.
And I thought m-maybe Jill's
being kept near a beach.
Okay. Um...
You said you were looking into
Tyler when you fell asleep.
What exactly
did you find?
I was looking into
his work history.
I mean,
he does a lot of odd jobs
all over the city...
landscaping, contracting.
And I thought
one of these jobs
may have given him access
to a hiding place...
maybe somewhere
off a beaten path
where he might be
holding Jill.
Okay. Uh, were any of the jobs
near a beach?
Did any of them
have anything to do with
the name Knight
or Shield?
A company name?
Maybe a client?
Well, he finished work
a few weeks ago for a job
on a company called
A Royal Hand Construction.
And the house was on a street
called Beachwood Canyon.
Show me on Streetview.
See, Tyler could have seen
this condemned house
while he was
working here for Royal.
Your dream
wasn't a premonition.
It was just your subconscious
processing information.
So you don't think
I'm crazy?
I'm not saying that.
But I think we should do it...
take a look at that house before
we talk to Harper and Lopez.
You wanted to see me, sir?
That was Garza.
Their cyber crime people
traced the web
of Rosalind's I.P. addresses
to a house
outside Seattle.
They're putting together
a surveillance team
to go there now.
Agent Garza has
invited you to join.
Really?
That... That's amazing.
Yeah, I-I'm in.
Jet leaves in an hour.
Sir.
♪
What the hell?
Oh, good morning,
Cop Cake.
Aaron: Oh, man.
Yeah, I'm thinking we need to
pay our catfish another visit.
Damn straight.
Alright.
You take the east side.
I'll take the west.
And then
meet in the middle.
Copy.
Radio if you see anything.
Will do.
♪
Nolan, I found her.
East side of the house
at the window.
♪
Stand back.
Cleared.
Check her.
She's alive.
Alright.
Stay with her.
I'm gonna clear the house.
Hey, Jill.
My name is Celina.
Everything's gonna be alright.
Patrol, 7-Adam-15.
Show us at
6577 Beachwood Canyon,
abandoned house.
Found a female kidnap victim,
possibly Jill Baskin.
Multiple stab wounds.
Requesting R.A.
and additional units.
Police!
Is anyone in here?
Come out with
your hands up now.
Hey!
Nolan, I see him!
Stop!
♪
Nolan: What do you got?
Officer Juarez?
♪
Officer Juarez, check in.
Officer Juarez,
please respond.
♪
[Siren wailing]
Victim's in the bedroom.
Severe blood loss,
but her vitals are stable.
Copy that.
We're on it.
Officer Juarez,
do you copy?
♪
Celina, do you hear me?
[Engine starts]
♪
Celina: Police!
[Grunts]
[Breathing heavily]
♪
[Siren wailing]
Nolan: Officer Juarez, respond.
7-Adam, um, it's Juarez.
I had eyes on the suspect.
I'm in pursuit.
Celina, I'm coming to you.
Where are you?
I don't know.
Are you on the trail?
No. Uh...
I think we were heading east,
but we turned.
[Rustling]
I see him.
Does he have a weapon?
I can't tell.
Celina, I need you to focus
so I can find you.
He's on the move.
7-Adam-15, my rookie's
in pursuit of suspect,
but the specific location
is unknown.
I am heading northeast
on trail road,
requesting airship
and all available units
to help locate suspect
and Officer Juarez.
Code 3.
Juarez, talk to me.
I've lost visual.
I don't know where he went.
Look around you.
What do you see?
Just trees
and a footbridge.
No buildings, no signs?
I-I see one of those
electrical boxes.
Great. Does it have any kind of
identifier on it?
A serial number?
Uh...
Yeah.
198962.
Control, I need the location of
an L.A. City electrical box.
Serial number 198962.
Dispatch: Copy, 7-Adam-15.
Sending the location
to your box.
Okay, Celina, hang tight,
I got you.
Copy that.
♪
[Both grunting]
Celina? Celina?
Damn it, dispatch,
where is my airship?
I have an officer
in need of help.
♪
[Groans]
[Heart beating]
[Choking]
♪
[Coughing]
[Handcuffs click]
It's okay.
[Breathing heavily]
You're gonna be alright.
How is Officer Juarez?
[Door closes]
Shaken up.
A little bruised.
Nothing serious,
thank God.
Not a great start.
She'll bounce back.
I meant you.
I know.
If that suspect had gotten
her gun away from her...
These last few days
have been extremely humbling.
Everything is moving
a hundred miles an hour.
I feel like I barely have time
to teach her
the most basic things
before everything goes sideways.
Translation...
You feel like a rookie again.
Yeah.
Well, to her credit,
Celina managed to fight off
a guy twice her size
after sprinting up a canyon.
She's got spirit.
Maybe a little too much.
You know anything
about horses, Nolan?
I really don't, sir.
Have a seat.
Young racehorses are
skittish and excitable.
To calm them down, they partner
them with older horses
to teach them
how to check themselves.
Eventually,
they come around.
It's the natural order
of things.
Officer Juarez, a word?
I imagine that was a pretty
tough first case for you.
[Luke Hemmings'
"Starting Line" plays]
Sir.
Something wasn't adding up,
so I requested
your full personnel file.
You read about my sister.
Yeah.
Abducted from your yard
when you were 9 years old.
I can't even imagine
what you went through.
I was supposed
to be watching her,
and I looked away
for a minute.
And after three weeks
of no leads from the police,
my mom hired a psychic.
That's who found her,
not the cops.
Which is why you put
so much stock in intuition.
Mm-hmm.
I was wrong earlier
when I said you don't
have the experience
to back up
your gut instincts.
See,
I think you blamed yourself
for what happened
to your sister,
and that made you an extremely
observant 9-year-old girl
so that you'd never miss
seeing danger coming again.
And over the years, you funneled
all that input into your gut.
See, I think you saw the blood
on the bumper of that car,
and before you understood
what you saw,
you translated it
into a dark aura.
And your premonition dream
about Jill's whereabouts,
that came after a long night
of meticulous,
evidence-based research.
So does that mean you're...
you're not washing me out?
Correct.
But I don't have
a crystal ball.
I don't know yet
if you are going to be
a good police officer.
But I am willing to trust my gut
and give it another shot.
Thank you, sir.
I won't let you down.
I'll see you tomorrow.
You know, if you ever need
a crystal ball,
you can always
borrow mine.
Kidding.
Good night,
Officer Juarez.
Good night.
♪
Alright, so here's the deal, Pavi.
I filled out the paperwork
charging you with a felony,
and I will file it today
unless you start using
your skills to help people.
And how much
does that pay?
Nothing.
But then again,
neither does prison.
I'm listening.
Alright, so, we have a friend
who has a community center
and he needs a volunteer to help
teach a computer literacy class
to the neighborhood.
You keep your nose clean,
you show up twice a week,
I'll shred these.
Otherwise, I've got
up to 18 months
to file your felony paperwork
with the D.A.
I thought you were gonna
take away all my electronics.
I was.
Lucky for you, Officer Thorsen
believes in second chances.
Just take the deal, kid.
Pavi's Mom: Pavi, why is there
a police car parked outside?
Okay. Alright. I-I'm in.
Just text me the details.
♪ Maybe they were never mine
♪ The walls are closin'
We did good.
♪
♪ The walls are closin'
[Police radio chatter]
Officer Chen? I'm Agent Miller
from the Seattle field office.
Nice to meet you, sir.
What do we know?
House belongs to
a Phyllis and Raymond Haymen.
Friends and family haven't
heard from them in over a week,
but their car's
in the driveway.
Any movement inside?
None. We can hear their phones
ringing inside,
but no one
ever answers them.
Well,
something's not right.
We were thinking
the same thing.
♪
FBI! Open up!
We have a warrant
to search these premises.
♪
Look at that.
- Captions by VITA...