Previously on
"The Rookie"...
Isabel.
I've been trying to find you.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
That was my wife.
- You were a nurse?
- No, a cop.
Narcotics.
Hi, it's Skip Tracer Randy.
I'm a bounty hunter now.
Promise you'll call me
if you get into any trouble.
Of course.
- Weird guy.
- Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
[coughing]
Bailey?
[sighing]
[gasps]
Ooh.
Are you okay?
Why is alcohol?
You and Libby really
tore it up, didn't you?
I didn't even hear you
come in last night.
I'm officially too old
to do shots.
How many did you do?
- Which bar?
- Yikes.
Well, maybe
you should think about
not trying to relive
your college days.
It is all Libby wants to do.
She says it makes the other
360 days of diaper changing
more tolerable.
Like tonight, she wants to go
to some underground party
where a van picks you up
on a street corner
and blindfolds you.
Yeah, that's not a party.
That's a...that's a kidnapping.
Just tell her
you don't want to go.
- I can't.
- Why not?
[gasps] Dude.
Last night was so much fun.
Oh, thanks again
for letting me crash here.
But don't tell Roger
if he calls.
I'm using the hotel allowance
to upgrade our festivities.
Why are you down there?
- Oh.
I'm, um...I'm just posing
for this photography project
that I'm working on.
It's like...it's like
the disconnect
between beauty and, um...
Aging.
Not aging.
Consumerism.
Fun.
Well, I'm gonna go for a run.
Do you wanna come?
Yeah, of course.
Just let me put my clothes on.
I'll be right there.
♪ ♪
You are in no shape
to go running.
I can't let her beat me.
That is a super mature attitude.
[sighs]
Shut up and hold my hair.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
[groans]
Oh. You had the clams.
♪ I'm gonna win for you like
I know you want me to do ♪
[sizzling]
That looks good.
Mm, thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
[clears throat]
There are other rooms
in the apartment for that.
I thought
you were sleeping in today.
No classes.
- I was,
but then I was pulled
out of my slumber
by the smell of pancakes.
Yeah? You want some?
One or two?
- Uh, three, please.
[doorbell rings]
- Three.
No, wait. Um, shoot.
Totally forgot.
Um...
Isabel, uh, texted me.
She's in town
and needed to talk,
so I...I just told her
to come here.
I hope that's okay.
Oh, yeah, um...[laughs]
Of course.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
I meant to tell you after
you got out of the shower,
but you know,
I got in the shower, and...
Stop.
Oh, please, stop.
I'll get it.
- [quietly] Sorry.
- It's okay.
Hi. You must be Isabel.
I'm Tamara.
- Hey.
Hey.
Look at you. You look great.
Oh, thanks.
Amazing what a few years
of sobriety does for the skin.
It's nice to see you again, Lucy.
Thanks for letting me
crash your breakfast.
No, no, not at all.
Um, can I get you something?
Wouldn't say no
to some coffee.
Okay.
Come over here.
[sighs]
- When did you get in?
- A few hours ago.
Is that the Isabel?
The ex-wife, Isabel?
Stop. You're so loud.
Yes.
Tim invited her here?
That's weird, right?
No.
I mean, it's totally fine.
It's...
It's a little weird.
I'm going to do
a little digging.
- No.
- Yes, I am.
Tamara, seriously, don't.
So is everything okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine,
but I need your help.
I worked a UC assignment
eight years ago,
before I fell from grace,
infiltrating the Teska family.
Oh, I know all about 'em.
Yeah, they're big time
in Sylmar.
Guns, drugs, prostitution.
Yeah, back in the day,
they were up-and-comers,
but they had big ambitions.
The boss was Frank.
He had a 10-year-old daughter, Dara.
Great kid. Super bright.
I'm sure you took her
under your wing.
Yeah. I mean, someone had to.
He was a single dad.
Barely paid any attention
to her.
I was part of the crew,
so I was at the house
all the time,
and we became close...
in that weird way you do
when you're pretending
to be someone else.
But after we arrested her dad,
I scattered, you know,
left that identity behind,
and went on to the next case.
I hadn't heard from her
in eight years.
Until now.
Yeah,
I had a answering service
through the department
as a firewall
between that life
and my real one.
Last night, they forwarded me
a message from Dara.
Nikki, it's Dara.
I know it's been forever.
I don't even know
if you still check this,
but I'm scared,
and I didn't know who to call.
Sorry. This was dumb.
I shouldn't have...
[tires screeching]
I have to go.
I called her back
a few hours later.
No answer.
Ran a quick social media check.
Reached out to her friends.
No one's seen her.
And you can't go
knocking on doors
in the old neighborhood
'cause you're out of cover.
Exactly.
No, why don't you
come down to the station?
I'll get a warrant
for her phone.
We'll find her.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
[pen clatters]
[phone ringing]
[grunting]
[sighing]
Well, that's where
that lives now.
I got it.
[clears throat]
Show-off.
You can start maternity leave
at any time.
[sighs] Too many open cases.
I'll take my leave
in a couple weeks.
All right.
[phone ringing]
Are you sure you're okay?
I have to pee
every five minutes,
there's a stabbing pain
in both my hips,
and I barely sleep,
but I am glowing, right?
Radiant.
Thorsen.
You're assigned
to Detective Lopez
as her personal aide
until further notice.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Don't thank me yet, son.
Officer Thorsen,
at your service.
What you need?
Honestly?
Antacids. Like, a lot.
I bought this on my way in
to work this morning.
You know, I don't think
you're supposed to take
that many.
Antacids it is.
Need anything else
while I'm out?
No.
Uh, yes.
Canned Chilorio, Sinaloa style.
I don't think
canned meat's gonna help
with your indigestion.
♪ ♪
On it. Yeah.
- And a cherry soda.
- Got it.
♪ ♪
What?
It's weird to be back.
Yeah, well, at least it's
under better circumstances.
Much.
Bradford.
Welcome back.
Isabel?
- Hey, Smitty.
I almost didn't recognize you
without the, uh...
Greasy hair and track marks?
[chuckles] No.
I was gonna say the badge.
Good to see you.
"Welcome back"?
Were you on vacation?
No, I was on leave
for a shooting.
I just got cleared.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Well, mostly.
Lucy thinks
I should start meditating.
- [laughs]
- I know, right?
The famous Isabel.
Yeah.
You ever work with her?
No, but I knew of her,
first as a rock star UC,
then as a cautionary tale.
Why is she back?
Uh, and old case.
You okay with that?
Why wouldn't I be?
It's not a big deal.
I mean, he...he's over her.
I know that.
Just making sure you do.
Totally. I...stop it.
So I did a deep dive
on Isabel.
♪ ♪
Yeah...what deep dive?
The one we talked about.
I'm pretty sure she's single,
and she's working with
a police officer
support network in Santa Fe
while she gets a degree
in social work.
See? I mean, it sounds like
she's built
a whole new life for herself.
This is amazing.
- Sure.
Or she wants Tim to see
she's doing well.
♪ ♪
He did say she looked good.
Look, it...okay.
Why, then,
would she agree to meet
and his new girlfriend's
apartment?
Keep your enemies close.
I'm just saying.
Tamara...[scoffs]
Chen, let's move.
Dara's uncle's on his way in.
Goodbye.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Where's your boot?
- Oh.
Grey gave her a personal day.
Rookies don't get
personal days.
Well, I guess if anyone
deserves an exception,
it is Juarez. [chuckles]
Side note...got something.
Bailey has a friend from
college visiting us right now.
Oh, let me guess.
They are partying
like it's 1999.
I have never seen Bailey
so hungover.
I have a friend like that.
She texts me every Friday night
at midnight
to ask me what I am up to
as if I do not have
babies at home.
All right, so when does
Princess Bad News leave?
Tomorrow, which is good.
[cell phone ringing]
I don't think Bailey's liver
can take another day.
Oh.
[cell phone ringing]
Do not answer that. Oh, you...
Randy, is this another
butt dial?
Nyla Harper, you jokester.
I would never dial you
with my buttocks.
No, I actually have a teensie,
tinsie frage for you.
Hypothetically,
when is trespassing a crime?
Always.
But what if you're trying
to help somebody?
Randy, I don't know how
to make this any clearer.
Do not trespass.
Okie-dokies.
Danke schoen, my wisest friend.
What was that about?
I hope to never find out.
Thanks for coming in.
I'm Sergeant Bradford.
We got a call this morning
about your niece Dara.
Ugh,
Ed always gave me the creeps.
He used to talk
directly to my chest.
- What did you do?
- Nothing.
I was trying to get a foothold.
I needed him to like me.
Said she seemed to be
in a bit of distress last night
and hasn't been able
to get in touch with her since.
I haven't seen her
since yesterday morning.
She's 18; she comes and goes
as she pleases.
What friend was this?
I've got her name
written down over at my desk.
Um, listen.
What I'm trying
to figure out here...
can you think of any place
that Dara might like
to hang out?
A boyfriend's house?
Not that I know of.
You sure this isn't just
an excuse to jam me up,
business I'm in?
No, sir. No.
This is purely a welfare check
on your niece.
You know, her dad gets
out of prison tomorrow.
What's his relationship like
with her?
Any strife
about him coming home?
Nah, nah.
We're excited to have him back.
Gonna throw a party.
That's great.
You did bring up your business.
I mean, is there any chance
that could be connected
to her disappearance?
Look, you...
you keep saying "disappeared."
She's probably just
sleeping one off
at a...at a friend's house.
Of course. Yeah.
Well, listen,
if you hear from her,
uh, please give me a call.
[tense music]
Okay?
♪ ♪
This way, Mr. Teska.
Any chance we can get
a warrant on his phone?
Not based on
what we have so far.
You should talk to Frank,
see if it's all one big,
happy family like Ed said.
♪ ♪
Hey, I need
a surefire hangover remedy.
Uh, pickle juice.
[cell phone ringing]
Harper says pickle juice.
Thank you.
- What now?
Hypothetically, if a person
did end up trespassing
and then found a dead body...
Whoa. Dead or murdered?
Uh, hypothetically murdered.
♪ ♪
Okay, look.
Whatever you do,
do not touch it.
[gasps]
In fact,
don't touch anything.
Oh!
Especially if it looks like
it was related to the crime.
[squeaking]
Ah! [gasps]
♪ ♪
Uh, h...
h-hypothetically,
if I, uh, fell
in the man's blood...
Okay, seriously,
what is going on?
Randy broke into
someone's house,
found a murdered man,
and then fell in his blood.
Hypothetically.
[door bangs]
- Police!
Show me your hands!
- Right there.
- Nyla, I have to go.
Don't move.
[machine beeps]
Cut it out.
[buzzer blares]
Oh, there you are!
Meine bestest freunde.
- Hey, Randy.
- You know this nutjob?
I do, which is why
I need to ask for a favor.
[buzzer blares]
Let me take over this case.
Oh, forget it.
Easiest solve I ever had.
I'm not just gonna
hand it to you.
Yeah, he didn't do it.
Like hell, he didn't.
We have been communicating
with him all day.
This is just a really bad case
of wrong place, wrong time.
Oh, no, no, no.
I am excellent with time.
I'm German.
- Randy.
You're not helping.
Please.
Look, in exchange, I will take
something else
off of your plate.
What...what's a case that has
been giving you grief?
[buzzer blares]
NoHo Doe.
- [inhales sharply]
- Mm.
Ooh, that sounds fun.
What's a NoHo Doe?
A torso found in a vacant lot
with no definitive
cause of death,
no witnesses,
and no way to ID him.
You give us this case,
I will take NoHo Doe.
[suspenseful music]
Deal.
Dieter's all yours.
It's Randy.
Dieter was my uncle.
He is not
a very good detective.
What's up, guys?
What's the haps?
Randy, we need you
to tell us everything
about why you were in
this house.
Don't answer that.
What are you doing here?
Representing my client.
Monica is your lawyer?
How do you two
even know each other?
He's helped me track down
a few...
hard to locate witnesses.
Oh, yeah,
that guy was hard to find,
but no one hides
from the fingers
of Skip Tracer Randy.
Look,
we're just treating Randy
as a witness in this case,
not as a suspect.
We just want him to tell us
what he knows.
That's fine,
as long as I'm present.
[buzzer blares]
- [sighs]
My freedom's been restored.
What should I do with
this second chance at life?
Eat a ghost pepper?
Oh, declare my secret love
to an unsuspecting friend?
Definitely not the last one.
Oh, just the ghost pepper, then.
- Okay, so what's next?
- [sighs]
Interdepartmental meeting.
I've been looking forward to it
all morning.
The chairs are super comfy,
and the donuts are heaven.
I mean, you could always
just buy yourself donuts.
Free donuts taste better.
[phone chiming, buzzing]
[clears throat]
Oh, crap.
What?
They switched the location.
To where?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Oh.
I can do this. [sighs]
- Yeah, you can do this.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
[groaning]
I can't do this.
Okay, you know what?
How 'bout I just go
and grab you a donut
and I can FaceTime you
in the meeting?
Deal.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[sighs]
You know what?
Uh... I got you.
Yeah.
- I met her at a bar.
- Met who?
The woman who hired me.
To do what?
Randy, just pretend
like we don't know anything.
Right. Okay.
So a bar is a place
where people...
I'm giving him back
to Scanlon.
Hold on.
Randy, I know linear thinking
is difficult,
but try.
Emily Johnson.
She'd read online about my fame
as a skip tracer bounty hunter
and asked to meet me.
- At a bar.
- Exactly. Yeah.
She told me she was being
stalked by a man
named Nelson Friske,
and would I scare
the bejesus out of him?
I don't know who is
this "BeJesus,"
but is he, like,
from the sequel?
Uh, yes.
Okay, so you showed up
at Nelson Friske's house,
and he was already dead?
Oh, as a dormouse.
Who exactly is Nelson Friske?
A 43-year-old day trader
with a prolific side hobby
of being an internet troll.
Oh, so potentially
dozens of suspects.
Yes, which is why
we need to find
this Emily Johnson.
Do you have a phone number
for her?
- Yeah, I can send to you.
- Great.
Now you go home.
- [huffs] But why?
I want to be with you guys,
my partners.
Sorry, Randy, you're just
too close to this one.
So I think, legally,
it's best for you
just to sit at home and wait
for us to unravel this mystery.
He's right. Go home.
Stay out of trouble.
[sighs] Of course,
because trouble
is not my middle name.
It's actually Randy.
Randy Randy.
Yeah. If anyone cares.
So how long
you been dating Lucy?
- A few months.
- Mm.
Are you seeing anyone?
I was, and then I wasn't.
And then I wa...
you know the drill.
They were nice.
It just...
you set the bar really high.
[video call ringing]
Here we go.
- [clears throat]
- Frank Teska.
I'm Sergeant Tim Bradford.
I'm in charge
of locating your daughter.
She's missing.
- What do you mean, missing?
You talk to my brother, Ed?
- I did.
He said he hasn't seen her
since yesterday.
Has she been in contact
with you at all?
[sighs] Not recently.
I get a card at Christmas.
Not for Father's Day, though.
Can't say I blame her.
Can you think of anywhere
she might go
when she's upset?
I don't know.
I mean, who'd go after Dara?
She's never hurt anyone.
Yeah, I mean, you've made
a lot of powerful enemies.
Is there any chance
someone's trying
to get to you through her?
No one would dare.
Okay.
Well, if you think of anything.
She's a good kid.
[sniffs]
She deserves better than...
Find her.
Yeah, we're doing
everything we can.
Yeah. Thanks.
How long
till he makes the call?
[radio beeps]
- Sergeant, I have the tap
on that call
from the prison to Ed Teska.
Patch it through.
Where the hell's
my daughter?
Police are telling me
she's missing.
Relax.
She's a teenager.
She'll turn up.
When I'm out of here tomorrow,
you and I are gonna
have to have a talk.
I'm hearing things,
and I'm not happy.
Stop listening
to the rumors.
People are trying
to come between us.
Don't let 'em.
Find my kid.
[line clicks]
Well, maybe
Ed's telling the truth.
Maybe he doesn't know
where Dara is.
Maybe, but he is
a professional liar.
He once had Frank convinced
someone greenlit a hit on him.
Had him running
from his shadow.
The motel.
What?
When Frank thought
he'd been greenlit,
he told me to take Dara
somewhere safe
while he dealt with it.
We stayed at a motel
by the beach.
Maybe she's there.
Okay.
So the number Randy gave us
for Emily was a fake.
Well, then I'm guessing
her name was fake too.
Well, if she is
one of Nelson's victims,
a fake name would make sense.
She wouldn't want us
to track her
through her online communications.
But then why involve Randy?
To create reasonable doubt?
I mean, it wouldn't even
have to be a good frame job
in order for it to work.
All her lawyer would have to do
is point to the 6'4" German man
found at the crime scene
covered in the victim's blood.
[cell phone ringing]
Oh, speaking of.
Huh.
Tell me you are at home.
Are you familiar with
the Britney Spears classic
"Oops!...I Did It Again"?
[sirens wailing]
Uh, I have to go.
I'll see you
back at the station.
Let me see your hands!
Again.
Hey, friends.
Randy, you're making it
very difficult
for us to not prosecute you.
I was just trying to help
you guys find the real killer.
If you find a lead,
just text us.
The good news is, we know
that fake Emily's real name
is Ariel Riser.
Uniforms found
$5,000 in cash
in her bedroom,
along with a note
that had your phone number
on it.
Mm, so someone paid her
to frame my client
and then killed her
to cover their tracks?
Yes, that is
what it looks like.
But the question is, why Randy?
Was he just a patsy,
or does our killer hold
a grudge against him too?
Why would anyone have
a grudge
against Skip Tracer Randy?
Everybody loves me.
- Right.
But pretending they don't,
why don't you give us a list
of all your bounties
and skip traces
from the past five years?
Hopefully, one of the names
on that list
will match one
of Nelson's victims,
and we will have our killer.
Great,
and I will start looking
at Nelson's social media.
No, you will not.
You will get us that list,
and then you will go home.
Randy, as your lawyer,
I'm begging you to stay there.
God, you are no funs.
You are zero with the funs.
You're like a monkey
allergic to bananas.
Please remind me
why we had to drive
all the way to this
specific coffee cart
instead of the one
five minutes from my bed.
Because they have
a liquor license,
and it...
[quietly] Hi.
Oh, hang on.
Please tell me we did not come
all the way here
so you could meet up
with some guy.
What?
We've been chatting online,
and he asked if we could meet.
Is that why you came to LA?
No!
Oh, come on, Bails, please.
I need this.
- What about your husband?
- Ugh, whatever.
Roger's in love
with his physical therapist.
[sighs]
Okay, fine.
- Yes.
But I'm staying here
with you.
I'm not having you get murdered
by some random man
you met on the internet.
[squeals] You are the best.
Grab us some margaritas?
Dara and I stayed here
for a week.
We ate junk food,
swam in the ocean,
danced on the bed.
I know it doesn't sound
like much,
but when you're spending
every second of the day
on high alert, waiting
for it all to go sideways,
it...it feels good
just to breathe.
I get it...
'cause I held my breath
every time you left
on a long-term assignment.
And then you'd come home, and...
And I'd still be gone
in my head,
no matter how much
I wanted to be there with you.
Anyway, um, so is that escape
why you think
Dara will come here?
[sighs] I don't know.
I could be projecting.
It just...she was scared.
She...she called me
for a reason.
Maybe it's 'cause
this is where she felt safe.
Okay, well,
if she does come here,
you're gonna need backup,
all right?
You're not a cop anymore...
no gun, no badge...
so Lucy's on her way here.
I can't believe, after
everything I put you through,
you're dating another UC.
I know.
[laughs]
But Lucy's different.
She isn't a junky in waiting?
You know
that is not what I meant.
I know, I just...
seeing you again brings it all
back up, you know?
I do.
I still have not
been able to find
a connection between Friske
and Randy.
What about you?
Uh, no, but I did make a list
of all the people
that Friske was trolling
who seem most likely
to kill him.
Who's at the top?
Brian Cole.
He is an accountant
from Glendale.
Friske hacked Cole's
dead wife's ClipTalk account
to send him taunting messages.
- That's sick.
- Yeah.
But he has an airtight alibi.
Next on the list are
a chef in Venice
whose restaurant closed
after Friske posted
a wave of fake reviews
and a gym owner in Hollywood
who lost his wife
after Friske leaked DMs
he'd sent to a female employee.
- Mm.
- Hey, Nolan.
You're fiancée's here.
- Oh, great. Uh, reception?
- Holding.
Just got brought in
for being drunk in public.
Mm.
Excuse me.
Uh, hey, why haven't you
arrested Randy yet?
He's been found
at two murder scenes.
Okay, I know from the outside
it doesn't make any sense...
To the DA, it looks like
you took Scanlon's case
to help out a friend.
Tell the DA
to come say that to my face.
Look, I know that's not
what's happening here,
but if you don't make some
headway on a new suspect soon,
the DA's talking about
going over your head.
All right.
Thanks for the heads up.
Of course. Where's Angela?
Uh, lunch.
Again.
Again. [chuckles]
[buzzer blares]
- Thank you.
Hey.
- [sighs]
- What happened?
Libby took me on her date
with a guy she met
on the internet.
He turned out to be a creep.
She started throwing fists
and ran away
when the cops showed up.
Okay, I'm starting to think
that maybe
Libby isn't the greatest friend
to have around.
I know.
[cell phone ringing]
I'm just so tired,
and I just really want
to go home and sleep.
I'm so sorry. Um...
Randy, this really isn't
a good time.
John, I found the killer!
I'm in the trunk of his car
right now!
Randy combed through
Friske's troll accounts
and came to the same conclusion
I did.
Brian Cole is a prime suspect.
Except for the fact that
Cole has an airtight alibi.
Exactly,
but Randy didn't know that.
So he went to Brian's house
to "gather evidence,"
and...[scoffs]
Hid in the trunk of Brian's car
when Brian came out
to take out the trash,
and now he's stuck in there.
Kay.
Is that the car?
- That's him.
[siren wailing]
Okay, we gotta get him
out of there on the DL.
Otherwise,
the DA is gonna flip out,
have the case reassigned,
and throw the book at Randy.
I might have an idea.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
How you doing, sir?
Uh, good afternoon, Officer.
License and registration, please.
So we received a call
saying that you swerved
over the double yellow line.
Have you been drinking today, sir?
- Absolutely not.
- Okay, great.
Can you step out of the car, please?
[clears throat]
- Sure.
Front of the car.
I'm gonna give you
a little field sobriety test.
Oh, that's not necessary.
Stand on your left foot, please.
[quirky music]
Yep. Ah, ah, ah.
Eyes on me, sir.
Can you recite the alphabet backwards,
only saying every other letter?
♪ ♪
Um... uh, Z...
- Uh-huh.
- X...
[whispering]
Wow, this is exciting.
Shh. Stay down.
Noted.
♪ ♪
[shushing]
- V...
- Yeah.
T...
- Leg up, please.
- Oh, higher?
Yeah. P...
- Yeah.
- Uh...
- All right.
Thank you.
Does that...
does that mean I can go?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, drive safe out there.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
Wow, that was thrilling!
I felt like Thomas Cruise
in "Missions Impossible."
Do you have any idea
how stupid that was?
- No.
- We already
looked into this guy.
He had nothing to do
with the murder.
Okay,
I know you want to help,
but involving yourself
with this case
will only give the prosecution
more ammunition
against you at trial.
Wait, does this mean
I have to go home again?
Oh, absolutely not. No.
Obviously,
you cannot be trusted
to stay out of trouble,
so you are coming with us.
Whoo-hoo! Reunited partners!
[upbeat music]
Uh, when am I issued
a service weapon?
Oh, my God.
Oh, here she is.
All right,
be careful out there, okay?
You haven't seen Dara
in eight years.
You don't know
what she's gotten herself into.
She's not a kid anymore.
And it's been a minute
since you've done this.
Yes, sir.
Always the protector.
- You wired up?
- Yeah.
The receiver's in my car.
Hey. Thanks for helping out.
Yeah, of course.
You have a history
that might work here?
I've got a backstory
that puts me
in Chowchilla for two years.
Let's go with that
if we have to,
say we met there.
Done.
I gotta admit,
I was hoping to, uh,
pick your brain a bit.
[chuckles]
[static crackling]
You want to know
my cheat codes for dating Tim?
[laughing] What? No!
- [laughs]
- No.
I've got him all figured out.
[static crackling]
No, I wanted to ask you
about your time undercover.
I mean, you are a legend.
- Hmm.
The cases you closed,
the people you put away.
I know it didn't end
the way you wanted.
No, it, uh...it didn't.
I'm sorry.
I...
I guess
what I'm trying to ask is,
with all the bad things
that can and did happen,
um...
You want to know
if it was worth it?
[soft music]
Yeah.
Yeah, um...
honestly, I...
I can't answer that.
Mm.
Being undercover derailed
my entire life.
I...I lost my husband,
my job, my self-respect.
Almost lost my life.
But I...I can't put all that
on being a UC.
Plenty of people make it out
without becoming
a full-blown addict.
There were just...
there were things
from my past that...
anyway, I, um...
from what Tim tells me,
you have much healthier
coping mechanisms.
Being a UC is hard.
You have to keep secrets
from the people
that are closest to you,
and you live in this constant
state of fight or flight.
That wears on your
relationships no matter what,
but if you go in
with your eyes open
and you're prepared
to make those sacrifices,
your experience might be
different than mine.
♪ ♪
I hope it is.
Yeah, unis brought
this guy in.
He's suspected of attacking
his boss with a bat.
Suspect wore a ski mask,
no DNA,
but the boss is convinced
it's him.
So we need a confession.
That would be ideal.
[sighs]
Good afternoon, Mr. Hayden.
I just have a few questions,
and we'll have you out of here
as soon as possible.
I didn't do anything.
Hold that thought.
[grunts]
- What's wrong?
- Gotta pee.
["Get Loose" playing]
♪ We got a good thing
going on tonight ♪
[breathes deeply]
Where were you
at the time of the attack?
Uh, the bathroom.
♪ We got them good vibes ♪
♪ That's how we choose
to live ♪
♪ We walk a fine line 'tween
proper and provocative ♪
Again?
♪ Like your boy Bobby says,
that's my prerogative ♪
♪ Girl,
what's your blood type ♪
♪ Always B positive ♪
♪ Get loose, get right ♪
♪ We got a good thing going ♪
Did anyone see you?
♪ ♪
Um, I'm not...
[belching]
♪ My body's talking ♪
Sorry. Never get pregnant.
I'm basically disgusting
24/7 now.
♪ But I'm catwalking ♪
♪ I'm striking
like lightning ♪
♪ My fire be frightening ♪
Should I call somebody
to take over?
Nah, I got him
right where I want him.
♪ Get loose, get right ♪
[laughs] Okay.
♪ Get right ♪
[snoring]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ ♪
How would you characterize
your relationship
with your boss?
♪ ♪
Uh... uh, normal.
I mean,
you know how bosses can be.
[sighs] Hold that thought.
I have to pee again.
It was me!
I attacked him.
He called me an idiot,
so I went and got a bat.
Just please
let me out of this room!
Great. Let me get some paper
so we can write up
your statement.
Mm.
How 'bout I get it?
[sighs]
♪ ♪
♪ We got a good thing
going on tonight ♪
The Venn diagram
of the people Randy knows
and the people he annoys
is a circle.
Yeah, but who did he annoy
enough to want him dead?
That's the tricky part.
Wh...hey, did we say
you could get up?
It is so boring over there.
I think I could be
more helpful here...
[phone chiming]
Working the case
with my partners.
Where do we start?
Randy, who just texted you?
Oh, it's from
my friend Cooper.
Cooper Logue? He owns a gym?
Ja! You know the Coops?
Is that the guy
that Nelson doxed
for sexting his employees?
Yes.
Randy, what did he text you?
Oh.
Oh, just a hilarious
indoor joke.
Yeah, Randy,
that's the symbol for death.
He's actually threatening you.
Oh, no, that is ridiculous.
We play pickleball together.
He sends me this emoji
to let me know
that I killed it on the court.
He is such a good sport.
I've defeated him,
I think, 21 times in a row,
and he does not mind at all.
[quirky music]
Oh.
- Mm.
I see now.
Context is very important.
♪ ♪
I think Cooper Logue
is the one who wants me dead.
Randy, I think
you might be right.
Do you know
where we can find him?
- I do.
- The only problem is,
we don't have any hard evidence
tying him to either murder.
What if he tried to kill me?
Hmm? I will be your decoy duck.
No, Randy, we can't do that.
Oh, come on. Just say yes.
I will go there,
get him all riled up,
say provocative things,
get his angry juices flowing.
No need.
I think you can just
be yourself.
Oh, really?
You think that would do it?
I got a great feeling
about this.
♪ ♪
There he is.
I wouldn't have pegged him
for a pickleball guy,
but all right.
- You ready to do this?
Ready.
Really think
he'll take the bait?
Hey, Cooper!
Ready for Randy
to hand you your hintern again?
Yeah! What's up, man?
I'm gonna treat you
like Seabiscuit ri...
Oh.
Well, there's your answer.
♪ ♪
Hey, drop the German!
Put the German down!
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, you get the issue
with the wire sorted out?
Yeah, we're all good.
It got disconnected somehow.
[chuckles]
- [clears throat]
- Check, one, two.
- All right, got you.
There's Dara.
Babe, we gotta go.
Time for you
to put Nikki back on.
Let's see if I still got it.
[clears throat]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Hey, it's Nikki.
Look at you.
You're all grown up.
I didn't think
you'd actually come.
Well, I'm here.
You gonna let us in?
- Who's she?
- Amber.
Nik brought me for, uh...
emotional support.
Your message made it sound
like things were poppin' off.
Thought we could use
some backup.
So how do you guys know
each other?
I did a stint in Chowchilla.
That's where you've been
all these years?
For part of it.
Listen, I know I left
without saying goodbye,
but when your old man
got busted,
I had to bounce, or I would've
been picked up too.
I didn't have a choice.
Right.
Everyone else gets to leave,
and I get left behind.
What's going on, D?
Why'd you call the old number?
[sighs]
My dad's getting out tomorrow,
and last night,
I heard my uncle
talking about taking him out
so he doesn't have to
hand back the crown.
[line ringing]
Hey, it's Bradford.
- What's up?
- We found the kid.
She says Ed Teska ordered
a hit on his brother.
I'll alert the prison,
get him put in solitary
until he's released.
Hey, four shooters just
showed up at the motel.
I need backup, code 3.
[line ringing]
- Hey, what's up?
- Four shooters just landed.
You got less than a minute.
Two are going in the front,
two are going around back.
They're here.
- Who?
- How many?
Four.
Tim says we've got 60 seconds.
Who's Tim?
Is there a back window,
someplace you can escape to?
There's a balcony,
but we're on the second floor.
What the hell is going on?
Who are you talking to?
Put me on speaker. Look.
If you get caught up in there,
it's a fatal funnel.
What else you got?
- I say we take the hallway.
Do a feigned retreat
to the south.
Dynamic entry
on opposing adjacent rooms.
Take long angles.
Wedge out and post up
until backup arrives.
But I'm gonna need a weapon.
That's not bad. Lucy?
Yeah, I can do that.
How long until backup arrives?
Backup's en route.
What the hell is going on?
Who the hell are you
with this...
this "hallway, wedge, post"
crap?
We're cops.
I'm retired.
She's active current.
You were undercover?
I know it's a lot, but I...
You're the reason
my dad was sent to prison!
You lied to me!
- Dara, please.
I can explain, but right now,
we need to focus on getting...
Hey!
[dramatic music]
[gunshots]
- Get back!
♪ ♪
Get back here!
[sirens wailing]
♪ ♪
[woman shrieking]
[gunshot]
[grunting]
[sirens wailing]
[panting]
♪ ♪
Hold still!
It's okay, all right?
We got you. You're safe now.
All right? It's okay.
Hey, I thought you weren't
leaving till tomorrow.
I changed my flight.
A car will be here any moment.
Oh. Car? I can just take you.
That's not necessary.
Is something wrong?
I have something
I need to talk to you about,
but I just don't know how.
How long
have we been friends?
You can say
whatever you want to me.
I think you might have
a drinking problem.
[upbeat dance music]
I might have
a drinking problem?
Listen, I've done my best
to keep up
on these yearly visits,
but I'm a mom of two now,
and I just don't
have it in me anymore.
I don't know how you manage
with all of your jobs
and hobbies,
but I'm afraid
you might be an alcoholic.
[phone chiming]
Oh, that's my ride.
I hope you're not mad,
and I hope that you take
what I said to heart.
Oh, I heard every word.
Why don't we take next year off
and just give me a little time
to get my life together
and things?
I'm proud of you.
Yeah.
[upbeat dance music]
♪ ♪
Oh, guys.
That was so much fun.
Not by my definition,
but you do you.
No, actually...yeah.
Stop...stop doing you.
And stop accepting jobs
that break the law
or put you in danger, please,
for all of our sakes.
I will... as soon as I help
this mysterious
and glamorous widow discover
who dumped her husband's body
in the reservoir.
[laughs]
Wow, I joshed you good.
That's the plot to "Chinatown,"
a classic film.
Want to come over tonight
and watch it?
- No.
- I have plans.
Okay, rain check it is.
- [clears throat]
- Get better soon.
I will do. Bye!
[elevator bell dings]
Hey, Sarge. Need something?
I'm here to escort you
to your car.
Oh, I just have
some paperwork to finish.
No, you're going home,
and you're gonna stay home.
I don't want
to see you back here
until you've given birth
to this child.
Understood?
Yes, Sarge.
- Good.
- [chuckles]
Relax. Kick your feet up.
Let Wesley dote on you.
You deserve it.
Thank you.
["With the Wind" playing]
Where you going?
To pee and get a snack.
You just live
five minutes away.
You think she'll be okay?
I hope so.
♪ Gotta fix
that broken heart ♪
- And you?
- Yeah.
You know,
when you go undercover,
people always warn you
about the fear, the danger,
but no one ever talks about
how hard it is
when you have to leave
someone behind.
And it's not like
you could come home
and talk to me about it.
This girl was clearly
important to you,
and I'd never heard her name
until this morning.
Patrol just found Ed Teska
murdered in an alley
in Koreatown.
Made a run at the king.
And his daughter, and missed.
That gets you killed
ten times out of ten.
♪ ♪
Want me to tell her?
No. I got it.
♪ ♪
I don't even know
your real name.
It's Isabel.
I know you're going through
a lot right now,
but it is vital
that you don't tell anyone
I was a cop.
It would endanger not only me,
but everyone who helped me,
whether they knew
who I was or not.
Meaning I'd put myself
in danger too.
Tell me the truth.
Was I just a way
for you to get to my dad?
At first, maybe,
but you needed someone.
Your dad barely remembered
to feed you.
And I saw how alone you were
at a moment
where I felt alone myself.
So I looked out for you
and took care of myself
in the process.
♪ ♪
I have something difficult
to tell you.
♪ ♪
Your uncle's dead.
♪ Feed that restless heart ♪
Good.
He tried to kill me.
The police are pretty sure
that your dad ordered it.
♪ Feed that restless heart ♪
And he's getting out
of prison tomorrow?
Yeah.
You gonna be there
when he walks out?
No.
I got money hidden away.
I'm gonna disappear
for a while.
I need to figure out what
the hell I want my life to be
and whether my dad
will be part of it.
♪ ♪
If you ever need me,
you know the number.
♪ ♪
Thanks for coming
when I called.
♪ That life no one thought ♪
Anytime.
♪ Let's find out
who we are ♪
Ooh.
[keys jingling]
♪ Outside, inside a world
inside a world ♪
Do you want a beer?
Yeah. Sounds great.
♪ ♪
She seems good.
Happy.
- Isabel?
- Mm.
- Yeah.
Yeah, she deserves it.
Hmm.
♪ ♪
♪ Feed that restless heart ♪
♪ It's burning up ♪
It was nice to get to know
the, uh, actual person
behind all your stories.
♪ Feed that restless heart ♪
Is that what you were doing
when you turned your mic off?
♪ ♪
No.
We were talking trash
about you, of course.
- Funny.
- Mm.
♪ Not on my own ♪
Can I share
something vulnerable with you?
Yeah. Of course.
♪ Not on my own,
not on my own ♪
I love working undercover.
I love it, but, um,
you know, I've never gone
as deep as Isabel did.
Six months here, a year there.
And you're worried
you won't be able to handle it?
No.
Um...
♪ ♪
I'm worried that you won't.
I'll be fine.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
I will.
♪ ♪
Come here.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Damn it.