Previously, on
"The Rookie"...
- Any other plans?
- I have to sell our dad's house.
We could make some money
if we put in a little effort.
Chief of Police
gave me a Golden Ticket.
I can pick any job I want.
- What are you gonna pick?
- He's gonna pick something lame.
- Training officer.
- I knew it.
Did I hear you're joining
the D.A.'s office?
- Next week.
- Do you want to come in?
I just wanted to make sure
someone checked on Lucy.
- He still has a pulse.
- What have you done?
Oh, don't trip
on the mat.
Rosalind cut my wrists,
not my ankles.
You just got out
of the hospital.
How tragic would it be
if my chic, yet affordable
welcome mat
sent you right back?
You know you're cute
when you worry.
I am cute always.
That's true.
Ooh.
New sofa.
Yeah. You kind of ruined
the last one with all the...
All the bleeding.
Hey, it's okay.
- No, it's not.
- It's what we make it.
And I say, let's make the most
of your day off
and cuddle up on the couch
to binge the crap out of
something mindless.
Deal?
- Deal.
- All right.
Knock knock. Hi.
I'm looking for
Lucy Chen.
Uh, yeah, that's me.
Detective Misha Porter.
I teach at the undercover
academy up in Sacramento.
Yeah,
I know who you are.
Well, I'm doing some recruiting,
and your name keeps coming up.
You've worked several
impressive operations.
Makes for an ideal candidate.
So I'm here to recruit you.
Uh...
When do classes start?
Next Monday.
Sorry for the late notice.
We had another candidate
fall out.
But I'm positive your sergeant
will approve it.
Yeah, he... he would, for sure.
It's just I have, um...
I have some things going on
in my personal life right now,
and...
If... it's not a good time,
I get it.
But you should know
my classes will open up
a ton of doors for you.
No, I-I know.
Detective Harper
has told me all about it.
You'll have every major unit
competing to poach you
from patrol.
Um, this is amazing.
Thank you.
I-I will definitely think
about this.
Okay.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Think about it?
No. Go out there
and tell her yes.
I can't.
Baby, you almost died.
But I didn't.
I'll... I'll be fine.
- Chris...
- Lucy, I'll be fine.
No.
I'm not leaving you.
Undercover school can wait.
So, what do you
want to binge?
♪ Oh, whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
*THE ROOKIE*
♪ I'm gonna win for you
Season 05  Episode 01
♪ Like I know you want me to do
Episode Title: "Labor Day"
♪ Hey!
Aired on: October 02, 2022.
We will talk about it
when we get home, okay?
I can't do this right now.
Because I can't.
Look, we'll talk
when I get home.
Everything okay?
It's fine.
Um, thanks for stopping by.
The Realtor just needs you
to sign a couple of things
before the open house today.
Absolutely.
What do you think?
Looks pretty good, right?
Unrecognizable.
The broker thinks
we're gonna have it sold
by the end of the week.
That's great.
Once this place sells, we can
finally put it all behind us.
Yeah. Yeah, it'll be nice.
Can move on.
Don't.
Don't what?
Have feelings?
Don't get all misty-eyed
over Hill House.
It's our childhood home.
Selling it means something.
Hopefully it means
a half a million dollars each.
I got to get to work.
Call me if you need anything.
Will do.
Now you're just showing off.
A 98 on your
training officer exam.
Pretty impressive.
Thank you, sir.
So next week, you're off
to F.T.O. School
for post certification.
And then, after that,
you will officially be
a Field Training Officer.
But until then,
I need someone
to finish training
Officer Thorsen.
You up
for a trial run?
Is that allowed?
It is if I say it is.
Harper has got him
most of the way there.
Only a few weeks
until he graduates.
I'm happy to do it.
And, sir, thank you for
all your help with this.
Please.
You're helping me out.
We've, um, come a long way,
haven't we, sir?
Yeah.
Or maybe it's about time
I start calling you Wade?
Get out of my office,
Officer Nolan.
Yes, sir.
And close my door.
Good morning.
Good morning,
Officer Nolan.
I prepped the shop,
loaded the war bags,
and I got you
this cup of coffee here.
Harper trained you well.
I mean,
if you want a challenge,
I can be the, uh, worst rookie
you've ever come across.
Just be yourself.
Okay. I can do that.
You know, typically, I like to
start my morning off with,
you know, a little TikTok dance,
just to get, like,
you know,
the hips warmed up.
It kind of helps...
A little less yourself.
Copy that.
Everything's controlled
through here and the app.
Okay.
Looks simple enough.
What was that?
Uh, my wife's in pre-labor.
And we're having a home birth.
And you just moved?
Well, the plan was to wait until
after the baby,
but then the nesting
hormones took over,
and the next thing I knew,
we were in escrow.
But I'm all over it.
I feel like I've trained
my whole life for this moment.
Cool.
All right. Assure Home Security
system is live.
Sensors on every door
and window.
Just need to put the app
on your phone.
I forgot
they were even coming today.
Oh, you got a lot
on your plate.
Just concentrate
on giving birth.
I've got the rest.
You know, when you said
you were gonna be
a good labor assistant,
I thought it was just one
of those things that men say
when they act like
they know something
but they really don't.
Well, this is actually
my third rodeo.
My ex had zero trust
in the medical system,
so both boys
were born at home.
You know, in a way,
I've actually got
more childbirth experience
than you do.
Thank God.
'Cause after last time,
I cannot imagine giving birth
in a hospital again.
Well, this birth
will be different.
The placenta is completely clear
of the baby's pathway.
Your OB-GYN signed off.
We got the midwife
on speed dial,
and if anything goes wrong,
hospital is four minutes away.
But just FYI, I can get us to
the hospital in two minutes
because I know a shortcut.
Uh, I don't think a sidewalk
is considered a short cut.
Mm-hmm. Mm, mm!
Contractions?
Mm-hmm.
Tell me we got this.
We got this.
Okay. Mm.
What was the color of the truck
three cars back?
Red.
- How many sex workers have we passed?
- Four.
What are the crime stats
for this area?
- In this last week?
- Yes.
Um,
three motor vehicle thefts.
Two burglaries.
And seven thefts from vehicles.
All right. Here's something
you won't know...
What is the best sealant to use
when joining plastic to tile?
I mean, there's a lot
of great options,
but probably something
silicone-based would work best.
How did you know that?
You told me that yesterday.
Right.
7-Adam-15,
I have a call for
a welfare check
at 707 Palm Street.
Show us responding.
Police.
Hey, Nolan.
Hold your breath.
He's gone.
And he's a cop.
Welcome to
the D.A.'s office.
Thanks.
I'm not gonna lie.
It's weird to be working here.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Uh, break room's
around that corner over there,
where you'll find
every old-school snack
you didn't think
they still made anymore.
Because they don't.
They're just old.
Seriously.
Don't eat them.
Good to know.
And this is
your office.
And these are
your case files.
That... is a lot.
Well, we like to keep up
a brisk pace.
You spend too much time
in any one case,
and the backlog
will kill you.
Hmm. Well, the good news is,
at least,
this one doesn't seem
worth pursuing.
Find the ones that are,
kick the rest.
Prosecutorial discretion
is a beautiful thing.
Have fun.
Yeah.
Thanks.
He one of ours?
Sheriff's Deputy.
His name's Garrett Patel.
He was dead when we arrived.
Carbon monoxide poisoning.
Let's make sure
we honor him
and not let anything
slip through the cracks.
- Right.
- Where's your rookie?
Uh, inside with T.I.D.
At this point in his training,
I thought it'd be valuable
for him to
process a crime scene
with them.
Smart. All right,
I'll keep an eye on him,
and you go to the morgue
with our victim.
Dr. Roberts has agreed
to do a rush preliminary exam.
All right. I'll swing by
afterwards, pick up Aaron.
Thanks.
So, this is the rebozo
lift and sift technique,
helps pull the weight
off the lower back.
Mm. Feels amazing.
It can really help once the
contractions get more intense.
What is that?
It's death metal. No...
Thrash metal. Thrash metal.
Mnh-mnh, no,
not at my home birth.
Help me up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You relax.
Stay here.
I'll go talk to them.
- Neighbor.
- What do you want?
W-We just moved in
across the street.
My... My wife and I
are having a baby, a home birth.
She just started
having contractions.
Uh, this music is not
on our labor play list,
if you know what I mean.
Um, can you turn it down?
No.
Okay, Nyla... Nyla, you don't
want to stress the baby.
I-I'm sure they'll turn it off
at some point.
Move.
Turn the music down.
Now.
Yo, turn it down.
Thank you so much.
All I'll say is,
I'm glad you're on my side.
You found something already?
Possibly.
I haven't done
the full autopsy yet,
but I found something concerning
on the external exam.
Several patches
of missing chest hair.
All around
the same position.
- Like it was pulled out.
- Right.
And I found some
adhesive residue
on the surrounding hair
and skin.
Tape.
So maybe he was wearing a wire?
Doing undercover work?
One other thing.
All right.
What am I looking at here?
I found these fibers
on his wrists.
I believe they're from
soft wrist restraints,
the kind that don't
leave marks.
Well, we didn't find anything
like that in the car,
which would suggest
he was restrained long enough
for the carbon monoxide
to do its job,
and then the restraints
were removed,
making it look
like a suicide.
But why would someone
go to so much trouble
to murder
a Sheriff's Deputy?
Undercover school
sounds amazing.
"Self-surgery."
"Six things to say
when your cover's blown."
"When your
informant is a double agent."
Yeah, you have to go.
This is where
I want to be.
Lucy, if you're staying here
out of guilt, don't.
This wasn't your fault.
Of course it was my fault.
Rosalind targeted you
because of me.
She's angry that
I didn't testify.
You don't know that.
Yes, I do.
I moved on.
She couldn't handle that.
She'd been looking forward to
torturing me on the stand.
And when I took that
away from her, she...
She tried to take you.
But she didn't.
Chris...
No.
Listen, if you skip U.C. school
because of this,
that's something
she wi be taking from you.
Hey.
Garrett Patel was assigned
to a special narcotics unit
in the Sheriff's Department.
Word is they run
mostly reversals.
Which means?
Which means
law enforcement officers
pose as drug sellers.
They flash real dope
to lure the buyers.
And then, when the money
is exchanged,
they make the arrest. Nice.
You think Garrett
was wearing a wire
as part of
an investigation?
Maybe. But it doesn't
explain his murder.
A staged suicide isn't exactly
a drug dealer's go-to.
They're a lot less subtle.
So what's next?
We reach out to his unit?
Garrett's ex-wife
just landed.
I'll talk to her first.
See if she has any insight.
Right.
We got divorced,
uh, five months ago,
but we still talked.
About work?
A little.
Garrett seemed really stressed.
And of course
he wouldn't tell me why.
Part of the reason why we split
was because it was clear
that he was keeping
things from me.
And it got really bad
at the end.
His narcotics buddies
would come over to play poker,
and the second I walked in
the room, they would get quiet.
Can I get their names?
Yeah, it's,
uh, Walt Lindbeck.
He's the team leader.
Super cocky.
Thinks he's God's gift.
Um, Simon Ayer.
He's a sweet guy.
He's young, like Garrett.
But Rick Croyer...
He just gave me
a bad feeling.
Look, don't get me wrong.
We had other problems
with our marriage.
But when Garrett started
hanging with "The Crew," that...
That was the beginning
of the end.
Wait.
They call themselves
"The Crew"?
When will cops learn?
Learn what?
Look, you can hang out
with other cops all you want,
but the second
you give your group a name,
it's just a matter of time
until you're under indictment.
Really?
Does that work for any name?
What if you call yourselves
"The Snuggle Bunch"?
- You're going to prison.
- Totally.
I can't explain it,
but it never fails.
Give yourself a name,
go to jail.
Noted.
But I think the judge
is gonna want
a little more than that.
So how are we going after
these guys?
You're kidding.
10 offers already?
That's incredible.
I know.
I'm a little in shock.
So, what's
the highest offer?
$50,000 over asking.
From a developer.
But there's also
this family.
The dad included the most
touching letter with the offer,
all about how much
it would mean to his kids
to finally have a home.
Okay, so,
what's their offer?
Asking.
So $50,000 less.
It's still more than
we expected to get.
Besides, the developer
will just tear it down.
Good. House is
an actual crime scene.
It should be torn down.
Listen, Genny,
I got to go.
Keep me posted.
Hey.
Uh, I'll do a number three.
- Coming right up.
- Thank you.
We got a number three.
What's up, gentlemen?
Hey.
You guys, uh, work with that
deputy that killed himself?
We did, actually.
Sorry for your loss.
Tim Bradford,
Mid-Wilshire Division.
My guys found the body.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, it's always tough
to lose someone
you were in the trenches with.
I just wish we had realized
how much he'd been hurting.
It's got to be rough.
Well, look, if you guys
need anything...
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Actually, uh...
you know,
we've been hearing some rumors
- about foul play.
- Yeah?
Hadn't heard that.
I can check, though.
You guys
working on something
that could have
come back on him?
Eh, that's tough to say.
We put away a lot
of bad hombres,
but nobody immediately
springs to mind.
Well,
I'll tell you this,
if someone did
kill Garrett,
they're not gonna survive
that trip to lockup.
I can do some digging
and get back to you.
Sergeant Lindbeck.
It's Walt.
Much appreciated.
Yeah. Least I could do.
Cops got to stick together, right?
Damn right.
- Take care.
- You too.
Those aren't grieving faces.
Those are guys terrified
of getting caught.
Great.
Where's my burrito?
Sorry. I got distracted trying
to gaslight crooked cops.
Crooked how?
- They're running reversals, right?
- Mm-hmm.
So instead of
arresting the dealers,
they're taking the cash
and cutting them free.
With their intel, they would
know exactly who to target.
And with their access
to real drugs,
they could make sales
seem legit.
And it's not like the dealers
can call the cops to complain.
I'll read Wesley in.
I need you guys
to hit up your CIs.
If The Crew
are ripping off dealers,
there's gonna be a lot of
pissed-off criminals out there.
Someone's heard something.
You know, Harper has got
the best CIs in the station.
You're right.
Nolan, call Harper.
She likes you best.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
On it.
That was a dirty lie.
Today is her due date.
Do you want to be the one
calling her about work?
You're an evil genius.
Emphasis on the "evil."
Damn straight.
Now give me half that burrito
before I turn my evil
against you.
So, how's Lucy?
Uh, you know,
she's still a little shaken.
Taking some time
to get Chris settled.
Remind me what you were doing
at her apartment
when you found Chris
bleeding out?
Just... dropping her off
after we got back from Vegas.
Mm-hmm.
What are you implying?
What do you think?
I was just dropping her off.
Mm-hmm.
You don't have to
answer that.
Nolan,
has someone been shot?
No. Did someone
catch Rosalind Dyer?
No.
Okay, then I'm hanging up.
Wait, wait, wait.
There's a corrupt group
of deputies.
They killed
one of their own.
All right, talk fast.
The whole point of a home birth
is to be left alone
to suffer in peace.
You're in labor?
Like right now?
Nolan, fast.
Uh, we think
they're ripping off dealers.
We need your best CI.
Uh, okay. Abel Law ton.
I will text you
his phone number.
Thank you. Good...
Good luck.
Hey. You still wading through
those case files?
No, I'm done.
You read them all,
or you just skimmed them
for the headlines?
- Well, I got the gist.
- Ah.
Jonathan, 19-year-old kid
arrested a year ago
on a gun charge.
Since then,
he's got his act together.
Taking trade school classes.
He's about to be credentialed
as a specialized pipefitter.
I'm gonna knock that one
down to a misdemeanor.
You're knocking down charges
while violent crime
is on the rise?
I don't think that
he's a violent criminal.
Huh. I think he carried
a gun for protection
in a neighborhood
where that makes sense.
I could run you down
my whole list,
but that would take a while.
No, no.
Just tell me how many cases you're gonna plead
out and how many cases you're taking to trial,
keeping in mind
the correct ratio
is nine plea bargains
for every trial.
Zero. And zero.
Well,
that's not an option.
I'm just exercising
my prosecutorial discretion.
Ha ha ha. Look.
Pick a case to charge,
any case,
by the end of the day, okay?
We didn't hire you so you can
give everyone a free pass.
Hey.
Hey. Got some time?
We have a case.
It's gonna be tricky.
Does it involve
punishing the poor?
No. Dirty cops.
I'll be right there.
You think it's too early
to get in the pool?
No.
Warm water
could help you relax
and relieve
some of your back pain.
What is that lovely smell?
Mm.
I rubbed the lavender oil
onto my skin
so that my scent could calm you.
You really do
think of everything.
Mm-hmm.
You were cool with it
in the beginning.
Is that the neighbors again?
I'm going over there.
Mnh-mnh.
No, no, no, no, you're not.
Just call in
a noise complaint.
Uh, fireworks?
No, that was gunshots.
Officer Nyla Harper.
Shots fired
near 5575 Orange Grove.
Well, looks like
a false alarm.
Didn't sound false.
Your neighbors said they were
watching "Dirty Harry."
That's got to be
what you heard.
Smitty, I am telling you,
I heard live gunshots.
We did a thorough search
of the house.
There was no sign
of foul play.
And the only guns
that I saw...
were on that homey's arms.
That dude is ripped.
Thank you, Smitty.
You are as much help
as I thought you would be.
You need a hand
with anything else?
No, thank you. Goodbye.
Maybe it was "Dirty Harry."
I mean, they've got a serious
sound system in there.
Those shots were from
a high-caliber weapon,
not a 40-year-old handgun.
It was a big gun.
Just saying.
Mr. Law ton,
thank you for coming in.
Yeah.
Uh, can you make it quick?
I-I-I don't like
being here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know, we could have
come to your place,
but that might have
jammed you up.
Okay, spare me the attitude,
all right?
You guys clearly need
something from me.
And I should warn you,
all right,
my rates have gone up
substantially since,
you know, I've been
selling intel to the Feds...
Yes, Harper did
warn us about that.
She told us to tell you,
"Remember Oceanside."
Okay. Uh...
On second thought, um...
Uh, for a friend of Harper's,
it's free.
Uh, what do you... what...
What do you need?
What do you know about anyone
ripping off drug dealers?
You mean those
Sheriff's Department guys?
Uh, yeah.
They hit up my boy, Junior,
for like 100K.
Okay, well, uh,
we need to talk to him.
So where is he?
He's in lockup.
Or... at least he was.
He's in the morgue now.
Got shanked in prison
like two hours ago.
They gave themselves a name.
When are cops gonna learn?
Clearly never.
And so far,
evidence is sketchy at best.
We think our victim
was recording
their criminal activity,
but we can't
find the recordings.
And we had
a potential witness,
but he magically got shanked
in prison earlier today.
All right.
So what about financial records?
If they're stealing
from drug dealers,
where is the money going?
Nowhere we can find.
Clearly, they're being
very disciplined
with the cash
they're stealing.
Then you need
the recordings.
Without them,
there's no case.
I know.
Hi.
Lucy.
Uh,
were we expecting you?
Oh, no. But I-I heard
today was the big day,
so I brought you some food
so you didn't have to go out.
That is
very sweet of you.
Uh, Nyla, Lucy's here.
So, it's totally vegetarian.
Ashwagandha...
Oh, my God!
You are glowing.
I am not,
but thank you.
And thank you
for the food.
Mm-hmm.
So, hey, while I'm here,
I wanted to
run something by you.
Um, I was offered a spot
in U.C. school.
That's great. That's g...
You... You deserve it.
Um, quick question.
- Mm.
What do you think about that
house across the street?
Oh, I-I didn't
really notice it.
So, the thing is, Chris just got
out of the hospital,
and he really
needs me to help him.
Okay, so, James thinks
that I should drop it,
but something is going on
over at that house.
I heard gunshots earlier on.
And they sent Smitty.
But I know Smitty is...
Nyla Harper.
Yes.
Are you roping Lucy
into your fantasy?
It's not a fantasy.
O-Okay.
I didn't mean it like that.
I apologize.
But the truth is,
labor induces a tidal wave
of physiological changes.
Hormone levels spike,
neurotransmitters jack up a kind
of fight-or-flight response.
Okay, is this just
your way of saying
that it's all in my head?
No.
All I'm saying is
you're about to give birth,
and you're hypersensitive
to anything that might
seem like a threat.
Yeah.
That seems logical.
Okay, uh, you know what?
I'm gonna... I'm gonna go.
Um, should I say yes?
To what?
To U.C. school?
Yes.
Say yes.
Oh...
I swear it'd be quieter
at a hospital.
Police!
Show yourself right now.
I don't want to hear it.
You broke the seal.
You're in my crime scene.
It was our guy
who went down.
You think we're just gonna
stand on the sidelines,
watch the LAPD
screw up the investigation?
- You buying this?
- No.
Listen,
we're all on the same team...
Wrong.
We're investigating a homicide,
and you appear to be attempting
to obstruct that investigation.
You don't know what
you're talking about, honey.
Come on, let's go.
We got a warrant
to search everything, Walt,
including you.
That's not happening.
You don't want to
walk into this.
Try me.
Aah!
Don't.
Get up. Get up.
Come on.
Hands behind your back.
Shipping receipt
with Garrett's name on it.
A million bucks
it's a recording
from the wire
Garrett was wearing.
You're under arrest, gentlemen,
for removing evidence
and obstruction.
Turn around.
Where's your buddy Rick?
How about you?
You can help yourself here.
Don't say a word.
Don't listen to him.
Where's Rick?
You know, you'd think
cops would be smarter.
This warrant
covers your phone.
Called Rick right before
we came in.
Hello.
Hey.
Tim and I found The Crew
at Garrett's house doing
some evidence tampering.
We think Garrett mailed
the recordings to himself
at Coast to Post
Mailbox Service,
7646 West Vernon.
We're on it.
Move your ass.
Rick's already on his way there.
If he gets there first,
he'll destroy the evidence.
Hit it.
Is it okay
if I take a quick shower?
- Yep.
- You sure?
Yep.
Okay.
"Dirty Harry" my ass.
You left the trunk open.
No, I didn't.
Hey, neighbor!
Hey, hey!
How you doing?
Sorry to bother you.
Oh.
Our cat ran out,
um, and she...
She's a-a total troublemaker,
um, but she's been declawed
so it's not safe for her
to be wandering around out here.
You haven't seen her,
have you?
No.
No. Okay. Uh, damn.
Well, please let me know
if you do.
Thank you.
Thanks again.
Okay, what the hell
were you doing over there?
Gathering evidence.
Without a warrant?
Don't lecture me.
My water just broke.
The law still applies.
Wait... W-W-What, what?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, come on, come on.
We got to get you
in the birthing tub,
and I got to call the midwife.
Come on.
All right.
You go around front.
I'll scope it out inside.
Copy that.
Hey!
Hey, you guys need to move.
Give me the package.
I-I'm looking.
Please don't point that at me.
Hurry up!
O-Okay. Okay.
Give it up, Rick.
Walt and Simon
are already in custody.
You're just making things worse
for yourself.
Stay here, all right?
Get down!
Give me your hands.
Both of them. Come on.
You broke my ribs.
You killed a cop.
You're under arrest.
Where you been?
Nyla,
you have the baby yet?
Hey, Nyla.
Aah. I need you to
look into my neighbors.
Um, I heard gunshots,
and I-I think
that there's something
going on
over there.
It's, uh,
5574 Orange Grove.
You literally sound like
you're having a baby right now.
Mm, basically.
And these guys, they are
messing with my birth plan.
Oh, oh. Okay.
Uh, I saw them moving
what could have been a body
into the trunk
of their car.
And I found hydrofluoric acid
in there as well.
But I-I saw all of this
without a warrant.
I'll run the homeowner
and any associates.
But I need you to focus on
having the baby.
If I find anything,
I'll get in touch.
Okay, okay. Thank you.
Um, did I hear you
talking to somebody?
Nope.
Ooh.
Ooh, ice chips.
Thank you. Yes.
Oh, oh!
Doesn't feel good to be on that
side of the table, does it?
No.
Prison's gonna feel
even worse.
And before you give me your song
and dance about your innocence,
you should know
Garrett wore a wire for months.
There are dozens of hours
of recordings.
You want a sample?
It's zero eight hundred.
We're about to meet a buyer,
Junior Mills.
Hey, where you been?
Let's go.
Sorry, Walt.
Just getting my head right.
Simon, what's up?
See how Garrett name checks
you and Walt? Smart.
Well, let's get in there.
It's payday.
You know how this works, Junior.
We let you get a taste,
now show us the money.
It's all there.
Great. Now beat it.
You got to be kidding me.
You got five
to start walking
and if we see you again...
Yeah, there it is.
Your crew stealing from
the drug dealers
you're supposed to arrest.
Most of them slink away,
but Junior talked.
Told anyone he could
about the crew who robbed him.
And Junior
ended up dead.
I don't know anything
about that.
You got one chance
to come clean.
Tell us everything you know,
and I'm prepared to
offer you leniency.
Walt will kill me.
He won't be able to get
anywhere near you.
I promise.
It's time to do
the right thing
for Garrett.
Where is the midwife?
She's on her way.
There's traffic.
Remember, don't scream.
It's... It's just wasted energy.
Channel it into breathing.
Aah!
Come on.
Okay, yeah, that's fine, too.
That's fine, too.
Come on. Here you go.
Mm.
I thought you said the second
one was always easier.
I said usually.
Maybe the third will be
the easy one, hmm?
Sorry.
That was too soon, too soon.
Let me guess, that's the midwife
saying she can't make it.
No, it's the Assure
Home Security app.
The security system has detected
an open window downstairs.
Someone's in the house.
Not necessarily...
Get my gun.
Okay, Nyla,
you are fully dilated.
This baby is coming
any minute now.
It's the murderers
from across the street.
Get my damn gun.
Okay, you stay here, okay?
I'll go check it out.
Stay here.
What? No... James, stay...
No. James, you...
Drop the gun.
I am in here giving life,
but I will take yours
if you even twitch.
7-Adam-200, shots fired,
officer needs help
at my location.
Hey!
Nyla!
Wait!
It's a girl.
Welcome to the world, kiddo.
I promise it won't always
be this insane.
Hey, are you okay?
Well,
all things considered.
Was I right about the body?
You were right.
GSW to the chest.
Looking like they had a hidden
basement in the house
where they put the body
when Smitty came calling.
You definitely win
the best childbirth story.
I don't know. You have
that whole Guatemala adventure.
Yeah, but I didn't
have the baby down there.
Accept the crown.
You earned it.
He's right.
T.I.D.s are finishing up downstairs.
You still got to talk
to the shooting team,
but they can wait
a few days.
You're on
maternity leave.
Yes.
Uh, no more investigations.
You promise?
Look, if an escaped convict
comes into
my Mommy and Me class,
then I will have
no choice.
But, barring that,
I will spend the next six weeks
just staring at
this little angel.
♪ Thought it'd be easy, easy
- ♪ To find my way, all the way home ♪
- Let me guess, an orphanage wants
to buy Dad's house
for a hundred bucks.
No.
Listen, I haven't been
entirely honest with you.
The phone call
this morning?
Yeah.
Rob and I are
having a hard time.
Like go to counseling
hard time?
Like divorce lawyers
hard time.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
But it's for the best.
Now, about Dad's house...
You want to sell it
to the happy family
because you're feeling nostalgic.
No, I want to sell it
to the highest bidder
because divorces aren't cheap,
and I need
to cushion the landing
into single mom-hood.
Wow. Uh, very smart.
So, is...
Is Rob moving out?
Actually,
I was thinking of moving.
To where?
Here.
I mean,
unless you don't want me to.
Are you kidding?
I think it's a great idea.
Good. Now give me a hug
'cause I just told you
my marriage fell apart,
and I'm trying to be strong,
but I'm feeling really sad.
How was your first day?
You know, I was worried
that it might be weird
working on the other side,
but I think
it might actually work out.
Don't get too excited.
You won't get to arrest
crooked cops every day.
I hope you're wrong.
I think I found my niche.
Yeah?
Hey.
I just wanted to apologize.
I wasn't much of
a T.O. today.
What are you talking about?
Everything
was happening so fast.
So if I didn't
slow down and properly...
No, look.
If you repeat this,
I will deny it.
But, um, after today,
you're definitely
my favorite T.O.
That's very kind.
You don't have to say that.
No, John, I-I-I mean it.
You know, you...
You teach by asking,
and that's a very
under-appreciated method.
So thanks.
You're welcome. Yeah.
♪ Finding my way,
finding my way ♪
Oh, and it's, um, Sir
or Officer Nolan
when we're on duty.
Yes, sir.
I will see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
What are you
in the mood for next?
Oh, um, anything,
as long as it's not
another cooking show.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Just checking in.
How are you feeling?
Okay.
Lucy's taking great care of me.
I have no doubt.
Hey, can we talk?
Uh, yeah, sure.
So, I, uh...
I hear you're on the fence
about going to U.C. school.
Chris called you?
Yeah,
which was unexpected.
Um, he wanted me to
talk to you.
It's not the right time.
He's gonna be fine.
You owe it to yourself
to go.
I know, but...
What happened to him
isn't your fault.
We were about to...
But we didn't.
We didn't.
Uh, are you trying to get rid of
me as your go-fer?
No.
No, I'm trying to
look out for you.
It's time for you
to move on.
And some time away
would be good.
It's a great opportunity, Lucy.
Mm-hmm.
You should go for it.
Captions by VITA...
Synchronized by srjanapala