Previously on "The Rookie"...
Hi. I'm Dr. Morgan
from the CDC.
My sister is dead.
They need to pay.
I get it.
My little sister was taken away
from me a long time ago,
and I spent
most of my life
thinking of all
the different ways
I would hurt
the person responsible.
I'm scared.
Elijah is coming
for us,
and they're counting on me
to protect them.
Lucy: Metro would be
a good fit for Tim.
How do you create
that opening?
I don't know, like you said,
the five-player trade.
Lieutenant Pine just called me
15 minutes ago,
- and I'm going over.
- That's great.
Detective Misha Porter.
I teach at the undercover
academy up in Sacramento.
Well, I'm doing some recruiting,
and your name keeps coming up.
I'm here to recruit you.
[Cellphone buzzing]
[Groans softly]
Who is it?
I don't know.
[Cellphone clicks]
Hello?
Noah: Loca,
you gotta stop texting.
I told you, I'm grabbing
a drink at Zona Rosa.
I'll be home when I'm home.
[Cellphone beeps]
[Yawns]
Wrong number?
- What's happening?
- The U.C. I trained with,
distress call.
He needs
a covert rescue.
- What are you doing?
- Backing you up.
[Dramatic music plays]
♪
Vince: A short drive.
What's the problem?
No problem.
You send the address.
I'll meet you there.
What?
You don't trust us?
No, dude.
I just told my old lady
I'd be around.
You know how it is.
[Vehicle approaches]
[Vehicle door opens]
Nono.
Oh, man.
What the hell?
You said you'd be home.
I got three sick kids
and someplace else to be.
- Damn, baby. I'm sorry.
- Damn, man.
You let your baby mama
- talk to you like that?
- Yo. Who is talk to you?
It's bad enough that you roll
into the club without me,
but you gotta do it with
all these inbred white boys.
- What'd you just say?
- Did I stutter?
Hey, chill!
All right.
She didn't mean nothing by it.
It's just displaced
anger towards me.
[Grunts]
Mm-hmm.
Now, I got to deal
with this tonight.
Can we hook up tomorrow?
Yeah. Okay.
This right here
tells me something
about
your commitment level.
Hey, Vince, you know
I'm down with the cause.
Really?
Hey, I'm just trying
to keep the peace!
[Engine starts]
Okay, let's go.
Damn,
you came in hot.
Damn.
All clear.
Noah Foster.
Tim Bradford.
I'm impressed you managed to
scrounge up backup this fast.
Yeah, I mean, helps
he was sleeping in my bed.
Oh! Oh, you're
that Bradford.
Curious to know
- what that means.
- No.
Okay, so, who did we
just rescue you from?
"The Army of Freedom."
Militia group
born in Victorville.
I started running with them
about a month ago.
Still haven't managed to breach
their inner circle yet.
Pushed a little too hard
tonight?
Maybe.
But I had to roll the dice.
They're about to move
something big.
That can't be good.
I need to go brief
my guys in Victorville,
then I need
a local assist.
Is that doable?100%.
We'll set you up
at Mid-Wilshire.
You...
[Chuckles]
Damn it, it's good to see you,
Hot Pants.
- Hot Pants?
- It's an inside joke.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
♪
[Sighs]
[Grunts] Sorry.
Excuse me.
Can I just...Okay. You know what?
We are a mess.
- Totally out of sync.
- What do you expect?
We're living in
Elijah's crosshairs.
[Sighs]
[Knock at door]
Who's that?
Oh, I forgot.
Charlie's starting today.
He's the private security guy
I hired.
I thought we agreed
that was a waste of money.
- We have two units on us 24/7.
- You said it was my call,
and I feel like more security
is always better.
I'm just saying we don't need
some massive Neanderthal
who smells like chaw
and gun oil in our house.
Mr. Evers, Charlie Bristow
from X-Ring Security.
[Chuckles]
Y-You're Charlie?
Mm-hmm.
Uh, I just assumed
that you were a man.
Mm-hmm.
No problem.
Happens all the time.
Please come in.
[Chuckles]
Detective Lopez,
it's a pleasure.
- You have a lovely home.
- Thank you.
I'm running late,
but first,
can you remind me
what your qualifications are?
Of course.
I spent eight years
in the SAS
working mostly counterterrorism
ops in Iraq and Afghanistan.
Went private the last three
years doing security work
for high-level individuals,
which brought me to Los Angeles.
That's impressive.
Okay, well,
- we have units on us 24/7.
- Yes, ma'am.
I introduced myself
to the officers out front
so we could coordinate
your movements.
First question,
do I go with you
or stay with Mr. Evers?
I can handle
my own security.
I have no doubt.
I've seen your
shooting record...
five-time LAPD champion,
pistol and long gun.
Uh, the thought was is that
you would be wherever Jack is.
And I'm working from home today
so I can have you get settled.
Great. Plenty of time
to get to know each other.
Wonderful.
♪
Hey. Honey.
Hey. Hey.
- Happy Valentine's Day.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Bailey: No, I'm not
calling you stupid.
I'm telling you,
the package wasn't delivered.
No, I don't want
to be put on hold.
Can you believe this?
Customer service
is an oxymoron.
She is an oxymoron.
[Alarm chirps]
Thank you for driving.
It is never a good idea for me
to operate heavy machinery
when doing this.
Any idea why we're having
a joint briefing?
No, but it looks
like Highway Patrol's
already here, too.
Yes. Hi. I'm here.
I don't care
what your system says.
Yes, I've checked
the front door.
It's a bike.
I think I would notice climbing
over a bike-sized box
to get into the house.
I mean...Yeah, I'm just gonna...
Hello.
This is the homeowner.
We did not receive the package,
and it was not stolen.
We would have caught it
on the door cam.
So either track the package
or just refund her money.
Thank you very much.
There you go.
What was that?
- Just being helpful.
- I was handling it.
It didn't seem like that.
Excuse me.
[Stammers]
Well, you seemed upset,
so I-I thought it would help.
If I needed help,
I would ask.
Actually, that's not true.
You never ask for help.[Scoffs]
Even when you need it.
I cannot believe
you are taking her side.
Nyla, she's my mother.
It's creepy.
She likes to look at Leah
through the baby monitor.
How is that creepy?
"I noticed your robe
was a little worn out.
I sent you a new one."
Free robe.
What's the problem?
She saw the robe on the monitor
while I was breastfeeding.
Oh.
[Sighs]
Cut her off.
♪
[Blows raspberry]
Tim: You're kidding.
Thanks.
Kidding about what?
Uh, nothing.
Okay.
You left so early.
I had this whole
Valentine breakfast planned.
You were up late.
I, uh... I let you sleep.
Yeah.
I'm s... I'm sorry.
It was so nice to catch up
with Noah, though.
Uh-huh.
We didn't keep you up,
did we?
No. It's fine. Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah, fine.
Yeah,
we should get in there.
The briefing's
about to start. Oh.
Finally.
I'll get right to it.
This is Detective Foster
with Victorville P.D.
He's been undercover
for the last three months.
Get a good look.
If you see him
in the field,
pretend like you don't know him,
but he is one of us.
That being said, Detective.
I've been working a group
called "The Army of Freedom."
Wannabe militia tough guys
who are becoming
increasingly active.
Yesterday, I caught wind
of a new operation.
Is it some kind of
- an attack?
- Possibly.
But what I did overhear
was talk of sourcing
lab equipment and chemicals.
Harper:
Mobile drug lab?
That was my first thought.
Then we're most likely
talking meth.
For most of these
radical groups,
narcotics is their main source
of income.
And two weeks ago,
my department brought down
their primary meth lab.
All those
volatile chemicals,
might as well be a bomb
driving around the city.
- Exactly.
- Did you get a plate?
No plate. No VIN.
From the quick look
I did get,
it was
a older white truck
with a purple
or blue faded stripe.
Did you have any luck
reconnecting with them
- after last night?
- No. My main contact,
Vince Jameson,
hasn't returned
any of my texts,
which means I've either
blown my cover
or he's a criminal
with poor social skills.
- Time will tell.
- A list of
known militia members
have been given
to L.A. CLEAR.
We'll coordinate through
them to have a central
hub of information.
Look, we're gonna do a full
court press on this truck.
If anyone sees a vehicle
even loosely matching
the description, let us know,
we'll stop and FI them.
Lopez and I
will hit up our CIs,
see if any of them have heard
of a mobile drug lab.
If anyone comes across
the actual truck,
isolate it,
and then call the bomb squad.
Sgt. Grey:
All right, that's it.
Be safe out there.
Bradford, Chen,
hold back.
Sgt. Grey: I want Metro
to be ready
to move on these guys
in a moment's notice.
- Of course.
- Not "of course."
Last week, I needed you
on the check cashing robbery.
It took Metro two hours
to show up.
We were on another job.
That's why you'll be riding
with Chen and Foster today.
So there'll be no delays.
I want this thing
off my streets ASAP.
Yes, sir.
Everything okay
with Bailey?
Oh, we started the day
with a fight.
You know, Valentine's Day, it...
it can be a lot of pressure.
No, it's not...
It doesn't matter.
It'll all blow over
by tonight.
We were planning on celebrating
tomorrow night anyway.
Mm.
Avoid the mad grab
for reservations?
No, we just know how exhausted
we'll be by the end of the day.
- Why do you say that?
- Oh, you don't know?
Valentine's Day is the most
dangerous day of the year.
♪
Thank you.
So, Sergeant Frey
hated Noah.
[Chuckles] I don't know
what I did to piss her off,
- but she adored you.
- Yeah.
I mean, everybody adores me, right?
Hm?
Yep.
[Radio chatter]
Hey, you really think you were
burned last night?
I was pushing pretty hard
to get intel.
Maybe I should have held
my nerve and gone with them.
Noah,
you know better than that.
Rule number one
of U.C. work...
Never follow to
a secondary location.
No mission is worth
getting yourself killed over.
Yeah, I know,
but it's driving me crazy
- I might have messed this one up.
- Yeah.
Well, hey,
have you called April yet?
She must be thrilled
that you're out.
We broke up.
Well, she broke up with me.
Oh.
Apparently,
I was "closed off"
and it was like
"dating a robot."
I'm sorry.
Well...
I'm starting to think
the undercover life
isn't conducive
to a happy relationship.
Well, I mean,
that probably depends
on the couple.
Is that why you're
still on patrol?
New relationship
trumps new career?
No. I've worked a few U.C.
cases since graduating.
Well, one.
Well,
far be it for me to judge,
but you were by far the most
talented cop at U.C. school.
Be a shame if you
didn't take the plunge.
All right, our search grid
is zone three,
La Cienega to Western.
Copy that.
Sir,
can you do me a favor?
Sure. Wait.
All the possibilities
just flashed before my eyes.
Uh, let's go with...
I'll see what I can do.
Well, there's a case file
I was hoping to read,
but since I'm a rookie,
I don't have access.
Oh, sure, I can talk
to Lieutenant Carradine,
see if I can get
a copy for you.
Which file is it?
My sister's murder.
Celina.
I just want to see
if they've really done
everything they can
to find the guy.
Are you sure that's it?
Because if it were me,
I'd want the file
to try and solve it.
I mean,
it doesn't hurt to try.
Actually, in this case,
it does.
You know what goes into
those reports.
The details, the photos.
I know what he did to her.
I was there at the hospital.
You were 9.
You think you know
what she went through.
If you were to read that report,
those images would haunt you.
And I need you focused
for your training.
Any other file.
Not that one.
I'm sorry.
All right, well, let me know
if you hear anything.
Any luck?
None of my CIs have heard
of this mobile lab.
[Cellphone chimes]
Got a lead?
Uh, no.
My mother-in-law
thinks Leah looks cold.
- Oh, she's visiting?
- No. No, no, no.
Uh, our baby cam
has a web feature,
and James sent her
the link.
So she can feel more connected.
That's great.
Okay. Are you...
Are you taking his side?
Since when is a pro-grandma
stance controversial?
Okay.
- Lopez, go to channel 13.
- What's up?
The whole mother-in-law
situation...
sweet or creepy?
Situational.
Why are you asking?
James hooked her up
with the baby cam feed.
Oh, no, that's
definitely creepy.
- You need to cut her off.
- Thank you.
Now, here's my question.
Wesley hired private security
on the Elijah front,
and he says he thinks
he hired a guy,
but this morning, an
ex-British Special Forces hottie
showed up at our door.
You think he's lying?
Uh...
More importantly,
what's her name?
Why?
So you can find a photo?
Uh, yeah.
It's Valentine's Day,
and I'm flying solo.
Charlie Bristow.
Charlie Bris...
♪
Wow.
Damn.
I'm sure she was probably
the most qualified candidate.
This woman is with your husband
right now?
Yes.
I would shut that down
so fast. Okay.
You guys... You guys, you are
all overreacting, all right?
Wesley is not
the cheating type.
He's not as squeaky clean
as you think.
Wait. Seriously?
There's a meth lab
cobbled together
by a bunch of mouth breathers
speeding through our city.
We need to focus.
Why are you so cranky?
First Valentine's Day.
You should be basking
in the glow of new love.
That's right.
What are you guys doing tonight?
We are not talking about
Valentine's Day plans
on an open channel.
Sgt. Grey: At least one of you
has some sense.
Nolan, Harper,
I need you to divert back
to the station.
We have a developing situation
that needs immediate attention. Copy that.
Copy.
And, Lopez,
get that woman
out of your house.
♪
[Helicopter blades whirring]
[Siren wailing]
Celina: Whoa. What the hell
is all this?
[Wailing continues]
[Radio chatter]
♪
Nolan: Shall we?
Nolan: Dr. Morgan.
I'd say it's a pleasure
to see you again,
but your news
is usually terrifying.
Well,
this is no different.
We had a containment failure
at LAX.
What does that mean?
Three travelers
who should have been
pulled aside for quarantine
weren't
and are currently at large
in Los Angeles.
What were
they exposed to?
Ebola.
Matthew Northrop, Kip Sherborn,
and Robert Betts
all landed at LAX
two hours ago
on the same flight
from Nigeria.
We need to track them down
and take them to St. Stephen's
for quarantine.
Based on when we think
they were exposed,
we've got
about five hours.
Okay. So just to clarify,
you want us to round up
Ebola patients
and, what,
transport them in the shop
with us?
An ambulance in hazmat mode will
meet you at every location.
But we should wear gloves
and face shields.
Yes. The good news...
Ebola is not airborne.
And if these men
are not exhibiting symptoms,
they are not infectious.
And if they are
exhibiting symptoms?
Exercise extreme caution
and avoid contact
with all bodily fluids.
Great. So it's
a regular Tuesday for us.
[Telephone rings]
We will exercise
all the cautions.
[Cellphone chimes]
Hm. Matthew Northrop's phone
just pinged at his house,
but no one
is answering.
Okay. Send us everything
you have on these guys.
You go grab Matthew.
We will focus on the other two.
Can do. We'll 9-5-2
when we get Matthew in hand.
Dr. Morgan: Good luck.
[Siren chirps, wails]
This Ebola thing won't be
on the news, will it?
I'm sure it'll get out eventually.
You don't want your mom
to worry.
I'll just tell her
it's my day off,
and I'll send some old pictures
of me at the beach.
You put a lot of effort
into protecting your mom.
How long has it been
since she left the house?
[Sighs] Five years?
You know, since the case
was never solved,
every guy she sees,
she thinks, "Is that him?
Did he kill my daughter?"
She can't handle it.
That's why
you want answers.
I can't pretend
it's selfless.
I want answers
for me, too.
I know it's the longest
of long shots,
but if there's any chance
I could help find this guy,
I don't care
what I have to go through.
Whatever it is will be nothing
next to what she endured.
I'm gonna do my best
to get you that file...
Really?
...but I'm going
to read it first
and then decide whether or not
to pass it along to you.
That's all I'm asking for.
Thank you.
♪
You know, you should cut
your mother-in-law some slack.
- Excuse me?
- Look, I'm sure this is hard
for her,
and she's just trying to be
a part of Leah's life.
And she is more
than welcome to do so,
but she does not need
24/7 access to my home.
Come over for brunch on a Sunday
like a normal grandparent.
Okay. And when's the last time
you invited her?
See?
Maybe if you
included her more,
she wouldn't go
all George Orwell on you.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
Minding my own business
starting now.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
[Siren wailing]
Is this gonna be awkward
with Bailey?
One way to find out.
Hi!
- Don't even.
- Yeah, she's still mad.
I'm not mad! I just don't know
how to ask for help.
Oh. You did not
say that to her.
Okay. Can we focus
on the task at hand?
Rhymes with "she-mole-a."
That's not even a word.
I know.
That was the joke.
It's so much better when you
have to explain the jokes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I didn't do it, Officers.
And firewoman. Huh?
Matthew Northrop?
Guilty as charged.
Why the face shields?
You were exposed to Ebola
on a recent trip.
We're gonna need you
to come with us.
Wait. What?
Yeah, you might want to pack
some toiletries
and a change of clothes.
Are you here alone?
Uh, yes.
Who you talking to, stud?
Ebola is spread
through bodily fluids.
Uh, ma'am, you're gonna want to
pack some clothes, too.
You gave me Ebola?
Uh, Mrs. Northrop, I-I know
this sounds scary, but...
- We're not married.
- But it said he...
Oh.
You're married?
We'll give you a moment
to put some clothes on.
Do I have to ride
in the same ambulance with him?
I'm afraid so.
Baby.
Baby, I can explain.
Did she seem more angry about
the Ebola or the wife?
♪
Pilot: Airship-1.
Still no sign of target truck.
No, I just want to know
if you heard from him.
Nah,
there's no problem, man.
I'm just trying to connect,
you know.
- Out with it.
- No, that's not
what happened.
- What?
- What is wrong with you today?
No. Listen, Darren.
No, no, no, no, no, man.
Nothing.
Bull.
You haven't... You haven't even
called me Hot Pants once.
I mean, is it... is it Noah?
Are you jealous?
Well, look.
I had to go home to her.
- No.
- You know how it is.
But...
This is about you
going behind my back
to get me into Metro.
Look, Vince knows
that I'm down to roll.
[Chuckles] I did not...
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's me.
I had to do something.
You were miserable
riding that desk.
Okay. Ok... Fine. But how do you
think that makes me look?
- What?
- How does it make me look?
My girlfriend has to solve
my problems for me?
Please tell me this is not
some fragile-male-ego thing.
That... That is not
what's happening here.
Are you just mad
that I solved this problem
better than you did?
You think
that's why I'm mad?
W... Come on!
We were just trying to help.
"We"?
Who else was involved?
Did I say "we"?
I meant "me."
Me was trying to help...
I was trying to help.
Oh, they're definitely
freezing me out.
None of my contacts
are getting back to me.
Dispatcher: 7-Adam-100.
L.A. CLEAR just flagged
an incoming 911 call from
one of your militia members,
Vince Jameson.
Would you patch it through, please?
Vince: [Weakly] Help.
I need help.
911 Operator: Yes, sir. What's
the nature of your emergency?
It got on me.
I can't breathe!
What got on you?
Sir, what were you exposed to?
They left me.
Please. I'm dying.
Dispatch, we need
the address for that call.
[Siren wailing, engine revs]
Sir, can you hear me?
We have officers on the scene
and an ambulance on the way.
Sir?
It might be too late.
He might not be alone.
Stay alert.
♪
[Train whistle in distance]
[Tense music plays]
♪
Body.
Geez.
♪
Meth did not do that
to his body.
No. That's chemical weapons exposure.
Look, your militia
is not making meth.
They're making
sarin gas.
♪
As if we're not busy enough.
[Radio chatter]
It's definitely
chemical-weapons exposure.
My guess is sarin gas.
I've seen it before.
- Where?
- Sorry. It's classified.
Boys love saying that.
Bring me up to speed?
We've been tracking
what we thought
was a mobile meth lab
tied to a militia group.
Oh, you got the lab part right
but the cook part wrong.
Lucy: Yeah, basically.
As if we're not
busy enough.
That's what I said.
Accidental exposure?
It seems likely.
They were either
loading supplies or...
Lucy: Or preparing
for an attack.
Worst case,
what kind of body count
are we looking at
if this is sarin?
Depends on several variables...
concentration of the gas,
population density,
weather conditions.
The good news is,
sarin evaporates quickly.
The threat is immediate
but short-lived.
Well, they'll want to release it
somewhere contained,
maximize
effectiveness.
I'll notify the brass
and the Feds,
put together
a target list.
I'll get another rapid response
team in the field.
[Cellphone ringing]
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I was just checking on you.
The news is crazy.
We're on top
of the sarin gas situation.
I was talking about Ebola.
There's sarin gas?
Forget I said anything.
I'll try.
Look, I just wanted to call
and say I love you
and I'm sorry
about this morning.
I'm sorry, too. We're both
under a lot of stress.
Uh, why is Charlie holding
our son?
Oh. Uh, he was fussing,
and she kind of swooped in.
She's really good
with him.
I gotta go.
Uh, Ange...[Cellphone beeps]
[Sighs]
Vince has a sister
in Eagle Rock.
Well, let's get her down here,
show her what happened
to her brother,
see if she knows anything.
We got
a situation.
A friend of our second
Ebola suspect
just heard that Kip's girlfriend
went into labor an hour ago.
Where?
[Sirens wailing]
♪
[Elevator bell dings]
Sir, I need you to stop
right there.
What's going on?
Seriously, I don't know
what's going on,
but I don't have time
for it.
My girlfriend
is about to have a baby,
and I barely made it back
in time.
I am so sorry,
Mr. Sherborn,
but you are gonna miss
that birth.
The CDC believes that
you have been exposed to Ebola.
You need to quarantine immediately.
Am I g...
Am I gonna die?
I...just got my life together.
I-I was gonna be a dad.
I always wanted to be a dad.
This can't be happening.
But it is.
And the most important thing
for your family right now
is for you to face this head on
and get treatment
if you need to, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
Can you make sure
she gets these flowers?
I'm sorry, sir,
but those are gonna need
to be quarantined, too,
since you touched them.
♪
Okay. Thank you.
All right.
Kip has been quarantined.
Both he and Matthew
have tested positive,
but since we isolated them
before they were exhibiting
any symptoms,
Dr. Morgan is confident
that the infection stopped
with them.
- Well, that's good.
- Yes, that is good.
However, given the timeframe
of the infection,
our boy Robert is probably about
to start exhibiting symptoms,
- if he hasn't started already.
- And that's bad.
And that is bad.[Cellphone chimes]
Is that
my sister's file?
Yes.
Okay.
Now that it's really happening,
I'm kind of scared.
You can bow out
at any time.
I know.
I mean, with cold cases,
what are the odds
her murder gets solved?
Well, DNA testing gets better
all the time,
and there certainly
is a possibility
that detectives missed something
crucial in their investigation.
But cases like this,
a murdered kid,
cops tend to pull out
all the stops.
For white kids, maybe.
The file will tell us
a lot about the quality
of the investigation
and if the investigators
had any bias.
Dispatcher: 7-Adam-15.
Priority traffic from CDC.
Last suspected carrier,
Robert Betts, was just seen
leaving an apartment building
near your location.
R.P. says Robert
is headed to work.
Hazmat team is en route.
Copy that. What's the make
and model of his vehicle?
No vehicle.
P.O.I. takes the bus.
[Dramatic music plays]
Control, 7-Adam-15,
I need D.O.T.
to shut down bus service
along Victory Boulevard.
Dispatcher:
Copy. Will notify D.O.T.
All right,
let's find this guy.
♪
Uh, Nolan, green jacket
at 11 o'clock.
Robert Betts, we need to stop
you right where you are.
[Hip-hop music plays
on headphones]
Robert Betts, LAPD.
We need you to stop right there.
All right.
Let's get him.
[Siren wailing]
♪
- Oh, my God!
- Whoa, whoa.
Driver, I'm gonna need you
to pull the bus over.
Right up there. Thank you.
[Siren wailing]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Siren stops, brakes squeak]
Nobody gets on or off the bus,
all right?
Robert Betts, I need you to come
talk to us for a minute.
Why?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Yes, sir. You're not in
any trouble at all,
but it is very important you
come speak with us right now.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry, folks.
We'll have you on your way
in a minute.
[Sirens wailing]
Nolan:
Right this way, sir.
- Come on over here.
- Shut the doors.
Hi, Mr. Betts. I'm sure this is
all a bit overwhelming,
but we're here to help you,
- okay?
- I don't understand.
We believe you were exposed
to the Ebola virus
on your recent trip
to Nigeria.
We're here to escort you
to a quarantine unit,
test you for the virus,
and make sure you get treatment
if needed.
Have you been feeling sick
at all?
Uh, no.
I-I mean, uh, m-my nose started
running a little while ago.
- Okay.
- Does that mean we need
to quarantine everyone else?
Yes. They may have been exposed,
even in that short amount
of time.
We'll need to take them
to St. Stephen's
for quarantine and observation
just in case.
Understood.
All right.
Phil: You don't understand.
I can't be late.
I'm in a big hurry.
You gotta let me go.
Cops said no one in
or out.
[Indistinct shouting]
Nolan: Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
[Taser crackling]
[Indistinct shouting]
Look. I'm sorry.
But I need you
back on the bus.
[Groans]
Everyone is going
to the hospital.
[Handcuffs clicks]
All right. Vince's sister should
be landing any minute.
Hook me up.
You think
she'll recognize you?
Only met her once. Wasn't clear
if she was a believer.
[Vehicle approaching]
[Engine shuts off]
Tim: Ms. Jameson.
I'm Sergeant Bradford.
This about my brother?
It is.
I'm sorry to inform you, but...
he was killed
earlier today.
What? How?
Let me show you.
[Zipper opening]
What the hell happened
to him?
Sarin gas.
But we think you know that already.
I do not. I have no idea
what Vince has been into.
We barely talk.
Ms. Jameson, your brother's
engaged in domestic terrorism.
The group he was working with
is still at large,
and they're planning
an attack.
We need you to tell us
everything you know.
I told you.
I don't know nothing.
Why don't you ask him?
He was with my brother
last time I saw him.
We tried,
but he lawyered up.
Okay. Look.
I wish I could help,
but I can't.
Now if you're done
with the questions,
I'm gonna go call my mom,
tell her about Vince.
♪
- You hear all that?
- Yeah.
[Engine starts]
♪
Well, hopefully we spooked her
enough to make a call.
[Handcuffs click]
♪
Thank you.
Control, target is on the move.
Has she made a call yet?
Dispatcher: Patching the tap
to your unit now.
[Beeping]
Raelynn: It's me.
Clint:
You shouldn't be calling.
What the hell happened
to Vince?!
Martyr to the cause.
He'll be a hero soon enough.
Yeah. Well, the cops
are right on top of us.
Doesn't matter. I'm on Pico,
heading for Union Station.
It'll all be over
in 30 minutes.
Let's go.
Pilot: Airship-1,
arriving at target location.
Eyes open for suspect vehicle,
white truck with blue stripe.
All units in the vicinity
of Union Station,
once we get a visual
on the truck,
we need to divert it
onto Mission Road,
where a roadblock
is being established.
Airship-1,
I have eyes on roadblock units.
7-Adam-15 and 7-Adam-9
are landing
at the roadblock location.
[Sirens wailing]
[Tires screeching]
♪
Nolan: All right.
Let's get the gas masks
from the war bags.
♪
Are we really about
to play chicken
with chemical weapons after
we played chicken with Ebola?
That's the job.
Better us than the people
at Union Station.
[Helicopter blades whirring]
♪
Metro units inbound.
First Team will stage up
with Nolan.
Second Team,
stage off site with us,
bring up the rear.
♪
Hey.
I hear there might be
some hazard pay involved.
I'd say sarin gas definitely
qualifies as hazardous.
I mean, you might even get
a medal.
I'd rather have the money.
Can't pay for a wedding
with a medal.
[Cellphone ringing]
It's my mom. If I don't answer,
she'll be worried.
Uh, do it quickly.
[Ringing stops]
Hola, mami.
I can't talk.
No,
I'm not working today.
Yeah.
I'm about to meet some friends.
I'll call you after, okay?
Te amo.
All right. Post up.
♪
[Helicopter blades whirring]
Pilot: Airship-1... Contact.
I have eyes on target vehicle.
Heading West on 4th.
7-Adam-7. We see it.
We're gonna spook them into
turning right on Mission.
♪
Hit lights and sirens.
Speed past them
to pull that Camry over.
Aaron:
He's gonna crap himself.
Yeah.
That is what I am counting on.
He will want to get as far
from us as possible.
[Siren wailing]
Pilot: Airship-1,
truck is turning.
♪
Approaching our street closure.
Come on. Come on. Turn right.
Turn right. Turn right.
[Dramatic music plays]
♪
Truck turning right.
ETA to roadblock, 20 seconds.
All right. Stay ready.
♪
[Sirens wailing]
[Tires screech]
♪
Sgt. Grey: Nolan,
what's the driver doing?
He's just sitting there.
♪
Driver,
turn off your engine.
Throw the keys out the window, now.
♪
Go.
[Drone buzzing]
♪
[Gunshots]
Oh, hell no.
Man: Shots fired.
Repeat... shots fired.
[Gunshots, glass breaking]
Back off
a little bit?
You're no fun.
Driver,
you are sitting in a truck
filled with
deadly nerve toxins,
surrounded by armed police
officers with gas masks.
Releasing the gas now
will result in only your death.
Firing your weapon again
Roll down your window.
Toss the gun out. Do it now.
[Drone buzzing]
♪
[Gun clatters]
With your left hand,
open the door from the outside.
Climb out.
[Drone buzzing]
All right. Step to the front
of the vehicle.
Lay down on the ground,
arms and legs out.
♪
All units,
suspect in custody.
We are Code 4.
♪
Nice.
I'm assuming
when you said Valentine's Day
was the most dangerous day
of the year,
you were
not expecting that.
No. No. Usually it's just
an unending series
of domestic calls.
[Cameras beep]
Thank you for getting
my sister's file.
Obviously, I don't expect you
to read it tonight,
not after what
we just went through.
I appreciate that.
And I will go over it
in the morning before roll call.
But?
But I did take
a quick glance at it already,
and those pictures were hard
to see, even for me.
Okay.
Nothing I say
is going to dissuade you, is it?
Look, it might be hard to look
at, but she experienced it.
How can I choose
to look away?
I'm not gonna pretend
to understand how you feel,
but I have a responsibility
to you to prepare you
for whatever comes your way
as a police officer,
and that includes
your sister's case.
You're not gonna do her
any good
by opening this door
before you're ready.
- Do you understand?
- I understand.
But I'm absolutely going to
open it as soon as I am.
And I'll be right there
with you.
[Reuben And The Dark's "Change"
plays]
♪
What is
that monstrosity?
So, I did a search
for the best apology flower,
and turns out
there are a lot of opinions.
So I got one of each.
I did not need
an apology.
I also took away my mom's access
to the baby monitor.
Because you are right,
we definitely need
that boundary.
Now, that I needed.
[Chuckles]
But, you know,
maybe we can invite her
to brunch on Sunday.
Seriously?
Where'd that come from?
You know,
I just thought it'd be nice
to have her over
a little more.
I'll extend the invitation.
Happy Valentine's Day?
Happy Valentine's Day.
Mm.
You ready to go?
I got dinner in the oven,
and your present is waiting
on the table.
Well, there's only one present
I want.
Oh. Okay.
[Chuckles]
But, I mean,
I will take the one
that's on the table as well.
Yeah. I figured
that was a given.
Mm-hmm. [Laughs]
♪ I know that
you've been changing, too ♪
♪ I've been
Hi.
♪ Changing
I get why you're angry.
Even though you were miserable
as court liaison
and I spearheaded
an almost impossible
five-player trade
to save you...
I shouldn't have done it
all behind your back.
Is that an apology?
Yes.
All right.
No! Look, because you never
would've let me work my magic
if I had told you,
and then I would have ended up
transferring to another station
to save you from yourself,
and... this worked out
so much better.
And if you can't see that,
I'm sorry not sorry.
♪
Okay.
I accept
your non-apology.
- Good.
So, are we going to dinner
or what?
We are.
But your, uh...
your outfit is missing
a little something.
What?[Drawer opens]
♪
Happy Valentine's Day.
Oh, wow.
It's beautiful.
Did you pick this out
yourself?
I did.
Is that shocking?
No.
You clearly have
good taste.
♪ I've been changing
Thank you.
♪ By change
♪ but I'm holding on
Do you want
to skip dinner?
No. I'm hungry.
And you're gonna need that fuel
for later.
♪ They say fear, like love
♪ Is a call into the wild
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
No worries.
Just making some dinner.
So you're not
still mad at me?
Oh, still a little mad.
But I'm also really hungry.
Well, that works great
for me.
Dare I ask why your anger
has subsided?
Well, I realized
that this was our first fight.
No. What?
That can't be right.
What about, um...
What about the time you lied
about having a husband?
Well, that wasn't
really a fight.
That was me keeping a secret
from you
and you being
justifiably upset.
Hmm.
It was one-sided.
In a fight, both parties need
to feel like they're right.
Well, I would like to apologize
for my part
in our first real fight.
I... F-For causing
our first real fight.
Thank you.
Moving forward, you need to stop
trying to fix everything.
And I will start trying
to ask for help more.
Deal.
Great.
Now will you
help me cook?
No.
- No?
- Nope.
[Laughing]
What do you mean, "No"?
No, no.[Laughing]
You don't get to say no.
Come here.
[Both laugh]
♪
So, how was your day?
It was quiet
in comparison.
But then again, World War II
would seem quiet in comparison.
Mm-hmm.
You're not really mad
about Charlie, are you?
Well, she's not even
in your league.
I know. Hmm.
It was never actually
about her.
It's everything...
the pregnancy, Elijah,
sarin gas, Ebola.
I just want one easy day.
♪
[Knock on door]
[Exhales deeply]
[Door opens]
Sorry to bother you, but
a messenger just delivered this.
There's no card, but it's
clearly from Elijah Stone.
♪
I mean... you got to
give the guy credit
for a holiday-appropriate
threat.
That's not funny.
I'm not laughing.
♪
Captions by VITAC...