1
00:00:00,100 --> 00:00:01,300
<i>Previously on</i> <font color="#ff8040">The Rookie</font>...

2
00:00:01,376 --> 00:00:04,713
People are gonna die,
and you can't save them.

3
00:00:04,713 --> 00:00:07,049
I ate their pain
like a five-star meal.

4
00:00:10,219 --> 00:00:11,345
Do you want to come in?

5
00:00:11,345 --> 00:00:13,722
I didn't know
that you were gonna be here.

6
00:00:13,722 --> 00:00:15,891
Tim and I were ju--
No.

7
00:00:15,891 --> 00:00:17,267
Have you decided
what you're gonna do

8
00:00:17,267 --> 00:00:18,393
with your Golden Ticket?

9
00:00:18,393 --> 00:00:20,395
So next week, you're off
to F. T. O. school.

10
00:00:20,395 --> 00:00:22,981
You will officially be
a Field Training Officer.

11
00:00:22,981 --> 00:00:24,775
Detective Misha Porter.
I'm here to recruit you.

12
00:00:24,775 --> 00:00:26,902
When do classes start?
Next Monday.

13
00:01:01,561 --> 00:01:03,146
Hi.
Is there a problem, Officer?

14
00:01:03,146 --> 00:01:06,817
Hi.
Um...where's the driver?

15
00:01:06,817 --> 00:01:08,902
It's a driverless car,
obviously.

16
00:01:08,902 --> 00:01:09,945
My dad designs them.

17
00:01:09,945 --> 00:01:12,155
He was busy,
so he told it to take me.

18
00:01:12,155 --> 00:01:17,327
Okay. Well, he --
um, it just ran a stop sign.

19
00:01:17,327 --> 00:01:19,830
The camera must
not have seen it.

20
00:01:19,830 --> 00:01:24,084
Right. But I'm gonna have to
write you a ticket.

21
00:01:24,084 --> 00:01:25,419
Why? I wasn't driving.

22
00:01:25,419 --> 00:01:28,213
Yeah, not --
not you, but, um...

23
00:01:28,213 --> 00:01:31,466
Um...

24
00:01:37,472 --> 00:01:39,182
Surprise!

25
00:01:39,182 --> 00:01:40,434
Oh!

26
00:01:40,434 --> 00:01:43,687
You're home from undercover
school, so, you know, mm.

27
00:01:43,687 --> 00:01:46,064
I love it.

28
00:01:46,064 --> 00:01:48,150
Well, mm...

29
00:01:48,150 --> 00:01:49,484
I'm gonna be late for class,

30
00:01:49,484 --> 00:01:51,028
but I want to hear
all about it tonight.

31
00:01:51,028 --> 00:01:53,363
Okay, great.

32
00:01:53,363 --> 00:01:54,323
Oh, wait.
You're --

33
00:01:54,323 --> 00:01:55,907
But -- Yep.

34
00:01:55,907 --> 00:01:59,369
Oh, God.

35
00:02:00,662 --> 00:02:02,080
Mm.

36
00:02:02,080 --> 00:02:03,498
Ah.
Hi.

37
00:02:03,498 --> 00:02:04,708
Hi.

38
00:02:04,708 --> 00:02:06,043
I'm so happy you're home.

39
00:02:06,043 --> 00:02:07,085
How are you?

40
00:02:07,085 --> 00:02:08,295
Great.
Mm?

41
00:02:08,295 --> 00:02:11,798
Uh, typing still
a bit of a challenge.

42
00:02:11,798 --> 00:02:14,092
And forget about
opening a jar.

43
00:02:14,092 --> 00:02:16,386
It hasn't been too much for you,
being back at work?

44
00:02:16,386 --> 00:02:17,679
Are you kidding?

45
00:02:17,679 --> 00:02:19,598
I was going out of my mind
sitting on the couch all day.

46
00:02:19,598 --> 00:02:22,559
There's something else
that's been helping me more.

47
00:02:25,896 --> 00:02:28,565
An online group
that's hunting Rosalind.

48
00:02:28,565 --> 00:02:30,942
They contacted me
a few weeks ago.

49
00:02:30,942 --> 00:02:33,070
They call themselves
"Dye-Hards."

50
00:02:33,070 --> 00:02:37,532
Hmm. Let me guess.
"D-Y-E" as in Rosalind "Dyer"?

51
00:02:37,532 --> 00:02:39,409
Exactly.
Mm-hmm.

52
00:02:39,409 --> 00:02:41,745
At first I thought
they were a bunch of kooks

53
00:02:41,745 --> 00:02:43,372
who just wanted to hear
about the attack.

54
00:02:43,372 --> 00:02:47,042
But, you know, th-their research
is actually really impressive.

55
00:02:47,042 --> 00:02:49,169
Uh, what kind of research?
What --

56
00:02:49,169 --> 00:02:50,587
They --
They scour message boards,

57
00:02:50,587 --> 00:02:53,340
subreddits,
and social media posts for tips,

58
00:02:53,340 --> 00:02:56,718
then compile the most credible
ones in an encrypted PDF

59
00:02:56,718 --> 00:02:58,303
they call
"The Mother Doc."

60
00:02:58,303 --> 00:03:00,305
And they...

61
00:03:00,305 --> 00:03:03,392
Well, I was hoping
you might take a look.

62
00:03:03,392 --> 00:03:06,186
Chris,
I'm a patrol officer.

63
00:03:06,186 --> 00:03:09,272
I-I -- Um, I'm not a part
of the investigation.

64
00:03:09,272 --> 00:03:11,566
But you're still a cop.

65
00:03:11,566 --> 00:03:12,943
Look, I wouldn't ask,

66
00:03:12,943 --> 00:03:14,903
but the task force
has been blowing me off.

67
00:03:14,903 --> 00:03:17,072
You are still recovering.

68
00:03:17,072 --> 00:03:19,741
You know, and it's --
it's not healthy

69
00:03:19,741 --> 00:03:23,036
to be immersed in
hunting Rosalind all day long.

70
00:03:23,036 --> 00:03:25,163
Just take a look.

71
00:03:25,163 --> 00:03:27,541
If you think it's
worth passing on, great.

72
00:03:27,541 --> 00:03:30,127
If not, totally fine.

73
00:03:30,127 --> 00:03:34,089
Fine. I will look at
"The Mother Doc."

74
00:03:34,089 --> 00:03:36,716
Thanks.

75
00:03:36,716 --> 00:03:39,219
Your first day
as a Training Officer.

76
00:03:39,219 --> 00:03:40,804
How does it feel?

77
00:03:40,804 --> 00:03:42,931
Well, considering
six weeks ago,

78
00:03:42,931 --> 00:03:45,767
I thought I'd have to wait
another...two years,

79
00:03:45,767 --> 00:03:47,352
pretty fantastic.

80
00:03:47,352 --> 00:03:48,770
What you got there?

81
00:03:48,770 --> 00:03:50,939
Nothing. Just a couple things
I didn't want to forget.

82
00:03:50,939 --> 00:03:52,649
Let me see, let me see.

83
00:03:55,861 --> 00:03:58,989
"How to set up a shop"?
"Processing a prisoner"?

84
00:03:58,989 --> 00:04:03,326
Nolan, I sincerely hope after
two years in the department

85
00:04:03,326 --> 00:04:05,871
and a month at the
F. T. O. Training Academy,

86
00:04:05,871 --> 00:04:07,706
you don't need
a crib sheet.

87
00:04:07,706 --> 00:04:09,207
No, sir. No, I just --

88
00:04:09,207 --> 00:04:12,294
I-I've been working towards this
so long,

89
00:04:12,294 --> 00:04:14,087
I just didn't want
to mess anything up.

90
00:04:14,087 --> 00:04:15,964
Oh, but you will.

91
00:04:15,964 --> 00:04:19,551
This is your first time training
a rookie officer from jump,

92
00:04:19,551 --> 00:04:22,304
making you
a rookie yourself.

93
00:04:22,304 --> 00:04:25,307
Which I'm sure you're not gonna
haze me about at all.

94
00:04:25,307 --> 00:04:27,642
You're gonna stumble.

95
00:04:27,642 --> 00:04:30,312
But you're a good cop
and you know how to do the job.

96
00:04:30,312 --> 00:04:33,315
Thank you, sir.
I needed that.

97
00:04:33,315 --> 00:04:36,067
Good, 'cause you're not
getting this back.

98
00:04:36,067 --> 00:04:39,404
Now, let's go
meet your rookie, boot.

99
00:04:41,072 --> 00:04:44,159
So, alright,
first things first --

100
00:04:44,159 --> 00:04:46,787
So, I'd like to congratulate
Officer Lucy Chen

101
00:04:46,787 --> 00:04:48,538
for successfully completing

102
00:04:48,538 --> 00:04:52,667
the D. E. A. Covert Operations
Training Academy,

103
00:04:52,667 --> 00:04:54,211
which is no small feat.

104
00:04:59,257 --> 00:05:01,301
Good to have you back,
Officer Chen.

105
00:05:01,301 --> 00:05:02,761
Happy to be back,
sir.

106
00:05:02,761 --> 00:05:05,514
Also, I have the privilege
to introduce

107
00:05:05,514 --> 00:05:09,810
Mid-Wilshire's newest
Training Officer, John Nolan.

108
00:05:09,810 --> 00:05:11,186
Hey, hey, hey.

109
00:05:13,063 --> 00:05:14,689
Good work.

110
00:05:14,689 --> 00:05:17,025
And since Harper has decided
to abandon patrol

111
00:05:17,025 --> 00:05:19,236
for a cushy desk job
with the detectives,

112
00:05:19,236 --> 00:05:21,696
today Nolan will take on
the responsibility

113
00:05:21,696 --> 00:05:23,240
of training
his first rookie.

114
00:05:23,240 --> 00:05:24,908
Officer, stand up,

115
00:05:24,908 --> 00:05:26,910
state your name
and badge number.

116
00:05:26,910 --> 00:05:30,121
I'm Celina Juarez,
badge number 53397.

117
00:05:30,121 --> 00:05:32,332
Officer Juarez,

118
00:05:32,332 --> 00:05:33,792
you have earned the right
to be in this room,

119
00:05:33,792 --> 00:05:35,919
but you must
prove yourself to stay.

120
00:05:35,919 --> 00:05:38,046
The way we do things
matters.

121
00:05:38,046 --> 00:05:40,632
Protocol and tradition
are the metal

122
00:05:40,632 --> 00:05:44,010
from which every cop
in this city is forged.

123
00:05:44,010 --> 00:05:45,720
You have anything
to add?

124
00:05:45,720 --> 00:05:47,722
I see you got top marks
at the Academy.

125
00:05:47,722 --> 00:05:48,890
Good for you.

126
00:05:48,890 --> 00:05:50,183
None of that matters
when you hit the street,

127
00:05:50,183 --> 00:05:51,560
so assume
you know nothing,

128
00:05:51,560 --> 00:05:53,144
and you'll never be wrong.

129
00:05:53,144 --> 00:05:54,729
Got it?
Yes, sir.

130
00:05:54,729 --> 00:05:57,357
That's it.
Be safe out there.

131
00:05:58,984 --> 00:06:01,361
Hi, I'm Celina --

132
00:06:01,361 --> 00:06:03,738
your new rookie who, uh,
apparently knows nothing.

133
00:06:03,738 --> 00:06:05,448
Oh, I wouldn't say
"nothing."

134
00:06:05,448 --> 00:06:07,158
Dean's List, D3 soccer,

135
00:06:07,158 --> 00:06:08,994
graduate classes
in criminal justice --

136
00:06:08,994 --> 00:06:10,245
pretty impressive.
Thank you.

137
00:06:10,245 --> 00:06:11,830
But I'm aware that
academia and street smarts

138
00:06:11,830 --> 00:06:13,164
are two different things.

139
00:06:13,164 --> 00:06:15,959
I like to think simple
common sense trumps them both.

140
00:06:15,959 --> 00:06:17,919
But if you have any questions,
you can always come and ask me.

141
00:06:17,919 --> 00:06:19,963
Yep, and me.
Hi. I'm Lucy Chen.

142
00:06:19,963 --> 00:06:21,256
Nice to meet you, ma'am.

143
00:06:21,256 --> 00:06:23,091
May I?
Please.

144
00:06:23,091 --> 00:06:24,259
Sergeant Bradford's right.

145
00:06:24,259 --> 00:06:26,428
The most important thing
is to never pretend

146
00:06:26,428 --> 00:06:27,846
that you know
something you don't.

147
00:06:27,846 --> 00:06:29,764
Pretending is what
gets you killed out there.

148
00:06:29,764 --> 00:06:33,018
You're very lucky to have
Officer Nolan as your T. O.

149
00:06:33,018 --> 00:06:34,561
He's a great listener.

150
00:06:34,561 --> 00:06:36,271
And if you ever want
to talk to another woman

151
00:06:36,271 --> 00:06:39,983
who was in your shoes
not that long ago, um, I'm here.

152
00:06:39,983 --> 00:06:41,735
Thank you.
That means a lot.

153
00:06:41,735 --> 00:06:43,153
Yeah, of course.

154
00:06:43,153 --> 00:06:45,280
You guys have
a great first shift.

155
00:06:45,280 --> 00:06:47,991
Thank you,
Officer Chen.

156
00:06:47,991 --> 00:06:49,576
Are you ready
to get started?

157
00:06:49,576 --> 00:06:51,119
Yes, sir.

158
00:06:51,119 --> 00:06:53,288
Congrats on making P2.
Thank you.

159
00:06:53,288 --> 00:06:54,456
I heard
you're doing a great job

160
00:06:54,456 --> 00:06:56,416
riding with Tim
as his Sergeant's Aide.

161
00:06:56,416 --> 00:06:58,001
Thanks, but look,
I'm ready to step aside

162
00:06:58,001 --> 00:06:59,461
now that you're back,
s--

163
00:06:59,461 --> 00:07:01,421
Wait, Tim said
I'm doing a great job?

164
00:07:01,421 --> 00:07:03,465
Uh, no. Sorry.
Oh.

165
00:07:03,465 --> 00:07:04,758
I-I made
that last part up.

166
00:07:04,758 --> 00:07:06,217
But, you know,
he hasn't replaced you yet,

167
00:07:06,217 --> 00:07:07,844
so he's happy.

168
00:07:07,844 --> 00:07:10,513
You should, um,
stick with him.

169
00:07:10,513 --> 00:07:11,973
Really? You sure?

170
00:07:11,973 --> 00:07:14,017
- Yeah.
- I mean, I could...

171
00:07:14,017 --> 00:07:16,102
...use some quiet time
riding solo,

172
00:07:16,102 --> 00:07:19,814
thinking about next steps
in my career.

173
00:07:19,814 --> 00:07:21,441
You haven't heard
a word I've said.

174
00:07:21,441 --> 00:07:24,319
No, sorry. Uh, yeah, I got
something I got to take care of.

175
00:07:24,319 --> 00:07:26,363
Excuse me.

176
00:07:26,363 --> 00:07:28,531
Good talk.

177
00:07:28,531 --> 00:07:30,367
Good morning.

178
00:07:30,367 --> 00:07:31,826
Thank God you're back.

179
00:07:31,826 --> 00:07:33,703
But first things first --

180
00:07:33,703 --> 00:07:36,247
I need to see photos
of Leah ASAP.

181
00:07:36,247 --> 00:07:37,540
Look.

182
00:07:39,167 --> 00:07:41,586
Oh, my God.
She's gorgeous.

183
00:07:41,586 --> 00:07:43,463
It must have been hard
to leave her this morning.

184
00:07:43,463 --> 00:07:44,506
Yeah, it was.

185
00:07:44,506 --> 00:07:45,965
You ready to think
about crime again?

186
00:07:45,965 --> 00:07:48,510
Yes.
What can I help with?

187
00:07:48,510 --> 00:07:50,762
Let's see.

188
00:07:50,762 --> 00:07:53,932
Jill Baskin.
Missing now for three days.

189
00:07:53,932 --> 00:07:55,892
Uh, any suspects?

190
00:07:55,892 --> 00:07:58,520
The roommate says Jill's
ex-boyfriend had a nasty temper,

191
00:07:58,520 --> 00:08:01,147
but I haven't been able
to find enough for a warrant.

192
00:08:01,147 --> 00:08:03,066
I'd love fresh eyes.

193
00:08:03,066 --> 00:08:04,234
Tyler Harvin.

194
00:08:04,234 --> 00:08:05,735
Alright,
I will jump on it.

195
00:08:05,735 --> 00:08:07,404
Thanks.

196
00:08:07,404 --> 00:08:10,240
This is your shop.
Do not call it a car,

197
00:08:10,240 --> 00:08:12,033
a cruiser,
or a black and white.

198
00:08:12,033 --> 00:08:12,909
It is where you work.

199
00:08:12,909 --> 00:08:14,577
Anytime you leave the shop,

200
00:08:14,577 --> 00:08:15,995
your body camera
needs to be on.

201
00:08:20,291 --> 00:08:22,877
Perfect.

202
00:08:22,877 --> 00:08:25,964
First, check the exterior
of the shop for any damage.

203
00:08:25,964 --> 00:08:28,591
You are looking for dents,
dings, scratches.

204
00:08:28,591 --> 00:08:29,968
We're gonna check
the back seat

205
00:08:29,968 --> 00:08:31,928
for anything a suspect
might have left behind --

206
00:08:31,928 --> 00:08:34,389
money, weapons...

207
00:08:34,389 --> 00:08:36,141
drugs.

208
00:08:36,141 --> 00:08:37,434
Was someone smoking weed
in here?

209
00:08:37,434 --> 00:08:39,060
I think that was me.

210
00:08:39,060 --> 00:08:40,186
Excuse me?

211
00:08:40,186 --> 00:08:43,732
No, it's not marijuana.
I-I saged the shop.

212
00:08:43,732 --> 00:08:46,943
You --
That's unconventional.

213
00:08:46,943 --> 00:08:48,695
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't think you'd notice.

214
00:08:48,695 --> 00:08:49,988
It's just that
it's my first day,

215
00:08:49,988 --> 00:08:52,407
and I figured I could use
all the help I could get, right?

216
00:08:52,407 --> 00:08:55,952
Sure. Next time,
just check with me first.

217
00:08:55,952 --> 00:09:00,665
Okay. Now, where was I?
It was...

218
00:09:00,665 --> 00:09:03,126
My Rook Book says you check
the trunk for equipment.

219
00:09:03,126 --> 00:09:04,586
The trunk.

220
00:09:04,586 --> 00:09:07,297
We're gonna need police tape.
We're gonna need road flares.

221
00:09:07,297 --> 00:09:09,507
Load up.

222
00:09:13,845 --> 00:09:16,014
Hey, you're back.
How was U. C. school?

223
00:09:16,014 --> 00:09:18,266
Challenging.

224
00:09:18,266 --> 00:09:20,268
How's life
working for the enemy?

225
00:09:20,268 --> 00:09:21,936
Not as weird
as I thought it would be.

226
00:09:21,936 --> 00:09:22,937
It's actually
pretty interesting

227
00:09:22,937 --> 00:09:24,272
seeing things
from the other side.

228
00:09:24,272 --> 00:09:27,650
That's great.
Um, how is Chris doing?

229
00:09:27,650 --> 00:09:28,985
Yeah, he seems fine.

230
00:09:28,985 --> 00:09:30,570
You know, they're starting
him off slow,

231
00:09:30,570 --> 00:09:31,780
nothing too intense.
Why?

232
00:09:31,780 --> 00:09:34,324
Has he talked to you
about this online community

233
00:09:34,324 --> 00:09:36,201
he joined
that's hunting Rosalind?

234
00:09:36,201 --> 00:09:39,496
No, but I could see
why that would worry you.

235
00:09:39,496 --> 00:09:41,039
Want me to
keep an eye on him?

236
00:09:41,039 --> 00:09:43,416
Yeah, I really do.

237
00:09:43,416 --> 00:09:44,501
Yeah, no problem.

238
00:09:44,501 --> 00:09:47,629
But, Lucy,
just give him time.

239
00:09:47,629 --> 00:09:49,339
We've both been
where he is.

240
00:09:49,339 --> 00:09:51,299
He'll get through it.

241
00:09:57,388 --> 00:09:58,973
What's the name of the store
we just passed?

242
00:09:58,973 --> 00:10:00,642
Huh?
Uh, it was, uh --

243
00:10:00,642 --> 00:10:02,977
You have no idea because
your face has been on your phone

244
00:10:02,977 --> 00:10:05,146
for the past 10 minutes.
Put it away.

245
00:10:05,146 --> 00:10:07,857
Sorry, sir. It's just, um...

246
00:10:07,857 --> 00:10:09,734
There's something going on
that I don't know how to handle.

247
00:10:09,734 --> 00:10:11,027
You know the deal.

248
00:10:11,027 --> 00:10:12,654
This is a personal-life
free zone.

249
00:10:12,654 --> 00:10:14,405
Yes, sir. But, uh,

250
00:10:14,405 --> 00:10:17,075
this is something that could,
like, derail my career.

251
00:10:20,078 --> 00:10:21,704
Alright.
What is it?

252
00:10:21,704 --> 00:10:24,332
I'm being blackmailed.

253
00:10:24,332 --> 00:10:25,542
Yeah, so, I, um --

254
00:10:25,542 --> 00:10:27,585
I sent this photo
to this girl on a dating app,

255
00:10:27,585 --> 00:10:29,587
you know, just shirtless,
nothing X-rated.

256
00:10:29,587 --> 00:10:31,047
A thirst trap,
you know?

257
00:10:31,047 --> 00:10:32,215
I wish I didn't.

258
00:10:32,215 --> 00:10:35,635
Turns out it was some dude,
and I was catfished.

259
00:10:35,635 --> 00:10:37,011
And now
he's blackmailing me.

260
00:10:37,011 --> 00:10:39,097
With what? You said
the photo didn't show anything.

261
00:10:39,097 --> 00:10:40,640
Right.
The -- The original one didn't.

262
00:10:40,640 --> 00:10:42,851
But then
he Photoshopped it.

263
00:10:42,851 --> 00:10:44,435
Whoa.
Yeah.

264
00:10:44,435 --> 00:10:45,854
What does he want?

265
00:10:45,854 --> 00:10:47,063
He didn't say.

266
00:10:47,063 --> 00:10:50,108
He just told me to wait
for further instructions.

267
00:10:50,108 --> 00:10:53,528
Well, I mean,
it could be worse.

268
00:10:53,528 --> 00:10:55,405
At least he was generous.

269
00:11:04,289 --> 00:11:08,334
Control, 7-L-19,
I have a 10-34 at The Nautilus

270
00:11:08,334 --> 00:11:10,420
near the corner
of Virgil and West Fourth.

271
00:11:10,420 --> 00:11:13,089
I'm going 9-5-4
to look for squatters.

272
00:11:40,200 --> 00:11:43,786
Control, 7-L-19, I'm code 4.

273
00:11:45,163 --> 00:11:48,625
There's no one here but me
and some spiders.

274
00:11:59,177 --> 00:12:01,054
Uh...

275
00:12:01,054 --> 00:12:02,305
Hey!

276
00:12:02,305 --> 00:12:05,558
Control, 7-L-19,
I need backup to my last...

277
00:12:06,768 --> 00:12:07,810
Damn it!

278
00:12:07,810 --> 00:12:09,479
Hey!

279
00:12:09,479 --> 00:12:11,606
Can anyone hear me?

280
00:12:15,902 --> 00:12:17,153
It's not funny.

281
00:12:17,153 --> 00:12:18,613
Thanks for
letting me drive.

282
00:12:18,613 --> 00:12:19,864
You know,
at the Academy,

283
00:12:19,864 --> 00:12:22,450
they said it would be six months
before I got the chance.

284
00:12:24,452 --> 00:12:26,496
Sorry. The -- The smell
will pass soon.

285
00:12:26,496 --> 00:12:27,705
No, it's alright.

286
00:12:27,705 --> 00:12:29,540
I, uh -- I know plenty of cops
who wear

287
00:12:29,540 --> 00:12:31,668
a St. Christopher's medal --
uh, protection.

288
00:12:31,668 --> 00:12:34,671
Mm.
Police are
a superstitious bunch.

289
00:12:34,671 --> 00:12:36,256
What about you?

290
00:12:36,256 --> 00:12:37,632
Do you believe in
that kind of thing or...?

291
00:12:37,632 --> 00:12:38,758
Superstitions?
Mm-hmm.

292
00:12:38,758 --> 00:12:40,260
No, no. Not really.

293
00:12:40,260 --> 00:12:43,471
In high school, I, uh, didn't
wash my hockey jersey for a year

294
00:12:43,471 --> 00:12:44,514
because of
a winning streak.

295
00:12:44,514 --> 00:12:45,682
Oh, see, that's gross.

296
00:12:53,356 --> 00:12:55,608
I didn't see this vehicle
commit a violation.

297
00:12:55,608 --> 00:12:57,068
Why are we
pulling them over?

298
00:12:57,068 --> 00:12:59,028
Something's wrong with it.

299
00:12:59,028 --> 00:13:00,655
We're gonna have to be
a little more specific.

300
00:13:00,655 --> 00:13:03,866
Officer Juarez, protocol is
we call it in first.

301
00:13:09,706 --> 00:13:11,416
Was I going too fast,
Officer?

302
00:13:11,416 --> 00:13:13,334
No, ma'am.

303
00:13:13,334 --> 00:13:14,544
Ask for I. D.

304
00:13:14,544 --> 00:13:17,505
Ma'am, I'd like to take a look
in your trunk.

305
00:13:17,505 --> 00:13:19,299
Guess that's alright.

306
00:13:20,758 --> 00:13:22,677
Uh, ma'am, that won't be
necessary.

307
00:13:22,677 --> 00:13:24,595
Officer Juarez,
come speak with me.

308
00:13:27,724 --> 00:13:28,975
What's the probable cause?

309
00:13:28,975 --> 00:13:31,394
There's something dark
coming from that trunk.

310
00:13:31,394 --> 00:13:32,979
Dark?
Like an aura.

311
00:13:32,979 --> 00:13:35,565
Officer Juarez,
we do not pull over vehicles

312
00:13:35,565 --> 00:13:37,108
because they give us
the heebie-jeebies.

313
00:13:37,108 --> 00:13:40,236
And we certainly do not search
trunks without probable cause.

314
00:13:40,236 --> 00:13:42,572
That is a form of profiling,
and I won't have it.

315
00:13:42,572 --> 00:13:44,741
But she consented, so I --
I don't care.

316
00:13:44,741 --> 00:13:45,992
She's an elderly woman

317
00:13:45,992 --> 00:13:47,994
who is clearly intimidated
by police officers.

318
00:13:47,994 --> 00:13:50,204
You're taking advantage
of that fear.

319
00:13:50,204 --> 00:13:51,164
Just look.

320
00:13:51,164 --> 00:13:52,749
No.
I'm...

321
00:13:58,713 --> 00:14:00,256
That's blood.

322
00:14:00,256 --> 00:14:01,716
I knew it.

323
00:14:09,223 --> 00:14:10,391
Alright, ma'am.
Thank you.

324
00:14:12,685 --> 00:14:13,936
How is she?

325
00:14:13,936 --> 00:14:15,396
Upset.

326
00:14:15,396 --> 00:14:16,606
I tried to dust her off.

327
00:14:16,606 --> 00:14:18,274
She still wants to file
a formal complaint.

328
00:14:18,274 --> 00:14:20,276
Look, I've never had to say this
to a rookie before,

329
00:14:20,276 --> 00:14:23,321
but you cannot pull someone over
for having a dark aura --

330
00:14:23,321 --> 00:14:25,239
or any kind of aura.

331
00:14:25,239 --> 00:14:27,658
Nolan, how could you let
your boot make a stop like that?

332
00:14:27,658 --> 00:14:29,660
I'm sorry, sir.
The situation got away from me.

333
00:14:29,660 --> 00:14:31,287
Okay, but what about the blood
in the trunk?

334
00:14:31,287 --> 00:14:33,498
She says she has a grandson that
sometimes borrows the car.

335
00:14:33,498 --> 00:14:35,124
He -- Maybe he spilled
something.

336
00:14:35,124 --> 00:14:36,084
Look,
we'll collect a sample.

337
00:14:36,084 --> 00:14:37,502
We'll test to see
if it's human.

338
00:14:37,502 --> 00:14:39,629
If it is,
then we really have a problem.

339
00:14:39,629 --> 00:14:41,422
Okay, but won't that mean
I was right?

340
00:14:41,422 --> 00:14:42,715
The crime was committed,
so --

341
00:14:42,715 --> 00:14:44,258
Yes, probably.

342
00:14:44,258 --> 00:14:47,095
But since the evidence was found
during an illegal stop,

343
00:14:47,095 --> 00:14:48,846
it's inadmissible in court.

344
00:14:48,846 --> 00:14:50,556
It's the fruit
of a poisonous tree.

345
00:14:52,558 --> 00:14:55,645
Nolan, think you can handle
taking this back to the station?

346
00:14:55,645 --> 00:14:57,730
Sir.

347
00:14:57,730 --> 00:14:59,315
You ever do anything
like that again,

348
00:14:59,315 --> 00:15:00,650
not only will you
be disciplined,

349
00:15:00,650 --> 00:15:02,235
you'll be
out of the LAPD.

350
00:15:02,235 --> 00:15:04,028
You got it?
Yes, sir.

351
00:15:04,028 --> 00:15:06,364
Now go apologize to that woman
and tell her she's free to go.

352
00:15:11,119 --> 00:15:13,287
Well, my catfish
just messaged me.

353
00:15:13,287 --> 00:15:16,040
Said he wants a PS5,
or he's gonna release the photo.

354
00:15:16,040 --> 00:15:17,125
That's it?

355
00:15:17,125 --> 00:15:18,459
I mean, they are
really hard to find.

356
00:15:18,459 --> 00:15:20,128
Okay.
Where's the drop?

357
00:15:20,128 --> 00:15:21,254
Looks like his apartment.

358
00:15:21,254 --> 00:15:22,421
So he's a dumbass.
Great.

359
00:15:22,421 --> 00:15:23,798
Alright,
we'll pick one up on the way.

360
00:15:23,798 --> 00:15:25,675
Oh, uh...

361
00:15:25,675 --> 00:15:27,176
I thought you weren't supposed
to negotiate with terrorists.

362
00:15:27,176 --> 00:15:29,095
Well, he's not a terrorist.
He's an idiot.

363
00:15:29,095 --> 00:15:30,888
But if we arrest him,
that photo becomes evidence.

364
00:15:30,888 --> 00:15:32,849
Everyone at the station
sees it.

365
00:15:34,225 --> 00:15:36,060
Good thing I got a gamer connect
in K-Town.

366
00:15:36,060 --> 00:15:38,479
Of course you do.

367
00:15:38,479 --> 00:15:41,023
Control, 7-L-19.
Do you copy?

368
00:15:42,358 --> 00:15:44,193
Oh!

369
00:15:47,321 --> 00:15:49,365
It's gonna be fine.
This is fine.

370
00:15:49,365 --> 00:15:52,201
They will do a welfare check
when I don't report in,

371
00:15:52,201 --> 00:15:55,163
and this is fine.

372
00:15:57,540 --> 00:16:00,668
Until then, I will read,

373
00:16:00,668 --> 00:16:03,838
because there is
nothing else to do.

374
00:16:08,009 --> 00:16:09,260
Morning.

375
00:16:09,260 --> 00:16:11,846
Hey. Need help again
with the copier?

376
00:16:11,846 --> 00:16:13,514
No, no.

377
00:16:13,514 --> 00:16:15,266
I've made peace with the fact
that it's possessed.

378
00:16:15,266 --> 00:16:17,310
I was just dropping by
to see how you're doing.

379
00:16:17,310 --> 00:16:19,187
You talked to Lucy.

380
00:16:19,187 --> 00:16:21,022
Yeah.

381
00:16:21,022 --> 00:16:23,399
I think the Dye-Hards thing
has spun her out.

382
00:16:23,399 --> 00:16:24,734
Yeah.

383
00:16:24,734 --> 00:16:27,361
That's why I didn't tell her
about it while she was away.

384
00:16:27,361 --> 00:16:29,989
Yeah, I wish she'd just
believe me that I'm fine.

385
00:16:29,989 --> 00:16:31,908
You probably don't know this
about me,

386
00:16:31,908 --> 00:16:35,077
but I was stabbed a few years
ago at the courthouse.

387
00:16:35,077 --> 00:16:38,581
What? No, uh, I didn't.
That's awful.

388
00:16:38,581 --> 00:16:40,625
I'm telling you this
so that you know

389
00:16:40,625 --> 00:16:43,544
that I've been
where you are.

390
00:16:43,544 --> 00:16:46,047
All I wanted was for people
to stop seeing me as a victim.

391
00:16:46,047 --> 00:16:47,673
Exactly.

392
00:16:47,673 --> 00:16:50,968
My friends on the message board,
they don't treat me like that.

393
00:16:50,968 --> 00:16:54,347
They see me as someone with
valuable insight into Rosalind.

394
00:16:54,347 --> 00:16:56,390
And that must feel great.

395
00:16:56,390 --> 00:16:59,936
It's like you're back in control
of your own narrative again.

396
00:16:59,936 --> 00:17:03,272
But simply saying you're okay
doesn't make it so.

397
00:17:03,272 --> 00:17:07,443
Just consider it.

398
00:17:07,443 --> 00:17:09,153
I will.

399
00:17:09,153 --> 00:17:11,280
Hey, if you're looking for
a community that understands

400
00:17:11,280 --> 00:17:14,951
what you've been through,
you got Lucy and me.

401
00:17:14,951 --> 00:17:18,621
Thanks.
I appreciate that.

402
00:17:18,621 --> 00:17:21,666
Okay, man.

403
00:17:23,084 --> 00:17:25,878
So why the hell was your rookie
driving in the first place?

404
00:17:25,878 --> 00:17:27,046
That's how I was taught.

405
00:17:27,046 --> 00:17:28,631
It's not standard practice.

406
00:17:28,631 --> 00:17:30,424
Once you've been a T. O.
for a few years,

407
00:17:30,424 --> 00:17:32,760
then you can get creative
with the guidelines.

408
00:17:32,760 --> 00:17:34,929
On your first day,
stick to the damn script.

409
00:17:34,929 --> 00:17:36,013
Yes, sir.

410
00:17:36,013 --> 00:17:37,056
Where's Juarez now?

411
00:17:37,056 --> 00:17:38,432
Writing up the report.

412
00:17:38,432 --> 00:17:40,101
I want you to
triple check it.

413
00:17:40,101 --> 00:17:43,145
All the paperwork surrounding
this needs to be immaculate,

414
00:17:43,145 --> 00:17:45,690
so make sure she specifies
that she was unable

415
00:17:45,690 --> 00:17:48,150
to articulate
the reason for the stop.

416
00:17:48,150 --> 00:17:50,361
Yes, sir. I'll also be writing
up a blue page on her.

417
00:17:50,361 --> 00:17:53,322
In it, you need to detail how,
as Juarez's T. O.,

418
00:17:53,322 --> 00:17:56,200
how you plan to correct her
moving forward.

419
00:17:56,200 --> 00:17:57,827
It may have been
her mistake,

420
00:17:57,827 --> 00:18:01,163
but as her supervisor,
she's your responsibility.

421
00:18:08,170 --> 00:18:11,090
That can't be true.
Can it? I...

422
00:18:14,468 --> 00:18:18,639
Now, this user is making
sense -- TruthHunter184.

423
00:18:18,639 --> 00:18:20,641
"Don't give Rosalind
the satisfaction.

424
00:18:20,641 --> 00:18:23,269
She eats her victim's pain
like a five-star meal."

425
00:18:26,022 --> 00:18:28,274
"Like a five-star meal."

426
00:18:29,859 --> 00:18:32,320
Rosalind said that to Nolan.

427
00:18:32,320 --> 00:18:33,738
Hey!

428
00:18:33,738 --> 00:18:36,115
Hey!
Can anybody hear me?!

429
00:18:38,534 --> 00:18:40,536
Yo,
I got what you asked for.

430
00:18:40,536 --> 00:18:41,746
Drop it and leave.

431
00:18:46,876 --> 00:18:48,044
Hello.

432
00:18:48,044 --> 00:18:49,629
Sergeant Bradford,
LAPD.

433
00:18:49,629 --> 00:18:52,548
Hi, uh, O-Officers.
What's up?

434
00:18:52,548 --> 00:18:54,050
You're blackmailing me.

435
00:18:54,050 --> 00:18:56,218
Do you have any idea
how serious of a crime this is?

436
00:18:56,218 --> 00:18:57,637
I could charge you
with a felony.

437
00:18:57,637 --> 00:19:00,222
Hold on, 'kay? I-I wasn't really
gonna release the -- the photo.

438
00:19:00,222 --> 00:19:02,058
I-I just --
just wanted the PS5.

439
00:19:02,058 --> 00:19:03,893
My mom won't get me one.

440
00:19:03,893 --> 00:19:05,728
Pavi,
are you talking to me?

441
00:19:05,728 --> 00:19:08,648
No, Mom. God!
Just stay out of it.

442
00:19:10,107 --> 00:19:11,233
Oh, I think we should
get Mom out here.

443
00:19:11,233 --> 00:19:13,027
No, whoa.
That's not necessary. No.

444
00:19:13,027 --> 00:19:14,862
Then delete the photo.
Now.

445
00:19:14,862 --> 00:19:16,155
Okay. Alright. Yeah.

446
00:19:16,155 --> 00:19:20,117
Deleting the photo. Okay.
See? It's gone.

447
00:19:20,117 --> 00:19:22,328
And get rid of
the dating profile, too, okay?

448
00:19:22,328 --> 00:19:24,121
It's messed up,
catfishing people.

449
00:19:24,121 --> 00:19:25,790
Yeah, done.

450
00:19:25,790 --> 00:19:28,167
Bad behavior
does not get a reward.

451
00:19:28,167 --> 00:19:30,836
You do anything like that again,
I'll make sure your phone

452
00:19:30,836 --> 00:19:32,880
and laptop are collected
as evidence.

453
00:19:32,880 --> 00:19:34,173
You got it?

454
00:19:34,173 --> 00:19:36,717
You suck.

455
00:19:36,717 --> 00:19:38,928
Sweet kid.

456
00:19:38,928 --> 00:19:40,346
So, what's up?
We taking this back or --

457
00:19:40,346 --> 00:19:41,972
Hell no.
Taking this home.

458
00:19:41,972 --> 00:19:43,516
You know how hard it is
to find one of these?

459
00:19:45,059 --> 00:19:47,228
Harper.

460
00:19:47,228 --> 00:19:48,813
Are you sure?

461
00:19:48,813 --> 00:19:50,231
What?

462
00:19:50,231 --> 00:19:51,524
Jill's blood was swabbed

463
00:19:51,524 --> 00:19:53,401
from the trunk of a car
during a traffic stop.

464
00:19:53,401 --> 00:19:54,735
Whose car?

465
00:19:54,735 --> 00:19:57,697
Whose car?

466
00:19:57,697 --> 00:20:00,074
Wait. They what?

467
00:20:01,325 --> 00:20:03,327
Do you know
how dead to me you are?

468
00:20:03,327 --> 00:20:05,663
The blood that you found
in the car belongs to a woman

469
00:20:05,663 --> 00:20:07,623
who has been missing
for three days.

470
00:20:07,623 --> 00:20:09,375
It is our only lead.

471
00:20:09,375 --> 00:20:11,460
And -- And now I hear
that it's a bad stop?

472
00:20:11,460 --> 00:20:12,753
I know. I'm sorry.

473
00:20:12,753 --> 00:20:14,130
It was my fault.
I'm --

474
00:20:14,130 --> 00:20:17,717
His rookie. Which means that
you are his responsibility.

475
00:20:17,717 --> 00:20:20,678
Nolan, I trained you
better than this.

476
00:20:20,678 --> 00:20:23,431
And now you are both
making me look bad.

477
00:20:25,307 --> 00:20:26,934
I just got off the phone
with T. I. D.

478
00:20:26,934 --> 00:20:28,269
When they went
to impound the car,

479
00:20:28,269 --> 00:20:30,396
they took a preliminary look
and said the blood appears to be

480
00:20:30,396 --> 00:20:32,356
only 10 to 12 hours old.

481
00:20:32,356 --> 00:20:33,607
Jill could still be alive.

482
00:20:33,607 --> 00:20:35,025
Oh, then we gotta
move quickly.

483
00:20:35,025 --> 00:20:36,402
Not so fast.

484
00:20:36,402 --> 00:20:37,820
I take it
you're Officer Juarez?

485
00:20:37,820 --> 00:20:38,863
Yes, sir.

486
00:20:38,863 --> 00:20:40,948
Wesley Evers
from the D. A.'s office.

487
00:20:40,948 --> 00:20:42,867
Since the blood evidence
you found is inadmissible,

488
00:20:42,867 --> 00:20:44,785
the LAPD will have
to figure out another way

489
00:20:44,785 --> 00:20:46,495
to implicate your suspect
in this crime.

490
00:20:46,495 --> 00:20:47,997
So we do have
a suspect?

491
00:20:47,997 --> 00:20:50,332
Our missing person's
ex-boyfriend, Tyler Harvin.

492
00:20:50,332 --> 00:20:52,042
The car belongs
to his grandmother.

493
00:20:52,042 --> 00:20:54,336
She confirmed that
he has regular access to it.

494
00:20:54,336 --> 00:20:56,881
So to nail this guy in court,
I need something concrete

495
00:20:56,881 --> 00:20:58,632
tying him
to Jill's disappearance.

496
00:20:58,632 --> 00:21:00,676
Without P. C.,
Carradine won't authorize

497
00:21:00,676 --> 00:21:02,303
a surveillance detail
on Harvin.

498
00:21:02,303 --> 00:21:04,680
But he did agree
to let me and Lopez

499
00:21:04,680 --> 00:21:06,474
run foot surveillance
ourselves.

500
00:21:06,474 --> 00:21:09,226
If we can catch Tyler engaging
in suspicious activity,

501
00:21:09,226 --> 00:21:10,811
Carradine said
he'd approve a full team.

502
00:21:10,811 --> 00:21:13,314
You're gonna try and run foot
surveillance with two officers?

503
00:21:13,314 --> 00:21:16,192
No, four. You and your rookie
are gonna start

504
00:21:16,192 --> 00:21:18,527
digging your way
out of my doghouse by helping.

505
00:21:18,527 --> 00:21:21,405
Remember, Harvin has
a history of violence.

506
00:21:21,405 --> 00:21:23,783
Don't underestimate him.

507
00:21:25,326 --> 00:21:28,037
I've got Harvin heading north
down Lake.

508
00:21:28,037 --> 00:21:31,332
Black pants, blue ball cap,
light-blue shirt.

509
00:21:31,332 --> 00:21:33,000
Roger that.
Standing by.

510
00:21:33,000 --> 00:21:35,878
Alright. I need you to focus on
what I'm about to say.

511
00:21:35,878 --> 00:21:37,671
Everything you learned
at the Academy

512
00:21:37,671 --> 00:21:40,508
goes out the window
the moment the adrenaline hits.

513
00:21:40,508 --> 00:21:42,343
You have to keep thinking,

514
00:21:42,343 --> 00:21:44,678
remain aware of your
surroundings at all times,

515
00:21:44,678 --> 00:21:46,847
and avoid
any physical contact

516
00:21:46,847 --> 00:21:48,390
unless someone's life
has been threatened.

517
00:21:48,390 --> 00:21:50,309
Yes, sir.

518
00:21:50,309 --> 00:21:51,352
I've got him.

519
00:21:53,312 --> 00:21:56,190
I'll pick you up
in the alley.

520
00:22:03,447 --> 00:22:05,908
Continuing west on Eleventh.

521
00:22:14,959 --> 00:22:16,877
He just turned onto Grandview.
He's heading north.

522
00:22:16,877 --> 00:22:17,920
That's us.

523
00:22:39,775 --> 00:22:41,277
He's running!

524
00:22:41,277 --> 00:22:42,653
Which way?

525
00:22:42,653 --> 00:22:44,905
North on Grandview,
west side of the street.

526
00:22:55,124 --> 00:22:56,792
Hey!

527
00:23:08,762 --> 00:23:10,598
I can't believe my career
was almost ruined by a kid

528
00:23:10,598 --> 00:23:11,891
whose mom still does
his laundry.

529
00:23:13,559 --> 00:23:16,353
When was the last time
you heard Chen on the radio?

530
00:23:17,938 --> 00:23:20,983
I can't remember. It was like
an hour ago, maybe two.

531
00:23:24,320 --> 00:23:26,030
Dispatch,
this is 7-Adam-100.

532
00:23:26,030 --> 00:23:28,490
Can you perform a security
check on Officer Chen?

533
00:23:28,490 --> 00:23:30,826
Hold on, 7-Adam-100.

534
00:23:30,826 --> 00:23:33,203
She's not responding.

535
00:23:33,203 --> 00:23:34,830
When was last contact?

536
00:23:34,830 --> 00:23:38,876
According to the logs,
it was over two hours ago.

537
00:23:38,876 --> 00:23:40,753
Alright, that's a problem
we're gonna talk about later.

538
00:23:40,753 --> 00:23:42,630
Right now, give me
her last known address.

539
00:23:48,552 --> 00:23:50,346
Chen?

540
00:23:52,973 --> 00:23:55,267
Chen!

541
00:23:55,267 --> 00:23:56,810
Yeah.

542
00:23:56,810 --> 00:23:58,562
Yeah, I'm in here.

543
00:24:02,608 --> 00:24:04,360
Hang on.
The door is stuck.

544
00:24:04,360 --> 00:24:05,819
Yeah, no kidding.

545
00:24:08,781 --> 00:24:09,698
You okay?

546
00:24:09,698 --> 00:24:11,450
I-I think I have a lead
on Rosalind.

547
00:24:11,450 --> 00:24:12,660
-What?
-How?

548
00:24:12,660 --> 00:24:14,703
Chris has been spending time
on these message boards

549
00:24:14,703 --> 00:24:16,372
filled with
armchair detectives

550
00:24:16,372 --> 00:24:17,665
that are trying to
track Rosalind down.

551
00:24:17,665 --> 00:24:18,749
You think one of them
found her?

552
00:24:18,749 --> 00:24:21,168
I think one of them
is her.

553
00:24:21,168 --> 00:24:23,671
I would add that it was
an error in judgment

554
00:24:23,671 --> 00:24:25,506
that you will not repeat.

555
00:24:25,506 --> 00:24:28,425
And this memorandum
is going to the Watch Commander?

556
00:24:28,425 --> 00:24:31,887
Yeah. And then he will run it
up the chain of command.

557
00:24:31,887 --> 00:24:34,515
Are they gonna wash me out?

558
00:24:36,850 --> 00:24:38,978
It's a possibility.

559
00:24:38,978 --> 00:24:40,854
You can be fired
for literally anything

560
00:24:40,854 --> 00:24:42,398
in your probationary period.

561
00:24:42,398 --> 00:24:45,401
But, on the other hand,
it's your first day.

562
00:24:45,401 --> 00:24:47,736
Your failure
is more so on me.

563
00:24:47,736 --> 00:24:49,571
Are they gonna find Jill
on time?

564
00:24:49,571 --> 00:24:51,073
I hope so.

565
00:24:51,073 --> 00:24:52,866
But you should prepare
for the worst.

566
00:24:52,866 --> 00:24:56,245
No, she's still alive.
I can feel it.

567
00:24:56,245 --> 00:24:58,414
The way you felt
the bad aura?

568
00:24:58,414 --> 00:25:00,582
Yes.

569
00:25:00,582 --> 00:25:04,712
Look, I-I know that
in the movies,

570
00:25:04,712 --> 00:25:06,839
police seem to rely on
their intuitions

571
00:25:06,839 --> 00:25:09,299
all the time
about a suspect.

572
00:25:09,299 --> 00:25:13,303
In reality,
this is not the case.

573
00:25:13,303 --> 00:25:15,139
What you see as intuition

574
00:25:15,139 --> 00:25:19,393
is actually years
of hard-won knowledge

575
00:25:19,393 --> 00:25:22,229
in how to interpret things
like body language.

576
00:25:22,229 --> 00:25:25,482
It's not a mystical power.
It's observation.

577
00:25:25,482 --> 00:25:28,610
And even then,
cops get it wrong all the time.

578
00:25:28,610 --> 00:25:30,988
With all due respect,

579
00:25:30,988 --> 00:25:33,323
reading someone's
body language sounds

580
00:25:33,323 --> 00:25:35,743
just as mysterious
as my feelings.

581
00:25:35,743 --> 00:25:38,078
That's because you don't have
the experience to back it up.

582
00:25:38,078 --> 00:25:40,789
You sound just like
the old-school instructors

583
00:25:40,789 --> 00:25:43,292
at the Academy,
going on about tradition

584
00:25:43,292 --> 00:25:46,920
while conveniently leaving out
the dark side of that tradition.

585
00:25:46,920 --> 00:25:50,299
I thought you wanted to be
a different kind of T. O.

586
00:25:50,299 --> 00:25:52,426
Why can't I be
a different kind of cop?

587
00:25:52,426 --> 00:25:54,303
Maybe one day you can be.

588
00:25:54,303 --> 00:25:57,306
But first, you have to learn
the fundamentals.

589
00:25:57,306 --> 00:25:59,224
But I was right
about the car.

590
00:25:59,224 --> 00:26:00,684
Yes, you were.

591
00:26:00,684 --> 00:26:03,103
And I bet you think it's unfair
that that stop was inadmissible.

592
00:26:03,103 --> 00:26:04,605
But I want you to think about
what would happen

593
00:26:04,605 --> 00:26:08,484
if the police were able to stop
people based on feelings alone.

594
00:26:08,484 --> 00:26:11,487
Where do we draw the line
between a dark aura

595
00:26:11,487 --> 00:26:13,489
and outright prejudice?

596
00:26:13,489 --> 00:26:17,701
That's why the rule exists.
To protect people.

597
00:26:17,701 --> 00:26:21,747
I don't see how the rules
are protecting Jill Baskin.

598
00:26:31,256 --> 00:26:32,674
Hey.
Lucy.

599
00:26:32,674 --> 00:26:34,009
Hey, what's going on?
They won't tell me.

600
00:26:34,009 --> 00:26:35,177
Sit down.

601
00:26:35,177 --> 00:26:37,846
Okay, so, um, I went through
"The Mother Doc,"

602
00:26:37,846 --> 00:26:39,807
and I think
I found Rosalind.

603
00:26:39,807 --> 00:26:42,810
What? Where?
That sighting in Rome?

604
00:26:42,810 --> 00:26:44,311
N-No. I --

605
00:26:44,311 --> 00:26:47,856
Are you familiar with
the username "TruthHunter184"?

606
00:26:47,856 --> 00:26:51,819
Yeah.
Uh, he lives in Atlanta.

607
00:26:53,362 --> 00:26:54,905
He doesn't?

608
00:26:54,905 --> 00:26:56,782
Lucy found
some irregularities

609
00:26:56,782 --> 00:26:58,242
in TruthHunter's
communication style,

610
00:26:58,242 --> 00:27:00,035
so she asked us
to look into it.

611
00:27:00,035 --> 00:27:02,121
I reviewed all of
TruthHunter's messages,

612
00:27:02,121 --> 00:27:03,872
and I agree
with Officer Chen.

613
00:27:03,872 --> 00:27:07,209
The forensic linguistics
are a match to Rosalind Dyer.

614
00:27:07,209 --> 00:27:10,003
But -- No, that doesn't
make any sense.

615
00:27:10,003 --> 00:27:12,589
Do you remember when
TruthHunter wrote

616
00:27:12,589 --> 00:27:16,176
Rosalind "eats her victim's pain
like a five-star meal"?

617
00:27:16,176 --> 00:27:17,928
Yeah.

618
00:27:17,928 --> 00:27:19,972
I heard Rosalind
use that exact phrase

619
00:27:19,972 --> 00:27:22,099
to describe the pleasure
she took at her trial

620
00:27:22,099 --> 00:27:24,685
when watching the agony
of her victims' families.

621
00:27:27,896 --> 00:27:30,691
I told her things about me,
about the investigation.

622
00:27:30,691 --> 00:27:32,234
It's okay.
You didn't know.

623
00:27:32,234 --> 00:27:33,694
Uh, so what do we do?

624
00:27:33,694 --> 00:27:36,280
I can message her,
try to set up a meeting.

625
00:27:36,280 --> 00:27:38,407
N-No. Uh, Rosalind will
see right through that.

626
00:27:38,407 --> 00:27:40,951
I agree. With this level
of intelligent psychopath,

627
00:27:40,951 --> 00:27:43,245
I would advise to err
on the side of caution.

628
00:27:43,245 --> 00:27:44,580
So we work with
what we've got.

629
00:27:44,580 --> 00:27:46,039
We get cyber crimes involved,

630
00:27:46,039 --> 00:27:48,250
and we see if we can track her
using her I. P. address.

631
00:27:48,250 --> 00:27:49,376
And if we find anything,

632
00:27:49,376 --> 00:27:50,627
we promise to keep you
in the loop.

633
00:27:50,627 --> 00:27:52,254
Thank you.

634
00:27:52,254 --> 00:27:53,589
Yeah. Uh, thanks.

635
00:27:57,467 --> 00:27:59,303
Hey. Are you okay?

636
00:27:59,303 --> 00:28:01,889
No.
I'm really not.

637
00:28:12,482 --> 00:28:16,695
Officer Nolan, I-I want
to apologize for yesterday.

638
00:28:16,695 --> 00:28:18,280
Look,
I was upset that my mistake

639
00:28:18,280 --> 00:28:19,823
may have put Jill
in further jeopardy,

640
00:28:19,823 --> 00:28:21,575
and I unfairly took it out
on you.

641
00:28:21,575 --> 00:28:23,118
I promise to do better.

642
00:28:23,118 --> 00:28:24,912
I appreciate that.

643
00:28:24,912 --> 00:28:26,914
I also thought about
our conversation.

644
00:28:26,914 --> 00:28:30,417
I want you to trust me
with your feelings.

645
00:28:30,417 --> 00:28:33,420
If you had confided in me
yesterday before the car stop,

646
00:28:33,420 --> 00:28:35,964
we could have avoided
this whole mess.

647
00:28:35,964 --> 00:28:38,258
So next time
you have an idea,

648
00:28:38,258 --> 00:28:40,761
no matter how crazy,
tell me about it.

649
00:28:40,761 --> 00:28:41,803
Oh, thank God.

650
00:28:41,803 --> 00:28:43,513
Because I had
the wildest dream.

651
00:28:43,513 --> 00:28:46,934
Okay, that's not exactly
what I...

652
00:28:46,934 --> 00:28:49,519
No, you're right. I'm sorry.
Tell me your dream.

653
00:28:49,519 --> 00:28:53,148
I was up half the night doing
a deep dive on Tyler Harvin.

654
00:28:53,148 --> 00:28:54,524
When I finally fell asleep,

655
00:28:54,524 --> 00:28:56,568
I-I dreamt that
I was on the beach

656
00:28:56,568 --> 00:28:58,654
and a body
washed up on shore.

657
00:28:58,654 --> 00:28:59,947
Jill Baskin?

658
00:28:59,947 --> 00:29:01,990
No. It was a man.
A giant, actually.

659
00:29:01,990 --> 00:29:04,493
Wearing an old-timey armor,

660
00:29:04,493 --> 00:29:07,204
holding a big wooden shield
with a crown on it.

661
00:29:07,204 --> 00:29:09,289
Okay.
And you think this knight

662
00:29:09,289 --> 00:29:11,208
had something to do with
Jill's abduction?

663
00:29:11,208 --> 00:29:13,502
I don't know.
But it was so vivid.

664
00:29:13,502 --> 00:29:16,505
And I thought m-maybe Jill's
being kept near a beach.

665
00:29:16,505 --> 00:29:19,132
Okay. Um...

666
00:29:19,132 --> 00:29:22,844
You said you were looking into
Tyler when you fell asleep.

667
00:29:22,844 --> 00:29:24,221
What exactly
did you find?

668
00:29:24,221 --> 00:29:25,889
I was looking into
his work history.

669
00:29:25,889 --> 00:29:27,432
I mean,
he does a lot of odd jobs

670
00:29:27,432 --> 00:29:29,893
all over the city --
landscaping, contracting.

671
00:29:29,893 --> 00:29:31,603
And I thought
one of these jobs

672
00:29:31,603 --> 00:29:33,522
may have given him access
to a hiding place --

673
00:29:33,522 --> 00:29:35,190
maybe somewhere
off a beaten path

674
00:29:35,190 --> 00:29:36,692
where he might be
holding Jill.

675
00:29:36,692 --> 00:29:40,362
Okay. Uh, were any of the jobs
near a beach?

676
00:29:40,362 --> 00:29:41,530
Did any of them
have anything to do with

677
00:29:41,530 --> 00:29:43,031
the name Knight
or Shield?

678
00:29:43,031 --> 00:29:45,075
A company name?
Maybe a client?

679
00:29:45,075 --> 00:29:48,245
Well, he finished work
a few weeks ago for a job

680
00:29:48,245 --> 00:29:52,624
on a company called
A Royal Hand Construction.

681
00:29:52,624 --> 00:29:56,294
And the house was on a street
called Beachwood Canyon.

682
00:29:56,294 --> 00:29:58,171
Show me on Streetview.

683
00:30:01,383 --> 00:30:03,677
See, Tyler could have seen
this condemned house

684
00:30:03,677 --> 00:30:05,679
while he was
working here for Royal.

685
00:30:05,679 --> 00:30:07,472
Your dream
wasn't a premonition.

686
00:30:07,472 --> 00:30:10,017
It was just your subconscious
processing information.

687
00:30:10,017 --> 00:30:12,019
So you don't think
I'm crazy?

688
00:30:12,019 --> 00:30:14,354
I'm not saying that.
But I think we should do it --

689
00:30:14,354 --> 00:30:16,732
take a look at that house before
we talk to Harper and Lopez.

690
00:30:16,732 --> 00:30:18,150
You wanted to see me, sir?

691
00:30:18,150 --> 00:30:19,484
That was Garza.

692
00:30:19,484 --> 00:30:20,986
Their cyber crime people

693
00:30:20,986 --> 00:30:23,613
traced the web
of Rosalind's I. P. addresses

694
00:30:23,613 --> 00:30:25,407
to a house
outside Seattle.

695
00:30:25,407 --> 00:30:27,200
They're putting together
a surveillance team

696
00:30:27,200 --> 00:30:28,410
to go there now.

697
00:30:28,410 --> 00:30:30,287
Agent Garza has
invited you to join.

698
00:30:30,287 --> 00:30:32,539
Really?
That -- That's amazing.

699
00:30:32,539 --> 00:30:33,915
Yeah, I-I'm in.

700
00:30:33,915 --> 00:30:35,125
Jet leaves in an hour.

701
00:30:35,125 --> 00:30:36,209
Sir.

702
00:30:37,294 --> 00:30:38,253
What the hell?

703
00:30:38,253 --> 00:30:40,172
Oh, good morning,
Cop Cake.

704
00:30:40,172 --> 00:30:43,550
Oh, man.

705
00:30:43,550 --> 00:30:45,719
Yeah, I'm thinking we need to
pay our catfish another visit.

706
00:30:45,719 --> 00:30:47,262
Damn straight.

707
00:30:47,262 --> 00:30:50,515
Alright.
You take the east side.

708
00:30:50,515 --> 00:30:52,017
I'll take the west.

709
00:30:52,017 --> 00:30:53,560
And then
meet in the middle.

710
00:30:53,560 --> 00:30:54,853
Copy.
Radio if you see anything.

711
00:30:54,853 --> 00:30:56,063
Will do.

712
00:31:18,919 --> 00:31:20,587
Nolan, I found her.

713
00:31:20,587 --> 00:31:22,547
East side of the house
at the window.

714
00:31:30,639 --> 00:31:32,265
Stand back.

715
00:31:43,318 --> 00:31:44,486
Cleared.

716
00:31:48,115 --> 00:31:49,991
Check her.

717
00:31:52,160 --> 00:31:53,912
She's alive.

718
00:31:53,912 --> 00:31:55,497
Alright.
Stay with her.

719
00:31:55,497 --> 00:31:56,915
I'm gonna clear the house.

720
00:31:59,167 --> 00:32:01,461
Hey, Jill.
My name is Celina.

721
00:32:01,461 --> 00:32:02,838
Everything's gonna be alright.

722
00:32:02,838 --> 00:32:04,297
Patrol, 7-Adam-15.

723
00:32:04,297 --> 00:32:06,591
Show us at
6577 Beachwood Canyon,

724
00:32:06,591 --> 00:32:07,926
abandoned house.

725
00:32:07,926 --> 00:32:10,720
Found a female kidnap victim,
possibly Jill Baskin.

726
00:32:10,720 --> 00:32:11,972
Multiple stab wounds.

727
00:32:11,972 --> 00:32:13,849
Requesting R. A.
and additional units.

728
00:32:13,849 --> 00:32:16,768
Police!

729
00:32:16,768 --> 00:32:17,894
Is anyone in here?

730
00:32:17,894 --> 00:32:20,355
Come out with
your hands up now.

731
00:32:24,401 --> 00:32:25,527
Hey!

732
00:32:25,527 --> 00:32:27,362
Nolan, I see him!

733
00:32:27,362 --> 00:32:28,822
Stop!

734
00:32:32,868 --> 00:32:34,578
What do you got?

735
00:32:34,578 --> 00:32:37,706
Officer Juarez?

736
00:32:39,166 --> 00:32:41,001
Officer Juarez, check in.

737
00:32:42,502 --> 00:32:45,505
Officer Juarez,
please respond.

738
00:32:59,394 --> 00:33:00,604
Victim's in the bedroom.

739
00:33:00,604 --> 00:33:02,272
Severe blood loss,
but her vitals are stable.

740
00:33:02,272 --> 00:33:03,398
Copy that.
We're on it.

741
00:33:03,398 --> 00:33:05,400
Officer Juarez,
do you copy?

742
00:33:07,485 --> 00:33:09,571
Celina, do you hear me?

743
00:33:19,039 --> 00:33:20,916
Police!

744
00:33:39,226 --> 00:33:41,978
Officer Juarez, respond.

745
00:33:41,978 --> 00:33:44,940
7-Adam, um, it's Juarez.

746
00:33:44,940 --> 00:33:47,275
I had eyes on the suspect.
I'm in pursuit.

747
00:33:47,275 --> 00:33:49,903
Celina, I'm coming to you.
Where are you?

748
00:33:49,903 --> 00:33:51,446
I don't know.

749
00:33:51,446 --> 00:33:53,990
Are you on the trail?

750
00:33:53,990 --> 00:33:55,742
No. Uh...

751
00:33:55,742 --> 00:33:59,287
I think we were heading east,
but we turned.

752
00:34:09,464 --> 00:34:10,632
I see him.

753
00:34:10,632 --> 00:34:11,967
Does he have a weapon?

754
00:34:11,967 --> 00:34:13,260
I can't tell.

755
00:34:13,260 --> 00:34:15,929
Celina, I need you to focus
so I can find you.

756
00:34:15,929 --> 00:34:18,890
He's on the move.
He's on the move.

757
00:34:18,890 --> 00:34:21,601
7-Adam-15, my rookie's
in pursuit of suspect,

758
00:34:21,601 --> 00:34:23,395
but the specific location
is unknown.

759
00:34:23,395 --> 00:34:25,563
I am heading northeast
on trail road,

760
00:34:25,563 --> 00:34:28,108
requesting airship
and all available units

761
00:34:28,108 --> 00:34:30,819
to help locate suspect
and Officer Juarez.

762
00:34:30,819 --> 00:34:31,820
Code 3.

763
00:34:31,820 --> 00:34:34,739
Juarez, talk to me.

764
00:34:36,700 --> 00:34:39,953
I've lost visual.
I don't know where he went.

765
00:34:42,497 --> 00:34:44,332
Look around you.
What do you see?

766
00:34:44,332 --> 00:34:46,459
Just trees
and a footbridge.

767
00:34:46,459 --> 00:34:48,211
No buildings, no signs?

768
00:34:48,211 --> 00:34:50,588
I-I see one of those
electrical boxes.

769
00:34:50,588 --> 00:34:52,299
Great. Does it have any kind of
identifier on it?

770
00:34:52,299 --> 00:34:53,550
A serial number?

771
00:34:53,550 --> 00:34:54,968
Uh...

772
00:35:00,974 --> 00:35:02,475
Yeah.

773
00:35:02,475 --> 00:35:05,353
198962.

774
00:35:05,353 --> 00:35:08,481
Control, I need the location of
an L. A. City electrical box.

775
00:35:08,481 --> 00:35:12,277
Serial number 198962.

776
00:35:12,277 --> 00:35:13,945
Copy, 7-Adam-15.

777
00:35:13,945 --> 00:35:17,532
Sending the location
to your box.

778
00:35:17,532 --> 00:35:20,535
Okay, Celina, hang tight,
I got you.

779
00:35:20,535 --> 00:35:22,203
Copy that.

780
00:35:27,709 --> 00:35:30,170
Celina? Celina?

781
00:35:30,170 --> 00:35:32,005
Damn it, dispatch,
where is my airship?

782
00:35:32,005 --> 00:35:34,049
I have an officer
in need of help.

783
00:36:42,867 --> 00:36:43,993
It's okay.

784
00:36:45,120 --> 00:36:47,122
You're gonna be alright.

785
00:36:55,630 --> 00:36:57,674
How is Officer Juarez?

786
00:36:57,674 --> 00:36:59,259
Shaken up.
A little bruised.

787
00:36:59,259 --> 00:37:01,219
Nothing serious,
thank God.

788
00:37:01,219 --> 00:37:03,430
Not a great start.

789
00:37:03,430 --> 00:37:04,889
She'll bounce back.

790
00:37:04,889 --> 00:37:05,974
I meant you.

791
00:37:05,974 --> 00:37:07,767
I know.

792
00:37:07,767 --> 00:37:11,271
If that suspect had gotten
her gun away from her...

793
00:37:11,271 --> 00:37:15,024
These last few days
have been extremely humbling.

794
00:37:15,024 --> 00:37:17,318
Everything is moving
a hundred miles an hour.

795
00:37:17,318 --> 00:37:19,154
I feel like I barely have time
to teach her

796
00:37:19,154 --> 00:37:22,157
the most basic things
before everything goes sideways.

797
00:37:22,157 --> 00:37:25,493
Translation --
You feel like a rookie again.

798
00:37:25,493 --> 00:37:27,287
Yeah.

799
00:37:27,287 --> 00:37:30,290
Well, to her credit,
Celina managed to fight off

800
00:37:30,290 --> 00:37:33,293
a guy twice her size
after sprinting up a canyon.

801
00:37:33,293 --> 00:37:36,921
She's got spirit.
Maybe a little too much.

802
00:37:36,921 --> 00:37:39,007
You know anything
about horses, Nolan?

803
00:37:39,007 --> 00:37:40,633
I really don't, sir.

804
00:37:40,633 --> 00:37:42,969
Have a seat.

805
00:37:48,308 --> 00:37:53,563
Young racehorses are
skittish and excitable.

806
00:37:53,563 --> 00:37:58,276
To calm them down, they partner
them with older horses

807
00:37:58,276 --> 00:38:00,779
to teach them
how to check themselves.

808
00:38:00,779 --> 00:38:03,156
Eventually,
they come around.

809
00:38:03,156 --> 00:38:07,285
It's the natural order
of things.

810
00:38:07,285 --> 00:38:09,621
Officer Juarez, a word?

811
00:38:13,166 --> 00:38:15,335
I imagine that was a pretty
tough first case for you.

812
00:38:15,335 --> 00:38:17,504
Sir.

813
00:38:17,504 --> 00:38:19,839
Something wasn't adding up,

814
00:38:19,839 --> 00:38:23,259
so I requested
your full personnel file.

815
00:38:23,259 --> 00:38:25,094
You read about my sister.

816
00:38:25,094 --> 00:38:26,846
Yeah.

817
00:38:26,846 --> 00:38:29,766
Abducted from your yard
when you were 9 years old.

818
00:38:29,766 --> 00:38:32,936
I can't even imagine
what you went through.

819
00:38:32,936 --> 00:38:34,687
I was supposed
to be watching her,

820
00:38:34,687 --> 00:38:37,273
and I looked away
for a minute.

821
00:38:37,273 --> 00:38:40,318
And after three weeks
of no leads from the police,

822
00:38:40,318 --> 00:38:42,028
my mom hired a psychic.

823
00:38:42,028 --> 00:38:44,072
That's who found her,
not the cops.

824
00:38:44,072 --> 00:38:46,658
Which is why you put
so much stock in intuition.

825
00:38:46,658 --> 00:38:47,700
Mm-hmm.

826
00:38:47,700 --> 00:38:50,161
I was wrong earlier

827
00:38:50,161 --> 00:38:51,830
when I said you don't
have the experience

828
00:38:51,830 --> 00:38:54,165
to back up
your gut instincts.

829
00:38:54,165 --> 00:38:57,418
See,
I think you blamed yourself

830
00:38:57,418 --> 00:38:58,753
for what happened
to your sister,

831
00:38:58,753 --> 00:39:03,216
and that made you an extremely
observant 9-year-old girl

832
00:39:03,216 --> 00:39:05,927
so that you'd never miss
seeing danger coming again.

833
00:39:05,927 --> 00:39:09,514
And over the years, you funneled
all that input into your gut.

834
00:39:09,514 --> 00:39:12,392
See, I think you saw the blood
on the bumper of that car,

835
00:39:12,392 --> 00:39:14,352
and before you understood
what you saw,

836
00:39:14,352 --> 00:39:19,315
you translated it
into a dark aura.

837
00:39:19,315 --> 00:39:22,193
And your premonition dream
about Jill's whereabouts,

838
00:39:22,193 --> 00:39:24,195
that came after a long night

839
00:39:24,195 --> 00:39:27,782
of meticulous,
evidence-based research.

840
00:39:27,782 --> 00:39:32,328
So does that mean you're --
you're not washing me out?

841
00:39:32,328 --> 00:39:33,872
Correct.

842
00:39:33,872 --> 00:39:35,290
But I don't have
a crystal ball.

843
00:39:35,290 --> 00:39:36,624
I don't know yet
if you are going to be

844
00:39:36,624 --> 00:39:38,084
a good police officer.

845
00:39:38,084 --> 00:39:42,130
But I am willing to trust my gut
and give it another shot.

846
00:39:42,130 --> 00:39:46,885
Thank you, sir.
I won't let you down.

847
00:39:46,885 --> 00:39:48,720
I'll see you tomorrow.

848
00:39:50,305 --> 00:39:51,764
You know, if you ever need
a crystal ball,

849
00:39:51,764 --> 00:39:53,600
you can always
borrow mine.

850
00:39:53,600 --> 00:39:55,310
Kidding.

851
00:39:55,310 --> 00:39:57,103
Good night,
Officer Juarez.

852
00:39:57,103 --> 00:39:58,771
Good night.

853
00:40:03,109 --> 00:40:04,903
Alright, so here's the deal,
Pavi.

854
00:40:04,903 --> 00:40:07,196
I filled out the paperwork
charging you with a felony,

855
00:40:07,196 --> 00:40:09,115
and I will file it today

856
00:40:09,115 --> 00:40:12,327
unless you start using
your skills to help people.

857
00:40:12,327 --> 00:40:15,330
And how much
does that pay?

858
00:40:16,664 --> 00:40:18,082
Nothing.

859
00:40:18,082 --> 00:40:19,751
But then again,
neither does prison.

860
00:40:21,252 --> 00:40:23,087
I'm listening.

861
00:40:23,087 --> 00:40:25,798
Alright, so, we have a friend
who has a community center

862
00:40:25,798 --> 00:40:28,343
and he needs a volunteer to help
teach a computer literacy class

863
00:40:28,343 --> 00:40:29,552
to the neighborhood.

864
00:40:29,552 --> 00:40:31,763
You keep your nose clean,
you show up twice a week,

865
00:40:31,763 --> 00:40:33,264
I'll shred these.

866
00:40:33,264 --> 00:40:34,682
Otherwise, I've got
up to 18 months

867
00:40:34,682 --> 00:40:37,101
to file your felony paperwork
with the D. A.

868
00:40:37,101 --> 00:40:39,354
I thought you were gonna
take away all my electronics.

869
00:40:39,354 --> 00:40:40,939
I was.

870
00:40:40,939 --> 00:40:44,025
Lucky for you, Officer Thorsen
believes in second chances.

871
00:40:44,025 --> 00:40:46,861
Just take the deal,
kid.

872
00:40:46,861 --> 00:40:49,322
Pavi, why is there
a police car parked outside?

873
00:40:49,322 --> 00:40:52,784
Okay. Alright. I-I'm in.
Just text me the details.

874
00:40:54,869 --> 00:40:59,207
We did good.

875
00:41:15,306 --> 00:41:17,684
Officer Chen? I'm Agent Miller
from the Seattle field office.

876
00:41:17,684 --> 00:41:19,852
Nice to meet you, sir.
What do we know?

877
00:41:19,852 --> 00:41:22,271
House belongs to
a Phyllis and Raymond Haymen.

878
00:41:22,271 --> 00:41:24,023
Friends and family haven't
heard from them in over a week,

879
00:41:24,023 --> 00:41:25,400
but their car's
in the driveway.

880
00:41:25,400 --> 00:41:26,609
Any movement inside?

881
00:41:26,609 --> 00:41:28,277
None. We can hear their phones
ringing inside,

882
00:41:28,277 --> 00:41:30,238
but no one
ever answers them.

883
00:41:30,238 --> 00:41:31,406
Well,
something's not right.

884
00:41:31,406 --> 00:41:32,824
We were thinking
the same thing.

885
00:41:39,330 --> 00:41:41,249
FBI! Open up!

886
00:41:41,249 --> 00:41:43,835
We have a warrant
to search these premises.

887
00:42:06,357 --> 00:42:07,150
Look at that.

