Previously on "The Rookie"...
Lucy:
What's Metro doing here?
Metro would be
a good fit for Tim.
There's an opening
in Metro.
Lieutenant Pine just called me,
and I'm going over.
That's great.
Monica.
What are you doing here?
Elijah Stone is my client.
Del Monte:
Elijah's attorney?
We used to be engaged.
Hi.
I'm his mother.
Nolan: The boxes?
Your mother sold me
snake oil?
This is my boss' wife.
Do you have any idea what this
could do to my career?
Goodbye.
♪
Celina:
Alright. Turn to your left.
[Camera shutter clicks]
Turn to your right.
You know, the boardwalk
is a public place.
I have a right to perform.
Well, it does not
give you the right
to pick your
audience's pockets.
[Chuckles] You know
I can get out of these, right?
You can try.
[Handcuffs clicking,
chain rattling]
Voilà.
I'm a master escape artist.
♪
Cute. Let's go.
Gil: You know,
no cage can hold me.
Yeah?
[Buzzer]
Alright.
What about this cage?
A magician
is always prepared.
[Flame hisses]
[Gasps]
[Men coughing]
How did you think
that was gonna work?
Yeah. No.
I didn't get that far.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Nolan: [In distance]
No. You said that already.
And I already
explained it to you.
That's ridiculous.
No. Absolutely not.
No. I'm done.
No...
I am done.
Your mom?
How'd you know?
[Sighs]
Your shoulders
are touching your ears.
What's the latest?
She is, uh, devastated
that she hasn't been
invited to the wedding.
Did you tell her we're
not doing a big thing?
We literally have
two guests.
Explained all that.
Doesn't matter.
Still a knife
through her heart.
Look, if it helps,
I don't mind inviting her.
No. No way. No. It's...
It's not even
about the wedding.
She wants me to pay her
not to come... $10,000.
What?
I know.
Don't worry.
She is not coming.
I will not let her
ruin our wedding.
Mm.
[Exhales softly]
Oh. [Chuckles]
♪
Did I miss it?
It's cute.
[Chuckles]
Why are you up so early?
I was gonna get a photo
of your reaction.
There's a Metro
training today.
As the newbie, it's my job
to, uh, haul in the gear
and the ammo.
Yeah, the newbie.
The boot.
I'm a sergeant.
Mnh-mnh.
You're still a boot
in my book.
[Door opens]
Oh. Hey.
Are you
just getting home?
Must've been
a heck of a party.
Yeah. Rager.
Mm.
Did I interrupt something?
No. No,
I-I was just heading out.
Uh, can't be late
on my first day.
Mm-hmm.
Bye.
Hey.
You're gonna
be great today.
Knock 'em dead.
Bye.
Good morning.
[Scoffs] Whatever.
He is!
Well, of course you'd say that.
Because it's the truth.
Like you've ever
cared about the truth.
Okay, that's enough.
I'd ask where this animosity
is coming from,
but I have an idea.
Okay, this has nothing
to do with our past
and everything to do
with the law.
Let's focus on the law,
then, shall we?
You're presenting
a motion to exclude.
Yes, Your Honor.
You disagree.
Mr. Parker is an eyewitness
to this crime.
He picked the shooter
out of a lineup.
His testimony is essential
to this case.
Ms. Stevens.
You know as well as anyone
eyewitness testimony is flawed,
and this witness
had a gun pointed at him.
High levels of stress
negatively impact memory.
Okay, but any eyewitness
to a crime
has experienced
high levels of stress.
Are we throwing out
the very notion of witnesses?
Do not put words
in my mouth.
Okay.
[Clears throat]
I'm inclined to side with Monica
on this one.
I'm excluding
his testimony.
Wha... On... On what grounds?
That's absurd.
Watch yourself.
I'm sorry.
I meant no disrespect. Um...
I'm gonna need a few minutes
to confer with my team.
Good idea.
[Door opens]
Thank you.
♪
Metro Cop: [Through headset]
Okay, you have an active
shooter still at large.
Your job is to locate the
suspect and stop the threat.
♪
Mad Dog: Bang. You're dead.
You're telegraphing.
You're dead. Bang. Dead.
You're dead. Dead.
Bang. Dead.
Bradford, this isn't patrol.
This is Metro.
Major crimes, terrorism,
barricades, hostages.
We are an elite unit.
Your form's got to be
perfect, man.
Alright.
Let's take 10.
[Sighs] What, there's only
one way to clear a room?
That's news to me,
'cause I've actually done this
a million times successfully.
Don't worry.
Happens to everyone.
Metro takes
some getting used to.
You'll get it.
Harper: That is the dumbest
ruling I've ever heard.
Yeah, I agree.
But we're gonna
have to make this case
without Parker's testimony.
Do you really think
the jury will convict without?
No. I'm filing
for a continuance.
My team needs to regroup.
Well, I guess
I'm not testifying today.
Oh, it's just as well.
I was gonna have to
hand this one over to you.
Well, there's nothing
like a baby to win over a jury.
Oh, well, we're gonna need
all the help we can get
without that testimony.
Didn't something similar happen
in one of Lopez's cases?
Just like last month.
I'm never assigned to anything
she's investigated.
I remember she was pissed.
She handed your office
a perfect case.
Practically had a bow on it,
and then it fell apart in trial.
It was the same judge.
Well, judges can be fickle.
It's hard to predict
how they'll rule.
But Rivas has been solid
until recently.
True.
You know, I clerked for him
back when I was starting out.
Monica and I both did.
Mind like a scalpel.
Yeah, but he is
getting older.
I mean, if he's
starting to slip,
someone should talk to him
about retiring.
I mean,
maybe a former clerk
who knows how
to cushion the blow.
[Leah crying]
Oh. Sorry.
Can't stop,
not even for a second.
It's okay.
I've literally been there.
You go.
I'll deal with Rivas.
Thank you. Yeah.
[Leah crying]
Yes, well, what is going on?
Hm.
[Elevator bell dings]
Oh! Hey. I just heard
of a new place to try for lunch.
It's Chinese-
Ukrainian fusion.
Is it cheap?
No. But...
What? You're rich.
No, my parents are rich, okay?
And I'm not gonna take
any more of their money.
Since when?
Since my mom
showed me a prototype
of a new Aaron Thorsen
action figure.
Wha... That sounds awesome.
No, look, I worked hard
to have people
take me seriously as a cop.
I'm not gonna undermine it
for a couple million dollars.
Hold on. I'm sorry.
A couple million?
Yeah.
Dude, if you're
not gonna do it, I will.
Lucy Chen, Fist of Justice.
What are you doing?
Hi.
I'm, uh... I'm working
on my side hustle.
Oh. What's on your head?
You have a... You have
a little something on your head.
Uh, no.
It's... It's nothing.
I just need to get situated
into my new office.
Aaron: Metro-Police liaison.
Best of both worlds.
That's right.
♪
Well, at least it won't
take too long to move in.
No.
[Giggles]
♪
[Sighing] Alright.
She's your mom.
I mean, how can you not have
your mom at your wedding?
She's a narcissist
and a borderline con woman.
She tried to fleece
Sergeant Grey.
Okay, that's not good.
And not even close
to the worst thing she's done.
Yeah,
but she's your mom.
Look, my mom's challenging,
but I can't imagine
getting married without her.
Which probably means
I'll have to get married
in her living room.
[Chuckles] Look,
I run into this all the time.
You have
a fundamentally good mom,
so of course
you can't imagine my situation.
You're right.
I don't know what you've
dealt with. I shouldn't judge.
Ace: I will.
She's your mother.
She gave you life, man.
We caught you trying to pawn
your mother's jewelry
to buy drugs.
You don't get an opinion.
♪
Aaron: Seriously, how do you
live on a cop's salary?
It's not that bad.
I mean, we make good money.
My paycheck just evaporates.
I mean, my dry-cleaning bill
alone is $500 a week.
How are we supposed
to afford that?
We're not.
W-What are you dry-cleaning?
Your jeans?
Everything.
Aaron...
do you know
how to do your laundry?
Laundry ruins your clothes.
Dry cleaning is the most
cost-effective in the long run.
What... Who...
Where did you hear that?
My mom.
[Cellphone ringing]
Hey, what's up?
I'm at my babysitting job,
and things are weird.
Cosmo says when he woke up,
both of his parents were gone,
and now no one's
answering their phone.
Okay.
We'll be right there.
[Cellphone clicks]
Thanks for coming.
Lucy: Yeah, of course.
Cosmo's in here.
These are the cops
I was telling you about.
Hi.
You good?
How's the cereal?
Mm, it's cereal.
Hey, I offered you
unicorn cloud bread.
You're the one
who wanted Wheetie Bran.
Weirdo.
Can I play on the Switch?
Go ahead.
How's he doing?
He hasn't said much.
I know he's scared. He just
doesn't want to admit it.
Did you notice any signs of
forced entry when you got here?
No. I-I used my key
to get in.
I looked around for a little.
Everything seems normal.
No broken windows
or anything.
How well
do you know the family?
I've been working here
for six months.
The dad's a little aloof.
He works a lot.
Some investment thing.
The mom's around more.
She runs a non-profit.
Alright, well, we'll check
with their employers.
[Door opens, closes]
Mr. Laetner.
I've been calling you.
You called the police.
Sorry, uh, yeah, um...
I couldn't find anyone.
I was scared.
I'm so sorry.
It's all been so crazy.
We had a family emergency.
My wife had to fly home
to deal with an aunt
who had a heart attack.
I should have told you.
It... completely slipped my mind.
Where did you say
your wife was?
Cincinnati.
Uh, she probably forgot
her phone charger. Typical.
This is all
a-a big misunderstanding.
And where were you?
Your son woke up alone.
I...took her
to the airport.
I thought I could get back
before he woke up.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
He's in his room.
I'll go talk to him.
I'm so sorry
you came out for nothing.
Well, we need to talk to your
wife to, uh, verify she's okay.
It's protocol.
You understand, right?
Right.
Um, I'll get you
her aunt's number.
I know I have it somewhere.
Here.
Just give us her full name
and approximate age,
and we'll find it.
Of course.
[Chuckles]
Should I take Cosmo
to school?
You know what? He's missed
half the day already.
Can you stay
and look after him?
No problem. Great.
Again, I'm so sorry
we wasted your time.
I'll see you later.
You buying that?
Not a word.
We should loop in
the detectives.
Hey. I'm taking a poll.
How old were you when you did
your first load of laundry?
Bailey: Ooh. No idea.
I was living at home, though,
so...14?
Okay, Aaron's answer was never.
He was never years old.
What?
He doesn't know how.
[Chuckles] I don't know
why I should be so shocked.
What about you?
6. I learned early
my mom wasn't gonna do it.
Also not shocking.
Alright, well,
I got to go, babe.
I'll see you later at lunch.
Yeah, wouldn't miss it.
[Cellphone clicks]
It is a good thing
you wore a helmet.
I think you're gonna be fine.
[Gunshots, glass breaking]
Tom: Aah!
[Horn blares]
[Gunshots]
♪
[Tires squealing]
[Engine revs]
♪
[Bailey grunting]
[Breathing heavily]
[Sirens wailing,
indistinct radio chatter]
Hey. You hurt?
I'm fine. My partner
just went into surgery.
Who shoots at an ambulance?
I don't know.
I saw a red sedan speeding off.
I wish I could be more helpful.
I'm sorry.
I mean, don't apologize.
You jumped in front
and hit the brakes.
That's badass.
Badass or bad luck?
This is the second partner
I've sent into the hospital.
Well, if you really think
you have bad luck,
I know a great curandera.
She'll cleanse it right out.
I might take you up on that.
Just got word
from the hospital.
Your partner and the patient
are gonna be okay.
[Sighing]
Oh, good. Thank you.
They'll have
police escorts
until we figure out
who the target was.
Think they were shooting
at the patient?
It could have just been
a random drive-by. I don't know.
Well, we've got
officers canvassing,
looking for
security footage.
We'll know more soon.
So, when you get done here,
check in with Sergeant Hadley.
She'll be
coordinating the grid.
On it.
I don't suppose you'll be
taking the rest of the day off?
Because I got shot at?
Silly question.
Sorry I asked.
You'll call me
if you need anything?
Thank you. I will.
What's so important you can't
even let me get to my office?
We think Judge Rivas
is on the take.
That's a big accusation.
I know. But I also know him.
I know how his mind works.
And his rulings
have been inconsistent
over the past three months.
And it's not random.
They're all tied and connected
to Monica and her firm.
He overwhelmingly
rules in her favor.
So you think she's bribing the
judge to protect Elijah's guys?
With Elijah
writing the checks,
she's under tremendous pressure
to bring results.
I wouldn't put it past her
to bribe a judge.
I'll try to get a warrant
to search his financial records.
Be careful.
Judges look after each other.
You have to approach
someone you trust.
Judge Zuckerman and I
go way back.
She will not warn Rivas.
But will she openly
go against another judge?
There's only one way
to find out.
If Rivas is corrupt,
it calls all his cases
into question.
Even the ones
he didn't throw.
No telling how many criminals
could go free.
I know.
Keep me posted.
Lucy:
How much do you spend on food?
I'm not sure,
but I think I still have
all my takeout receipts.
Okay.
How much do you order in?
You know, I feel like
there's a right answer,
but I don't have an idea
what it is.
Cooking is a lot more
cost-effective, but...
You do know
how to cook, right?
Oh, yeah.
I make the perfect martini.
Lopez: You were right
about Sonia Laetner.
She wasn't on
any flight manifest,
and none of her family in Ohio
has heard from her.
What about her cellphone?
It last pinged near their house,
then went dead.
We're gonna find her body
in Griffith Park, aren't we?
Bring her husband in.
I want to talk to him. Okay.
♪ This is your gunpoint
confession ♪
[Target pops up,
paintball gun fires]
[Heavy metal music playing]
Mad Dog: [Through headset]
There's no excuses
for a bad shot.
Metro never misses.
♪ A serpent tongue,
a jealous type ♪
Good call.
Mikey's a lovely man.
Although his ex-wife
might disagree.
[Target pops up]
♪ Leeching hope
from the ones you know ♪
♪ I will not leave you whole
[Alarm blares, bell rings]
Yeah, Bradford. Nice.
[Applause]
Mad Dog: Well, clearly
you got the goods to be here.
And now that you're one of us,
you get the company ink.
What are you talking about?
What ink?
It's the tattoo
we all have, brother.
It's how we
show our loyalty.
Oh, come on.
We all know
that as soon as a group of cops
get the same tattoo,
they're going to prison.
What are you
trying to say?
♪
Alright, let me see it.
[Laughs]
Lighten up, brother. Here.
Here.
Have a unicorn.
Too kind.
[Laughs]
Too kind. Thank you.
♪
They're testing you,
seeing how far you'll bend.
Yeah, I saw
the same kind of thing
when I was
in the military.
Not about how many stripes
on your sleeves with this crew.
It's all good.
Team building.
If you're gonna lead this team,
they need to know who you are.
Show them the Tim Bradford
that was tapped to join Metro
in the first place.
Thanks.
Lopez: Mr. Laetner,
if your wife, Sonia, is in Ohio,
do you have any idea why
her car was parked in Hollywood
with her phone and purse
still inside?
Deon: I don't know.
See, in my line of work,
when a woman takes a last-minute
trip with no money,
9 times out of 10, her husband's
got something to do with it.
So where's Sonia?
I don't know.
I swear.
That's the truth.
Look, you're right.
I-I did lie
to your officers earlier.
But he said if I involved
the police, he'd kill Sonia.
Who said that?
The man who took her.
Look, Sonia never
came home last night.
I was about to call the police
when my phone rang,
and they said if I ever wanted
to see her again,
I'd have to pay him
$250,000.
I need the number.
It said "blocked."
Listen. I know
I-I shouldn't have lied,
but I'd really prefer
to handle this myself.
Unfortunately, that's no longer
an option, Mr. Laetner.
And you owe it to your wife
to use every resource available
to bring her home safely.
What do you think
I've been trying to do?!
You're right.
I-I'm... I'm sorry.
It's alright.
It's a stressful situation.
Now, what can you tell me
about the man's voice?
To the left.
[Video game beeping]
To the right.
To the left.
Oh! Watch out!
Mm.
[Explosion, beeping stops]
I thought you were gonna
get first place.
You don't want
to play again?
You know,
I don't like to brag,
but I'm, like, really good
friends with the cops here.
They're doing
everything they can
to make sure
your mom comes home to you.
And until she does,
you can call me.
Whenever you want.
Even if it's just to talk.
Got it?
[Footsteps approaching]
Cosmo, let's go.
He did not look happy.
Lopez: He's not.
What happened?
Claims Sonia was kidnapped
for a ransom
but doesn't want
the cops involved.
Do we buy that?
He's already lied to us once.
I'm not taking anything
at face value.
You spend a lot of time
at the house.
Do you think he'd hurt her?
No. He's...
He's never been violent.
I've heard them argue
maybe like twice.
Why?
Do you think he killed her?
I'm not ruling anything out.
We need a team
to search the house.
Once they're done,
I want units parked outside.
If he leaves
for any reason,
I want him followed.
You got it.
I'm gonna get a warrant for
his phone. For whatever reason,
he cannot be allowed
to make a money drop alone...
if there even is
a money drop.
Alright. Come on.
[Siren wailing]
Nolan: Detectives just
got a partial plate
from the surveillance footage
near the ambulance shooting.
Shooter left driving
a 1992 red Sentra.
What do you got here?
New car fire.
No obvious sign of arson,
but that's for the investigators
to decide.
Let's call in an 11-85
for impound to our location.
Copy that.
So any news on that shooting
from this morning?
It's got all my guys
a little on edge.
Yeah. We got a lot of good
detectives working on that.
We'll let you know
as soon as we learn something.
Appreciate it.
Tow truck's 30 minutes out.
Nolan: Right.
[Gunshots]
Get down. Get down.
[Gunshots continue]
Pull him up.
We got you. We got help coming.
Call it in.
Control, shots fired
at our location.
We have a firefighter down.
He is conscious and breathing.
Send an R.A. and backup.
[Engine revving,
tires screeching]
[People shouting indistinctly]
Control,
also send an airship.
Suspect fleeing location,
red sedan, east on Olympic.
Captain Burke: [Through phone]
We answer more than
1,000 calls a day.
My people can't do their jobs
with a bullseye
on their backs.
Effective immediately,
the LAPD will dispatch units
to accompany
your firefighters on calls.
We had cops at the
burned-out car. Didn't help.
You need to
catch this guy now!
[Click, dial tone]
Yeah.
[Knock on glass]
You wanted to see me, sir?
Yes.
Your mother called.
Sir?
As in me.
As in asking why
her son is dodging her calls.
She even called Dispatch.
I am so sorry.
Save your apologies.
I don't want to hear
from your crazy mother again.
I'll get... If you...
I'll...
Go.
♪
Nolan: You okay?
I'll be better
once there's not some psycho
gunning for every fire crew
in the city.
We'll find him.
It's only a matter of time.
[Cellphone ringing]
Yeah.
Mom?
Well, it's from
a different number.
Hello.
Dr. Schnitzel:
Hello. I'm Dr. Schnitzel.
Your mother was just admitted,
and we need to verify
her insurance.
Really? Dr. Schnitzel?
You... You... You really think
I'm gonna buy that?
I don't...
Look. You tell my mom
it's not happening.
Alright?
A-And word of advice...
Don't let her pull you
into any of her schemes.
What was that?
Ah, vintage Mom.
She's moved on to number 5
in her playbook...
pretend to be sick
for sympathy,
get me to give my credit card
number to an accomplice.
Cosmo would love this.
I've never seen a kid
who was such a health nut.
[Chuckles]
You've been putting in
a lot of hours at their house.
Not that many.
And you're working
the night shift somewhere.
This morning, you were
not coming home from a party.
Not dressed like that.
You were coming home from a job.
What's going on with you?
You need money
or something?
♪ I'd just play along
I got to get
that first month, last month,
and security deposit.
♪ Now you're leaving
It's not like
I can stay here forever.
Why would you say that?
Of course you can.
How's that gonna work?
You, me, and Tim?
And that's assuming you wouldn't
want to get your own place.
Either way,
there's no room for me.
[Door opens]
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Ready for the movie?
I found out
that "Time After Time"
is on a streaming platform.
I think I'm gonna crash.
Are you sure?
David Warner is amazing in this.
♪ Before I started
[Door shuts]
Well, I guess it's just us.
Popcorn?
Yeah, sure.
Any chance your judge signed off
on the warrant?
Uh, short answer, no.
"Insufficient probable cause."
No judge wants to imply
that a fellow member of the
bench is guilty of malfeasance.
Well, no warrant,
no evidence.
No way of proving
your judge is bent.
I'm having a hard time
believing it myself.
He's one of the most
honorable people I know.
Yeah, I guess no one
is incorruptible.
[Sighs]
You know, his chambers
are just a few doors down.
What if I go talk to him?
I've been where he is.
Maybe he'll open up.
I don't have
any better ideas.
I got to go.
Wesley.
You're working late.
Yeah, you, too.
Just chatting with Rivas?
Reminiscing.
You know, a lot's changed.
We split up.
You got all sanctimonious.
You sold your soul
to the devil.
[Both scoff]
It's really that simple to you,
isn't it?
Good and evil.
In this case, yeah.
It is.
See you in court. Hmm.
[Elevator bell dings]
[Sighs]
[Knock on door]
[Door opens]
Oh, Mr. Evers.
[Door closes]
I'm afraid
I was just leaving.
I'll be brief.
I know you're
throwing cases.
I beg your pardon?
I don't have any evidence.
Monica's too smart for that.
Elijah Stone
is too smart for that.
You didn't know, did you?
He is her biggest client.
Every time she asks you
to rule in her favor,
it's for one of his guys.
You're helping
rebuild his empire.
I'm helping? The whole reason
he's back on the streets
is because of you!
I know!
I am well aware
of my part in all this.
Which is why I know that
you haven't slept in months,
you can't concentrate,
and sometimes your heart
races so fast,
you think you're having
a heart attack.
A life lived
in the service of justice.
I always wanted that
to be my legacy.
It still can be.
Help me put Elijah
where he belongs.
He goes after
anyone who crosses him.
I'm sure you could cut a deal
for witness protection.
And I'm sure I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Please leave.
You know how to reach me
if you change your mind.
♪
Hey.
Any updates on Cosmo's mom?
Uh, no. We had units
parked outside all night.
There was no movement.
But, you know, they have
his phones tapped,
so if the kidnappers call,
we'll know.
Do you think
she's still alive?
Listen.
If it's about money,
they have every incentive
to keep her alive
until they get
what they want.
[Cellphone ringing]
Cosmo?
Cosmo: Dad says
I'm not going to school,
and he won't
come out of his office.
Can you come over?
I'll be right there.
Hey. I don't think
that's a good idea.
I have to.
Tamara? Um, I'll be
parked outside, okay?
You got here early.
I did.
I had a thought this morning.
Our shooter is specifically
targeting firefighters.
You don't just
get up one morning
and decide to start
shooting at LAFD.
This is what
it escalated to.
Okay, so you thought
it may have started somewhere.
Exactly. So I started
looking into
any case that involves
the fire department...
complaints, lawsuits,
patrol calls...
anything and everything.
I can help.
No need.
I got him.
His name is Anthony Pickett.
He's a firefighter...
ex-firefighter,
to be specific.
Got cut
and didn't take it well?
Yeah, he made it
through the academy
but washed out
during probation.
Other firefighters found him
to be difficult and aggressive.
He actually picked a fight with
an old-timer who later found
the hose had been cut
on his breathing apparatus.
Mm. Short fuse.
Few days after that, he showed
up at the station that cut him
looking to get his job back.
Unit was called out, but
he seemed to accept his fate.
But apparently,
he couldn't let it go.
Okay,
how do we know it's him?
Cross-referenced
his registered vehicle
with our description
and partial plate.
It's a match.
I already put out a BOLO.
I'll send units
to sit on the house.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Good work.
Lucy: Thank you.
I know I volunteered us
for the most boring
detail ever.
Of course.
You're worried about Tamara.
I get it. Yeah.
Plus, it gives me time
to apartment-hunt.
Mm.
It's hard to find a place
with a pool.
♪
Yeah. I mean,
you might need
to be a little flexible
with that one.
Well, I used your "rent should
be 30% of your salary" rule...
Oh.
...and... and there's like
nothing in my price range.
Well...
hold on.
That place is cute.
Yeah.
This place is trash.
Uh, that place
looks like my apartment.
[Video game beeping]
[Door opens]
[Door shuts]
I'm gonna go
check on your dad.
[Beeping continues]
Deon: [Muffled]
No. You listen to me.
If you do anything to hurt her,
I swear...
That's not possible.
You're not giving me
enough time. I need more time.
I can't!
No. She's got
nothing to do with this.
And how do I know that?
[Cellphone clicks]
Please...
let me talk to her.
Put her on.
[Cellphone rings, clicks]
Hey.
I think Deon's on the phone
with the kidnappers now.
I don't have your money!
I can hear him shouting.
What's he saying?
I can't make it out.
He's emotional.
[Muffled]
I'm sorry. Please put her on.
It has to be them. Please.
Tamara, the detectives
are listening
to all of his known phones,
okay? He's under surveillance.
Just let the investigators
do their job.
All you got to do is make sure
that kid is safe. That's it.
His known phones.
What if he's on a burner?
Tamara...
[Muffled] No. She's got
nothing to do with this!
How do I know that? Huh?
Please... let me talk to her.
Put her on.
He's saying, "Let me
talk to her. Put her on."
"I don't have your money.
I spent it."
...think you'd miss it.
"I didn't think you'd miss it."
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry."
Please. Don't hurt her.
"Please don't hurt her."
Uh, Tamara, don't let him know
that you heard him, okay?
Just get as far away as you can.
We're heading in right now.
That bastard.
This happened because of him.
[Muffled click]
He hung up.
I got to go.
♪
What are you doing?
Listening in?
Yeah.
I heard everything.
You did this for money?
You don't understand.
You're right.
I don't understand.
Police are on their way.
Let them help you.
No. These guys will kill her!
[Banging on door]
Aaron: [Muffled]
Police!
[Door opens]
Mr. Laetner, you need
to come with us.
Time to come clean. Which one of
your clients did you steal from?
Are you sure Cosmo's okay?
Tamara is with him.
He's fine.
You need to focus.
We know you were
skimming money,
and we know someone took
your wife in retaliation.
Who was it?
Reed Butler.
That wasn't very smart.
He's killed for a lot less.
I know.
But I figured he's a criminal.
I'm stealing back
the money he stole.
It's justice, kind of.
How noble of you.
Look, I know I'm not innocent
in all this,
but my wife is.
Please help.
I need you to call
the people who have your wife
and tell them
you've got the money.
Set up a place
for the exchange.
He knows I don't have the money.
He'll know I'm lying.
Tell them a family member
came through,
wired it to you
this morning.
Okay. A-And then?
Then you're gonna
write down a confession
detailing how you embezzled
money from a client.
I'm going to jail,
aren't I?
Probably.
[Voice breaking]
I'm such an idiot.
No argument
from this side of the table.
Rivas texted
early this morning.
Was it a full
admission of guilt?
"Can we talk?" He's been careful
not to admit anything,
but I can tell he wants to.
[Sighs]
Judge Rivas?
♪
He's cold.
It looks like there's
no injury, no blood.
It looks like
maybe a heart attack.
Elijah did this.
We don't know that for sure.
At his age...
But Monica
saw me last night.
She knew I could
get through to him.
Elijah had him killed
to protect her.
♪ No definition
♪ Not empathy
Tim: Alright, everyone
switch to channel 9.
Listen up. We have
a confirmed hostage situation
at that compound
across the street.
Hostage is Sonia Laetner.
White female, dark hair.
Last seen with an orange sweater
and black pants.
We've identified
five suspects on site,
but there could be more.
We don't know which building
our hostage is being held in,
so we need to clear everything.
Detective Lopez
will be our spotter.
She'll provide overwatch.
Why not let Metro
provide overwatch?
Because we need
all our boots on the ground.
And there's no one I'd rather
have on my six than La Adelita.
Oh.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I-I had no idea.
You're a legend
at the range.
No worries.
Go get her back.
You heard her.
Let's move.
No mistakes.
♪
In position.
Are we clear?
♪
Main concourse is clear.
Green and go.
♪
[Through speakers] ♪ Money in
the mattress, pull up stunt ♪
♪ Running to the money
like my last name Gump ♪
♪ Got a briefcase in the trunk,
hell nah I ain't no punk ♪
♪ I do what I want
not what you say ♪
♪
[Speaking indistinctly]
[Whispering]
Cover me.
♪
[Indistinct conversation]
[Stones clattering]
Police!
Drop the weapon!
Step away from the weapon.
Put your hands up.
Hand up. Turn around.
Put your hands on your head.
♪
Hands behind your back.
B Team, two in custody.
♪
Adam Team, I need trailers
for one in custody. Ramp room.
Moving forward on our sweep.
It's how I envisioned it ♪
♪ I make it rain
and she go ham ♪
♪ Girl pop it for the gram
make me wanna ♪
[Loud bang]
Mad Dog: Freeze! Police!
Get on the ground!
Don't move! Don't move!
The ground! Now!
C Team, two in custody.
♪
[Sonia sobbing]
Swan: Shut up already!
I said shut up!
♪
Kill the power
when I give the signal.
♪
It is what it is.
Crying about it
ain't gonna do no good.
♪
[Sobs]
[Phone line ringing]
♪
Tim: [Quietly]
Come on. Just take one step.
[Ringing continues]
Something's wrong.
Time's up.
[Gunshot, Sonia screams]
[Sobbing]
♪
Tim: It's okay.
Adam Team, one in custody.
Hostage is safe.
We are Code 4.
It's okay. You're safe now.
[Mid-tempo music playing
on car radio]
7-Adam-15,
eyes on suspect.
♪
[Car door opens]
Nolan: Police!
Don't.
You move an inch
towards that trunk,
I'll be forced to shoot you.
Hands in the air.
Now!
Okay.
Step back
towards my voice.
Again. Again.
On your knees.
♪
Suspect in custody.
We're Code 4.
Better bring in
the bomb squad.
Someone brought a grenade
to the party.
[Breathing heavily]
You're welcome!
For what?
Well, I created an Excel
spreadsheet for your expenses.
I used something similar
when I first started on the job.
It is super helpful.
And I-I can send you
the app, as well.
Mm-hmm.
And trust me.
You're gonna feel so gratified
when you hit your target
at the end of the month,
and you'll see that those, um...
those juices
aren't on the daily budget. Sorry.
Mm.
Appreciate that, but...
I talked to my mom
last night,
and she's backing down on
the whole action-figure thing,
so it's all good.
Oh. So you're
taking her money again.
Yeah, I-I just
can't live in poverty.
Uh...
It's not poverty.
Aaron!
[Indistinct conversations,
siren wails in distance]
Hey, Bradford.
Good job out there today. Thanks.
They're a good bunch
once you get to know them.
Yeah.
I'll take your word for it.
Nothing against Patrol, but...
Metro is a different beast.
We get called in situations that
are already at a boiling point.
That kind of stress
creates a special bond.
And I'm on
the outside of that.
And every single one of them
was, too, at some point.
Give it a little time.
Okay.
You want to grab
a beer with us?
Do I have a choice?
It's tradition.
New guy buys a round.
[Chuckles]
Come on.
[Nightlands' "Whiplash"
playing]
Yes, I'm happy
to send over my references.
And I can start
whenever you need me.
Thanks.
Hey. You looking
for another job?
Uh, Cosmo's parents are
definitely getting a divorce.
Sonia wants to keep me on,
but she's not sure
if she can afford it
with all the legal fees, so...
You're not still worried about
having to move out, are you?
I just don't want
to be a burden.
You're not.
Tamara, look.
I get it. Your whole life,
you've been displaced
from one home to another,
but that's over now.
Girl, we're family.
You couldn't get rid of me
if you tried.
♪ To think too much
Thanks.
But I will get
my own place eventually.
Mm-hmm.
I don't plan
to be the weirdo roommate
when you and Tim
start having babies.
[Inhales sharply]
That's a long way off.
But I don't know.
Maybe it could work out.
I heard you're
a really good babysitter.
[Inhales sharply]
You can't afford my rate.
It's like that?
It is.
Okay. And you're really gonna
leave all your artwork behind?
[Indistinct conversation]
Monica: Wesley. Keep bothering
me and my associates,
I'll happily
alert the press.
Judge Rivas is dead.
Yes, I heard.
What happened?
Heart attack.
[Sighs]
But we both know that's a lie.
Elijah had him killed for you.
That's ridiculous.
He believed in you
when you were starting out.
And for good reason.
I am an excellent lawyer...
and profoundly litigious,
so watch the accusations.
I did warn you.
This is the price
of working for Elijah.
Well, if you're done mansplaining,
I've got some actual
work to do.
♪ Comparison's a thief
I guess Elijah finally
found his perfect lawyer,
one with
as little morality as him.
What I can't decide
is if the woman that I
fell in love with in law school,
who was kind and loving,
is just gone
or if she never really existed.
♪
Were you always just a sociopath
putting on an act?
♪
He'll kill you, too,
you know.
Eventually.
♪ Better days are coming fast
[Cellphone chimes]
Another text.
You are a hero
to firefighters everywhere.
So they admit
that police officers
aren't entirely useless.
Today.
Tomorrow, the rivalry resumes.
I'll take it.
[Laughs]
[Cellphone ringing]
Is that your mom again?
Foxburg Memorial Hospital.
Hello?
Yes, this is he.
♪
I don't understand.
Oh.
Alright, thank you.
What?
♪
My mom died.
- Captions by VITA...
♪