[Music playing indistinctly]
♪
[Siren chirps]
[Music stops]
♪ Is that a baton
in your pocket ♪
♪ Or are you just happy
to see me? ♪
License and registration, please.
♪ She puts the "short"
in "shorty" ♪
♪ And he looks like
he wants to chase me ♪
♪ Cop cuties, cute and on duty
♪ Navy blue booties,
go ahead and lock me up ♪
♪ Arrest me,
but make it sexy... ♪
Sorry. Sorry.
♪ Arrest me, but make it sexy
♪ Sell me some meth, please
♪ So I can get arrested
by this daddy of a cop ♪
♪ With his daddy cop walk
Just give me a second.
♪ And his daddy cop arms
and his daddy cop butt ♪
♪ Ow
♪ Cop cuties, cute and on duty
♪ Cop cuties,
cute and on duty ♪
Singer and Celina:
♪ Arrest me, but make it sexy
♪ Arrest me,
but make it sexy ♪
What? It's catchy.
♪ Arrest me,
but make it sexy ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Thanks.
Hey. DA's office just thanked me
for a 14% decrease
in officer no-shows in court.
Not bad for one week.
Well, instead of putting
the court notices
in the officer's box,
I serve it to them directly,
that way they can't say
they didn't get it.
That's great,
but isn't that a lot of work?
What else do I have
going on?
Well...
Oh, down to my last one.
What, Smitty?
He avoids court
like a salad.
Hey, Smitty.
♪
Hey, it's
"House Mouse" Bradford.
How's court liaison
treating you?
All good.
♪
Oh, sorry. No can do.
That's my day off.
You don't like money?
Yeah, I like money.
You get OT the whole day,
you know.
It's not just comp time?
No, you scroll down to
the bottom of your time sheet
and click "For Pay."
20 years,
no one told me that?
♪
Good looking out.
I owe you a beer.
Oh, no, no.
No, it's all good.
♪
Good work.
You made Smitty happy.
Hey. Hang in there.
Good morning.
Today's gon' be a tough one.
Heat wave has maxed out
the power grid.
Expect more citywide
rolling blackouts.
Officer Juarez,
what's the acronym
that best applies
to heat waves?
♪
Oh.
[Mouthing]
Cheetah?
♪
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm having a blackout of my own.
See me after.
Yes, sir.
[Whispering]
"Cheetah?"
You know this.
♪
CHEAP.
"C"... Check the vulnerable.
Check your partner.
"H"... Hydrate.
"E"... Eat light meals.
"A"... Avoid prolonged sun.
"P"... Pace yourself.
You can't do everything.
Look, conserve your energy.
Make smart choices.
Heat equals more violence.
Blackouts equals more theft.
It's gon' be
a busy day today,
so pace yourself.
[Power shuts down]
Don't worry.
The city has laid out top dollar
for a state-of-the-art
generator,
which should turn on
right about... now.
Not everyone else is gon' be
so lucky,
so be safe out there.
Everyone's 10-8.
[Indistinct conversations]
Yes, sir?
The heat wave's been here
for a week.
She doesn't know
what CHEAP is?
Uh, well...
I assume you reviewed it
with her.
Uh...
Nolan, either
you reviewed it with her
and she forgot, or you forgot
to review it with her.
So who do I have
a problem with?
I did go over it with her.
Yes, sir.
She... She just forgot.
She's riding with me today.
Sir?
I want to see
what else she forgot...
what else
you didn't drill into her.
Are you evaluating her
or are you evaluating me?
You. You have an issue
with that?
No, sir. No. No, I...
Did the A/C come back on?
Because it's so...
Officer Juarez,
you're riding with me today.
Come on.
Any advice?
Uh, yeah. I would just go light
on the astrology talk
and crystals.
And auras.
And tarot cards, too.
And...
And definitely no dreams.
Okay, so keep it professional.
No hobbies.
Yes. Unless you come up
with one of those case-solving
insights, then yes,
you speak right up.
Okay. So you want me
to be myself?
Yes. And also no.
Just if you get one of those
feelings, go back and figure out
the facts that led you
to feeling that way.
Okay, so don't be my... me.
Juarez, let's go.
You're gonna be great.
♪
Please be great.
Hey. How's it going?
I see you have a lot to,
uh, liaise.
And enjoying
every minute of it.
I thought we said we would
never lie to each other.
That was a lie.
You're miserable.
No.
Mm-hmm.
No, it's not that bad.
You know, nice people.
Low stress.
Wait, wait.
Um, that reminds me...
Next week.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Be safe out there.
[Chuckles]
I'll see you
at the end of shift.
[Sighs]
I, uh, speak Spanish.
Okay, that's not good.
Great spot. Tell me why.
Well, I'm not sure.
I can just tell
something's wrong.
Bad aura? A feeling?
A hunch?
Well, stopping someone
on a hunch is illegal,
Sergeant Grey. Correct.
Tell you what.
Why don't we walk that way
while you talk it through?
Pretend you don't see them.
Okay, well,
the store is open.
No one's in distress,
and there's an employee
with them.
He's even laughing.
Why does it bother me?
So we're getting closer.
Tell me what you know
or we walk away.
There's a crime happening
right now, Officer Juarez.
♪
Each one of those saws
is about 900 bucks.
I mean, that's almost nine grand
in tools.
In a blackout,
debit cards don't work,
and who walks around
with nine grand cash?
See, that, Celina,
is absolutely perfect.
Control, 7-Adam-200.
I got a plate.
2-William-Adam-Charlie-4-8-4.
Hey, guys, quick question.
Great tools there.
Did you pay cash or card?
♪
[Grunts]
Hey, hey, hey.
Sgt. Grey: Hey.
Turn around. Turn around.
[Man grunts]
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Nolan: No, I agree.
A dollar is a lot
for a glass of lemonade,
but that's just
smart business,
not price gouging.
Certainly doesn't buy you
the right to threaten anyone.
Yeah, especially not a bunch
of 9-year-old girls.
Woman:
Turn to the left.
Kicking over their stand,
threatening them.
They were terrified.
You're lucky
that the oldest one
doesn't have
her black belt yet.
That could have been
a lot worse, Andrew.
Yeah.
[Powering down]
Okay. According to Grey,
they should be back on
about... now.
I guess you need
Grey's magic touch.
Yeah.
Want to go check it out?
Oh, you guys
are already on it.
Any luck?
I think it's dead.
Nolan:
Check the battery?
Yeah. All good.
Maybe the coolant
leaking?
I don't see any.
Maybe the shut-off valve
is closed. I'll check it out.
Hey.
Buddy, hey, we got it.
You know,
it's a little crowded in here.
You mind?
[Dramatic music plays]
You guys
from this precinct?
I'm new here,
so maybe we haven't met yet.
I am.
Bobby here's usually
with the 57th.
Okay.
Huh.
Well, nice to meet you.
♪
LAPD doesn't have precincts.
No such thing as the 57th.
Impersonating an officer
and stealing police property
are both felonies.
I'm sure they didn't
teach you that
in your imaginary police academy.
We weren't trying
to steal the generator.
Then what were you doing?
I noticed the smell
this morning.
You smell it?
[Groans] Yeah.
I-I figure an animal
got in there and died.
Could be a rat,
but it's a big smell for a rat.
Maybe a raccoon.
Skunk. Mountain lion.
You think a mountain lion
got in there and died?
Well, there's one way
to find out.
Can I see
those lock cutters?
Maybe I should cut it.
I mean, if it's a mountain lion,
you probably want to shoot it.
Well, I mean, if it's dead,
I won't need to shoot it, right?
Oh, good point.
Control, Seven-L-19.
I'm at unit 15.
About to cut the lock
to make entry.
♪
[Both coughing]
[Dramatic music plays]
♪
Whew. Ugh.
That ain't good.
♪
Poor thing probably got trapped
looking for food.
[Gasps]
♪
That's not good.
So if you weren't trying to
steal the generator, then what?
Our friend got pinched this
morning, and we thought,
you know, knock out the power,
get her out.
You do realize locks work
without electricity, right?
Wait,
this ain't maximum security?
We like to keep things simple,
like our criminals.
We find low tech
gets the job done.
Hey, you guys Code-4?
Yeah. That state-of-the-art
generator
was in a state
of disrepair.
Those guys had done
a real number on it,
but we managed to get it working.
Good, 'cause
General Services would take
about a week to fix it.
As soon as you get finished
processing them,
I need you back 10-8.
Pending calls are piling up.
I have to open up a CP just
to deal with these power issues.
Celina's going to be my lead.
Really? That's great. That's...
So things are going well?
So far.
Yeah. She's very well-trained,
don't you think?
She has good instincts.
You can't teach that.
No, no, but you can certainly
teach someone
to sharpen those skills.
♪
Command Post lead...
that's pretty impressive.
Yeah, they almost never
give that to an officer
who's got less
than five years on.
We... We never spoke
about it.
Yeah, but she'll do fine,
I'm sure.
Which is what we want.
It is about her, right?
Yeah, no, yeah, definitely. Yeah.
♪
Body was in a freezer.
The power's been
in and out for days.
The surge must have
finished the freezer off.
Victim thawed in the heat.
Manager called it in.
The manager said the unit
was rented by an RJ Cash.
Alright.
RJ Cash, huh?
Looks like him.
Are y...
Are you identifying him?
Oh, not officially,
but, yeah.
Career criminal...
mostly nonviolent,
but career scam artist.
Loves to target the elderly...
or loved.
My uncle used to refinish pianos.
I can tell you right now
that is worth a fortune.
Mm. Yeah, I bet a lot
of the stuff in here is.
So, stolen?
Or grifted.
Uh, get as many serial numbers
as you can
and run them through RMS.
Maybe we can track down
some of his victims.
You got it.
You want to get some air?
Yeah, for sure. I stopped
breathing three minutes ago.
I'm about to pass out.
Is there any chance we could
get Tim in on this?
He's Court Liaison.
What does that have to do
with this?
[Scoffs] Nothing.
I'm just trying to find a way to
keep him from losing his mind.
Is there no other position
he can move into?
No.
Everything is at a standstill.
All right, well,
then you're gonna
have to shake things up...
create an opening.
Like when a team
needs a player,
but they're up against
a salary cap.
Well, what does that mean?
It means you got
to get creative.
Find a weak link and
start a five-player trade.
Whoa. Say more.
All right, let's say that
Tim wants to go to Vice.
McNichols is already there,
but everyone knows
he wants Narcotics.
That was
a very ambitious plan,
trying to take out the station's
power to spring your friend.
Loyalty's important.
Plus, she owes me money.
Unfortunately, you won't get
a chance to spend it
unless it's at
the prison store.
Uh...
Destruction of government
emergency equipment... felony.
Grand theft... felony.
Impersonating
a police officer... felony.
Attempted rescue
of a prisoner... felony.
Carrying a loaded firearm
in the commission of a crime
is...
Felony?
That's right. Wow.
I hope your friend
appreciates your sacrifice.
Maybe this wasn't the best plan
on my part.
You think?
Tell you what...
you knock down my charges
and give me probation,
and I'll give you something
better than some fool
in a cop uniform
running around in your basement.
Okay. It's got to
be something really great.
It is.
You know about ghost guns?
♪
Any luck with
the serial numbers?
Yeah.
I mean, I got over 100 items.
About 30 victims.
Nice work.
And I found RJ's most recent
employer, Beatrice O'Malley.
I imagine some of the stolen
property must be hers,
so let's get her
in here as well.
Yeah, you got it.
Oh, what's Metro doing here?
Uh, Lopez caught a break
on a ghost gun dealer.
It's their case.
They move as a pack.
That's the alpha
and her right hand, Kevin Hicks.
Metro would be
a good fit for Tim, hmm?
It's a tough gig.
The hours are brutal.
Hicks looks dead on his feet.
I know he's got
triplets at home.
His wife does publicity
for the department.
I mean, Hicks might be up
for a transfer.
A bit more family time.
And if he left Metro,
Tim could take his spot.
You make it sound easy.
Hicks would only leave
for a comparable job,
and there aren't that many.
And if there were,
they're filled.
How do you create
that opening?
I don't know, like you said,
the five-player trade.
What could go wrong?
A lot,
for both you and Tim.
If sergeants feel like
they're being manipulated,
then they will never
trust you again.
And they talk.
So the next time you need
a favor, and you will,
the answer will be no forever.
So tread lightly.
♪
Lieutenant Pine,
Angela Lopez.
Oh, Angela.
This is Kevin Hicks.
Thanks for looping us in.
Of course.
It's Metro's case.
It just fell in our laps.
Okay, listen up.
This is Detective Lopez.
She's about to share
some information
your sorry asses couldn't find
if it was gift wrapped for you.
Detective, please tell my team
how it's done.
Okay.
I'm gonna make this quick.
[Whispering] Come on, come on,
just pick up. Pick up.
[Sighs]
Celina, did you reach DWP's
Joint Response Coordinator?
Left messages, sir. Three.
So what about Fire's
Emergency Response Captain?
Did you get ahold of FEMA?
No, sir.
I-I'm still working on it.
ADT?
They were next
on the list, sir.
Celina, you got to get ahold
of these people.
What about the other
Watch Commanders?
We need Civil Unrest
React Teams.
Do you need something?
I can help her.
No, it's okay.
I've got it.
No, you don't, Boot.
I got a buddy
at DWP Joint Response.
I can give you
his direct line,
and I can help coordinate
the React Teams.
Please do.
[Indistinct conversations]
Come on, Boot.
You want to learn how to do this
or not?
Hey, you're Hicks, right?
Yeah. Alright,
what you need?
Got an op
about to jump off.
Oh, um,
I heard you have triplets.
That must be a lot of work.
[Laughs] Yeah. Tougher than
anything LAPD can throw at me.
Yeah, I bet.
I imagine having kids
must make you reevaluate
your priorities.
Yeah, wife's not too happy.
So, listen.
Um, my roommate
is an excellent babysitter,
and she's always looking for
work if you ever need someone.
Really?
Mm.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
Detective, Lieutenant.
They say it's gonna hit 100.
Thanks.
Nolan and Thorsen are the ones
that made the original bust
that gave us our tip.
Nice work.
Thank you.
Right place at the right time.
I know you.
You're the guy who got
the golden ticket, right?
That's right, I did.
Expected you to go Metro,
but you took T.O. instead.
Interesting move.
I like teaching the kids.
Matter of fact,
my trainee is heading up
the Command Post
as we speak.
You don't say. Well, if you ever
do consider Metro,
give me a call.
It's a tough test,
but I will make sure
you get a good tutor.
Thank you very much.
Shall we?
Listen up.
Today's op is a UC gun buy-bust.
I'm the UC.
Targets are using a pharmacy as
a front to sell ghost guns.
Trouble sign is hands up,
gun out, or running away.
Bust sign is fingers
through the hair.
Hold sign
is dropping the purse.
Metro Sergeants Shab
and Watson have been working
this case for months,
but Detective Lopez here
uncovered the code
the gun sellers need to hear
in order to sell weapons.
We weren't able to get close
enough for our own visuals,
but luckily, Metro was able to
hack into the security cameras,
so their cameras
are now our eyes and ears.
Everybody sharp today.
No fear, no regret,
no mistakes, no excuses.
"Metro" on three.
One, two, three.
All: Metro.
♪
Metro seems normal.
You'll have a blast there.
Oh, no, thanks.
Text Lopez... Eric Mills,
A.K.A. "Knuckles" on her six.
Hawaiian shirt, jeans.
Unknown if armed.
[Cellphone vibrates]
Picking up?
Dropping off.
I have an issue
that needs to "go away."
My prescription's
for Charcoal Cough Syrup.
Sure. We've got that.
Cash only.
It's got to be untraceable.
[Tense music plays]
Wait, I know this chick.
How do I know you?
You don't know me,
and you don't want to know me.
[Chuckles] Yeah.
I do.
[Gun cocks]
[Powering down]
Damn it.
We have rolling blackouts.
UC's in trouble
and we have no visual.
No visual.
[Engine starts]
Seven-Adam-15
moving in for rescue.
♪
I need eyes on the UC.
Nearly there.
Trying to get visual.
You got 10 seconds,
and then we're going in.
Start talking.
♪
[Groans]
[Gun cocks]
♪
Hold. Everyone hold.
Negative!
Officer rescue now!
I see her purse.
She's deployed the hold signal.
Stand by.
[Coughing]
Look, I don't know
who you think I am,
but I ain't her.
I am in a hurry.
Now, either we have a deal
or I can take my cash
somewhere else.
♪
All right, all right.
Take it easy.
What do you want?
[Coughing]
I need a .45, 15-round mag,
and it has to be a ghost.
♪
1,000 bucks. Untraceable.
Thanks.
[Thuds]
♪
Go get them.
Go! Go!
Officer: Police!
Officer ♪2: Get down
on the ground.
Don't move!
Juarez, you want to tell me
what's going on?
Yeah, well, I left word
for the, uh, Watch Commander
at Hollywood Division.
I'm still waiting to hear back.
Okay, you can 10-22
all that.
I'm more concerned
about you.
Okay, sir. I'm so sorry.
I'm usually more focused.
You trying
to reach someone?
My mom. She's barely left
the house in years.
She's a shut-in.
She lives alone.
Her power went off earlier,
and she's not
answering her phone.
I'm just worried.
Why didn't you say something?
She needs a welfare check.
Yeah, I wanted to,
but with the Command Post...
Hey, remember CHEAP?
C... Check in.
That is your job.
Come on.
I'll clear it with Grey.
♪
RJ is dead?
We found him this morning,
stuffed in a storage locker.
Oh, that's awful.
What happened?
We're not sure, but I understand
that he worked for you.
Yes. He was such a help.
I'm not so good at computers.
[Laughs]
He set up my online banking.
All those passwords
are just impossible to remember.
I don't know what
I would have done without him.
Have you checked
your accounts recently?
Oh, everything's
on autopay.
Okay. You need to do
a thorough accounting.
RJ was a thief and a grifter,
and he wipes out his targets.
No, no, th-that's not right.
He wouldn't do that.
I'll call her son.
He lives in New York.
We'll get this all sorted, okay?
Did you ever see RJ argue
with anyone?
Did he ever seem
scared at all?
No. He was fine
until he stopped coming in.
Okay.
Thank you for your time.
If you remember anything at all,
just give me a call.
♪
Sir, there's one thing
I haven't told you.
You know how I spent the day
doing administrative work?
What about it?
Well, my mom sort of thinks
that's what I do all day,
every day.
She doesn't know
I go on patrol.
So you want me
to lie for you?
Well, not lie, exactly.
Just focus on the small portion
of the truth
and then exaggerate it. No.
Celina.
Mama, I've been calling you.
You didn't pick up.
My phone died.
No power to charge it.
This is my boss,
Sergeant Bradford.
And this is my mom,
Karla Juarez.
Oh. [Speaks Spanish]
Okay, Mami,
I'm the police now.
You'll always be my baby.
God, it must be 100 degrees
in here.
[Sighs]
Reminds me of a sauna.
It's good for your skin.
Yeah, in 10-minute increments,
not all day.
You have birds?
Lorca y Neruda.
They're my muses.
I sell paintings of them online.
It's how I pay my bills.
Okay, Mama,
you can't stay here.
You got to come with us
to a cooling center.
What about the birds?
You can bring them.
I can't.
It's been years
since she's left the house.
It's dangerous out there.
I worry so.
And I told you,
you have nothing to worry about.
I'm safe at the station.
That's right. Taking calls
and gathering information.
Well, thank you for keeping
my baby safe.
Of course, ma'am.
Listen, I've got
an apex generator
in the back of the shop.
Let me bring it in here
and get the A/C up and running.
No, no, no, I don't want
to be a bother.
Oh, it's not for you.
It's for Lorca and Neruda.
I'm sure they could use
a little cooling off.
[Birds chirping]
Okay. For the birds.
Is he single?
This, my dear, is how garlic
shrimp scampi changed my life.
And this is how a brilliant man
won my heart with a generator.
[Chuckles]
I do feel a tiny bit guilty
being the only ones
with power.
And air conditioning.
I know. We must have gotten
40 calls today,
all from people
needing help.
It's bad out there.
It's only gonna get worse.
Well, here's
to a quiet evening.
Cheers.
[Knock on door]
Pardon me.
Oh.
Did you check your texts?
I didn't, but...
Uh, our power is out
and it is too hot
for Leah to sleep,
and we have some personal things
that are about to go bad.
No, please. Welcome.
You're welcome.
Come, come, come.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, aww.
Are you sure you don't mind?
Of course!
What do you guys need?
Your fridge.
Oh, yeah.
Stick that in right over there.
But not next to the creamer,
though. That would be bad.
[Chuckles] It happens.
We have shrimp scampi.
Do you guys want any?
He's allergic to shellfish.
I'm allergic to shellfish.
Can I make something else
for myself?
There's plenty in there.
Please help yourself.
[Doorbell rings]
Hey.
Sorry. We know it's late.
Can you believe
how hot it is out there?
Right, at this time
of night?
Whew. Oh, my God.
Air conditioning feels so good.
Hey.
The only air conditioning
we have is in the car.
Can I charge the car?
Yeah. I'll get you a cord.
Can I get you a glass of wine
first?
Yes. Yes, please. Ohh.
Hey, bud.
Daddy needs some wine.
Hey.
Lucy. Sure, why not?
Come on in.
Oh, you look surprised.
Wait, weren't you
on the group text?
No, no.
I turn off my phone when...
[Stammers] Wine?
Tequila. Double.
♪
I need it.
We have a big problem.
♪
I got it.
Hicks leaves Metro,
goes to IA.
Remington moves to Motors.
That means
Watson gets into SWAT.
Halsey comes over to Metro.
There's still a spot for Tim.
Remington's wife won't let her
on a motorcycle,
so that's a non-starter.
♪
Okay, um, Fujii retires, hm?
Halsey goes to Metro
and Madison goes to Robbery.
Hmm?
Primm will go to Vice?
No, they hate each other.
Okay.
Um, Jones goes to SWAT.
And Bob's your uncle.
Yes.
[Knock on door]
Oh, no.
What?
Well, the only way this works
is if Fujii retires,
and the only person
who can convince her
to do that is...
Smitty.
Yeah.
Hey, Tim.
This is unexpected.
What's your... What is the...
What's the...
What are you...
What's up?
Uh, I-I heard
you had power.
I was hoping
you had the game on.
Yes. Yes.
I mean, yes, we have power.
The game is... We can...
Come in. Come in.
But is that Lucy's car?
Uh, yes.
Come on in.
Hey, guys, look who it is.
It's a party.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Just enjoying the A/C.
You okay?
Yeah.
Couldn't be better.
♪
15 years. That's what you're
looking at for arms trafficking.
Wait, don't I have a Second
Amendment right to sell guns?
It's a right to bear arms,
not sell them.
Right.
You know,
I've done a lot of time.
Kind of done with
the whole prison thing.
Then give us something.
All right.
What about...
Oh, no, if I give him up,
he'll kill me.
We can protect you.
Not from this dude.
Oh, what about...
No, she owes me 12 large.
Wait. If someone owes me money
and they get arrested,
I'm out that money, right?
Probably.
Then definitely not her.
Oh, you're
a regular phone book.
I stay busy.
Oh. What about Kingston?
Prentiss Kingston?
The King of Fentanyl?
One of his lieutenants
buys from me.
Does that get me anything?
I think we could work
something out.
Sold.
Gotta love career criminals...
they know how to play the game.
Your gun dealer rolled?
Gave us
a major fentanyl distributor.
Wesley's working out
his plea deal now.
What's that?
Uh, I got the ME's report
on my dead body.
The cause of death was
a bilateral pulmonary embolism
caused by ingesting
metallic mercury.
He was poisoned.
Yeah, over a long period
of time.
It looks like he was suffering
from confusion,
mood swings, tremors.
♪
Beatrice's caretaker
had a tremor.
Maybe whoever targeted RJ
is also targeting her.
I don't know who any of
those people are.
No reason you should.
Awesome.
Great.
[Muffled] Chen.
Smitty.
[Normally] Want some?
Uh, no, I'm good.
But I...
I could use a favor.
A favor? Hmm.
That would mean you'd owe me.
Technically.
Lay it on me.
You went to the academy
with Lauren Fujii.
I did.
Well, she needs to retire,
and I need you
to talk her into it.
Hmm.
If Lauren Fujii retires,
Watson goes to Vice,
Primm goes to Motors,
Hicks could move over,
and Tim takes
the open spot in Metro.
♪
How...?
I'm smarter
than people think.
Uh...
Yeah.
Smitty, you got to do it.
I mean, if not for me,
think of Tim.
Tempting, but Fujii and I had
a bit of a falling out.
Oh. I'm afraid to ask why.
Let's just say it had something
to do with salsa night.
Okay, okay. Well, um...
here's how you can make up
for whatever you did.
Her family lives
in San Jose,
and A-I Meta Network is looking
to hire a new head of security.
They're paying
400 grand a year.
You would be her hero
if you brought her this job.
400 G's?
Maybe I'll take it.
Oh. You would be great,
but that doesn't really
help me out.
And also, Smitty,
it's a lot of work.
Pass.
Yeah.
But if I talk to her,
you got to do me a favor.
Mm-hmm. Nothing weird.
Nothing weird.
♪
Promise.
Deal.
Thank you.
♪ Cop cuties, cute and on duty,
navy blue booties ♪
♪ Go ahead and lock me up
♪ Arrest me, but make it sexy
What are we singing?
Oh, nothing, sir.
Listen, I know
I screwed up yesterday.
I appreciate
the second chance.
Celina, these evaluations
aren't meant to punish you.
They're meant to make you better
at the thing you're worst at.
Do you know
what that is?
Asking for help.
That's right.
Tim told me about your mom.
Look, you've endured
unimaginable loss,
and you've carried
that weight alone.
But now you have a new family
of brothers and sisters.
Remember that.
Copy that, sir.
Next time
I need help with something,
I won't keep it to myself.
Very good.
Now, today is a do-over.
Today, every call that comes up,
you're in charge.
And you're driving.
Did you find out
what happened to RJ?
We are making progress.
Tell me, did you work
at Mercy of Saint Vincent's
from '96 to '05?
Oh, that's how I injured my hip.
I had to retire.
Okay. Did you know
that nine patients died there
from heavy metal poisoning?
Oh, I-I wasn't aware of that.
Mercury was found
in all nine victims,
all of which
were your patients.
Were they? Um...
That was such a long time ago.
I don't really remember.
Mercury poisoning is also
what killed RJ Cash.
And your caretaker, Sharona,
is at the hospital.
I noticed that her hand
had a tremor,
which is also a symptom
of mercury poisoning.
The doctors are looking
at her right now.
Thank you.
For what?
For catching me.
I-I don't know
why I keep doing this.
S-Sometimes it's like
I'm watching somebody else.
Thank you for stopping me.
♪
Hey, what's going on?
Lopez's gun dealer says
a huge amount of fentanyl
moves through that house.
What if we get exposed?
Incidental contact won't
give you an overdose,
especially if it's already been
cut or pressed into pills.
But what if it
hasn't been cut yet?
Pure fentanyl?
Mm-hmm.
Two micrograms kills you
if inhaled.
That's less than half
a grain of rice.
Okay, Juarez.
You're senior officer on scene.
What do we do?
Well, I mean,
we call a sergeant.
Great. You're here. Proceed.
That's usually correct.
But very soon, you might be
most senior officer on scene.
So what do we do?
♪
I mean, you surround
and call out.
You set up a perimeter,
call into the house,
and you get them to surrender.
Is that right?
I'm not saying.
Make a decision.
♪
Control, Seven-Adam-15.
Can I get six additional units
to 956 Oakwood Court?
Code-3.
Dispatch:
Six units en route, Code-3.
Good work.
Now what?
Recon.
See what we're dealing with.
Let's go.
Alright.
Come on with me.
[Muffled heavy metal music
playing]
♪
[Dramatic music plays]
There's a kid in there.
They've got a 5-year-old
little girl in there
while they're manufacturing.
Yeah, we found empty
cardboard boxes in the trash
which used to be packed
with gelatin capsules.
That means they are
cutting pure fentanyl
and filling the capsules
in the house.
We need to get that kid
out of there.
Should we try a diversion?
See if we can try the old
"Sorry Sucker" gag.
It's a classic.
You smash, I grab?
Copy that.
Does that mean I'm not
in charge anymore?
Only in spirit.
Let's go.
You're with me.
[Thud]
[Car alarm blaring]
Whoops.
[Engine shuts off]
[Car alarm continues]
[House door opens]
[Car alarm chirps, stops]
You did not
just hit my car!
Yeah, I did.
Sorry about that.
Looks like minor damage, though.
Aaron: Don't worry. The city
will pay for all the damages
and rental car inconvenience.
Yeah. I'll just need to get
some of your information
for the accident report.
Can I get your name?
[Blenders whirring]
[Video game music plays]
Hi. My name is Celina.
What's yours?
Listen, I'm sorry to stop
the game,
but there's an emergency
and we need to go outside.
Do you want to come with me?
♪
[Screaming]
[Blenders stop]
[Screaming continues]
Hey, show me your hands.
Put your hands
behind your head.
[Spoon clangs]
♪
Baby girl!
[Radio crackles]
♪
[Men grunting]
[Gunshots]
[Girl screaming]
♪
[Blenders whirring]
Help! I got the kid!
Help her!
♪
[Grunts]
[Handcuffs click]
♪
Celina's still in there.
Watch out.
♪
[Muffled] Celina!
Celina!
♪
Officer Juarez is down.
She's not breathing.
Let's go.
I need Narcan!
[Siren wailing]
Come on.
Easy, easy.
Come on. Come on.
[Sirens wailing,
helicopters whirring]
[Narcan sprays]
Come on, Celina.
Celina.
Celina, come on, wake up.
Come on back.
Celina! Hit her again.
Come on.
Come back to us, Celina.
[Narcan sprays]
Celina?
Celina, can you hear me?
Come on, Celina.
[Sirens wailing]
Hey.
My hand.
What'd you say?
You're crushing my hand.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Over here, guys.
Come on.
Good work in there.
Mm-hmm.
♪
[Knocks]
Hey.
Hey. How you feeling?
And don't just say fine.
I-I'm still pretty shaken.
But, um, thank you
for saving me.
Like I said, family.
Yeah. What you did
took guts today.
Yeah, saving a kid
like that.
I mean, there's got to be
a medal in there somewhere.
There definitely is.
I'll get on the paperwork.
Or maybe it would be better
coming from her FTO.
I'm happy to do it.
I'm curious, though, would that
qualify me for a medal as well?
No.
Yeah, that's not
what's important right now.
But having a training officer's
very first rookie
qualify for a medal
in her first few months
on the job would put me
in some pretty rarefied air.
But again,
not important right now.
♪ When you first met me
moons ago ♪
Hey.
I just heard Lauren Fujii
is retiring.
Really?
That's surprising.
Yeah, apparently she got
some great gig up in San Jose
paying her a ton of money.
Wow. Good for her.
With her out,
Watson moves over to Vice,
Primm winds up in Motors,
and Hicks takes his place.
I don't know how you
keep all that straight.
Don't you get it?
It means there's an opening
in Metro.
Well, at least there was.
Lieutenant Pine just called me
15 minutes ago,
and I'm going over.
That's great. Congratulations.
Thanks. Grey gave me
a rock-star review.
Yeah, well, he should.
You're amazing.
I'm excited.
[Laughs]
I'm excited. Let's go to dinner
tonight and celebrate.
T... Tonight, I can't.
I'm sorry.
I really, really want to,
but I can't.
I promised my friend
that I would help him
with something.
Tomorrow night.
Hm?
Okay.
Sure.
Do you need any help?
No, no. It's something
I got to do on my own.
But tomorrow night,
it is a date.
We are gonna celebrate you.
Congratulations.
They're really lucky
to have you.
Thank you.
[Laughs] Okay.
I got to go.
Good job.
♪ Who did I think you were?
♪ When we danced
in the setting sun? ♪
♪ When you said
that you'd love me forever ♪
♪ And I was getting ready
to run ♪
[FaceTime ringing]
♪ Ready to run
Hola, mija.
How was your day?
Oh, you know, just a lot of
filing, a lot of paperwork.
Almost done, though,
so I'll be heading out soon.
I always thought police work
was so dangerous.
It is.
I got a paper cut today.
Ay, mija, you need
to be careful.
[Laughing]
I know. I am. I promise.
♪
I'll admit,
I've been lax about cleaning it.
How lax?
Uh, either Clinton or Bush
was the president.
W... Which Bush?
♪
It's been a while.
A deal's a deal.
I'm happy it worked out
for Tim.
Yeah.
Oh! Hey. Whoa!
Hey, where are you going?
Aren't you gonna help?
And miss
Monday Night Football?
♪ Who did I think I was?
It's not Monday.
[Baby babbles]
Yeah, yummy.
♪ And perhaps
I'll feel like this forever ♪
Hey. Where's your laundry?
Leah had a little accident.
♪ Ready to run
Thanks.
Lopez: [Laughs]
How about some noodles?
♪
The Four Seasons
has power.
Oh, yes.
[Respirator hissing]
♪ Oh, it's already begun
♪ I'm getting ready,
ready to run ♪
♪ Oh, it's already begun
♪ I'm getting ready,
ready to run ♪
Oh, dear God.
- Captions by VITAC...
♪