[traffic honking]
[dog barking]
I'm just saying,
I never would've thought
to cast that spell.
Well, what can I say?
I'm a natural-born warlock.
And look, if you tell
anybody I said that,
I'm gonna put a hex
on your wisdom save, okay?
Man, is it even worth
trying to get some sleep
before our shift?
No, look, trust
a professional party kid
like me, it's better
to just tough it out
than try to get
a lame hour and a half.
[cat screeching]
- Whoa. What was that?
What was what?
[silence]
Look, I love wandering around
in dark alleys
at 4:00 in the morning
like anyone else,
but if you go looking
for trouble, you find it.
Okay?
[screeching]
[person screams]
I heard that.
- Should we call it in?
And, what, get laughed at
when we find out
it's just a cat in heat?
No thank you.
[sighs deeply]
Mm.
[barking]
[breathes deeply]
[screech]
[clang]
You go right over here.
[tense music]
♪
Psst.
Hey.
[grunts]
Aaron?
Aaron!
Yeah.
Whoa!
Guys, put your gun down.
We are police officers.
You do not wanna do this.
Celina, look out!
[blow lands]
[high-pitched ringing]
[footsteps]
Remember this:
Covered face, shroud of shame.
No escape when you're to blame.
Cry me a river,
back to the start.
Dog deliver a live part.
[dialing phone]
Officer down.
Officer...
[breathing heavily]
Aaron.
[dramatic music]
Aaron. Aaron.
You should be asleep.
Well, I don't sleep so well
when you work the late shift.
Right back at ya.
But I did need to turn
the corner
on Simone's garage conversion,
so it's for the best.
[radio clicks]
- Engine-53,
I have a priority dispatch
to a GSW.
Male victim, not conscious,
not breathing.
Off-duty officer involved.
I'll show you en route.
- John, I gotta go.
A cop's been shot.
Do you know who?
What division?
No. But I'll call when I can.
[siren wailing]
[engine turns over]
[intense music]
♪
[phone buzzing]
[groans]
[sighs]
Hello?
[sirens wailing]
What happened?
[tires screech]
♪
Over here!
Celina!
What happened?
They shot him.
I couldn't stop it.
It's not your fault,
it's not your fault.
GSW to the left shoulder.
I can't find an exit wound.
Tell St. Stephens
we have a level one GSW.
Large amount of blood loss
on the scene.
Prep a massive transfusion protocol.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't move. Don't move.
Don't move.
Did you lose consciousness?
- No, I don't think so.
Wait. Maybe I did.
Any numbness? Tingling?
No, I'm fine.
Just a little dizzy.
Help him.
- We will, but I need you
to stay still.
[sirens wailing]
Set a perimeter
to two blocks out.
I'm setting a command post
at Wilton and Third.
I need six additional units
for canvassing.
Notify crime scene
and the lieutenant.
Sir, we got ambushed.
Three men in these crazy masks.
I don't know
where they went, or...
or how long ago, but we need
to secure the scene,
look for the shell casing...
it must've ejected
near the north wall.
Celina, we're on it.
Harper's gonna meet you
at the hospital
to take a statement, all right?
Hey, how bad?
It's bad.
[sirens blaring]
Hey, I heard it was Thorsen.
GSW to the back.
Celina says they were ambushed.
Three men with masks.
I'll coordinate
with the canvassing officers.
Run everyone
in a 5-mile radius
who's on parole, probation,
for assaulting a cop.
Yes, sir.
[elevator dings]
- I can walk by myself.
- I know.
- Did you set the ADT alarm?
- Yes.
Uh, hi, my wife's water
just broke.
Doctor Schneider
told us to come in.
Gunshot to
the posterior left shoulder.
He has a pulse, but he's
critically hypertensive.
[dramatic music]
Blood pressure 80/54.
We gave him two large bore IVs.
- GCS?
- Seven.
Oh, no.
♪
One, two, three.
I need trauma labs.
Hang a unit of blood.
O neg.
[monitor beeping rapidly]
♪
Patient's not protecting
his airway.
Prepare to intubate.
I want a 7.5 tube, 23 to the T.
Start 20 Etomidate, 80 of roc.
♪
Positive breath sounds,
both sides.
♪
Pulse is weak and thready.
I need to see
what we're dealing with.
The ultrasound unit is ready.
[monitor beeping]
[elevator dings]
Hey, I'm looking for...
thank you.
Hey, what happened?
They rushed Aaron to the ER.
- What about Celina?
- I don't know.
I didn't know she was hurt.
My water broke.
Let me up!
I got work to do!
- Hey, hey.
- Let me up!
Okay, I'm fine.
- Hey, hey, relax, relax.
Hey, it's me, okay. Relax.
They're just gonna
check you out and make sure
you're not hurt, okay?
He told me something,
the guys in the masks
they said I...I needed
to remember.
All right,
he's gonna check you out
and make sure you're all right.
- No, no, no!
I need to tell you now.
What if I forget?
All right, all right.
Stop, stop, stop!
Just give a second,
just give a second.
All right,
this is officer John Nolan,
badge number 25253,
taking a statement
from Officer Juarez
on the assault on her
and Officer Thorsen.
Go.
Remember this:
Covered face.
- Covered face.
Shroud of shame.
- Shroud of shame.
No escape when you're
to blame.
No escape
when you're to blame.
♪
Celina, look out!
[gunshot]
Cry me a river.
C-cry me a river.
Back to the start.
Dog deliver a live part.
Dog deliver
a live part.
Dog deliver a what?
A live part.
I don't know what it means.
That's what he said, I swear.
- Okay, no. It's okay.
You got...you did great.
I got it.
I'm sorry,
but we need to treat her.
She could have
a fractured skull, brain bleed.
Put a rush on that CAT scan.
[somber music]
♪
[sound muffled]
- How is he?
[sound clears]
John.
Uh, I don't...I don't know.
It...it looks bad.
Why isn't he in surgery yet?
They have to do
a FAST exam first.
[stammers] Do we know
if they were targeted?
I don't know
if we know anything yet,
but she had me record a riddle
that they told her
during the assault.
- A riddle?
- I know. It sounds crazy,
and with her head injury, I'm
not even sure she got it right,
but she was adamant.
- [groans]
- We have to get you upstairs.
It's fine,
it's just early labor.
Angela.
[breathes shakily]
Okay.
Excuse me.
But...but send me the riddle.
If this baby's
anything like Jack,
it'll be a while
before she makes an appearance.
Wesley and I can fill the time
before she comes.
- All right. Good luck.
- Thanks.
[pained groan]
both: Hey.
[sighs] Vance is the best
trauma surgeon around.
Aaron's in good hands.
- Okay.
So, what...what do we do next?
Well, Celina's your rookie.
No one will hold it against you
if you stay by her side.
Trust me, I will never
hear the end of this
if I don't get straight
to figuring out who did it.
She said they were
wearing masks.
- What kind?
- The terrifying kind.
I'll get a sketch artist
to come in and sit with her,
soon as the doctors are done.
[intense music]
♪
Right upper quadrant, clear.
Pericardial sac, clear.
Pelvic area, clear.
Left upper quadrant...
I'm seeing free fluid.
Most likely the spleen.
[monitor beeping]
- BP is plummeting!
I can start more blood.
- No time.
We gotta get him to the OR.
[beeping continues]
♪
Prepare for
exploratory laparotomy
and probable splenectomy.
Stay on top of the blood.
Estimated blood loss,
at least 500.
Start Levophed.
[intense music]
♪
All right, listen up.
All time off has been canceled.
All OT approved.
Catching these suspects is
the department's top priority.
All right,
this is what we know so far:
at approximately 4:00 a.m.,
Officers Thorsen and Juarez
were attacked.
Officer Thorsen was shot
and is currently in surgery.
A blood drive has been
set up at the hospital.
If you can donate, please do
at the end of shift.
Officer Juarez
sustained a concussion,
but has been providing
Nolan and I
with the details
of the assault,
including sketches of the masks
the assailants wore.
Those are not store-bought
Halloween masks.
No, they are not.
So, our first job is to try
and identify the manufacturer
and then hopefully track them
back to our assailants.
- I'd like to help with that.
- Sold.
We are currently pulling
cell tower records
for that area.
There shouldn't be a lot
of activity
at that hour in the morning.
Intel is also combing
through social media
to see if anyone
has posted video
of the attack or the aftermath.
Yeah, and I've also
compiled a list of everybody
that's done time for
assaulting a police officer,
but so far,
nobody's jumping out.
Most of those guys were drunk
and sucker punched a cop.
It's something else.
A lot of this still
doesn't make sense.
So we need a list
of top-priority questions
to answer.
I mean, it seems obvious
that they were targeted.
Why else the masks
and the riddle?
So was this specifically
about Aaron and Celina?
Yeah, and why not
just kill Aaron?
[officers clamoring]
Look, from the description
that Celina gave
of the shooting,
they easily could've
just shot him in the head.
All I am asking is if there was
a reason they did not.
Fair enough. What else?
Thorsen's not just a cop,
he's a public figure.
So is it related
to his family?
Right.
Or were they sent by Elijah?
Even behind bars,
he still has power.
You'd think he'd target
Angela first, but you're right.
We should look into it.
Anything else?
Are they done?
[dramatic music]
♪
- [grunts]
- Uh...
I'm not sure
you should be doing that.
It's fine.
They have computers.
[pained grunt]
- Ah, you know what?
How about I take over, okay?
I'll take that.
- [exhales]
Oh. Okay.
[breathes deeply]
[knock at door]
Hi.
Is this the puzzle palace?
- Mm-hmm.
- Luna, how are you?
A little shaken,
but I'm not the one
who's about to push out a kid.
Not sure how "about to" I am.
My cervix refuses to dilate.
I was always told
the second birth was easier.
They just tell you that
so that
you'll go through it again.
Is that the riddle?
It is.
Please tell me you majored
in riddles in college.
Not quite, but I do
three crossword puzzles a day,
so I am here to offer my brain.
We're happy to have you. Okay.
"Covered face, shroud of shame.
"No escape when you're
to blame.
"Cry me a river,
back to the start.
Dog deliver a live part."
Well, the first line
seems pretty obvious,
given that they were
wearing masks.
"Covered face,
shroud of shame."
The mask hides someone's shame.
They're guilty,
and they know it.
But is that too easy?
What if the covered face
is figurative
and it's about the victim,
not the attacker?
"No escape
when you're to blame."
When you're to blame,
not when I'm to blame.
So this person thinks that
Aaron and Celina are guilty.
"Cry me a river."
Don't make excuses.
"Back to the start."
Where did this all begin?
With an arrest?
If it's someone that
Aaron and Celina arrested,
that would make sense.
These attackers
are blaming them
for ruining their lives.
I'm sure Grey has someone
pulling their unit histories.
Have you heard
any updates on Aaron?
Just that he's in surgery.
[monitor beeping]
- BP and O2 are falling.
We got a bleeder somewhere.
The lungs are filling
with fluid.
Prepare a chest tube.
[intense music]
♪
[machine suctioning]
[beeping stops]
Okay.
On to the next problem.
[door opens]
[knocks] Hey!
Can we come in?
- Of course.
- We wanted you to have
a calming place of recovery,
so...
quartz for healing,
obsidian for protection.
Thank you. You didn't have
to go through all this trouble.
It's Los Angeles.
We got this
in the hospital gift shop.
And if you're up
for a challenge,
your favorite meatball sub.
[gasps] I am starving.
I could eat two of those.
I knew it.
I bought you two.
Bailey called me crazy.
I stand corrected.
Um, any updates on the case?
Well, we have a long list
of people that didn't do it.
Then that's progress,
I guess.
Can I, um...
can I ask you something?
Of course. Yeah.
I'm gonna go see if there's
any updates on Aaron.
Thanks.
What's on your mind?
I should've called it in.
The second we heard something,
I shouldn't have left his side.
Look, if there's something
you can learn from this...
a lesson you take...great.
But this doesn't sound
like a rational assessment.
This sounds like
blaming yourself.
I am. How can I not?
You were ambushed,
and you were outnumbered,
and despite a nasty knock
to the head,
you managed to call for help
and administer first aid
before EMTs could arrive.
Celina, because of you,
Aaron has a chance.
So no more blaming yourself.
- [sighs]
And if you ask me
very nicely,
I could help you
with these subs.
Get your own.
Worth a shot.
Great news.
Aaron's out of surgery.
I'll go check.
I'll let you know.
[sighs]
We ran into a few hiccups,
but the surgery went
as well as can be expected.
He's gonna be okay?
Well, I can't promise that.
The next 12 hours
are gonna be critical.
Any word on his parents?
They're on a plane
flying back from Dubai.
Happy to update them
once they arrive.
Thank you, Doctor.
[elevator dings]
Hey. We heard the good news
about Aaron.
Unfortunately, none of our CIs
have heard anything
about a gang targeting cops.
And we're in the same boat
with the masks.
They're clearly custom,
but we've struck out
with every manufacturer
in Southern California.
- What about Elijah?
- They've been going over
communication in and out
of prison,
and nothing indicates
that he's playing at anything.
Anything positive
on the riddle front?
Not yet. The front half
is deceptively simple,
but he back half
is a head-scratcher.
Angela and Wesley
are deep into it.
I hate to say it, but this
is not gonna break tonight.
Go home, get some sleep.
Night shift will run
whatever leads come in.
The rest of us will have
clearer heads
in the morning, I hope.
- You're gonna stay with Aaron?
- Yeah.
And I'll keep an eye
on Celina too.
Thank you.
It's gonna be all right.
It's gotta be.
I can't lose another.
I know.
Why don't we get
some dinner in you?
Gonna be a long night.
[Creepoid's "Horse Heaven"]
Yeah.
♪ It's gonna
♪ Kill you all
♪
♪ Coming up on the horizon
- Come here.
- Yeah. [sniffles]
♪ The sun is bleeding out
♪
♪ Meet me at the meadow
♪ When the petals
♪ Are falling off
Remember when we entered
the Caverns of Depravity
and faced off against Glabrezu?
Baldr-Ray kept calling it
the Labradoodle.
Of course that ugly
four-armed hellspawn
went straight
for the spellcaster.
40-some points of damage.
You were down zero.
Your first death save failed,
and the second,
and I thought it was over.
But then, on your third roll,
a natural 20.
And before it even knew
what was happening,
you thunderwaved that
Labradoodle into lava flow.
That's what we need now, Aaron, okay?
I need you to roll
a natural 20
and destroy that Labradoodle.
Well, I...I guess
in this analogy,
the Labradoodle is...is death,
but you know what I mean.
Come on, Aaron.
♪
[dog barking]
Okay, so I know
we usually watch TV and relax,
but how would you feel
about perusing the Internet
for creepy masks?
Ooh, dream date.
I'll get my laptop.
- [laughs]
Excellent.
[dark music]
♪
Hey, um...
Join me in the bedroom
just for a second.
Why?
Because one of them is right
outside the kitchen door,
and I want you to call 911.
- Okay.
- You good?
Yep.
[dialing phone]
[line trilling]
- I'll set the table.
911. What's your emergency?
Officer in trouble.
2273 Lakeview Drive.
This is connected
to the shooting this morning.
Show yourself. Now.
Hands in the air.
♪
Send police and ambulance.
[music intensifies]
Bailey!
[both grunting]
♪
[struggling efforts]
[blow lands]
[pained groan]
[grunting]
[yelps]
[groans]
Come on.
[both grunting]
[blow lands]
[groaning]
[knife clatters]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[grunting]
[screams]
[groaning]
♪
It's over.
The cavalry's coming.
Give it up.
♪
Do it again.
Final warning, dumbass.
Give it up!
[sirens wailing]
Hey!
[grunts]
[sirens, tires screeching]
[pounding on door]
Officer Nolan,
can you hear me?
We're Code 4.
Shooter is down in the kitchen.
[sirens wailing]
Hey. You okay? You hurt?
No, I'm just
a little banged up.
- You?
- No, same, same.
[dramatic music]
We have to warn everybody.
If they came after us, they
could be going after them too.
Whew.
Leah's finally asleep.
I swear,
that kid is part nocturnal.
I don't think that's a thing.
Then you explain it. Here.
No. I gotta stay sharp.
How can I help?
You can't. I can't even seem
to help right now.
These guys just attacked
two of our police officers
and then just disappeared
without a trace.
They even collected their
shell casings on the way out.
[phone ringing]
Hey.
[dramatic music]
We have to go! Now!
What? What? What?
♪
Leah! Grab my gun.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
No.
Nyla! Gun!
- She's gone.
- What? What do you mean?
[intense music]
♪
Where is she?
[car engine turns over]
Oh, God.
[tires screech]
Call...call 911.
Silver sedan.
License plate says L or I, or...
[grunts]
I can't see it.
[groans]
Get that...
I can't tell what it's...
[baby cries]
[gasps]
Here, here!
Hi! Hi!
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
Oh.
Hey, sweetie.
[sobbing]
[sirens wailing]
- Who hired you?
- I don't know
what you're talking about.
I'm just a tourist here to see
the glamour of Hollywood.
- And kill cops.
- You're pretty smug
for someone who just got shot
and stabbed.
It's not the first time.
No, we know.
We ran your prints.
Hamza Young.
Professional mercenary
wanted in connection with
three foreign assassinations.
You don't get out of bed
for less than 20K a day.
- Who hired you?
- If you read my file,
you know I'm not a guy
who talks to cops.
So let the medics through.
I need a hospital
and a lawyer.
All right, listen.
We're in DEFCON 1 territory.
We have to assume all hitters
have the same skill level,
which means we need to isolate
everyone we care about.
That is gonna take
a lot of space...
a whole floor of a hotel.
Aaron's parents just rented
one at the Peninsula.
I tried to talk 'em out of it,
but they texted back,
"It's only money."
All right. We'll need
heavy security in the lobby
and a SWAT team guarding
every elevator or stairs.
We should move everyone covertly,
make the homes seem occupied,
see if we can draw them
into another attack.
Two teams on each home
should be enough.
How many officers is that?
On top of the ones
at St. Stephens?
45, 50.
I'm pulling everyone I can.
How are Harper, James,
and the baby?
Shaken up. They took Leah
to get checked up
at the hospital, which is
where you guys are going
to get cleaned up.
- Fine, but after that,
I'm getting right back
into the game.
It's time we start
playing offense.
[pained groan]
Celina must've
heard the last line wrong.
Maybe it's
"dog deliver a live heart."
Okay,
and what would that mean?
- No idea.
- [groans]
Okay, uh, bog deliver,
fog deliver...
Why are we taking this
at face value?
We've already established
that the first few lines
are deceptive.
What if the last line isn't
what it seems to be, either?
Well, dog backwards is god.
Live part backwards...
evil trap.
That's it.
Semordnilap.
[playful music]
Do not have a stroke
on me now.
"Palindromes" backwards.
And if the word is backwards,
maybe the sentence is, too.
"Trap evil a reviled god."
[sighs]
Yeah, that's not better.
Uh, what's this?
Work.
We actually put
important things on that board.
Anyway, it's time.
We're at 24 hours.
Time to have this baby.
- Great.
Uh, one minute.
"Trap evil a reviled god."
It's a line from a play.
- Huh.
- Okay, I do think giving birth
should be the priority
right now.
Totally, I just need
to make a quick detour.
Detour?
Do I look like a taxi service?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- Okay. Come on, honey.
So according to the feds,
Hamza flew in two weeks ago
from Poland,
then disappeared off the grid.
How's Leah?
She's fine, thank God.
James is taking her
to the hotel.
Listen, to piggyback off
your question from yesterday
as to why they didn't
kill Aaron...
Why didn't they take
your daughter?
Why grab her
just to leave her behind?
I don't know.
I've been asking myself
the same question.
It's almost as if their goal
is to torture you
as much as possible.
Nyla.
We solved the riddle.
It pointed us to an obscure
one-act play,
Look at their costumes.
I airdropped it to you.
Okay, we talked to Harper.
Now we really need to go.
Yeah, we got this.
Go have that baby.
A play?
[dark music]
We have a suspect.
The masks our attackers
are wearing
were for a play back in 1996.
It ran for three weeks
before closing.
The theater company sold
all of their props and costumes
to Second Life Theater Supply.
Where they sat on a shelf
until 15 of them were purchased
last week by Roy Gracco.
Gracco is a two-time felon
with a history of violence.
What's his beef
with Mid-Wilshire?
We don't know yet,
but his first felony conviction
came from an arrest
that we made,
but the arresting officers
have since transferred.
I still don't understand
the point of this riddle.
Why are they pointing us
down this path,
and should we follow?
- We have no choice.
But we're showing up
with overwhelming force
in case there's another ambush.
Everyone stay on your toes.
Let's go.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Alpha ready.
- Bravo ready.
Three, two, one.
♪
Clear.
Front room clear.
It's freezing in here.
[tense music]
Clear.
Drop the gun!
Drop it!
On your front side!
I think he's dead.
♪
Control, suspect is down...
not conscious, not breathing,
cool to the touch.
He's 10-5-5.
Must've cranked the AC
to slow the decomp.
It's Gracco.
But why?
[intense music]
♪
It's a trap.
Abort! Abort! Abort!
- Fall back!
- Everyone out!
- Let's go!
- Let's go, let's go!
- Get out now!
- Go, go, go, go, go.
Control, I need the bomb squad
to the target house
for a full sweep.
Send the M.E. and TID out here,
standing by
for a priority search
once the house is clear.
I don't understand.
Was Gracco in charge
of this crew or not?
M.E. puts Gracco's
time of death
before Aaron and Celina
were ambushed.
So the riddle lead us
to Gracco's house
so we could be
blown to kingdom come.
Are we any closer
to catching this guy?
'Cause it's starting
to feel like
we're not getting anywhere.
All we've done since Aaron
has been shot
is follow the clues
they wanted us to have.
TID is processing the house.
These guys are pros.
We're not gonna find anything.
We should move on.
- What? No.
Not yet.
Look, if Gracco is a patsy,
then we should be asking
why him?
He's a felon with a history
in Mid-Wilshire.
Yeah, sure, but there are
hundreds of guys like that,
so why Gracco?
Did they pull his name
out of a database,
or is there
some kind of a connection?
You think it's personal?
I mean, look, if...
if I was gonna go
to the extreme
of targeting police officers,
why not take out some of
my enemies along the way?
Costs us nothing
to run with that.
Check Gracco's
known associates,
family, coworkers,
anyone he did time with
that might hold a grudge.
Run them against people
that we arrested.
And say a prayer
while you're at it.
[phone rings]
We can use a little
divine intervention right now.
It's Wesley.
What's wrong?
- Uh, nothing.
Angela had the baby.
It's a girl.
- Hey!
- Ooh!
- [laughs]
That is some much-needed
good news.
Sending our love.
- Hi!
- Hey!
Did you catch
the bad guys yet?
Not yet, but we're on it.
You just focus on you
and that little angel.
Hey, um, what about Aaron?
He's still in a coma.
Come on, Aaron.
You can't let
that Labradoodle push you
into the Sea of Sorrow.
You have to rally.
Help me find
the Staff of Healing.
We have a list.
These seven people
have a troubled history
with both Gracco and one of us.
The top four
are the most hardcore...
Bill Gyst, Demarcus Hahn,
Keegan Ray, and Mariela Cruz...
all of them violent felons
we've arrested
in the last three years.
Bradford, I want Metro
knocking on their doors.
Even if they're not
behind the attacks on us,
they like to fight.
- All right.
I'll get Lieutenant Pine moving
on setting up the raids.
What about the other three?
Non-violent offenders
who did time with Gracco...
Donald Weathers, Luke Moran,
and K.D. Howard.
Nolan, Harper,
you check out Weathers.
- I'll take Moran.
- You're not going by yourself.
I'll go with her.
Pine's got every Metro officer
in the city mobilized.
She can spare me.
- All right.
I'll have Jan and Rodriguez
visit Howard.
But everyone, stay sharp.
If you even think
you see something off,
call for backup.
Let's go.
You should be out
kicking doors with Metro.
I'm good.
I don't need you
protecting me.
I know.
So clearly what you're saying
is you need me protecting you.
- Clearly.
- [laughs]
You know me so well.
I'm happy it's you at my six.
Back at you.
Police. Open up.
Luke Moran,
we need to talk to you.
- What do you wanna do?
- I wanna kick it in
and see if he's in there,
but we need a warrant for that,
and we're not gonna get it
without probable cause.
[clatter]
[clattering continues]
[tense music]
♪
[footsteps approaching]
- Stop right there!
- Adam-100, we got a crowd
coming towards us,
multiple armed suspects.
We need help right now.
- Adam-100 issued a help call
at 52101 Santa Rosa...
- Hey, stop moving!
- Drop your weapons!
Drop the weapons!
Go, go, go!
[Jane's Addiction's
"Mountain Song"]
♪ Oh
♪
Go. Up, up, up!
I'll hold 'em off.
What? No.
We have the higher ground.
We stand a chance,
but only together.
♪
[gunfire]
Okay.
We hurt as many as we can
retreat up the stairs.
Okay, but they're gonna
expect us to push.
Let's go the other way.
- Pull not push...copy that.
- Yeah.
♪ Comin' down the mountain
[screams]
♪
♪ One of many children
[all grunting]
♪ Everybody held
their own opinion ♪
♪ Everybody held their own
opinion ♪
♪ Holdin' it back
it hurts so bad ♪
♪ Jumping out of my flesh
and I said ♪
♪
[screams]
[siren wailing]
♪
♪ Cash in now, honey
♪ Cash in now
♪ Cash in now, baby
[siren wailing]
♪
Holy...
Go, I'll try and
even the odds from here.
♪ Cash in, Miss Smith now
♪ Cash in now, baby
♪ Oh, oh, oh
♪ Oh, oh
♪
[gunfire continues]
[siren wailing]
I'm out of ammo!
♪
♪ I was comin' down
the mountain ♪
♪
♪ I met a child, man,
she had pin eyes ♪
♪
[grunting]
♪ We had the same opinion
Ahh!
[grunts]
♪ Jumpin' out of my flesh
and I said ♪
[gunshot]
- [grunts]
♪ You better cash in
[grunts]
♪
- Whoa, whoa!
- Ah, oh, go, go!
♪
[lock clicks]
7-Adam-15, I have Bradford
and Chen secured upstairs.
♪
[sirens wailing]
- Freeze! Don't move!
[indistinct shouting]
[tense music]
Control, I've got
two injured officers
and multiple suspects injured
by blunt force trauma and GSWs.
- Don't move!
- At least 12 for transport.
This is a mass-casualty event.
♪
All units, I have eyes
on Aaron and Celina's attacker.
Black pants, brown jacket,
and a mask.
Just ducked in a doorway
north end of the alleyway.
♪
Airship-1,
inbound from the east.
Airship-2,
inbound from the south.
[phone line trilling]
Talk to me.
I screwed up.
They're on me.
Hey, you knew it would
come to this.
I know.
I just wish we hurt them more
for all they took from me.
Trust me,
you hurt them a lot.
I couldn't have done
any of it without you.
Oh, please.
I saw a wrong that
needed to be righted.
And hopefully, it's given you
a bit of dignity.
It has.
Thank you.
[footsteps approaching]
I've gotta go.
Lincoln-200, I'm in the
basement looking for suspect.
[radio chirps]
[radio chatter]
Just us.
[sighs]
You should be
on your way to the hospital.
We'll go after.
[intense music]
♪
[gunshots firing]
[breathing frantically]
[panting]
- You're trapped, Luke!
- That's close enough!
I must say, the list
of possible masterminds...
you were at the bottom.
Doesn't surprise me at all.
I don't get it.
You did 90 days
for elder abuse.
How'd you end up here?
Because that 90 days
destroyed me!
I was beaten,
forced to humiliate myself
to survive.
My mom died
while I was in there.
I lost my job, my home.
Everything.
I was just a case to you.
But you...
you were my apocalypse.
Well, it's over now.
Drop your gun and step out,
and keep your hands
where we can see 'em.
No.
[somber choral music]
I'm not goin' back.
♪
[gunfire]
[beeping]
What's happening?
We have a code blue,
room ten.
Code blue, room ten.
Aaron.
It just doesn't add up.
[sirens wailing]
[laughs]
Oh, look at 'em go.
Hot damn,
that is money well spent.
I mean, Luke had motivation
for days,
but how the hell
does a guy like that
afford to hire
a dozen mercenaries?
Weaponizing Luke Moran
against the LAPD
has driven every cop in the
city away from our target.
And by the time they realize
the damage we've done,
we'll be long gone.
♪
[dramatic music]
Damn it.