Previously on "The Rookie"...
I'm not
a kid anymore, Dad.
I'm going to college
in a few months.
Are you gonna shadow me
across campus?
Don't think I haven't
considered it.
Actually,
I was thinking of moving.
- To where?
- Here.
I think it's
a great idea.
- Where are you?
- An open house.
Are you... Are you and Chris,
uh, moving in together?
You guys are happy, right?
Do you want to get dinner
sometime?
I owe it to Chris to end things
the right way with him.
Ask me again. After.
Deal.
♪
Luna:
You hate New York.
I don't hate
New York.
Every time we visit,
you are always
counting down the seconds
until you can get home
to your beloved Los Angeles.
It's your home, too.
For the past 27 years,
by the way.
L.A. is where I live
and where we have built
a life.
But New York is home.
[Scoffs] It's like
everyone born here
is auto-enrolled
into the cult of New York.
And you got our daughter
going to school here. Ugh.
♪ Take my crown
♪ Never be the same
♪ Yeah, this my town
♪ Get ready for the sound
What time is Dominique
meeting us here again?
Noon. So we can
go get unpacked,
maybe mess up
the bed a little?
I like
the sound of that.
[Both chuckle]
Hey!
Get over here, man.
Man, what you doing,
huh, huh?
What the hell
are you doing?!
This fool tried
to steal our luggage.
It's the bellman.
♪
What's he wearing
a hoodie for?
This is a hip
New York hotel.
That is his uniform.
I'm sorry, man.
Wait a second here.
No, no.
- [Scoffs]
- Mm-hmm.
I love this city.
Whoa!
Hey!
God, I hate this city.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Crumbs in the bottom
of my bag, I'm starving ♪
[Beep]
ADT Voice: Armed Stay.
I don't even have to go
to the front door.
I can set it
from anywhere.
We're living
in the future.
[Beep]
Disarmed.
Ready to arm.
There we go. [Sighs]
That should brighten
things up around here.
- Thank you so much.
- No problem.
Anything else you
need me to install
or repair
while I'm here?
Yes. But I couldn't
possibly impose
any more than
I already have.
Please don't
worry about it.
No, I remember
what it was like
getting divorced,
moving to Los Angeles,
only I didn't have
any young kids to raise.
Yeah, I thought it
was gonna be hard,
like... exhausting,
soul-crushingly hard.
I was right.
Well, I am here for
all your home-repair needs
or any stoic, manly opinions
if Tim is unavailable.
Thanks.
I know it was in here.
Something missing?
My charm bracelet.
I had it in this
embroidered box, and I just...
I know I packed it in here.
Here, let me
help you look.
I get one for every
big event...
you know, wedding,
each of the boys' birth, anniversary.
Were any of the charms
worth much?
Some of them.
♪ And I'mma make us
a reservation ♪
You don't think
the movers stole it
when they packed it up?
I could certainly
look into it,
see what I find out.
Thank you.
I'd ask Tim,
but he's so busy this week
as acting
watch commander.
I'm sorry.
No end-of-shift time off
on my watch.
When does Sergeant Grey
get back?
Okay.
Heard you were
in the big office today.
Yeah, just, uh, keeping it warm
for Grey.
Something I can
help you with?
I was hoping I'd get
your opinion.
Um...
Lucy and I have been
looking at houses to buy.
Yeah, she, uh... she mentioned
something about that.
You know her taste.
Um, is this
worth showing her?
Um...
it's nice.
Lucy: What's nice?
Oh, uh...
I think I found
the house.
Oh, great. [Chuckles]
Uh, before I send
you the listing,
I'm gonna call the agent
and make sure
it's still available.
I'll call you
when I get to the office.
I can't wait.
How's the breakup going?
I'm in
the planning stages.
I'm just reviewing
the literature.
Literature?
Lucy,
a psychology journal
is not gonna tell you
how to break up with Chris.
I mean, uh, just invite him
to your office
and ask for his playbook.
Quick and easy.
His playbill?
His playbook.
When you get
kicked off the team,
you have to turn in
your playbook.
It's a metaphor.
No, it's cruel.
I'm... I'm gonna
handle it my way.
If... If you're having
second thoughts...
No, I... I'm not.
Good.
Hey, uh, your company
just moved a Genny Bradford.
There seems to be
an object missing.
It's a bracelet last seen
in an embroidered box.
No, sir. Excuse me.
No, no one is accusing
anyone of anything.
But if you could
just contact the team,
see if they know anything,
it'd be much appreciated.
Okay. Thank you.
No joy?
He said, "Let me
get back to you."
I don't want to
sound cynical...
He's blowing you off.
Ah.
You seeing this?
Control, 7-Adam-15,
possible 2-11 in progress.
Subject white male,
black pants, plaid shirt.
♪
- ♪ 1 for the money
- ♪ What are we talking about?
Police!
Show us your hands!
♪ What are we talking about?
Hey! I got him.
I got him.
♪ They talking 'bout funds
round here ♪
Stop! Stop!
♪ They talking 'bout guns
round here ♪
♪ I'm a hold it down
like I'm my mamma's son ♪
Stop!
[Siren wails]
Control, 7-Adam-15, foot pursuit
of suspect, west on 8th.
♪ You gotta let me finish
♪ You know I'm lit-erally
always winning ♪
♪ Stay on my biz markee,
I keep 'em spinning ♪
♪ Ooh, she so thick-skinned,
you gotta let me finish ♪
♪ Never disrespect
the queens in the room ♪
Hey! Get down!
Stop!
♪ For my lady, man,
I'll leave you in this tomb ♪
♪ You ain't Jesus
♪ Everybody want
the tea and the soup ♪
♪ Wendy Williams,
more cream, more greed, baby ♪
♪ That's just how I see it
♪ Yeah, every man for himself
♪ Yeah, yeah, hey
♪ Only the strong will survive
when you out here ♪
♪ Out here
[Siren wailing]
♪ Hey, it's a dog-eat-dog world,
no fear ♪
♪ No fear
Celina: Hey, stay down.
Stay down, stay down.
Stay down.
[Handcuffs click]
You okay?
Yeah.
How about you?
Anything broken?
[Grunts] I'm fine.
Just arrest me already.
Oh, you're for sure
under arrest.
[Breathes heavily]
Then let's go.
I just gotta call my girlfriend.
She'll post bail.
Ah, well, I'm glad
you got a plan,
but you took
a pretty hard fall.
First, we're gonna
take you to the hospital
and get you checked out
before we can process you.
Shall we?
How about next time,
you run and I drive?
Let me get back
to you.
[Horns honking]
Thought you said Dominique
was supposed to meet us here
- at noon.
- She was.
She's usually early.
Maybe she was
up late studying.
- Or partying.
- [Laughs]
You check her ClipTalk?
It won't tell us much.
It's her cover page.
- Her what?
- You know the kids.
They have their real
social media accounts
and then the fake ones
that they give to their parents.
Are you...
And you're okay
with that?
She tells me everything.
I don't need to stalk her.
She tell you
why she's late?
No.
But I do know
where her dorm room is.
[Knock on door]
Luna: Hi.
You must be Marta.
Dominique has said
the nicest things about you.
Oh, right.
You're the parents.
Yeah.
We're the parents.
And we're looking
for Dominique.
She was supposed to meet us
at the hotel.
I'm sure if you guys had plans,
she'll be home any minute.
Marta, I appreciate you
having my daughter's back,
but now is not the time
to cover for your roommate.
Her bed's made.
It hasn't been slept in.
[Door closes]
Honestly,
I don't know where she is.
Let's just call her.
We have.
Several times.
Is this her desk?
Yeah.
She's studying finance.
These are all
humanities courses.
Oh. Um...
So she didn't tell you
that she switched majors?
No, she did not.
[Sighs]
When was the last time
you seen her?
Uh, just after dinner.
Like 12 hours ago?
I'm sure she's fine.
She has all of these rules.
Uh, never leave your drink unattended,
be smart about social media,
never walk alone,
always keep a phone charger
with you.
"Wade's Way."
[Chuckles]
I thought I was talking
to myself.
Did she happen
to tell you
where she was going
after dinner?
Saint Genesius.
The church?
Just a couple bumps
and bruises.
The scrape on his forearm
is about the worst of it.
Oh, thank you.
And, uh, thanks for the ice.
Any time. I'll get the hospital
clearance form for you.
Be right back.
- Nolan: Hey.
- Hey.
Ryan checks out.
We can take him to processing.
Great. I just got a call
from the movers.
Turns out the manager
wasn't blowing me off.
So they found
the bracelet?
One of the movers fished it out
of the trash.
Why was one of her prized
possessions in the garbage?
He's looking into it.
He'll call me back.
Hmm.
Hey, can we go now?
I've never seen anyone
so anxious to go to jail.
Hmm.
You know, you haven't said
anything since we pulled out.
I'm just thinking
about things.
I'm a good listener.
[Inhales,
exhales deeply]
Uh... yeah, I-I need to break up
with Chris.
- Finally.
- What?
Look,
he's a good dude and all,
but, like [chuckles]
nowhere near your level.
I just don't know
how to handle it.
You know, I don't want
to hurt him.
Okay.
Well, let's act it out.
You know,
if you've rehearsed it,
then it'll be a breeze.
Okay.
Um...
the process of
buying a house together
has made me think about
some things and...
Wait, hold on.
Time out. Time out.
Y-You're buying a house
together?
- T...
- Yikes.
That is not helpful.
You're right.
I-I'm sorry.
- As I was saying...
- Yeah.
[Clears throat]
Okay.
Chris, it's not fair
that we move in together
when I'm having
this much hesitation.
And you're
such a great guy.
You know, you deserve someone
who is sure of all of...
What...
Are you crying?
[Voice breaking] I'm sorry.
It's just that, um...
It's okay.
...I thought that everything
that we've
been through together,
like, this meant something.
What are you doing?
- I'm channeling Chris's pain.
- What?!
You need to be prepared for
an emotional response, okay?
Let's just take it
from the top.
This time,
I'll go the angry road.
- No.
- Yes.
What...
Dispatcher: 7-Adam-19,
we have an R.P. claiming
there's a Na'vi
breaking into a car.
Uh, a what?
Na'vi. It's an inhabitant
of Pandora from "Avatar."
Ask her if it's
a full-grown one,
'cause those things
are like 9 feet tall.
Aaron, it's a fictional character.
LAPD.
Whoa.
Oel ngati kameie.
Excuse me.
What?
I-It's Na'vi.
It means "I see you."
[Chuckles]
Sir, we received a report
that you're trying
to break into this vehicle.
No. No, no, no.
This is... This is mine.
I just locked my keys inside.
Even worse, I locked my tickets
in there, too,
and the preview screening starts
in like 20 minutes.
For what movie?
Both: "Avatar:
The Way of Water."
Yeah, man!
I cannot wait!
I already got my tickets
for opening day.
Oh, man.
It's gonna be so great.
Okay. Look. We can help you
get into the car,
but we need to see some
identification first.
Is that in the car
as well?
No. It's in my loincloth,
but it's...
- it kinda slipped underneath...
- Uh, ok... okay.
We're good.
Could you please run to the shop
- and grab my slim jim?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna take a flyer
on this one.
- Oh, I'm so excited!
- Oh, there's... Oh!
Oh, sir... [Chuckles]
You're...
You're just covered
in blue paint.
Oh.
Hey!
Genny. Hey.
No one told me you were here.
I'm here to see Nolan.
He was trying to track down
my bracelet.
The one with the charms?
What happened to it?
Uh, well, I tracked down
the movers.
They said they saw a kid
throwing it away.
They said it sounded
like... Tyler.
But he knows
I love that thing.
Why would he...
Because he's mad at me and
blames me for the divorce.
- I should go.
- You want me to talk to him?
No. It's fine.
I got it.
- Thanks again.
- Of course.
[Buzzer]
This is taking too long.
We'll get you in front of
a judge just as soon as we can.
I don't care
what they charge me with.
I need to post bail
and get out of here.
Just calm down.
You'll get your turn.
Buzz one!
[Buzzer]
What makes him so certain his
girlfriend's gonna bail him out?
If I was her, I'd take this time
to reevaluate my relationship.
- You piece of crap!
- Nolan: Hey, hey!
Hey!
Get your hands off of him!
Buzz one!
♪ One, two, three, go
♪ Break down the door,
we arrive on sight ♪
♪ Everybody wants to know
if they doin' it right ♪
Code-99!
♪ Put your fist through a wall
cuz we bouta incite ♪
♪ Let's start a fight,
let's start a fight ♪
Code-99!
♪ Let's start a fight
♪ It's burning bright,
my fists are tight ♪
♪ My momma always told me two
wrongs don't make a right ♪
[Alarm blaring]
♪
Secure him.
Get these guys back
in their cells.
Add assaulting an officer
to the charges.
♪
Yeah, I'm good.
- Really. Hey.
- What happened?
Uh, the guy we just brought in
wasn't very popular.
Make sure he gets a cell
by himself.
- You guys okay?
- Yeah, a little banged up.
- You good?
- Yeah. I'm good.
Get over to the hospital.
Get yourselves checked out.
No, we're... we're really good.
We're good.
- Yeah.
- Watch Commander's orders.
Yes, sir.
What is she doing at a church
on a Wednesday night?
None of it makes sense.
I'm starting to wonder how much
we really know our daughter.
Luna: Thank you.
Season your admiration
for a while with an attent ear,
till I may deliver upon
the witness of these gentlemen,
this marvel to you...
for 20 pieces of silver.
I'm sorry,
what's happening?
I believe it's one
of those immersive
theatrical experiences.
We don't have time
for this.
Have you seen this girl,
Dominique Grey?
I pray thee,
what you seek lies ahead.
But the path is dark.
Wade, let's just go
find her ourselves.
[Medieval choral music plays]
♪
What the hell was she
doing there?
Seriously.
You know how many
times I tried to get her
- to come to the theater with me?
- Sgt. Grey: Not now, Luna.
Avenge me.
Avenge me!
Pity me not,
but lend thy serious hearing,
to what I shall unfold.
We are looking for our daughter,
Dominique Grey.
Do you know her?
Thou shall be bound to revenge
when thou shalt hear my tale!
He won't break character.
Let me try.
We seek thou helpist
searching for this fair maiden.
That is the lady Ophelia,
but she is not here, alas.
Another plays in her stead.
Hey, hey, speak English,
dammit!
Dom's not here.
She flaked.
Her understudy's
playing Ophelia.
Dom?
She hates that name.
Yeah, and she gets stage fright
ordering from the drive-through.
When's the last time
you saw her?
At last night's show.
- Before the cops were called.
- Called for what?
Gertrude saw her boyfriend
with another girl,
and the two went at it.
We had to call the cops.
Dom and Gertrude
left after that.
Where'd they go?
No idea.
Gertrude wanted to burn her
boyfriend's vinyl collection.
Maybe she did.
All I know is
neither of them showed up today.
Should we start
calling hospitals?
We're gonna find her.
And she's gonna have a crazy
story about losing her phone
and crashing with
a friend of a friend.
And forgetting that her parents
were flying in today?
No, that is
not like her.
Experimental theater
is not like her.
I don't think
we can rule out anything.
Here she is.
Hey.
Sergeant Grey.
Mrs. Grey.
Detective
Olivia Terry.
I hear you're worried
about your daughter.
Yes, Dominique.
She's a student at NYU.
We flew out for a visit,
and she never showed up.
How long?
We were supposed
to meet up around noon.
She was last seen
at 10 p.m. last night.
You know what I'm
gonna say, right?
We have to wait 24 hours
for a missing persons.
I'm aware.
But we do know
that there was a fight
at the performance
she was at.
Cops were called.
Here at Saint Genesius?
Yes.
She may have gone
with a friend
to confront
one of the combatants.
We just don't have any names
or addresses.
Look, she's a college student
feeling her new freedoms.
Are you a parent?
I'll get you the names
and give you a call.
But remember, your badge
means nothing here.
Don't go all cowboy
on my streets.
You need something,
reach out.
Thank you.
Okay, one more visit today
and you guys get a free X-ray.
Yeah,
you get your card punched
every time you get
your face punched.
[Laughs]
Should I assume that
prisoner brawl in holding
equals a boatload
of paperwork?
Uh, technically,
it's two boatloads.
EMT: Move!
We're coming through!
Man: Folks,
we got a code blue.
Let's get
that crash cart prepped.
What happened?
Found him in his cell unresponsive.
One, two, three.
No pulse. His heart stopped
twice on the way here.
Dr. Hurley: He's in V-tach.
Paddles.
[Paddles whirring]
- Everybody clear.
- Charged.
Clear.
[Thud]
- [Beeping]
- Nurse: Charging.
Is he gonna be okay?
[Flatline]
Clear.
[Thud]
[Flatline]
Do you think he got hurt
in the arrest?
Maybe?
Charging at 360.
- Clear.
- [Thud]
Celina: As the
arresting officer,
it's my responsibility
to keep him safe.
Yes, but we have no idea
what went wrong,
so let's not make
any assumptions.
But what happens if he
doesn't pull through?
Tim: It'll be considered
an in-custody death.
An investigation
will be launched to determine
if your use of force
was within the law or...
Or if something I did
caused him to be here.
[Flatline]
Time of death...
11:14.
Nolan: Sir, for what it's worth,
I don't believe Officer Juarez
did anything wrong.
I hope you're right.
I'm gonna have to put you
on admin leave.
- W... Am I fired?
- You are not fired,
but you cannot act in a police
capacity until you're cleared.
Until then, I'm gonna need
your gun, your badge,
and your body cam.
You'll get these back
once you're cleared
of any wrongdoing.
♪
And if I'm not cleared?
If you're not cleared,
you could be facing
murder charges.
♪
- You here about Ryan Davis?
- Yeah.
You were the acting
Watch Commander
- when the death occurred?
- Yep.
Where's Officer Juarez now?
In interrogation
with Officer Nolan.
You allowed her T.O.
to wait with her?
He's her union rep.
A-And you don't think
that's a conflict of interest?
That's up for I.A. to decide,
and they cleared him.
Once we're finished with Juarez,
we'll need to talk to you.
To get your
official statement.
And so you can walk us
through exactly
what protocols you followed
after the death occurred.
Before we get started,
I just wanted to say
these kinds of interviews
are uncomfortable for all of us,
but Mr. Evers and I are here to
protect the city of Los Angeles.
Wesley: Which means we'll be
conducting this interview
as if you were a suspect
in a murder investigation.
- Got it?
- Mm-hmm.
This has been explained
to Officer Juarez.
You're aware as
a police officer,
you do not have the right
to remain silent?
Yes. I.A. advised me
of my Lybarger rights.
Let's jump right in.
After you tackled
Mr. Davis,
did you notice any signs
of a head injury?
No, he seemed
perfectly fine.
He didn't exhibit any, um,
confusion, dizziness,
sensitivity to light?
N-Not that I observed,
but we took him to the hospital
just to make sure.
Before the encounter,
did Mr. Davis do
or say anything
that might have made
you want to hurt him?
N-No.
No, of course not.
Remember, you don't have
anything to hide.
Wesley: That's what
we're here to determine.
If you did everything
by the book,
that's good for both you
and the city.
It limits our liability.
But until we know for sure
whether your actions contributed
to Mr. Davis's death,
we need to be prepared.
To prosecute me
for murder?
Yes.
Wesley:
Shall we continue?
She's never even mentioned
a friend named Gertrude.
I'd remember.
Well, they're close enough
for Dominique to follow her here
to confront her boyfriend.
Looks like something else
she kept from us.
Have you seen this girl?
Sgt. Grey: [Clapping]
Hey. Hey.
Can I get your attention?
We are looking for our daughter,
Dominique Grey.
My wife and I have a photo.
If you wouldn't mind
taking a look,
we'd appreciate it.
Hey, hey, you.
- Do you know who thi...
- [Sighs] Wh... What's going on?
Luna: This is our daughter, Dominique.
You might know her
as Dom.
We're her parents.
We've been searching for her.
- Dom is missing?
- Yes.
We heard that she might have
come here last night
with her friend Gertrude.
Yeah, that's... that's me.
I'm... I'm Gertrude.
When's the last time
you saw her?
[Scoffs]
We came over to confront
my boyfriend
about that skank
he brought to the show.
I punched him.
And then we started
making out.
All right,
that tracks so far.
Where was Dominique
in all this?
Well, Sian brought
co... conut water
and that's not really
Dom's scene,
so I think she got a cab
back to the dorms.
Fine. Thank you.
If she reaches out,
please call us.
- Okay?
- Yeah. Totally.
Now we know why she didn't tell
us about her friend Gertrude.
Yeah.
♪
Nolan: You can go home,
you know?
No, I can't.
What if I'm the reason
that guy's dead?
I don't think you are.
I looked at the
body cam footage.
That was a takedown any one
of us had done 100 times.
More likely it happened
during the fight in processing
or a preexisting condition.
But even if he had
an aneurysm
and I'm the reason
it went off today
and not five years
from now...
Ryan robbed
a jewelry store.
He ran from the police.
He made those choices.
I know what
you're going through.
In my case,
I was directly responsible.
I shot and killed a man
who pointed a gun at me.
And it took me a long time
to come to terms with that.
But I did.
How?
How can you do your job
knowing it might happen again?
By focusing on
the good I do.
I don't know if I can.
How did Ryan die?
We're trying
to determine that now.
Did he have
any health issues?
I don't know. We haven't been
dating that long.
Do you know
where he's been staying?
He kind of just bounces
from motel to motel.
What about his baby?
What baby?
He has a kid.
The mom bailed.
When he does jobs,
he has this soundproof box
he puts the baby in.
He does what?
So the crying
doesn't call attention.
You don't have the baby?
We looked into Ryan's
possessions and found this.
Tim: Well, he's not staying
at a Four Seasons.
That narrows it down
a little.
There's still dozens
of low-end hotels and motels
we need to search.
Everybody, listen up.
We have an eight-month-old
infant
that was abandoned
four to five hours ago,
and we need to call every motel
within a five-mile radius.
Then 10, then 15.
Based on what Ryan's
girlfriend told us,
this has been Ryan's M.O.
for a while now.
So he knows how to stay
under the radar.
He probably checked in under
a pseudonym and paid with cash.
Well, that's gonna
make it hard to find him.
Exactly, so start with
the lowest of the low,
places that rent by the hour
and don't check I.D.
and work your way up.
We don't stop until we
find this missing kid.
Got it?
♪
[Horns honking]
Okay, so she helps Gertrude
confront the boyfriend,
then what?
I don't know.
Excuse me. Can I take a look
at your security footage
from last night?
Sorry, no can do.
Well...
[Stammers]
I'm a police officer.
That says Los Angeles
Police Department.
I don't think that does
any good in New York.
Then there's
the whole warrant thing.
Look, man,
my daughter is missing.
We know she was at a party
at this building.
I just need to check
to see
if she left
with someone or alone.
I need
to stop you there.
I would love to help you out,
but I can't.
I don't have the authority,
and my boss is off.
And I would get fired
if I failed to protect
the privacy of our tenants.
D-Do you hear
what I'm telling you?
- My daughter is missing, man!
- Luna: Wade.
I got this.
Look, I just need you
to go back,
check the security footage, okay?
If you don't want me to go
back there, that's fine.
That's fine. Just...
You can protect the privacy
of your tenants,
but I'll give you
a picture of her...
Excuse me.
May I ask you
for a favor?
- Right now!
- Luna: Wade Grey!
I found her.
That's her jacket.
- Who are you calling?
- Dispatch in L.A.
Soon we'll have an address
on that car in no time.
♪
Luna: She got in the car but
never made it back to the dorm.
That's bad.
There's no way
that's not bad.
I won't survive
if she...
I know. I know.
Me either.
Hey, and we're gonna
find her, okay?
Okay.
Should we call
that detective?
If I was her, I would say
we didn't have enough to go on.
So it's just us then?
Hey.
I'd rather you have my back
than anyone at Mid-Wilshire.
That's gotta be him.
Excuse me.
Can I take a second, please?
Um, okay.
Am I good cop
or bad cop?
Trust your judgment.
- Ralph Stevens?
- Yeah.
I'm Sergeant Grey.
You, um, drove this girl
last night?
- Yeah.
- What time?
Where'd you pick her up?
Where'd you drop her off?
Who are you again?
Sergeant Wade Grey.
Do you have a badge?
That's not NYPD.
Are you from the boonies
or something?
L.A.
So why do I gotta talk
to you?
The girl is missing.
Any information would be
greatly appreciated.
Oh, of course. Yeah.
I, um, picked her up
outside some place.
Big party
was popping off.
Dropped her
at Sixth and Avenue C.
She lives
on Fifth and B.
There was a truck
blocking the street,
so she asked me
to let her out.
Did you notice
anyone following her?
Anyone that may
have looked suspicious?
In that neighborhood?
Yeah, everybody.
I'm really sorry I couldn't be
any more help, guys.
One more question.
- Did she tip?
- Uh, yeah.
Luna: How much?
25%.
If you guys don't mind,
I...
I got another ride
I gotta go pick up.
Yeah.
Thanks for your time.
- She always tips big.
- Yeah.
Seems like
he's telling the truth.
Yeah.
[Engine starts]
Sgt. Grey: He's lying.
I told Dominique if she's
ever taken by someone
to disable the taillight.
He has her.
I know it.
Now it's time to call
the detective.
Detective Terry has units
rolling out wherever he stops.
Good.
If you get too close,
he's gonna see you.
I know how to do this.
Okay. You're right.
♪
I'm just nervous.
And scared.
Dominique and I have...
We've always been so close,
but there's been so much
she's been keeping from us.
And now
if we don't find her,
we're never gonna know
who she really...
Don't say it.
You can't think that way.
We're gonna find her.
Give Terry the address.
9226 Rugby Road
in Queens.
Hurry, please.
♪
Let's go.
Aren't we supposed to wait
for the detective
with the patrol unit
to come?
[Groans]
I'll be sure to apologize.
[Grunts]
♪
- [Muffled scream] Help!
- Dominique!
Dominique: Dad!
♪
[Screaming]
Mom!
Luna: Dominique!
- Dominique: Dad!
- Luna: We're coming for you!
[Grunting]
Dominique!
♪ Can't stop falling
[Grunting]
♪ Fall down, fall down
Dominique: Dad, please!
♪ It's coming around this time
[Grunting]
♪ Fall down, fall down
Ah!
[Metal clatters]
♪ Down, down
[Breathing heavily]
Sgt. Grey: Hey! Hey!
- Hey.
- [Breathing heavily]
[Siren wailing in distance]
Are you... You okay?
Mm-hmm.
[Whimpering]
God, I hate New York.
[Both chuckle]
- [Exhales deeply]
- NYPD Cop: Sergeant Grey!
Over here. We're safe.
[Chuckles]
So sorry.
Got all turned around.
I just got assigned to Queens
last week.
I'm so used to the grid
in Manhattan.
It's all right. The Grey family
handled business.
[Laughter]
- Officer...
- Smitty.
Of course it is.
[Chuckles]
No one matching Ryan's
description had rented a room
from the Sea Shanty's Inn.
I've been going through
his credit card statements.
No hotels, but he has been
to a bunch of other places.
Most of them
are coffee shops.
Guess his kid's not sleeping
through the night yet.
Oh, Lila regressed hard
at nine months.
We had switched to formula,
and she...
Wait. He's got to be using
formula, right?
Right. Got it.
Uh, he went
to this 24-hour pharmacy
in the middle of the night
two nights ago.
When your kid wakes you up
at 2:00,
you're not going more than
a block for the formula.
Okay.
[Mouse clicks]
City Center Hotel.
That's got to be it.
Lucy and Aaron
are nearby.
[Siren wails in distance]
- [Horn honks]
- [Helicopter blades whirring]
Is it possible
to get negative stars?
Uh... Uh, no. Just...
Hola, Antonia. Um...
estoy buscando un bebé.
Y un hombre malo.
Dos, sesenta y tres.
Gracias.
263.
[Siren wailing in distance]
[Rock music plays in distance]
♪
Gun.
[Gunfire]
[Gun clicking]
♪
[Grunting]
[Grunts]
You got him?
- Huh?
- Do you got him?
- Yeah!
- I'm going to 263!
Hey! Police! Open up!
I'm coming in.
[Breathing heavily]
♪
[Sirens wailing]
[Baby cooing]
♪
Oh. Hi.
Oh, my gosh.
Call it in.
Baby's safe. Code-4.
7-Adam-19, show a Code-4.
Baby's safe.
I'm calling a locksmith.
[Door closes]
You need something
more secure.
Dad, it's fine.
You can never be too safe.
You see how things can happen.
I got abducted
out in the world
by two creeps
with a history of stalking.
The deadlock wouldn't
have saved me.
But if it makes you feel better,
I'll get three.
The only thing that's gonna
make me feel better
is bringing you home.
But I'm not gonna push it.
Unless you want
to come home.
You have been through
so much.
I think I should stay.
I feel like if I run home now,
I'll never come back.
Okay. If you change your mind,
you know you...
I know. Thank you.
- [Luna exhales deeply]
- For everything.
You know, I was in that
basement, and I thought,
"Mom and Dad are here,
and they're gonna find me."
And you did.
Oh, honey.
[Chuckles]
[Police radio chatter]
Sorry.
I don't want to interrupt.
It's okay.
What is it?
The coroner's report
came back.
They concluded
it wasn't your fault.
[Exhales deeply]
His spleen was ruptured
during the fight in holding.
The coroner was able to confirm
it through video surveillance.
Someone clearly stomped
on his side.
But your arrest had nothing
to do with it.
So I'm still a cop?
If that is
what you want.
It is.
Good.
Once the paperwork
is finished,
you'll be cleared
to return to work.
[Exhales deeply]
Thank you. [Sniffles]
You have no idea
how relieved I am.
Oh,
I-I think maybe I do.
Go home. Get some rest.
I'll see you here next shift.
[Exhales deeply]
Okay.
One more practice run.
No.
That's not necessary.
I-I know how
I'm gonna handle it.
- Oh, nice.
- Mm-hmm.
You know, I knew my acting
skills would come through.
So, uh,
what are you thinking?
I'm gonna stop rehearsing
and just go with my gut,
you know?
This isn't a play,
it's real life,
and I just need to be present
in the moment
and the right words
will come.
- I like that.
- Lucy: Yeah.
It's a terrible plan,
but I like the sentiment.
Mm-hmm.
- Good night, Aaron.
- Okay.
[Knock on door]
- Hey.
I was thinking sushi
for dinner tonight.
- Mmm.
- I could go for some unagi.
Ooh. Um...
- Uh, or Thai.
- Lucy: No.
I...
I mean, it's, uh...
it's not that. Um...
Okay.
What's going on?
[Sighing] Oh.
Aaron was right.
I should've practiced more. Okay.
- [Chris chuckles]
- [Lucy clears throat]
What?
Um...
I need you to give me
your playbook.
Wait. What?
Are you breaking up
with me?
You know
what that means?
I thought things were good.
[Exhales sharply]
I thought we were, uh...
Okay.
L-Let's sit down.
No. I-I-I can't stay.
- No.
- I have to go.
Wait.
We should talk.
What's there to talk about?
[Scoffs]
You don't love me.
What else is there?
♪
Thanks for coming over.
Well, you sounded so stressed
on the phone.
Did you... Did you talk
to Tyler about the bracelet?
♪ You'd be the first
I did.
And he screamed at me
for an hour.
Moving to L.A.
ruined his life.
He wishes he could live
with his dad.
I'm the worst mother ever.
Ooh. Yeah.
I've been the worst dad ever
more than once.
Comes and goes.
Well, this is actually
my first time.
We were so close
before all of this.
He does realize he'll still see
his dad, though?
I don't know if he will.
I mean, Rob's
in a pretty bad place.
He always drank, but a couple of
years ago, he lost his job,
and then it just...
got worse.
He hasn't shown much interest
in the boys or visitation.
That's rough. Sorry.
So, then how did you become
the bad guy in all that?
♪ It will take more
than one try ♪
I haven't told them,
so I guess they think I'm
the one standing in the way.
And I know I have to tell them
the truth. I-I know.
I just...
I don't want to hurt them.
You know, when my dad left, uh,
my mom tried to keep up
the pretense for a while
that he'd be back.
She even had me convinced
he was a spy.
- That could work.
- Worked for me.
But, uh, no, we...
we always find out eventually.
I know.
I'll talk to Tyler tonight.
♪ By your side
♪ Escape
Lucy: How's it going?
[Sighs]
Counting the seconds
until Grey returns.
What are you doing back?
I talked to Chris.
♪
How did it go?
Uh, awful.
Yeah.
But it's done.
♪ Through the spaces
So, did you have something
you were gonna ask me?
♪ Filling the room with light
I can't remember.
Don't make me hurt you.
♪ I can watch you
with unflinching eyes ♪
Do you want to go out
on a date?
Yeah. I do.
♪