[Elevator bell dings]
♪ Na, na, na-na-na
♪ Na-na-na-na-na
Yeah! Come on!
♪ Take a look at us, yeah
Oh, hi. Hi.
♪ From the top to the bottom,
yeah ♪
♪ You know we got it
♪ Hey, we about to turn it up
Hey.
♪ Just can't get enough
♪ Hey, we don't even have
to flex ♪
♪ Yeah, already know
we the best ♪
♪ Got me like na, na,
na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na-na-na-na
Oh.
I love your music.
Thank... Thank you.
♪ We're just getting started
♪
♪ Yeah
H-How are you...
Detectives.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪
[Mellow music plays]
Oh.[Music stops]
You're here.
I live here.
I went to bed at 1:00,
and you still weren't home.
Oh,
I came home around then.
I must
have just missed you.
Trivia went late.
And how was trivia?
Amazing.
I came up with this obscure fact
about Josephine Baker,
so I'm feeling pretty good
about myself.
You are such
a smooth liar.
And I guess
I shouldn't be surprised.
All that
undercover training.
I'm not lying.
I saw Tim drop you off.
[Sighs] Thank God.
I am so over coming up
with cover stories.
Okay.
Why the big secret?
You're both single.
I mean, we're just keeping it
under wraps
until we figure things out.
Well, if you ever need me to,
uh, clear out for the night,
you know, play my music real
loud, just let me know.
We're not
sleeping together.
Why not?
We're taking it slow.
We want to do this right.
So you're not sure
how you feel?
No. I know exactly
how I feel.
I mean, this is the most
amazing relationship
I've been in since ever.
Okay. And you're waiting
why, again?
Morning.
Um... tonight is the night.
Oh. Really?
Yes, really.
My place or yours?
Jealous dog
or nosy roommate?
Tamara knows.
What? You told her?
No, she has eyes.
I didn't have to.
But she is staying at her
friend's tonight, so...
Sgt. Grey: Hey. Coincidence.
I was just gonna call you.
Lopez needs Aaron's help
on a surveillance,
so I was thinking,
why don't you
two ride together today?
- Great.
- Yeah, whatever you need, sir.
Great.
Mm, this is gonna
be awkward.
It doesn't have to be.
We've ridden together
hundreds of times.
Never as a couple.
On the streets,
we won't be.
So are you telling me
you're not gonna be
thinking about tonight?
Not at all.
Thank you.
Me neither.
I can't tell you about
the Elijah investigation.
I know.
I just need to make sure
someone is on it.
Wesley, a major drug kingpin
just used the LAPD
to take out two
of his rivals.
Quite a few someones
are on it.
He's not done with me
or Angela.
I know. The lawsuits
made that very clear.
The lawsuits were a game.
He doesn't care about her badge
or my family's money.
He wants to torture us.
And then quite possibly
kill us.
That does not
change the fact
that we cannot have
this conversation.
Are you hassling Harper
about Elijah?
No, I'm trusting
the process.
I said nothing.
I was never here.
Good.
Remember, the nanny's
staying late.
Date night.
How could I forget?
So,
who are we surveilling?
His name's Serrano Rivers.
I got a tip from a CI
that he's running guns.
It's not enough
for a warrant, but...
But maybe he'll screw up
and we can catch it.
It's weak,
but it's all I got.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
I could tell Grey that
I got food poisoning.
Just to get out
of riding with me?
Yeah, I mean,
I get the day off,
we avoid [sighs]
all this weirdness.
Wins all around.
You're overthinking this.
We leave our personal life
at the door, just like always.
Oh.
And you can
just shut it off?
At 7:59,
I'm your girlfriend.
At 8:01, I'm... I'm your what?
Your subordinate?
Yeah.
Really? Hmm.
What?
My duty belt.
My Taser is on the wrong side.
Normally, you would be all
over me for something like this.
- You did that on purpose?
- Mm-hmm.
You don't do Tim Tests.
I do Tim Tests.
Well, that's 'cause
this isn't a Tim Test.
It's a Lucy Lesson.
And admit it,
you are taking it easy on me.
We're not even on duty yet,
and our dynamic has changed.
Get in the car.
It's called a shop.
♪
You wanted to see us?
A prisoner's en route
to St. Stephen Hospital.
He's donating a kidney.
And you want us
to help stand guard?
The guy must be
pretty bad
if the sheriffs
can't handle it themselves.
[Sighs]
It's Oscar Hutchinson.
You got
to be kidding me!
Wait,
who's Oscar Hutchinson?
He is the worst person
in the world.
I'm sorry. My...
My brain broke a little.
Did you say
he's donating a kidney?
Yes, his daughter, Ashley,
had a kidney infection
which resulted
in end-state renal disease.
So our Oscar Hutchinson
is donating a kidney
just out of the kindness
of his heart?
I don't buy it either.
He has some play here.
Hospital does have lower
security than the prison does.
And all the drugs
and sharp objects he could want.
So round up
whoever you need, okay?
Don't let your guard down
for a second.
[Elevator bell dings]
All right.
Let's split up.
Greg, Emma, you guys set up
at the nurses' station.
I want three of you
on the north hallway,
three of you
on the south hallway.
Hospital security already
has the staircases covered.
Thanks.
All of this
for one man?
Yes.
One man convicted of murder
and multiple violent felonies.
One man who has escaped
a prison convoy,
stabbed our friend Wesley,
and escaped federal agents.
Now, he is selfish, amoral,
brutal, unethical,
ruthless, unconscionable,
and selfish.
Already said selfish.
Yes, I did, because
he really, really is.
Lambert, Juarez.
Anything we need to know?
Nothing out of the ordinary
for Oscar.
He already hit on
three nurses
and picked his handcuffs
with a pen he stole.
I hear you got
a history.
That's an understatement.
Hi, John. Uh, what,
no get-well gift?
I was hoping
for chocolates.
You can't eat them anyway...
too close to surgery.
Well, there's teddy bears, balloons.
You are aware of my heroic
and unselfish act here, yes?
The last thing you are
is selfless.
This is all a ploy.
We're simply here
to make sure you don't succeed.
He only sees the bad
in people.
Whereas I, on the other hand,
only see the good.
And you are looking
very good to me.
You didn't tell me you had
such a sexy rookie, John.
Bailey must be jealous.
Okay.
Maybe quit staring.
You're freaking me out.
She's freaking me out.
You're gonna die.
Nice. Nice try.
I've been threatened by girls
a lot tougher than you
- and taller.
- I-It is not a threat.
Death is coming for him.
[Loud clatter]
All right.
Okay, she's for real?
When it comes
to Officer Juarez,
I've come to
trust her instincts.
If she says you're gonna die,
I-I'd be worried.
Well, hell,
we're all gonna die, right?
Yeah, some of us
sooner than others.
Okay. Can we swap
Harper back in?
'Cause she's
a lot less creepy.
We're not here
for your comfort, Oscar.
We're here to arrest you
when you try to escape.
And endanger the life
of my daughter?
You misjudge me.
I don't have
any ulterior motives.
I'm here as a father.
Ashley:
He's extorting me.
I had to put $50 in his prison
commissary account
before he'd even
pick up the phone.
He says after the surgery,
I owe him $100 a week.
I am so sorry
about that.
At least he's going through
with the surgery.
I thought I was gonna be
in dialysis until I died.
I had just gotten
out of prison,
finally got my life together,
then this hit.
I heard you had your sentence
reduced for good behavior.
Seems like you've learned
your lesson.
Yeah...
"Don't be like Dad."
Don't worry.
As soon as this is over,
I am done with
shady dirtbag criminals.
You brought flowers?
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
Uh, this is Duke,
my boyfriend.
Hey."Get well, Mom."
Mix up at the florist.
Aaron, any movement
at the back?
Aaron: All quiet.
It must be nice
being a criminal.
Just sleep in
every morning.
I can only imagine.
We left Jack
with Patrice last weekend,
went up to Ojai,
I still woke up at 5:00.
Today, I slept until 5:30.
I am feeling pretty good.
[Both chuckle]
Your burrito okay?
Yeah, it was fine.
Ugh, I might be coming down
with something.
I've felt off
the last couple days.
Hm.
Um, I'm gonna get
some antacids.
- Do you want anything?
- No, I'm good.
♪
[Sighs] Okay.
[Cellphone chimes]
♪
You're kidding.
[Sighs]
Hey.
So, you haven't noticed?
That you're carrying your coffee
in your gun hand?
Of course I did.
I just haven't said anything,
because these Lucy Lessons
are pointless.
You really don't think
you're treating me differently?
You're not a rookie.
You want to change up
your duty belt,
carry your coffee
in your right hand,
it's up to you.
You know,
this isn't about us.
I'd give Thorsen
the same leeway.
Mm?
[Sighs]
Officers,
you have to do something, man.
This guy over here
is destroying my business.
Okay.
What's the problem?
I do everything right,
a-and he just parks a van
and throws up a sign.
[Laughs] Really?
You called the cops?
His customers
are coming to me
because my product's
better and cheaper.[Scoffs]
You can afford
to undercut me,
because you don't pay
the taxes or rent.
Sir, we're gonna
need to see your paperwork.
♪
Sergio:
Is my bag out there?
Yes,
your bag is out here.
I'm guessing the keys
to your van are in there?
Maybe.
I don't have
time for this.
Control, 7-Adam-100.
Start a tow truck
to my location.
[Chuckles] Okay.
The transplant team
is on the way.
They should be here
within the next couple of hours.
And you'll let us know
when it's go time?
- Of course.
- Thanks.
So, I had no idea
that, uh, foreseeing someone's
death was one of your powers.
It's not like I actually
saw him die in my mind.
It's more of a...
like a feeling, like a sense.
- Of what?
- Just total darkness.
[Oscar shouts, grunts]
Lambert: Hey!
♪
Come on! Get off!
Get off! Come on.
Get! Get!
Hands.
Give me your hands.
Nolan: What did you do?[Handcuffs click]
What did I do?
I was just sitting here.
You seriously
don't remember me?
I did 10 years
because of you!
Oscar: Well, you're gonna have
to be more specific.
I've thrown a lot of guys
under the bu...
Rod Carmichael.
You haven't aged a day.
Damn.
Get him out of here.
Let's go. Come on, move.
Looks like I beat
your prophecy.
Celina: No.
What do you mean, no?
I just survived
an attempted murder.
Yeah, and yet
nothing's changed.
Death is still coming
for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm confused.
It's not that someone
stole the uniform.
The orderly actually
works here?
Yeah, for the past
seven years.
Got out of prison,
turned his life around.
And now he's thrown it
all away.
Oscar tends to have
that effect on people.
[Sighs] Of all the hospitals
in the city,
and he ends up in one
where someone wants him dead.
What are the odds?
Pretty solid, actually.
Yeah, the city's lousy
with people who want
to see Oscar dead.
Well,
I need to examine him,
make sure it's still safe
to do the surgery.
Of course.
You really think Oscar's
still in danger?
Of dying? Yes.
But I can't tell how.
I mean, it could just as easily
come from a heart attack.
Or during
a transplant surgery.
Mm-hmm.
Duke.
Uh, hey, Officers.
Ashley's room's
one more down.
Right. Um, I just,
you know, get lost.
♪
Ooh. Ashley must have gotten her
taste in men from her mom.
Okay, so we are
citing you out, which means
we will not be taking
your fingerprints
or your mug shots
as long as you promise
to show up in court.
Anything
to get out of here.
Wait a minute.
- Where are my earrings?
- I put them in the bag.
Sure you did.
They're a half-carat each.
I didn't take your earrings.
I know they were in there.
Must be a nice perk
of the job.
[Locker door closes]
Pocket whatever
catches your eye.
Sir,
no one stole anything.
This is robbery.
Wait a minute,
you had your gun.
This is armed robbery.
I'm sure your earrings
will turn up.
And we'll call you
when we have them.
I want a receipt.
We don't issue receipts.
Look, it's all in the report.
If you want to file a complaint,
you can do so at the front desk
on your way out.
I didn't take the earrings.
I know.
This stuff happens sometime.
No, it doesn't,
not to me.
God, I've been so focused
on us.
Did I screw up?
Harper:
You're kidding.
You're not kidding?
I thought you decided
you were done having kids.
Yeah, I decided.
And... And I took the pill
and went on with my life,
and somehow
Wesley manifested this.
Okay. He's a lawyer,
not a wizard.
No. He wanted Jack
to have a sibling.
He made this happen.
Siblings are fun.
Lila loves being a big sister.
It's not that.
It's just Jack just started
sleeping through the night.
It felt like I almost had
my life back under control.
Mm. I'm sorry.
[Gate opens]
Ugh, it's him.
Target's on the move.
♪
[Sighs]
[Engine starts]
♪
It's not here.
Let's check the lockers again.
We checked them
twice already.
We'll keep checking
until we find them.
Wait.
O-Okay. Okay, look.
You need to file a memorandum
with the chief.
It's protocol.
I get it.
We're not there yet.
Well,
how long can it wait?
I have discretion
with things like this.
We find the earrings,
no paperwork necessary.
But if we don't,
you need to report me to IA.
[Sighs]
Maybe janitorial
swept them up.
Duke.
You, uh, get turned
around again?
Yeah. Man, this, uh...
this place is confusing.
[Chuckles] I'm just trying
to find the bathroom.
End of the hall,
you make a right.
You're the best.
♪
What are you doing?
Show me your hands.
♪
[Alarm beeping]
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
He's having a seizure.
What do we do?
Put him on his side.
He take anything?
He took everything.
[Grunting]
Ashley?
I-Is Duke okay?
Well, he had a seizure
from taking a medicine cabinet's
worth of
prescription pills.
Uh, there was
blood pressure medication,
antibiotics, Vicodin.
I think there was
an industrial-strength laxative there.
He's lucky
he didn't die.
Is... Is he
under arrest?
Yes, yes,
we will process him
just as soon as he's
cleaned up and released.
I thought it was weird
he kept wandering off,
but I-I never imagined
he was treating
the patient rooms
like a pill buffet.
Honey,
of course you didn't.
It's an incredibly
stupid move.
I know what
you're thinking...
I picked a guy
just like my dad.
Well, yeah,
only dumber.
Uh, we did notice
the similarities.
Good news is they're about
to come get you for surgery,
and this will
all be over soon.
Right. I'm gonna go
check on Oscar.
Excuse me.
We all set for the surgery?
My team is prepped
and ready to go.
The sooner we get this guy
out of my hospital, the better.
Where were you?
Bathroom.
Hospital is full of cops,
and he's cuffed to the bed.
- What's he gonna do?
- Hey, guess what.
GrubMonkey delivers
to the hospital.
This means you're gonna have
to delay the surgery, right?
Yes,
for at least 12 hours.
Oh, my, that's right.
I wasn't supposed to eat.
I am so sorry.
I was just so hungry.
But, you know...
since we're not having
the surgery tonight,
do you think I can have
dessert?
♪
Lopez: Serrano might be
meeting someone in there.
Clubs are a good place
to talk business.
Interferes with
any listening device.
Or he just likes
to party.
Think I went dancing here
a few times.
It was called something else, though.
Oh, yeah.
I remember those days.
Night starts at 10:00,
stumble home at 3:00.
Or not at all.
I kept a whole wardrobe
in my car.
♪
That was me.
I miss feeling
like my life is my own.
Mm.
Aaron: If you need someone
to go inside
and keep an eye on him,
I'm available.
Party on your own time.
We need to be ready to move
when he does.
♪
How much longer are we
gonna follow this guy?
A couple hours.
Angela, we have spent
the entire day on him.
You missed date night.
I know.
We'll bail soon.
One overnight bag,
as promised.
Nolan: Thank you.
No problem.
Hey, Oscar.
How you doing, girl?
You know,
it must be hard
knowing that it's just
a matter of time
before Nolan cheats on you
with his new, hot rookie.
Wow. [Scoffs]
That was a really lame attempt
to get under my skin.
You feeling okay?
Oscar just found out
he's doomed to die.
Cancer?
Celina.
Celina what?
Well, just foresaw
Oscar's death.
Oh, yeah.
He's, uh, toast.
Oh, well, in that case,
stay away from him tonight.
I won't.
Yeah, me, too.
You making your rookie
work overtime?
Oh, no, I offered.
I could use the extra cash.
Oh, I had a feeling.
There's an extra toothbrush
and a makeup kit in the bag.
You're the best.
- Call me if you need anything.
- I will.
Oh, if he comes home
with so much as a bruise,
I will hunt you down
and strangle you
with your own intestines.
You're a lucky man.
Don't I know it.
Sorry. I meant to be
out of here by now.
Mm. [Groans]
Don't worry about it.
[Sighs]
We canceled our date.
What happened?
Well, Tim and I
rode together today,
and it really drove home
all of the problems
with dating your boss.
It did seem tricky, but I didn't
want to say anything.
Does that mean you guys
are breaking up?
No.
We'll figure out
how to make it work.
Great.
How?
[Snoring]
Okay.
[Sighs]
He really shouldn't
be sleeping.
Oh, no, he's, um...
he's got a new baby at home.
Figured I'd let him
catch a few.
Ah. And how are you
holding up?
Well, we're getting
time and a half, right?
- Ah, yes, we are.
- Then I'm good.
[Chuckles]
- I'll be right back.
- Mm-hmm.
What are you doing?
[Sighs] I'm leaving.
This was stupid.
I never should have gotten
involved with Oscar again.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Maybe we should just
take a breath.
He's using me.
This is all
just an excuse
so he can get out of jail
for a couple days.
Yes, and that's
best-case scenario.
Worst-case involves
three dead hospital staff
and an international manhunt.
Then why am I here?
Because if you wait it out
on the donor list,
you might never
find a match.
I'll take my chances.
I don't want anything from him.
I thought everything
was going to be okay.
That maybe he'd had
a change of heart.
And then I find out he ordered
a hamburger to get out of it.
I mean, who does that?
I'm his daughter.
I know. And you can't force him
to have parental instincts.
I get it. Look, I thought
my dad was a loser.
But yours is on an entirely
different level,
and you don't deserve
any of this.
I was just
deluding myself.
♪
He'll never go through
with the surgery.
That may be true,
but I think
somewhere deep down,
Oscar does have affection
for you.
And I'll be here
doing everything I can
to make sure
he stays on track.
So... maybe you can
just stick it out.
Okay. [Sniffles]
Okay.
Thanks.
Oh, look,
it's Nostradamus.
Any more good news
for me?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to upset you earlier.
You didn't.
And yet you
sabotaged your surgery
to keep from
going under the knife.
Oh, please.
I was hungry,
so I ordered a burger.
And I'm an anarchist.
Okay.
You know, it's cute
the way you think
you can
get inside my head.
You can't.
Nobody can.
Okay.
Honey, I've been at risk
of dying since I was in diapers.
I'm very comfortable
with the feeling.
Is that why
you betray everyone
so they don't have
a chance to hurt you?
Duh.
What?
It's possible that doing
something selfless
is the only thing
that can change your fate.
Does Nolan know
you're this devious?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Harper: It's late.
We should go.
Lopez: Yeah.
Thanks for helping out
with this.
I feel like
I wasted everyone's time.
Well, sometimes it just
doesn't pan out.
Don't worry about it.
♪
You lied to me!
Look, I got a tip that Serrano
was working for Elijah,
and I knew
that if I told you...
Did you learn
nothing from last time?
He's getting his car.
We should go.
No. You are ruining
this investigation
by just being here.
Nyla...
Get out of the car.
- What?
- Get out of the damn car!
[Sighs]
[Engine starts]
♪
Show me your hands!
Don't shoot.
Why are you
following me?
It's my job.
If I may?
Slowly.
♪
"In-house Investigation
for..."
[Sighs]
You gotta be kidding me.
You work
for Elijah Stone?
For his law firm.
My job was to follow you,
make sure you were steering
clear of him.
And, oops, you weren't.
Can I go now?
Tell your boss
I said hello.
Tell her yourself,
'cause you're gonna
see her real soon.
[Engine starts]
♪
Lucy,
your boyfriend's here.
Did she tell you
I figured it out on my own?
I'd make
a great detective.
I have no doubt.
Hey.
I thought we canceled.
Uh, we didn't.
Oh.
I'll be in my room.
[Chuckles]
Listen, I-I've been going
over things from today.
What if someone found
the earrings
a-and assumed they belonged
to a female officer
so they left them
in the women's locker room?
Yeah, I checked already.
I mean, come on.
Y-You have
to report it now.
- I know.
- I mean, if it was Aaron,
you would have reported him already.
I know,
but it's not Aaron.
I-It's you.
And you can't be objective
when it comes to me, right?
Mm-hmm.
And thus endeth
the Lucy Lesson.
♪
The what?
[Laughs]
The earrings
were never missing?
Nope, I set them aside,
and I gave them
back to Sergio after work.
That's evil and impressive
and evil.
I know, but you weren't
facing the problem.
Okay, well, now I am.
So what do we do?
There she is.
We were just talking about you.
I hope you get double
working this late.
Don't worry about me.
You two have been
stalking my client.
We were surveilling
a known gun-runner
who led us
to your client.
I'm supposed to believe
you weren't already
- trying to link them.
- We weren't.
Already repeating
a pattern of harassment.
I mean, you're practically
doing my job for me.
Okay. I know
this is a game to you.
You live in
a gated community
with all the security
that money can buy.
But Elijah is waging a war
that can kill countless people
when he's done.
How can you not care
about that?
I'm protecting my client against
a campaign of police harassment.
Keep this up, and I will have
all of your badges.
Sir...
Stop.
I don't want to hear it.
Go home.
We'll deal with this tomorrow.
Good morning.
This is Dr. Acker.
He'll be observing
the procedure today.
Great. I can verify Oscar
hasn't eaten a bite.
- He's ready for surgery.
- You're sure?
If he got away from you at
any point, we can delay again.
- It's not a problem.
- That won't be necessary.
Wonderful.
I'll notify the team.
Great.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
She seem a little
different to you?
Yeah. Like, nervous.
And that doctor was giving me
a really weird vibe.
Totally.
What?"Weird vibes"...
I'm rubbing off on you.
[Scoffs] Yeah.
Let's check
with the hospital,
make sure that doctor
is on the up and up.
We only have
two real options.
Break up or one of us leaves
Mid-Wilshire.
It should be me.
No.
No, you love it here.
No, I do, but there isn't an
open sergeant supervisor job
anywhere else
in the division.
I checked.
Which means you would have
to take a demotion.
And that's not happening.
So...
Lucy, I...No, it'll be fine.
Rookies leave
their first station
after making P2
all the time.
That's true.
So this is
the best move, right?
Maybe. But we don't need
to decide right now.
How you feeling?
Good.
Oscar's ready?
He'll be
right behind you.
You were right.
The new doctor is not a doctor.
I ran a surveillance still
of him through ViCAP.
His name is Troy Hoffman.
Multiple priors,
in and out of prison,
including a stint
with Oscar.
Do you think he's here
to help Oscar escape?
I don't know.
But he certainly
has leverage on Oscar's doctor.
I mean, we can cancel
the surgery, regroup.
I don't want
to spook anybody
till we know
what's going on.
We need to separate Troy
from the doctor.
- Can you run interference?
- Piece of cake.
Let's go.
Well, Oscar,
how does it feel
to finally do something good
for a change?
Awful. Never again.
Celina: I'm sorry.
I-I know you're busy,
but I-I've been having
this pain on my side.
Do you think
it's cancer?
Unlikely.
Well, you can't be certain
without examining me, right?
I looked it up online.
Or, uh, Cast Syndrome.
Cast Syndrome.
That... That seems really bad.
Who is this guy?
We know he's not a doctor.
Three men broke into my house
last night.
They're holding
my family hostage.
If I don't kill Oscar
during the surgery,
they say I'll never see
them again.
I'm sorry. What?
Uncuff me from this bed, Nolan.
- I want to get off.
- Shut up.
We need to get this guy
off the board
before he can warn
his friends.
All I'm asking for
is your gut instinct.
- Is it fatal?
- No, now get out of my way.
♪
Hands up.
That's right.
So what's your protocol?
Your guys
waiting for you to call them?
Go screw yourself.
The only way her family lives
is if Oscar dies.
What did I ever do
to you?
Betrayed my brother
to the Southern Front.
Got him shanked to death
in prison.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna need
a little more specificity,
like maybe a name
or a year.
Okay. That doesn't matter
right now.
And you are the worst person
in the world.
Get his phone.
♪
Looks like he's been calling
every half an hour.
Last phone call
was 20 minutes ago.
All units, possible hostage situation
at the home
of Dr. Charlene Bernard.
The address is...19531 Mission Mile Road.
7-Adam-100.
We're half a mile from there.
Code 3 silent to possible 207.
Hurry. They're waiting
on a phone call.
In nine minutes, they're gonna
know something's wrong.
[Engine revs]
♪
It's one house up
on the left.
♪
All right,
we'll cut through there.
We'll approach
through the backyard.
Control, 7-Adam-100.
Code 6 at 207.
Tell backup that we're gonna
come in through the rear.
♪
7-Adam-100.
207, one suspect in sight.
We have exigent circumstances
and are entering the premises.
♪
[Gun cocks]
Drop the gun![Bottle shatters]
[Taser crackling]
♪
You okay?
- Clear.
7-Adam-100,
207 suspects in custody.
Code 4.
7-Adam-100, copy.
Nice job.
That means you are
officially under arrest,
and you have a surgery
to get to.
If you are still up
for it.
Are you kidding?
I'll do what I have to
to get this psychopath
out of my hospital.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
I have been
severely traumatized by this.
I'm gonna need at least
a couple of days
before I am
emotionally ready
for any kind
of medical procedure.
No problem. While you recover,
we'll just call everyone
you've ever wronged
and tell them where to find you.
You wouldn't do that.
She wouldn't do that.
If she doesn't,
I will.
Fine, surgery it is.
[Elevator bell dings]
There he is.
Out of prison two days,
and already two people
have tried to murder you.
Is it weird
that I'm flattered?
Clearly, I make
an impact on people.
So did polio.
Oscar, I've given up trying
to figure out
what makes you tick.
Well, what's the verdict,
Miss Cleo?
Am I still gonna die?
Eventually.
But the darkness that surrounded
you has receded.
For now.
Don't worry.
Soon enough, I'm sure you'll be
back in someone's cross-hairs.
Well, I'd be lying
if I said
that this whole experience
has given me
a fresh outlook
on the world.
But it has made me realize that
no matter what happens to me,
a piece of me lives on
in my daughter.
Unless her body rejects it
for being too toxic.
Sticks and stones, Nolan.
Incidentally, the deal
you forced your daughter
to make about putting money
into your account weekly,
that's not gonna happen.
She owes you nothing.[Chuckles]
Disappointing,
but understandable.
Can I interest you
in my CI services?
For a reasonable
weekly rate,
I can rat out a cornucopia
of prison-based criminality.
Hmm. No, thanks.
What about you,
Officer Juarez?
As a rookie, you need to
build a network of informants.
And nobody's more of a rock star
at informing than me.
♪
What?
Nothing.
Oh. Ha.
Hmm. That's funny.
We should go. Now.
No, seriously,
I'm not worried.
Like, not at all.
Can't con a con man.
I owe you an apology.
Definitely.
I lied to you, I put you
in a terrible situation,
and I endangered
the investigation.
And?
I'm sorry.
["Oceans Engines" plays]
♪
♪ Saturday sunset I'm scared.
♪ We're lying on my bed
I check on Jack
12 times a night.
Every time
the phone rings,
I worry it's a cop standing
over Wesley's body.
Elijah is coming
for us,
and they're counting on me
to protect them.
That is what he wants you
to think.
You are playing his game,
but you have to be smarter.
And you have to know
that I have got this.
I know you do.
Okay.
Nice work today.
You, too.
It's not a bad way
to end our partnership...
saving a family.
Yeah. Although, we're...
we're still not partners.
I mean,
on the job anyway.
♪ 'Cause while
you're wolfin' down liquor ♪
It's gonna be so weird
going to a different station,
knowing I'm not gonna
see you all day.
Yeah. And there's no guarantee
that our shifts will sync up.
♪ But answer this, babe
I hadn't thought of that.
Wait, wait, wait.
So by doing the right thing,
we're gonna see
each other a lot less?
Most likely. Yeah. No.
♪ I pray the block
in my airway dissipates ♪
I'm gonna put in my transfer
request in the morning.
♪ And instead deters
your airplane's way ♪
♪ But heaven denied
Before you ask me
how my day was
or why I was out
so late last night...
♪ Destiny decried
...I can't tell you.
Okay.
Can you tell me why
an obstetrician appeared
in our calendar?
I put that
in the shared calendar?
Yeah.
Okay. Well...
we're having a baby.
Happy now?
♪ I'm givin' up the ghost
Very.
♪ But don't get me wrong
But I know
you don't feel ready.
I don't.
And the timing could not be
worse with Elijah back in play.
I know.
♪ I guess this is where we say
It's not ideal,
but we can handle it.
Of course we can.
♪ I know I'll be all right
Your vasectomy appointment's
on the 7th.
♪ Someday I'll be fine
[Chuckles]
Got a minute?
Sure.
[Door closes]
[Clears throat]
♪
I've been keeping
something from you.
Lucy and I started dating
a few weeks ago.
♪ Like blush wine
and sonorous soirées ♪
[Sighs]
I suspected as much.
Sir,
we wouldn't have lied,
but we needed time
to figure out how we felt.
And since we're having
this talk,
I assume it's serious.
It is.
But for it
to be appropriate,
I need to move out
of her chain of command.
[Clears throat]
Okay.
Unfortunately, there's only
one position open
that will do that.
I'll take it.
It's not a great job.
Doesn't matter.
I'll take it.
Lucy:
So, I've been thinking.
Hollywood division
would be kind of ideal.
Well,
it's not necessary.
I talked to Grey.
And you're looking at
the new Court Liaison Sergeant.
But that's a desk job.
Yeah.
Out of your chain of command.
You'll be bored
out of your mind.
That doesn't matter.
Look, you and I will get to see
each other every day,
a-and you won't have
to travel to some,
I don't know, far away station
where they're gonna make you
work the midnight shift
because you're a newbie.
Tim, it's...
It's done.
Okay?
No sense in arguing
about it.
But we're so good
at arguing.
♪
I know.
But I'm hoping that
we're good at certain
other things, as well.
Oh?
♪ Sitting on my hands
Want to find out
right now?
Yeah.
♪ In the bed,
in the car, in my heart ♪
♪
♪ Standing on the stage
♪ Howling quiet
[Giggles]
♪ Like a wolf in the dark
♪ High
[Laughs]♪ G-G-Good
- Captions by VIT...
♪