I have so many questions, I
don't know where to start.
So I'll open with...
"Where you headed?" To
the bar on the corner.
I'm taking my brother
for one last drink.
I'm sorry for your
loss. As am I.
But y-you can't just
be transporting a...
There is a body in
there? Yes, sir.
My brother Kenny.
Uh, who knows the next
time I'll see him, if ever.
If you know what I mean.
Yeah. No, actually,
I don't know what
you're talking...
I'm sorry. Could you open
the lid for us, please?
Yeah.
Oh. We there yet?
Your brother's
not dead. No, sir.
So why is he in a coffin?
Oh, we just found it on the
side of the road a ways back.
Pretty cool, right?
Okay, but you said
it was the last drink and
you'll never see him again.
Yeah, well, he's moving
to the Valley tomorrow,
so who knows? I just...
It's right behind my eyes.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh ♪ It's like a hot knife.
♪ I'm gonna win for you like
I know you want me to do ♪
Alright, so, what do we have?
Ji-hoon Kim... 49,
liquor-store owner.
Two gunshots to the head.
Also has a fractured
jaw and bloodied ear.
There were broken
bottles inside.
He fought off a robber?
Or tried to. Looks like he
tried to make a run for it.
Anyone see anything?
Hey, Detectives. A C.I. of
mine says Double R did it
because our victim
wouldn't pay up.
Double R? Some new girl gang.
I'm sorry, did he just act
like girls aren't dangerous?
Yes, he did. In front of two
of the most dangerous women who
have ever walked this earth.
Who could have you assigned
to traffic control on
the surface of the sun.
Officer Jan,
we need you inside.
Uh, yeah, Copy
that. I'm on my way.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You better run.
Good morn...
Oh. Good morning.
Sorry. Ignore me.
Please continue.
We need to talk.
That's never a good
start to a conversation.
So, I've been
speaking with Celina.
Oh! I just discovered
a worse one.
The energy in your house is off.
Our house. That's
really sweet,
but not the point.
Okay. I'm excited to
hear what the point is.
Ever since the engagement,
whenever I'm here,
I feel off center, if
that makes any sense.
But I couldn't put
my finger on it.
But after talking to
Celina, we realized
that the wallpaper
color in the bedroom
doesn't line up with
your astrological sign
and the couch fabric
is completely counter
to your birth element.
Okay, see, the plan was for
you to rub off on Celina,
not the other way around.
What about the blocked
energy? Oh, don't you worry.
I'll talk to Celina today all
about that blocked energy.
Bye!  Love you.
Okay. That's it.
Be safe out there.
But before you leave,
one more thing,
what you've all
been waiting for.
So, I'll make this quick.
Pay raises from the
last union negotiation
have gone into effect.
- Yeah.
- Yay.
Check your pay stubs,
and we'll see what...
You're interrupting a briefing.
Are you Sergeant Wade Grey?
No. That'd be me.
You've been served.
"Elijah Stone vs. The
City of Los Angeles, LAPD,
Wade Grey, Wesley Evers,
and Angela Lopez."
A civil suit and
a Pitchess motion.
Alright. Briefing's over.
What's a
Pitchess motion?
It's a request to see
a cop's personnel file.
Everything... IA complaints,
even the bogus ones.
It's a great way to,
uh, block energy.
Why don't you go set up the
shop. I'll meet you out there.
Hey, union rep.
Anything you can do to help?
Not much I can do
about the lawsuit.
As far as the
Pitchess motion goes,
I can call the City
Attorney's office right now
and make sure they're
following POBR on that.
Thanks.
I've been hit with
20 Pitchess motions
and never had a judge grant one.
Yeah, but if it is granted,
Elijah can use it to
support his claims
of "violation of civil rights,
false arrest by a peace
officer with a warrant,
racial profiling,
civil conspiracy."
This is unbelievable.
I mean, the guy is a
major drug trafficker.
If he thinks he can sue
a defense attorney turned
prosecutor and win,
he doesn't know how badass my
husband is in the courtroom.
Damn straight. Uh, you
want to take a minute,
or should we ask about Chen?
What about Chen?
We caught a D.B. this morning,
a shopkeeper who refused
to pay protection money
to a street gang
called Double R.
Rowena Razors out
of Rowena Gardens?
Gang task force doesn't
have much on them
except their leader,
Shana Quelli.
She was released from Valley
State Prison three months ago.
She's been extorting
store owners on her turf.
Our victim
took a stand,
and the Razors made
an example out of him.
Harper and Lopez need you
to infiltrate the gang
to get some evidence,
murder weapon.
A confession would be best.
Uh... they're not going to
let me anywhere near them.
You're U.C. now, right?
Gaining access and building
trust is the name of the game.
You got it.
I'll figure it out.
Hello, ma'am. We
had a noise complaint.
Yelling. Everything okay?
I was just arguing with my son.
Ain't no need for the police.
Okay, so what's
the problem, ma'am?
My son, Tabin. Mm-hmm.
He won't listen.
He cuts school. He won't
pick up after himself.
And the mouth on that boy.
And how old's your son? 15.
He threaten you? He
knows he better not!
Okay. Any drugs, weapons,
other criminal behavior?
Tabin? Absolutely not.
I see him drifting.
He's running the streets
instead of doing schoolwork.
Told him he's gonna
end up like his sister.
I already lost one child.
I'm not gonna lose another.
And let me guess... He didn't
want to hear that, huh?
He says I don't know
what I'm talking about.
Starts yelling and...
and slamming doors.
I told him, "You break my house,
I'mma break your head."
Okay. Well, we can't arrest him
if he hasn't committed a crime.
Ain't nobody asking
you to do all that.
You can't talk to him, put
the fear of Jesus in him,
help keep him out of trouble?
I pay your salaries.
You know what? We
should defund y'all ass.
Look, um, I-I'll
talk to him, okay?
Is he inside?
Mm-hmm.
She did not call the cops on me.
Ma! Hey, hold on.
It's... It's alright.
Tabin, right?
Officer Thorsen.
Call me Aaron.
She's crazy, okay?
Your mom didn't call us, okay?
But she is worried about you.
What am I supposed to do?
Stay cooped up in here?
I-I want to live my life.
Right, and she wants you
to live a long and good
life, too. All moms do.
You know, it's just, sometimes,
they can trip about everything.
Listen. I know how
you feel, okay?
My mom, she's a
piece of work, too.
Sometimes I feel like she's
the kid and I'm the adult.
Yeah. Yeah. You know.
Right. But you still got
to show her respect, okay?
No matter how angry you get.
When I was your age,
I was angry, too.
Listen to her, right? If
you get upset or whatever,
just take a beat
before answering.
I mean, she changed
your diapers, man, okay?
You owe her that.
I hear you. Anything
else bothering you?
Kids at school? Nah.
You use? No, sir.
Good. Any gangs
pressuring you to join?
No, no.
Here's my card, alright?
It's got my cell on it.
Anything stresses you out,
you give me a call, okay?
But no more slamming
these doors. You feel me?
Yes, sir.
Alright.
Yeah, as their union rep, I
just wanted to touch base.
Thank you very
much for your time.
What'd they say about
the Pitchess motion?
That Lopez's and
Wesley's marriage
is going to complicate things.
Elijah's gonna try
to prove prejudice.
He may actually have a case.
Yeah, that's not good.
No, that's not good at all.
Uh, now, what was Bailey
talking to you about,
uh, our house's
energy being blocked?
Okay, look, she came
to me for advice.
And you suggested redecorating?
Okay, look,
it's more than that.
It's about having your
home's energy line up
as you build a home together.
It's that couch.
She hates the couch.
Definitely the couch. It's like
a positive-energy black hole.
I'd start there.
"Start"?
Enjoy.
Have a great day.
Thank you.
Double latte, cranberry scone?
You know me well.
Damn. He's taking
the last one?
♪ And if you real about it ♪
Hello, Wesley.
Elijah. What,
you following me?
Well, I heard you come
here every morning.
Well, the best scone in town.
You know, I never
would have guessed
from your sad, little office
or that beater that you drive
that you're old-money rich.
What's it like having
generational wealth?
I don't care about money.
I care about justice,
the rule of law.
Spoken like someone
with a ton of money.
Hmm. Well, don't worry.
I'll be relieving
you of your burden.
♪ Get in, get in ♪
It's been nice, but
you need to leave.
Your lawsuit's malicious.
I'm not leaving.
This is my spot.
Well, not anymore.
Given the fact that you
planted evidence on me,
are married to a
police detective,
and have the full force of
the D.A.'s office behind you,
it's easy to see how
you kept your job.
My only choice was to file a
restraining order against you.
The judge granted it.
This gentleman here
just served you.
I'mma be here every day, which
means you'd better not be.
Wesley.
Take the scone. That's
all you're gonna get.
It's that kid Tabin.
"Took a beat like you said.
Now Mom has me grocery shopping.
Thanks a lot." Smile emoji.
"What time's dinner?"
I think that kid's
gonna be alright.
Be careful. Puppies
are a lot of work.
What?
You just got a puppy.
Meaning I'm blurring the lines?
Meaning protect
your personal space.
Lucy got a puppy over a year
ago. Now she's living with her.
I mean, as long as
his mom's a good cook.
Oh, hey. I ran a
record management search
on the Rowena Razors.
Here is everything from
the gang task force.
They are playing catch-up.
I... This doesn't make sense.
I mean, criminal
history, arrest reports.
These girls are heavy hitters.
They've all done time
for meth trafficking,
attempted murder, manslaughter.
Why is the current
intel so light?
Well, you said it. Girls.
Everyone dismisses female gangs
as some sort of
throwback curiosity,
like the Pink Ladies.
And if they do take
them seriously,
they are written off as
drug mules or prostitutes,
not the ones who are
actually calling the shots.
This is what I was
trying to say earlier.
It's gonna be tough to get in.
They'll be a tight-knit
group, you know?
Suspicious of outsiders.
Yeah. No doubt.
But don't make the same
mistake that men do
and write them off
as just little girls.
They're a real threat.
Well, so am I.
Remember, those stop signs
are there for a reason.
Drive safe.
You know, here's
what's concerning me.
About what? Bailey.
She's feeling off-center
ever since she proposed.
It's not you. It's the
energy in your house.
Let's just say,
for the sake of argument,
it's not about the couch.
Mm-hmm. I just don't like
that she doesn't feel
comfortable in our home.
Gun!
Police! Drop the gun!
7-Adam-15. Shots
fired at our location.
I need assistance.
Check on the victim.
Good boy.
Police. I know
you're in there.
Throw the gun out.
Now step out nice and slow.
Keep your hands
where I can see them.
Turn around.
Hands on your head.
Step towards me.
Right there.
Alright.
Nice dog.
Code 4. Suspect in custody.
He got what he deserved.
I'm sure you feel that way,
but no one deserves that.
He's dead.
Yeah, well, bullets
will do that.
No, I mean, like, he's a corpse.
Skin's cold and pale.
The vessels in his
eyes are trucking.
I mean, I'd say he's been
dead for at least an hour
before she shot him.
Why would she shoot someone
You'll see
that little trailer
halfway down on the left.
That's where I found her hiding.
Hello, sir.
Our victim is Alvin
Mitchelssen. He's an M.D.
He was working at a urgent
care center in Woodland Hills.
This his residence? Yes, sir.
Any family? Uh,
he's got a wife
we're trying to get ahold
of. She hasn't picked up yet.
I had realized
there was no blood
coming out of the bullet
holes, which was weird.
But then I saw blood
pooling on the seat,
and that's when I realized
he was already dead.
The M.E. found a stab
wound on his lower back.
They figure that's the
likely cause of death.
There was no blood
leading to the car.
So we figure he was stabbed as
he was entering the vehicle,
but he was losing
blood so quickly,
he passed out before he was able
to drive himself to a hospital.
Um...
Good work, both of you.
This guy must
have been a piece of work
for two people to set out
to kill him on the same day.
Uh, sir, would you mind
if Juarez and I continued
working this case?
I know you have your hands full
with the Elijah Stone stuff.
I appreciate that.
Okay. You two work this.
Just keep me in the loop
with any developments.
Yes, sir. Head back.
Talk to the shooter.
If we can figure out
why she wanted him dead,
maybe we can determine why
someone else would
want him dead, too.
Got it. Um...
What am I charging her with?
Um, desecration
of a human corpse?
Right. But if she didn't
know it was a corpse...
Then it'd be attempted murder.
But... But without a victim...
Alright. Give me a second.
Bradford, we have a suspect
who fired into an already
expired individual.
Ooh, that's a tough
one. Could be murder one,
but maybe just
discharging a firearm.
They either get a
trial or a ticket.
Thanks for nothing.
Uh, you know what?
I'll just call the D.A.'s
office when I get back.
I'm sure they've done
this a hundred times.
May...
Probably not a hundred.
That doesn't seem very...
Yeah.
I could pose as a store
owner, get them for extortion.
No. We need them for the
murder. Keep looking.
Oh.
What is it? One of the Razors,
Vina Cordon...
There was a 4-15 called
at her house today,
and Tim and Aaron took it.
Hey, you guys caught
a 4-15 this morning?
Yeah. It was cute.
Cute? All puppies are cute.
Until they borrow
your earrings and they lose one.
Yeah, the mom asked us to
talk to her 15-year-old son.
He's a good kid.
Aaron's protégé has been
texting him nonstop.
"Who should I take to
prom? What's good on Hulu?"
Did the mom mention a daughter?
Yeah, she said she lost one.
Didn't want her son to
end up the same way,
and I thought she meant,
like, O.D. or something.
No. Uh, Vina Cordon.
She runs with the Rowena Razors.
R-2. We want to
put Lucy under,
but we can't find an in.
Your kid might be our ticket.
If your puppy vouches for
her, it can go a long way.
I don't know. Having a kid act
as a C.I. on his own sister?
I mean, they might
not even be in touch.
She doesn't have
any violent priors,
but we like the gang leader
for doing our shop owner.
Okay, so you're not
going after the sister.
The kid's a minor. We're gonna
need the mom's permission.
No, I-I'm not feeling that.
Why would we put him
in this situation?
I get it. But it's one intro.
It's not like it's
a buy or anything.
Yeah, but it opens the door.
Isn't there another
way? There really isn't.
Alright, look, how about we keep
an eye on the kid ourselves,
make sure he's safe?
If we don't do this,
we risk letting a suspect
get away with murder.
Understood.
Sure. Whatever you need.
Great. We'll set it up.
Well, do you want to tell us
why you shot Alvin Mitchelssen?
A few years ago,
my dad hurt his back at work.
And Dr. Mitchelssen gave
him opioids for the pain.
And he just kept...
upping the dosage.
And I went and I told him,
"My dad is abusing the pills.
He needs help."
And Dr. Mitchelssen
just ignored me.
My dad
O.D.'d three months ago,
and he would still
be around today
if it wasn't for that monster.
Well, did you report him
to the medical board?
I did everything that
you were supposed to do,
and no one cared.
I wasn't gonna just
let him kill my father.
He had to pay.
And that is why I killed him.
And I am ready for whatever
consequences that may bring.
Well, Abby, I've got
some good news for you,
and I've got some
good news for you.
Dr. Mitchelssen was already dead
when you shot him this morning.
Uh, I don't
understand.
So I'm... I'm not being
arrested for murder?
No. We will be charging
you with vandalism,
discharging a firearm in public,
and mutilation of a corpse.
So I'm not gonna be spending
the rest of my life in prison?
No. After we process you,
you'll be free to go,
and someone will explain to you
how you can get your gun back.
Keep it.
Having it in the house
in the first place
is what got me here.
Look, it's a big decision.
You know, we don't usually
involve minors, but
it's the only way.
I knew this Shana
girl was nasty.
I told Vina, "Stay
away from her."
Is it dangerous? It's
just an introduction.
One meeting. But we'll be
set up on surveillance.
You'll be there? Yes, ma'am.
And what do you think?
Is this a good idea?
I think it's our best bet to
get Shana off of the streets.
That's not what I asked.
Do you think he should do it?
Yes.
If we can get Vina away
from Shana, then...
maybe she'll come back home.
I hope so, baby.
Alright. I'll do it.
Do I get a gun?
No.
Do I at least get
to wear a wire?
No.
You guys are real cops, right?
Thank you for coming in. We
just had a few questions.
Would you like to sit?
Yeah.
First, uh, may I
say how sorry we are
for the loss of your husband.
Oh. Thank you.
I-I'm still in shock.
I can only imagine.
When was the last time
you spoke with Alvin?
This morning.
I had a conference downtown,
so I left before him,
which is unusual.
He's usually out the door first.
Can you think of anyone who
would want to harm your husband?
I don't understand.
What do you mean,
harm my husband?
W-Well, he was stabbed.
Right before he was shot.
Somebody stabbed
him, then shot him?
Two people, we think.
At the same time? No.
So two different people
killed my husband?
No, technically, just one.
None of this makes
sense. He's a doctor.
He... He dedicated his
life to helping people.
I-I knew he had heart problems.
That's what I thought you
were gonna tell me killed him.
I-I don't understand why
someone would want him dead.
So there's nothing
you could think of
that could lead to this?
I mean, no arguments
with co-workers, patients?
All his patients loved him.
Well, thank you very
much again for coming in.
And we are so sorry
for your loss.
Uh,
Rich, would you show
Mrs. Mitchelssen back
to the front desk?
If we have any more
questions, we'll be in touch.
Uh, please...
find whoever did
this to my husband.
Of course.
Sounds like she didn't
really know her husband.
Or he's a really good liar.
♪ If you gon' do
it, do it right ♪
♪ So if I hit it once, I
know I can do it twice ♪
♪ Anything come up out my
mouth, I'mma back it up ♪
♪ Don't judge me cuz
Yeah, that's the sister, Vina.
I have
Shana, the shooter.
Copy. Lucy, you're up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa.
Yo.
You didn't invite me?
What you want?
You Vina? Who are you?
UPS.
I got a special
delivery for you.
What the hell you
doing with my brother?
Get over there.
Put that gun away. Is that
how you're gonna thank me
for saving your
brother from the cops?
You a'ight? Yeah.
Man, you're wearing some
dumb genes in your family.
Got some nerve to be
talking like that. Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look, cops saw me boost a six.
They chase you? Two blocks.
They would have caught him
if I didn't stop and
let him in my ride.
That's the last time
I help a kid in need.
Can't blame her...
you rolling up on
a house like that.
Could've been a drive-by.
Yeah. Well, I like
to make an entrance.
And exit, too.
Stay good, little man.
Peace.
Yo, chica.
Mm-hmm. Chill.
Grab a drink.
Alright.
Promise me you're
not gonna freak out.
I never freak out. I'm
a very calm person.
Don't even wo... Whoa.
This...
This is so... much.
Are we... Are you... Are we
redecorating the entire house?
You said you weren't
gonna freak out.
Listen, there are just some samples
I wanted to look at together.
Okay, can we just talk about why
you're not comfortable at home?
I mean, this morning, you said
you've been feeling off-center.
I think we should try
to figure out why.
I want you to be
happy everywhere.
I am. Not entirely, though.
You know this has nothing to
do with you. I'm just weird.
Okay, well, maybe it doesn't
have anything to do with me,
and maybe it has something to
do with the house after all.
What do you mean?
There's nothing of yours
there. It's all my stuff.
Today we'll go get
some of your things,
bring it over to the house,
and then it'll be our place.
Thank you.
Oh, come on. I'm sorry I
didn't think of it sooner.
You know, there is
this one lounge chair
that I love and
I've been missing.
And every time you sit in it,
it feels like it's hugging you.
See? A hugging chair.
That sounds like a
wonderful addition.
Oh,
hey. Hey, girl.
How you doing? Hi.
Yeah. Oh, this is nice.
Ooh.
A-An investigation
had been launched
by the Medical
Board of California.
Dr. Mitchelssen was
racking up complaints,
mainly about
over-prescribing opioids.
He had all of his scripts
filled at just one pharmacy,
deep in the Valley. That's
not suspicious at all.
Mm-hmm. Alright.
Back to business.
Um, unless you two want
to handle the pharmacy,
and I'll get the chair?
No,
no. Go, go, go.
Don't worry about the chair.
What's up? I got news.
Elijah's Pitchess motion failed.
He won't be able
to get his hands
on all the B.S. IA
complaints in your file.
But? But he decided
to file his own.
Against me? On what grounds?
He claims you kicked him in the
nuts and slapped him around,
pulled his hair,
body-slammed him.
Never happened, although now
I'm regretting my restraint.
I know. Hey, it's his
word against yours.
He won't win.
We thought he'd spent
a lifetime in prison.
Now he's walking free.
Don't underestimate him.
Listen, don't let
Elijah Stone get to you.
You got this.
You know, we keep it cool
like that. You want a beer?
Yeah.
♪ Money be da mission,
city slickin' ♪
♪ Back to back whips,
no penny pinchin' ♪
Appreciate it.
You from L.A.?
Phoenix.
My cellie at Valley
State lives here,
so I'm crashing on her couch.
You were at Valley?
10 months.
I did 24.
Who's your cellie?
Shawty Ross.
I know Shawty.
You were cellies?
Hm.
That says something.
Tell her I said what up.
For sure.
Shawty's a C.I. on
D.O.J.'s payroll.
She'll confirm Lucy's cover.
Okay. Good. We should
pull Tabin out now.
No, he's fine.
Sir, no, it's not. You
are endangering this kid
all because it's good
for Lucy's career.
Excuse me?
time, walk
out a free woman.
Ain't no
surprise. Shawty don't play.
I shouldn't have said
No, she don't.
So, what game you guys run?
Cars? Vike, goodfella, monkey?
What's the deal? Drugs
bring too much attention.
Yo, what'd you say about my
sister? We stick to the shadows.
Yeah, let's just say we
in the security business.
Hey!
Oh, yeah. You see it, huh?
You see it?
Put that away.
Are you good? Yeah, I'm good.
Good? You just
got your ass beat.
Hell yeah, he got
his ass whupped.
Hey, look, take this.
Settle up with him later.
Come on.
Nah. I'm... I'm good.
Boy can't even hold a gun.
Scared of a gun!
"Nah. I'm good."
Alright. She's in. Let's
peel off.
Roger.
Come on.
Look, it may feel
like a big deal now,
but things like this always blow
over, okay? People will forget.
You're just saying that.
Nah, it's true, man. You know
how many times I been beat up?
Is that why you're so ugly?
Get off me!
Get away from me!
Don't touch me!
Ma'am! Where's
my son?! Where...
I knew I
shouldn't have allowed this.
You said it wasn't dangerous.
It was just a little
dust-up with another teen.
You call this a dust-up?
Well, I call it a screw-up.
And what about Vina? You
put her in danger, too?
Maybe I should tell
her what's going on.
Ma'am, you can't do that.
You expose that we have
an officer undercover,
it'll jeopardize their
life and your son's.
He's right. As soon as
Tabin made his introduction,
I should have pulled
him out immediately.
My son's done playing
cops and robbers.
You hear? Yes, ma'am.
Come on, baby.
With all those prescriptions
Dr. Mitchelssen was writing,
I mean, you'd think this pharmacy
would be a little busier.
Well, that's why
they don't look busy.
They're shipping in bulk.
License and
registration, please.
Uh, did I do something
wrong, Officer?
We'll get to that.
Alright.
You mind telling me
what's in the van?
Just, uh, making
some deliveries.
Show me.
Ta-da!
Just some boxes.
Why
don't we open them up
and take a look? Uh...
I don't think I have to do that.
Do I?
Normally... no.
You wouldn't have to show
me what's in the boxes.
But, the fact is, your pupils
are the size of pinholes,
and you can't seem to
stop licking your lips,
which makes me believe you're
driving under the influence.
Now I can see
what's in the boxes.
The law is so confusing.
Not if you don't break it.
Step back.
Did you know it's illegal to
possess prescription drugs
assigned to anyone else?
"Janet Wilson." I'm
guessing that's not you.
That's my nana. Mm.
I'm her caregiver.
Mm.
"Thomas Jeffries."
Poor Thomas. He's having
such a tough time.
Hands
behind your back.
What do you know about
Alvin Mitchelssen?
Never heard of him.
Dr. Alvin Mitchelssen?
Look, we've got a dead
doctor writing prescriptions
getting filled out
at that pharmacy.
And here you are, picking
up those very same scripts.
Whoa. Hold on. You're
not hanging that on me.
Then who are we
hanging it on? Uh...
Look, I noticed the
ink on your hand.
Rolling Seventies? That's
a tough group of guys.
I'm guessing they're gonna
sell these pills on the street.
You're just a middleman.
Tell me this, though.
Any of those guys
willing to do your time
for you if they were here?
Mnh-mnh.
Come on, man. Just tell
us who's in charge,
and we'll keep your
name out of it.
Callis Caputo, okay?
He did the doctor.
Where do we find this Callis?
This is a good party.
Except for my brother
getting his ass whupped.
Yo, my moms got him so whipped,
he ain't ever gonna make
it on these streets.
I mean, ain't that a good thing?
Maybe he'll get to
live a regular life.
Doing what? Whatever he wants.
Yeah, what you know?
Don't disrespect me.
She ain't.
Sit down.
I told you, you got to chill.
'Specially after you know.
What happened? You
nosy, you know that?
Step off.
That's Shawty's girl.
We got to make a
run. Want to come?
Yeah. Soon as I finish this.
I already paid you.
We're gonna be by
twice a week now.
I-I can't pay that.
That's what the liquor store
owner said. You heard about him?
"I can't pay."
Even when I put a gun to his
head. He left me no choice.
Okay.
I'll pay you whatever you want.
You know what? Hey, man.
He said he could pay.
Don't interrupt me when
I'm doing business.
I already told you.
Do not disrespect me.
Stop.
The liquor store was enough.
We don't need more blood.
And I told you to
get rid of that.
It's my lucky piece.
Get rid of it.
See you in a few days.
The City Attorney's offering
to pay you a settlement.
You should take it.
You know, I lost everything
when I decided to help you get
your wife back from La Fiera.
You turned me into a pariah.
Now I have to start
from the bottom.
But it's all good.
I will win, and the
damages will be paid out
from everyone's
personal accounts.
Now, that may not
hurt you, Richie Rich.
But it most certainly will
hurt Nolan and Harper and Grey.
Where they gonna find a half
a million dollars each, huh?
I'll keep coming, adding more of
your little friends to my suit.
I'll take everything
away from you
until you say sorry for taking
everything away from me.
You want me to
apologize? To you?
Something along these lines.
In public.
And, Counselor,
make me believe it.
Sir, we I.D.'d a suspect
for our homicide.
His name is Callis Caputo.
He's a member of the
Rolling Seventies.
Yeah, he's holed up at his
shop, surrounded by his crew.
We need to be smart with how
we go about bringing him in.
This could get ugly.
They've been itching to
start trouble for weeks now.
I don't want to
put a match to it.
Well, then, sir, I
think I have an idea.
Yeah? You need to run.
The cops are coming for you.
How do you know? They
picked me up earlier.
This is my one phone call, and
I'm using it to warn your ass.
Run!
They're here already.
My car's parked behind
the repair shop,
halfway down the block.
Keys are in the wheel well.
Go now.
♪ Hit the breakers,
yeah, we're gone ♪
Stall the cops.
♪ I only do it for the chase
♪ To see the look
on their face ♪
♪ Big Electric
♪ Ultra Thesis
♪ Cut Express It
♪ Can you feel it?
Looking for these? ♪ Whoo
Hands.
Alright, come on. Watch your
head.
Yeah, this is John Nolan.
You're kidding me.
Oh, my God. You're
not kidding me.
No, I-I didn't see that coming.
Alright, thank you
very much for the call.
What was that? That
was the coroner.
The tox report came
back on Dr. Mitchelssen.
It wasn't the shooting
that killed him,
and it wasn't the
stabbing, either.
Before all that,
he was poisoned.
That's what stopped his heart
before he bled out
after being stabbed.
Okay, so there's yet
another murderer out there?
Yeah. But not for long.
Care for a little overtime?
Look who it is.
What's up? I just
told Harper and Lopez
that I've made
Vina as the shooter
in the liquor store murder.
Tabin's sister? Not
the gang leader?
Look, I'm just
checking up on you
after your little ass-whuppin'.
Man, I'm good. Fine.
Alright.
Look, I need you to
hold something for me.
N-No. No.
I'm sorry, Aaron.
She practically admitted
to pulling the trigger.
I'm pretty sure she's got
the murder weapon on her now.
Come on. No.
Just hold it.
Use it if you need to.
Vina? I don't want
to blow my cover.
We got it.
You know anything about
this?
Police! Get on your knees now!
What the hell? Vina,
you're under arrest
for the murder of Ji-hoon Kim.
What, you called them?
No, baby, I swear I didn't!
Get on your knees!
Alright! Alright.
Gun! Wait! No!
Wait! What the hell
are you doing?!
Tabin, what are you
doing? Drop the gun.
No, no, no, no, no, no. You
brought this mess to my house.
Tabin, give me the gun, man.
Put it down! You did this!
No... Vina,
you did this.
Drop the gun!
Tabin, look at me.
No!
Give me the gun.
Put it down! Give
me the gun, man.
Give me the gun. Give
me the gun, Tabin, okay?
Just give me the gun.
Come on. Give me the gun.
You used me.
What you mean?
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
We just wanted you home.
Officer Nolan.
Did you find out who
killed my husband?
We did.
And we're looking at her.
What are you talking about?
It struck me as odd,
but I couldn't quite
put my finger on why...
Why you acted so surprised
when I told you your husband
was shot and stabbed,
as if you expected
something else.
Something like poisoning, which
would have presented to us
as a heart attack,
like you assumed.
And it would've worked, had he
not already been shot.
And stabbed. And
stabbed. Thank you.
You're welcome.
That's insane.
We put a pharmacy out
of business today.
They were filling
illegal scripts.
They have you on
video surveillance
using one of Alvin's scripts
to purchase the drugs you
used to stop his heart.
♪ You can feel it
in the moment ♪
Did you know that he
was under investigation,
about to go to prison for being
a complete and utter idiot?
I thought I was at least owed
the life-insurance policy.
Mrs. Mitchelssen, you're
under arrest for murder.
Officer Juarez, cuff her.
♪ Like it was your last
♪ Live extra ordinary
We matched Vina's gun.
It was definitely
the murder weapon
at the liquor store killing.
So thanks for the help.
Hey, how's your puppy?
I reached out a couple of
times to see how he was doing.
And? Did he respond?
Oh. Hey, you put a
killer in prison today.
Yeah.
It's his sister.
He'll get it someday.
♪ But you can't let up
I hope so.
♪ No, you can't let go
Good night.
♪ 'Cause you got that dream
♪ In your mind, oh
Hey, uh, I just wanted
to say I'm sorry
for what I said about Lucy.
That was totally out of line.
It was.
It's all good.
Look, sometimes
tensions get high,
but we get the job done.
You had my back,
the way you threw yourself
in front of Mom for me.
Oh, yeah, she was
gon' lay you out.
Come on.
♪ 'Cause you could
never really hold it ♪
I don't have a choice.
Let's fight
him in court.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
From the heart, Counselor.
Thank you for coming.
I'd like to apologize
to Elijah Stone
for some of my conduct while
acting as his defense attorney.
I made statements to the LAPD
which broke
attorney-client privilege,
I misrepresented the
nature of his business,
and I cooperated in
an LAPD investigation
that involved wiretapping.
My actions have been
reported to the state bar,
and I have been reprimanded.
Mr. Stone's reputation
has been tarnished,
and for that, I am sorry.
I'm relieved that
justice has been served.
Mr. Stone deserves
a second chance...
and the full faith
of the community.
Thank you. Thank you.
I accept your
apology, Mr. Evers.
I will also accept an
undisclosed settlement
from the City of Los Angeles.
I'm glad to see our
elected officials working
to right this egregious wrong.
I hope you all have
learned your lesson
and will strive to do better.
Thank you.
Smile.
What are you smiling about?
I did a thing.
What kind of thing?
Close your eyes.
I'll show you.
Oh, no.
Keep walking.
You trust me,
right?
Walking, we're
walking, we're walking.
And... open your eyes.
I know we said we'd go this weekend
together and get your stuff.
I thought I'd surprise you.
Oh, thank you.
♪ If I could wish upon a star ♪
Now let's put it
back in storage.
Yeah. Whoa, what? I
got your big hug chair.
I don't want that
thing hugging me.
It's hideous. Oh, it's not...
that hideous.
No, really, it is.
Especially next to
all your furniture.
You have such good taste.
Yeah, especially in fiancées.
Aww. ♪ Over the
hills and far away ♪
Well, it can go back.
But this... has to stay.
I made it.
You don't say.
It spent an hour too
long in the kiln.
No, no, it's perfect.
This is excellent.
It'll live right here. Aww.
And he will bring us luck.
There. Now it's our home.
I'm sure that doesn't
mean anything.
Oh.
But you never "gnome."