Previously on "The Rookie"...
Sgt. Grey: Rosalind Dyer,
the most rare of unicorns...
a female serial killer.
Congratulations.
I underestimated you.
Rosalind, you are never
going to walk free.
Who are you supposed
to deliver the drugs to?
Roy Hajek.
Wisco will give you
your cash on the way out.
Or you could do
another job for me.
And we'll need a driver,
so bring your old lady.
Hello!
If we're gonna sell
that we are, you know,
actually boyfriend
and girlfriend,
then we might have to...
[Door opens]
I just received
a formal request
to temporarily assign you
to another station.
That means I'll miss
my T.O. exam.
The station you're going to is
four hours away, on the border.
[Gunfire]
[Grunts]
[Buzzer]
[Cell door opens]
[Indistinct talking
in distance]
Good morning.
What a beautiful day
for a trial.
Oh.
And who are you?
Your shadow...
Deputy Suriel.
I'll be with you every second
you're outside of this prison.
Hmm.
Well, then, I hope
you're good company.
Oh, I'm great company...
if you're not my prisoner.
♪
♪ Na, na-na
♪ Na, na-na, na, now
[Breathing heavily]
* Na, na-na
♪ Na, na-na, na, now
♪ Na, na-na
[Exhales sharply]
♪ I'm on my way
♪ Na, na-na
♪ Na, na-na, na, now
♪ I'm on my way
This is not a break-in.
I'm just coming home
from the run.
Surprise!
[Chuckling] What?
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
But it is not my birthday.
I know. It's your half birthday,
which is just as important.
Oh, my God. Does that count
against my actual age?
No. In fact...
It was the only candle
they had at the store.
Thank you.
This is so great.
When did you even have time
to do this?
I was gone 30 minutes. Yeah,
I was gonna mention,
you know,
you really should think about
doing some more cardio
at your age.
Cake says I'm 20.
The cake is a lie, John.
Oh, well,
it's very sweet.
And I'm sure not at all
an effort to cheer me up
because today is
Rosalind's trial.
Well, you know, you can ask
to be assigned somewhere else.
I know, but somehow
that just doesn't feel right.
Shall we have
some of this cake?
After I cheer you up
in the shower.
Oh, God,
it is my birthday.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
whoa, oh, oh *
Whoo! [Giggles]
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
[Michael Nau's "Love Survive"
plays]
♪ Only my love survive
♪ Only my love
[Knock on door]
[Music stops]
Yeah?
Morning.
Uh, hi.
Um, are you on your way
to school?
In a few.
You should take
the long way around.
You know, they already
started blocking off
some of those streets
around the courthouse.
I know.
You told me.
[Chuckles]
I could blow off class
if you want.
We could go shopping
or see a movie.
I'm gonna be fine.
I'm not gonna be
anywhere near Rosalind.
Tim and I
are station-bound,
waiting for
the phone to ring.
On your undercover thing?
Yeah. The original
go-time fell through,
and it's just been
radio silence since then.
Is this the same undercover
thing you and Tim
were discussing
the other night?
♪
I already told you
that kiss didn't mean anything.
Right, right.
It was for the case.
Make out. Stop crime.
That totally tracks.
Go to school.
Okay.
Well,
have a great day.
With your boss.
Who you kissed.
Get out!
And close the door!
[Chuckles]
[Door closes]
Lopez:
You kissed Lucy?
No, no.
No, Dim kissed Juicy, okay?
Or Jake kissed Sava. Whatever.
The... The point is,
we had to be comfortable
going undercover,
so we practiced
being a couple.
How much
did you practice?
It was just a kiss.
Not that big of a deal.
Then why are we
talking about it?
Because what if it wasn't
just a kiss for her?
You think Lucy
has feelings for you?
No.
Then she probably sees it
how you do.
Just a weird thing
you had to do for work.
Right.
Timothy.
Do yo have feelings
for Lucy?
No.
No, I'm dating Ashley.
And Lucy is with Chris.
And I'm her superior officer, so...
All true.
Not what I asked.
[Tires screech]
♪
What's the Chief
doing here?
Sgt. Grey: All right,
settle down and listen up.
We got a big day
ahead of us.
The Rosalind Dyer trial is going
to complicate all of our lives.
But before that,
Chief Coleman has
some good news.
Chief.
Thank you, Sergeant.
I'm sure you're all aware
of Officer Nolan's heroic stand
down at the border
which landed a dozen
dangerous felons in custody.
In light of your courageous
and exemplary service,
I've decided to offer you
any assignment in the LAPD.
Any unit, any division,
any position you want
the department to train you for
is yours.
It's what we unofficially call
the Golden Ticket.
Thank you, Ma'am.
[Applause]
It's a big decision.
Don't rush it.
I won't.
Sergeant.
Chief.
What'd I miss?
Nolan got
a Golden Ticket.
Wow.
Congratulations,
Officer Nolan.
Thank you, sir.
I once said
you'll never make detective.
I happily stand corrected.
Don't waste your ticket
by becoming a detective, Nolan.
You know how hard
they have to work?
Go with recruiting.
You get paid
to fly around the country
and talk up the LAPD.
Boring.
You go with air support.
The city will pay
for flight school,
and you'll always have
a backup career.
Do I need
a backup career?
K-9 is the way to go.
Overtime is $200 an hour,
and you get to keep the dog.
Sgt. Grey:
And if all you want is money,
the department will pay you
to learn computer forensics.
Or I could use the ticket
to get back on track
for becoming a training officer
this year.
[Laughter]
That's funny.
[Chuckling] Yeah.
Kidding.
No, I mean, uh... no.
I, uh, certainly have
some thinking to do, yeah.
He's gonna pick
something lame.
Oh, for sure.
♪ When I walked in the Jam,
your girl was clockin' ♪
♪ Sweatin', smilin',
boy, she was jockin' ♪
Sorry. Jake's phone.
It's Hajek.
♪ So I grabbed her by the arm,
and I took her outside ♪
Sgt. Grey: All right.
Back to Rosalind Dyer.
Yo, I thought you were
never gonna call.
Hajek:
Had to iron out a few details,
but the job's back on track.
Is your lady squared away?
Hell, no.
You think we don't got
lives of our own,
waiting around
on some mystery gig?
Relax. The payday's
worth the suspense.
Wisco and Lyon
are taking point.
And we're adding your buddy
Dayvion Mosby for extra muscle.
Yo, Dayvion's money.
Dayvion's handsy.
Get someone else.
He's already hired.
Deal with it.
So what time
we meeting up?
Two hours.
I'll get back to you
with the details.
[Cellphone beeps]
This Dayvion guy shows up,
it's over.
Then I need to make sure
he doesn't.
[Reporters talking
indistinctly]
[Siren wailing]
♪
[Indistinct conversations]
Hey.
Kind of, uh,...
kind of a circus.
Seriously. Which makes it
that much harder for me
to wrap my head
around the fact
that you and Rosalind
have a relationship.
It's not like we were dating.
Uh, changing the subject...
Chief of Police
gave me a Golden Ticket.
As in Willy Wonka?
As in I can pick any job
I want in the department.
Wow.
What are you gonna pick?
Uh, am I crazy
for wanting to use it
to get back on track
to being a training officer?
Well, you know,
they give you a dog
if you join
the K-9 Unit?
Okay, if you want a dog,
we can just get a dog.
[Chuckles]
Del Monte:
All right, everybody, listen up.
Can you gather around?
Have your attention
for a second, please.
Thank you very much.
I'm Sean Del Monte.
I'm prosecuting the case
against Rosalind Dyer.
This is Chris Sanford
from my office,
Sergeant Grey, LAPD.
This is Captain Duane Tovar
from the Sheriff's Department.
He's overseeing all security
at the courthouse.
It is my hope
that this trial will close
a very painful chapter
in this city's history
and bring some peace to the
families that she's destroyed.
With that, I'd like to turn it
over to Captain Tovar.
Duane?
Thank you.
This is a rendering
of the Superior Courthouse.
We have 840 daily employees,
7,000 daily visitors.
There are 50 courtrooms.
The Dyer trial will be on the
sixth floor of the West Wing.
The escort team will arrive at a
secret entrance to avoid crowds.
Sergeant Grey's team
will be there
to secure the sixth floor
and escort the prisoner
to and from the courtroom.
[Sirens wailing]
Man: The package is in route.
E.T.A. 30 minutes.
We will have eyes on Rosalind
every second of the day.
Do you think I'm a monster,
Deputy Suriel?
I think it's not my job
to decide.
Do yo think
you're a monster?
No.
I think I'm a genius.
I just had the misfortune
of excelling at mutilation
instead of music.
Okay.
[Vehicle door closes]
That's him.
Hey, Dayvion.
What's up, Officers?
Just here for
a quick parole search.
Come on in.
I ain't got nothing to hide.
Actually,
let's start with your car.
[Snickers]
That's not my car.
Oh, no?
Well, let's just check
to be sure.
[Car alarm beeps]
That's not
a good start, man.
♪
[Sighs]
Oh.
And it just got worse.
I suppose this isn't
your gun, either?
All right.
[Handcuffs click]
Ugh. Why couldn't my
doppelganger be less greasy?
It's actually surprising
how easily you turn skeevy.
Oh.
Looking good, Juicy.
I am seriously second-guessing
this tactical decision
to wear a thong
for authenticity.
It's like...
* When I walked in the Jam ♪
♪ Your girl was clockin',
sweatin' ♪
Yo. Are we doin' this
or what?
Hajek: We are.
Meet my guys
at Whittier Air Strip.
30 minutes.
Air strip?
I thought this job was local.
It's not.
That a problem?
Uh, yeah,
that's a problem.
I travel with
three suitcases minimum.
It requires precision
to look this good.
Tough. I'm paying you to drive,
not to play dress up.
So get your ass
to the Air Strip
or look good in a coffin.
[Cellphone clicks]
We got to call it off.
What's the problem?
Once we're in the air,
no backup, no surveillance.
Things go sideways,
we're completely on our own.
Plus, we'll have no idea
where they're going.
It's not worth the risk.
I'm pulling the plug.
Uh, wait. Hold on. The pilot
has to file a flight plan.
You could follow along
in the LAPD plane.
The paperwork to get that
authorized will take all day.
And you're wheels up
in an hour.
I mean, I can get a private jet
there in 45 minutes.
Also, what kind of caviar
do you guys like?
I'll just get
an assortment.
[Cellphone beeps]
[Police radio chatter]
[Tires screech]
♪
[Door opens]
[Chains rattling]
♪
Hello, John.
Rosalind.
You look good. Happy.
Would you say
that's job satisfaction?
Or Bailey?
I'd say
it's seeing justice served.
He's such a boy scout.
John Nolan.
Megan Suriel.
I assume you've been briefed
on our security arrangements.
I have.
Let's go.
You know,
I follow Bailey on Instagram.
Oh, I love that cake
she made this morning.
And Luna, too.
She is getting good on a horse.
Oh, and Lucy's
little friend Tamara...
she is doing so well
at SMC.
Am I supposed to applaud
that you can use social media?
Or are you hoping
I'll be unsettled
that you're name-dropping people
I care about?
I think it's the only
party trick she's got.
I was so disappointed
Lucy decided not to testify.
I was really looking forward
to seeing her again...
revisiting
our favorite song.
Will you please send her
my love?
No.
[Tires squeal]
♪
Yo. Nice ride.
You're late.
Yeah, well, our quickie
wasn't so quick.
Where's Dayvion?
Flaked.
That ain't like him.
That's exactly like him.
Hajek's pissed.
We had to scramble
to get a replacement.
That's Sway.
Hi, sexy.
I'm Sava.
What's up?
Jake.
We got a lot of gear.
It's a big job.
Mm-hmm. Are you gonna
finally tell us what it is?
When we're airborne. First...
Cellphones.
Mm.
Lyon: You'll get them back
when it's over.
Can't risk
operational security.
You hear that, baby?
We're in
the big leagues now...
using terms like
"operational security."
[Chuckles]
Get in the damn plane.
♪
You heard the man.
Get in the damn plane.
♪
They're boarding.
How's that jet coming?
It's almost here.
[Cellphone chimes]
Hajek's crew just filed
their flight plan.
Where are they going?
Vegas.
[Siren wails,
indistinct conversations]
[Sighs]
Hey, Beth.
Wondered if I'd run into you.
Wesley. Did I hear you're
joining the D.A.'s office?
Next week.
I'm here defending my last case
before the transition.
[Metal detector beeping]
I was shocked to hear
you're representing
Rosalind Dyer.
Thought corporate law
was your thing.
Corporate law
is my dad's thing.
I need to pave
my own way.
Well, representing
the most brutal serial killer
in L.A.'s history... that'll
certainly put you on the map.
This is me.
I would wish you luck,
but, uh...
I hope your client
rots in hell.
Well, you're not alone.
Crap, I'm late.
Uh, take the stairs.
The elevators are a nightmare.
Thanks.
[Elevator bell dings]
The package
is on the sixth floor.
We're shutting it down now.
[Police radio chatter]
Whoa. This area is secure.
You need to go back downstairs.
I'm Beth Veston,
attorney for Rosalind Dyer.
You can see your client
in the courtroom.
My client has
a lawful right
to appear in civilian clothing
at trial.
She gets changed, or you get
sued and I get a mistrial.
So spunky.
Don't you just love her.
That room right there
is for counseling clients.
She can change there.
I will be present.
What about attorney/client
privacy?
I'll close my ears.
Peel off and secure each door.
No one else
comes in this hall.
See you soon, John.
Get in there.
[Chains rattling]
Can't I sit?
You're gonna be
sitting all day.
Step back.
It's already
been searched.
She's just
doing her job.
[Sighs]
All right.
Get her dressed.
Well, aren't you
going to uncuff me?
Not all the way.
Your attorney can help you
get dressed.
I'll uncuff you in stages,
starting at the bottom.
[Chains rattling]
[Groaning]
♪
[Panting]
Did I do it?
Is she dead?
You did great.
Get her keys.
[Laughs]
♪
This is taking too long.
Sgt. Grey: Nolan, there's been
a credible bomb threat.
We're evacuating
the courthouse.
So I need you
to secure Rosalind
and put her back
on the prison transport.
[Alarm blaring]
It's Rosalind.
She's trying to escape.
[Girls Against Boys'
"Bullet Proof Cupid" plays]
[Coughing]
Rosalind is out of pocket.
She may be dressed as a deputy.
Repeat,
Rosalind has escaped.
We need to lock
this building down.
♪ If you see something
you could like ♪
♪
I have eyes on Dyer.
Red hair, Deputy uniform.
Repeat,
Rosalind Dyer is 45-32.
Woman:
Stay calm. Keep moving.
Nolan.
What's going on?
Stop that deputy!
[People screaming]
Give me your hands!
♪
♪ It's a lot more physical
right now ♪
[Sirens wailing]
♪ Everybody everywhy
♪
♪ It's gonna paralyze you
[Siren wailing]
♪
♪ Paralyze you
♪ When I step up and I pop it
now, can't nobody stop it now ♪
♪ All the girls be muggin',
jealous *
Nice guns.
Your friends
are so grumpy.
Ain't no one here to have fun.
It's a job.
That's what everyone
keeps saying.
Except so far,
it's just been
the world's lamest
bachelor party.
Yo, y'all gonna tell us
what this gig is or what?
You know
who Roman Krupka is?
Nope.
He imports H
for the Monarch Cartel.
So, the competition.
Something like that.
Krupka's paranoid,
doesn't trust computers,
never keeps
a written record.
The details of his operation
exist in one place...
"The Brain."
A man
named Leonard Madris.
[Scoffs] Ain't that
a little dangerous...
making one man the center
of your whole operation.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, it is.
That's why Madris is kept
under heavy guard.
Barely leaves
Krupka's compound.
But we received
a solid tip
that he's headed to Vegas
this weekend.
With his bodyguards?
Never goes
anywhere without them.
That's where
you come in.
You guys take out the guards
while I grab Madris.
And then we torture The Brain
for every detail.
[Scoffs]
And take over
the business.
Oh.
It sounds like we should be
getting paid more.
Mm-hmm.
Tough.
Like my mom used to say...
"You get what you get,
and you don't get upset."
Well, this seems a lot bigger
than we thought.
Yep.
[Elevator bell dings]
Sgt. Grey:
So, what are you doing here?
I thought you were on
maternity leave.
I was until "Jacqueline
the Ripper" escaped.
What can I do?
Are you sure? You're like
eleventy months pregnant.
Okay,
let me amend that.
What can I do that does not
involve leaving the station?
Rosalind's lawyer's
in the box.
Says she'll only talk
to Nolan.
Why don't you do
the interview with him?
It's a full house.
Rosalind mentioned them
by name.
We got protection units
for everyone else.
Oh, I know.
I said hi to the one
outside my house
as I was leaving.
And by the way,
love the shoes.
[Both chuckle]
Nolan: Hey.
What's this I hear
about a Golden Ticket?
Well, that hardly seems
important right now.
All I am saying is
welcome to the club.
Thank you.
You look like you're ready
to give birth at any moment.
Do you want to sit?
I will never be able
to get back up.
You know, I could ask Bailey
to call the firehouse,
have them bring in
a gurney,
just so at least
you could lie down?
You had me at...
"do the job from bed."
I'll do it.
I saw Bailey in the break room.
Come on, Tamara.
Let's get some snacks.
We are going to be here
for a while.
Wesley knows
the lawyer.
Really?
A little.
We went to high school together.
Our families move
in the same circles.
Meaning... she's rich?
Beyond.
Any insight into why
she would do this?
Not really, no.
I mean, she was always
a little creepy.
Very bright,
but casually cruel.
I always chalked it up
to privilege.
Clearly,
Rosalind hired her
because she sensed Beth
would make a good acolyte.
Like Caleb.
Has she asked
for a lawyer?
No.
She's representing herself.
Let's go talk to her, then.
[Door opens]
Who are you?
Detective Harper.
And I am supposed to be
at home in bed right now,
so forgive me
if I skip the small talk.
You confessed
to killing Deputy Suriel.
Why'd you do that?
Rosalind talked about you
all the time.
The boy scout.
Honestly, it made me
a little jealous.
Look,
you clearly need help.
Tell us
where Rosalind is.
We'll push for you
to get sentenced
to a psychiatric hospital.
I'm not crazy.
I'm special.
Rosalind showed me that.
[Scratching]
What are you doing?
I'm supposed to
tell you something.
People are gonna die.
[Chuckles]
People are gonna die,
and you can't save them.
[Chuckles]
[Doorbell rings]
Can I help you?
Yes.
Your daughter sent me.
♪
[Crying]
[Crying] Help me!
[Clatters]
♪
[Cellphone chimes]
Look at this.
No way.
What?
Rosalind Dyer
just escaped.
Wisco: I'm glad we're not
in L.A. tonight.
That chick gives me nightmares.
Yeah, but it'd be
the perfect night to run wild,
'cause the cops will totally be
distracted looking for her.
How long till we land?
15 minutes.
Plenty of time.
For what?
Mile high club, baby.
I never thought
you'd ask.
How could this happen?
I don't know.
But every law enforcement agency
in Southern California
is on it, okay?
She won't be out long.
D-Did...
Uh, did she have help?
Another apprentice.
Like Caleb?
I mean...
Stop, okay?
Stop.
We can't worry
about that right now.
If your head is not 100%
in the game,
it'll get you killed.
You're right. I-I know.
I just... It's... I'm fine.
I-I can do this. No.
No, you're not.
I'm pulling the plug
as soon as we land.
Uh...
No.
Look, the stakes
are too high.
This is our one chance
at Madris.
The news threw me for a second,
but I'm...
I'm fine.
I can do this.
[Knock on door]
Yo, finish up.
We're landing.
[Breathes deeply]
Okay.
Lucy, if you change your mind,
you just say the word.
I will.
Okay?
Mm-hmm.
Let's go.
Wait.
What?
We're supposed to be
hooking up in here.
What?
[Sighs]
♪
Okay.
Um... that's good.
Yeah.
Let's do this.
♪
♪ Luck be a lady tonight
♪ Luck, if you've ever been
a lady to begin with ♪
♪ Luck be a lady tonight
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
♪ Luck be a lady tonight
[Slot machine dinging]
♪
[Slot machines beeping]
Room keys.
Wisco and I are on
either side of you.
Sway's across the hall.
We have some time,
so rest up.
Who sleeps in Vegas?
We're hitting the clubs.
No. You're staying close,
and you're staying sharp.
Jake!
We're on the move
at first light.
Jake!
Hey, girl.
Oh,
don't "hey, girl" me.
You weren't even
gonna look at me?
Didn't I tell you
the next time I saw you
I'd light that greasy hair
of yours on fire?
[Sighs]
You lost a lot of weight, huh?
Oh, hey. Hello?
Back off.
You must be the new skank.
[Chuckles]
Who are you calling
a skank?
Aah!
You better get
the hell out of here.
If I see you again,
I'm gonna rip
this janky-ass hairpiece
out of your head.
Hmm?
That's enough.
What? You want me
to let her go?
Please.
[Breathing heavily]
Psycho.
She's cute.
You two need to keep
a low profile.
The last thing we want
is for you to get arrested
over some B.S.
with an ex.
Yo, we'll be on
our best behavior.
Scout's honor.
Mm, screw that.
We are going to hit
the casino
and see if we can get lucky
three times in one day.
Hm?
♪ Dream big
and never change up ♪
♪ Flexin' on my haters, goin'
places, changing time zones ♪
♪ You can hate, I'mma let you
hate and get my shine on ♪
Tim:
Mind if we sit in?
Lopez:
It's a free country.
♪ Hit the club and I flex,
you flex, I flex, you flex ♪
♪ Hit the gram and I flex,
you flex, I flex ♪
Target's Leonard Madris.
Madris knows where everything
in Roman Krupka's operation
is buried...
and everyone.
Where is he? I'll have
Vegas P.D. pick him up.
They haven't told us.
We make our move first thing
in the morning.
We won't know anything
until we're en route.
What happened
with Rosalind?
She hired
a psychopath lawyer
who helped her kill a deputy
and escape.
I knew it.
Another Caleb.
You need to protect Tamara.
Already on it.
She's at the station,
and we have protection details
on everyone we think
Rosalind might even think
about going after.
Are you sure
you're up for this?
If you need to pull
the rip cord, I understand.
She's solid.
Okay.
I'll contact Vegas P.D.,
and with any luck, they'll get
a location on Madris tonight
so we can snatch up your crew
before bullets start flying.
What happens if we don't
catch him in time?
We have to be creative.
Remember,
our priority is saving lives,
even if that means
we lose Madris.
Let's go.
That's it for me.
You won all that
just now?
Yeah.
Can you help me?
If you let me keep some.
Eh...
I got something.
I found an article
Beth published
in her school's
law review.
And she argues that criminality
is a construct that changes
based on the prevailing
social mores of the culture.
Sounds pretentious.
I don't entirely disagree.
Mm. Towards the end,
she defends cannibalism.
Ooh. Okay.
Well, she lost me there.
Morally flexible.
Just Rosalind's type.
I get what Rosalind saw in Beth
and what she needed from her,
but what does Beth
get out of this?
Tamara: Love?
She's infatuated
with Rosalind?
Maybe.
Nolan: I think you're gonna want
to see this.
They've been scrubbing security
footage from the courthouse.
This BMW was parked
by the south exit.
It's registered
to Nicole Veston.
Beth's mom?
Okay, so she borrowed
the car for the day?
No. Beth's car is still parked
at the courthouse.
So she left it there
for Rosalind.
Probably had
a change of clothes
and a burner phone
ready to go.
We don't think
the mom is in on it, do we?
No, no.
Beth hates her parents.
It's more likely
she used their car to hurt them.
Anybody I ever knew
who hated their parents
were also scared
of them.
That is what she's getting
out of this relationship.
Rosalind's gonna kill her
parents for her.
Man: Go, go, go!
Secure the perimeter.
[Police radio chatter]
♪
Bodies!
She cleaned out the safe.
Sir.
[TV beeps]
Hello, John.
Oh, it really was nice
to see you happy this morning.
And I thought maybe you'd like
to see me happy, too.
Ah.
[Nicole groans]
Really is
like riding a bike.
Authorities urge caution
and calm tonight
as the city reels from the news
that Rosalind Dyer has escaped.
[TV shuts off]
They don't know anything
we don't.
[Remote clatters]
Yeah.
Ugh,
my head is killing me.
You're really good at this,
you know?
The whole
undercover thing.
Thank you.
Uh, do you mind if I take
the first shower?
No, it's fine.
Hey, you hungry?
Yes. I would get some
French fries if you're ordering.
Yeah. O-Okay.
Um... fries.
[Shower running]
♪
Man: All even here
in the late-going 89th minute.
2-2.
[TV shuts off]
The water pressure
is epic.
And I'm totally taking
one of these robes.
Wait.
That's not stealing, right?
No, no. They'll just
charge it to Hajek.
Then we should take two.
[Chuckles]
What?
Do you want
to talk about it?
About what?
The airplane bathroom.
Your apartment.
Look, I-I don't know.
Call me crazy, but it just
doesn't feel like pretend.
Uh...
It's an intimate act.
I mean,
we'd have to be dead inside
for it to not trigger
something, right?
It... It's basic biology.
Okay, so...
So you're saying
it's not a big deal?
Doesn't mean anything?
Right? I...
[Cellphone ringing]
Yo.
Lopez: It's me.
Can you talk?
Yeah. I'm just alone with Lucy
in the hotel room.
Uh-oh.
What do you got?
Las Vegas P.D. got a location
on Madris.
We're mobilizing with LVPD...
unless you think you need us.
No. We should be good
until morning.
When we get Madris,
we're coming back
to grab Hajek's crew.
All right.
We'll be ready. Good luck.
Don't do anything
I wouldn't do.
They get a line
on Madris?
Yeah.
Good. Okay. Uh,
I'm gonna blow-dry my hair.
Otherwise, it'll be crazy
in the morning.
[Blow dryer running]
[Knock on door]
Melanie: Hey, Jake.
Hey, Jake.
I know you're in there.
[Grunts]
[Breathing heavily]
Hey, buddy.
This girl says you're not Jake.
[Zip tie creaks]
Go get her.
[Blow dryer running]
[Grunting]
Don't kill her yet.
No, you got this
all wrong.
Chick hasn't seen me
in forever.
I lost weight.
So what?
She said you guys hooked up
three weeks ago,
you had quite the gut.
[Punches landing in distance,
Wisco grunting]
[Melanie screams]
[Grunting]
Are you okay?
[Groans] I'll live.
Hands behind your back!
Do it now!
[Zip tie creaks]
[Grunts]
Hands behind your back.
[Zip tie creaks]
Oh, gosh. Remind me
not to take a guy out
while I'm wearing
a robe.
I showed him
the entire world just now.
♪
Rosalind's only been out
for 12 hours
and three people
are dead.
This isn't your fault.
[Sighs]
Well, I was the one
that pushed
to try her
for Caleb's crimes.
She was already gonna spend
the rest of her life in prison.
No. Y-You wanted to give
Caleb's victims closure.
Yeah. But I also wanted
the glory of trying that case.
Now I got to live
with that.
Ah. Go home.
Get some sleep.
There's a police escort
waiting for you downstairs.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna finish
this bottle.
[Chuckles]
Good night. Go easy. Yeah.
See you.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, Chris.
Yeah?
When you see Lucy tonight...
tell her I'm sorry.
Yeah. I will.
♪
Hey, it's me.
I-I know you're not
checking your messages.
You probably don't even have
your phone with you.
But, uh, I wanted to call
and say I'm thinking about you,
and, uh, I can't wait
until you're home.
Please, just, uh, call me
the second you hear this.
[Cellphone beeps]
Hey.
[Engine starts]
♪
Wake up,
sleeping beauty.
Did we catch her?
No.
But I am here
to take you home regardless.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Not a great start
to maternity leave.
Well, taking it easy
is not your strong suit.
No,
but I have other gifts.
So many other gifts.
Here's your first lesson
in self-care...
You ready?
Step one... leave the station.
Mm.
Is step two eat ice cream
for breakfast?
How'd you guess?
[Chuckles]
Bye, guys.
[Door closes]
Agent Garza just called.
A Porsche registered
to the Veston family
crossed the border
three hours ago.
So Rosalind is gone?
It's safe for us all
to go home?
That's right.
[Cellphone chimes]
Sweet.
Lucy just texted.
She's headed back
to the apartment.
Well, it's been real.
I wouldn't want to hide from a
crazed killer with anyone else.
Let's go find my wife.
We'll give you a ride home.
So how long do you think
Rosalind will lay low?
If she's smart, forever.
She sticks her head up
even for a second,
the feds will find her.
She won't stop killing.
She can't.
As long
as she keeps quiet,
takes people
that won't be missed,
she could fly under the radar
for a very long time.
She's not that modest.
Getting caught was the best
thing that ever happened to her.
She wants us to know
exactly what she's capable of.
On that terrifying note
[sighs] let's go home.
All right.
Good work today.
Not good enough.
Hey, some days
are like that.
I'm sure this is the furthest
thing from your mind,
but have you decided
what you're gonna do
with your Golden Ticket?
Yes, I have.
Woof woof?
Very funny, but no.
Detective?
Also no.
Training officer.
[Nat and Alex Wolff's "Glue"
plays]
[Laughs]
I knew it,
and I admire it.
Of course, everyone else is
gonna give you endless grief...
Of course.
[Laughs]
But I know you're doing it
to give back.
And that's noble
as hell.
If I want to be part
of the change,
I need to put my money
where my mouth is.
Literally.
Do you know how much
forensic techs can make?
Yes. I...
[Laughs]
I'll schedule your T.O. exam
as soon as possible.
Well, maybe give me
a couple days to study up.
I've been
a little busy.
Will do. Right.
I cannot wait to get out
of these clothes.
Yeah. I'm not gonna miss
that hairdo.
I kinda like yours.
[Chuckles]
Thank you
for walking me up.
Yeah. No problem.
I guess this is it.
Tomorrow, we are back
to being us.
Right.
And everything
that happened undercover
we will just
leave behind.
Right.
Yeah. What happens undercover
stays undercover.
[Both chuckle]
You know, in a sense,
since we haven't been debriefed,
we're still undercover.
♪ I swear I said your name
I-I guess you're right.
Mm-hmm.
♪
♪ At this point,
no one believes you're real ♪
Do you want to come in?
♪ I swear I said your name
30 times tonight ♪
I-I... I shouldn't.
♪ At this point,
no one believes you're real ♪
♪
♪ I swear I said your name
♪ Just make it sound good
♪ Make it sound good
Can I make you a drink?
I'm good.
♪ Make it sound good
[Chuckles]
♪ Make it sou...
Oh. Chris.
I didn't know
that you were gonna be here.
Tim and I were ju...
No.
Wait.
He still has a pulse.
[Cellphone beeping]
Yeah, this is
Sergeant Tim Bradford.
I need an ambulance at 2733
Elmhurst Drive, Apartment 610.
[Voice breaking]
Tim.
[Cellphone rings]
One sec.
Hello?
Hello, John.
Rosalind?
I have to be quick.
We're refueling.
But I just wanted to make sure
someone checked on Lucy.
What have you done?
♪
[Cellphone beeps]
- Captions by VITA...