Previously on "The Rookie"
and "The Rookie: Feds"...
Need a ride?
John Nolan.
People are gonna
start to talk.
You set the bar pretty high
the last time you were here.
There he is!
[Engine revs]
Hey, what's going on?
John, this is my training agent,
Carter Hope.
That's not... I'm not...
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
Do you want to get dinner
sometime?
I owe it to Chris to end things
the right way with him.
Ask me again. After.
What's going on?
I need you to give me
your playbook.
Are you breaking up
with me?
So, did you have something
you were gonna ask me?
Do you want to go out
on a date?
Yeah. I do.
[Lau.ra X Nova's
"Get Creative" plays]
♪ I was overthinking,
are we linking ♪
♪ I'm addicted,
can you fix it? ♪
♪ Hot top with
a feminine flavor ♪
♪ Pop up fresh,
ready to be taken ♪
♪ I be making
lime and lemons ♪
♪ Get the sugar
for the tasting ♪
♪ Sit back,
watch me get creative ♪
♪ I was...
♪ Overthinking
♪ Are we linking
♪ I'm addicted
♪ Can you fix it?
♪ Hot top with
a feminine flavor ♪
♪ Pop up fresh,
ready to be taken ♪
♪ I be making...
♪ Lime and lemons
♪ Get the sugar
for the tasting ♪
♪ Sit back,
watch me get creative ♪
♪ Get creative,
get creative ♪
[Cellphone buzzing]
Oh.
[Cellphone clicks]
Hi. I'm almost there.
No.
No... No, you're not.
No, I'm not. Sorry.
Um, are you?
No! Uh...
Does this restaurant
have a dress code?
Uh... no.
I mean, you could wear
cargo shorts if you wanted.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean, what does it matter,
as long as you're comfortable?
Nice try.
That was clearly a test.
[Laughs]
And you should know better
than to test the master.
[Scoffs]
What are you wearing?
Yeah, um,
I don't know yet,
but I do have
a lot of outfits
that I am not
going to wear, so...
Well, we are
running low on time.
Traffic's getting ugly.
Yeah, totally.
I... It's silly.
I just need
to make a decision.
Uh, yes.
The green dress.
It is decided.
Great.
Well,
I-I'll see you soon.
Okay. Bye.
♪
No. Oh, my God.
[Soft piano music playing]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
It's... It's good bread.
Yeah, it's... it's such
a nice assortment.
Mm-hmm.
The breadsticks... Yeah.
♪
[Breathes deeply]
[Chuckles]
What did you order, again?
Oh, the sea bass.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. It's good.
[Chuckles]
I almost ordered the sea bass.
Oh, cool.
Mm-hmm.
♪
Why is this so weird?
We've eaten together
literally hundreds of times.
Because, you know,
our other meals
only ever held the promise
of being shot at afterwards,
you know?
And not, like,
naked time.
Naked time?
[Both laugh]
Please. I mean, we've seen
plenty of naked people
after we ate.
Yeah, that's not...
No, no, no.
I know. I know. I know.
I-I feel like I might...
I... I might just need you
to reset your expectations
a little bit.
You're not gonna
see me naked for...
a while.
[Chuckles]
I mean, I don't want
to rush into that.
I wanna
take things slow.
Go on this date,
maybe a second date,
have our first real kiss.
I just don't think we should
jump into bed together,
just because we know
each other so well, right?
I mean, do you...?
No, I...
Agreed.
Yeah?
[Engine revs]
[Door closes]
♪
Are you worried someone from
the station is gonna walk in?
What?
You are.
No, I...
Wow.
What are the odds?
Um...
[Pots and pans crash,
indistinct shouting]
What was that?
Uh, restaurants can be
a stressful environment.
Chef: Get out of my kitchen!
Cook: Yeah, yeah.
Get out of my kitchen now!
Goodbye!
Should we do something?
See ya!
It'll blow over.
You don't like my rules,
you can get the hell
out of my restaurant!
Knife.
LAPD!
Drop the knife.
Call 911.
Tim: Drop it.
[Knife clatters]
Tim:
Get on your stomach.
Hands behind your back.
Lucy: Are you okay?
Okay, just put some
pressure on it.
[Handcuffs clicking,
spectators murmuring]
What are the chances someone
from the station walks in now?
[Sirens wailing]
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
So, get a croissant?
Did you happen to make...
Ohh.
Two sugars.
Thank you.
I got you a croissant
from the place that you like.
Thanks.
You know, Jack slept
through the night.
He did?
Mm-hmm.
He's been doing that
a lot lately.
Just get to the point.
[Inhales slowly]
I thought it might be time
for us to think about
talking about
having another kid.
[Laughing]
Okay. Um...
Okay.
I mean, it's not that funny,
but, um...
I-I-I know
that it's a lot, but...
I mean, we want Jack
to have a sibling, right?
[Sighs]
Do we?
I mean, I-I grew up
with four brothers,
and I had to fight
for everything...
food, clothes,
my own room.
I never had a hot shower
until I moved out.
Well, I grew up alone,
my family oppressively
fixating on every breath,
and being an only child
was lonely.
I don't know,
maybe for us,
it could be
somewhere in the middle?
Can we think about it?
[Sighs]
[Car horn honks]
[Telephones ringing,
indistinct conversations]
Hey.
[Chuckles]
Okay, we can't
deny the facts.
We were both at the restaurant.
It's in the police report.
And for all we know,
the witness reports mention
the fact that we were
sitting together. Yeah.
This is not strange.
I mean, coworkers eat together.
It's a thing.
At the most romantic restaurant
in town?
Right.
Well, I mean,
we could come clean.
Are you ready for that?
Are you ready for
Smitty's commentary on us dating
or the "oohs"
every time we walk into
the roll call room
together?
Or we could lie.
[Scoffs]
Okay, I have an idea.
I heard from a C.I.
that there were
drugs coming out
of the kitchen.
And... And you asked me
to join as backup.
Right. Like a soft
undercover infiltration.
Not bad.
Thank you.
Nolan: Morning.
Uh, yeah, we were there,
uh, investigating a tip,
and then this whole other
crime popped off.
Yeah, Lucy's C.I. was convinced
they were dealing drugs.
Mm-hmm.
What?
Nothing.
Celina: No, you're doing good.
You're doing good.
[Laughs] Sorry.
Those two have gotten close
lately, haven't they?
You think something's
going on with them?
Oh, I'm sure he's just
being nice to the new rookie.
Boss wants to see you guys.
Have a safe one.
♪
I think you know how I feel
about coworkers dating.
♪
When I started,
no one thought much of it.
But things have changed.
We're now more aware of how
power dynamics can skew things.
Even the most innocent
of relationships
can become a distraction.
Hey, trust me, I get it.
We spend 12 hours a day together.
Feelings are bound to develop.
But we can't afford
even a hint of impropriety.
We couldn't agree more.
Good. Look...
I don't want to be the old guy
interfering with people's lives,
especially their love life,
but this whole Aaron and
Celina situation has me worried.
The Aaron and Celina situation.
Aaron's barely out
of long sleeves.
Half the town still thinks
he's a killer.
And Celina's making progress.
She needs to focus
on getting through
her probationary period.
Will you talk to them?
Yes, of course we...
Yes.
Not a problem.
Thank you.
♪
Oh, the irony.
Are you gonna
talk to Aaron?
About his love life?
Can't wait.
[Chuckles]
When are you gonna
talk to Celina?
I can't tell her
not to date a cop.
That is
so hypocritical.
Oh. I'm gonna
get Nolan to do it.
That's cheating.
Mm-hmm.
Alright, so the 529
has a lot of advantages.
Alright? I mean, the tax savings
are substantial.
Yes, but you have to
use it for college.
Oh. What, you don't think
Leah's going to college?
Oh, no, no,
she is going to college.
I will make her
go to college.
But what if she gets a full ride
and all of our money is tied up
and we've got nothing
to spend it on?
Uh, I just don't think that
we should assume
she's gonna get that much
in financial aid.
Okay, the kid is a genius.
She is already talking.
She did not say,
"I love you, Mom."
I heard it.
She's five months old!
Okay, you know what?
You just... You just
don't understand her
in the way that I do.
We have a unique bond.
Please take a seat. We'll be
with you in just a few minutes.
Thank you.
We'll talk
about it later.
Mm-hmm.
[Police radio chatter]
So, you and Aaron have been
hanging around a lot lately.
Yeah.
Yeah, he seemed like
a party boy at first,
but, you know,
he's got a lot of depth.
Yeah, I-I agree.
Mm-hmm.
And just so you know, um...
dating other cops
can be tricky.
And as a rookie,
it's probably best
that you just don't.
Okay, wait.
Are you telling me who
I can and cannot date?
Isn't that
crossing a line?
No. Well,
I mean, that...
That's...
Yeah... This...
That's not what
I'm trying to do.
That's what
it sounds like.
Okay. Uh...
Y-Your first year as... as
a rookie can be overwhelming.
I am just trying to
protect you.
You know people talk, right?
And cops talk more.
It's 2022.
I mean, I-I think we've moved on
from men in power
telling us
how to live our lives.
People can say what they want.
I couldn't care less.
So you... you
are dating him?
None of your business. Sir.
Right.
♪
You and Celina dating?
Sir, that's
a personal question,
and you have said
on numerous occasions
that this is
a personal-life-free zone.
It is.
But here we are.
Yes or no?
Sir, with all due respect,
would it matter if we were?
Cops date all the time.
I mean,
you were married to a cop.
Look, if... if I was in her
chain of command, I'd get it.
You know, people would wonder
if I was making decisions
based on
our relationship.
They'd wonder if she was
dating me under duress.
Whew!
It would be a nightmare, man.
One of us would probably
have to transfer
to a whole
different station.
Forget I asked.
[Sighs]
Well, if we ever
finish up here,
maybe we can
grab breakfast
before I head over
to the community center.
It is my day off.
I'm getting a massage.
You sure?
I mean, we're doing a big
community cleanup initiative.
James: Whoever brings in
the most litter
gets a prize.
[Ominous music plays]
You have got to be
kidding me.
Oh, I thought it
was a cute idea.
♪
What?
That third person in line,
that is Todd Shelf.
You know him?
He is
a serial bank robber.
[Clears throat]
Okay, well, m-maybe he's, uh,
just here
to make a deposit.
No.
He's here to
rob this bank.
I need you to say
the word "grout."
The bank is
about to be robbed.
G-R-O-U-T.
Okay, grout.
Gender, race, over,
under, task.
It's how to quickly
describe suspects
in a way that
cops will understand.
Try it on Todd.
Okay, um...
Male, white,
black jacket, dark pants,
and his task is
killing us.
Close enough.
♪
[Sighs]
There by the door.
Number two?
Also male, white, black jacket,
uh, gray pants,
and taking out security.
[Sighs] Todd always runs
a three-man crew.
There's someone
I haven't made yet,
but we are
running out of time.
Go outside
and wait for the cavalry.
No, no. I'm not... I'm not
leaving you.
But you will,
because you know
that I have got this.
♪
[Clears throat]
[Door opens]
♪
Marjorie: Yeah, that whole thing
was finalized by end of day.
I'll be with you
in just a moment.
I am Detective Nyla Harper.
Your bank is about to be robbed.
I need you to hit
the silent alarm now.
[Gun cocks]
♪ One of these days
♪ Mr. Opportunity gonna be
knocking on my door ♪
Bank robbery!
Everybody down!
[Woman screams]
Everybody stays calm,
everybody lives.
On the floor, now!
♪ I'll be a spectator
in an audience of whores ♪
Cellphones on the ground!
♪ Run until I fall
♪ One of these days,
I'll win the lottery ♪
Now!
Alright, no one moves,
no one gets hurt.
Hurry up!
♪ I'm gonna get myself a job
Back away
from the window!
♪ One of these days
Get down!
♪ They're gonna stop the world
♪ And I won't even care
Fill it!
No dye bags or you're dead.
♪ I'm gonna finally
believe in God ♪
♪ Any day now
Get up!
Safe deposit room, now.
Come on. Let's go.
♪ One of these days
♪ Any day now
Come on!
Silent alarm, now.
♪ Any day now
[Police radio chatter]
You're mad at me.
No, sir.
Look, Celina, I would not
be doing my job
as your
training officer
if I didn't tell you
the realities of the LAPD.
Dispatch: 7-Adam-15, 7-Adam-20,
and 7-Adam-100 to monitor.
2-11 bank, in progress.
Manually activated
hold-up alarm
at 71414 Wilshire at Westwood.
More to follow.
Code 3?
Yeah, but we shut it down
two blocks out.
Don't let them know
we're coming.
Surround them
in silence.
Copy.
[Sirens wail]
♪
[Quietly] Why aren't you
doing anything?
Right now, they are just
going for property.
It's stuff.
Stuff that is insured.
They're bank robbers.
You're a cop.
I am outnumbered
and outgunned.
Patrol will take them off
when they go outside.
Roger: Alright.
Give me the money!
Yeah, I call BS
on that.
What are you doing?
No! Put that away!
Citizen's arrest.
Drop your gun!
[Gunfire]
[Spectators screaming]
♪
Give me your belt.
[Gunfire, screaming continues]
♪
[Groans]
[Tires screech]
[Gunfire, indistinct shouting]
7-Adam-100.
We're on scene
covering the A-side.
What are you doing here?
Nyla and I
were inside.
Cops!
♪
She's still in there.
There's at least two suspects.
I have the GROUT.
All units, stand by for
robbery suspect descriptions.
Suspect One,
Todd Shelf,
male, white,
black jacket, dark pants.
Suspect Two, male, white,
black jacket, gray jeans.
♪
Hey, everybody out!
Up! Out the door!
Come on!
Come on! Let's go!
Hurry up! Move it!
Let's go! Right now!
Come on! Let's go!
Come on! Out the door!
Come on! Move!
Move It! Let's go!
Outside!
♪
[Sirens wailing]
Move, move!
♪
Get down!
The suspect's headed
north on foot.
We need backup
and air support.
Let's go.
♪
Come on!
Move!
[Car horn honks,
indistinct shouting]
♪
[Engine starts]
Roger: Wait!
Move, move!
Get down!
Stop! Stop!
[Grunts]
♪
[Exhales deeply]
[Siren wailing]
There he is.
Suspect One sighted
westbound on Redondo.
♪
Look out!
[Engine revs]
[Tires screech]
Hang on.
♪
[Tires screeching]
Whoa!
[Police radio chatter]
[Car hissing]
[Celina coughing]
You good?
Yeah.
[Engine revving,
tires screeching]
Pilot: Airship-3 on scene. No
sign of Suspect One's Mustang.
7-Adam-100. On foot,
searching for Suspect Two.
Send additional units
to my north and east.
We'll keep searching
this grid.
Dispatch: Copy, 7-Adam-100.
[Helicopter blades whirring]
♪
[Police radio chatter]
Harper,
status of victims?
Well,
our cowboy's arm's a mess.
With any luck,
he will never use a gun again.
And the citizen just landed
at the hospital.
She's gonna need surgery.
Leave it to a good guy with
a gun to really screw things up.
Thanks to him, we have
two suspects in the wind.
Actually, I'm pretty sure
it is three.
Todd always works
a three-man crew,
so there is someone
that I did not identify.
Outside the bank?
Maybe a lookout.
Or one of the customers
who was just laying low
in case they needed
to engage.
Nolan, heard you
destroyed another shop.
Let a suspect
get away?
Oh,
that's not on me.
It turns out bullets and engines
don't go together.
Mm! It is a poor craftsman
who blames his tools.
Yeah, you got me there.
If you were driving that car,
it wouldn't have
dared gotten shot.
Exactly.
Is this your new rookie?
Mm-kay, girl.
Do you know how lucky you are
to have this man as a T.O.?
Mm-hmm. It's because I have
Jupiter in my second house.
Shut up. I do, too.
Oh, my God. My solar return...
Simone, focus.
Grey:
How's Garza doing?
We'll talk.
It's too soon to tell.
Well,
I'm praying for him.
Thanks. We all are. Yeah.
You're here to help?
Yes, I am.
We did a quick dive into
your crew leader, Todd Shelf,
and found
something interesting...
a wire payment
to an alias two days ago.
For how much?
Half-a-million dollars.
You think he was paid
to rob a bank?
Which is crazy
because, most times,
the money comes from
the bank robbery, not for it.
Yeah, but that explains
something that has
been bugging me.
Todd's crew is suspected in
at least six bank robberies
over the past several years,
and in every one of those,
they have only gone
for the cash.
Until today, when they hit
the safe deposit boxes.
How many did they open?
17.
Likely trying to hide what they
were actually looking for.
We need a list
of the owners.
Something in
one of those boxes
was worth
half-a-million dollars.
♪
Stop!
[Car alarms blaring,
dogs barking]
[Bullets ricocheting]
[Car horn honks]
[Tires screech]
[Bone cracks]
[Grunts]
Ahh!
[Groaning]
7-Adam-100.
Shots fired.
In foot pursuit of Suspect Two.
600 block of Kenmore.
Hey,
we need to end this
before someone gets caught
in the crossfire.
I'm down.
What's the plan?
Alright.
You stay low.
I'm gonna distract him,
then you shoot him.
That's a terrible plan.
Trust me.
[Mid-tempo music playing
through headphones]
[Car alarm blips]
[Grunts]
[Gunfire]
♪
[Music continues
through headphones]
Drive!
[Gasps]
I said, drive!
Suspect, drop the gun,
exit the vehicle, now!
Back off or she's dead!
[Siren wails]
[Siren quiets]
Post up, block the streets.
He's got a hostage.
7U1, Suspect Two has
taken a hostage
inside a vehicle
at 9321 Kenmore.
Mobilize Metro
and alert command.
♪
Rear-view mirror.
Tilt it down.
Stop. Now side view.
Stop.
I said back off!
I will kill her, I swear to God!
You don't
have to do that, okay?
Let's just take
a big breath.
Screw that! Clear the street
and let us go, now!
I can't do that,
and you know it.
[Groans]
What should I do?
Have dispatch
RMS the address.
Let's get a background
on everyone who lives here,
see if we can get
a cellphone
for the woman
he's got hostage.
Sure this guy's safe deposit box
was the target?
Simone:
17 boxes were opened.
Only one belonged to
a known hacker
on everybody's watch list,
so no doubt he's got something
juicy hidden in there.
He's running to somewhere.
Taylor Barnes.
We have a few questions
for you.
Yeah, um,
I'm kind of busy.
Where you going?
Um, vacation.
You're taking your goldfish
with you?
She gets lonely.
Mr. Barnes,
we know you have
a safe deposit box
at Bank of Los Angeles.
And we believe the bank
was robbed
because of
what was in it.
But you already know that,
which is why
you're running
for your life.
What?
That's... That's crazy.
I-I don't know what you're
talking about.
Mr. Barnes.
If you're in danger,
we can protect you.
Really?
Yes.
Sweetie, we can.
But you have to tell us
what was in the box.
♪
A list...
of federal undercover assets
I hacked from the FBI.
I was negotiating with a guy
to buy it for $5 million,
but he figured out
where I was keeping it,
decided it would be cheaper
to steal it.
Who's the buyer?
[Gunshot]
[Groans]
Sniper!
♪
[Helicopter blades whirring]
[Police radio chatter]
♪
Remember this morning,
when dating in secret
was our biggest problem?
God, that feels like
a million years ago.
Yeah.
Did you talk to Aaron?
And?
He neither confirmed
nor denied.
But...?
But he pointed out that
it wouldn't be problematic
because he's not
her superior
and doesn't fall
in her chain of command.
Oh.
[Cellphone chimes]
I got our hostage's
phone number.
Her name is
Vanessa Greer.
[Cellphone rings]
It's the police.
Answer it.
On speaker!
[Cellphone clicks]
H-Hello?
Hi, Vanessa.
This is Sergeant Bradford.
You can call me Tim.
Try to stay calm.
We're gonna get you
out of there, okay?
I'm... I'm scared.
I know.
Enough!
I'm not negotiating,
Bradford!
Back everybody away
from the house and let us leave,
and then I'll drop her off
around the block.
You know
I can't let you leave.
Then I hope you brought
some body bags.
[Sobs]
Alright. Alright, listen.
Just give me 10 minutes.
I've got to get these cars
out of the street.
It's a parking lot out here.
You got 2 minutes!
Hang up.
Hang up!
You're not really gonna let him
drive away, are you?
No. I got a plan.
We need to get
that list back.
I assume you're
starting to
pull your undercover agents
from the field.
It's not that easy.
It's not just the agents
that are in jeopardy,
it's the C.I.s
that vouched for them.
For every cover blown,
multiple people die.
Detective Harper
have any luck
identifying
the third accomplice?
Not yet.
She and Lopez are still
scrubbing the bank footage.
Maybe I was wrong.
Maybe this time
it wa just the two guys.
There's gotta be another
bank robber. I trust your gut.
Well, so far,
no one stands out
as doing anything
out of the ordinary.
Not a teller
or a customer.
It's someone hiding
in plain sight.
We'll find them.
[Sighs]
Want to hear
something funny?
Yes, please.
This morning,
my husband told me
he's ready
to have another child.
Oh.
Oh, he's ready. Mm.
Okay,
that's good to know.
[Both chuckle]
He was an only child and wants
Jack to have a sibling.
And you grew up in a house full
of troublemaking brothers.
As much as I complain
about them,
it was fun
growing up in our house.
In between all the battles
and arguments,
it was a house
filled with love.
I'm not anti-siblings.
No, but you've finally gotten
your footing as a detective
and you're not ready
to hit pause again.
Exactly.
I get it.
[Cellphone rings]
Yeah?
You're kidding.
What?
T.I.D. found
a gun in the bank.
Found it where?
A potted plant
near the north wall.
Our mystery accomplice felt
the heat and ditched the gun.
Let's scroll back through video
and see who was near there.
No, I don't need to.
I know this video by heart now.
It was the woman
who got shot.
Control, I need the nearest unit
to head to Saint Stephens.
Our third suspect should be
coming out of surgery
any minute now.
♪
[Woman speaking indistinctly
over P.A.]
[Monitors beeping]
Man: Okay. I'll get on that.
[Muffled conversation]
♪
[Cellphone rings]
[Cellphone clicks]
Where are you?
At the hospital.
Just got out of surgery.
Have you been made?
Not yet.
But, look,
it's only a matter of time.
Did you get the list?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
it was in the box,
just like
the guy told you.
Is Roger with you?
We had to split up.
Last I heard,
the cops had him cornered
with a hostage.
He'll go down shooting,
which means we get
to keep his cut.
Yeah, and if he doesn't,
if they arrest him...
Won't matter. Only I know
the name of the buyer.
Good point. Call me
when you're clear, alright?
I'll let you know
where to meet up.
[Cellphones click]
♪
[Elevator dings]
Hi, we're looking for
the woman
that was shot
during the bank robbery?
[Winces, groans]
513.
Thank you. This way.
Oh.
♪
Call it in.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Suspect Three is in the wind.
I repeat,
♪
[Crying]
Are you
sure about this?
I'm sure he's gonna kill her
if we don't do something.
Where's my distraction?
It's ready
and waiting.
Alright. Ready?
Yeah.
Let's do this.
♪
[Crying]
[Engine starts]
Here we go.
Get ready to back out.
[Sirens wail]
Lucy:
Hey! Stop there!
Aaron: Cut him off!
Right here!
Get back!
What the hell?
Aaron: Hey! Back it up!
Back it up!
Turn around!
Back up.
You gotta back up, man.
You gotta back this up.
We need you to back it up.
Clear on out.
Come on! Back, back, back, back,
back, back, back, back.
Let's go!
Back it up, back it up.
Come on.
You, on the east side
of the street,
you need to back it up, too.
All personnel need to clear
the street. Let's go.
Back it up!
[Gasps]
Aaron: Back it up,
back it up.
♪
Keep going!
Yeah, come on!
Back it up, come on!
[Crying]
Shut up!
[Sirens wailing]
[Drill whirs]
♪
[Crying]
Here we go!
♪
[Static flares twice]
That's the signal.
Man: Go, go!
[Gas hisses]
[Both coughing]
♪
In the car!
You got no play here.
It's over. Throw out your gun,
give yourself up.
[Coughing]
♪
[Gun clatters]
[Screams]
You're working with
two other people.
What are their names?
[Handcuffs clicking]
Forget it.
I'm not ratting anybody out.
Aah!
Your buddy Todd
left you behind.
You're looking at
decades in prison
unless you give up
your partners.
Fine.
All units,
thanks to Sergeant Bradford,
we got the phone numbers
of the other two bank robbers
and we're tracking them.
Live updates will be sent
to your box.
Proceed with caution. These two
are armed and dangerous.
♪
[Engines starting]
[Helicopter blades whirring]
♪
Both of their cellphones
are still in this area.
Both haven't moved
in a few minutes.
Think they've
gone to ground?
No.
♪
Suspect Three's.
She must've bought
a new burner phone
and ditched this one.
7-Adam-15, we found
Suspect Three's burner phone.
Signal's been static
for about three minutes.
They're likely
still in the area.
♪
7-Adam-100, we've got
the other one, also dumped.
Signal static
for less than two minutes.
Given how slowly they were
moving beforehand,
I'd say they're
most likely on foot.
Yeah, which means
their first priority
is going to be
finding a clean car.
If you want a selection
to choose from,
I know where I'd go.
♪
[Car door closes
in distance]
[Car lock chirps]
♪
7-Adam-100, fourth floor is
clear, headed to five.
♪
[Exhales deeply]
New phone. Nice.
[Cellphone rings]
[Cellphone clicks]
Yeah?
We have the list,
but, uh, we got some heat on us,
so the price has gone up.
The hell
are you doing?
Try adding another zero.
Oh, my God.
Then we got a deal.
[Cellphone clicks]
Seriously?
Look, nothing has gone right
on this job.
We deserve every penny we can
squeeze out of these guys.
Hell yeah.
[Both laugh]
Oh!
♪
Maybe you were wrong.
[Seatbelts click]
[Engine starts,
tires screech]
[Engine revs]
[Tires screech]
♪
[Engines revving]
[Metal crunches]
[Metal creaking]
♪
[Tires squeal]
Okay, what's the protocol
here, Sarge?
Don't move.
Don't breathe.
[Metal creaking]
Ooh. Ohh.
Um...
you got a plan B?
Open the door, slowly.
Mm-hmm.
Climb out.
What about you?
We both can't get out
at the same time.
[Metal creaking]
Okay,
then you go first.
There's only room for one of us
to be a hero here,
and I outrank you.
Sir, with all due respect,
Lucy will kill me
if I let you die,
so I'm dead either way.
Get out of the shop,
Aaron!
♪
Yes, sir.
[Door screeching]
Oh...
♪
What are you doing?
I'm adding some ballast!
[Metal creaks]
It's your turn!
♪
[Crashing]
We don't have to pay
for that, do we?
7-Adam-100,
suspects fled
in a gray Dodge Ram,
last seen exiting
the parking structure
of 8th and San Pedro.
Copy that. We just heard
a loud crash a minute ago.
Yeah,
that was our shop.
We need transport back
to Mid-Wilshire.
Nolan. The truck.
♪
In the truck!
Show me your hands!
Clear.
♪
These are the two phones Nolan
and Tim found in the trash.
Maybe something on them
can help track Amy.
Our team will
turn them inside out.
Midnight shift's
been briefed.
BOLOs are out
county-wide.
The only question is,
is the exchange happening
in town or somewhere else?
My money is on here.
She's got a paper list
and she's gonna want cash.
And she can't get on an airplane
without being arrested.
Exactly.
Okay.
We'll keep working it
from our end.
I'll assign Nolan to liaison
between the two investigations.
Appreciate it.
♪
Well, I'm glad
you didn't die.
You owe me a redo
on our date.
It's what gave me
the will to live.
In my mind,
I'm hitting you right now.
That's good to know.
Wait, so,
what's this about?
It's okay,
just trust me.
Sir, I've been thinking
about your warning
that dating Aaron
could be bad for me.
Wait, that's what we're
talking to Nolan about?
M-My apologies. You were right.
It's none of my business.
Great, conversation over. No.
I want this behind us.
The truth is,
Aaron and I have been playing
Dungeons Dragons together.
That's why
we're so close.
You know, bonds formed
in the heat of battle.
It's just, like,
every once in a while.
But if I wanted to
date him, I would.
In fact, maybe I will.
Do you want to
go out tonight?
You know I'm
a Scorpio, right?
Oh, no. Forget it.
I-I can't do Scorpios.
But I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
♪ It's a feeling that boils
in my brain ♪
[Sighs]
Yeah, that's a deal breaker
for a lot of girls.
♪ But I'm not sure I'm able
♪ I'm wobbling out on the wire
♪ And the lights could go out
♪ With the break of a cable
You okay?
Hm.
It was a different
kind of day.
Yeah, that... that,
it was.
I'm really glad
you're okay.
Me, too.
But?
[Sighs]
There was a version of today
that ended bad for both of us,
and it got me thinking,
what would happen to Leah
if something
happened to us?
Okay, do we really have to have
this conversation right now?
Okay, um...
Alright, well, there's...
there's always my mom.
Mm.
Oh, come on.
She's not that bad.
Alright,
she is that bad,
but I turned out okay.
Okay, we will
cross her off the list.
Which leaves, uh...
Not Donovan. Um...
How about
my cousin Ginger?
Uh...
I haven't even
met her,
and you
roll your eyes
every time you read
her ClipTalk posts.
What about... my ex?
Then Leah would be
with the boys.
Yeah, I'm not having
your ex raise my daughter.
So then you see
our problem.
[Both sigh]
I know today
was a crazy day,
but did you get a chance
to think about
giving Jack a sibling?
I did.
Sounds like a no.
I can't do the whole thing
again right now.
The idea of feeling sick
and exhausted for the next year,
puking at crime scenes,
pumping at work...
No,
I-I totally get it.
But maybe we could revisit this
question in, say, six months?
Try two years.
[Knock on door]
♪ Even when everything is fine
♪ Hey, I've been falling apart
these days ♪
Hi.
Uh, sorry to drop by unannounced.
No, come in.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, um, we just...
We have something that
we would like to ask you,
both of you.
With all the drama today,
we've been thinking about
who would raise Leah
if something happened
to us.
Yet it turns out neither of us
trust anyone in our families.
But we do trust you.
You'd want us
to take Leah?
♪
Of course.
We'd... We'd love to.
I mean, first,
we'd be very sad
because you're dead, but...
[Laughter]
But then we'd raise her
like our own.
♪ Even when everything is fine
You're the richest people
we know.
Oh, I get it.
I get it.
♪ I've been falling apart
these days ♪
Tim: Treats of Vietnam.
[Chuckles]
That's where we ended up.
♪ Watching my heart
So, I guess this is
our official first date.
Mm, last night was,
for sure.
I mean, it's a better story
for the grandkids.
♪
We've got
grandkids now.
[Laughs]
Nice.
♪
Do not
break into that car.
What? What car?
Hey, moron!
♪
You know he's just going to
break into a car
in a different neighborhood.
Well, then some other cop
can arrest him.
♪ Round and round
♪ Circle the drain
♪ I'm going down
♪