Previously on "The Rookie"...
What?
My mom died.
Lopez:
Her name is Abril Rodas.
Her Sicarios hit
three competing gangs
at the same time
she cut down Elijah's crew.
Unlike La Fiera,
I kill only
when it's strategically advantageous.
I'll take everything away
from you until you say sorry
for taking
everything away from me.
Harper: Moses didn't kill
Quinlan's guys.
Elijah did,
to provoke a war.
[Suspenseful music plays]
Relax. If I wanted to kill you,
you'd be dead already.
This is amazing.
I put in all this work,
and you're just
handing me your badge.
Tell me, Detective, is this
criminal trespass, burglary?
Neither. I disabled
your security system.
I was never here.
Well, I'd better get
a witness.
Let her sleep.
You made her work hard,
and your wife wouldn't be happy
to read about her
in the police report.
I also disconnected
your phone lines
and jammed your cell.
♪
All right.
If you're not here to kill me,
then what?
♪
I'm pregnant.
Congratulations.
Save it. We both know
what your end goal is.
One day you're gonna wake up
and decide you're done
playing with us
and put my family
in the ground.
I would never...I'm not wearing a wire.
It's just us here.
♪
I tried to lock you up,
but I failed. You won.
So, what,
you're giving up?
If it was just me,
I'd fight you in the street
with a claw hammer,
take you apart
like a horror film,
and gladly pay
the consequences.
But I've got responsibilities
bigger than me,
so I'm offering a trade.
What could you possibly
have to offer me?
Abril Rodas.
She killed eight of your men.
We found you cowering
in a cabinet.
I bet you still have nightmares
about her.
Keep talking.
She's moving north,
building her empire,
and earning herself
a DEA/FBI/LAPD task force.
I'm on it and offering to
feed you intel from the inside
so you can take her out.
Pass.
I wasn't finished.
You see, she knows
you were behind the hits
on Moses' crew.
They worked for her.
She can't let that stand.
So she's sending Sicarios
to put you in the ground.
I can give you
a fighting chance.
If she's really
coming after me,
then why not just wait
until my death?
Because you have an ability
to come out on top
that borders on miraculous.
That I do.
Which is why I'm confident
I can handle my own business.
Don't say no just yet.
Think hard, because my offer
has a clock on it.
♪
I'd rather not have
this baby in prison,
but if you turn me down,
I won't wait for Abril.
I'll do what I have to do
to protect my family.
And I'll make it hurt.
♪
Understood.
[Sliding door opens, closes]
Let's go.
Did he take the bait?
He nibbled. It'll take more
to get him on the hook.
Mm. This is a big risk.
Last chance to bow out.
I'm all the way in.
[Train whistle blows]
[Birds chirping]
[Brakes squealing]
[Gasps]
It's sweet.
Yeah. No, it's
a Norman Rockwell painting...
if Norman Rockwell was a
sociopath with a sense of humor.
Well, I'm here with you
the whole time.
Look, I-I'm not looking to
relive my childhood here.
I'm just gonna get
my mom's affairs in order,
and we'll be back in L.A.
by tomorrow night.
Your mom just died.
Maybe we can change our flight
and stay a few days.
[Chuckles] Look, the airline
lost our luggage.
The only rental available
was that powder-blue pillbox.
Trust me, this is the universe
saying, "Get in and out quick."
Oh, hey, you must be
one of Evelyn's customers.
I'll be with you
in one second.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Oh. I'm her son,
John Nolan.
Really?
I thought her son was a cop.
Protect and serve.
- You know what's weird?
- That you're a cop, too?
Yeah. And Evelyn's only son,
John Nolan.
You want to try again?
[Chuckles] Josh. Cherry.
I've heard
so much about you.
And you're
impersonating me why?
Old habit.
I mean, it was Evelyn's idea
to help sell her line
of self-defense gear.
She said you gave
your blessing, so...
I haven't said a kind word
to my mother in over a year.
Taser and pepper spray,
"Endorsed by Captain John Nolan,
LAPD."
You got a promotion
and didn't tell me?
[Sighs]
You're aware impersonating
law enforcement
is a crime?
[Chuckles] I can see
you need time to grieve.
[Clears throat]
Leave the box, Josh.
And keep my name
out of your mouth.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry
for your loss.
Well, that was different.
No, that was every day
growing up.
Well, we have a lot of work
to do here
if we're wheels up tomorrow.
How do you feel
about controlled burns?
[Chuckles]
I'm not gonna be any fun
this trip.
[Chuckles] It's okay, 'cause
I'm enough fun for both of us.
Mm. So true.
I guess
I should say thank you...
burglary and
a fourth amendment violation,
both under cover
of authority.
You're looking
at federal prison,
plus a seven-figure civil suit.
And the legal fees alone
are gonna pay
for my house in Tuscany.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Give me one reason
why I shouldn't walk
straight into Grey's office
and demand he fire you.
Because if I get fired,
I'm useless to Elijah,
and he's gonna need
all the help he can get.
Has he told you about Abril?
Blah, blah, blah.
Yes, the world is full
of monsters.
I'm not buying your offer
for one second.
Who cares?
You're just an employee.
[Scoffs]
But here's the thing...
Abril won't see it that way.
The people she's sending won't
care about your legal tricks.
They will gut you just like
everyone else in Elijah's orbit.
If you have any vacation days,
I'd take them.
I never run from a fight.
Fight?
Red, you won't
even see it coming.
[Cellphone beeps]
You're up.
[Jet engine roaring]
Yeah, I'm ready.
I'll see you at home.
Oh, oh.
It's okay.
[Chuckles]
Wesley.
How did you get in here?
Everybody has a price,
and I am very rich.
And what exactly
have you bought?
Besides a quick death.
A deal with the devil,
I hope.
Moses Warden
was your man in L.A.
And?
I know who killed
his crew...
well, your crew...
disrupted your network.
And you came all this way
just to tell me?
How selfless of you.
I have an agenda for sure.
We have a mutual enemy...
Elijah Stone.
He stabbed La Fiera
in the back,
took over her territory
in L.A.
Right, before you tried
to take him down yourself
and failed. [Scoffs]
You and the LAPD.
That's right.
And now he's stronger than ever.
But the win
made him feel invincible.
So he took out
your soldiers,
and now he's coming
for everything you own.
And you're just willing
to hand him over to me?
To have his death
on your conscience?
And a lot more.
Well, he's threatening my
family. I don't have a choice.
Ah. How is el niño?
He's gotten so big.
I follow Angela online.
My secret account.
♪
Jack is my everything.
And I'm gonna keep him safe,
even if it means
making a deal with you.
♪
Okay.
But you know what happens
if you betray the devil...
to you and your niño.
I do.
♪
[Clears throat]
Well, he survived
first contact.
Thank God.
Sorry I'm late.
What did I miss?
Garza: Abril Rodas.
She was La Fiera's
right-hand woman
until La Fiera
went after the wrong people
and ended up
with a bullet in her heart.
Wrong people?
Yeah.
She had Abril
kidnap Angela Lopez.
She took Angela back
to Guatemala
to steal her unborn kid.
Small group of LAPD officers
ran an off the books...
but sanctioned...
operation to bring her back.
Based on Elijah's intel.
Angela killed La Fiera
in self-defense
as we were escaping,
leaving Abril in charge.
It says here Abril
doesn't sleep?
Huh.
Is that even possible?
Well, it shouldn't be.
Angela was with her for a week,
24/7.
She said she never even saw her
take as much as a cat nap.
Fascinating.
Love to interview her.
Yeah, well, she's got multiple
outstanding warrants,
so she's not coming
into the States anytime soon.
No, but her girlfriend is.
That's actually why I was late.
Uh, DEA just intercepted a call
to Daylin Morales from Abril,
ordering her
to come to Los Angeles.
Rumor has it Daylin murdered
her entire family
when she was 16
on Christmas Day.
Abusive parents?
No, not as far as I know.
She taped the whole thing,
said it was her audition reel.
And it must have worked,
'cause three months later,
she emerges a Sicaria.
Hooked up with Abril
last year.
Hmm. Matt, I don't have to tell
you how dangerous this plan is.
And yet you're going to.
You're pulling the pin
on two grenades,
hoping to disarm them
before they fill
the streets with blood.
That's one way
to look at it.
And the other?
We're playing offense, Wade.
Are you sure you don't even want
to have a small funeral?
Well, my mom doesn't have
any friends,
just acquaintances,
like the grifter
we met at the house,
and she had marks.
Not really interested
in hearing those eulogies.
Stacy: John.
Oh. Hey, Stacy.
Hey.
I've been meaning to call.
I was so sorry to hear
about your mom.
Thank you. Stacy,
this is Bailey Nune, my fiancée.
Hi.
Fiancée?
Good for you.
I grew up with John.
Oh. So if I need
embarrassing stories...
I am your girl.
Or you could tell the time
I took on four bank robbers
and saved your life.
[Laughs]
Right. You're that Stacy?
Yeah. Um, if you need
anything while you're in town,
- please let me know.
- Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah. You, too.
She's pretty.
Did you two ever...?
Oh, once in high school,
but I was an idiot.
She moved on.
[Gasps]
The one who got away?
No.
Yeah, a little.
Oh. One second.
Hi. Uh, Shirley, right? We spoke
on the phone this morning.
Uh, John Nolan.
Oh, yes.
Please accept
my deepest condolences.[Horn honking]
Why don't I park?
Then you can come in.
Uh, well, this will really only
just take a minute.
John, let her park.
It... It's fine.
Our Platinum package
is a wonderful choice.
Our most popular.
Uh, that sounds lovely.
I'm thinking
more along the lines of
the "Parental Trauma" package.
Perhaps something
previously used,
or just a cardboard box?
They had a very complicated relationship.
[Horns honking]
I'm sorry to hear that.
Although, having known Evelyn
for a few decades,
I'm not surprised.
You're looking for our most
cost-effective option.
Bingo.
Well, then,
cremation's your best bet.
Perfect.
Uh, when can we do that?
This afternoon.
Okay. Uh, just let me know
when to pick her up.
[Horn honking]
Man: Hey, get off the road!
Nice to meet you.
[Vehicle approaches]
[Tires screech]
♪
- What's the word?
- Cop's intel checks out...
[Tires screech]
[Rapping] ♪ Better watch how
you move 'cause these... ♪
[Gun cocks]
[Horn honking]
♪ When I say
it's real out here, I... ♪
♪
Our contact in Guatemala
says Abril's mobilizing.
Hitters are en route,
led by her girlfriend.
Hot little number.
Trying to find out more.
We'll do it fast.
We need to hit them before
they have time to get set up.
Well, we could always take up
that cop on her offer.
No. This is my city.
Abril makes a move on me,
we send her girlfriend home
in pieces.
♪
[Squeaking]
There's just so much trash.
And we haven't even
gone upstairs.
[Chuckling]
What are you wearing?
Oh, I got something toxic
on my one and only shirt,
and so I found this in a box
labeled "defective."
"Party Aminal."
What's defective about that?
Who the hell is this?
I don't know,
but I am guessing it's not good.
Is it true?
The bitch is dead?
If you're referring
to my mother, then yes.
But I'm the only one
who gets to call her names.
Whoa, whoa.
Hold on, hold on.
No can do. Your mom's got
something that belongs to us,
and we want it back.
[Suspenseful music plays]
Get out of the way now.
Nolan:
Yeah, that's a nice gun.
I got one of those, too.
But I also have
one of these.
[Groans]
♪
Now, get in your truck
and drive away
or I'll get my girlfriend
to beat you up, too.
Listen, we just want
to take a quick look inside.
You all can stay out here
and keep your nose clean.
Unless you want me to get
local law enforcement involved,
I suggest you get
out of here now.
I'll see you around.
You better hope not.
What was that about?
I don't know.
Maybe the other John Nolan
will know.
Oh, and we're engaged,
by the way.
Oh, yeah. No, I know.
It's just "girlfriend"
was funnier.
Garza:
Just take a seat.
I'm good.
♪
He's gonna call.
I'm glad you're so confident.
But since I'm the one betting
my family's safety on the hope
that he does,
I'm gonna keep pacing.
Well, we knew that Elijah
was gonna be cautious,
especially with the information
coming from you.
And that's why we're gonna
give him a little push.
As soon as he finds out
that Abril is after his guys,
he's gonna be begging
for your help.
And when exactly is
this psychological warfare
supposed to begin?
Right about now.
Get off of me!
This is B.S.!
I didn't do anything wrong.
♪
I want my damn phone call.
[Handcuffs click]
Nolan: Remember us?
[Sighs] How'd you find me?
Foxburg is a small town,
and you're not exactly
a criminal mastermind.
Your eye looks
pretty painful.
Let me guess...
two guys in a pickup truck
find you before we did?
What? No.
I had a little accident.
Josh, here's the thing.
We're on a clock.
We have a flight
to catch tomorrow.
We don't have time
for your drama.
So just tell us what those guys
were looking for
in Evelyn's house.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Come on. Knock it off.
You were clearly looking
for something
when we met you at the house.
Look, you don't owe
my mother anything, all right?
That woman was a user
who felt no guilt
about leaving other people
holding the bag.
Just the sooner you cut bait
with her, the better.
Do you think
I don't know that?
Look, I can't help you.
If you were smart,
you'd move up your flight
and get the hell out of here.
Lunch?
Yeah.
Nice work.
How'd the other teams do?
Good, good.
All five of Elijah's
top lieutenants
are in custody, quick
and quiet, as planned.
Okay. So as long as no one saw
the arrests,
Elijah just might believe
that Abril is responsible.
But we can only hold them
for 12 hours
before we have to let them
make a phone call.
Think that's enough time
to spook Elijah?
On its own, no.
But we're not done
turning up the heat.
Turns out our murdered judge
kept a diary.
Laura and Brendon are on
their way to jack Monica up.
And I got a plane to catch.
Elijah, calm down. I haven't
heard anything about it,
but I will check with my sources
inside the department
and get back to you.
Ms. Stevens, we have a warrant
for your arrest.
♪
[Gasps]
Well, let me see it.
I have a legal right
to read it.
Search warrants are being
conducted as we speak
at your home and office,
seizing all client files and
communications related to cases
adjudicated by
Judge Daniel Rivas.
It's... It's right there.
♪
Attorney-client privilege
expressly protects those files.
Well, it did until you bribed
a federal judge
looking for preferential
rulings for your clients.
♪
That's a lie.
And this warrant isn't worth
the paper
that it is printed on.
When all this is over
and I walk away,
I will take great pleasure
in shoving this up your...
Okay, handcuff time.
Turn around.
Brendon:
I'll take your bag.
♪
[Handcuffs click]
Let's go.
♪
Perfecto.
Go get them, guys.
I'll say this about your mom...
that woman hustled.
I mean, the sheer volume of
scams is a little awe-inspiring.
I mean,
luxury bottled air.
♪
Healing crystals.
Oh.
Enhancement undies.
Don't forget the, uh,
Hair Today Shampoo.
"Restores luster
to lifeless locks."
Ooh, give me that.
All my toiletries
are in the lost luggage.
Yeah, I would not put this
anywhere near my hair.
I think it's probably
gonna be motor oil
or industrial lubricant
of some kind.
[Sniffs]
What?
Oh.
Well,
it's neither of those.
What is it?
It's not shampoo either.
Don't say something bad.
I'm thinking heroin.
[Sighs] Mom.
[Knock on door]
Johnny boy!
Oh! McCheese![Claps hands]
Get in here.
Oh, man. How are you?
Oh, good to see you.[Laughs]
Steve, this is Bailey Nune,
my fiancée.
Wow. You went out to Hollywood
and hooked up with a starlet.
[Laughs]
It's nice to meet you.
John told me you two were, um,
troublemakers back in the day.
No comment.
Although, by the sounds of it,
he's still getting into trouble.
Heroin shampoo?
Yeah. This is not mine.
This is all Evelyn.
Yeah, that sounds right.
I mean. uh,
I-I am sorry for your loss.
Uh, but the number of complaints
I got about your mom...
let's just say that there's
an entire file cabinet
down at the station
for her.
So sorry about that.
Did you get a chance
to run the plate we sent you?
Oh, didn't have to.
Uh, Decker Conroy
and his brother Perry...
they're at the center
of the local drug trade
around here.
I'll, uh...
I'll go to the usual haunts.
Shouldn't take long
to find them.
I may have an easier way.
Hey, guys. Let me first just say
I'm sorry for how I reacted.
I've been going
through a lot.
I, uh, got a lot going on here,
and I didn't have all the facts.
Yeah. So what's up?
That badge was fake
or what?
Oh, no. That's...
That's real.
I am a patrol officer with the
Los Angeles Police Department,
which means, of course,
I don't have
any legal jurisdiction
here in Pennsylvania.
[Chuckles] So, like, you
can't... can't even arrest us.
Nolan: That's right.
So you can take your property,
and you're free to go.
What about the guns, man?
Oh, sorry. I gave those to a cop
who actually can arrest you.
Howdy, boys.
Drop the bag, hands in the air.
What the hell is this?
[Siren wailing]
Man.
[Handcuffs clicking]
Here you go.
But we should have
a proper catch up.
I would love that.
Though it's gonna have to be
in Los Angeles.
We are out of here tomorrow.
Have a nice flight.
- [Laughs] Anyway, Cheese.
- Take care, Johnny boy.
♪
So, where were we?
Barely started.
Right.
♪
Love the outfit.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you say something?
I was busy writing
a lawsuit in my head.
I'm Supervisory Special Agent
Matthew Garza with the FBI.
You've been apprised
of the charges against you,
and I'd like to give you
an opportunity to address them.
Thank you,
but I'll wait for my lawyer.
As is your right.
Mm.
But you did bribe
a federal judge,
and we believe that you're
responsible for his death.
But see, that's not
your real problem.
Your real problem
is that you failed your boss.
You exposed
Elijah's organization
to an FBI investigation.
And one day soon,
whether you are under
house arrest or in jail,
he's gonna have you killed.
[Flatly]
Oh, no. I'm so scared.
Listen, if you think
I'm gonna betray my oath
as a lawyer
the way Wesley did,
you're a moron.
And don't bother
offering me witness protection.
You think I'm gonna work
at a Cinnabon in Albuquerque?
I'd rather be shanked
in prison.
No, you wouldn't.
You're a survivor.
Exactly.
So kindly get out of my face
until my lawyer arrives.
Arrested for what?
Where did you hear that,
and where is she being held?
Lucy: Sounds like he heard
about Monica.
Elijah:
Well, find out.
What about Hazy
and the others?
And he's missing
his lieutenants.
[Indistinct hip-hop music
playing]
Listen to me.
I'm calling you back
in 10 minutes.
And if you don't have
an answer,
you're going missing, too.
Not over the phone, boss.
What are you doing?
Getting some clarity.
[Hip-hop music continues]
♪
Lopez: Took you long enough
to call.
[Scanner beeps]
♪
Satisfied?
Never.
[Car stereo beeps,
volume increases]
[Music continues]
♪
I'm accepting your offer.
Tell me how
to take down Abril's hitters,
and you and your family
are safe.
You don't have much time.
They've already taken out
your street-level bosses.
Word is they came heavy.
Well, heavy won't matter
in an ambush.
And I got firepower
for days.
They're staying at a house
in North Hollywood.
She brought two specialists
with her from Guatemala.
The rest is local muscle.
Is the task force up
on her yet?
No. She won't be here
long enough,
and we won't have time
to get warrants.
She's here to hit you
and you fly home,
so you need to move first.
♪
Well, I guess
this is goodbye...
unless something goes wrong.
Make sure it doesn't.
I did my part.
♪
[Car stereo beeps,
volume decreases]
♪
Get a team together.
Recon the location.
If everything is on the up,
we hit them tonight.
♪
[Engine revs]
[Engine starts]
He took the bait.
It's going down tonight.
[Knock on door]
Can't wait
to see who that is.
Stacy!
I figured you'd be swamped,
so I swung by the Sunrise Diner.
You did not get me
a pulled pork sandwich.
I did not.
[Bag rustles]
I brought you two.
You are an angel
straight from heaven.
Bailey:
Two of what?
Two of
the best sandwiches
you have ever tasted
in your entire life.
And I have two for you,
as well.
[Gasps]
I apologize, by the way,
for the mess.
No, not at all. I can't imagine
how hard this must be for you.
Do you want wine? I think
I saw a box in the fridge.
Way ahead of you. Oh.
And a beer for John.
Marry me.[Laughs]
Sadly,
you're already engaged.
Who am I to stand
in the way of true love?
John did tell me earlier
you were the one that got away.
Aww!
That just made my day.
But he's all yours.
I got the new boyfriend
perfectly trained,
and I don't have the strength
to start again.
He is a lot of work.
I'm right here.
[Both laugh]
[Thud in distance]
What was that?
Stay behind me.
Is that necessary?
We've already had
quite the day.
[Rattling]
♪
[Breathing heavily]
Josh!
What the hell
are you doing?
[Sighs] Nothing.
Josh?
I'm looking for the spare set
of keys to Evelyn's car.
You broke in to steal
his mother's car?
Josh, you know better
than that.
I wish that were true.
Josh, why are you
stealing my mom's car?
'Cause, I'm a dead man
if I don't get
the hell out of Foxburg.
Hey, hey, hey.
Does this have anything to do
with the drugs you've been
selling with my mother.
W... The fake supplements
were her idea.
No, not the supplements,
the heroin.
She was selling heroin?!
And didn't cut me in?
Eh, it doesn't matter.
She would have just screwed me
over like she did
with the generators.
I'm afraid to ask.
Me too.
I'm game.
What generators?
Evelyn and I sold a bunch
of portable generators
to a group of people,
and they're unhappy.
Okay.
What group of people?
They, you know, like guns and
don't like the government.
Like a militia?
Josh:
Yes, a militia!
Why do they want you dead?
Apparently, the reason
your mother got such a good deal
is because they're defective.
As was my mother.
Just give them the money back.
I can't! It's gone!
She must have used it all
on her next big idea.
Okay. Well, you're not
getting the car
'cause I already
sold it online.
Look, your best bet here
is just go pay Steve a visit
at the sheriff's station
and just throw yourself
on his mercy.
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
No, h-he's just gonna rub it
in my face,
and I'm not giving him
the satisfaction.
Josh, that is a dumb reason
to avoid asking for help.
[Gunshots]
[Josh groaning]
Bailey: Okay. Okay.
[Gunshots]
Here.
Josh.
[Groans]
[Gunshots continue]
[Light switch clicks]
Bullet went all the way through.
He's lucky.
That's the militia outside!
Yeah.
I figured that out.
I need to stop
the bleeding.
[Banging on door]
Will this work?
Yeah, actually.
What the hell
are you doing?!
Saving your life.
[Groans]
[Gunshots]
Stacy, you okay?
I'm starting to think
you're bad luck.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
Call Steve, tell him
to bring backup.
Do you have
any more magazines?
Nine rounds left.
[Gunshots]
[Screams]
Steve's on his way
with the state police.
Taser.
[Door crashes,
Stacy screams]
[Taser crackles]
[Gunshots]
♪
Reload.
Okay.
[Both shout]
[Taser crackling]
[Gunshot]
[Siren wailing]
Okay. All right. Uh...
[Chuckles]
Ladies.
John, what do you got?
[Dog barking in distance]
It's okay. We're Code-4.
[Handcuffs click]
Anybody hurt?
Yeah. Josh is gonna need
an ambulance...
GSW to the abdomen.
Three more GSWs
to the guys who attacked us.
Nothing personal,
Johnny boy,
but I cannot wait for you
to go back to L.A.
You and me both.
And me. [Sighs]
[Spanish music playing
indistinctly]
♪
Feels like
they're buying it.
Well, they haven't left yet.
That's a good sign.
Harper:
They buying it?
So far.
Guys, I'm feeling
a little vulnerable right now.
What if they decide
to start shooting?
You're doing great.
Lucky for us, you're a match
for our psycho killer.
Now move away
from the window.
We got to tease them
a little bit,
give them that itch.
♪
Why haven't they called Elijah
to get the green light?
'Cause they're good
at their jobs...
measure twice, cut once.
Lopez, you think Elijah just
sends them in
once he decides it's safe?
No. He'll want to be here.
Elijah's ego's too big
to let someone else hit
Abril's people for him.
Alpha Team, status check.
They're circling...
making their way closer.
He's clearly checking
for a tail,
but we're doing
multiple handoffs.
It's nice to have
federal resources.
♪
C'mon, make the call.
Still no sign of a tail?
♪
Mnh-mnh. No.
All right.
♪
[Cellphone clicks, beeps]
[Sighs]
Yo, three inside.
Partying a little.
Clocked a few noisemakers...
loud ones.
Here we go.
Any sign of eyeballs?
None. LJ took a lap
around the block... all quiet.
♪
But we should wait
till later.
Maybe. But what if some of
their friends show up?
Suddenly we're going
to a much bigger party.
Turn right here,
look for follow cars.
Keep going straight.
♪
Alpha Team handing off.
Bravo Leader:
Copy. Bravo has contact.
♪
Alpha Team headed to safe house.
ETA two minutes.
♪
You still there?
Yeah.
I think we're clear.
And I think we can't wait.
The goal
is the out of towners.
We can visit the locals
any time.
I need a yes or a no.
♪
I don't know, boss.
I think we should wait.
Yes or no?
♪
Say yes.
Yes.
I'll be there in a minute.
All right, here we go.
Remember, we need the target
to be armed and on the premises.
Once they make armed
unlawful entry,
then we can take them down.
Not before.
Alright.
♪
Target on site.
Copy.
House Team in position.
♪
Here we go.
They're on the move.
♪
[Bottle clattering]
No.
♪
It's over.
All teams stand down.
[Dramatic music plays]
It's over.
♪
Screw that. We can arrest them.
They're right there.
[Engine starts]
For gun charges? That will
only hold them for a minute.
That's not enough.
[Engines revving]
♪
He walked away,
so we do, too.
And then what?
We go back to work,
find another way.
♪
Let her go.
Well, where do you want
to start?
You mentioned something
about a controlled burn?
You know, there's this little
thing I like to call
throwing money
at the problem.
Hire someone?
Yes.
Oh, my God, I love it.
Why the hell didn't
I think of that?
Great. Let's just get the photo
albums and be done with it.
I saw them over here.
Oh, I forgot all about this.
[Gasps]
Oh, who signed it?
Mike Schmidt,
best player in Philly history.
It's our baseball team.
I love when you mansplain...
although I'd argue
that Steve Carlton gave Schmidt
a run for his money.
Unless you're one of those
"pitchers can't be MVPs"
cavemen.
Guilty as charged.
No, I remember my mom
got us tickets to this game
and then talked our way
past the security guard
to get him to sign it.
Man, I can't believe
she didn't sell it.
I think we should put that
on our mantle.
That's a great idea.
Look on the bright side...
the last 24 hours have been
a little slice of hell,
but this house is
more inheritance
than most people get.
You could sell it, pay for
the "Parental Trauma" package
and the cleanup crew,
and still turn
a pretty healthy profit.
I think that sounds
like a great plan.
Yeah.
Knock knock.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
About last night?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
[Laughs]
But there's something
I need to tell you.
- Uh-oh.
- Yeah. I was looking
at your mom's accounts,
and, well,
the bank's foreclosing
on the house.
She hadn't paid the mortgage
in a year. It's a done deal.
I'm sorry.
[Both laughing]
That... That is the perfect
ending to this whole debacle.
Here you go. It's all yours.
We have a plane to catch.
I... What, what?
It was so nice to meet you.
Please come visit.
We have lots of room.
Okay?
Got a delivery
for Evelyn Nolan.
Let me guess,
you got about $100,000 worth
of something ridiculous?
My money's
on diet supplement.
I'm feeling...
food storage systems.
Ah.
Protein shakes.
Can one of you sign
for the delivery?
No, no. Sorry. We don't know,
uh, Evelyn Nolan.
No, you can talk to her, though.
Thank you, Stacy,
for everything. Bye.
Run.
Jack's down for his nap.
I don't know
if I'll ever sleep again.
Try not to worry.
We've got units parked
in the front and back 24/7,
and Garza sent
a very clear message to Elijah
that we're off-limits.
You really think
he'll listen?
For the near future,
while he figures out
how much exposure he's facing.
Did you really threaten
to fight Elijah
in the street
with a claw hammer?
Grey heard it on the wire.
I did.
But it was all a bluff.
I'd dust him from a thousand
yards with a 220 grain,
disappear before the sound wave
even reached him.
You're kidding, right?
Yeah.
Mm.
I think if all else fails,
we should just break open
the trust fund,
just buy an island.
I'm not running.
I know.
But maybe we could buy
an island anyway.
[Chuckles]
I'll send you some listings.
What about Abril?
I think we're in the clear
for now.
As far as she knows,
Daylin and the Sicarios
were sent right back home
because they're on
a federal watch list.
Mm.
I can't imagine
she has any idea
about the con
we just ran on Elijah.
♪
And now it all makes sense.
Well, this isn't
a zero sum game.
We can help each other.
♪
I'm listening.
Captions by VITAC...
♪