1
00:00:02,476 --> 00:00:05,813
People are gonna die,
and you can't save them.

2
00:00:05,813 --> 00:00:08,149
I ate their pain
like a five-star meal.

3
00:00:11,319 --> 00:00:12,445
Do you want to come in?

4
00:00:12,445 --> 00:00:14,822
I didn't know
that you were gonna be here.

5
00:00:14,822 --> 00:00:16,991
Tim and I were ju--
No.

6
00:00:16,991 --> 00:00:18,367
Have you decided
what you're gonna do

7
00:00:18,367 --> 00:00:19,493
with your Golden Ticket?

8
00:00:19,493 --> 00:00:21,495
So next week, you're off
to F. T. O. school.

9
00:00:21,495 --> 00:00:24,081
You will officially be
a Field Training Officer.

10
00:00:24,081 --> 00:00:25,875
Detective Misha Porter.
I'm here to recruit you.

11
00:00:25,875 --> 00:00:28,002
When do classes start?
Next Monday.

12
00:01:02,661 --> 00:01:04,246
Hi.
Is there a problem, Officer?

13
00:01:04,246 --> 00:01:07,917
Hi.
Um...where's the driver?

14
00:01:07,917 --> 00:01:10,002
It's a driverless car,
obviously.

15
00:01:10,002 --> 00:01:11,045
My dad designs them.

16
00:01:11,045 --> 00:01:13,255
He was busy,
so he told it to take me.

17
00:01:13,255 --> 00:01:18,427
Okay. Well, he --
um, it just ran a stop sign.

18
00:01:18,427 --> 00:01:20,930
The camera must
not have seen it.

19
00:01:20,930 --> 00:01:25,184
Right. But I'm gonna have to
write you a ticket.

20
00:01:25,184 --> 00:01:26,519
Why? I wasn't driving.

21
00:01:26,519 --> 00:01:29,313
Yeah, not --
not you, but, um...

22
00:01:29,313 --> 00:01:32,566
Um...

23
00:01:38,572 --> 00:01:40,282
Surprise!

24
00:01:40,282 --> 00:01:41,534
Oh!

25
00:01:41,534 --> 00:01:44,787
You're home from undercover
school, so, you know, mm.

26
00:01:44,787 --> 00:01:47,164
I love it.

27
00:01:47,164 --> 00:01:49,250
Well, mm...

28
00:01:49,250 --> 00:01:50,584
I'm gonna be late for class,

29
00:01:50,584 --> 00:01:52,128
but I want to hear
all about it tonight.

30
00:01:52,128 --> 00:01:54,463
Okay, great.

31
00:01:54,463 --> 00:01:55,423
Oh, wait.
You're --

32
00:01:55,423 --> 00:01:57,007
But -- Yep.

33
00:01:57,007 --> 00:02:00,469
Oh, God.

34
00:02:01,762 --> 00:02:03,180
Mm.

35
00:02:03,180 --> 00:02:04,598
Ah.
Hi.

36
00:02:04,598 --> 00:02:05,808
Hi.

37
00:02:05,808 --> 00:02:07,143
I'm so happy you're home.

38
00:02:07,143 --> 00:02:08,185
How are you?

39
00:02:08,185 --> 00:02:09,395
Great.
Mm?

40
00:02:09,395 --> 00:02:12,898
Uh, typing still
a bit of a challenge.

41
00:02:12,898 --> 00:02:15,192
And forget about
opening a jar.

42
00:02:15,192 --> 00:02:17,486
It hasn't been too much for you,
being back at work?

43
00:02:17,486 --> 00:02:18,779
Are you kidding?

44
00:02:18,779 --> 00:02:20,698
I was going out of my mind
sitting on the couch all day.

45
00:02:20,698 --> 00:02:23,659
There's something else
that's been helping me more.

46
00:02:26,996 --> 00:02:29,665
An online group
that's hunting Rosalind.

47
00:02:29,665 --> 00:02:32,042
They contacted me
a few weeks ago.

48
00:02:32,042 --> 00:02:34,170
They call themselves
"Dye-Hards."

49
00:02:34,170 --> 00:02:38,632
Hmm. Let me guess.
"D-Y-E" as in Rosalind "Dyer"?

50
00:02:38,632 --> 00:02:40,509
Exactly.
Mm-hmm.

51
00:02:40,509 --> 00:02:42,845
At first I thought
they were a bunch of kooks

52
00:02:42,845 --> 00:02:44,472
who just wanted to hear
about the attack.

53
00:02:44,472 --> 00:02:48,142
But, you know, th-their research
is actually really impressive.

54
00:02:48,142 --> 00:02:50,269
Uh, what kind of research?
What --

55
00:02:50,269 --> 00:02:51,687
They --
They scour message boards,

56
00:02:51,687 --> 00:02:54,440
subreddits,
and social media posts for tips,

57
00:02:54,440 --> 00:02:57,818
then compile the most credible
ones in an encrypted PDF

58
00:02:57,818 --> 00:02:59,403
they call
"The Mother Doc."

59
00:02:59,403 --> 00:03:01,405
And they...

60
00:03:01,405 --> 00:03:04,492
Well, I was hoping
you might take a look.

61
00:03:04,492 --> 00:03:07,286
Chris,
I'm a patrol officer.

62
00:03:07,286 --> 00:03:10,372
I-I -- Um, I'm not a part
of the investigation.

63
00:03:10,372 --> 00:03:12,666
But you're still a cop.

64
00:03:12,666 --> 00:03:14,043
Look, I wouldn't ask,

65
00:03:14,043 --> 00:03:16,003
but the task force
has been blowing me off.

66
00:03:16,003 --> 00:03:18,172
You are still recovering.

67
00:03:18,172 --> 00:03:20,841
You know, and it's --
it's not healthy

68
00:03:20,841 --> 00:03:24,136
to be immersed in
hunting Rosalind all day long.

69
00:03:24,136 --> 00:03:26,263
Just take a look.

70
00:03:26,263 --> 00:03:28,641
If you think it's
worth passing on, great.

71
00:03:28,641 --> 00:03:31,227
If not, totally fine.

72
00:03:31,227 --> 00:03:35,189
Fine. I will look at
"The Mother Doc."

73
00:03:35,189 --> 00:03:37,816
Thanks.

74
00:03:37,816 --> 00:03:40,319
Your first day
as a Training Officer.

75
00:03:40,319 --> 00:03:41,904
How does it feel?

76
00:03:41,904 --> 00:03:44,031
Well, considering
six weeks ago,

77
00:03:44,031 --> 00:03:46,867
I thought I'd have to wait
another...two years,

78
00:03:46,867 --> 00:03:48,452
pretty fantastic.

79
00:03:48,452 --> 00:03:49,870
What you got there?

80
00:03:49,870 --> 00:03:52,039
Nothing. Just a couple things
I didn't want to forget.

81
00:03:52,039 --> 00:03:53,749
Let me see, let me see.

82
00:03:56,961 --> 00:04:00,089
"How to set up a shop"?
"Processing a prisoner"?

83
00:04:00,089 --> 00:04:04,426
Nolan, I sincerely hope after
two years in the department

84
00:04:04,426 --> 00:04:06,971
and a month at the
F. T. O. Training Academy,

85
00:04:06,971 --> 00:04:08,806
you don't need
a crib sheet.

86
00:04:08,806 --> 00:04:10,307
No, sir. No, I just --

87
00:04:10,307 --> 00:04:13,394
I-I've been working towards this
so long,

88
00:04:13,394 --> 00:04:15,187
I just didn't want
to mess anything up.

89
00:04:15,187 --> 00:04:17,064
Oh, but you will.

90
00:04:17,064 --> 00:04:20,651
This is your first time training
a rookie officer from jump,

91
00:04:20,651 --> 00:04:23,404
making you
a rookie yourself.

92
00:04:23,404 --> 00:04:26,407
Which I'm sure you're not gonna
haze me about at all.

93
00:04:26,407 --> 00:04:28,742
You're gonna stumble.

94
00:04:28,742 --> 00:04:31,412
But you're a good cop
and you know how to do the job.

95
00:04:31,412 --> 00:04:34,415
Thank you, sir.
I needed that.

96
00:04:34,415 --> 00:04:37,167
Good, 'cause you're not
getting this back.

97
00:04:37,167 --> 00:04:40,504
Now, let's go
meet your rookie, boot.

98
00:04:42,172 --> 00:04:45,259
So, alright,
first things first --

99
00:04:45,259 --> 00:04:47,887
So, I'd like to congratulate
Officer Lucy Chen

100
00:04:47,887 --> 00:04:49,638
for successfully completing

101
00:04:49,638 --> 00:04:53,767
the D. E. A. Covert Operations
Training Academy,

102
00:04:53,767 --> 00:04:55,311
which is no small feat.

103
00:05:00,357 --> 00:05:02,401
Good to have you back,
Officer Chen.

104
00:05:02,401 --> 00:05:03,861
Happy to be back,
sir.

105
00:05:03,861 --> 00:05:06,614
Also, I have the privilege
to introduce

106
00:05:06,614 --> 00:05:10,910
Mid-Wilshire's newest
Training Officer, John Nolan.

107
00:05:10,910 --> 00:05:12,286
Hey, hey, hey.

108
00:05:14,163 --> 00:05:15,789
Good work.

109
00:05:15,789 --> 00:05:18,125
And since Harper has decided
to abandon patrol

110
00:05:18,125 --> 00:05:20,336
for a cushy desk job
with the detectives,

111
00:05:20,336 --> 00:05:22,796
today Nolan will take on
the responsibility

112
00:05:22,796 --> 00:05:24,340
of training
his first rookie.

113
00:05:24,340 --> 00:05:26,008
Officer, stand up,

114
00:05:26,008 --> 00:05:28,010
state your name
and badge number.

115
00:05:28,010 --> 00:05:31,221
I'm Celina Juarez,
badge number 53397.

116
00:05:31,221 --> 00:05:33,432
Officer Juarez,

117
00:05:33,432 --> 00:05:34,892
you have earned the right
to be in this room,

118
00:05:34,892 --> 00:05:37,019
but you must
prove yourself to stay.

119
00:05:37,019 --> 00:05:39,146
The way we do things
matters.

120
00:05:39,146 --> 00:05:41,732
Protocol and tradition
are the metal

121
00:05:41,732 --> 00:05:45,110
from which every cop
in this city is forged.

122
00:05:45,110 --> 00:05:46,820
You have anything
to add?

123
00:05:46,820 --> 00:05:48,822
I see you got top marks
at the Academy.

124
00:05:48,822 --> 00:05:49,990
Good for you.

125
00:05:49,990 --> 00:05:51,283
None of that matters
when you hit the street,

126
00:05:51,283 --> 00:05:52,660
so assume
you know nothing,

127
00:05:52,660 --> 00:05:54,244
and you'll never be wrong.

128
00:05:54,244 --> 00:05:55,829
Got it?
Yes, sir.

129
00:05:55,829 --> 00:05:58,457
That's it.
Be safe out there.

130
00:06:00,084 --> 00:06:02,461
Hi, I'm Celina --

131
00:06:02,461 --> 00:06:04,838
your new rookie who, uh,
apparently knows nothing.

132
00:06:04,838 --> 00:06:06,548
Oh, I wouldn't say
"nothing."

133
00:06:06,548 --> 00:06:08,258
Dean's List, D3 soccer,

134
00:06:08,258 --> 00:06:10,094
graduate classes
in criminal justice --

135
00:06:10,094 --> 00:06:11,345
pretty impressive.
Thank you.

136
00:06:11,345 --> 00:06:12,930
But I'm aware that
academia and street smarts

137
00:06:12,930 --> 00:06:14,264
are two different things.

138
00:06:14,264 --> 00:06:17,059
I like to think simple
common sense trumps them both.

139
00:06:17,059 --> 00:06:19,019
But if you have any questions,
you can always come and ask me.

140
00:06:19,019 --> 00:06:21,063
Yep, and me.
Hi. I'm Lucy Chen.

141
00:06:21,063 --> 00:06:22,356
Nice to meet you, ma'am.

142
00:06:22,356 --> 00:06:24,191
May I?
Please.

143
00:06:24,191 --> 00:06:25,359
Sergeant Bradford's right.

144
00:06:25,359 --> 00:06:27,528
The most important thing
is to never pretend

145
00:06:27,528 --> 00:06:28,946
that you know
something you don't.

146
00:06:28,946 --> 00:06:30,864
Pretending is what
gets you killed out there.

147
00:06:30,864 --> 00:06:34,118
You're very lucky to have
Officer Nolan as your T. O.

148
00:06:34,118 --> 00:06:35,661
He's a great listener.

149
00:06:35,661 --> 00:06:37,371
And if you ever want
to talk to another woman

150
00:06:37,371 --> 00:06:41,083
who was in your shoes
not that long ago, um, I'm here.

151
00:06:41,083 --> 00:06:42,835
Thank you.
That means a lot.

152
00:06:42,835 --> 00:06:44,253
Yeah, of course.

153
00:06:44,253 --> 00:06:46,380
You guys have
a great first shift.

154
00:06:46,380 --> 00:06:49,091
Thank you,
Officer Chen.

155
00:06:49,091 --> 00:06:50,676
Are you ready
to get started?

156
00:06:50,676 --> 00:06:52,219
Yes, sir.

157
00:06:52,219 --> 00:06:54,388
Congrats on making P2.
Thank you.

158
00:06:54,388 --> 00:06:55,556
I heard
you're doing a great job

159
00:06:55,556 --> 00:06:57,516
riding with Tim
as his Sergeant's Aide.

160
00:06:57,516 --> 00:06:59,101
Thanks, but look,
I'm ready to step aside

161
00:06:59,101 --> 00:07:00,561
now that you're back,
s--

162
00:07:00,561 --> 00:07:02,521
Wait, Tim said
I'm doing a great job?

163
00:07:02,521 --> 00:07:04,565
Uh, no. Sorry.
Oh.

164
00:07:04,565 --> 00:07:05,858
I-I made
that last part up.

165
00:07:05,858 --> 00:07:07,317
But, you know,
he hasn't replaced you yet,

166
00:07:07,317 --> 00:07:08,944
so he's happy.

167
00:07:08,944 --> 00:07:11,613
You should, um,
stick with him.

168
00:07:11,613 --> 00:07:13,073
Really? You sure?

169
00:07:13,073 --> 00:07:15,117
- Yeah.
- I mean, I could...

170
00:07:15,117 --> 00:07:17,202
...use some quiet time
riding solo,

171
00:07:17,202 --> 00:07:20,914
thinking about next steps
in my career.

172
00:07:20,914 --> 00:07:22,541
You haven't heard
a word I've said.

173
00:07:22,541 --> 00:07:25,419
No, sorry. Uh, yeah, I got
something I got to take care of.

174
00:07:25,419 --> 00:07:27,463
Excuse me.

175
00:07:27,463 --> 00:07:29,631
Good talk.

176
00:07:29,631 --> 00:07:31,467
Good morning.

177
00:07:31,467 --> 00:07:32,926
Thank God you're back.

178
00:07:32,926 --> 00:07:34,803
But first things first --

179
00:07:34,803 --> 00:07:37,347
I need to see photos
of Leah ASAP.

180
00:07:37,347 --> 00:07:38,640
Look.

181
00:07:40,267 --> 00:07:42,686
Oh, my God.
She's gorgeous.

182
00:07:42,686 --> 00:07:44,563
It must have been hard
to leave her this morning.

183
00:07:44,563 --> 00:07:45,606
Yeah, it was.

184
00:07:45,606 --> 00:07:47,065
You ready to think
about crime again?

185
00:07:47,065 --> 00:07:49,610
Yes.
What can I help with?

186
00:07:49,610 --> 00:07:51,862
Let's see.

187
00:07:51,862 --> 00:07:55,032
Jill Baskin.
Missing now for three days.

188
00:07:55,032 --> 00:07:56,992
Uh, any suspects?

189
00:07:56,992 --> 00:07:59,620
The roommate says Jill's
ex-boyfriend had a nasty temper,

190
00:07:59,620 --> 00:08:02,247
but I haven't been able
to find enough for a warrant.

191
00:08:02,247 --> 00:08:04,166
I'd love fresh eyes.

192
00:08:04,166 --> 00:08:05,334
Tyler Harvin.

193
00:08:05,334 --> 00:08:06,835
Alright,
I will jump on it.

194
00:08:06,835 --> 00:08:08,504
Thanks.

195
00:08:08,504 --> 00:08:11,340
This is your shop.
Do not call it a car,

196
00:08:11,340 --> 00:08:13,133
a cruiser,
or a black and white.

197
00:08:13,133 --> 00:08:14,009
It is where you work.

198
00:08:14,009 --> 00:08:15,677
Anytime you leave the shop,

199
00:08:15,677 --> 00:08:17,095
your body camera
needs to be on.

200
00:08:21,391 --> 00:08:23,977
Perfect.

201
00:08:23,977 --> 00:08:27,064
First, check the exterior
of the shop for any damage.

202
00:08:27,064 --> 00:08:29,691
You are looking for dents,
dings, scratches.

203
00:08:29,691 --> 00:08:31,068
We're gonna check
the back seat

204
00:08:31,068 --> 00:08:33,028
for anything a suspect
might have left behind --

205
00:08:33,028 --> 00:08:35,489
money, weapons...

206
00:08:35,489 --> 00:08:37,241
drugs.

207
00:08:37,241 --> 00:08:38,534
Was someone smoking weed
in here?

208
00:08:38,534 --> 00:08:40,160
I think that was me.

209
00:08:40,160 --> 00:08:41,286
Excuse me?

210
00:08:41,286 --> 00:08:44,832
No, it's not marijuana.
I-I saged the shop.

211
00:08:44,832 --> 00:08:48,043
You --
That's unconventional.

212
00:08:48,043 --> 00:08:49,795
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't think you'd notice.

213
00:08:49,795 --> 00:08:51,088
It's just that
it's my first day,

214
00:08:51,088 --> 00:08:53,507
and I figured I could use
all the help I could get, right?

215
00:08:53,507 --> 00:08:57,052
Sure. Next time,
just check with me first.

216
00:08:57,052 --> 00:09:01,765
Okay. Now, where was I?
It was...

217
00:09:01,765 --> 00:09:04,226
My Rook Book says you check
the trunk for equipment.

218
00:09:04,226 --> 00:09:05,686
The trunk.

219
00:09:05,686 --> 00:09:08,397
We're gonna need police tape.
We're gonna need road flares.

220
00:09:08,397 --> 00:09:10,607
Load up.

221
00:09:14,945 --> 00:09:17,114
Hey, you're back.
How was U. C. school?

222
00:09:17,114 --> 00:09:19,366
Challenging.

223
00:09:19,366 --> 00:09:21,368
How's life
working for the enemy?

224
00:09:21,368 --> 00:09:23,036
Not as weird
as I thought it would be.

225
00:09:23,036 --> 00:09:24,037
It's actually
pretty interesting

226
00:09:24,037 --> 00:09:25,372
seeing things
from the other side.

227
00:09:25,372 --> 00:09:28,750
That's great.
Um, how is Chris doing?

228
00:09:28,750 --> 00:09:30,085
Yeah, he seems fine.

229
00:09:30,085 --> 00:09:31,670
You know, they're starting
him off slow,

230
00:09:31,670 --> 00:09:32,880
nothing too intense.
Why?

231
00:09:32,880 --> 00:09:35,424
Has he talked to you
about this online community

232
00:09:35,424 --> 00:09:37,301
he joined
that's hunting Rosalind?

233
00:09:37,301 --> 00:09:40,596
No, but I could see
why that would worry you.

234
00:09:40,596 --> 00:09:42,139
Want me to
keep an eye on him?

235
00:09:42,139 --> 00:09:44,516
Yeah, I really do.

236
00:09:44,516 --> 00:09:45,601
Yeah, no problem.

237
00:09:45,601 --> 00:09:48,729
But, Lucy,
just give him time.

238
00:09:48,729 --> 00:09:50,439
We've both been
where he is.

239
00:09:50,439 --> 00:09:52,399
He'll get through it.

240
00:09:58,488 --> 00:10:00,073
What's the name of the store
we just passed?

241
00:10:00,073 --> 00:10:01,742
Huh?
Uh, it was, uh --

242
00:10:01,742 --> 00:10:04,077
You have no idea because
your face has been on your phone

243
00:10:04,077 --> 00:10:06,246
for the past 10 minutes.
Put it away.

244
00:10:06,246 --> 00:10:08,957
Sorry, sir. It's just, um...

245
00:10:08,957 --> 00:10:10,834
There's something going on
that I don't know how to handle.

246
00:10:10,834 --> 00:10:12,127
You know the deal.

247
00:10:12,127 --> 00:10:13,754
This is a personal-life
free zone.

248
00:10:13,754 --> 00:10:15,505
Yes, sir. But, uh,

249
00:10:15,505 --> 00:10:18,175
this is something that could,
like, derail my career.

250
00:10:21,178 --> 00:10:22,804
Alright.
What is it?

251
00:10:22,804 --> 00:10:25,432
I'm being blackmailed.

252
00:10:25,432 --> 00:10:26,642
Yeah, so, I, um --

253
00:10:26,642 --> 00:10:28,685
I sent this photo
to this girl on a dating app,

254
00:10:28,685 --> 00:10:30,687
you know, just shirtless,
nothing X-rated.

255
00:10:30,687 --> 00:10:32,147
A thirst trap,
you know?

256
00:10:32,147 --> 00:10:33,315
I wish I didn't.

257
00:10:33,315 --> 00:10:36,735
Turns out it was some dude,
and I was catfished.

258
00:10:36,735 --> 00:10:38,111
And now
he's blackmailing me.

259
00:10:38,111 --> 00:10:40,197
With what? You said
the photo didn't show anything.

260
00:10:40,197 --> 00:10:41,740
Right.
The -- The original one didn't.

261
00:10:41,740 --> 00:10:43,951
But then
he Photoshopped it.

262
00:10:43,951 --> 00:10:45,535
Whoa.
Yeah.

263
00:10:45,535 --> 00:10:46,954
What does he want?

264
00:10:46,954 --> 00:10:48,163
He didn't say.

265
00:10:48,163 --> 00:10:51,208
He just told me to wait
for further instructions.

266
00:10:51,208 --> 00:10:54,628
Well, I mean,
it could be worse.

267
00:10:54,628 --> 00:10:56,505
At least he was generous.

268
00:11:05,389 --> 00:11:09,434
Control, 7-L-19,
I have a 10-34 at The Nautilus

269
00:11:09,434 --> 00:11:11,520
near the corner
of Virgil and West Fourth.

270
00:11:11,520 --> 00:11:14,189
I'm going 9-5-4
to look for squatters.

271
00:11:41,300 --> 00:11:44,886
Control, 7-L-19, I'm code 4.

272
00:11:46,263 --> 00:11:49,725
There's no one here but me
and some spiders.

273
00:12:00,277 --> 00:12:02,154
Uh...

274
00:12:02,154 --> 00:12:03,405
Hey!

275
00:12:04,705 --> 00:12:07,758
Control, 7-L-19,
I need backup to my last...

276
00:12:07,868 --> 00:12:08,910
Damn it!

277
00:12:08,910 --> 00:12:10,579
Hey!

278
00:12:10,579 --> 00:12:12,706
Can anyone hear me?

279
00:12:17,002 --> 00:12:18,253
It's not funny.

280
00:12:18,253 --> 00:12:19,713
Thanks for
letting me drive.

281
00:12:19,713 --> 00:12:20,964
You know,
at the Academy,

282
00:12:20,964 --> 00:12:23,550
they said it would be six months
before I got the chance.

283
00:12:25,552 --> 00:12:27,596
Sorry. The -- The smell
will pass soon.

284
00:12:27,596 --> 00:12:28,805
No, it's alright.

285
00:12:28,805 --> 00:12:30,640
I, uh -- I know plenty of cops
who wear

286
00:12:30,640 --> 00:12:32,768
a St. Christopher's medal --
uh, protection.

287
00:12:32,768 --> 00:12:35,771
Mm.
Police are
a superstitious bunch.

288
00:12:35,771 --> 00:12:37,356
What about you?

289
00:12:37,356 --> 00:12:38,732
Do you believe in
that kind of thing or...?

290
00:12:38,732 --> 00:12:39,858
Superstitions?
Mm-hmm.

291
00:12:39,858 --> 00:12:41,360
No, no. Not really.

292
00:12:41,360 --> 00:12:44,571
In high school, I, uh, didn't
wash my hockey jersey for a year

293
00:12:44,571 --> 00:12:45,614
because of
a winning streak.

294
00:12:45,614 --> 00:12:46,782
Oh, see, that's gross.

295
00:12:54,456 --> 00:12:56,708
I didn't see this vehicle
commit a violation.

296
00:12:56,708 --> 00:12:58,168
Why are we
pulling them over?

297
00:12:58,168 --> 00:13:00,128
Something's wrong with it.

298
00:13:00,128 --> 00:13:01,755
We're gonna have to be
a little more specific.

299
00:13:01,755 --> 00:13:04,966
Officer Juarez, protocol is
we call it in first.

300
00:13:10,806 --> 00:13:12,516
Was I going too fast,
Officer?

301
00:13:12,516 --> 00:13:14,434
No, ma'am.

302
00:13:14,434 --> 00:13:15,644
Ask for I. D.

303
00:13:15,644 --> 00:13:18,605
Ma'am, I'd like to take a look
in your trunk.

304
00:13:18,605 --> 00:13:20,399
Guess that's alright.

305
00:13:21,858 --> 00:13:23,777
Uh, ma'am, that won't be
necessary.

306
00:13:23,777 --> 00:13:25,695
Officer Juarez,
come speak with me.

307
00:13:28,824 --> 00:13:30,075
What's the probable cause?

308
00:13:30,075 --> 00:13:32,494
There's something dark
coming from that trunk.

309
00:13:32,494 --> 00:13:34,079
Dark?
Like an aura.

310
00:13:34,079 --> 00:13:36,665
Officer Juarez,
we do not pull over vehicles

311
00:13:36,665 --> 00:13:38,208
because they give us
the heebie-jeebies.

312
00:13:38,208 --> 00:13:41,336
And we certainly do not search
trunks without probable cause.

313
00:13:41,336 --> 00:13:43,672
That is a form of profiling,
and I won't have it.

314
00:13:43,672 --> 00:13:45,841
But she consented, so I --
I don't care.

315
00:13:45,841 --> 00:13:47,092
She's an elderly woman

316
00:13:47,092 --> 00:13:49,094
who is clearly intimidated
by police officers.

317
00:13:49,094 --> 00:13:51,304
You're taking advantage
of that fear.

318
00:13:51,304 --> 00:13:52,264
Just look.

319
00:13:52,264 --> 00:13:53,849
No.
I'm...

320
00:13:59,813 --> 00:14:01,356
That's blood.

321
00:14:01,356 --> 00:14:02,816
I knew it.

322
00:14:10,023 --> 00:14:11,191
Alright, ma'am.
Thank you.

323
00:14:13,485 --> 00:14:14,736
How is she?

324
00:14:14,736 --> 00:14:16,196
Upset.

325
00:14:16,196 --> 00:14:17,406
I tried to dust her off.

326
00:14:17,406 --> 00:14:19,074
She still wants to file
a formal complaint.

327
00:14:19,074 --> 00:14:21,076
Look, I've never had to say this
to a rookie before,

328
00:14:21,076 --> 00:14:24,121
but you cannot pull someone over
for having a dark aura --

329
00:14:24,121 --> 00:14:26,039
or any kind of aura.

330
00:14:26,039 --> 00:14:28,458
Nolan, how could you let
your boot make a stop like that?

331
00:14:28,458 --> 00:14:30,460
I'm sorry, sir.
The situation got away from me.

332
00:14:30,460 --> 00:14:32,087
Okay, but what about the blood
in the trunk?

333
00:14:32,087 --> 00:14:34,298
She says she has a grandson that
sometimes borrows the car.

334
00:14:34,298 --> 00:14:35,924
He -- Maybe he spilled
something.

335
00:14:35,924 --> 00:14:36,884
Look,
we'll collect a sample.

336
00:14:36,884 --> 00:14:38,302
We'll test to see
if it's human.

337
00:14:38,302 --> 00:14:40,429
If it is,
then we really have a problem.

338
00:14:40,429 --> 00:14:42,222
Okay, but won't that mean
I was right?

339
00:14:42,222 --> 00:14:43,515
The crime was committed,
so --

340
00:14:43,515 --> 00:14:45,058
Yes, probably.

341
00:14:45,058 --> 00:14:47,895
But since the evidence was found
during an illegal stop,

342
00:14:47,895 --> 00:14:49,646
it's inadmissible in court.

343
00:14:49,646 --> 00:14:51,356
It's the fruit
of a poisonous tree.

344
00:14:53,358 --> 00:14:56,445
Nolan, think you can handle
taking this back to the station?

345
00:14:56,445 --> 00:14:58,530
Sir.

346
00:14:58,530 --> 00:15:00,115
You ever do anything
like that again,

347
00:15:00,115 --> 00:15:01,450
not only will you
be disciplined,

348
00:15:01,450 --> 00:15:03,035
you'll be
out of the LAPD.

349
00:15:03,035 --> 00:15:04,828
You got it?
Yes, sir.

350
00:15:04,828 --> 00:15:07,164
Now go apologize to that woman
and tell her she's free to go.

351
00:15:11,919 --> 00:15:14,087
Well, my catfish
just messaged me.

352
00:15:14,087 --> 00:15:16,840
Said he wants a PS5,
or he's gonna release the photo.

353
00:15:16,840 --> 00:15:17,925
That's it?

354
00:15:17,925 --> 00:15:19,259
I mean, they are
really hard to find.

355
00:15:19,259 --> 00:15:20,928
Okay.
Where's the drop?

356
00:15:20,928 --> 00:15:22,054
Looks like his apartment.

357
00:15:22,054 --> 00:15:23,221
So he's a dumbass.
Great.

358
00:15:23,221 --> 00:15:24,598
Alright,
we'll pick one up on the way.

359
00:15:24,598 --> 00:15:26,475
Oh, uh...

360
00:15:26,475 --> 00:15:27,976
I thought you weren't supposed
to negotiate with terrorists.

361
00:15:27,976 --> 00:15:29,895
Well, he's not a terrorist.
He's an idiot.

362
00:15:29,895 --> 00:15:31,688
But if we arrest him,
that photo becomes evidence.

363
00:15:31,688 --> 00:15:33,649
Everyone at the station
sees it.

364
00:15:35,025 --> 00:15:36,860
Good thing I got a gamer connect
in K-Town.

365
00:15:36,860 --> 00:15:39,279
Of course you do.

366
00:15:39,279 --> 00:15:41,823
Control, 7-L-19.
Do you copy?

367
00:15:43,158 --> 00:15:44,993
Oh!

368
00:15:48,121 --> 00:15:50,165
It's gonna be fine.
This is fine.

369
00:15:50,165 --> 00:15:53,001
They will do a welfare check
when I don't report in,

370
00:15:53,001 --> 00:15:55,963
and this is fine.

371
00:15:58,340 --> 00:16:01,468
Until then, I will read,

372
00:16:01,468 --> 00:16:04,638
because there is
nothing else to do.

373
00:16:08,809 --> 00:16:10,060
Morning.

374
00:16:10,060 --> 00:16:12,646
Hey. Need help again
with the copier?

375
00:16:12,646 --> 00:16:14,314
No, no.

376
00:16:14,314 --> 00:16:16,066
I've made peace with the fact
that it's possessed.

377
00:16:16,066 --> 00:16:18,110
I was just dropping by
to see how you're doing.

378
00:16:18,110 --> 00:16:19,987
You talked to Lucy.

379
00:16:19,987 --> 00:16:21,822
Yeah.

380
00:16:21,822 --> 00:16:24,199
I think the Dye-Hards thing
has spun her out.

381
00:16:24,199 --> 00:16:25,534
Yeah.

382
00:16:25,534 --> 00:16:28,161
That's why I didn't tell her
about it while she was away.

383
00:16:28,161 --> 00:16:30,789
Yeah, I wish she'd just
believe me that I'm fine.

384
00:16:30,789 --> 00:16:32,708
You probably don't know this
about me,

385
00:16:32,708 --> 00:16:35,877
but I was stabbed a few years
ago at the courthouse.

386
00:16:35,877 --> 00:16:39,381
What? No, uh, I didn't.
That's awful.

387
00:16:39,381 --> 00:16:41,425
I'm telling you this
so that you know

388
00:16:41,425 --> 00:16:44,344
that I've been
where you are.

389
00:16:44,344 --> 00:16:46,847
All I wanted was for people
to stop seeing me as a victim.

390
00:16:46,847 --> 00:16:48,473
Exactly.

391
00:16:48,473 --> 00:16:51,768
My friends on the message board,
they don't treat me like that.

392
00:16:51,768 --> 00:16:55,147
They see me as someone with
valuable insight into Rosalind.

393
00:16:55,147 --> 00:16:57,190
And that must feel great.

394
00:16:57,190 --> 00:17:00,736
It's like you're back in control
of your own narrative again.

395
00:17:01,036 --> 00:17:04,372
But simply saying you're okay
doesn't make it so.

396
00:17:04,372 --> 00:17:08,543
Just consider it.

397
00:17:08,543 --> 00:17:10,253
I will.

398
00:17:10,253 --> 00:17:12,380
Hey, if you're looking for
a community that understands

399
00:17:12,380 --> 00:17:16,051
what you've been through,
you got Lucy and me.

400
00:17:16,051 --> 00:17:19,721
Thanks.
I appreciate that.

401
00:17:19,721 --> 00:17:22,766
Okay, man.

402
00:17:24,184 --> 00:17:26,978
So why the hell was your rookie
driving in the first place?

403
00:17:26,978 --> 00:17:28,146
That's how I was taught.

404
00:17:28,146 --> 00:17:29,731
It's not standard practice.

405
00:17:29,731 --> 00:17:31,524
Once you've been a T. O.
for a few years,

406
00:17:31,524 --> 00:17:33,860
then you can get creative
with the guidelines.

407
00:17:33,860 --> 00:17:36,029
On your first day,
stick to the damn script.

408
00:17:36,029 --> 00:17:37,113
Yes, sir.

409
00:17:37,113 --> 00:17:38,156
Where's Juarez now?

410
00:17:38,156 --> 00:17:39,532
Writing up the report.

411
00:17:39,532 --> 00:17:41,201
I want you to
triple check it.

412
00:17:41,201 --> 00:17:44,245
All the paperwork surrounding
this needs to be immaculate,

413
00:17:44,245 --> 00:17:46,790
so make sure she specifies
that she was unable

414
00:17:46,790 --> 00:17:49,250
to articulate
the reason for the stop.

415
00:17:49,250 --> 00:17:51,461
Yes, sir. I'll also be writing
up a blue page on her.

416
00:17:51,461 --> 00:17:54,422
In it, you need to detail how,
as Juarez's T. O.,

417
00:17:54,422 --> 00:17:57,300
how you plan to correct her
moving forward.

418
00:17:57,300 --> 00:17:58,927
It may have been
her mistake,

419
00:17:58,927 --> 00:18:02,263
but as her supervisor,
she's your responsibility.

420
00:18:09,270 --> 00:18:12,190
That can't be true.
Can it? I...

421
00:18:15,568 --> 00:18:19,739
Now, this user is making
sense -- TruthHunter184.

422
00:18:19,739 --> 00:18:21,741
"Don't give Rosalind
the satisfaction.

423
00:18:21,741 --> 00:18:24,369
She eats her victim's pain
like a five-star meal."

424
00:18:27,122 --> 00:18:29,374
"Like a five-star meal."

425
00:18:30,959 --> 00:18:33,420
Rosalind said that to Nolan.

426
00:18:33,420 --> 00:18:34,838
Hey!

427
00:18:34,838 --> 00:18:37,215
Hey!
Can anybody hear me?!

428
00:18:39,634 --> 00:18:41,636
Yo,
I got what you asked for.

429
00:18:41,636 --> 00:18:42,846
Drop it and leave.

430
00:18:47,976 --> 00:18:49,144
Hello.

431
00:18:49,144 --> 00:18:50,729
Sergeant Bradford,
LAPD.

432
00:18:50,729 --> 00:18:53,648
Hi, uh, O-Officers.
What's up?

433
00:18:53,648 --> 00:18:55,150
You're blackmailing me.

434
00:18:55,150 --> 00:18:57,318
Do you have any idea
how serious of a crime this is?

435
00:18:57,318 --> 00:18:58,737
I could charge you
with a felony.

436
00:18:58,737 --> 00:19:01,322
Hold on, 'kay? I-I wasn't really
gonna release the -- the photo.

437
00:19:01,322 --> 00:19:03,158
I-I just --
just wanted the PS5.

438
00:19:03,158 --> 00:19:04,993
My mom won't get me one.

439
00:19:04,993 --> 00:19:06,828
Pavi,
are you talking to me?

440
00:19:06,828 --> 00:19:09,748
No, Mom. God!
Just stay out of it.

441
00:19:11,207 --> 00:19:12,333
Oh, I think we should
get Mom out here.

442
00:19:12,333 --> 00:19:14,127
No, whoa.
That's not necessary. No.

443
00:19:14,127 --> 00:19:15,962
Then delete the photo.
Now.

444
00:19:15,962 --> 00:19:17,255
Okay. Alright. Yeah.

445
00:19:17,255 --> 00:19:21,217
Deleting the photo. Okay.
See? It's gone.

446
00:19:21,217 --> 00:19:23,428
And get rid of
the dating profile, too, okay?

447
00:19:23,428 --> 00:19:25,221
It's messed up,
catfishing people.

448
00:19:25,221 --> 00:19:26,890
Yeah, done.

449
00:19:26,890 --> 00:19:29,267
Bad behavior
does not get a reward.

450
00:19:29,267 --> 00:19:31,936
You do anything like that again,
I'll make sure your phone

451
00:19:31,936 --> 00:19:33,980
and laptop are collected
as evidence.

452
00:19:33,980 --> 00:19:35,273
You got it?

453
00:19:35,273 --> 00:19:37,817
You suck.

454
00:19:37,817 --> 00:19:40,028
Sweet kid.

455
00:19:40,028 --> 00:19:41,446
So, what's up?
We taking this back or --

456
00:19:41,446 --> 00:19:43,072
Hell no.
Taking this home.

457
00:19:43,072 --> 00:19:44,616
You know how hard it is
to find one of these?

458
00:19:46,159 --> 00:19:48,328
Harper.

459
00:19:48,328 --> 00:19:49,913
Are you sure?

460
00:19:49,913 --> 00:19:51,331
What?

461
00:19:51,331 --> 00:19:52,624
Jill's blood was swabbed

462
00:19:52,624 --> 00:19:54,501
from the trunk of a car
during a traffic stop.

463
00:19:54,501 --> 00:19:55,835
Whose car?

464
00:19:55,835 --> 00:19:58,797
Whose car?

465
00:19:58,797 --> 00:20:01,174
Wait. They what?

466
00:20:02,425 --> 00:20:04,427
Do you know
how dead to me you are?

467
00:20:04,427 --> 00:20:06,763
The blood that you found
in the car belongs to a woman

468
00:20:06,763 --> 00:20:08,723
who has been missing
for three days.

469
00:20:08,723 --> 00:20:10,475
It is our only lead.

470
00:20:10,475 --> 00:20:12,560
And -- And now I hear
that it's a bad stop?

471
00:20:12,560 --> 00:20:13,853
I know. I'm sorry.

472
00:20:13,853 --> 00:20:15,230
It was my fault.
I'm --

473
00:20:15,230 --> 00:20:18,817
His rookie. Which means that
you are his responsibility.

474
00:20:18,817 --> 00:20:21,778
Nolan, I trained you
better than this.

475
00:20:21,778 --> 00:20:24,531
And now you are both
making me look bad.

476
00:20:26,407 --> 00:20:28,034
I just got off the phone
with T. I. D.

477
00:20:28,034 --> 00:20:29,369
When they went
to impound the car,

478
00:20:29,369 --> 00:20:31,496
they took a preliminary look
and said the blood appears to be

479
00:20:31,496 --> 00:20:33,456
only 10 to 12 hours old.

480
00:20:33,456 --> 00:20:34,707
Jill could still be alive.

481
00:20:34,707 --> 00:20:36,125
Oh, then we gotta
move quickly.

482
00:20:36,125 --> 00:20:37,502
Not so fast.

483
00:20:37,502 --> 00:20:38,920
I take it
you're Officer Juarez?

484
00:20:38,920 --> 00:20:39,963
Yes, sir.

485
00:20:39,963 --> 00:20:42,048
Wesley Evers
from the D. A.'s office.

486
00:20:42,048 --> 00:20:43,967
Since the blood evidence
you found is inadmissible,

487
00:20:43,967 --> 00:20:45,885
the LAPD will have
to figure out another way

488
00:20:45,885 --> 00:20:47,595
to implicate your suspect
in this crime.

489
00:20:47,595 --> 00:20:49,097
So we do have
a suspect?

490
00:20:49,097 --> 00:20:51,432
Our missing person's
ex-boyfriend, Tyler Harvin.

491
00:20:51,432 --> 00:20:53,142
The car belongs
to his grandmother.

492
00:20:53,142 --> 00:20:55,436
She confirmed that
he has regular access to it.

493
00:20:55,436 --> 00:20:57,981
So to nail this guy in court,
I need something concrete

494
00:20:57,981 --> 00:20:59,732
tying him
to Jill's disappearance.

495
00:20:59,732 --> 00:21:01,776
Without P. C.,
Carradine won't authorize

496
00:21:01,776 --> 00:21:03,403
a surveillance detail
on Harvin.

497
00:21:03,403 --> 00:21:05,780
But he did agree
to let me and Lopez

498
00:21:05,780 --> 00:21:07,574
run foot surveillance
ourselves.

499
00:21:07,574 --> 00:21:10,326
If we can catch Tyler engaging
in suspicious activity,

500
00:21:10,326 --> 00:21:11,911
Carradine said
he'd approve a full team.

501
00:21:11,911 --> 00:21:14,414
You're gonna try and run foot
surveillance with two officers?

502
00:21:14,414 --> 00:21:17,292
No, four. You and your rookie
are gonna start

503
00:21:17,292 --> 00:21:19,627
digging your way
out of my doghouse by helping.

504
00:21:19,627 --> 00:21:22,505
Remember, Harvin has
a history of violence.

505
00:21:22,505 --> 00:21:24,883
Don't underestimate him.

506
00:21:26,426 --> 00:21:29,137
I've got Harvin heading north
down Lake.

507
00:21:29,137 --> 00:21:32,432
Black pants, blue ball cap,
light-blue shirt.

508
00:21:32,432 --> 00:21:34,100
Roger that.
Standing by.

509
00:21:34,100 --> 00:21:36,978
Alright. I need you to focus on
what I'm about to say.

510
00:21:36,978 --> 00:21:38,771
Everything you learned
at the Academy

511
00:21:38,771 --> 00:21:41,608
goes out the window
the moment the adrenaline hits.

512
00:21:41,608 --> 00:21:43,443
You have to keep thinking,

513
00:21:43,443 --> 00:21:45,778
remain aware of your
surroundings at all times,

514
00:21:45,778 --> 00:21:47,947
and avoid
any physical contact

515
00:21:47,947 --> 00:21:49,490
unless someone's life
has been threatened.

516
00:21:49,490 --> 00:21:51,409
Yes, sir.

517
00:21:51,409 --> 00:21:52,452
I've got him.

518
00:21:54,412 --> 00:21:57,290
I'll pick you up
in the alley.

519
00:22:04,547 --> 00:22:07,008
Continuing west on Eleventh.

520
00:22:16,059 --> 00:22:17,977
He just turned onto Grandview.
He's heading north.

521
00:22:17,977 --> 00:22:19,020
That's us.

522
00:22:40,875 --> 00:22:42,377
He's running!

523
00:22:42,377 --> 00:22:43,753
Which way?

524
00:22:43,753 --> 00:22:46,005
North on Grandview,
west side of the street.

525
00:22:56,224 --> 00:22:57,892
Hey!

526
00:23:07,362 --> 00:23:09,198
I can't believe my career
was almost ruined by a kid

527
00:23:09,198 --> 00:23:10,491
whose mom still does
his laundry.

528
00:23:14,059 --> 00:23:16,153
When was the last time
you heard Chen on the radio?

529
00:23:17,538 --> 00:23:20,583
I can't remember. It was like
an hour ago, maybe two.

530
00:23:23,920 --> 00:23:25,630
Dispatch,
this is 7-Adam-100.

531
00:23:25,630 --> 00:23:28,090
Can you perform a security
check on Officer Chen?

532
00:23:28,090 --> 00:23:30,426
Hold on, 7-Adam-100.

533
00:23:30,426 --> 00:23:32,803
She's not responding.

534
00:23:32,803 --> 00:23:34,430
When was last contact?

535
00:23:34,430 --> 00:23:38,476
According to the logs,
it was over two hours ago.

536
00:23:38,476 --> 00:23:40,353
Alright, that's a problem
we're gonna talk about later.

537
00:23:40,353 --> 00:23:42,230
Right now, give me
her last known address.

538
00:23:48,152 --> 00:23:49,946
Chen?

539
00:23:52,573 --> 00:23:54,867
Chen!

540
00:23:54,867 --> 00:23:56,410
Yeah.

541
00:23:56,410 --> 00:23:58,162
Yeah, I'm in here.

542
00:24:02,208 --> 00:24:03,960
Hang on.
The door is stuck.

543
00:24:03,960 --> 00:24:05,419
Yeah, no kidding.

544
00:24:08,381 --> 00:24:09,298
You okay?

545
00:24:09,298 --> 00:24:11,050
I-I think I have a lead
on Rosalind.

546
00:24:11,050 --> 00:24:12,260
-What?
-How?

547
00:24:12,260 --> 00:24:14,303
Chris has been spending time
on these message boards

548
00:24:14,303 --> 00:24:15,972
filled with
armchair detectives

549
00:24:15,972 --> 00:24:17,265
that are trying to
track Rosalind down.

550
00:24:17,265 --> 00:24:18,349
You think one of them
found her?

551
00:24:18,349 --> 00:24:20,768
I think one of them
is her.

552
00:24:20,768 --> 00:24:23,271
I would add that it was
an error in judgment

553
00:24:23,271 --> 00:24:25,106
that you will not repeat.

554
00:24:25,106 --> 00:24:28,025
And this memorandum
is going to the Watch Commander?

555
00:24:28,025 --> 00:24:31,487
Yeah. And then he will run it
up the chain of command.

556
00:24:31,487 --> 00:24:34,115
Are they gonna wash me out?

557
00:24:36,450 --> 00:24:38,578
It's a possibility.

558
00:24:38,578 --> 00:24:40,454
You can be fired
for literally anything

559
00:24:40,454 --> 00:24:41,998
in your probationary period.

560
00:24:41,998 --> 00:24:45,001
But, on the other hand,
it's your first day.

561
00:24:45,001 --> 00:24:47,336
Your failure
is more so on me.

562
00:24:47,336 --> 00:24:49,171
Are they gonna find Jill
on time?

563
00:24:49,171 --> 00:24:50,673
I hope so.

564
00:24:50,673 --> 00:24:52,466
But you should prepare
for the worst.

565
00:24:52,466 --> 00:24:55,845
No, she's still alive.
I can feel it.

566
00:24:55,845 --> 00:24:58,014
The way you felt
the bad aura?

567
00:24:58,014 --> 00:25:00,182
Yes.

568
00:25:00,182 --> 00:25:04,312
Look, I-I know that
in the movies,

569
00:25:04,312 --> 00:25:06,439
police seem to rely on
their intuitions

570
00:25:06,439 --> 00:25:08,899
all the time
about a suspect.

571
00:25:08,899 --> 00:25:12,903
In reality,
this is not the case.

572
00:25:12,903 --> 00:25:14,739
What you see as intuition

573
00:25:14,739 --> 00:25:18,993
is actually years
of hard-won knowledge

574
00:25:18,993 --> 00:25:21,829
in how to interpret things
like body language.

575
00:25:21,829 --> 00:25:25,082
It's not a mystical power.
It's observation.

576
00:25:25,082 --> 00:25:28,210
And even then,
cops get it wrong all the time.

577
00:25:28,210 --> 00:25:30,588
With all due respect,

578
00:25:30,588 --> 00:25:32,923
reading someone's
body language sounds

579
00:25:32,923 --> 00:25:35,343
just as mysterious
as my feelings.

580
00:25:35,343 --> 00:25:37,678
That's because you don't have
the experience to back it up.

581
00:25:37,678 --> 00:25:40,389
You sound just like
the old-school instructors

582
00:25:40,389 --> 00:25:42,892
at the Academy,
going on about tradition

583
00:25:42,892 --> 00:25:46,520
while conveniently leaving out
the dark side of that tradition.

584
00:25:46,520 --> 00:25:49,899
I thought you wanted to be
a different kind of T. O.

585
00:25:49,899 --> 00:25:52,026
Why can't I be
a different kind of cop?

586
00:25:52,026 --> 00:25:53,903
Maybe one day you can be.

587
00:25:53,903 --> 00:25:56,906
But first, you have to learn
the fundamentals.

588
00:25:56,906 --> 00:25:58,824
But I was right
about the car.

589
00:25:58,824 --> 00:26:00,284
Yes, you were.

590
00:26:00,284 --> 00:26:02,703
And I bet you think it's unfair
that that stop was inadmissible.

591
00:26:02,703 --> 00:26:04,205
But I want you to think about
what would happen

592
00:26:04,205 --> 00:26:08,084
if the police were able to stop
people based on feelings alone.

593
00:26:08,084 --> 00:26:11,087
Where do we draw the line
between a dark aura

594
00:26:11,087 --> 00:26:13,089
and outright prejudice?

595
00:26:13,089 --> 00:26:17,301
That's why the rule exists.
To protect people.

596
00:26:17,301 --> 00:26:21,347
I don't see how the rules
are protecting Jill Baskin.

597
00:26:30,856 --> 00:26:32,274
Hey.
Lucy.

598
00:26:32,274 --> 00:26:33,609
Hey, what's going on?
They won't tell me.

599
00:26:33,609 --> 00:26:34,777
Sit down.

600
00:26:34,777 --> 00:26:37,446
Okay, so, um, I went through
"The Mother Doc,"

601
00:26:37,446 --> 00:26:39,407
and I think
I found Rosalind.

602
00:26:39,407 --> 00:26:42,410
What? Where?
That sighting in Rome?

603
00:26:42,410 --> 00:26:43,911
N-No. I --

604
00:26:43,911 --> 00:26:47,456
Are you familiar with
the username "TruthHunter184"?

605
00:26:47,456 --> 00:26:51,419
Yeah.
Uh, he lives in Atlanta.

606
00:26:52,962 --> 00:26:54,505
He doesn't?

607
00:26:54,505 --> 00:26:56,382
Lucy found
some irregularities

608
00:26:56,382 --> 00:26:57,842
in TruthHunter's
communication style,

609
00:26:57,842 --> 00:26:59,635
so she asked us
to look into it.

610
00:26:59,635 --> 00:27:01,721
I reviewed all of
TruthHunter's messages,

611
00:27:01,721 --> 00:27:03,472
and I agree
with Officer Chen.

612
00:27:03,472 --> 00:27:06,809
The forensic linguistics
are a match to Rosalind Dyer.

613
00:27:06,809 --> 00:27:09,603
But -- No, that doesn't
make any sense.

614
00:27:09,603 --> 00:27:12,189
Do you remember when
TruthHunter wrote

615
00:27:12,189 --> 00:27:15,776
Rosalind "eats her victim's pain
like a five-star meal"?

616
00:27:15,776 --> 00:27:17,528
Yeah.

617
00:27:17,528 --> 00:27:19,572
I heard Rosalind
use that exact phrase

618
00:27:19,572 --> 00:27:21,699
to describe the pleasure
she took at her trial

619
00:27:21,699 --> 00:27:24,285
when watching the agony
of her victims' families.

620
00:27:27,496 --> 00:27:30,291
I told her things about me,
about the investigation.

621
00:27:30,291 --> 00:27:31,834
It's okay.
You didn't know.

622
00:27:31,834 --> 00:27:33,294
Uh, so what do we do?

623
00:27:33,294 --> 00:27:35,880
I can message her,
try to set up a meeting.

624
00:27:35,880 --> 00:27:38,007
N-No. Uh, Rosalind will
see right through that.

625
00:27:38,007 --> 00:27:40,551
I agree. With this level
of intelligent psychopath,

626
00:27:40,551 --> 00:27:42,845
I would advise to err
on the side of caution.

627
00:27:42,845 --> 00:27:44,180
So we work with
what we've got.

628
00:27:44,180 --> 00:27:45,639
We get cyber crimes involved,

629
00:27:45,639 --> 00:27:47,850
and we see if we can track her
using her I. P. address.

630
00:27:47,850 --> 00:27:48,976
And if we find anything,

631
00:27:48,976 --> 00:27:50,227
we promise to keep you
in the loop.

632
00:27:50,227 --> 00:27:51,854
Thank you.

633
00:27:51,854 --> 00:27:53,189
Yeah. Uh, thanks.

634
00:27:57,067 --> 00:27:58,903
Hey. Are you okay?

635
00:27:58,903 --> 00:28:01,489
No.
I'm really not.

636
00:28:12,082 --> 00:28:16,295
Officer Nolan, I-I want
to apologize for yesterday.

637
00:28:16,295 --> 00:28:17,880
Look,
I was upset that my mistake

638
00:28:17,880 --> 00:28:19,423
may have put Jill
in further jeopardy,

639
00:28:19,423 --> 00:28:21,175
and I unfairly took it out
on you.

640
00:28:21,175 --> 00:28:22,718
I promise to do better.

641
00:28:22,718 --> 00:28:24,512
I appreciate that.

642
00:28:24,512 --> 00:28:26,514
I also thought about
our conversation.

643
00:28:26,514 --> 00:28:30,017
I want you to trust me
with your feelings.

644
00:28:30,017 --> 00:28:33,020
If you had confided in me
yesterday before the car stop,

645
00:28:33,020 --> 00:28:35,564
we could have avoided
this whole mess.

646
00:28:35,564 --> 00:28:37,858
So next time
you have an idea,

647
00:28:37,858 --> 00:28:40,361
no matter how crazy,
tell me about it.

648
00:28:40,361 --> 00:28:41,403
Oh, thank God.

649
00:28:41,403 --> 00:28:43,113
Because I had
the wildest dream.

650
00:28:43,113 --> 00:28:46,534
Okay, that's not exactly
what I...

651
00:28:46,534 --> 00:28:49,119
No, you're right. I'm sorry.
Tell me your dream.

652
00:28:49,119 --> 00:28:52,748
I was up half the night doing
a deep dive on Tyler Harvin.

653
00:28:52,748 --> 00:28:54,124
When I finally fell asleep,

654
00:28:54,124 --> 00:28:56,168
I-I dreamt that
I was on the beach

655
00:28:56,168 --> 00:28:58,254
and a body
washed up on shore.

656
00:28:58,254 --> 00:28:59,547
Jill Baskin?

657
00:28:59,547 --> 00:29:01,590
No. It was a man.
A giant, actually.

658
00:29:01,590 --> 00:29:04,093
Wearing an old-timey armor,

659
00:29:04,093 --> 00:29:06,804
holding a big wooden shield
with a crown on it.

660
00:29:06,804 --> 00:29:08,889
Okay.
And you think this knight

661
00:29:08,889 --> 00:29:10,808
had something to do with
Jill's abduction?

662
00:29:10,808 --> 00:29:13,102
I don't know.
But it was so vivid.

663
00:29:13,102 --> 00:29:16,105
And I thought m-maybe Jill's
being kept near a beach.

664
00:29:16,105 --> 00:29:18,732
Okay. Um...

665
00:29:18,732 --> 00:29:22,444
You said you were looking into
Tyler when you fell asleep.

666
00:29:22,444 --> 00:29:23,821
What exactly
did you find?

667
00:29:23,821 --> 00:29:25,489
I was looking into
his work history.

668
00:29:25,489 --> 00:29:27,032
I mean,
he does a lot of odd jobs

669
00:29:27,032 --> 00:29:29,493
all over the city --
landscaping, contracting.

670
00:29:29,493 --> 00:29:31,203
And I thought
one of these jobs

671
00:29:31,203 --> 00:29:33,122
may have given him access
to a hiding place --

672
00:29:33,122 --> 00:29:34,790
maybe somewhere
off a beaten path

673
00:29:34,790 --> 00:29:36,292
where he might be
holding Jill.

674
00:29:36,292 --> 00:29:39,962
Okay. Uh, were any of the jobs
near a beach?

675
00:29:39,962 --> 00:29:41,130
Did any of them
have anything to do with

676
00:29:41,130 --> 00:29:42,631
the name Knight
or Shield?

677
00:29:42,631 --> 00:29:44,675
A company name?
Maybe a client?

678
00:29:44,675 --> 00:29:47,845
Well, he finished work
a few weeks ago for a job

679
00:29:47,845 --> 00:29:52,224
on a company called
A Royal Hand Construction.

680
00:29:52,224 --> 00:29:55,894
And the house was on a street
called Beachwood Canyon.

681
00:29:55,894 --> 00:29:57,771
Show me on Streetview.

682
00:30:00,983 --> 00:30:03,277
See, Tyler could have seen
this condemned house

683
00:30:03,277 --> 00:30:05,279
while he was
working here for Royal.

684
00:30:05,279 --> 00:30:07,072
Your dream
wasn't a premonition.

685
00:30:07,072 --> 00:30:09,617
It was just your subconscious
processing information.

686
00:30:09,617 --> 00:30:11,619
So you don't think
I'm crazy?

687
00:30:11,619 --> 00:30:13,954
I'm not saying that.
But I think we should do it --

688
00:30:13,954 --> 00:30:16,332
take a look at that house before
we talk to Harper and Lopez.

689
00:30:16,332 --> 00:30:17,750
You wanted to see me, sir?

690
00:30:17,750 --> 00:30:19,084
That was Garza.

691
00:30:19,084 --> 00:30:20,586
Their cyber crime people

692
00:30:20,586 --> 00:30:23,213
traced the web
of Rosalind's I. P. addresses

693
00:30:23,213 --> 00:30:25,007
to a house
outside Seattle.

694
00:30:25,007 --> 00:30:26,800
They're putting together
a surveillance team

695
00:30:26,800 --> 00:30:28,010
to go there now.

696
00:30:28,010 --> 00:30:29,887
Agent Garza has
invited you to join.

697
00:30:29,887 --> 00:30:32,139
Really?
That -- That's amazing.

698
00:30:32,139 --> 00:30:33,515
Yeah, I-I'm in.

699
00:30:33,515 --> 00:30:34,725
Jet leaves in an hour.

700
00:30:34,725 --> 00:30:35,809
Sir.

701
00:30:36,194 --> 00:30:37,153
What the hell?

702
00:30:37,153 --> 00:30:39,072
Oh, good morning,
Cop Cake.

703
00:30:39,072 --> 00:30:42,450
Oh, man.

704
00:30:42,450 --> 00:30:44,619
Yeah, I'm thinking we need to
pay our catfish another visit.

705
00:30:44,619 --> 00:30:46,162
Damn straight.

706
00:30:46,162 --> 00:30:49,415
Alright.
You take the east side.

707
00:30:49,415 --> 00:30:50,917
I'll take the west.

708
00:30:50,917 --> 00:30:52,460
And then
meet in the middle.

709
00:30:52,460 --> 00:30:53,753
Copy.
Radio if you see anything.

710
00:30:53,753 --> 00:30:54,963
Will do.

711
00:31:17,819 --> 00:31:19,487
Nolan, I found her.

712
00:31:19,487 --> 00:31:21,447
East side of the house
at the window.

713
00:31:29,539 --> 00:31:31,165
Stand back.

714
00:31:42,218 --> 00:31:43,386
Cleared.

715
00:31:47,015 --> 00:31:48,891
Check her.

716
00:31:51,060 --> 00:31:52,812
She's alive.

717
00:31:52,812 --> 00:31:54,397
Alright.
Stay with her.

718
00:31:54,397 --> 00:31:55,815
I'm gonna clear the house.

719
00:31:58,067 --> 00:32:00,361
Hey, Jill.
My name is Celina.

720
00:32:00,361 --> 00:32:01,738
Everything's gonna be alright.

721
00:32:01,738 --> 00:32:03,197
Patrol, 7-Adam-15.

722
00:32:03,197 --> 00:32:05,491
Show us at
6577 Beachwood Canyon,

723
00:32:05,491 --> 00:32:06,826
abandoned house.

724
00:32:06,826 --> 00:32:09,620
Found a female kidnap victim,
possibly Jill Baskin.

725
00:32:09,620 --> 00:32:10,872
Multiple stab wounds.

726
00:32:10,872 --> 00:32:12,749
Requesting R. A.
and additional units.

727
00:32:12,749 --> 00:32:15,668
Police!

728
00:32:15,668 --> 00:32:16,794
Is anyone in here?

729
00:32:16,794 --> 00:32:19,255
Come out with
your hands up now.

730
00:32:23,301 --> 00:32:24,427
Hey!

731
00:32:24,427 --> 00:32:26,262
Nolan, I see him!

732
00:32:26,262 --> 00:32:27,722
Stop!

733
00:32:31,768 --> 00:32:33,478
What do you got?

734
00:32:33,478 --> 00:32:36,606
Officer Juarez?

735
00:32:38,066 --> 00:32:39,901
Officer Juarez, check in.

736
00:32:41,402 --> 00:32:44,405
Officer Juarez,
please respond.

737
00:32:57,294 --> 00:32:58,504
Victim's in the bedroom.

738
00:32:58,504 --> 00:33:00,172
Severe blood loss,
but her vitals are stable.

739
00:33:00,172 --> 00:33:01,298
Copy that.
We're on it.

740
00:33:01,298 --> 00:33:03,300
Officer Juarez,
do you copy?

741
00:33:05,385 --> 00:33:07,471
Celina, do you hear me?

742
00:33:16,939 --> 00:33:18,816
Police!

743
00:33:37,126 --> 00:33:39,878
Officer Juarez, respond.

744
00:33:39,878 --> 00:33:42,840
7-Adam, um, it's Juarez.

745
00:33:42,840 --> 00:33:45,175
I had eyes on the suspect.
I'm in pursuit.

746
00:33:45,175 --> 00:33:47,803
Celina, I'm coming to you.
Where are you?

747
00:33:47,803 --> 00:33:49,346
I don't know.

748
00:33:49,346 --> 00:33:51,890
Are you on the trail?

749
00:33:51,890 --> 00:33:53,642
No. Uh...

750
00:33:53,642 --> 00:33:57,187
I think we were heading east,
but we turned.

751
00:34:07,364 --> 00:34:08,532
I see him.

752
00:34:08,532 --> 00:34:09,867
Does he have a weapon?

753
00:34:09,867 --> 00:34:11,160
I can't tell.

754
00:34:11,160 --> 00:34:13,829
Celina, I need you to focus
so I can find you.

755
00:34:13,829 --> 00:34:16,790
He's on the move.
He's on the move.

756
00:34:16,790 --> 00:34:19,501
7-Adam-15, my rookie's
in pursuit of suspect,

757
00:34:19,501 --> 00:34:21,295
but the specific location
is unknown.

758
00:34:21,295 --> 00:34:23,463
I am heading northeast
on trail road,

759
00:34:23,463 --> 00:34:26,008
requesting airship
and all available units

760
00:34:26,008 --> 00:34:28,719
to help locate suspect
and Officer Juarez.

761
00:34:28,719 --> 00:34:29,720
Code 3.

762
00:34:29,720 --> 00:34:32,639
Juarez, talk to me.

763
00:34:34,600 --> 00:34:37,853
I've lost visual.
I don't know where he went.

764
00:34:40,397 --> 00:34:42,232
Look around you.
What do you see?

765
00:34:42,232 --> 00:34:44,359
Just trees
and a footbridge.

766
00:34:44,359 --> 00:34:46,111
No buildings, no signs?

767
00:34:46,111 --> 00:34:48,488
I-I see one of those
electrical boxes.

768
00:34:48,488 --> 00:34:50,199
Great. Does it have any kind of
identifier on it?

769
00:34:50,199 --> 00:34:51,450
A serial number?

770
00:34:51,450 --> 00:34:52,868
Uh...

771
00:34:58,874 --> 00:35:00,375
Yeah.

772
00:35:00,375 --> 00:35:03,253
198962.

773
00:35:03,253 --> 00:35:06,381
Control, I need the location of
an L. A. City electrical box.

774
00:35:06,381 --> 00:35:10,177
Serial number 198962.

775
00:35:10,177 --> 00:35:11,845
Copy, 7-Adam-15.

776
00:35:11,845 --> 00:35:15,432
Sending the location
to your box.

777
00:35:15,432 --> 00:35:18,435
Okay, Celina, hang tight,
I got you.

778
00:35:18,435 --> 00:35:20,103
Copy that.

779
00:35:25,609 --> 00:35:28,070
Celina? Celina?

780
00:35:28,070 --> 00:35:29,905
Damn it, dispatch,
where is my airship?

781
00:35:29,905 --> 00:35:31,949
I have an officer
in need of help.

782
00:36:40,767 --> 00:36:41,893
It's okay.

783
00:36:43,020 --> 00:36:45,022
You're gonna be alright.

784
00:36:52,530 --> 00:36:54,574
How is Officer Juarez?

785
00:36:54,574 --> 00:36:56,159
Shaken up.
A little bruised.

786
00:36:56,159 --> 00:36:58,119
Nothing serious,
thank God.

787
00:36:58,119 --> 00:37:00,330
Not a great start.

788
00:37:00,330 --> 00:37:01,789
She'll bounce back.

789
00:37:01,789 --> 00:37:02,874
I meant you.

790
00:37:02,874 --> 00:37:04,667
I know.

791
00:37:04,667 --> 00:37:08,171
If that suspect had gotten
her gun away from her...

792
00:37:08,171 --> 00:37:11,924
These last few days
have been extremely humbling.

793
00:37:11,924 --> 00:37:14,218
Everything is moving
a hundred miles an hour.

794
00:37:14,218 --> 00:37:16,054
I feel like I barely have time
to teach her

795
00:37:16,054 --> 00:37:19,057
the most basic things
before everything goes sideways.

796
00:37:19,057 --> 00:37:22,393
Translation --
You feel like a rookie again.

797
00:37:22,393 --> 00:37:24,187
Yeah.

798
00:37:24,187 --> 00:37:27,190
Well, to her credit,
Celina managed to fight off

799
00:37:27,190 --> 00:37:30,193
a guy twice her size
after sprinting up a canyon.

800
00:37:30,193 --> 00:37:33,821
She's got spirit.
Maybe a little too much.

801
00:37:33,821 --> 00:37:35,907
You know anything
about horses, Nolan?

802
00:37:35,907 --> 00:37:37,533
I really don't, sir.

803
00:37:37,533 --> 00:37:39,869
Have a seat.

804
00:37:45,208 --> 00:37:50,463
Young racehorses are
skittish and excitable.

805
00:37:50,463 --> 00:37:55,176
To calm them down, they partner
them with older horses

806
00:37:55,176 --> 00:37:57,679
to teach them
how to check themselves.

807
00:37:57,679 --> 00:38:00,056
Eventually,
they come around.

808
00:38:00,056 --> 00:38:04,185
It's the natural order
of things.

809
00:38:04,185 --> 00:38:06,521
Officer Juarez, a word?

810
00:38:10,066 --> 00:38:12,235
I imagine that was a pretty
tough first case for you.

811
00:38:12,235 --> 00:38:14,404
Sir.

812
00:38:14,404 --> 00:38:16,739
Something wasn't adding up,

813
00:38:16,739 --> 00:38:20,159
so I requested
your full personnel file.

814
00:38:20,159 --> 00:38:21,994
You read about my sister.

815
00:38:21,994 --> 00:38:23,746
Yeah.

816
00:38:23,746 --> 00:38:26,666
Abducted from your yard
when you were 9 years old.

817
00:38:26,666 --> 00:38:29,836
I can't even imagine
what you went through.

818
00:38:29,836 --> 00:38:31,587
I was supposed
to be watching her,

819
00:38:31,587 --> 00:38:34,173
and I looked away
for a minute.

820
00:38:34,173 --> 00:38:37,218
And after three weeks
of no leads from the police,

821
00:38:37,218 --> 00:38:38,928
my mom hired a psychic.

822
00:38:38,928 --> 00:38:40,972
That's who found her,
not the cops.

823
00:38:40,972 --> 00:38:43,558
Which is why you put
so much stock in intuition.

824
00:38:43,558 --> 00:38:44,600
Mm-hmm.

825
00:38:44,600 --> 00:38:47,061
I was wrong earlier

826
00:38:47,061 --> 00:38:48,730
when I said you don't
have the experience

827
00:38:48,730 --> 00:38:51,065
to back up
your gut instincts.

828
00:38:51,065 --> 00:38:54,318
See,
I think you blamed yourself

829
00:38:54,318 --> 00:38:55,653
for what happened
to your sister,

830
00:38:55,653 --> 00:39:00,116
and that made you an extremely
observant 9-year-old girl

831
00:39:00,116 --> 00:39:02,827
so that you'd never miss
seeing danger coming again.

832
00:39:02,827 --> 00:39:06,414
And over the years, you funneled
all that input into your gut.

833
00:39:06,414 --> 00:39:09,292
See, I think you saw the blood
on the bumper of that car,

834
00:39:09,292 --> 00:39:11,252
and before you understood
what you saw,

835
00:39:11,252 --> 00:39:16,215
you translated it
into a dark aura.

836
00:39:16,215 --> 00:39:19,093
And your premonition dream
about Jill's whereabouts,

837
00:39:19,093 --> 00:39:21,095
that came after a long night

838
00:39:21,095 --> 00:39:24,682
of meticulous,
evidence-based research.

839
00:39:24,682 --> 00:39:29,228
So does that mean you're --
you're not washing me out?

840
00:39:29,228 --> 00:39:30,772
Correct.

841
00:39:30,772 --> 00:39:32,190
But I don't have
a crystal ball.

842
00:39:32,190 --> 00:39:33,524
I don't know yet
if you are going to be

843
00:39:33,524 --> 00:39:34,984
a good police officer.

844
00:39:34,984 --> 00:39:39,030
But I am willing to trust my gut
and give it another shot.

845
00:39:39,030 --> 00:39:43,785
Thank you, sir.
I won't let you down.

846
00:39:43,785 --> 00:39:45,620
I'll see you tomorrow.

847
00:39:47,205 --> 00:39:48,664
You know, if you ever need
a crystal ball,

848
00:39:48,664 --> 00:39:50,500
you can always
borrow mine.

849
00:39:50,500 --> 00:39:52,210
Kidding.

850
00:39:52,210 --> 00:39:54,003
Good night,
Officer Juarez.

851
00:39:54,003 --> 00:39:55,671
Good night.

852
00:40:00,009 --> 00:40:01,803
Alright, so here's the deal,
Pavi.

853
00:40:01,803 --> 00:40:04,096
I filled out the paperwork
charging you with a felony,

854
00:40:04,096 --> 00:40:06,015
and I will file it today

855
00:40:06,015 --> 00:40:09,227
unless you start using
your skills to help people.

856
00:40:09,227 --> 00:40:12,230
And how much
does that pay?

857
00:40:13,564 --> 00:40:14,982
Nothing.

858
00:40:14,982 --> 00:40:16,651
But then again,
neither does prison.

859
00:40:18,152 --> 00:40:19,987
I'm listening.

860
00:40:19,987 --> 00:40:22,698
Alright, so, we have a friend
who has a community center

861
00:40:22,698 --> 00:40:25,243
and he needs a volunteer to help
teach a computer literacy class

862
00:40:25,243 --> 00:40:26,452
to the neighborhood.

863
00:40:26,452 --> 00:40:28,663
You keep your nose clean,
you show up twice a week,

864
00:40:28,663 --> 00:40:30,164
I'll shred these.

865
00:40:30,164 --> 00:40:31,582
Otherwise, I've got
up to 18 months

866
00:40:31,582 --> 00:40:34,001
to file your felony paperwork
with the D. A.

867
00:40:34,001 --> 00:40:36,254
I thought you were gonna
take away all my electronics.

868
00:40:36,254 --> 00:40:37,839
I was.

869
00:40:37,839 --> 00:40:40,925
Lucky for you, Officer Thorsen
believes in second chances.

870
00:40:40,925 --> 00:40:43,761
Just take the deal,
kid.

871
00:40:43,761 --> 00:40:46,222
Pavi, why is there
a police car parked outside?

872
00:40:46,222 --> 00:40:49,684
Okay. Alright. I-I'm in.
Just text me the details.

873
00:40:51,769 --> 00:40:56,107
We did good.

874
00:41:12,206 --> 00:41:14,584
Officer Chen? I'm Agent Miller
from the Seattle field office.

875
00:41:14,584 --> 00:41:16,752
Nice to meet you, sir.
What do we know?

876
00:41:16,752 --> 00:41:19,171
House belongs to
a Phyllis and Raymond Haymen.

877
00:41:19,171 --> 00:41:20,923
Friends and family haven't
heard from them in over a week,

878
00:41:20,923 --> 00:41:22,300
but their car's
in the driveway.

879
00:41:22,300 --> 00:41:23,509
Any movement inside?

880
00:41:23,509 --> 00:41:25,177
None. We can hear their phones
ringing inside,

881
00:41:25,177 --> 00:41:27,138
but no one
ever answers them.

882
00:41:27,138 --> 00:41:28,306
Well,
something's not right.

883
00:41:28,306 --> 00:41:29,724
We were thinking
the same thing.

884
00:41:36,230 --> 00:41:38,149
FBI! Open up!

885
00:41:38,149 --> 00:41:40,735
We have a warrant
to search these premises.

886
00:42:03,257 --> 00:42:04,050
Look at that.

