[phone line ringing]
- Hey.
I need your help with a case.
Aren't you supposed to be
on maternity leave?
What are you, my husband?
Look, forget I said anything.
What's up?
I have an open file
that's almost ready
to hand off
to the DA's office.
If I take care of it now,
it won't be hanging
over my head when I get back.
Wanna help me out?
- Sure.
[door clicks]
[quirky music]
What you doing?
Trying to figure out
the crib assembly.
In the closet?
It's peaceful in here.
Who's on the phone?
Customer service.
Do you have your
order number handy, ma'am?
- Hi, Aaron.
- Hi.
Angela,
I know you're working.
Wrap it up,
or I'm gonna call Grey
and tell him what you're doing.
[sighs]
In the future,
you could disguise your voice.
I'm not comfortable being
pulled into your web of lies.
Get over it.
I need you to collect DNA
from a suspect.
I'll text you his name.
Okay. Do we have a warrant?
No.
Then how am I supposed
to get his DNA?
You wanna be a detective?
Figure it out.
♪ I'm gonna win for you
♪ Like I know
you want me to do ♪
All right, let's get to it.
Special of the day:
Frank Teska.
Frank spent two decades
working his way up
from a street-level enforcer
to a proud boss
of a renaissance crew
that ran everything
from prostitutes to drugs.
Then Frank's temper
got the best of him.
took an eight-year fall
for involuntary manslaughter.
Although there was nothing
involuntary about it.
More recently...
that is, last week...
Frank exited prison
and, we believe,
took out his brother, Ed,
to reestablish leadership.
We have prison intel
over Frank's
last few months inside.
He was making a push
to get into
the ghost gun business.
Specifically,
3D-printed weapons,
which are invisible
to metal detectors.
Next-generation ghost guns
are printed using
a high-strength,
nylon-based polymer,
which is illegal to buy in bulk
without proper paperwork.
Now, this morning, METRO
raided Ridgeside Chemicals
based on intel that Frank
was about to take a delivery
of 300 gallons of that polymer.
Which leaves Frank
without a supplier.
Exactly.
Which is where
Officer Chen comes in.
She'll be going undercover at
Southland Chemicals in Venice,
the only other local
manufacturer of the polymer.
And I'll be living
at the Langholm apartments.
So until further notice,
if you see Officer Chen
out in the world,
do not acknowledge her.
All those assigned to support,
see Sergeant Bradford.
Everyone else,
let's get to work.
♪
- Mornin'.
- Hey.
You feelin' all right?
Yeah, I'm just taking it
a little slow this morning.
I, uh, saw some friends that
I haven't seen in a long time.
Oh, you need
a little carefree time.
Just be careful
not to burn yourself out.
I won't, but ever since
we got justice for Blanca,
it's like this weight
has been lifted,
like my soul feels lighter,
you know what I mean?
I do, and I'm happy for you.
I even signed up
for this dating app, YouSpark.
I can't remember the last time
I even flirted with a guy.
Well, let's hope
sparks fly soon.
Gotta love
a Daddy Cop joke.
Hey, I need you to run
down to the morgue for me.
Fun. Why?
Remember NoHo Doe?
I do.
A torso found
in North Hollywood,
no definitive cause of death,
and no means to ID him.
It was a dead-end case
I took on
to keep Skip Tracer Randy
out of jail.
Was that the right decision?
Definitely not,
but I have to solve it now.
To that end, an arm was found
near Silver Lake Reservoir
this morning.
Gotta be connected
to the torso, right?
No...no pun intended.
Not necessarily.
There are a surprising amount
of severed limbs in this city.
Mm.
♪
- Oh.
- Kay.
♪
Thorsen, what are you doing?
Looking for DNA.
It looks like
you're moonlighting
at the sanitation department.
Yeah, I could see
how you could think that.
You know,
it's not often that you find
a young, budding detective
with this amount of dedication
to solve a case.
Tell me you came by
this evidence legally.
I mean, I might've committed
a minor trespass
to gather evidence,
but per police procedure.
Translation: you walked
on the suspect's property,
dug through their trash bins,
and brought
all their trash here.
Basically.
Well, you're not sorting
through that filth
in my station.
Get it out of here.
And Thorsen,
this table better be spotless
when you're gone.
Yes, sir.
I called Hard Luck.
What...really?
He's such an unreliable CI.
No, he's just a little
twitchy sometimes.
He's the only informant I got
who has an in with Frank Teska.
So he's gonna point Frank
in the direction
of your new identity
at Southland.
Yeah, or he'll go
on a three-day bender
and wake up in Reno.
No, he won't,
'cause I told him
it was for you.
He knows it's important to me.
Aw.
Undercover love.
[laughs]
I'm sorry to say the new arm
is not a match for NoHo Doe.
Yeah, I figured
it was too much to hope for.
But the method of amputation
on it is confounding.
How so?
I've never seen
such well-defined
traumatic separation of tissue.
I honestly don't know
what instrument was used
to remove it.
A katana? Lightsaber.
No and no.
Any idea what was used
to chop up NoHo Doe?
Definitely a blade
done post-mortem,
but I have no idea
what the cause of death was.
I did find evidence
that your torso owner
had a hip arthroplasty.
So if we find a severed limb
with hip hardware,
it's most likely our guy?
Exactly,
and then I'll be able to ID him
off the serial number.
- Outstanding.
Thank you very much.
Shall we?
Looks like we're going
on a leg hunt.
This job is so weird.
[chuckles]
[Abby Holliday's
"Ohio Laundry Room"]
♪
Hello.
I'm Larry Ellis,
and you must be Jamie Hall.
I can't tell you how excited
I am to be part of this...
Oh, uh...uh,
it's nice to meet you too, Larry.
Um, maybe you could show me
to my office.
♪ Just in time for summer
- It's not the right leg.
- It is a right leg.
No, I mean
it's not the correct leg.
But we'll take it
off your hands.
[sighs] 20 bucks.
Five?
Anything you need, I'm here.
So just let me know.
[chuckles]
And again,
I am so happy to help the LAPD.
"NYPD Blue"
is my favorite TV show,
so you can imagine.
Uh, Larry,
I really appreciate the offer,
but you know, the best thing
you could do for me
is to treat me like
all your other employees.
And you know, this should
really be the last time
that you mention the LAPD, okay?
Yes, of course.
Copy that.
[chuckles]
Uh, I've been practicing
all the lingo.
No lingo.
- No lingo.
- Yeah, okay.
I'm just a regular
plastics salesperson.
[clicks tongue]
[chuckles]
♪ I will never blame you
♪ You were dealt
a hell of a hand ♪
♪ If I were you
♪ I would have done
♪ The same thing
[phone ringing]
♪ If I were you
Jamie Hall.
You all set up, Jamie?
Yeah, all good.
Although we should probably
keep an eye on my boss.
He's a little overeager.
Want me to have
a talk with him?
No, no. I've got it.
Are you good?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we got you covered
out here.
Wherever you go, we go.
Well, that's comforting,
but I meant, like,
are you good?
Do you mean
do I miss you already?
No.
I'm fine.
You are such a jerk.
Hey, will you keep an eye
on Tamara for me?
You know, just check in on her
every once in a while?
Of course.
And don't worry about her.
I'll keep an eye on her.
You just focus on the job.
♪ Even if it takes
How long do you think
this'll take?
Day, week, couple months.
Hard to tell.
Oh, do not finish
this season of "Top Chef"
without me.
I can't make any promises.
You ever wish
you had a normal job?
One where people
don't shoot at you?
Not once.
[chuckles]
Yeah, me either.
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Ooh
False alarm.
It's only a foot.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh
Making any friends?
There's a lovely lady, Delores.
She's got a lot
of cute stories
about her grandkids.
This past weekend, apparently,
little Jimbo ate
a dozen marbles.
Well, well, well.
what do we have here?
I've been going through
this dude's trash for days,
and I can't find a single thing
with his DNA on it.
Seems pretty impossible, right?
'Cause I basically leave
a trail of DNA everywhere I go.
Whoa, whoa, TMX.
It's actually "TMI," Smitty.
"Too much information."
Pretty sure I'm right.
Earwax.
Yes. Let's go.
Is the monotony
getting to you?
I don't mind it.
I just don't want it all
to be for nothing.
Frank must be in a rush
to make those guns
and get paid.
Can't be much longer.
I'm sure
he's checking you out,
seeing if the story
Hard Luck has fed him is true.
[car door opens]
[tense music]
Hi.
Good morning.
We need to talk.
♪
Uh, I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
No, but I know you.
I know your real name's
not Jamie Hall.
Look, I don't know
what you're talking about,
but if you'd like
to buy plastics,
I'm happy to invite you in.
Otherwise...
- Lisa Thompson.
Born in Flagstaff,
currently wanted
on two counts of felon fraud
for cashing bad checks.
Now, you want me to go inside
and tell your boss,
or are you gonna take
a little ride with me?
[tense music]
♪
Why don't we go for a walk?
So what do you want?
To get to know each other
a little better.
If we're gonna be in business,
we gotta establish a rapport.
Trust.
Who said
we're doing business?
Me.
Look, I came to LA
to start over,
so I am very respectfully
just gonna pass, okay?
Yeah, well,
that's not really an option.
I need access
to certain protected plastics,
and you need
to not go to prison.
But this is a very
low-risk thing for you.
A few barrels a month
get misplaced.
That kind of loss is normal,
and it's built into
the company's profit margin.
I just need you
to hide the missing inventory
from your boss.
You do that, and I'll pay you
5,000 bucks a month, huh?
How's that sound?
Tempting, but I think
I would just prefer
to give my notice today
and let you make this deal
with the next girl
that sits behind my desk.
Look, I'm trying
to be nice here, hmm?
But the alternative
to you saying yes
is me drowning you
in that canal.
So how about you get onboard,
like, right now?
♪
Yeah,
when you put it that way,
I guess I'm in.
Great.
We'll have dinner tonight?
Hammer out the details, hmm?
I'll pick you up at your place
at 8:00?
Okay.
Good.
♪
[laughs] Liar.
Liar.
Mentiroso.
So how goes
the online dating?
Uh, a giant cesspool
of self-absorbed narcissists
with no love to give.
- [chuckles]
Sounds like my childhood.
And yet, you're still swiping.
I mean, just look.
They all look so good,
you know?
And then you do
a little digging
and find out they're actually
ten years older,
four inches shorter,
married with children,
and just looking
for a side piece.
Prime example.
Oh, he's handsome
and not unfamiliar.
That's...
Oh, my God! Is that Smitty?
- I know.
I mean, he was a slice.
But that is false advertisement
for a profile pic.
I'll say.
How did you and Bailey meet?
Oh.
She just showed up
at my door one day.
A gorgeous, multitalented,
half-naked woman
wrapped in a towel.
And now we're engaged.
- I hate you.
- [chuckles]
My point is I wasn't looking.
That's when love shows up.
7-Adam-15,
RP found a leg
at the Hollywood Reservoir.
Do you want the call?
- Yep.
Hey.
You called about the leg?
Yes. Uh, Scott.
We were out for a walk,
and Buddy here found it.
I've been trying
to get him to let go,
but he's become quite attached.
Oh, no problem.
All we have to do
is offer him something
he wants more
than a severed leg.
Do you always carry
dog treats?
Yeah. Tip from a friend.
Hey, Buddy. Here you go.
Here you...
[dog growling]
Easy, easy.
[dog barks]
Wow, okay.
Really?
You choose a rotten leg
over chicken waffle bits?
Yeah, he does this sometimes.
[chuckles]
Last month, he fell in love
with an avocado
and carried it around
till it was mush.
Is he a rescue?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, it took forever
to get him to trust me.
Now he freaks out
if my mom gives me a hug.
Oh, territorial.
Makes sense.
Um, he has attachment issues.
Maybe if I get
a little closer...
[dog growling]
Can I?
Uh, yeah, sure.
[dog growling, barking]
- Oh.
- Hey.
That's good boy.
- Nice.
There.
You see the metal hip joint?
Coroner can use that
to identify the body.
Is there anything else
we can help with, Officer...
Celina.
No, thank you.
♪
Okay. Come on.
Hey, how'd I do?
The dumpster diving
was a good tactic.
The DNA was a match.
Yeah, one man's trash
is a pregnant woman's
case closed.
Thanks for helping me out.
Hey, you know,
I could take on another.
I mean, every time
I work one of your cases,
I'm learning just a little bit
more to help me make detective.
All right.
There's this one witness
to a liquor store burglary,
but I can't get him
to talk to me,
or any cop, for that matter.
Oh, I bet
I can get him to crack.
The guy hates the police.
It's impossible.
[quirky music]
But now I have to stop
talking to you,
because Wesley is
staring me down hard.
But I'll send you his name.
♪
Wrong number.
Oh.
[phone ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
What's up?
How you doin'?
Better, now that we've got
some movement on Frank.
I was bored
to early onset rigor mortis.
Yeah,
crooks have their own schedule.
We call it "dope time."
- Hmm.
So where are we, case-wise?
Yeah, he made contact,
asked me to dinner.
Romantically, like a date?
Well, ostensibly,
it's about business,
but he did just get
out of prison,
so odds are he's hopeful for
a little somethin'-somethin'.
Legally, there's two forms
of entrapment.
The first is offering
so much money
that an otherwise reasonable
person commits an illegal act.
The second is sex.
Yeah, if a UC puts sex
or love on the table
as inducement to crime,
it automatically becomes entrapment.
The courts realize that love
makes people do crazy things.
Right, so I'm...
should we cancel dinner?
No, but keep it professional.
If he starts saying
that he's doing it for you
or for love, you gotta walk.
Yeah. Hey.
Should I push a little
about his brother?
No, because you're still
trying to build a foundation.
Once he trusts you,
he will hang himself.
But we should get
a decent wire for her,
because he could get
a little handsy.
Mm. All right.
Pull the top of the line
from HIDTA.
We'll reconvene and brief
two hours before your date.
Any questions?
All right.
[tense music]
♪
You okay?
Five by five.
You gotta treat this
like any other op
and treat Lucy
like any other UC.
I know.
All right.
Ooh.
Man, it really reeks in here.
Yeah, Grey is not happy
with Aaron.
[phone chiming, buzzing]
Another match?
- Uh, I don't know.
There is seriously no good man
in Los Angeles...
who are single, of course.
What about Scott?
The citizen with the dog?
I don't know.
What about him?
Well, based on your little
interaction before,
I'd say he was interested.
[chuckling]
What are you talking about?
No, he wasn't.
Yes, he was.
Oh, my gosh.
Why are you smiling?
Because for someone
who's so connected
to the universe,
you seem a little blind
when it comes
to the romantic signals.
What signals?
There were no signals.
There were signals?
- [laughs]
Okay, that's not funny.
You're right.
I'm a little freaked out.
I've never done
anything like this before.
If I get caught,
I'm looking at serious time.
Prison's not so bad.
You do your time,
meet new business associates.
Most importantly, you learn
what you're really made of.
Helps you see the world
more clearly.
What did you learn?
Family can't be trusted.
Yeah, I hear that.
I mean, the whole reason
I cashed those bogus checks
was 'cause my dad stole
my rent money.
My brother made a move
against me.
I put him in his place.
What place is that?
[engine revving]
[dramatic music]
[tires squealing]
Get down!
[gunfire]
[people screaming]
[tires squealing]
Put that away...the gun.
Shots fired,
93107 Wilshire Boulevard,
black Honda Accord headed east.
[suspenseful music]
- Copy that.
- [sighing] Okay.
Units are on their way.
In pursuit.
[tires screeching]
[siren wailing]
We gotta help these people.
Gotta go!
Cops are on their way!
♪
[horn honking]
Suspects are out of the car
and on foot.
Driver is a Black male
with a hoodie, headed north.
I'm in foot pursuit
of the shooter.
He's a white male,
brown pants, headed south.
♪
[dog barking]
[gun clicking]
[both grunt]
[siren approaching]
You're under arrest.
♪
Let's go. Get up.
You okay?
Yeah. Gun was empty.
I got lucky.
Otherwise...
♪
What the hell was that?
Were they shooting at you?
They weren't gunning
for the busboy.
Hmm, well,
it's been nice knowing you.
Hey!
- You're not backing out here.
Our deal's still on,
you understand me?
Yeah, ju...just relax, okay?
I'm...I'm scared.
I just...I've never been
shot at before.
I have.
You'll get used to it.
Do you know who's after you?
Two choices.
His guys or my guys.
"His guys," who?
Your brother?
Yeah.
Some of his people didn't come
onboard when I took over,
and some of my people
might be feeling
I'm weak enough
to take a shot at.
But they're gonna find out
quick how wrong they are.
Well, look,
I am in way over my head.
I get that I don't have
a choice on whether or not
I'm helping you, but if you
could just keep the body count
out of my backyard,
that would be great.
No promises.
Are you okay
to get home by yourself?
Yeah, no problem.
Thanks for dinner.
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
I'll be in touch.
♪
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[engine starts]
♪
[phone clicks]
[line ringing]
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah, you?
Yeah, I am now.
We got the shooter,
but the driver got away.
Meet me at the laundry room
in your building.
Yes. See you in 30.
[knock at door]
Hey.
- Hey.
That was really scary.
Yeah,
I about had a heart attack.
Does Frank know
who took a run at him?
Not for sure, but he's
clearly in a tenuous position,
even with his own crew.
- If you need to tap out...
- No.
The fact that
he can't trust anyone
actually strengthens my in.
He needs an ally.
I can be that
and hopefully bring the whole
thing down from within.
Has he tried anything?
No, but I can handle it
if he does.
I know.
Yeah, knowing
and feeling okay about it
are two different things.
Look, it's not my first time.
I know.
It's probably
what makes it worse.
All right, now's not the time
to talk about this.
I know
you'll bail on the operation
if you don't feel it's safe.
So if you are good, I'm good.
- I'm good.
- Good.
I gotta get back
to the station.
Grey's waiting
for a status update.
Wait, no, hey.
[soft music]
Lock the door first.
♪
Told you there were signals.
What?
Okay, now I'm nervous.
What do I say?
Well, start with "hello."
I'll be over here.
[whistling]
both: Hey.
Hey, hi.
Hey, Buddy.
Look what I have for you.
Here you go.
Yeah, Buddy was wondering
if we could get that leg back.
He really misses it.
Ooh, sorry. It's evidence.
So he's just gonna have to find
another one,
which I've discovered,
it actually isn't that hard
to find in Los Angeles.
Wow, good to know.
Also terrifying.
Yeah, well,
do you need anything else?
'Cause my boss is waiting.
- Uh, no.
Well, yes. Sorry.
I've been on dating apps
so long,
I've forgotten how to ask
someone out in real life.
Dating apps are the worst.
Wait.
Are you about to ask me out?
I am.
Uh, do you wanna get
dinner tonight,
or tomorrow,
or really,
whenever you're free?
I'd like that.
I know a great place
with a dog-friendly patio.
Oh, we love
a dog-friendly patio.
Great. It's a date.
- [chuckles]
- That rhymed.
Yes, it did.
Uh, don't be late,
or I'll be irate.
Ooh.
Yeah, went a little bit far.
- Just a little bit.
- Celina!
I gotta go, but uh, here.
Here's my card.
Call me...or text me,
or whatever people do
these days.
Okay.
- Hi.
- Hey, uh, good news.
The M.E. got the serial number
off the prosthetic hip joint
from that last leg,
so he is no longer "NoHo Doe."
His name is Trip Linden,
and he was reported missing
a month ago.
Well, who reported him?
[laughter]
- Dude, this is ridiculous.
Hi.
Uh, Detective Harper.
Thank you for coming in.
Can you tell me your names
so I know who's who?
Um, Mark.
Hank.
Okay, great, and uh,
I understand you're both
friends with Trip Linden?
Yeah. Yeah, did you find him?
I'm afraid we did.
Parts of him.
Wait, wait.
What does that mean?
We found his torso
and one of his legs.
They look scared.
Dismemberment is scary.
That doesn't mean
they're guilty.
[scoffs]
That's messed up, man.
I'm sorry to be the bearer
of such upsetting news.
Were the three of you close?
Yeah, yeah.
We hung out all the time.
You know,
he had the sickest collection.
Have you ever shot an RPG?
Just...
- [chuckling] Come on, man.
Trip owned an RPG?
No, no.
I mean, not if it's illegal.
Look, he definitely
never broke the law.
Okay, and I understand
the two of you
reported him missing?
Yeah, 'cause the last time
we saw him,
he was heading to Vegas and...
to meet up with some chick,
and he just never came back.
I mean, if they had something
to do with his death,
they wouldn't have
reported him missing.
You'd be surprised
how many people think
that'll throw us off the scent.
Uh, can you describe
this woman?
Oh, no, sorry.
We never met her.
Maybe she did something
to him, you know?
Like... like she was the lure
to some sicko.
Theorizing.
That's never a good sign.
Maybe he's just trying
to be helpful.
No, they're trying
to offer up another suspect.
All right,
we will look into her.
Did Trip have any enemies?
No, no. Trip was the best.
Not that bright, but...
- Hey, yo.
Don't speak ill of the dead, man.
Come on.
Sorry.
He was not that bright?
No, he just...he didn't make
the best of choices,
but he was a great guy, really.
Either of us had a problem,
and he was always there for us.
See if you can corroborate
any part of that story.
Will do, and I'll check
their social media too.
I've become a black belt in
Googling the lies out of men.
[elevator bell dings]
I'm here, y'all,
in the belly of the beast.
Tune in to the next video
to see what happened.
Oh, and uh, remember
to like and subscribe.
Mr. Perry,
thanks for coming in
to talk about the robbery.
You're welcome,
but like I told
the pregnant detective,
I don't wanna get involved.
I only came in to shoot
some ClipTalk videos.
Hey, look, I get it, okay?
You don't wanna talk
to the cops.
Most people don't.
But we know
you saw the robbery.
You were right outside
the store when it happened.
So is there anything
you remember
of the driver
or the car or an...
- Not a chance.
- Look.
I got 4 million followers
on ClipTalk.
What? No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
[phone clicks]
I could tag you,
get your name out there.
You have to do
better than that.
Dance challenge.
[upbeat music]
♪ Watch out, 'cause
♪ I'm coming your way, yeah
♪ Nonstop, I can do this
all day, yeah ♪
♪ Go work
what your mama done gave ya ♪
♪ Mama done gave ya
♪ Mama, mama done gave ya
♪ Whole world all yours
♪ For the taking,
bring it home ♪
What in the hell?
Sorry, sir.
Just, um, cracking
another case.
- ♪ Mama done gave ya
- What in the hell?
This is awesome.
Uh, guy who robbed
the liquor store.
License plate started with 3JR,
silver Accord.
3JR. Yes!
Okay.
[dog barking]
[phone chimes]
[engine revving]
[tires squealing]
- Get in!
- Frank.
- Now!
- O...okay.
[suspenseful music]
What's wrong?
I know who shot at us.
I gotta take him down.
I need a lookout.
♪
[tires squealing]
[tense music]
♪
[gun clicking]
Where are we?
This is where
all the magic happens.
3D printers are inside.
Okay, wait, so you think
it was one of your guys
who took a run at you?
- Yeah, Grant.
You stay out here.
Call me if you see anything.
♪
[phone ringing]
Hey.
Why are you here?
Okay, so Frank's driver
was the shooter,
and now I'm acting
as his lookout
while he goes inside
to kill him.
What exactly is my play here?
First priority is
to stop a murder.
So be a good lookout.
Every cop in LA is about
to land on this location.
- Okay.
- All right, bye.
8-500, I need additional units
at my location.
Code-3.
♪
[hip-hop music playing]
[rapping indistinctly]
♪
[glass clinking]
[laughter]
[suspenseful music]
Hey, we gotta go.
The cops are coming.
- How?
- I don't know.
But we don't have much time.
Frank, you are an ex-con
with a gun.
I don't know anything
about law,
but I'm pretty sure
that sends you back.
Let's go.
Come on.
♪
[sirens wailing]
[tires squealing]
The car matches
Morgan's description
of the robbery vehicle.
Anything inside?
Not that I can see,
but I haven't checked
the trunk yet.
- Whoa.
[coughing]
The air fresheners
are just making it worse.
Yeah.
7-Adam-7,
I have a possible 187.
[flies buzzing]
Alley off of 1700 block
on Tustin.
Send detectives and TID.
[dramatic music]
♪
[muffled dance music playing]
[singing in Spanish]
Police!
♪
Anyone in there?
Show me your hands.
♪
[music stops]
We got another body.
[phone clicks]
[phone chimes]
Looks like this guy died
of a heart attack.
How can you tell?
His search says
"signs of a heart attack."
Okay, so after
a successful burglary spree,
heart attack and trunk guy
get into a disagreement, right?
Which leads
to trunk guy's death,
and then heart attack puts
trunk guy in the trunk,
tries to cover the smell
before he can decide
what to do with him,
makes it all the way back here
to the auto shop,
and then the effort
was a bit too much and...
[snaps fingers]
Pop goes his heart.
That's some good detecting.
I know, right?
Vegas PD struck out.
They have no record of Trip
coming to town
with a mystery woman.
But IT was able to get
into Trip's cloud account.
Turns out he enjoyed making
videos with Mark and Hank.
What kind of videos?
Not that kind of videos. Worse.
In one of the clips,
they shot a cow with an RPG.
What is wrong with people?
After combing through
several soul-crushing hours
of footage, we found that.
[gunfire]
[laughter]
All right,
what am I looking at?
The idiots got their hands
on a .50 caliber machine gun.
[gunfire]
[laughter]
They're just blowing up watermelons.
Right, until Trip goes out
onto the range and...
[gunshot]
[laughter stops]
There goes his head.
Trip!
He's dead! What do we do?
Well, that is definitely
enough to get a warrant.
Right, so what do you say
we let SWAT go
and take care of arresting
the heavily armed survivalists?
Where's the fun in that?
- [laughs]
- Let's go.
I mean, she's...
she's kidding, right?
I'm afraid not. [sighs]
[panting]
That was crazy.
How the hell am I supposed
to go to the office after that?
[gun clicks]
You got ten seconds
to convince me
you're not a cop.
♪
[tense music]
I'm not a cop. I...
Then how the hell did you
know they were coming?
A police scanner app.
I can show you.
A what?
A police scanner app.
Can...can I just...
Look.
I have never been
a lookout before, okay?
So when you ran inside,
I thought this might be useful.
I downloaded it,
and the first thing I heard
was the warehouse address.
I...I almost peed my pants!
You could've just run,
left me inside
to get killed or arrested.
Why didn't you?
Honestly,
it didn't occur to me,
although at this moment,
I...I really, really wish I had.
[sighs]
When you're about to be
released from prison,
those last few weeks,
you're just dreaming,
you know,
about the outside world.
All the things you're gonna do,
all the meals you're gonna eat,
all the money
you're gonna make,
the women you're gonna...
well, you get it.
Yeah.
But you know,
then you get out,
the world's different.
It's moved on without you.
And the place
you thought you held in it,
it doesn't exist anymore.
You realized you've, you know,
lost a step or two.
Eight years is a long time.
Yeah, and I wasn't exactly
a millennial when I went in.
There's gotta be other things
you were dreaming about inside
besides money, food, and women.
Yeah, my kid.
But she took off
when I got out.
Why?
Look,
I was never a good dad.
Always wrapped up
in being the tough guy,
causing mayhem, getting paid,
making money.
She...well, gave her
no time at all.
She deserved better.
You could reach out now,
try to fix things.
Where is she?
Ohio.
She tried going off the grid
so I couldn't find her,
you know?
But I found her pretty easy.
You could visit.
You know,
try to make things right.
Nah.
She'll never forgive me.
Maybe not.
Even if she doesn't, though,
it'll matter that you tried.
[soft music]
I just met you.
I don't know you.
But it really seems like
you don't wanna be
living your life
like this anymore.
[chuckles]
I should go.
- Okay.
Hey, uh, thanks again.
And I'm sorry about,
you know...
Threatening my life
on multiple occasions?
[laughs] Yeah.
Bygones.
Frank.
I'll see you later.
Hmm.
Not if I see you first.
[phone ringing]
Where are you?
I'm outside
the cover apartment.
Frank just dropped me off.
We grabbed Grant
and the other two,
got enough weaponry
to hold them until we try
to get a ballistics match
for the restaurant shooting
and Ed's murder.
Yeah, fingers crossed.
I think this op is done.
You sure?
Yeah.
I mean, he's got no crew,
no product.
It's over.
- That's too bad.
- Why?
I was looking forward
to another laundry room hookup.
[siren wailing]
- We couldn't find his fingers.
He tried to evade arrest
using a grenade launcher,
and...and failed.
- It hurts! Ahh!
[groaning]
Hey, uh,
I put a BOLO out for Mark.
Hopefully we can get him
before he finds out
there's an arrest warrant
for him.
[elevator bell dings]
- Right.
I don't think
that'll be a problem.
Hey, excuse me.
I heard my friend
was brought in
in some kind
of explosives accident.
Mark, hey.
Hank is in treatment.
Uh, we just need
to talk to you.
Stay back!
We didn't mean to hurt Trip.
[tense music]
It was an accident.
♪
[grunting]
Nice work, Mama.
OB appointment?
Yeah. What?
I couldn't just stand here
and do nothing.
Detective.
Grey said
you were looking for me.
Uh, yes.
Remember that arm
the M.E. flagged at the morgue?
Yeah, the one with
the, uh, unique cut?
Yeah, well, it might not
have been related to NoHo Doe,
but it is related
to a case in Arizona.
A coroner there found an arm
that was severed
with that same mystery tool,
and both were done while
the victim was still alive.
That's horrible,
and it means we're looking
at a possible serial killer.
Should we be calling the feds?
Yeah, I already did.
- John Nolan.
- As I live and breathe,
Simone Clark,
what a pleasure to see you.
Pleasure to be seen.
What up, girl?
- Hey, Simone.
Does this mean Garza's unit
is taking this case?
Oh, yeah.
It's the reason
I joined the FBI,
so that I could swoop in
and steal the thunder
right out from under
local law enforcement.
Technically,
you're not required
to rub our noses in it.
But where's the fun in that?
Why don't you bring me
up to speed on everything,
and then I can steal
your theories
and pawn them off as my own?
[ultrasound whooshing]
Baby looks great.
Angela,
you're on the home stretch.
Thank God, because I'm
strictly at the loafer stage.
I can't tie my shoelaces anymore.
Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
What are you doing here?
I, uh, just wanted to deliver
the news in person.
I texted you
to meet me in the lobby.
Seriously?
Baby, you know
how I feel about open cases.
I promise I'll be ready
to nest after this.
Please tell me
you closed the case.
Oh, better.
I closed seven cases.
Well done, Officer Thorsen.
I'll make sure
Caradine knows you stepped up.
Yeah, and also, thank you
so much for the opportunity.
Yeah.
You know, Aaron is a great
girl's name too, so...
We...we were waiting
to be surprised.
[Hayden Calnin's
"Warm With You"]
♪
[sighs]
I need a big meal, a hot bath,
and some quality sexy time,
and then I'm gonna sleep
for 24 hours.
What, what is that? What?
I just...
Isabel used to always crash
after a long-term assignment.
It would take her months
to come back to life.
Well, this was only a week,
so I think one night's sleep
will do me.
You know what?
I do have to come clean
about something, though.
Um...
I know I made you promise
to not watch "Top Chef"
without me,
but I couldn't wait!
I'm sorry!
♪ We could build a house
- Bad girlfriend.
- No.
- No, I'm sorry!
Horrible.
♪
So...
Why didn't you tell me
you almost died
chasing down the shooter
at the restaurant?
Because I didn't.
- [scoffs]
- Who told you?
It doesn't matter.
We'll set aside the fact that
you left it out of the report
so I wouldn't find out.
I did not.
What?
Okay.
The gun was empty, right?
So this is
much ado about nothing.
Besides, I know for a fact that
you don't tell me everything
that happens to you
when you're undercover.
N...no, no.
You know for a fact
that Isabel didn't.
If this is gonna work
between us,
I need to know that
you can see the difference.
Of course I can.
Okay? But...
listen, I need you
to take it seriously
if I ever sound the alarm
about something.
Otherwise, the pain
of what I went through
will have been for nothing,
and I can't lose you
the way I lost her.
You won't.
I'll walk away
before it ever gets close
to anything like that, okay?
I promise.
♪
♪ We could build a house
away from here ♪
Good luck on your date.
Thank you.
I'm really excited.
Maybe I should just throw
some tarot cards,
you know, just to make sure
Scott and I have a future.
Or maybe you should
just live your life
and see where it takes you.
That's so much scarier.
Yeah, sure,
but it's that discovery
that makes it
so much more special.
Look, take Bailey and me.
We have not landed
on a wedding date yet,
but I know when that day comes,
it's gonna be amazing.
You're getting married
in September.
[chuckles] Nice try.
We're not talking about
anything before next spring.
That's nice, but trust me.
It's gonna happen in September.
Because you threw down
some tarot cards?
No.
Don't stay out too late,
have fun,
and text me when you get home.
Yes, sir.
♪ Yeah, I just wanted warmth
with you ♪
♪
Hey.
What do you think about
getting married in September?
[dramatic music]
♪
Damn it.