Previously on "The Rookie"...
I tried to lock you up,
but I failed.
So, what,
you're giving up?
Mr. Evers, Charlie Bristow
from X-Ring Security.
I never run from a fight.
You won't
even see it coming.
Ms. Stevens, we have a warrant
for your arrest.
My sister's murder. Celina.
I just want to see
if they've really done
everything they can
to find the guy.
There's no card, but it's
clearly from Elijah Stone.
[Banging on door]
Coming.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's wrong?
I read
my sister's case file.
My mom lied to me.
The day
my sister was taken,
my mom had a headache
and we were being,
you know,
just noisy kids.
So she sent us
outside to play
while she went inside
to lie down.
We were out there for
about an hour or so
before I got distracted
and Blanca disappeared.
I was frantic, running around
the block, looking for her.
And when
I finally ran home,
my mom was coming
up the street.
I thought she had just
come out of the house.
Which is what she told
responding officers.
But later she admitted
to the detective
that she had run out
to the store
and... and a friend she had met
there corroborated it.
A-A friend I've never
even heard of before.
Sounds innocent enough.
Maybe she just went
to grab some Advil
or something
for dinner?
Well, then why lie
about it?
I bet she was afraid
she'd get in trouble
for leaving two young kids alone.
And then
the worst happened.
Why stick to the "I was home
the whole time" version with me?
I wasn't gonna rat her out
to CPS.
Look, I am sure there are
a dozen innocent explanations
for every untoward one
you're imagining.
Maybe.
If it wasn't my mom,
if it was just some
random witness lying to you,
what would you think?
I would think...
"What else
is she lying about?"
Monica: You'd think
I'd get tired of winning.
You know,
I almost feel bad
beating you guys
in court. Again.
- No, you don't.
- You're right. I don't.
What was the most
impressive part of my defense?
Gotta be when I pointed out
the recent changes
in the judge's handwriting
made it impossible to know
for sure that those
were actually his words.
Somehow you knew he had
early-onset dementia,
a condition that clearly
affected his handwriting.
Did I? Hmm, maybe he
shared that.
[Scoffs]
But the loss of
his mental faculties
certainly didn't
help your case,
which is why you didn't
argue it in court.
It really
doesn't bother you
that he's dead
because of you?
There is no evidence
that Judge Rivas
died of anything other than
a heart attack.
And if I hear that you
or your office
is saying
anything different,
I will sue you and the city
for defamation and win.
Now,
if you'll excuse me,
I have a client's deposition
to get to.
Sgt. Grey:
I'll keep it short.
This unholy team-up between
Elijah's organization
and Abril's has had real-world
effects on our streets.
Yeah, last night,
there was an incident
at a cookhouse
in Vernon.
Seven dead inside
and a 10-year-old neighbor
caught a stray bullet.
The child is out of surgery,
but it's still touch-and-go.
We started a collection
in the break room
if you'd
like to contribute.
We need to clamp down.
Let's start making their costs
of doing business untenable.
Hit up your C.I.s.
Word is, Elijah is orchestrating
a large buy.
We can't allow that
to happen.
Alright, be safe out there.
Sir, you remember
I let Celina
take a look at her sister's
case file.
And I told you
that could get tricky.
You did, and it is.
But she did manage to find
a discrepancy in the report
I think bears
looking into.
Maybe speak
with a witness.
[Sighs]
Okay, just give
the cold-case detective
working the file
a heads-up.
Yes, sir.
And keep an eye on her.
Last thing we want
is her to compromise
her sister's murder investigation.
Of course.
Hi.
Uh, don't hate me.
What did you do?
No, you're
supposed to say,
"I could never hate you."
[Sighs] Fine.
I got mad at you
a few months back
after a Tim Test.
Which one?
The... Oh, weird.
I honestly
don't remember.
But so,
that's not important.
What did you do?
I signed you up to be
a "Make a Dream" mentor,
and then I totally forgot
about it.
I'm sorry.
For when?
Today.
12-year-old cancer patient
Jordy Yates
is on his way right now.
[Groans]
What?
I...
C... It's a good thing.
Lifting up a sick kid
who's having a really hard time.
What could you possibly
be doing with your day
that would be more important
than that?
Nice job boxing me in.
Thank you.
- Where are you going?
- I got to go on patrol.
No, no, you and I
are gonna be entertaining
our "Make a Dream" kid
together.
[Sighs]
No. What else
could you possibly
do with your day
that's more important?
Right. Yep.
I should have seen
that coming.
Hey, there.
We are not going on patrol
this morning.
There's someone
coming to the station
that we need to talk to.
You got my mother
to leave the house?
No, and you will not
be the first person
to ask her about these...
Lies.
Discrepancies.
She needs to be questioned
by the detective
working the case, okay?
It's important she's not
prepared the first time
she's confronted
with this on record.
I know you
already know this.
I do.
So, who are we talking to?
The mystery man she says
she ran into at the store...
Edwin Guzman.
That's great.
I-I already have, uh,
a list of questions.
Um, "How did you
know my mom?
Were you having an affair?
Did you lie for her?
Do you know why my mom lied
to me for my entire life?"
Okay, whoa, whoa.
I think it's important
that I be the one
doing the questioning.
But I can be there?
Yes, as a fly
on the wall.
Thank you.
Let's go.
[Elevator bell dings]
Hi, Mr. Yates.
I'm Lucy Chen.
This is
Sergeant Tim Bradford.
Thank you so much
for doing this.
This is my son, Jordy.
Say hi.
Hi.
Hear you
wanna be a cop.
- [Chuckles]
- Yeah.
Okay, well, you're gonna be
hanging with us today.
So, I just... I come back
to pick him up at 3:00?
- Yeah.
- We'll take
good care of him.
Alright, be good.
[Elevator bell dings]
Alright, buddy?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'll be back.
Alright, Jordy,
so I'm thinking processing.
You want to take
your fingerprints,
get a mug shot taken?
I guess. Okay.
Okay, remember, I will be
talking to Mr. Guzman.
You will not be talking
to Mr. Guzman.
Absolutely.
Hello, sir.
Thank you very much
for coming in.
This shouldn't
take too long.
We just have a couple
of questions for you.
Hi.
I'm Celina Juarez.
I think you
knew my mother?
Celina, I haven't
seen you since
I saw you
and your sister...
You've grown up.
I have.
W-What's this about?
We understand you were
with Celina's mother
the day her sister
was abducted.
Yes, I was.
She said she was home.
Did she lie to me,
or did she lie to the police?
Officer Juarez.
I don't know. Maybe...
Maybe she just forgot.
You don't forget where you were
when your kid was taken.
Okay, Celina.
I need you to find
Officer Thorsen,
see if there's anything
he needs.
Why?
Because
I'm telling you.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Guzman, please.
[Door closes]
Just a second.
So... what were you
and Mrs. Juarez
doing that afternoon?
I told the cops back then.
Wouldn't this be in a file?
Oh, yeah. You ran into each
other at the corner store.
She was out getting milk.
Mr. Guzman, I highly recommend
you take this opportunity
to tell me the truth.
Lying once to the police
during a child murder
investigation is one thing.
But to do it again...
Okay, I-I didn't want Karla
to get into trouble.
You know, she was going through
so much.
And I-I thought,
if I told the cops,
that... that she might
lose Celina, too.
So, were the two of you
even together that day?
Yes.
But not at the store.
Celina's mom had been
in a car accident
a couple months prior.
Around the same time that
I-I screwed up my back at work.
And our doctors
prescribed opioids.
I mean, they... they didn't
know about them then.
You got addicted?
Yeah, and, uh,
the doctors cut us off, and...
we found our own dealer.
We were both in
a real bad place.
That's what Celina's mother
was doing
out of the house
that morning.
She was scoring.
With me.
Uh, after Blanca
was taken
[sighs] Karla never
took another pill.
I mean, she...
she quit cold turkey
because of...
of guilt and grief.
I should have told
the cops the truth.
But it wasn't relevant, right?
I mean, had nothing
to do with the reason
that... that
Blanca was taken.
Well, that'll be
for an investigator to decide.
And one will be in touch.
Mr. Guzman, I implore you
not to share this conversation
with Karla.
You really don't want to add
criminal conspiracy
to the list of possible charges
against you.
I won't. And...
And I actually haven't
spoken to her in years.
Look, um, can you tell Celina
how sorry I am?
And if you haven't
been through it,
I don't think you can understand
what opioids do to you.
I mean, we were lost
for a long time.
[Sighs]
I know that we messed up.
I'll tell her.
[Sighs] Thank you.
[Door opens]
Uh, Officer Gonzalez
down there
can show you
the way out.
What did he say?
I can't tell you
just yet.
I have to get the detectives
involved first.
Lucy: Okay, give me
your meanest face.
[Camera shutter clicks]
Okay.
Now look miserable.
Nailed it. Perfect.[Camera shutter clicks]
It doesn't exactly feel like
we're making dreams come true.
He looks like
he hates us.
No, I don't think
it's that.
I mean, maybe...
maybe he doesn't like
having his picture taken.
Maybe he doesn't feel well.
I mean, he does have cancer.
Okay. Let's move on.
What's next?
Okay.
Oh, ooh.
Where did he go?
Jordy?
[Sighs]
[Bag zips]
[Keys jingle]
[Car alarm chirps]
[Dramatic music plays]
[Gasps]
Oh!
Hello, Counselor.
No pressure.
But if you can't convince me
why I should let you live...
I'm gonna feed you
into the wood chipper.
[Wood chipper grinding]
- This is so shortsighted.
- How so?
I have been nothing
but loyal to you.
I'm the reason you're free
in the first place.
The FBI
raided my office.
They have documents related
to my business because of you.
Your legitimate business.
There was nothing incriminating.
You're talking to me
like I don't know what
the hell I'm doing.
And I'm trying really hard
to not be insulted.
I mean, how do I know
if I can ever trust you again?
Because when
I was in that cell,
I didn't fold and call
my friendly prosecutor
to get a deal
like I could have!
No, I dug in
and got right to work
on the case,
on the facts.
And I got their evidence
thrown out!
Because that's my weapon...
the law.
I mean, there are plenty
of morally flexible lawyers
in this town.
None of them are half the lawyer
I am.
And I can
guarantee you,
none of them hate
the LAPD and the D.A.
as much as I do right now.
You're gonna want to tap
into that desire for vengeance.
That same desire you have
for Lopez and Wesley.
[Gun cocks]
[Chuckles]
[Sniffs]
♪
[Grunts]
[Chuckles]
So... what do you
have in mind?
Use me to get inside
their investigation into you.
It's gonna cost you a little bit
of money and some players,
but it'll be worth it
in the long run.
Okay.
I'm interested.
What's the first step?
You're gonna
need to hit me.
[Elevator bell dings]
[Indistinct conversations]
[People gasping]
Wesley: Two-time felon
looking at 20-plus years...
yeah, I think
we can get him to,
- uh, agree to a plea.
- You think?
Are you okay?
What happened?
You were right.
I'm in over my head.
Elijah just made me
beg for my life,
and I'm gonna make him
pay for it.
I can't wait to tell
the "Make a Dream"
people we lost the kid.
We didn't lose him.
We misplaced him.
No, Tim, he has cancer,
and we lost him.
He's probably raiding
the snacks.
How can you
be so calm?
What if this
was your kid?
You and I both know
that 99% of the time
the missing kid
is playing hide-and-seek
and fell asleep
under the bed.
You know what? If...
If we ever lose our kids,
I'm gonna need you to take
this a lot more seriously.
Hold up, our kids
would know better
than to pull
a stunt like this.
I mean, look,
we're doing great so far.
Lucy: Oh, thank God.
Hey, I, uh, found this kid
wandering around.
He said he
belongs to you.
Yeah, he's slippery.
So, uh, what were you guys
talking about?
Uh, he kept asking me what
my childhood pet's name was.
Okay. Why?
A report for school, about...
Pets?
Uh, yeah.
Alright, well, let me know if
you have any further questions.
Okay?
[Lucy chuckles]
Alright, thanks.
What do you wanna do next?
Uh... How about
the kit room?
Oh.
That's where we
get our war bags.
Okay.
Well,
do you like dogs?
We have some cuties
in the K-9 unit.
Okay. [Sighs]
What kind of kid
doesn't like dogs?
Tim...
Know what?
Sit down.
Lucy:
Oh, you know what?
What about
the impound lot?
Aw, to hear
my nephews tell it,
it's all about
Pokémon and, uh, manga
with, like, ghosts on a toilet
and stuff like that.
I don't know.
Where'd he go?
Oh, no,
you're kidding. No.
This is ridiculous.
Did you see a little kid
come through here?
- Oh, no. Sorry.
- No?
[Groans]
Yeah, that'd be great,
thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Hey, I need your advice.
- What's up?
I-I just started
helping Celina
dig back into
her sister's case.
That sounds dicey.
You have no idea.
I just interviewed a guy
who says that Celina's mother
left the girls home alone while
she went out to score drugs.
So her sister
was kidnapped
while her mom
was getting high.
- Does Celina know?
- No, no, not yet.
That opens up a whole
new world of suspects...
drug dealers,
other addicts.
Exactly what
I was thinking.
I'll talk to Carradine,
have the file
added to my caseload.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
If you'll testify about
what happened today,
we've got Elijah
on kidnapping
and half a dozen
other charges.
No, I'm not testifying
in open court.
Even if he's convicted, he'll
have me killed from prison.
So, what good are you?
I know about his plans.
He's expanding,
creating new partnerships.
We know he teamed up with Abril.
What else?
Yeah, that's old news
at this point.
But I can give you intel
on things you don't know about.
But it has to be intel you could
have gotten some other way.
I need to walk away
with full immunity
and Elijah believing
that I'm still loyal.
Otherwise,
there's no deal.
What does the D.A.'s office
feel about that?
She says she
has valuable intel.
We'd love to see
her prove it.
Elijah
has money problems.
As in,
he's got too much of it.
Millions in cash
that he's been stockpiling.
He's looking for a way
to launder it.
Oh, poor guy.
He's meeting with a money
launderer this afternoon.
I know where and when.
If this is a trap,
you are done.
You're going to prison
for a very long time.
The intel is good.
Give us a minute.
We need to discuss this further.
Look, I, um...
I need to know
this won't get back
to Elijah.
Your cooperation
will be strictly guarded.
[Door opens, closes]
What do you think?
I think a scorpion
just asked us
for a ride
across the river.[Scoffs]
You heard her offer?
Yeah.
You've known her the longest.
[Clears throat]
Do you think she'll turn
on Elijah?
Monica is only loyal
to herself.
All I know for sure is,
he scared her.
And when she's scared,
she gets angry.
Well, if we're
gonna play this out,
we're gonna
need Metro today.
[Cellphone ringing]
[Groans]
[Sighs]
It's Grey.
Do you think that he knows
that we lost the kid twice?
Yes, sir.
So, I need you to come over
to the D.A.'s office
while Metro starts
their engines
on the op this afternoon.
Uh, yeah, o-okay.
I-I just... I can't
break free at the moment,
so I-I'll send Po and Harris,
and I'll fold in later.
Got it.
I really hope you're enjoying
your revenge for that Tim Test.
I'm really not.
Come on, come on.
[Sighs]
[Dramatic music plays]
[Wood chipper grinding]
♪
[Cellphone chimes]
[Sighs]
You texting Elijah?
He's texting me.
A-And if I don't respond,
he'll get suspicious.
Oh, so what
are you gonna say?
"With the D.A. now.
They're buying every word."
Yeah. Hmm.
[Cellphone swishes]
Am I lying?
Do they believe I'm here
to help take down Elijah?
Not fully.
Do you?
No.
Maybe.
If I've learned
anything about you,
it's that
you're not a victim.
If Elijah really did terrorize
you this morning, um,
I don't imagine you'd roll over
and take it.
Hey.
I guess they
do believe you.
Sgt. Grey: You're part
of a very small group
that knows
she's cooperating.
So if this gets out,
we know who to look at.
I'll be dead, but at least
we'll know who to blame.
It won't get out.
According to Monica,
Elijah's been looking
for new partners to help him
launder his extra money.
And he's found one...
Angels Check Cashing.
Alright,
what are we looking at?
Elijah's done
his due diligence.
He's ready
to finalize the deal.
He will be there today
with at least $2 million.
He will be armed.
So will his guys.
How many guys?
Usually two bodyguards,
at least.
They carry handguns
and keep automatic weapons
in the spare-tire
compartment.
Alright, anyone makes a move
for the SUV, we drop them.
This is our ops plan
with an overview
of how today will go.
It also has everyone's
numbers listed.
[Scoffs]
Asterisks are next to those
who will be present.
Make sure you study it.
Any questions?
[Cellphone ringing]
It's...
It's not Elijah.
But I do have
a meeting to get to
if I'm gonna keep up appearances.
Okay, let's mobilize.
Good luck.
[Camera shutter clicks]
Keep that phone close.
We will be reaching out.
You better hope
this goes smoothly.
I've learned better
than to put my trust
in the competency
of the LAPD.
Maybe you'll surprise me.
♪
There you are.
Hey,
what did Lopez say?
That she will investigate
this new angle.
Nothing may come
of this,
but rest assured,
she'll do everything she can.
Thank you.
I mean, this is more hope
than I've had
in a long time.
There's more.
It's about your mother.
Guzman told you
what they were doing?
Were they
having an affair?
No.
What then?
Look, whatever you
tell me can't be worse
than the scenarios
I've created in my head.
It seems your mother
hurt her back a while ago.
I remember.
I used to have to
pick things up for her.
Your mother became addicted
to the painkillers
that the doctor
prescribed for her.
And then he cut her off.
On the day your sister
was abducted,
your mother
was buying drugs.
No.
No, that... that...
that's not right.
I'm afraid it is.
And it explains
why she lied
to the police
and to you.
She was ashamed.
So she... she... she...
she told us to...
to play outside to...
to get rid of us,
to... to keep us busy
so she could score?
Your mother
was an addict.
She wasn't
thinking clearly.
She was supposed to
keep us safe,
and she wasn't
even there.
All these years,
I mean, do you have any idea
how much I've blamed
myself?
Hey, you were just a kid.
It wasn't your fault.
I know.
It was hers.
Are you buying this
whole Monica reinvention?
If someone I work for
tried to put me in a wood
chipper, I'd flip on them.
If someone tried to put you
in a wood chipper,
they'd be in
the wood chipper.
True.
[Chuckles]
[Dramatic music plays]
♪
Is that Elijah?
It looks like his SUV.
Yeah, it also looks like
every other SUV.
Did anyone get a positive I.D.
on Elijah?
Sgt. Grey: Negative.
What do you think?
Hit it or hold?
Look, I know
you really want Elijah,
but we can't be sure
that he's inside.
That's not important
right now.
We have intel
that a crime
is being committed
at this address.
That's what
we should focus on.
Alright,
we're green and go.
[Dramatic music plays]
♪
[Tires screech]
Police. Put the bags down.
Let me see your hands.
Line up.
Hands on the counter.
Where's Elijah?
Who?
You know who.
Lotta money here.
$2 million, $2.5 million maybe.
Possessing money
isn't a crime.
Yeah, but carrying
a loaded firearm
under your clothes without
a concealed-carry permit is.
But I'm sure you have
one of those, don't you?
Search the SUV, too.
Hope you have
a good lawyer.
Don't worry about me, shorty.
Just worry about yourself.
You did not just
threaten my partner.
Move.
[Wood chipper grinding][Gun cocks]
[Engine revs]
Get in.
[Car door closes]
They raided the place,
got Wyatt
and the $2 million.
This better
be worth it.
I told you,
if we didn't sacrifice
an important piece,
they'd know it
was a setup.
But if you're
feeling sad,
I can just keep
all of these
police phone numbers
to myself.
Or maybe I can put us
on a group thread,
maybe share
some fun memes.
I got you
what you asked for.
Now it's your turn.
[Chuckles]
You're safe...
for now.
[Cellphone chimes]
[Sighs]
Okay.
Well, this will make
tonight's meeting
a lot more secure.
We can track
every member of Metro
through their phones.
Make sure they're nowhere
near us.
Elijah, I told you,
a meeting right now
is not a good idea.
The LAPD
is all over you.
Postpone a week,
at the least.
If I reschedule,
Abril is gonna wonder why.
You want to tell
our new business partner
the police
are all over us?
[Cellphone chimes]
It's the cops.
[Ringing]
Harper: I cannot wait to hear
the story you're about to sell.
What, did Elijah
have a tummy ache?
Or maybe he was just at home
watching his stories?
I don't know why
he wasn't there.
Elijah doesn't explain
himself to me.
But he was pissed that
you took Wyatt off the board
and confiscated
a couple million.
If you can't use the bust
to build a case
against Mr. Stone,
perhaps the LAPD
should reconsider
your qualifications
as a detective.
[Chuckles]
Man, I love your
fighting spirit,
but you are not gonna steamroll
your way through this.
We need intel that leads us
directly to Elijah.
If we don't get that,
you don't get your immunity.
We knew she might have been
playing us,
that she
was after something.
But it couldn't
just be about
getting the ops plan
like we suspected.
There's got to be
a bigger game at play here.
Or at least
Elijah sacrificed Wyatt
and a large sum of money
to get what he was after.
$2 million
is a cheap price to pay
to be able
to track our movements.
And Wyatt has already
called for a lawyer.
So we're not gonna get
anything from him.
Alright, well, then
all we can do
is wait for Elijah's
next move.
Tim: What the hell
are you doing?
Nothing.
Really? Because it looks like
you're Googling
"how to delete
traffic tickets."
You know you can't do that
from these computers.
Traffic citations
are managed
in a completely
different office.
Which is a good thing,
because accessing
or altering a police computer
is a crime.
I'm sorry.
My dad said we couldn't afford
all the fines, and...
Uh, your dad
put you up to this?
Okay, do you
even have cancer?
- Tim.
- Yeah, that part's true.
Okay, but you lied about
wanting to be a cop?
Of course.
Cops are wack.
I wanted to be on the sidelines
for a Rams game.
But he said if I could
figure out a way
to get rid of his tickets,
he'd buy me an e-bike.
[Scoffs] That's why
you were asking about
old pet names
for potential passwords.
That's clever.
Okay, so, if you have
to Google your crime,
you're clearly
not a hacker.
How'd you get
into our system?
Found this.
[Scoffs]
Really? Did he
have to write that down
to remember it?
What's this about?
Where's Jordy?
He's down the hall.
He's fine.
Why am I in here?
My kid's sick, and you're
treating me like a criminal.
You are a criminal,
Mr. Yates.
And you made
your son one, too.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You forced him to choose
a police station
for his "Make a Dream"
because you thought
he could get in
and expunge your record.
We could charge Jordy
for unauthorized
computer access
and attempted burglary.
You can't do that.
He didn't know.
He's got cancer.
Nobody
wants to charge Jordy.
You, on
the other hand...
It's just
a couple of tickets.
It's 37.
And you used a minor
in the commission of a crime.
Do you understand that
that is a felony?
His medical costs
are killing us.
And if I didn't get
those tickets taken care of,
it... it'd cost me
my car and my license.
I know I messed up,
but I can't go to jail.
My family needs me.
♪
Alright, you're not going
to jail, Mr. Yates.
You're going to "Daddy and Me
Traffic School."
There's an arcade.
Jordy will love it.
I don't know what to say.
[Sniffles]
How can I make it up
to you?
Be a better father
to your son.
[Elevator bell dings]
I have to be quick.
Elijah thinks I'm here
bailing out a client.
Why the urgency?
I just found out there's going
to be a high-level meeting
at the Van Nuys
airfield tonight.
- With who?
- Elijah didn't say.
But he was nervous
about it.
My guess is that it's someone
connected to Abril.
What time?
9:00.
I'll text "the Pharmacy"
if I hear anything more.
[Elevator bell dings]
Do that.
You buying any of this?
I'm buying there's a meeting,
but not at the airfield.
Alright, we need to figure
out where, and fast.
I'll call Garza, see if anyone
on the federal level
knows about
Abril's movements.
Alright, everyone, quiet down.
Bring it in.
Sgt. Grey: So, we got intel
a little while ago
that Elijah Stone
has a high-level meeting
scheduled for tonight
at Van Nuys airfield.
Metro has four units en route
to that location as we speak.
[Sirens wailing]
♪
Elijah: Talk to me. LAPD took the bait.
Metro cops just blew by me
on their way to the airfield.
Good, tracking a dozen
cellphones in those vehicles.
By the time they figure out
it's a wild goose chase,
it'll all be over.
Now, thanks to six
night-shift officers
and a dozen burner phones,
Elijah believes
that the LAPD
will be chasing shadows
down at the airfield.
Now, the real target
is Elijah's associate Daylin.
Feds tracked her entering
the country two hours ago.
We got eyes on her.
She's gonna lead us to that
exact meet-up location.
So let's mount up
and get 'em.
♪
Daylin just pulled in.
Still no sign of Elijah.
Yeah. Good.
Get our truck rolling.
Daylin just landed.
We're one minute out.
♪
[Cellphone buzzes]
Monica just texted.
"Meet moved
to Port of L.A.
East Container Yard.
Happening now."
She either grew a conscience
or she's covering her ass.
I'm gonna go with "B."
If we weren't here already,
we'd be screwed.
[Radio static]
Tim: Heads up.
Black SUV and box truck
entering the container yard.
It's gotta be Elijah.
Yeah, after earlier,
I'll believe it when I see it.
♪
Elijah is here,
and so is Monica.
Buenas noches.
It is, indeed.
So, shall we show each other
something sexy?
Yes, please.
[Truck rear door opens]
500 pounds
of premium cut.
$8 million in cold,
hard cash,
plus an extra $2 million
as your fee
to wash the money
for me.
Pleasure doing business
with you.
Two trucks, drugs,
and money.
[Radio static]
We have eyes on the exchange.
Tim,
you ready to move in?
[Radio static]
Tim: Negative.
East team's radios
just went out.
Working on
getting them back.
We can't wait.
Roll everyone you can.
[Dramatic music plays]
♪
[Indistinct conversation]
Police!
Get on the ground!
[Gunfire]
[Indistinct shouting]
[DMTV's "Allostatic Age"
plays]
♪
[Gasps]
♪ With a twist and shout
[Sirens wailing]
♪ The curtains burning up
♪ And so goes the house
[Tires screeching]
♪ Oppression olympians
♪ Algorithm static
[Train whistle in distance]
[Footsteps approach]
[Grunts]
[Dramatic music plays]
[Both grunting]
♪
[Breathing heavily]
Good night.
[Gun cocks]
Get on the ground!
Do it now!
[Grunts,
breathing heavily]
Did you miss,
or do that on purpose?
On the ground now!
Yeah,
you probably missed.
But now you
can't shoot me.
Get down!
Last warning.
Or what?
How's that gonna look?
You just happen to be
the one to shoot me?
No body cameras,
no witnesses?
You can't pull the trigger now, Angela.
We have
too much history.
Stay where you are.
Do not come any closer.
I will shoot you.
"Breaking news...
LAPD Detective Angela Lopez
was arrested today
for the revenge killing
of Elijah Stone."
No one
will believe that.
"An LAPD spokesperson confirmed
Elijah Stone was unarmed
when he was murdered
by Detective Lopez."
Come on.
You sat in my kitchen,
threatened to fight me in
the street with a claw hammer.
I'm saying, let's go!
[Breathing heavily]
Unless you're all mouth.
Good.
But know this.
I'm gonna punch you in that baby
as many times as I can.
Ugh!
[Breathing heavily]
That's the only one
you're gonna land.
[Grunting]
♪
[Breathing heavily]
Here, you hook him up.
You deserve it.
Thanks.
[Groaning]
[Cellphone chimes]
[Handcuffs clicks]
When you find out
what I've done,
you're gonna wish you
had killed me.
What the hell
are you talking about?
You'll find out.
[Dramatic music plays]
What have you done?
♪
Where?
On our way where?
♪
[Knock on door]
No, I'll get it.
[Grunting]
[Gunfire]
♪
Move, move, move!
[Gunfire]
♪
Hey!
[Glass shatters]
[Knife unsheathes]
♪
[Grunts]
[Bar clangs]
Down!
[Gunfire]
[Groaning]
[Handcuffs clicks]
Oh, Celina, I saw the officer
at my door
and I imagined the worst.
I'm fine.
[Breathing shakily]
What's happening?
You know
I can't be outside.
I can't deal with the noise
and the lights.
Mami, stop.
Breathe.
Okay. We'll get you home
as soon as possible.
Okay.
But, first, they're gonna
ask you questions
about Blanca's case.
Why?
Did they find something?
Do they know who did it?
No.
But they want to know where
you were when it happened.
I was...
I was lying down.
I had a headache.
W-We went over this
so many times.
No, Mami.
No more lies.
I know about the drugs.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I stopped that day,
I swear.
You lied to me
my whole life.
I know.
♪
How could I tell you
the truth?
That I abandoned you?
That it was my fault
that she got taken?
You'd hate me.
I can't handle that.
[Crying]
The detectives
are waiting.
[Exhales sharply]
♪
[Door opens]
[Sighs]
"Daddy and Me Traffic School"
sounds fun.
Yeah.
The kid gets
$5 in tokens, too.
It was a really nice gesture, Tim.
Look, I wanted to throw
that guy in jail
for putting his son
in that position.
But?
You're a good influence.
You're gonna make a really great
dad one of these days.
I'm gonna have to if
you keep losing our
kids everywhere you go.
Come on. Stop it.
Sir, any news on Abril?
Just spoke to Garza.
The Feds have everything
we got off Elijah's phone.
They were in
regular contact.
So, with any luck,
they'll be able to pinpoint
the base of her operations.
Okay,
with Elijah in jail,
all the drug dealers
he had under his thumb
are gonna be climbing
for his crown.
It's whack-a-mole,
narco edition.
Yeah, but for now,
we can enjoy the win.
Tomorrow we'll worry
about all that.
You're free to go.
[Handcuffs unlock]
You know,
that was a smart move,
texting us
at the last minute.
Now we can't say
you weren't cooperating.
Elijah had me
tied to his hip.
I warned you about the location
change as soon as I could.
That is exactly what
a smart lawyer would say.
And the classified
operations report
I leaked
to a drug lord?
Right. About that.
Um, I've written a report
that will stay
in my computer
for up to five years.
I intend to keep this report
on my computer.
But if your name ever crosses
my desk again,
you will be charged
with obstruction of justice,
conspiracy, wire fraud,
and burglary.
I can hold this
over your head
until the statute of limitations expires.
So, between now and 60 months
from now,
assuming I don't die,
your ass belongs to me.
Oh,
and we planted the report.
It was full
of false information.
All the phone numbers
were fake.
Yeah.
So, you never
really trusted me.
Are you surprised?
Impressed.
You're finally learning.
Maybe one day you will, too.
I have to say,
this whole thing has been
a, um,
learning experience
for me.
I'm thinking about, uh...
...thinking about
turning over a new leaf.
I won't hold my breath.
["Falling Outside" plays]
[Sighs]
How is Celina?
Oh,
she hasn't said much.
I think she's still processing.
Is any of this
gonna help catch the guy?
It might.
We're tracking Karla's dealer
and known associates.
It doesn't help that
the whole thing
happened 15 years ago.
If any of them
were involved,
they've had plenty of time
to destroy evidence
or get their story straight.
I can't imagine what a blow
this has been for Celina.
You know,
just a week ago,
she and her mother
had a great relationship.
Packed with lies.
Yes, true.
But... they were close.
I hope they
can get there again.
Me too.
♪ It's an illusion
[Ringing]
I thought you should know,
the Feds have Elijah's phone.
It's only a matter of time
before they kick in your door.
Of course.
And, Abril...
let me know
if I can be of any help.
♪
[Sighs]
I can't believe
it's finally over.
I know.
I wanted to celebrate,
but the bullet holes
are a bit of a mood killer.
Ah, I don't know.
I think we
should keep them.
It's a great
conversation starter.
So you could tell the
story of how you fought
off a hired hitman?
Exactly. Like,
I'm working that
into every conversation
until the day I die.
[Both chuckle]
That's fair.
It was very heroic.
How about we patch up
all but one?
♪ You gotta let it go
Deal.
And by "we,"
you mean...
Nolan, obviously. Yeah.
Come on.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
You know,
on the bright side,
no matter how bad
this place looks,
Elijah is somewhere
far worse.
[Door buzzes]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Door closes]
Man: Hey, neighbor.
I got a veritable library
over here.
What's your jam?
Science fiction,
thriller, romance?
You got any
revenge stories?
Boy, do I.
Captions by VITAC...
♪