All right.
Now turn right.
Are you sure
you were born in March?
Oh, I think she knows what month
she was born in.
Who are you, little one?
Are you here of
your own free will,
or are you a droid
locked in servitude?
She doesn't even know
what planet she's on.
Okay, that's fair.
But the state of California
did require her to show
her birth certificate
when she got
that driver's license.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just saying...
You know, Pisces are normally
way too gentle
to go on a drunken
vandalism spree.
There's nothing normal about
the people we interact with.
You are destined for more
than this, little one.
Do you want to know a secret?
I'm not really
Danielle Vonderclomp.
My parents adopted me
from a Lithuanian orphanage
when I was 2.
My history,
shrouded in darkness.
I believe that I am
secretly a princess
destined to go back home
one day to rule.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Your Highness, are you saying
your parents just made up
a birthday for you?
Well, duh.
I told you so.
Please don't.
She's a Leo, for sure.
I said don't.
Have you seen my hair tie?
Nightstand.
I swear I looked here.
So, today's the day?
It is. And...?
And... great.
You think I'm going
back to work too soon?
I voiced my opinion,
and I respect your decision.
Right. It's just that...
Well, technically,
you were dead.
I mean, you were gone,
and they brought you back.
I just think maybe it might
take you more than a week
to get past that.
Yeah, but it's not like
that's the first time.
Sure, but...
Whoa, wait. What?
You've been dead before?
I knew
this was a bad idea.
We should've used a service
to cover Justine's vacation.
Your mom just wants
to spend more time with Jack.
Why hire a temp nanny
when he's got family?
Because a nanny
would be on time.
I have to go.
Can you stay until she shows?
Yeah. Go.
Mami!
Huh?
Call 911!
We should let Marshall
pick every restaurant
for all the sergeant's meetings.
Did you try that
breakfast sandwich?
No. Ashley's got me on
this Whole30 thing.
No bread.
Oh, you're missing out.
Hey, Smitty.
Yeah, Sarge?
You can't park your
personal vehicle in spots
designated for marked units.
The RV isn't my vehicle,
it's my house.
#VanLife.
You can't park your house
in marked spots either.
Any chance he retires soon?
You aren't that lucky.
Okay.
She needs a couple stitches,
and I'd like to admit her,
get a CAT scan to make sure
nothing more serious presents.
Of course.
Thank you, Doctor.
Are you single?
Mom!
Because I have four sons.
One's a priest,
but the others could use
a successful, young,
beautiful woman like yourself.
That's sweet, but I'm engaged.
Oh, congratulations.
You let me know
if it doesn't work out.
Sure thing.
Mom.
I need you to tell me what happened.
I'm fine.
Where's my grandbaby?
At home with Wesley.
Well, let's go see them.
The doctors are overreacting.
You're not leaving
until they clear you.
I once worked an eight-hour
shift with a broken wrist.
Last time I heard that story,
it was a six-hour shift
with a sprain.
Point is, I'm tougher
than I look.
I know how tough you are,
but I need you
to tell me what happened.
Nothing.
I don't want to freak you out.
I'm a cop. Nothing freaks me out.
I was on my way to see you
when a big man grabbed me.
I whacked him with my purse.
He threw me down.
What aren't you telling me?
Nothing.
I'm sure it's a misunderstanding.
Mom.
"Tell your son
he's out of time."
Out of time for what?
I don't know.
That's all he said.
Which son?
I don't know!
It has to be a misunderstanding.
Your brothers
are all such good boys.
My brothers used to
stuff me in a pillowcase
and drag me around
the neighborhood.
And look how tough it made you.
They did you a favor.
What's with all these diets
Ashley has you on?
Her dad's having heart trouble.
Burglary. 10:00.
Control, 7-Adam-100,
we got a burglary in progress.
4-9-1-9-2 Figueroa.
Send additional units.
Hey! Show me your hands!
Foot pursuit. White adult male.
Black hoodie,
jeans, headed south.
Get off of me!
It's okay.
I got it, I got it.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Just, uh, tweaked my back
on the takedown.
Oh!
You're not fine. You're in agony.
We're taking you
to the hospital.
What happened?
He must have been going
at least 70.
Lost control, hit a couple
parked cars, flipped.
Several deep lacerations.
Possible internal bleeding.
Uh, don't move.
It's stuck again.
Here. I'll pinch.
You lift.
Got it.
...three, up!
All right.
Headed to Saint Stephen.
And what do we do next?
We, uh, wait for backup
to secure the scene,
then head to the hospital.
Why?
Well, a death investigation
triggers different protocols.
We go with the victim
in case he dies.
Nicely done.
How's your mom?
Okay, I think.
She keeps going on about
how it was a misunderstanding.
Uh, you think one of
your brothers is in trouble?
It wouldn't be the first time.
If one of them is a reason
for Mom's attack,
I will rain down
hell's own fury.
Okay. So, technically,
this can't be your case.
I know. It's your case.
I'm not even here.
Good, because it's
a major conflict of interest
for you to investigate
your own brothers.
I know.
Plus, if I do it,
I might end up
killing one of them.
Huh.
And here they come now.
That's Damian,
my oldest brother.
Also known as Father Lopez
or Father D.
Amen to that.
He started a nonprofit
teaching job skills
to former gang members,
so he's got just as many friends
as he does enemies.
And that's
Benjamin "Benny" Lopez.
Second oldest.
He was Gordon Gekko for Halloween
from the time he was 3.
When he was 12,
he opened an investment account
using lawnmower earnings
and our abuelita's
Social Security number.
Her portfolio
is better than mine.
And that's Cruz.
Middle child.
In and out of rehab
since he was 18.
Just can't seem
to get it together.
When I became a cop, my mom made
me promise to never arrest him.
I thought you had four brothers.
Bruno's the youngest,
but he's been in New York
since college.
I really don't think
he's involved.
Angela, what's going on?
Mom's in the hospital.
She okay?
Wait. What happened?
Well, why didn't you have us
meet there?
Your mother was
attacked this morning
on her way to Angela's house.
She suffered a blow to the head.
The doctors are
running some tests.
Who would attack Mom?
Hold on.
Is that why we're here?
What, you think it's our fault?
The assailant said, "Tell your
son he's running out of time."
So, yeah, I think one of you
is at fault,
and no one's leaving
until I get answers.
All right, if one of you
wants to make this easy
and just confess,
that would be awesome.
All right, then.
Hard way it is.
Come on.
Really?
What is this?
I'm just gonna move you
real fast.
That's an exit wound.
Control, Engine 53.
Advise Saint Stephen
we have a gunshot victim.
ETA six minutes,
and advise PD we have a GSW.
Oh! Calm down, buddy.
We're almost at the hospital.
Oh!
It's gonna be okay.
I thought I fixed it.
It's fine.
You hold pressure.
I'll go get another gurney.
No!
Greg!
What happened?
Our patient must've attacked him.
Why?
I found a gunshot wound
when I was cleaning him up.
He would know the hospital
would have to report
that gunshot to the police.
He's gone inside the hospital.
We need to lock it down now.
Security guard.
Hi. John Nolan.
Jasper Lee.
Hospital's locked down.
All incoming calls
are being rerouted.
Okay, we're gonna have to
post up at all the exits,
check everyone's I.D.
before they leave.
Does that mean you've got
an I.D. on this guy?
Rob Lukasey.
He left his wallet in the car.
A laundry list of priors.
- Uh, Celina, can you get him
a photo to distribute? - Will do.
He's in bad shape.
His first priority will be
patching himself up.
Well, we can put extra security
on the pharmacy
and storage rooms.
But the truth is,
there's medical supplies
everywhere in here.
I got more officers
coming to help,
but I'm sure I don't
have to tell you
what a big job this is gonna be.
8 floors, 600 beds,
34 operating rooms.
In our simulations,
a thorough search
takes five hours.
Hmm.
Well, let's get to it.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Agh. Nolan.
You all right?
Yeah, uh, fine.
What... What's
the lockdown status?
Uh, we got, uh, everything
checked off the list, but...
No, call Grey and tell him
Tim is not here as a supervisor.
He's here as a patient.
I told you, I'm fine. Agh!
Oh, my God.
Ohh, okay.
Okay, I'm not fine.
Get me a doctor.
"Tell your son
he's out of time."
Any idea what that means?
No. No. If I did,
I would tell you.
Ask him about his record.
I was getting to that.
So, you got a couple arrests
for public intoxication
and multiple DUIs.
Ancient history.
I've been sober for one year
and 47 days today.
Whoa.
What are you doing here?
I'm representing my client.
What?
Hey, Ange.
You're not even a defense attorney anymore.
Look, I know.
This is my chance to get one
of your brothers to like me.
They're never gonna like you.
Objection... argumentative.
Your mother-in-law is
in the hospital right now
because of him.
Objection... speculation.
All right. Enough.
You, sit down.
Yeah.
You, go back inside.
All right.
That was dope.
Yeah.
Can we get back on track?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look, I've been trying
to tell you,
that last DUI was the best thing
to happen to me.
I've been clean and sober
ever since.
I understand you work with
a lot of ex-cons.
Guilt by association.
Really, Detective?
It's all right.
My mission is to help people
get out of the gang life.
What if one of the gangs
got tired of you interfering
and decided to send a message?
By attacking my mother?
No.
The people that I work with,
they might not
always agree with me,
but they respect the collar.
Even if they didn't,
they know my sister's a cop.
So if it's not because of you,
which brother do you think
I should be focused on?
Cruz, Clearly.
Uh, sorry.
I just need to respond to this.
As I was saying...
A thousand apologies.
Uh...
It never ends. Uh...
Sorry.
No, you're not.
Uh, what exactly is
your business, Mr. Lopez?
Um...
- I...
- Okay.
Hey, while I have you here,
Angela's been dragging her feet.
We really gotta get
baby Jack baptized.
No, you know, I just...
I don't really want to get in the middle of...
of what you guys have...
Well, I know.
I know you're not Catholic.
What's your denomination?
Protestant?
I don't know.
Is that even an option?
No.
Oh.
I'm gonna go with Episcopalian.
Sure.
Look, I get it.
Your line of work,
there is
a lot of money at stake.
Might drive a person
to violence.
The guys I work with, they're not gonna
beat up someone's mom.
That's too kind.
They'll just sue you to death.
Can I just answer that one...
Mnh-mnh.
Ask him about his credit report.
I was getting to that.
So, we ran your credit report,
and we saw that
you took out a $15,000 loan.
You wanna tell us about that?
You don't have to answer that.
Yes, he does.
The loan is for college classes.
I'm getting my bachelor's
in accounting.
I didn't want to
say anything in case
I couldn't hack it
because I know
what you think of me.
And I know I screwed up a lot.
I know you have no reason
to trust me.
But whatever's going on,
it's not me.
Clear on floor two.
Floor three clear.
Heading to four.
Okay. Thank you.
Well, our suspect
killed a woman this morning.
Home invasion in West Hollywood.
The victim's husband
managed to get the gun
away from the suspect
and shoot him as he escaped.
Okay, so he's looking at
life in prison if we catch him.
When we catch him.
God, I hate hospitals.
Doesn't everyone?
Yeah, I guess.
Hey.
How's your partner?
Shattered cheekbone.
Plastic surgeon's on his way in.
You're going back to work?
I'll wait until he's out of surgery.
Right.
I just found out this morning
Bailey has been dead
more than once.
I know.
I felt it when I first met her.
One had something to do with,
uh, flying?
Wow. Yeah.
A-A-A halo jump went sideways.
This is Nolan,
fourth floor west.
We just found
the suspect's bloody clothes.
Looks like he tried to patch
himself up best he could.
Right, and then changed
into some scrubs.
He'll still need an I.D.
in order to exit the building.
Well, if he can break
into a house,
he can steal
a staff I.D.
I'll run down
all the gang members
who work for Father Lopez.
Cruz agreed to a drug test,
so we should have those results
in a couple hours.
For the first time in his life,
I actually think he's innocent.
I've always been so hard on him.
Maybe if I had been
more supportive,
he would have gotten clean sooner.
You know better.
Addicts only get clean
when they are ready.
Oh. There you are.
Uh, you okay?
You're looking a little shiny.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm... I'm fine.
I just feel a little warm.
Look, I thought you should know,
hospital's locked down
while they search
for a homicide suspect.
I'm heading over to supervise.
There's a killer in the hospital
with my mother?
Relax. She's fine.
I assigned Thorsen
to watch her door.
Hi, ma'am. I'm Officer Aaron Thorsen.
Hm?
I've been assigned
to keep you safe,
and I just want to let you know
that there's nothing
to worry about.
You are handsome.
Thank you.
Do you have any sisters?
No, I'm an only child.
Cousins?
My second eldest son, Benny,
he is successful, sweet,
goes to church on Sundays.
Mm.
But he needs a woman
to settle down with.
Are you asking me to set up one
of my cousins with your son?
And in return, I will set you up
with my niece, Isabella.
She's a professional dancer.
You got a picture?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
It's probably
just a muscle spasm.
You didn't have to clock out.
Of course I did.
Oh, hey. I'm just
searching for bad guys.
All clear here.
Wait, so Nolan's leaving
someone on every floor?
Yes. We've been cops
for more than 10 seconds.
We can handle this.
Hey, Doc, what's the word?
When we took that bullet out
a few years back,
there was a-a fragment that was
too complicated to remove.
I remember.
Bullet?
I was shot.
It wasn't a big deal.
I saved his life
first day on the job.
It was a huge deal.
Back to the fragment.
The pain you're experiencing
is because the fragment
has migrated closer
to your spinal column
and is pressing up
against a nerve.
We'll need to do surgery
to remove it.
Okay.
Uh, when?
Well, I mean, hold on.
Wh-What are the risks?
Well, we are talking about
the spine, so...
yes, it's risky.
But it's laparoscopic.
So if all goes well,
he'll be home by dinner.
If?
I know it's scary,
but leaving the fragment
in place is much riskier.
Well, then we do surgery.
Thank you.
Uh...
I'm gonna get back
to the search.
South wing is clear.
Headed to north.
Sir. Are you...?
Oh, my... Oh!
I... I need help over here!
Ah, good thing I was
on the Whole30 diet.
That food poisoning is no joke.
Marshall can never pick
the breakfast place again.
Never.
Oh, no.
This is kind of fun.
It's like a sleepover.
Oh, God.
Should I call the nurse?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- You need to get back
to the station immediately. - What?
What? Why?
Because if we're both
out of commission...
Based on seniority...
Smitty's in charge.
Oh.
Yeah. You're still standing there.
Go.
Yeah.
Hey, man.
All right, bro.
Smitty.
Smitty!
Hey!
Wha... What's going on?
Acting Sergeant Smitty.
Right. Why is Casey Curtis
leaving the station?
End of shift time off.
When you're in charge,
you can let all your friends
go home early.
But we're short today.
You know how many units
are attached
to the hospital event, right?
Self-care is important.
Smitty...
- Get out!
- All right!
What the hell
is going on?
We caught the guy who beat up
Father Lopez's mother.
We heard what happened
to your mom and wanted to help.
So you abducted a man?
It was a citizen's arrest.
On what evidence?
He's been talkin' smack about
Father Lopez for weeks!
The whole hood heard him.
He's lucky that's all I did.
Hypocrite's sleeping
with my wife.
With me, now.
You're sleeping with his wife?
You're a priest.
I know.
Been struggling
with my vows recently.
Are you kidding me?
Jumping to adultery
is more than just struggling.
We all fall short
of the glory of God.
But I really don't think Carmody
had anything to do with Mom.
I have to look into it.
You never know
what people are capable of.
I didn't know you were
capable of this.
You know,
with your injury,
you could retire right now
if you wanted.
She's right.
Are you trying to get rid of me?
It's not a crazy idea.
My dad waited too long
to call it quits.
He can't do any of
the things he planned on.
It's a good deal.
Disability pay is the average of
your last three years of income,
50% salary plus overtime.
That's about 60%
of your current take home.
And that's tax free, right?
Yes, it is.
Plus, my dad gets
a cost-of-living adjustment.
That's a 3% raise every year,
for life.
I never really
did the math before.
Just think.
We both love to travel.
I always did want to see a game
at every Major League stadium.
W-We could even
move out of L.A.
I mean, I can be
a lifeguard anywhere.
Right? So long
as there's a beach.
I hear Bali has
a bunch of those.
That's true.
This is so exciting.
No, I haven't decided anything.
No, I know, but...
Free money?
You'd be crazy not to, right?
Hm.
Anybody else hungry?
Probably not the best time,
right?
I'll pass.
I'm just gonna grab something
from the cafeteria.
Bye.
Just think about it.
Okay.
Have they been assessed yet?
Here's the thing.
Melody... she's wonderful.
I love her to death.
She's my favorite cousin.
But?
But I-I don't think
she's right for Cruz.
You know, he needs
someone who's solid
and is gonna call him
on his B.S.
You're thinking Tara.
You're not wrong.
Okay, Angela just sent me
a photo of this guy Carmody.
Is this the man
that attacked you?
No.
No?
Mnh-mnh.
Oh.
Okay, I told her that they're
gonna be releasing you soon,
so she should be on her way.
Oh, hey, did you set up
Wesley and Lopez?
No.
She never needed my help.
She was born
knowing her own mind.
Yeah, that sounds like Lopez.
Can I see Isabella
one more time?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Wow!
Yeah, I'm telling you.
Very flexible.
Clear.
You know, cops spend an awful
lot of time in hospitals.
Whatever your aversion is,
you're gonna have to
deal with it.
I know.
I have to ask...
You don't see dead people?
No.
I mean, who doesn't feel
a presence from time to time?
Me.
Most everyone I know.
Yeah, but I'm not crazy.
I don't see dead people.
Good.
It's just that hospitals
remind me of my sister.
When they found her,
she was in bad shape.
She, uh, held out for two weeks,
and I visited every day.
I'm sorry.
Next floor?
Yeah.
She's one of the best
surgeons in the country.
I'm not worried.
It's okay if you are.
Eh, it's just a little
spinal surgery, you know?
Might be fine.
Might be paralyzed for life.
Excited to find out which.
I'm gonna go stretch
my legs while I still can.
Agh.
That's the spirit.
Mm.
- Hey.
Agh.
Agh!
It was the shooter.
Don't try to move.
I can't.
What happened?
The fragment must've shifted
towards Tim's spinal cord,
and that's what's causing
his paralysis.
Can you tell my sister, please?
Sure.
Hey, do not tell Chen.
She's got enough on her plate.
We need to get you
into surgery stat.
Agh!
If you two hit it off...
Mm-hmm.
...I expect you to name
your firstborn after me.
Okay, that's a deal.
Mom, are you setting up Aaron?
Yes.
Don't you think he'd be perfect
for Isabella?
Izzie's way out of his league.
No offense.
No, I agree.
Any news on Tim?
No.
He's still in surgery
for about two more hours.
Oh.
Go join the manhunt.
Okay.
Your brothers texted me
to say you interrogated them
at the station
like common criminals.
You know I don't like it when
you fight with your brothers.
Mom, you were assaulted.
Aw.
You're lucky you're okay.
But one of your sons
is in serious danger.
And if there's something
you're not telling me,
you're not protecting them.
You're leaving them at risk.
I told you everything.
Tell me again.
I went outside to wait
for my rideshare.
Out of nowhere,
a man attacked me.
I hit him with my purse.
He said, "Tell your son"...
Back up.
Rideshare?
What happened to your car?
I gave it to Benny.
What do you mean,
you gave it to Benny?
He said he needed it.
I didn't ask.
You've reached Benjamin Lopez.
Leave a message.
Hey, how's Tim?
Still in surgery.
Is Benny still at the station?
No. He went to work.
Why?
He lied.
He's having money problems.
I tried to call him,
but he's not answering.
We ran his credit report.
We didn't see
any outstanding loans.
An enforcer going after family?
That's off-the-books debt.
He's into a loan shark.
We need to find him
so I can kill him
before somebody else does.
Jan.
Where's everybody going?
Pool party at Mario's.
- No...
- No.
Uh, we don't have
the staff for that.
Y-You have to stay.
Well, Acting Sergeant Smitty
says we don't.
Oh. Can you
talk to them?
I believe it was Tim and Grey
who sent you back
to rein in Smitty.
They don't respect me, but...
What are you talking about?
You just saw. I...
Yeah, that's because
Smitty told them to go home.
You just have to tell them
something different.
Hey.
After everything
you have been through,
how often you
have proven yourself,
there is not a cop in here
who would not have your back
if you asked.
Uh, hey, guys, listen up.
I need your help.
We have two sergeants
out of commission
in the hospital right now
and a murder suspect
on the loose.
That search has us
spread pretty thin.
We need all hands on deck
right now.
I'm sorry, but the pool party,
it has to wait.
- You got it, Chen.
- All right.
Let's go, guys.
She needs us.
You heard her.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you!
So, does this mean
you're in charge now?
Yeah, I guess so.
Cool.
I'll be in the breakroom.
Being in charge is exhausting.
Nolan!
He cut the wire so the alarm
wouldn't go off.
Nice catch.
I'll cover.
I see blood.
Should we split up?
Well, proper procedure says
we stay within
40 feet of each other,
hearing distance,
just in case
anything goes wrong.
If you'd rather
stick together...
No. I can handle it.
We got to find this guy fast.
All right.
I'll go left.
You go right.
We'll meet up back here.
Copy.
Jasper.
Not a sound,
or I'll blow your head off.
Celina!
7-Adam-15, I have an officer
down and another one missing.
7-Adam-15?
7-Adam-15, I have
priority traffic.
Be smart.
Just keep moving...
All units clear the air
for priority traffic.
...and everything will be fine.
Adam-15 go.
I can't raise
Officer Juarez on the radio.
She may have been 2-0-7'd
but still in the hospital.
I need additional units
to help search.
Turn that off.
- I said turn it off!
- I did.
Where are we going?
To the ambulance bay?
Just shut up and keep moving.
Okay. Okay.
Get in.
Oh.
Just give me a minute.
Look, there's no
happy endings here.
You know that, right?
Shut up.
You need to get
your wounds treated.
You should have
kidnapped a doctor.
Shut up.
I just need to catch my breath.
Let me at least take a look
at your wounds.
Nice try.
Look...
police officers have a sworn
responsibility to render aid,
even to people
trying to kill them.
Lift your shirt.
Okay.
All righty.
Okay. Uh...
Listen.
You need this.
Okay?
These are antibiotics.
You can see the label
right there.
Oh, forget it.
We gotta go.
It'll just take two seconds.
And your wounds are definitely
infected by this point.
Just let me do this.
Okay. Okay.
Come on.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let me see.
Okay.
Now you're gonna
drive us out of here.
Let's go.
Okay. All righty.
Aah!
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Just give it a second.
Give what a second?
How did you manage that?
I showed him the antibiotic,
but then with a little
sleight of hand, morphine.
Impressive.
My sister and I used to do
these little magic shows.
I'll bet they were amazing.
It was.
Should be good to go.
Am I under arrest?
Depends.
You got a permit?
Yeah.
Back at the house.
What are you doing here, Benny?
Are you asking as a cop
or as my sister?
I'm asking as a sister.
I'm listening as a cop.
I bought some stocks
on a margin.
The stocks went south.
Margin got called.
I didn't have it.
How much?
500 grand.
Hmm.
I sold everything
I could get my hands on.
I was still a hundred short.
So you went to a loan shark?
I know I screwed up.
I can fix it.
No.
You're gonna let us handle it.
What is this loan shark's name,
and where can we find him?
Anyone ever tell you
not to lend to a guy
whose sister is a cop?
Detectives.
I haven't done anything illegal.
Just a legitimate loan
to a guy who's down on his luck.
Well, your legitimate
collection agent
landed my mom in the hospital.
Emilia wasn't kidding
when she said
she got you with her purse.
You are under arrest
for assault,
with an enhancement
for elder abuse.
Don't mess with the Lopez women.
It doesn't end well.
The doctor said they got
the bullet fragment.
There's nothing to worry about.
That's great.
I never thought I'd be so happy
to feel pain in my life.
You okay?
No.
There's something
I have to tell you.
Ash...
I spent my whole life
worrying about my dad.
If he was late getting home,
Mom would pretend
everything was fine,
but I know she was terrified.
When I saw you wheeled
into surgery,
I realized...
I can't do that again.
Are... Are y-you
breaking up with me?
I'm sorry.
I just got out of surgery.
I know.
I thought I'd get it in
before the anesthesia wore off.
I... still love you.
I'll probably be in love with
you for longer than I'd like.
And if there was any chance
you were going to retire...
I know.
Can I get you anything?
No.
Okay.
I'll go, then.
So, now how do you feel
about hospitals?
I love them.
- Nah, today was great.
- You're good to go.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
You know, that, uh,
morphine move was very smart.
I would not have
thought of that.
Thank you.
Uh...
What is it?
Oh, you're gonna
think I'm crazy.
No, never.
It was my sister's idea.
Oh.
Mm.
As in you saw her or...?
No.
I can't really explain it.
I-I feel like she was with me.
It's weird.
Oh, well, I think that's
a... a lovely thought,
as long as there were no,
you know,
auditory hallucinations...
No.
I had to ask.
Oh.
Uh, Watch Commander's office.
Sergeant Grey is unavailable.
End of shift is denied and...
Hey, there you are.
I was just calling.
Hey.
So, how'd it go?
It was great.
It was...
I just spoke with
the Communications Supervisor.
Said you did a masterful job
managing calls
with half the normal staff.
Hmm.
Thank you.
I am so ready to give you
your job back.
Understood.
Good night, sir.
Good night.
Oh, uh, how was
Tim's laparoscopic?
Yeah. Um...
He ended up needing
emergency spinal surgery.
Are you okay?
Uh, why didn't anyone tell me?
No, I'm... I'm good.
I'm good.
Doctor said I'm gonna
make a full recovery.
And I told everyone
to keep you in the dark.
Why?
I didn't want you to worry.
So, just to be clear...
You thought you might
be paralyzed,
but you were worried about me?
You know what?
Slow your roll, Chen.
Clearly, I misspoke.
I was worried about the station.
And I knew you'd be
too concerned about me
to take over for Smitty.
Mm-hmm.
I heard you saved the day,
though.
Being sergeant's not so hard.
I don't know why
you're always complaining.
Really?
Just smooth sailing?
No. It was awful.
How do that many things
go wrong in one day?
That wasn't even
a particularly bad day.
Where's Ashley?
Yeah, I-I, uh...
I sent her home.
She was exhausted.
Okay. Hm.
What are you doing?
I'm keeping you company.
You don't have to do that.
I know.
Okay, okay.
- Oh, okay.
- Just open it.
- Sure. Okay.
- He's fine. He's fine.
Okay, so and then the door
opens, and Wesley walks in
to represent me.
All of us.
I thought Angela's head
was going to explode.
Good man, looking out for
your brothers-in-law.
Whoa.
Good man?
- Brave man.
- No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Not... Not so brave.
I knew that
she would understand.
Angela believes
in tough love, sure.
But no one is more protective
of the people she cares about.
Oh.
I have something to say.
Mom, you don't have to.
Yes, I do.
It's something I should have
said a long time ago to you.
I know you always thought
I didn't pay you
enough attention growing up,
that all my focus
went to your brothers.
I always denied it,
but you were right.
It's not because
I didn't love you as much.
You're my daughter,
my only daughter,
and I love you in a way
that is only for you.
But you didn't need me
as much as much.
Not the way they did.
Since you could crawl,
you took care of yourself.
And when you could walk,
you took care of your brothers,
even though they were
older than you.
And I relied on you.
I came to expect it.
But as strong as you were,
I should have realized that
you still needed your mother.
I love you, mija.
And I'm sorry.
To Angela.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- To Angela.
- Salud.
Salud.
Mom, I love you.
Thank you.
Are you still worried
I went back too soon?
No. Actually, you seemed
pretty amazing today.
I guess the only
question left is,
are you ever gonna fill me in
on the whole
"I was dead before" thing?
Well, there's not much to tell.
You already know about
the second time...
My oxygen regulator
malfunctioned on a halo jump.
Luckily, the other guys noticed,
pulled my ripcord,
and brought me back to life
on the ground.
That is so badass.
And the first time?
Two words... Big Foot.
See, I don't even know
why I bother.
'Cause you love me.
Fair enough.
You know, the first two times
I was brought back to life,
I was scared, but only a little.
And I moved on pretty quickly.
But this... this last time,
all I could think about
was losing you.
I've never been happier
or felt more seen or loved.
And the thought
of losing a second
of whatever time we have left
was heartbreaking.
So here's my question.
John Nolan...
will you marry me?
Try and stop me.
Captions by VITAC...