Oh, thank you for
coming out so quickly.
Celina: Not a problem.
You said you'd been
a victim of a robbery?
Yes.
Sorry.
I'm a little shaken.
Perfectly understandable.
I didn't think something
like this could happen.
Everything seemed so safe.
And, uh,
what all was stolen?
A poleax, a cloak of undying,
and my giraffe, Nexi.
I have to get her back.
It took two weeks of grinding
to save up for her egg.
Oh, don't look at me.
This is not my brand
of out there.
Um, sorry. I'm lost.
Uh, they broke
into your apartment...
Not this place.
My "Cloudmaster" mansion.
♪
In Shadow Realm.
Someone stole these items
from a VR world?
Not someone...
DragonSlayer6498.
♪
Here. You can question
him yourself.
Oh, the... Okay.
♪
[Laughs] Wow.
No, no, no.
No. Nope. Nope.
Can't see.
[Screaming]
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Now, every week,
a new real estate agent
wants to list the house.
I really should consider
selling mine.
Tim and Genny made a fortune
selling their dad's place, right?
Yeah, they sure did.
But you still
have tenants in yours.
[Sighs]
And they're great.
This sweet older couple that
have been together for 50 years.
It's very inspirational.
And what do you charge
for rent?
$3,000 a month.
And your mortgage is $2,000.
That is great passive income.
[Dog barks in distance]
Right?
Theoretically.
They don't always
pay their rent on time.
Late a few days?
More like a few months.
Bailey, how... how long has it
been since they paid rent?
Did I mention that they were
high-school sweethearts?
Six months.
They haven't paid their rent in
six months. I'll talk to them.
Now, I think maybe
I better handle it.
We all know that old people
are your kryptonite.
My grandmother raised me.
And she did a lovely job.
[Groans]
[Exhales sharply]
♪
Solving crimes
one meme at a time?
Uh, balancing the awfulness
of humanity
with a little baby time.
Leah's huge.
When did that happen?
I know. She's gonna be
crawling any minute now.
Hmm. Unlike Angela,
who skipped right to walking.
Damian,
what are you doing here?
I need a favor.
If this is about baptizing Jack,
can you just...
Oh, I already handled that.
What?
Yeah.
Last time I was over
for dinner,
I brought a little holy water and...
Is that kosher?
Different religion.
♪
Oh, you mean if it's cool?
Uh, yes.
Technically, I have a license
to baptize anytime, anywhere.
Without even asking?
You'll thank me later.
I'm here
about one of the gang members
I've been counseling,
Mateo Ramirez.
He was about to renounce the
life, and then he disappeared.
His family hasn't heard a word,
and I'm worried.
Who does he run with?
Quinlan Wright's crew.
We know Quinlan.
He's been coming up fast
with a young crew.
Yeah.
He's been making big moves,
scooping up
Elijah's territory.
So you'll look for Mateo?
He's a good kid,
deserves a fresh start.
Sure.
Text me his cell number,
and we can start tracking him
where it was last pinged.
Thank you.
Those kids are lucky
to have you.
But next time you come
to my house,
I'm gonna search you
for communion wafers.
[Footsteps approaching]
Hey.
Nolan: Hey.
What was wrong
with the old coffee machine?
Ooh. Lead levels, for one.
Mice infestation, for two. Here.
Thank you very much.
Here, let me do it.
See? It's easy.
That is easy.
Yeah. I watched
a ClipTalk tutorial.
So, what'd you guys get up to
last night?
Nothing.
I went to
the new Chagall exhibit.
Oh, yes.
Bailey wants to check that out.
You should
totally take her.
You get such a great sense
for the evolution of his style.
It's good.
We will. Okay.
Thank you
for the rec and the bar.
Yeah.
See ya.
[Footsteps departing]
"Nothing?" You had all morning
to come up with a cover story,
and that's
what you went with?
Whoa, whoa.
He bought it, didn't he?
Mm.
What if he had asked you
a follow-up question
about the exhibit?
Let him. I read the catalog for
the exhibit cover to cover.
Mm-hmm.
[Breathes sharply]
I hear you have
Citizen's Academy today.
I do.
Do you have any tips?
Yeah. Uh, look, you're gonna get
a lot of busybodies
who are way
into their neighborhood watch.
But the ones you have to be most
careful with... screenwriters.
Mm.
Do not give them
your business card.
You'll be up to your eyeballs
in scripts.
Okay. Thank you. Yeah.
So, um,
what are you doing tonight?
"Nothing"... I hope.
Nothing sounds perfect.
♪
Hello.
- Good morning.
Welcome
to Citizen's Academy.
Uh, I'm Officer Lucy Chen,
and I will be
your instructor today.
So, as you know,
this is an outreach program
where you learn a little bit
about the LAPD
and how we do things here.
And one of the first things
we always do
is run background checks
on everybody who signs up.
So, Chris Pike, Jack Harris,
you have prior
felony convictions
for robbery and assault,
so that will disqualify you
from learning
how we do business here.
Officer Simmons
will show you out.
Thank you.
And, Janet White...
Not only do you have
a record,
but you have an outstanding
warrant for your arrest.
Finn will happily escort you
to processing.
Right this way.
You can tell me
why stealing a fire truck
seemed like a great idea.
Okay.
So now that that's out
of the way, let's get started.
Yes?
We're allowed to use whatever
happens here in our scripts,
right?
As long as we change
the names?
♪
Mm-hmm.
Hey, so, I have some ideas on
how I think we can increase
the LAPD's social media presence.
Think I should run them
by Grey?
Absolutely.
[Police radio chatter]
Are you just saying that so you
can watch him shoot me down?
[Ringtone plays]
Genny? What's up?
Genny: I'm at Tyler's
baseball practice.
Spellman Field.
[Indistinct shouting]
Things are getting really ugly
between one of the parents
and the coach.
Woman: No!
Woman ♪2:
Why can't you just...
On our way.
How is he supposed to show you
what he can do
when he is stuck
in the outfield?!
I know what he can do.
I want Cody on that pitcher's
mound immediately
or I'm having you fired!
You do know I'm coaching
the kids for free, right?
Then we're paying you
what you're worth.
Okay, guys, maybe we could
discuss this in private.
What's the problem?
[Laughs]
Oh, this... this idiot wants
to put my kid on the outfield!
He's a pitcher!
No, he's not.
Blake is the only one
with any actual pitching skill.
Uh, I don't have to pitch, Coach.
Really, I-I like the bench.
See? Bench him.
You want to know why your son's
in the outfield, Celeste?
Because he's terrible!
He is the worst player
I've ever coached.
[Shouts]
Tim: Okay, ma'am,
now you're going to jail.
What? No, I...
Woman: Oh, my God,
what just happened?
But, uh, he's a pitcher.
Sir, are you okay?
No.
I quit.
Does this mean
practice is canceled?
He's our third coach.
Might mean
the season's canceled.
Hang on. What about...
What about Tim?
♪
Nothing.
No, it's a great idea.
♪
You love baseball,
and you wanted to be
more involved
in Tyler's life.
Please, Uncle Tim.
We'll have the best time.
I promise.
♪
It's an important distinction.
A robbery
is when you take something
through the use
of force or fear,
and a burglary is when
you break into a structure
to commit a crime.
Yeah?
What's a B?
The... [Chuckles]
That is a TV term.
Under California statutes,
it's not a thing,
so don't use it.
[Laughs]
Yeah?
What happens when you call the
police about domestic violence?
Well, great question.
A domestic violence call
is a mandatory arrest.
If we're called to a home,
somebody is
going away in handcuffs.
The days of cops looking
the other way are long gone.
But, like,
what happens to the victim,
you know, if they don't have
a place to stay?
Um, there are amazing shelters
in the city.
It's a scary situation,
um, and it might seem like
there's no place to go,
but I promise,
everyone has options.
I mean, I was just curious.
Yeah, no.
Of... Of course.
Nolan: Six months
is a long time to go
without paying rent,
but times are hard.
I can understand Bailey's
reluctance to force the issue.
[Police radio chatter]
Permission to speak freely, sir?
Proceed.
You and Bailey are too nice
to be in the L.A. landlord game.
[Dog barking in distance]
You think they're
taking advantage of us?
Oh, I-I know they are.
Look, my cousin,
he let a tenant stay so long,
he changed the locks and took
advantage of the squatter laws
to all but steal the house.
To be a landlord
in this town,
I mean, you got to be willing
to cut a bitch...
Well, figuratively speaking, sir.
Got it... so less Mr. Nice Guy,
more stone cold killer.
Mm-hmm.
Good morning.
Oh, hello, Officers.
How can I help you?
Bailey Nune is my fiancée
and also your landlord.
She mentioned you might be
a little behind on rent.
Six months late, in fact.
Malcolm, can you come here?
He's here about the rent.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Officer.
We've been struggling
a little recently.
But... But we have the money.
I-It's just tied up.
But it shouldn't be much longer.
I understand. I get it.
I've been where you are.
But Bailey has given you
lots of time to resolve this.
I agree completely.
I will hand-deliver
the rent on Wednesday.
But I-I will have to take
a couple hundred off.
We've had a few
maintenance issues.
Oh, did you bring those up
with Bailey?
Oh, no, no. We...
We didn't want to trouble her.
I am also a contractor.
If anything else comes up,
you just shoot them over to me,
and I'll be here Wednesday
for the back rent.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
You bet.
♪
I'm not gonna see them
Wednesday, am I?
I'm telling you, just sign over
the lease now.
Harper:
7-Adam-15, 2331,
we're working a missing person,
Mateo Ramirez.
His cellphone last pinged
at the old Florence Kitchen.
You free to meet us there?
Can do.
[Beeps]
[Suspenseful music plays]
♪
I don't like this.
Something bad happened.
The unfortunate effects
of supply chain issues?
No. No, this is as close
as I've ever felt to evil...
♪
Find anything?
True evil.
Huh?
The place does give off
a certain vibe.
♪
And this is weird.
What?
This is fresh plasterboard.
Why fix a wall in a place
destined for a wrecking ball?
I'm gonna call Mateo's cell,
see if we can hear anything.
[Beeps]
[Line ringing]
[Muffled ringtone plays]
[Suspenseful music plays]
[Ringtone continues playing]
♪
[Pipe clatters]
Careful.
[Ringtone continues playing]
♪
[Nolan grunts]
Ohh.
Ugh.
[Ringtone continues playing]
[Metal clatters]
♪
[Coughing]
[Ringtone continues playing]
♪
Nolan: You need a minute?
No, sir.
You ever seen anything
like this before?
Not exactly like this,
but I have seen plenty of things
I wish I could unsee.
I mean, I've known how brutal
the world can be
since I was a kid,
but, I mean, it's still shocking
when you come face to face
with it.
And yet it's when
it stops being shocking
that you really need
to worry.
Yeah. [Sighs]
Alright. What can I do?
TID's on the way
to process the scene.
Why don't you go outside,
wait for them,
and show them the way in?
♪
So, we thinking cartel?
Or cartel-inspired.
Mateo was affiliated.
He ran with
Quinlan Wright's crew.
I'd bet money the rest
of these guys did, too.
Yeah. We'll know for sure
once we I.D. them.
Celina okay?
Yeah. She will be.
I'm not sure if it helps
or if it hurts that she sees
this as...
Evil incarnate?
Yeah.
You believe in that?
A hundred percent.
Uh, do I believe
in the embedding
of a metaphysical force
within the body
that turns people
into monsters?
No comment.
But I know for a fact that
this is only gonna get worse.
If this really
is Quinlan's guys,
then this is likely
the beginning of a gang war.
With who?
Moses Warden.
That's my pick.
They've been fighting over
Elijah's territory for months.
Well, maybe we pay both
these guys a visit,
impress upon them
how bad it would be
if they were to
take it any farther.
It's worth a try.
A shot across the bow
is not gonna stop them,
but it might slow them down
long enough
for us to put bracelets
on the monsters who did this.
[Sighs]
[Sirens wailing]
[Telephones ringing,
indistinct conversations]
You avoiding the pastries.
I don't blame you.
They look sad.
[Sighs]
I need to watch my figure.
My boyfriend hates women
who let themselves go.
Oh, well, what does it matter
what he thinks? It's your body.
He's helping me.
You know, I need the motivation
to be the best I can be.
Oh, and if you slip up?
What does he do then?
Uh...
He's cool about it.
It's my body.
You know, like you said.
You know, sometimes
controlling behavior...
it... it can be, like,
a red flag.
[Chuckles]
Um, t-that's not...
uh, he's just looking out
for me.
I-I shouldn't have said anything.
The bathroom's
that way, right?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Okay.
[Soft music plays]
♪
[Keys clacking]
[Beeps]
You'll never guess
who's coaching Little League.
Nolan?
No. Sergeant Friendly.
What? How did that happen?
Can I watch?
Guys, it's not that big
of a deal, alright?
Uh, Tyler's coach quit,
so I'm just gonna sub
until they find a replacement.
Hmm.
What's this?
Uh, so, one of the "students"...
Kyra Cook.
Um, her boyfriend, Oliver,
is recently divorced,
and his ex has
a restraining order against him
for domestic violence.
Hmm. Do you think
he's abusing Kyra?
Yeah, I do.
I mean, I'm not...
I'm not sure
how I can help, though.
Well, if she won't admit
it's happening,
what can you do?
She came to Citizen's Academy
for a reason.
Maybe... Maybe she wants help,
but she's still too afraid.
I think I just need
to find a way
to make her feel comfortable
enough to ask for it.
♪
Bailey's tenants
sent over a list of things
they say need repairing.
It numbers in the hundreds.
Replace the spa jets?
She doesn't even
have a hot tub.
[Police radio chatter]
You still struggling?
No.
Well, a little.
I know. I-I need to get over it.
I'm a cop.
I'm going to see
messed-up things.
True. It doesn't mean
you have to act like
it doesn't have an impact
on you.
I mean,
Harper didn't blink.
Harper has seen things
that would give
Freddy Krueger nightmares.
[Sighs]
Alright. So who's this guy
we're going to jam up?
Quinlan Wright.
Got his start working corners.
Graduated to trafficking.
Spent two years in Pelican Bay
and got out just in time
for Elijah's fall.
Okay, how do you keep
all these players straight?
I mean, it seems like
they're rising
and falling
every five minutes.
Takes work. Uh, CIs on the
street, regular check-ins
with the different desks...
detectives, narco, gangs.
I was planning on waiting
till you had a few more months
under your belt
to do that deep dive.
Oh, I'm ready now.
The more I know,
the less surprised I'll be.
[Laughs]
Ah, if only that were true.
♪ We don't ever stop,
we don't ever drop ♪
♪ We keep rollin',
I know that you better rock ♪
♪ We the veterans, yup,
you in steady shock ♪
♪ We just better men
Man: I got nothing.
♪ We number one
while you settle for two ♪
♪ Better review, way overdue
♪ If they can have us,
they won't settle for you ♪
♪ We in go mode,
back down by the post ♪
♪ Like my lone gun stunned
kinda loco ♪
Help you?
We're here
to see Quinlan.
Not here.
[Indistinct conversations]
Get 'em.
Unstoppable, baby!
Nolan: Thanks.
Stop playing with me, man.
Get off the court.
And yet I'm looking
right at him.
♪ Goin', goin', yeah,
we in go mode ♪
Officers, man, we in the middle
of a game here.
Look like you guys
could use a breather.
♪ Goin' slow-mo
I can go all day...
And all night.
Hmm. Then you should, uh, cut
back on the little blue pills.
You funny.
What y'all doing here, man?
Here to offer
our condolences.
Four of your crew
were found dead today.
Yeah, I heard.
♪ Got the pedal all the way
to the floor ♪
♪ And I'm ready to go now
They was good boys, too.
We're doing what we can
for the families.
And plotting revenge
against the ones who did it?
Look, if you got a name,
I'm all ears.
Here.
You know the name.
Hi, there.
We're here to talk to Moses.
And don't say he's not here,
because we watched him
pull in a few minutes ago.
[Dog barking in distance]
You moved up in the world, Moses.
I know you?
I hooked you up a couple times
when I was working patrol.
Oh, yeah.
Didn't recognize you
without the lady cop bun.
Congratulations
on the promotion.
You look good
out of uniform.
Oh, I know.
We're here about the bodies
that you dropped
in Mid-Wilshire.
Walled them up,
hoping we wouldn't find them.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Come on.
Everyone in town knows
you and Quinlan
are fighting for territory.
Trust me, if I was gonna
make a move on Quinlan,
I wouldn't make it
a mystery.
I'd string his guys up
so everyone would see.
Look, I don't want this
getting out of hand
any more than y'all do, alright?
I'm not thinking about
retaliating against Moses.
[Laughs]
♪
You've already set something
in motion.
[Radio beeps]
Harper, Lopez, heads up.
You got trouble
headed your way.
[Gunfire, glass shattering]
♪
[Gunfire stops]
[Tires screeching]
♪
I hope you've enjoyed
this little taste
of police work today.
I know I've enjoyed
sharing with you. So thank you.
Your questions
were very eye-opening.
Have a nice day.
[Indistinct conversations]
Yeah.
Kyra,
could you stay a minute?
[Indistinct conversations]
[Clears throat]
I was just thinking
about your question,
"Where do domestic
violence victims go
when they don't have
anyone to stay with?"
I was just curious.
Of course. I, um...
I would just kick myself
if I didn't...
If you're scared
to go home,
I could get you a place
in the shelter tonight.
No one would ever need
to find out where you are.
What would happen to him?
Would you arrest him?
Depends what you tell me.
Does he hit you?
No. He would never do that.
He just
loses his temper...
you know, punches walls,
stuff like that.
Yeah. I can only imagine.
That's really scary.
You know, that kind of violence,
it can escalate really quickly.
So just be honest
with yourself.
Do you feel safe with him?
Not always.
Why don't we get you
a bed for tonight?
Maybe a little bit of time
away would be good.
[Breathes deeply]
Okay.
Thank you.
You guys okay?
Yeah.
Moses's shop
has seen better days.
Where's he?
Slipped out the back
as soon as the shooting started.
You know he's gonna go back
at Quinlan twice as hard.
Be sure to brief the midnight
shift and the gang desk.
This war's
gonna keep escalating
until they
take each other out.
[Hip-hop music plays]
♪ Gimme, gimme,
give it good and plenty ♪
♪ If you want it from me, then
it's gonna cost a nice penny ♪
♪ Like good times,
I'm sweet lemmy ♪
♪ 'Cause if I ain't got it,
then, baby, it ain't any ♪
♪ Grand Puba,
you know how I get it lit ♪
♪ I get a lot of money just for
talkin' a lot of... ♪
♪ Girls go crazy 'cause
they lovin' how I spit ♪
♪ And you ain't got to worry
'cause you know... ♪
♪ Iconic, smooth as Delfonic
Woman: Get up!
Everybody, bring it in.
♪ So back up
Let's go. Hustle, hustle.
Guys, nice work.
There's room for improvement,
but I'm seeing
a lot of heart out there, okay?
Uh, Blake,
let's see you pitch.
Alright. Let's go back out.
Back to drills.
Hi. Um, who are you?
What?
I...
The... "A lot of heart"?
They're kind of a mess.
They're kids.
It's supposed to be fun.
Yeah.
This is weird, right?
[Chuckles] Our dad coached
Tim's a little league team
for all of three days.
He has literal scars.
[Children shouting]
He's trying not
to be like him.
Yeah.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
Well, I mean,
there is such a thing
as over-correcting.
Hey, guys.
Bring it in. Huddle up.
What are you doing?
You know,
kids need to have fun,
but they also need
a little bit of structure.
Hey, hustle up. Okay.
Uh, my name is Lucy.
I am Coach Bradford's friend,
and we're gonna start with
the basics... throwing the ball.
So, first things first,
make sure the ball
is secure in your mitt.
Eyes on the target.
Step out with the opposite leg
from your throwing arm.
Follow through.
Ball lands back in the mitt.
And we'll cycle through that, okay?
We're not gonna move on
until everybody gets it.
So spread out.
Let's give it a try.
You heard her.
♪
Oh. Oh.
[Brakes squeal]
[Engine shuts off,
gearshift clicks]
[Dog barking in distance]
Alright. Are you ready to get
tough about the back rent?
Oh, big time.
[Hip-hop music plays]
Why are there so many lights on, though?
♪
I don't know.
Weird.
♪
You here for the shoot?
What shoot?
Where's Maeve and Malcolm?
♪
Nolan:
I don't think they're here.
♪
Are they filming a porno?
On my furniture?
I prefer the term
"adult film."
How much are they charging you
to film here?
$1,500 a shoot,
four shoots a week.
$1,500... That's...
Six thousand dollars.
A week.
I'm... I'm gonna kill them.
[Indistinct rap music plays]
I think you two should co-coach.
You were great together.
Oh, no, no. I'm... I'm ready to
hand over the reins entirely.
Not a chance.
No, but seriously.
I saw today why you work
so well together.
I-I... It's just, uh...
We spend so much time together
on... out on the job.
Mm-hmm.
It's so great that Tyler
has been making friends
so quickly after moving here.
Yeah. I mean,
Blake's mom works crazy hours,
so he practically lives
at our house. Mm.
Hey, guys? We're about done.
Let's wrap it up.
[Baseball bats clatter]
[Children shouting]
My mom just texted,
my dad's
coming to the game tomorrow.
Oh, that's great.
We'll make sure he gets
the best seat
in the house.
Here, honey.
[Dog barking in distance]
What's up?
Blake's dad ran out on them
a year ago.
Oh. Do you know why?
Outstanding warrants for assault
and attempted murder.
[Suspenseful music plays]
If he shows up tomorrow, we're
gonna have to arrest him.
Blake will be devastated.
Well, maybe we'll get lucky
and he'll flake
on his son again.
[Cellphone rings]
Yeah, here's hoping.
Excuse me. Hello.
Sherice: Officer Chen,
it's Sherice from the shelter.
The woman you sent over...
Kyra... she's a problem.
What's going on?
She kept asking if her friend
Linda was here,
and when I told her it was
illegal for me
to disclose anything about the
people who stay in my shelter,
she asked to be moved.
Yeah, I think I know
what's going on.
Uh, I'm sorry about that.
I-I'll head over right away.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
There's something going on
with my domestic.
You want me to come?
No, it's okay.
I got it.
[Horns honking, siren wailing]
You're leaving?
[Car door closes]
A friend says
that I can stay with her.
Kyra, you don't have
to lie to me.
You're going back
to Oliver.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You asked about Linda, right?
[Scoffs]
I know that your boyfriend's
ex-wife is named Linda.
You're crazy.
Did he tell you to ask
for her and the kids?
She stole his kids
and pumped them full of lies.
He just wants to explain.
Kyra, we know that he has
been beating her for years.
You don't understand.
No, I do.
I think he's using you.
And maybe you were
telling the truth earlier
that he doesn't hit you,
but statistics say
that he will, okay?
So you need
to get out of that house.
I'm done talking.
Wait. [Stammers]
Look, take my card, okay?
You can call me.
Take it.
[Engine revving]
[Tires screech]
Kyra, get in.
[Hard rock music plays]
You don't have to go
with him.
[Car door opens]
You don't.
♪
Yeah, she does.
Get in the damn car.
Oliver, you need to wait.
Kyra and I
are still talking.
♪
I've got nothing more
to say to you.
♪
[Car door closes]
You have yourself
a nice night.
♪
[Car door closes]
[Engine revving]
[Dog barking in distance]
There's nothing you can do
until she files a police report.
She's not gonna do that.
She's under his spell...
which is baffling to me,
even though I understand
the psychology behind it.
Listen, I-I had this...
this case early on,
and the woman would call us,
we'd arrest her husband,
she'd change the story.
The details made no sense.
D.A. couldn't prosecute,
and she'd go stay at a shelter
for a while,
and then she'd go back
to him.
I just...
I could never make sense of it.
What happened to her?
He killed her.
And afterwards, the, uh,
doctors showed us a C.T. scan,
and there was so much damage,
you would think she was
a professional boxer.
Oh, God.
No wonder her story
changed so much.
These cases
are frustrating and hard.
All you can do
is keep circling back.
And she may never
be ready to leave,
but it's important she knows
that we'll be there when she is.
Thank you.
Hey. Sorry to interrupt.
Did you get my e-mail
about the deadbeat tenants?
[Sighs]
I did.
Bailey is renting to
these nightmare septuagenarians
who have a history
of torturing landlords.
They grew toxic mold
in their last rental
to avoid paying rent.
Which means you need
to start playing hardball.
Oh, listen,
I can do that.
Mm. I have my doubts.
Look, it's just that
him and Bailey
are just way too nice
to be landlords.
Totally.
O-O-Okay, hold on.
You are a complete badass
out on the streets,
but off-hours...
I mean, you're a little...
Easy target.
A push over.
Hmm. Alright. The good news
is they haven't paid rent,
so you can start
the eviction process today.
Based on their history, they'll
probably take it to court.
Because of the backups, it'll
take a while to get a date.
Uh, if you're lucky, you'll be
rid of them in three months.
Three...
[Sighs]
So meanwhile,
I'll be out legal fees,
and they'll pocket $18,000
renting out the place
to make "adult films."
Wonderful.
Okay, wait...
they're doing a porn set?
You didn't tell me that.
I was afraid you would find
a way
to make it my fault.
No, no. Regardless,
that is what's gonna save you.
Yeah, he's right.
The lease terms
specifically prohibit that.
Makes the case
more clean cut.
Great. Just you wait and see how
much of a pushover I can be.
♪
I-Is it too late
to call in sick?
No sick days for rookies.
♪
Taking Elijah off the board
gave us brief peace.
Now there's blood
in the streets.
Moses has been around
for a long time.
He even has legitimate
businesses as fronts.
He's smart and measured
until he's pushed into a corner.
And Quinlan is young and wild
and not trying to wait his turn.
Did the night shift
hear anything
about Moses hitting back?
No. Not a peep, which somehow
makes me more nervous.
At least that means
there's no new bodies.
Or none
that we've found yet.
I'm not religious per se,
but there's a lot
I'd like to get off
my chest.
The confessional's
really just for Catholics.
Uh, totally get it.
Uh, maybe we could talk
on your way out.
Mnh-mnh.
Or not.
[Clears throat]
♪
I have a lead.
[Sighs]
A kid in my congregation...
one of Mateo's friends...
he came to me this morning and
asked me to tell you something.
When you say "friend," you mean
they used to bang together?
Yeah.
He told me Moses's crew
is transporting
a big shipment
of drugs today,
hidden in merchandise
for his auto shop.
Wait, I thought you said your
informant is in Quinlan's gang.
He is.
[Suspenseful music plays]
What?
There's just...
There's no way
a street-level kid
would know something like that,
especially about
a rival gang.
Unless someone
wanted him to know.
Quinlan sent him
to tell you.
He wants the LAPD
to do his dirty work for him.
I'm... I'm not following.
He tips us off
so we take Moses off the board.
Quinlan wins the war without
losing any more of his guys.
So you're not gonna act
on the tip?
Oh, no.
We definitely are.
Doesn't matter
if Quinlan's trying to play us.
Any chance we have to put Moses
behind bars,
we're gonna take it.
♪
[Ringtone plays]
Hello.
Where the hell
did you go, huh?!
[Objects crashing]
Lucy?
Where the hell did you go?!
Kyra, are you okay?
He's really mad.
I told you to find her!
He says that it's my fault that
he can't see his kids.
It's gonna be worse for you
...if I have to find her!
Yeah, okay.
What I'm gonna need you
to do right now, Kyra,
is get into
a public place, okay?
[Dramatic music plays]
Who the hell
are you talking to?
Nobody.
I'm sorry. [Screams]
Kyra?
[Beeps]
Control,
I have a possible 2-73-5
at 9213 Longview Avenue.
Send additional units.
[Beeps]
[Siren wailing]
♪
[Siren stops]
[Gearshift clicks]
♪
LAPD! I'm coming in!
[Doorknob rattles]
[Door crashes]
Hey! Get off her.
Hands where I can
see them.
♪
Back up.
[Groans]
Make me.
You really want to add
assaulting a police officer
to your charge?
In for a penny.
♪
Oh!
[Both grunting]
♪
[Shouts]
[Both straining]
♪
[Grunts]
[Groans]
Put your hands
behind your back.
[Handcuffs click]
[Gun cocks]
♪
Kyra, put the gun down.
[Voice breaking]
He's not a bad guy.
He just
gets mad sometimes.
He was about to kill you.
No. I overreacted.
I shouldn't have called.
No, you made the right decision.
You are in danger here.
They took his kids.
He is the reason
he lost them.
No! His wife... she...
No, no, no, no.
I know what he said to you,
Kyra, and that's a lie.
♪
You don't understand.
Okay.
♪
None of that matters.
What matters right now is
the choice that you are making.
Okay? If you shoot me,
you're not gonna save him,
but you will go away
to prison forever, okay?
Just... put the gun down.
[Breathes sharply]
♪
Kyra...
you have the power
right now to save me, okay?
Just put the gun down.
♪
It's okay.
[Siren wailing]
[Gun clatters]
[Sobs]
Turn around.
[Handcuffs click]
[Sobbing]
♪
[Train whistle blows]
Lopez:
According to our source,
Moses's truck should be
pulling in any minute.
Copy that.
Can I ask you a question
while we wait?
Go for it.
What's your take
on true evil?
Does it exist?
Evil as in the devil
or guys with broken brains
who get off on torture?
The first one.
Look, I think looking for
some mythical creature to blame
for all the messed up stuff
human beings do is a cop out.
I disagree.
I mean, yeah, there are some
depraved people in the world,
but you can't say
that you haven't seen people act
in a way
that you can't explain.
[Suspenseful music plays]
♪
That's it... green cab.
Standby for the hand-off.
[Brakes squeal]
♪
And there it is.
Move in.
♪
Police!
Show me your hands!
Now!
♪
Face the truck.
You good?
Yeah.
♪
[Handcuffs clicking]
[Creaking]
♪
Turn around.
[Flashlight clicks]
♪
Score.
Drugs confirmed inside.
Congratulations.
You're both under arrest.
Any idea how much weight
they're transporting?
Not yet, but even if a quarter
of these boxes are loaded,
we're talking tonnage.
It's weird how your worst day
is suddenly our best.
What would make it better for
both of us...
if you rolled over on Moses.
[Tires screeching]
♪ F-Feed 'em all their meds
♪ Till they forget
what the drugs cost ♪
♪ People never question what
you're selling them guns for ♪
♪ Beat 'em in the head
with the message ♪
♪ With the blunt force
[Gunfire]
Gun!
Get down!
Go, go, go, go, go!
♪ Let 'em suck on your exhaust
till the sun's gone ♪
♪ Make 'em bleed from it
while they dream of it ♪
Shots fired. Three men
armed with submachine guns,
shooting from the south east.
Need backup, Code-3...
♪ When all else fails,
start a war up ♪
Moses must have sent
a follow car.
Those aren't Moses's guys.
I recognize the big one
from Quinlan's crew.
Why would Quinlan tip us off
only to send a hit team?
♪ 'Cause if it ain't dead...
Cover me.
♪ Bleed your customer,
get yourself free ♪
You guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
Although I'm wishing
I had the long gun right now.
[Gunshots]
Do you wanna play offense
of defense?
What do you think?
Alright, you cover fire.
We'll advance on the vehicle.
[Gunfire]
♪ Tell him to buy a pet,
help him to buy a house ♪
♪ Chain him to a fence and
get your pound of flesh out ♪
♪ Sell nicotine, caffeine,
energy drinks ♪
[Glass shatters,
tires screech]
♪ They'll work till they forget
to breathe, dream, or think ♪
♪ Or worship celebrity...
[Glass shatters]
Get your guns outside
the vehicle.
Hands behind your back.
Let's go. Drop them!
Out of the car.
Step out of the car.
Go. Out.
Turn around.
Hands against the car.
[Gun clatters]
We're code-4.
We need R.A.s
for five G.S.W. victims.
I think we need to have a talk
with our informant.
I was just thinking
the same thing.
[Sighs]
My brother says you told him
about the drug shipment.
What we need to know
is who told you.
It's alright, Ricky.
You can tell her.
It was Quinlan.
Mm, no.
See, you wanted us to think
it was coming from Quinlan.
But why would your boss
ask the LAPD
to intercept his rival's
drug shipment
and then send
his own guys in?
He had to know
they'd get arrested.
I think someone else asked you
to tip us off.
Someone who would benefit
from both Quinlan and Moses
being taken down.
We just need you
to tell us who that is.
I can't.
He'll kill me.
Who?
♪
Listen to me.
I know you're scared.
We can protect you,
but only if you help us.
Angela's telling the truth.
You know she's my sister, right?
If she says she has your back,
she's got it.
♪
Ricky: He paid me $5,000
to tell you about the shipment.
Lopez: Who paid you?
Elijah Stone.
[Distorted gunfire]
♪
Moses didn't kill
Quinlan's guys.
Elijah did,
to provoke a war.
He had Moses and Quinlan
soften each other up,
then he sent us in
for the kill.
Not that we can prove
any of it.
All we have is
Ricky's testimony.
Which Elijah will claim
that he tipped off the police
about an illegal activity,
like any upstanding citizen would.
After everything we went through
to take him down,
less than a year later,
he's right back
where he started.
I have to tell Wesley before
he finds out some other way.
[Soft music plays]
Angela can't be anywhere
near this investigation.
Neither of them can.
I know.
She won't like it,
but Elijah's seven steps ahead.
One wrong move,
he'll have her badge.
♪
Come on, hit it!
[All cheering]
God! Every time!
Be encouraging.
Yes. Good. Good job.
Good try.
We're gonna work on that.
Blake, you're up, bud.
Alright, you've got this.
Eye on the ball.
Let's go, let's go.
[Clapping]
Good job, buddy.
Whoo! [Clapping]
He looks scared.
You make him nervous.
I'm nervous, huh?
You're making him nervous.
[Sighs]
Blake, you got this, bud.
♪ I didn't realize
♪ You were cheering me on
[Cheers and applause]
Yeah! Whoo!
Go, Blake!
All the way!
Take second!
Yes!
Yeah!
That's how you do it!
Great job!
♪ Who didn't learn how to feel
♪ I'm just the Bad News Bears
♪ You want me to win
Is that your kid?
Oh, yeah.
♪
You're doing this now?
Calm down.
No one wants Blake to see you
taken off in cuffs.
Don't do anything stupid, and
we can all just enjoy the game.
Okay?
♪ But I had to drive
all the way out here ♪
Okay.
♪ Way out here
♪ Just to figure out
how to cry ♪
Maeve?
Malcolm?
I'll just post
the eviction notice.
Uh, I don't think
we need it.
♪
They took everything,
e-even the doorknobs.
♪ I'm just a kid
who didn't learn how to feel ♪
They left my bed.
Of course they did.
Well, at least
you got them out.
I feel so stupid.
How could I fall for this?
After Jason,
you'd think I'd learn.
Listen. After everything
you've been through,
you still have it within you
to trust people.
I find that admirable.
♪ I didn't know
I was the one to root for ♪
I mean, yeah, sure,
you could pull it back a smidge.
So, what now?
Do we put out an APB?
Tempting.
But given their track record,
I would think they're halfway
to another state by now.
Now, let's just focus
on finding some new tenants
and do the mother of all
background checks.
No. I'm ready to sell.
Really?
Yeah.
This is my old life.
You and your place...
it's my future.
♪
And we're gonna have to do
some work on this place,
though, before we sell.
"We"?
I-I mean, I'll help,
but I'm not a contractor.
No. You're more
of a supervisor. Mm.
Gotta play to my strengths.
Mm-hmm.
- Captions by VITAC...
♪