♪ Get up,
we're getting ready to roll ♪
What about Kilimanjaro
for the honeymoon?
You mean like to climb?
It's more of
a strenuous hike.
Is there a beach
at the top?
Ooh, I don't want to lie,
but I do want you to say yes.
Celina: Morning!
Morning.
I made you coffee, and
I found your special milk.
Thank you. No.
No, no more special milk.
No more extra pillows.
Hotel Nolan
is officially closed.
Two nights
is more than enough.
I know. I'm back in my place
tonight, I swear.
Uh, my new mattress
and white-noise machine
arrived today.
I wish I had that machine
last night.
That sound
was driving me crazy.
I didn't notice anything.
I did.
Every time I thought
it was going to stop,
it just ramped
back up again.
Was I snoring?
No. It was much softer
than that.
Like scratching.
Oh, probably a raccoon.
I'll check the crawl space
when I come home.
What do you know about
the history of your house?
I know what year
it was built.
No, I mean, like,
has anyone died here?
My house is not haunted.
You don't know that.
The only unwanted entity
in this house,
I'm looking at right now.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
Bah-bah-bah. Ohh.
[Imitates explosion]
Any chance you're gonna
make it to the pediatrician
appointment today?
I mean, if everyone just
confesses to their crimes,
sure, but I doubt it.
Well, the thing is
Jack is due for
his vaccinations today.
And you're usually there
to soothe him.
He'll be fine. Just give him
Tylenol and cuddles.
I know. I just don't want him
to feel betrayed.
Like I took him to this place
he got jabbed by needles.
Better he feels
I betrayed him?
Y-Yeah.
[Chuckles]
I can see who's gonna be
the disciplinarian.
I got to go.
Bye, honey!
[Children's music playing]
[Both laughing]
So, uh, I've been thinking.
Things are good between us.
Yeah.
You know, we've been
through a lot,
and we've come
through it stronger.
I agree.
[Chuckles]
So, uh, maybe it's time
to move in together.
[Chuckles] Maybe. Sure.
I mean, your place
is kind of small, though.
I-I know, but with
my new promotion,
I could maybe afford a cardboard
box deep in the Valley.
Wait. You want
to buy a house?
Yeah. That's what
grownups do, right?
And I know you won't go anywhere
without Tamara.
So what if we got a place
with a converted garage?
I'll have to
think about it.
Great.
Let's talk tonight.
I'll start looking
at listings.
So, I think I've proven myself,
you know,
with my contributions to cases,
and, you know,
I-I know I'm young,
but I really think that I could
really help out around...
Hey, sir, I was wondering
if I could have a minute.
You got 20 seconds. Go.
Okay. So you remember
the diamond case, right?
It was my...
my first case.
Look, you're not gonna get
to the point at this rate.
Okay.
I want to be a detective,
and I will do anything
to make that happen.
Is that it?
Yes.
Alright.
Shadow Harper
and Lopez today.
- Hey, Tim.
- Yeah?
I'm reassigning Aaron
for today.
Lucy, that means
you're back on gopher duty.
Okay.
[Clears throat]
I could handle
one day alone.
Is there some reason
you two can't ride together?
♪
Of course not.
No, sir.
Good.
Sorry.
Um...
I'll go get the gear. Okay.
Officer Thorsen
reporting for duty.
Grey just
signed off on it.
Told you he would.
I didn't realize
you wanted to be a detective.
I mean, to me, it seems like
the most effective way
to make sure other people
aren't railroaded like I was.
'Cause the detective
that was assigned my case,
he dropped the ball
every step of the way.
Well, he was French.
So, what, you've never seen,
like, a bad American detective?
That's fair.
But I do have to
warn you,
being a detective is nothing
like being on patrol.
The hours are brutal,
and the cases are
emotionally devastating
in a way that patrol
can't prepare you for.
Are you sure
you want this?
Yes, I'm sure.
What do you say
we start with a test?
Oh.
How about a game
of five questions?
Okay. Let's go. Yeah.
As a detective, you need to
ask the right questions,
so I'll send you the first page
of a case file.
You can ask us five questions
and five questions only.
So think carefully about what
you need to know to solve it.
Oh, I got this.
Alright,
so the records get dodgy,
but so far I haven't found
anyone who's died in your house.
On your land
is a bigger question.
Okay. I appreciate
all the hard work.
I think I'm just gonna
call an exterminator.
Look, I-I think you need
to broaden your understanding
of what's possible.
Have you tried ayahuasca?
Nolan: Hmm.
You know, it really shifts
the way you see the world.
I think
it'd be good for you.
Is that the one that makes you
vomit uncontrollably?
It's very cleansing.
Yeah, I-I think
I want to keep
my perception
the way it is.
[Police radio chatter]
So...
how's single life going?
It's good.
No one to complain
when I watch football
all Sunday.
You didn't leave
the house once?
I walked Kojo.
Tim, what?
[Chuckles]
I spend all week outside.
No, I know, but we live
in a vibrant city.
There's always something
amazing going on.
Okay, so, don't get me wrong,
I love L.A.,
but it is not
a vibrant city, okay?
It's a loosely stitched together
patchwork of strip malls.
You're hopeless.
[Cellphone rings]
Chris:
Hey! You busy?
Uh, no.
Wh-Where are you?
An open house.
It was on my way to work.
Uh, what do you think?
It needs some work,
but, uh,
it's three bedrooms.
Yeah, I... I can't really see
anything. Can we talk later?
Okay. Love you.
Yeah.
Are you... Are you and Chris,
uh, moving in together?
No. Uh, it's...
I mean, he seems to
think you are.
Yeah, I mean,
I don't know.
He kind of sprang it on me
this morning.
You guys are happy, right?
Yeah.
Those are the obvious
next steps.
Yeah, no, we're super happy.
It's... It's good.
Dispatch: 7-Adam-100,
I have an in-progress vandalism
on West 3rd
south of Olympic.
Yeah. Show us responding.
[Siren wails]
Krishna: No, no, no, no!
Not the Corvette!
You should've
thought of that
before you flirted
with that whore!
Babe! Aah!
Lucy: Oh, my God.
Our accountant?
She's 60!
And a stone-cold fox!
Tim: Okay, ma'am... ma'am,
put down the golf club.
Krishna: Oh, yeah?
Sir, no!
Put the golf club down!
You wouldn't dare!
Is this what you want?
Okay, that's it!
Enough! Weapons down!
Weapon?
It's a golf club.
Now.
I... Look, Officer,
this is a misunderstanding.
Who called you?
That doesn't matter.
It was the busybody
across the street, wasn't it?
I bet she's posting
on Nextdoor!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
of course she is.
You know, what else has she got
in her sad little life?
She needs to put down the phone
and take in her garbage bins!
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Actually, can you guys
do something about that, huh?
She just leaves them
out there for days.
Not our jurisdiction.
[Sweetly]
Okay. Fine.
Mm. So where do you want
to go for brunch?
In bed.
Mmm. I like the way
you're thinking.
Okay. Either of you want
to make a report
about the damage
to your cars?
[Sighs]
At this point,
we have the body shop
on speed dial.
♪
So, have you thought of
your first question?
Yes.
I already went over the file
you gave me.
The remains were found
on the grounds
of the La Brea Tar Pits complex,
and a female guard went missing
one month prior.
Correct.
And it's always
the boyfriend.
Okay. First question.
Was she seeing anyone?
Yes. And he also worked
at the museum.
A paleontologist.
Oh, okay. So he had access
to the grounds.
Interesting.
Did he have an alibi?
No, he did not.
Okay.
So why haven't you and Bailey
set a date?
Oh, we're enjoying
being engaged.
Hm. Have something to do
with her crazy ex?
Are they even divorced?
Uh, yeah, they have been
for a while now.
How did you
even know about that?
I mean, cops gossip.
Really? About me?
What else do they say?
Well, they don't say, like,
anything bad.
They just mention...
[Engine revs, tires screech]
Whoa.
Light it up.
[Siren wails]
[Tires screech]
Ma'am?
Uh, ma'am, can you turn
the engine off for me?
Pam: I can't stop. I have to
keep driving. I'm sorry.
Ma'am, I need you
to stop the car.
What is that
around your neck?
He made me put it on.
He said to drive
or he'd kill me.
Ma'am, is that a bomb?
[Crying]
I have to go.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to die.
I have to go.
Ma'am? Ma'am?
No. No!
[Tires squeal]
♪
Pilot: Air-3 is lifting off now.
ETA... 5 minutes from target.
You made the right call. We have
to assume it's a real explosive.
Coordinating with
the bomb squad now.
Yes, sir.
What would you like us to do?
Follow her, but stay
out of radio range.
Yes, sir.
If the bomb has
a remote trigger,
our radio signal
could set it off.
Celina: Dropping back.
We'll clear the streets.
Air support's on its way.
Sir, maybe we can get
a court order
for all the cell carriers.
Get phone numbers attached
to her home address.
It's already in process.
7-Adam-100, 2331,
stand by
for victim information.
Copy.
Where do you want us?
Scout for a staging area.
Bomb squad needs
a wide-open space.
We have to limit
potential casualties.
There's an empty lot
near Nolan's location.
Perfect.
I'll send backup to you now.
So, Harper, Lopez, Nolan says
the driver's under duress.
Said she was told
to keep driving
or the bomb would detonate.
Did he give her
a destination?
No. Doesn't seem to be
about a target.
She's the target.
So we need to find
whatever we can on her.
Whoever chose her
did it for a reason.
We're on it. Nolan...
bomb squad needs to know
what they're dealing with.
Can you get a picture?
No problem.
Turning off radio, going dark.
Want you to pull up
next to that car.
Try and stay parallel.
The bomb car?
Yeah.
Okay. Getting closer
to the bomb car.
[Engine revs]
Alright.
Closer. Alright.
[Crying]
Uh, it's a hinged collar
secured around her neck,
kind of like handcuffs. Nolan...
With quarter-twenty tapped
standoffs at regular intervals.
Nolan.
The explosive is built
into the side of the unit.
Contains C-4. It's connected
with red and green wires.
J-John!
Almost done.
No, we have to fall back.
I just need a better look
at the clasp.
It's... It's secured
under her chin
with a pin post lock, dual-post
shackle-style mechanism.
[Tires screech]
God. Did you get it?
That was some slick driving.
Thanks.
Okay. Hopefully,
that's all they need.
I-I mean, that was
a pretty precise description.
Oh, in my previous life,
I was a contractor.
I'm surprised you remember
your past lives.
Celina.
I'm sorry.
Just kidding.
Lopez: We're on our way
to the victim's house now.
I need a scrub of
all social-media posts.
Thanks.
Pam's a lawyer.
We should start
with her client list.
I already put in a call
to her old law firm.
She had
a criminal-defense practice,
so there's no telling
who she pissed off.
Look at you.
I mean, if I want to become
detective before I'm 30,
I got to be on my game, right?
Does that mean you've thought
of your third question?
I have, but I don't
want to just assume
that the paleontologist
boyfriend did it,
so I need a more complete
picture of the guard's life.
Does she have
a criminal record?
As a matter of fact,
she was under investigation
at the time
of her disappearance.
They suspected her of stealing
small artifacts from the museum
and selling them
on the black market.
Maybe she got greedy
or threatened
to go to the police,
and whoever she was working with
decided she was a liability.
Is there a question
in there?
Not yet.
[Police radio chatter]
Perfect.
There's plenty of space to...
[Punk music playing,
skaters chattering]
Boy: Awesome, dude.
Flag on the play.
Parking lot is not empty.
Sgt. Grey:
Clear it out now.
I'm redirecting the bomb squad
to your location.
Hey! LAPD! We need you guys
to clear out! Let's go!
There's a bomb!
Run like hell!
Let's go!
[Children shouting]
Boy: Let's roll!
[Skaters shouting
indistinctly]
[Siren wails]
We have Pam's
mobile number.
[Cellphone rings]
Hi. It's Pam, right?
My name is John.
We have the bomb squad
on the way to help you out.
You are gonna be okay.
Right now,
I need you to follow us.
Can you do that?
I need to call my mom.
I need to tell her
that I love her.
We can do that, but right now,
I need you to follow us
so we can meet up
with the bomb squad, okay?
He told me
to keep driving.
He said that I would die
if I didn't.
Pam, that's a lie.
Bomb squad says there's no GPS
on your collar, alright?
He can't tell
if you're stopped or not.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Yes, Pam, I am sure.
Now we're gonna pull out
in front of you
and you're gonna
follow us, okay?
[Breathes shakily]
Okay.
[Engine revs]
[Siren wails]
[Helicopter blades whirring]
Pilot: I have a visual.
Will maintain contact.
Alright, Pam.
Now, I want you to park
right up next
to the orange cone
that Sergeant Bradford
is setting out.
Okay?
Okay.
♪
Yeah, you got it.
Gonna take you to a safe spot.
Alright, Pam, just checking in.
How are you doing?
Um... not great.
Please get this thing
off of me.
That's what
we're here to do.
Alright. And there they are.
Bomb squad is here.
We're gonna have you
out of that in no time.
Now, Pam, earlier you said you
wanted me to call your mother.
Is there anyone else
you want me to get ahold of?
No. Not really.
Is that pathetic?
Not at all.
There's nothing like
a traumatic event
to make you realize that your...
that your life is empty.
Come on, Pam.
I don't believe that.
[Sniffles]
My entire life is work.
I have no friends.
I'm completely alone.
You're not alone, Pam.
'Cause I'm here now.
Everyone here
is here to help you.
I need you to cut off
your engine now, Pam.
You see that guy behind you
in the doughboy suit?
That's Mike. Mike is absolutely
the best there is.
Alright? He's gonna get you
out of there in no time.
The only problem is, uh,
he tells very bad
dad jokes,
so I'm gonna have to
apologize in advance.
Alright.
He's there at your window.
Mike: It's locked.
I just need you to reach down
and open the door, okay, Pam?
I can't.
I can't move. Hey...
Yes, you can do this.
You can do this, Pam.
Just take a...
take a nice deep breath.
Reach down.
Unlock that door.
[Crying] I-I can't.
I can't. I can't.
You got this.
I know as soon as I move,
this thing's gonna go off!
No, come on. Come on, Pam.
It's almost over.
Mike is right there.
You just
need to open the door for him.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
You got this, Pam.
Okay.
[Exhales sharply]
I'm gonna reach over.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna unlock it, okay?
[Collar beeping]
It started beeping.
Do you hear that?
Why is it beeping?
It's beeping.
Uh, don't worry about that, Pam.
Just open the door, okay?
[Collar beeping rapidly]
Just open that door.
[Officers screaming]
♪
[Sirens wailing,
skateboarders chattering]
Nolan: Go get those kids
out of here!
Celina: Okay.
- This is crazy.
- It's crazy.
Girl: Yo, this is
so crazy, yo. Wait.
We were just skating.
Look, look.
Look at this.
I need you all to back up
another 10 yards.
Yo, Officer, what happened?
I heard a lady blew up?
We're not sharing
any information at this time.
Back up!
[Siren wails]
[Fire extinguisher spraying]
[Indistinct conversations]
I pushed back
the perimeter.
Good.
Do you think
she felt it?
Her death?
Yeah.
No.
But everything up to that point
was torture.
What'd the bomb squad
say?
They confirmed what
we already suspected.
Device appears
to be homemade
using items you can find
at any hardware store.
Do they know what
triggered the explosion?
Most likely, the device
was on a timer,
but they need to put the bomb
back together to be sure.
Ah, that's gonna be
a hell of a jigsaw puzzle.
I'm sure videos are already
popping up on social media.
And the news choppers
are already here.
[Helicopter blades whirring]
Okay, well, if her car and her
license plate get leaked online,
it's not gonna be long
till her name does, too.
Ohh, I can't imagine
finding out something
about someone I love
like this on ClipTalk.
We're not gonna
let that happen.
Nolan, I want you and Juarez
to go to the victim's house.
Right.
Who would do
something like this?
[Helicopter blades whirring]
It's officially
a homicide.
Was anyone else
injured?
Nothing serious.
That's strange, right?
I mean, bombs are usually
for mass-casualty events.
If you want to kill one person,
a gun is a lot easier.
They didn't just want her dead.
They wanted her terrified.
[Cellphone chimes]
Hold on. I just got video
footage from Pam's house.
Can't see his face.
Alright. The garage camera's
triggered 7 minutes later.
Is there
any other angle?
No, that's it.
Wait, wait.
Go back real quick.
Yeah. I feel like
she recognizes him.
Yeah, she doesn't
seem scared.
Whoever he is,
she wasn't expecting trouble.
Alright, mother's name is
Marianne Winfield.
62, works in PR, and...
man, she's about to receive
the worst news of her life.
Alright.
I'll do the talking.
It's better
if only one of us speaks.
That way,
the person can focus
a little easier
on what we're telling them.
Well, I can do it.
You sure?
I have to make my first
death notification sometime.
Might as well be today.
Okay.
Don't speak
in euphemisms.
No "passed on"
or "in a better place."
Just be direct.
"We have bad news.
Your daughter Pam was killed
today in an explosion."
You know, when the police
told my mom
that they'd recovered my sister,
they said, "We found her."
And for a second,
we thought...
So you understand
how important this is.
Yeah. I do.
Okay.
♪
[Murmuring] Celina Juarez.
This is Officer John Nolan.
♪
Lucy: That poor woman.
The last moments of her life
must have been agony,
just wondering if the bomb
was gonna go off,
praying it wouldn't.
I'm guessing
that was the point.
No way someone goes through
that much trouble of building
something like that unless they
want to terrorize their victim.
Yeah.
[Cellphone rings]
Hey.
I saw the news.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine,
but it's crazy out here.
Okay. Look, if you
don't have time, I get it.
But a Realtor friend of mine
just slipped me a listing.
It hasn't been
posted online yet.
So, uh, if you like it,
I think we should move on it.
Wow. Um, okay.
Chen, chat with your boyfriend
on your own time.
He's in a mood.
I'll let you go.
Just text me and let me know
what you think?
Yeah, I-I'll do that.
Thanks.
Pam Winfield was an in-house
counsel at Sunvale Oil
for the past five years.
Security e-mailed me
a list of people
who sent threatening letters
to the company.
The first guy lives
over on Orange Grove.
Alright, let's go
pay him a visit.
How's the Tar Pits
case going?
I haven't been
thinking about it.
After what happened,
it seems kind of silly.
Part of being a detective
is juggling cases,
switching between
wildly different gears.
Okay. Um...
Okay. We have the boyfriend.
We have the artifacts broker.
Both have motive
to kill the guard.
I-I feel like I need to know
more about the theft.
Like, how did she get roped up
in this in the first place?
Is that
a fourth question?
Yes. Did the guard
take the job at the museum
in order to gain access
to the artifacts?
It's hard to say,
but we do know
that her
black-market contact
was also her
high-school sweetheart.
Another love interest?
[Pen clicks]
Okay.
Now we're getting somewhere.
This is a lot.
Watching her die,
having to tell her mother.
It's more than anyone should
have to deal with in a day.
But our shift
isn't over yet.
I know. I'm okay.
[Cellphone rings]
Hey. Where are you?
I'm under the house.
Why?
I keep hearing this noise,
and it's driving me crazy.
And you thought
it would be a good idea
to go under there
by yourself?
That's why
I FaceTimed you.
That's not the same.
It's not...
Wait. What is that?
What is what?
Aah!
Bailey?
Bailey?! What is what?!
Bailey!
Sorry. False alarm.
It's just this guy.
Oh, God!
What is that
doing under there?
I don't know.
Should I move it?
Yeah.
No! No! Not till
you consult an exorcist.
Look, if you don't want to
move in, just tell Chris that.
That's...
The question is,
why don't I want to move in?
I don't get what the problem is.
I mean, Chris is great.
We're great together.
We never fight.
Maybe that's the problem.
Oh, you think we should be like
that couple from this morning?
No, I'm not saying that,
but... No.
But do you guys not fight
because you don't
disagree on things,
or because you don't think
it's worth the bother?
Lucy.
Yeah?
You deserve someone
who's worth the effort.
[Engine revs]
[Tires screech]
What was that?
[Siren wails]
He...
♪
Control, 7-Adam-100.
There is a second bomb.
Repeat.
There's a second bomb.
What's your name?!
Lucy: Hey!
[Grunts]at's your name?
[Siren wailing]
[Cellphone rings]
Get me as close
as you can, okay?
Tim: Right.
Hey. Reach out.
[Grunts]
Reach out. Reach out. Okay.
Can you get closer?
Yeah.
Here, here, here.
Got it!
♪
Hi. I'm Lucy.
Hi. H-He told me
to keep driving.
I don't want to die!
Sir, we're here to help you.
What's your name?
Creighton.
Creighton Mitchell.
Okay. Creighton,
we're gonna try
and get you to drive
somewhere safe.
You think
you can do that?
[Breathlessly]
I can't breathe.
I feel like I'm dying.
I think I'm dying.
Creighton, you're probably
having a panic attack right now.
I just need you
to try and stay calm.
Maybe turn on the radio
for some music?
Woman: [On radio]
A woman is dead today
after an unknown assailant
apparently strapped
an explosive device
to her neck.
Oh, my God!
This happened to somebody else?!
And she's dead?!
Creighton,
listen to me.
That is not gonna be you, okay?
You can bet your ass
this isn't gonna be me!
♪
Creighton!
[Tires screech]
♪
Creighton, stop!
You could detonate
the device!
I'm not just gonna wait
for this thing
to blow my head off!
Everyone, back up!
Get inside the house!
There's a bomb!
Back up!
Clear it out! Clear off
the sidewalk! Let's go!
[Creighton grunting]
♪
[Grunting]
[Clang]
Ow!
[Breathing heavily]
I'm alive!
[Laughs]
♪
[Whirring,
indistinct radio chatter]
Yeah, so the bomb
was on a timer.
He had 3 minutes left.
It's a good thing he bailed
when he did.
We would have never
made it on time.
How long
did he have total?
Couldn't tell
from the device,
but as long as he was driving
plus 3 minutes.
Okay, thanks. Bye.
What time was the device
activated?
Uh, I don't know.
Uh, a while?
He activated it right before
he put me in the car.
Alright, we'll get the GPS
off your car.
Lucy: What exactly can you
remember from this morning?
I was going to work.
I-I-I heard a knock at the door
and when I answered it,
Richard was standing there
with a collar and a gun.
Richard?
Dormer.
Richard Dormer.
I-I used to work with
his sister at Sunvale.
Oh. Sunvale Oil?
Did you know
Pam Winfield?
Yeah. Why?
The woman they were
talking about on
the radio this morning,
uh, that was Pam.
What?!
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Were you close?
I-I-I mean,
I-I worked with her.
Wh-What is this?
What's going on?
That's what we're trying
to figure out here.
What did Richard
say to you?
He told me if... if I didn't
put the collar on,
he'd kill me.
And he didn't
give you any reason?
[Sighs]
It was all so fast.
I-I-I don't know.
I don't know.
Uh, do you have
his sister's number?
She might be able
to give us some insight.
No, no.
She's... She's dead.
Do you know
what happened?
We...
[Sighs]
We sent her abroad
to handle a deal,
and she was kidnapped
and... she was killed.
How were you and Pam
involved?
It was our call,
whether or not
to pay the ransom.
I mean... And we were
going to, I-I swear.
But, you know,
you negotiate these things.
You... It's how you do it.
They expect you to do it.
But these guys, they panicked
or... I don't know.
All I know is...
she died over there.
7-Adam-15, I need you
to pick up Richard Dormer.
Proceed with extreme caution.
He might be our bomber.
[Engine revs]
Stay alert.
Watch his hands.
[Tires screech]
Richard Dormer, keep your hands
where I can see them!
Is this all for me?
Turn around.
Get on the ground.
I'm unarmed.
I know how this ends.
I don't mind
going to prison.
Turn around and get
on the ground, now.
[Handcuffs rattle]
Lopez: We need the bomb squad
to do a search
before we process
the house.
You don't have to be afraid.
The explosives are gone.
The third bomb's
already out there.
♪
Harper: Apparently there were
three people who signed off
on negotiating rather
than paying the ransom...
Pam, Creighton,
and Henri Parsons,
the company CEO.
You have a phone number?
Yes, but he is not answering.
Lopez is getting authorization
to track it as we speak.
Alright, well,
based on Creighton's GPS,
he had 43 minutes
from the time
the bomb was activated
until it was detonated.
Why 43 minutes?
You're the detective.
Okay. Henri drives
a black BMW 5 Series,
and he lives
in Cheviot Hills.
We could head up there,
drive a grid.
It's a start.
Okay. I guess we should pick up
a pair of garden shears.
[Scoffs] Don't think we can
rely on that working again.
Yeah.
[Cellphone chimes]
[Scoffs]
More home listings?
Yeah.
Oh, you've
gotta be kidding me.
This one's in Monrovia.
Who wants to live in Monrovia?
It looks like Chris does.
Do you love him?
I mean, we haven't even
been dating that long.
It's not...
He loves you.
I know.
I know, and I feel like
I should love him back.
He's so great
in so many different ways.
It's just...
He's just not...
You know, you killed
an innocent woman today.
There was nothing innocent
about Pam Winfield.
She got what she deserved.
She experienced exactly what
she forced my sister
to experience...
43 minutes of terror
and then darkness.
What do you mean?
Where she was abducted,
where they held her,
and where she died.
It took 43 minutes
to drive her out to the desert
to be executed.
Kidnappers killed
your sister.
It wasn't Pam's fault
or Creighton's fault
or Henri's!
She trusted them!
She believed their promises
that if anything happened,
they would have her back!
[Scoffs]
♪
You know, every single person
in that company is guilty.
Every single one.
They all knew
she was taken,
and not one person
fought for her.
Not one.
People she worked with
for years
just sat on their hands
and let her die.
Henri's not just
driving around randomly
like the others,
is he?
♪
Now, I've been assuming
foul play,
but maybe the victim
committed suicide
or got drunk
and had an accident.
Was there a question in there?
You've only got one more.
No. No, there's not.
[Cellphone rings]
Nolan,
what do we got?
The third victim isn't just
randomly driving around.
He's on his way
to Sunvale Oil offices.
The third bomb's gonna
take out the whole company.
♪
[Engine revs]
[Tires screech]
Stay with him.
Yeah.
[Employees screaming]
Nolan:
Keep moving. Keep moving.
The far side of
the parking lot. Keep...
♪
Control, 7-Adam-15.
I've located our third victim.
Corporate offices, Sunvale Oil.
He's confirmed on site.
♪
Celina: Nolan's inside
with the bomb.
We need to clear
the building.
♪
We need you to clear out. Move.
Everyone, listen up!
We have a credible threat
at this location!
I need everyone
to move with purpose!
Aaron: Come on. Everybody
move quickly but stay calm.
Let's go. This way.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Let's spread out and make sure
there are no stragglers.
♪
Mr. Parsons. Mr. Parsons.
Hey. I'm John Nolan.
Help me.
Please help me.
That's why I'm here.
That's why... What's this?
He... He told me
to stream an apology.
Okay. First, we're gonna get
all these people out of here.
Folks, come on.
We're gonna move outside.
No. He told me
not to let them go.
He said he'd kill me
if they left.
Relax. Okay? No... You've been
told a lie. Okay, folks?
The bomber is right now
outside in my car.
I can guarantee he does not have
a remote trigger with him.
This bomb is on a timer.
You're sure?
100%.
Nice and safe, guys.
Everyone move outside.
Downstairs.
The far side
of the parking lot
as fast as you can, alright?
Quick and safe.
How long ago did he put
this bomb on your neck?
Huh? Uh...
You gotta think, okay?
The timer is for 43 minutes,
so you have to think.
How long ago did he put this
on your neck?
Uh... uh...
More than a half-hour.
Uh, maybe 40 minutes?
Okay. That's... not great.
It could be worse.
Everyone out!
Come on, ladies. Move, move!
What about me?
You and I, we're gonna
focus on this bomb, okay?
Let's take a look here,
see what we've got, alright?
Stay nice and calm
for me.
Tell me how to
disarm the bomb.
No.
My T.O. is up there,
and he's not gonna leave
someone who is scared and alone.
If that bomb goes off,
you're killing him, too.
Yeah, well, he's making
a choice to stay.
And you're making a choice
to kill people.
There have to be
consequences!
My sister is dead.
They need to pay.
Look, I get it.
Nolan: This is the hinge point.
My little sister was taken away
from me a long time ago,
and I spent
most of my life
thinking of all
the different ways
I would hurt
the person responsible.
But all that hate
just ate away at me
until I didn't
recognize myself.
Your sister
wouldn't want this.
Okay.
This is entirely smooth.
I can't get in from the back.
I want my apology.
I want him to admit
what he did
for the whole world
to hear.
[Breathing heavily]
Where does this go?
Is the bomb squad coming?
Yeah, any minute now.
I only have a couple
of those left.
"We."
I'm staying with you
till we figure this out.
♪
The floor is clear.
We should go.
The bomb squad is almost here.
John?
Go.
You don't
have to do this.
Yes, I do.
Harper, go.
♪
[Siren wails]
[Cellphone dials]
[Cellphone ringing]
♪
Nolan:
Not a good time.
Richard says he'll tell us
how to disarm the bomb
if Parson just admits
what he did.
I didn't do anything.
I was negotiating.
Hey. Your semantics are
gonna get us both killed.
[Breathing heavily]
I'm sorry.
We let her die.
It was my fault.
I made the call.
Susan Dormer is dead
because of me.
[Sighs]
There's two wires in the back,
a red and a green one.
Cut the green wire.
[Knife clicks]
♪
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
He's lying.
What?
He doesn't want an apology.
He wants Parsons dead.
Cut the red one.
♪
Are you sure?
Yes.
♪
[Bomb powering down]
[Breathing shakily]
Okay. Nice and easy.
♪
[Gasps]
Nolan: Thank you.
And... thank you.
You saved my life today.
That kind of insight
in a rookie is... remarkable.
[Camera beeps]
You know, I...
I wouldn't be
making so much progress
without
such a great T.O.
Thank you again.
You know,
I wouldn't mind at all
if you repeated that
in front of Sgt. Grey.
Just saying, repeating things
is good in general.
Sgt. Grey, imagine...
Have you seen "Inception"?
I'll walk you through it.
Okay, so, I think
I solved your case.
You have one more question
you could ask.
Nope.
Don't need it.
Hmm. Cocky.
Alright, let's hear it.
Okay, so, the victim was dating
one of the scientists
who worked at the Tar Pits, right?
And she was part
of a smuggling ring
that sold artifacts
on the black market.
So, was it
a jealous lover
or a criminal enterprise
gone wrong?
Actually, it was both.
She was sleeping with both
the smuggler and the scientist,
and they found out
and they killed her together.
I think you have a long road
to detective, Officer Thorsen.
Wait.
Was I at least close?
You had
five questions.
Right.
And you never asked
the a of the remains.
Well, no, no, no.
The... The... The file said
that she was 32
when she went missing.
Right, but the bone
was thousands of years old.
You see, the Tar Pits
are constantly
turning up
ancient remains.
So in... in this case,
the killer was
a-a saber-toothed tiger.
Wait. What happened
to the missing guard?
Oh, she was found
in Mexico a year later.
You see, you assumed
that there was a connection
between the female remains
and the missing woman. Yeah.
First rule of investigation...
Don't make assumptions.
♪
[Grunts]
Oh.
Looks like a toy store
threw up in our house.
Well, Jack got
two shots today.
I didn't want him to
associate me with needles.
Did he cry?
No.
Did you cry?
That's irrelevant.
Not according to
our living room, it's not.
Doesn't Jack already have
a basketball hoop?
Well, yeah, but now
he's got an outside one
and an inside one...
[Sighs]
[Chuckles]
[Buzzes lips] Ohh.
I don't know how you deal with
watching him get shots so often.
Well, I know
it's for his own good.
I know I have to be tough
to show him how to be tough.
And... I fill him full of
ice cream right after.
Oh, you didn't tell me
that trick.
Because you want
to be his favorite.
I'm already his favorite.
[Laughs]
♪ It's the epilogue
♪ Of the sequel to the first
Welcome home!
[Door closes]
Thank you for cleaning off
all those cobwebs
and clown...
before I got home.
Can never clean that clown
off my mind, though.
Ugh.
Where is he now?
Outside.
Where he belongs.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, geez!
[Laughs]
I couldn't help myself.
♪ Where she was
born and raised ♪
We are gonna take it
outside to burn.
The only way to kill
this kind of evil is by fire.
Nolan:
You got that right.
So, if it was just a doll,
what was making the noise?
Well, when I got off the phone,
I found something else.
A puppy!
Oh.
This little guy was making
all that ruckus.
Can we keep him?
No.
I'll just give him a bath.
No, I mean,
that's... that's not a puppy.
That's a coyote.
♪ 'Cause you feel safe
in the light ♪
How did you get him
in a crate?
♪
Hey. We need to talk.
Let me guess.
Chris wants to buy
a house in Chatsworth?
No.
[Scoffs]
Look, this clearly
isn't working out.
I don't know why
you won't just admit it.
Unless... Is it guilt?
Is it because of
what Rosalind did to him?
Oh, like I'm the only one
that's stayed too long
when things
aren't working.
You dated
a lifeguard.
You don't even like
going to the beach.
This isn't about me.
Uh...
No, it's not.
This is not about me.
This is about you... Okay.
...staying in this
safe relationship...
because you're scared.
Of course I'm scared.
If we do this
and it doesn't work,
I'll have ruined
the most important
relationship in my life.
♪ Never trust a man
♪ I'm scared to go home
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said, um...
No. Um...
You're right.
So we should just keep going
the way we have been, right?
It's not worth the risk.
♪ I'm working on safe
♪ I'm working on plan
Unless it is.
♪ Life is just adjusting
to the dealer's latest hand ♪
Do you want to get dinner
sometime?
Yes.
Yeah?
[Chuckling] Yeah.
No. Uh...
I... S... Oh.
Okay.
No, no.
It's just, um...
Not yet.
I owe it to Chris to end things
the right way with him.
Ask me again.
Later. After.
Deal.
♪
- Captions by VITA...