Previously on "The Rookie."
I read my sister's case file.
My mom lied to me.
I'm here because
I have to do this.
Because what happened to me
was so awful
I need to make sure it doesn't
happen to anyone else.
Celina's mom had been
in a car accident.
Her doctors prescribed opioids.
On the day that your sister
was abducted,
your mother was buying drugs.
All these years, I mean,
do you have any idea
how much I've blamed myself?
Hey, you were just a kid.
It wasn't your fault.
I know.
It was hers.
[yawns]
Oh, don't you look cozy!
It's my day off
and I intend to relax.
- You're going to relax?
- Oh, yeah.
Okay, let me translate that
into Bailey.
That means you're going to
teach four capoeira classes,
do a 10-mile hike,
run for mayor?
Excuse me, governor.
No, I'm doing
absolutely nothing.
- Okay.
- I'm serious.
I'm gonna read trashy magazines
and stream '90s sitcoms
and do nothing.
I give the whole thing
20 minutes.
I can do anything
I set my mind to,
even nothing.
You go, girl.
It's supposed to be beautiful
this weekend.
I was going to power wash
the outdoor furniture.
Oh, I can do that.
Oh, you're baiting me.
Nice try.
I'm doing nothing today.
- Sure you are.
Listen, if you change your mind
about the governorship,
I'd be honored to be
your first gentleman.
[sighs]
Governor Nune.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
I kinda like it.
♪ I'm gonna win for you ♪
♪ Like I know
you want me to do ♪
[yawns]
- Hey.
When did you get in?
Uh, depends.
What day is it?
That bad, huh?
Look, I'm...I'm 80% sure
it's...it's Thursday.
It's Tuesday. Yeah.
What were you guys
working on last night?
Uh, murder suspect.
We were there all night.
I stayed up anyways.
Thought maybe I'd get lucky
and he'd turn himself in.
Not quite.
Um, he did show up, though.
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
- Oh, babe.
Took on five metro officers?
You gotta love that confidence.
Yeah.
What's all this?
What?
I'm studying for
the detective's exam.
- Since when?
- I didn't tell you?
I...no, I don't think so.
If I'm gonna work undercover,
the best move is to become
a detective in some division,
like intelligence
or narcotics, right?
Right.
So you got the tap.
Harper and Lopez
are backing me.
All I have to do is score
in the top 12, which...
Which you will.
Mm.
Well, I guess
we should get used to
not seeing each other so much.
Mm, right.
Yeah, between detective's hours
and metro hours...
Hm. It's okay.
We'll figure it out.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry I haven't been
around as much lately.
I've been busy.
I actually started working on
your case.
Well, I...I haven't made
much progress,
unless destroying my
relationship with Mom counts.
Look, I know you'd want me
to forgive her, but I...
I...I don't...
I don't think I'm ready.
Well, I gotta get to work.
Where's Celina?
Oh, she's visiting
her sister's grave.
Today's the anniversary of
the day she was taken.
I know. That's what I have to
talk to her about.
I found two similar
kidnappings;
one four years after Blanca
and another seven years
after that.
In every case, the victim was
six years old,
taken while playing outside,
and the parent has
a history of substance abuse.
That sounds like
a serial killer.
But why target the children
of drug addicts?
I don't know.
And every case happened on
the same day.
Today?
I'll handle it.
Thank you very much.
Is that the sign-up list
for the detective's exam?
It is. Two weeks to go.
- I'll be ready.
- I have no doubt.
Brave move, Chen.
I don't know about that.
I think it's the next step
for me.
Sure, but you'll never make
top 12.
What is that
supposed to mean?
One of the detectives
has it out for you.
So no matter how well you do
on the written,
they're gonna sink you
on the oral.
What? Who?
I don't know.
Good luck.
- Is he right?
- Rarely.
But I will ask around,
see if there's any truth to it.
Thanks.
He abducted more kids?
Two, that we know of.
And on the same day
as your sister.
That's today.
Okay, that's creepy.
So there could be another one today.
Or not.
Right.
You know, I...I visited
her grave this morning,
and she wasn't there.
I know you think that's crazy.
That aside, why do you think
she wasn't there?
I don't know.
But lately she's felt so, like,
far away.
And I don't know
what's changed.
7-Adam-15,
we have a possible 207
at 9215 Detroit Street.
- It's a kidnapping.
- Possible kidnapping.
7-Adam-15, show us responding.
I can take the lead on this.
- No, I'm good.
You know,
when Blanca was taken,
there were dozens of cops.
And most of them were terrifying,
but there was one that
made me feel like
everything was going to be Okay.
I want to be that person
for someone else.
Maybe it's Carradine.
I called him out for stealing
my lunches from the fridge.
Okay, and you think
he's that petty?
Maybe. I...
[groans]
Who do you think it is?
- I think,
and stay with me on this one...
- Mm-hmm?
Maybe you shouldn't believe
everything Smitty says
or anything Smitty says.
Yeah, but what if
he is right?
The oral part of the exam is
so subjective.
If even one person on the panel
has it out for me,
it'll tank my score.
Yeah, I never expected
a police station
to be so much like high school.
- I know.
Except, I mean,
now I'm one of the cool kids.
It's him. It's the same guy.
I don't...we don't know that.
Most of the time
they're playing somewhere.
We find them in minutes.
- No, that's not what this is.
I can feel it.
- Did you find her?
- No, ma'am.
We have to find her!
She's six. She's scared.
We know. That's why we're
here.
We just need a few details.
- What details?
My daughter is missing.
I said that on the phone!
Okay, maybe you can
let us inside,
and we can help you look.
- She's not inside.
I looked.
She was playing outside.
I...I heard a scream,
and she was gone.
- You heard her scream?
- Yes.
7-Adam-15.
I need additional units
on my location.
Notify search and rescue.
What's he doing?
Is he calling someone?
He's calling everyone.
In ten minutes,
there will be dozens
of police officers
and volunteers
looking for your daughter.
Olivia.
Her name's Olivia.
That's a really pretty name.
How about I help you find
a photo of her?
Yeah.
[sirens wailing]
We'll do two more of those,
at least by the next...
- Nolan.
- Here we are.
Any updates?
We turned the house
upside down,
checked the adjacent yards.
We're widening the search.
- Security cameras?
- We got what we can.
A lot of people aren't home.
- It's him, isn't it?
- We don't know that.
Look, we see the parallels,
but you cannot leap
to conclusions.
I mean, it's the anniversary.
She's six years old,
taken from her front yard.
What was that?
I checked.
Olivia's mother has
a history of drug abuse.
Just like my mom. I mean,
just like the other victims.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Well done. Just double back
to check if anybody wasn't
home.
We'll interview friends
and family.
Okay.
Oversee the canvass teams
and widen the perimeter.
Hey.
How can we help?
We need to comb through
the other cases,
find any connections we can
between them.
Any of the girls that
were taken,
did any of them survive?
No, all the girls were
found dead
less than a month after
they disappeared,
except Blanca,
who was found near death.
What was different about her?
Best guess,
she was the first.
He didn't know
what he was doing.
Well, he does now.
He won't make that mistake again.
You know your jobs.
Get it done.
- Celina.
- Yeah.
Hey, look, I just wanted
to say that
I remember what it was like
to not know what happened
to someone you love. I mean,
there were a bunch of times
I thought we had a lead and
nothing ever panned out.
So don't get my hopes up.
Yeah, I guess that's what
I'm trying to say.
Yeah, no. Thank you.
I gotta stay objective. Yeah.
Anything south of
Hobart Street,
you take it all the way down...
Hang on a sec. You got that?
Bailey.
I know what I said
this morning,
but I heard you needed more
bodies for the door to door.
So here I am.
- I wasn't gonna say anything.
I'm just going to check in
with the civilian team.
Hey, what's on your hands?
Uh... wood stain.
Okay, so you went to power
wash the outdoor furniture...
It just looked so bad
after all the rains
that I had to sand it
and refinish it.
[sighs]
- I tried to do nothing.
- Yeah, I know.
It's important you tried.
- Yeah.
- You're doing great.
- Okay.
Yeah, I'll call you back.
All right, bye.
Detective Dave Delgado.
Sergeant Wade Grey.
[both laughing]
Man, thanks for coming down.
Have a seat.
- Yeah, man.
I heard you had a lead on
the Juarez case.
I ran three red lights
getting over here.
Well, I hope we didn't
waste your time.
Eh, if I wasn't here,
I'd be watching "Bosch"
in my underwear.
- [chuckles]
- Never retire.
Look, we know everything
in the case file.
What we need is
what's not in the file.
Well, there was this one guy,
Drew Heslov.
Lived in the area,
didn't have an alibi.
And he's a Megan's Law 290
sex offender.
Not much to build
a case around.
Exactly.
But I interviewed him.
Real creep.
Felt like he was enjoying
the whole thing.
All right,
we'll check him out.
I hear the, uh...
the sister's a rookie here.
She is.
She'll make a good detective
one day.
She has great instincts.
Yeah, well, she came by them
the hard way.
Something like that
happens when you're a kid,
changes the way
you see the world.
Yeah.
[distorted shouts of
playing children]
Celina, vamos!
[giggles]
Celina!
Celina.
- Officer Chambers! Hey!
- [chuckles]
I thought I might see you at
the cemetery this morning.
Well, I...
I must have missed you.
You know, I saw the picture
of your graduation.
But it's a whole other thing
in person.
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you.
There's someone
I want you to meet.
This is my TO, John Nolan.
This is Officer Joel Chambers.
- Pleasure.
- Nice to meet you.
Yeah, Joel's one of the cops
who helped look for Blanca.
Joel Chambers.
Thank you, sir.
I don't remember seeing
your name on the report.
Yeah, we've been going over
the case file.
I...I didn't, uh,
write a Form 3.
In a case like this,
everyone just pitches in.
Right.
Now, when we found her,
when she was in the hospital,
Joel visited every day.
I have something.
It's a shoe print.
- Excuse me.
[clears throat]
Can I offer a hand?
- Oh, sorry.
I can't let anyone inside
without detective approval.
I...I promise
I know better than to
contaminate a crime scene.
[chuckles]
- Rules are rules.
- Of course.
She's a good kid.
[phone ringing]
Smitty, what's up?
I don't want you to worry
about the detective's exam.
I'm on it.
- Wait, what?
- Leave it to Smitty.
- No, Smitty.
Please don't...
[call disconnects]
God.
He hung up.
So you won't be
making detective.
But, um, there's other
career paths, right?
This the guy that
Delgado mentioned?
Yeah, Drew Heslov.
Back in the aughts he did
five years for
lewd acts with a minor.
He's been on probation
ever since.
We are less than a mile
from Olivia's house.
- Officers.
- Can we come in?
We both know
I can't stop you.
Mm-hmm.
Where were you between 10:00
and 11:00 this morning?
Why?
What happened?
Sir, just answer
the question.
[sighs] I was here.
Alone?
Yeah.
Move aside.
[groans]
That's a gift.
Really? For who?
One of my nieces.
You don't have any nieces.
I like dolls.
That's not a crime.
Per the terms of
your probation,
you're not allowed to own
children's toys.
This is harassment!
I think you two should leave.
Sit down.
Now.
Do not move,
do not touch anything,
or you will be in violation of
your probation.
7-Adam-7.
We need additional units
to 7858 West Cedar.
Detectives.
You have a minute?
- What's up?
Earlier today,
an officer dropped by.
He worked Blanca's case
back in the day.
According to Celina,
he visited constantly.
- A little overinvolved?
- Maybe.
And today,
he tried to get inside
the crime scene's
inner perimeter.
Maybe these kinds of cases
hit home for him
and he wants to help.
Or maybe he wanted
an excuse for his DNA
to be at the scene.
I looked into him.
He had a daughter,
lost custody of her
when she was six years old.
The same age as
the missing girls.
And today was
his daughter's birthday.
[helicopter whirring]
Look, I know it's not
a slam dunk, but I think
it deserves a closer look.
Nolan is right.
There's something off
about Officer Chambers.
How do you want to proceed?
Joel's been on duty
all morning.
We want to check
his shop's GPS,
see if he went anywhere
near her house.
He has a history with
Olivia's family.
I can bring him in
under the guise of
needing background intel.
- Good.
The minute he realizes
he's a suspect,
he'll ask for his reps
and shut down.
Lucy and Aaron
have a new suspect.
I'll check in with them
and report back.
All right. Keep me posted.
Do you see that?
Harper and Lopez are making
secret calls in their car.
They'll update us when
they get something concrete.
You know what's going on.
If you're keeping
something from me
because you think
I'm too close to the case,
please don't.
How well do you know Joel?
Yeah, we've kept in touch.
Why?
Does he ever talk about
his daughter,
the one he lost custody of
when she was six?
No.
Wait. You...you don't...
you don't think he did this?
Did you know today is
her birthday?
So you think...what,
he just takes these girls
to replace her?
Maybe. It's a theory.
No, it's a coincidence.
Maybe that's why
he gets involved,
because it reminds him of her.
Okay, I know this is hard
for you to hear...
Hard to hear?
He's the reason I'm a cop...
because of him.
Listen, you're wrong,
and he didn't do this.
- Find anything?
- No sign of Olivia.
He could have built
all sorts of hidden areas
over the years.
We need dogs and infrared.
Already requested.
Mr. Heslov,
I'm Detective Lopez.
Does the name Olivia Vargas
mean anything to you?
That's what all this
is about?
You think I did
something to her?
Answer the question.
Have you ever met
Olivia Vargas?
Ah, it's hard to say.
A picture might jog my memory.
Yes or no.
Come on.
Give me a few details.
We are going to
turn this house inside out.
If we so much as find a hair
that doesn't belong here,
you're going to prison.
Do you need details on that,
or do you remember
what it's like
to be a pedophile behind bars?
These cases are the worst,
just every parent's nightmare.
You have kids?
- Yeah, a daughter.
Losing her would destroy me.
So if you need any help,
I'm here.
He's wearing different shoes.
Are you sure?
I am.
His other ones had
a zipper on the side,
so they don't have to be tied.
Yeah, he saw that we found
a shoe print at the scene.
Probably threw the old ones
in the LA river.
I mean, or his old ones were uncomfortable,
or Nolan's wrong.
Celina, I'm aware
of the history.
But if you can't examine
the facts objectively...
Sorry. I'm...I'm good.
Joel was called
to Olivia's house
several times before
the abduction.
He was also called to
the second and third victims'
homes.
We gotta know if Blanca fits
the same pattern.
Bring Carla in.
Let's see what she remembers.
There's no record of
an arrest
or any sort of calls made to
our house.
And only your mom knows
for sure.
We'll find out.
According to the logs,
Joel was at a premise check
at a warehouse
at the time of the abduction.
GPS on the shop says that
he was there 30 minutes.
How far is the warehouse
from Olivia's house?
Far enough
he would have to drive.
Or maybe he had
a car stashed there.
Look, I can go to the location,
drive the route from
Olivia's and back,
see if it even works.
- Keep me updated.
- Yeah.
So according to the file,
you answered a 415 at
Olivia's house.
That's right.
It was about a month ago.
The neighbor called it in.
Olivia's mom was kicking out
her most recent
deadbeat boyfriend.
Yeah, we are actually
looking into him.
And did you see Olivia?
Yeah, she was
hiding in a corner.
Pretty badly shaken.
She begged me not to
take her mom away.
- And you didn't?
- No signs of abuse.
There wasn't much I could do
but refer them
to Child Protective Services.
You ask me,
we're far too lenient
with parents.
You'll get no argument
from me there.
CPS is overwhelmed.
Even when there's abuse,
the parents get them back
half the time.
It is maddening.
I mean, so many deserving
parents out there
just struggling through
the adoption process.
Exactly.
You also participated in
the search for Celina's sister?
Is that right?
It is.
Why? You don't think
the two cases are related?
Oh, it's just an avenue
we're exploring.
[exhales heavily]
Oh.
I really need to get home.
My birds are...
I know, okay,
but this is important.
We'll get you home
just as soon as we can.
We just need to know
if you remember meeting
an Officer Joel Chambers.
Of course.
He was very helpful.
He...he still checks in on me
years later.
And when did you
first meet him?
[sighs]
It was such a long time ago.
Mami, I need you
to tell me everything,
no matter how upsetting.
There were so many
police officers around.
Okay, so you met him
after Blanca was taken?
- I guess so.
- Mami!
Celina.
[soft tense music]
Look... I get it.
I...I used to think
you wouldn't leave the house
because you didn't
have answers,
because everyone
you crossed on the street
could be her killer,
but I understand now.
You left once and
the world ended,
so you never left again.
Guilt is what's kept you
locked away.
And the only way out is
to tell the truth.
♪ ♪
Okay.
About a month before
Blanca got taken...
Officer Chambers found me
passed out in my car.
I was high.
I had drugs on me.
I begged him not to arrest me.
I told him I had to get home
to you and your sister.
And he drove me home.
Did he talk to
your daughters at all?
[sniffles]
He waited in his car.
And I went and
brought them outside.
He watched us play, and...
and then he drove away.
I'll let Harper know.
Wait.
You don't think he took her?
We're not sure yet.
I was so grateful
he didn't arrest me.
I never thought...
[breathes shakily]
Is that the reason
he took Blanca?
Because of me?
[sobbing]
[notification chimes]
Uh, just one more thing.
We talked to Celina's mom, Carla.
She says you picked her up
before the kidnapping?
You could have arrested her
and you didn't.
- Really?
- Yeah,
You said you didn't
meet them until
after Celina's sister
went missing.
Oh.
Uh, I guess I forgot.
- Ah.
You meet so many people
in our line of work.
You remember everyone
that you picked up
when you were on patrol?
- Oh, God, not a chance.
I have two kids, so I can
barely remember breakfast.
Uh, give me a minute, will you?
- Of course.
Hey, am I free to go?
It'll just be a second.
Detective Lopez.
Found something.
What is it?
[dramatic music]
According to Tim,
Joel had plenty of time
to drive from the premise shack
to Olivia's house.
Just because he could have
doesn't mean he did.
I saw his face when
I caught him in the lie.
He was terrified.
Well, do you think
you could get more
if you keep questioning him?
No.
He asked if he was free to go.
He knows he's a suspect.
He's forcing you
to show your hand.
[phone ringing]
Angela, you're on speakerphone
with Wesley and Nyla.
We found something at
Drew's house.
It's Olivia's teddy bear.
Drew's our guy. He took her.
[distorted voices echoing]
[ringing music]
♪ ♪
[echoing] Celina.
Celina.
- Celina.
- Yes.
Lopez wants him
in interview three.
Yes, right.
So this means
Joel's innocent, right?
We don't know
anything for sure.
Hey, you sure it's
Olivia's teddy bear?
Lab's working on
a DNA match now,
and Olivia's mom IDed it
as hers.
So where does that leave us
in the Joel theory?
I still like Joel.
He has been overly involved
in both cases,
and he lied to us
about his prior contact
with Celina's mother.
Yeah, but any good
defense attorney will argue
that his only crime is
caring too much.
Both abductions happened on
his daughter's birthday.
Coincidence?
Well, that's why
he got so involved.
He saw his daughter in
these two girls.
It's shaky, but you only need
one jury member to buy that.
The teddy bear,
on the other hand,
Drew's lawyer will have a hell
of a time explaining that away.
You found it in his backyard.
Anyone could've gained access.
Look, if you are Joel,
you know that they found
a boot print.
The first thing you do is
throw those boots away.
The second thing you do is
throw suspicion
on someone else.
He knew Drew was
a suspect back in the day,
the perfect patsy.
I can sell that.
Okay, we're a long way
from a jury.
There's a missing girl
out there.
She's the priority.
Can you press Joel,
get a confession?
No, he knows I'm onto him.
We could arrest.
- But that starts a clock.
We have 72 hours
to bring charges.
And we're not ready for that.
Then we let him go.
Keep working Drew.
On it.
So I wanted you to be
the first to know,
we got him.
- Really?
- I don't know if you remember
the guy from Blanca's case,
Drew Heslov?
Yeah, he had
a prior conviction.
Yep, that's the guy.
They found Olivia's teddy bear
in his yard.
Did you bring him in?
Yeah, he's in processing
right now.
Huh.
- So thank you...
- Oh.
- For all of your help.
- Of course, of course.
Listen, it's time
for me to clock out,
but if you need anything else,
you got my cell.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
We need a surveillance team.
That's six cops now out there
looking for Olivia.
I told him that we found
Olivia's teddy bear,
but he did not ask
about Olivia.
He doesn't need to.
He knows exactly where she is.
I am telling you, it is Joel.
We can't let him
out of our sight.
Let's alert metro.
[radio chirps]
Walking to
his personal vehicle,
silver pickup truck.
California plates, two, George,
Adam, Tom, one, two, three.
[engine starts]
North Compass Point has him,
westbound Whilshire.
Number two lane,
approaching a stale green.
Two for cover.
Wheatley, Bradford.
- Go for Wheatley.
Confirm we have
all six units on this,
four compass points,
two rovers.
- Affirm, boss.
- Good.
Everyone keep radios low,
cover coats on,
and be ready for crazy Ivans.
He may do a counter.
We cannot let him get away.
Can you ID this item?
Aw, it's a teddy bear.
Was it hers, that Olivia kid
you were asking about?
- Yes.
- Oh, she must be young.
Eight years old?
Younger?
Have you ever seen this item
before?
No.
Then how do you explain
its presence in your backyard?
What?
How did Olivia's favorite toy
come into your possession?
[handcuffs clatter]
- It didn't.
I don't know.
You're lying.
- I'm not lying.
We found it in your backyard.
No!
[sighs]
Look, I know what I am.
I know what I've done.
But I swear, I've never
laid eyes on that kid.
[tense music]
Bradford, this is Wheatley.
Target has landed
in the parking
of a home improvement store.
I'm pulling into the other
entrance to the parking lot.
All right, Bradford copies.
All units compass up.
Standby for roll call in three.
Target is making contact
with another subject.
Male, white, blue jacket,
black pants.
Target is handing the subject
his gym bag.
Subject number two is
walking away with the gym bag.
All units, stay with primary.
Confirm, you don't want
anyone going with
that secondary?
No, no. He knows
he's under surveillance.
He's trying to split the team.
Secondary is approaching
a black Charger.
He'll be away in five, four,
three, two...
Miller, Jones, Clark,
go with secondary.
Wheatley, Smith, and I will
stay with primary.
And get me six
additional units ASAP.
Copy that. Secondary units,
work off encrypted channel 18.
Bradford on point.
Primary's approaching
a motorcyclist.
They're talking.
Primary is taking
the motorcycle.
I have eyes on primary.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Wheatley, Bradford,
what's the ETA on
those additional units?
ETA nine minutes.
Copy that.
We have a fresh green.
Looks like
he's picking up speed.
He knows we're here.
I just hit the lights.
[siren wailing]
[rock music]
♪ ♪
Control, can I get
an airship assist?
Metro, Pico and Washington.
Copy, Air 5 is closest.
She's en route.
ETA 3 minutes.
Speeds approaching 100.
Sarge, I can stay with him.
He's now 120,
getting on the 405 North.
- On the shoulder.
- Negative, shut it down.
- Sarge, he took a kid!
- Speed's 130.
Negative, shut it down.
It's not worth plowing into
some innocent family.
Copy that. Shutting down.
[sirens wailing]
Primary is gone.
Damn it.
- You let him get away?
- Celina.
- Excuse me?
- Joel has her.
I mean, he's probably on
his way to kill her right now.
We're all aware of
the situation, Officer Juarez.
Okay, then why weren't there
more units?
I mean, how could this happen?
My apologies, sergeants.
Officer Juarez, Joel is a cop.
He knew our techniques,
and he used them against us.
There's nothing metro
could have done.
He is gone.
The only question now is where?
- Where could he be?
- Better.
Listen up.
Our suspect is a cop.
He's been meticulous and smart
every step of the way.
We need to be smarter.
No one pulls
something like this off
without leaving a trail.
Find it.
Let's go.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Uh, sorry,
I just needed a minute.
Oh, of course.
You know,
I never knew my father.
When I was little,
I used to wish Joel...
What do I tell Olivia's mom?
I mean, she's so scared.
She's counting on us
to find her.
- And we will.
- But what if we're too late?
What if we have to tell her
that Olivia's gone,
and it's our fault that we...
- Okay.
Maybe you need to take
a little break.
I can't. I can't do anything
else until we find her.
Sarge?
Looks like
they've got something.
We've been combing through
Joel's unit history,
every name, address,
license plate he logged
while on duty over
the last three months.
Yeah, six weeks ago,
he cleared a pair of squatters
out of a foreclosed home.
It's a low income area,
mostly industrial.
But you could easily get
in and out
without anyone noticing.
- That's a slim lead.
Yeah, except it's less than a
mile away from Olivia's house,
and he cleared it three days
after he first met the family.
He was getting
everything in place.
Okay, well, then that's it.
Olivia's there.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
All inbound units,
metro unit on scene.
Vehicle registered to our
suspect is parked out front.
No sign of our 207 victim.
Second team is 9-7.
We're in the alley behind
target on Sheldon.
All right,
we need eyes inside.
Let's get a ball cam ready.
What's the play?
We need to get
a better look inside,
see how much firepower's
in there.
Ball cam's live.
[soft tense music]
♪ ♪
Okay, I can see him.
He can see us.
- What about Olivia?
- No sign of her.
So we breach, right?
I mean, we have to find her.
If she's alive, that's
a sure way to change that.
We need to get him talking.
Her best chance is
if we can end this
without firing a shot.
You give me some cover,
I'll get a phone to Joel.
Phone drop.
Get ready to approach.
♪ ♪
Joel, we're just gonna
throw a phone
on the other side
of the door, all right?
All we want to do is talk,
settle this before anyone
gets hurt.
♪ ♪
I confirm suspect has
a 9 millimeter
in his right hand.
No other weapons are visible.
[whirring]
Wait, what was that?
Turn it around.
She's out cold.
Probably drugged.
[gunshot echoes]
What was that?
He shot the camera.
[phone rings]
- This is Sergeant Bradford.
Did you think
I wouldn't notice
your little eye rolling around?
You know I had to
take a look,
assess the situation.
- Who's that?
- [shushes softly]
Is that Olivia?
No more cameras
and get your guys back.
I can do that for you
but I need you to do something
for me.
I need to make sure
Olivia's okay.
She's fine.
I'm protecting her.
Okay, that's great.
But it would help
if we could see her.
No, not a chance.
I show my face,
you're gonna blow it off.
[line disconnects]
He thinks
he's protecting her.
That's gotta be
a good thing, right?
He thought he was
protecting Blanca too.
He's probably justifying
the murders,
death being better than
the life they were living.
Yeah, but if he's not
willing to talk,
then we need to go in.
[line ringing]
[phone rings]
I am done talking.
It's me. It's Celina.
Joel?
Yeah.
I'm outside.
Listen, I...I know that
you don't understand.
Her parents didn't deserve her.
- I know.
You did it to keep her safe,
just like the others,
just like...like Blanca.
I think they remind you
of your daughter.
I just want to be
a father again.
Why don't they understand?
They just keep crying and
begging to go back home.
I gave them a better life
than they ever had,
and they want to go back to
some loser drug addict?
Tell him
what he wants to hear.
You're right.
They needed you.
They...they needed a father,
someone to...
to guide them, to...
to keep them safe.
But Olivia's not safe
right now, is she?
Not with all these
guns outside.
We need to get her
out of that house.
We're not leaving.
I don't trust anyone out there.
Okay, well, then
what about me?
How about I...
I come get Olivia?
Joel, it's over.
You need to know that.
End it by doing what
you wanted to do.
End it by protecting her.
[call disconnects]
Do you think
he's gonna let her go?
- I don't know.
- All right, we're in position.
As soon as she's clear,
we breach.
Celina!
- Celina, hey!
We're good.
Look alive.
Move, move.
- [whimpers]
- It's all clear.
Breach.
[door slams]
Go, go, go.
Clear.
Clear in here.
- Clear.
Good.
There. Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Clear.
Clear!
[faint rustling]
Clear.
[suspenseful music]
Drop the gun.
♪ ♪
Drop the gun!
Drop it!
[gunshot]
Suspect down. Send an RA.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Hey, Harper.
Um...
Tim is still in with IA.
Look, the officer involved
shooting interview
is very thorough.
Tim's fine.
- Right.
Hey, Chen.
I've got news for you.
It's not a great time, Smitty.
It's about
the detective exam.
The detective blocking you
is Prim.
He heard about your little
scheme to help Bradford
and was less than impressed.
Oh, the five player trade.
Turns out treating people
like puppets
wasn't the best way to
make friends.
Thank you, Smitty.
I did warn you.
I know.
Hey.
Let him talk to Grey first.
Hey, come in.
All done with IA?
Uh, yeah.
I'm sure you'll be cleared to
return to work in no time.
I hope so.
Hey.
You know you had to
take the shot.
I know.
Just 'cause he wanted to die
doesn't mean
he wasn't dangerous.
I know.
[sighs]
Is there anything I can do?
Can I get back to you
on that?
Take your time.
You know, it's her first time
visiting Blanca's grave.
I honestly never thought
she'd make it here.
How was she on
the drive over?
Shaky. She didn't say a word.
She's still not here...
Blanca.
And I think I know why.
She moved on.
She knows I don't need her anymore.
You want to go join your mom?
I brought him into our lives.
No, he preyed on
your illness.
You can't blame yourself.
[voice breaking]
But I do.
And I blame myself for
all the days and weeks
leading up to it.
I was barely there.
Short-tempered,
sleeping all the time.
[sighs tearfully]
They were the last days of
her life,
and I wasted them.
You were addicted.
It's not your fault.
Mama, I know you can't forgive
yourself, but...
I want you to know that
I forgive you.
[soft hopeful music]
[sobs]
Oh, baby.
[sobs softly]
I forgive you.
♪ But it's over ♪
I'm sorry.
Jack is asleep.
And according to my watch,
I paced up and down our hallway
for a total of 12 miles.
[sighs]
I thought that was impressive.
What's this?
A mommy blogger posted
top 10 ways to prevent
your kid from getting taken.
You know the vast majority of
missing kids are taken by a...
A non-custodial parent.
I know.
This was a hard case.
♪ Set my soul on fire ♪
♪ Take me to the light ♪
Celina's mom...
I don't know how
you survive that.
♪ Set my soul on fire ♪
♪ Take us to the light ♪
If you're worried about
Jack's safety,
we could always have
Charlie come back.
Charlie?
Oh, the smoking hot
ex-SAS bodyguard?
I'm not saying I want that.
Just thinking about
your peace of mind.
- Hmm, how selfless.
- [laughs]
You are a bad ass.
And I'm no slouch.
Jack and the new baby
are gonna be safe.
Okay?
♪ You wouldn't recognize me
now ♪
Yeah.
[crying]
I'll get him.
[continues crying]
♪ Till it's full of hope,
set my soul on fire ♪
"AirTag your kids"?
[scoffs] No.
♪ ♪
Mm...no.
How are you doing
with everything?
I'll be okay.
You know,
maybe you should try...
Exercise before going to bed?
Yeah, I know.
It's not the first time I...
No, I...I know it isn't.
I know that. I just...
I...I want to be helpful.
I know.
Thank you.
You need help studying?
There's no way
I would have scored
as well on the sergeant's
exam without you.
That's true.
You owe me.
- I don't owe you.
- You owe me.
♪ Set my soul on fire ♪
Okay.
We saved a kid,
solved a cold case,
and helped our friend
find closure.
And there's still technically
three hours left
on my day off.
- Oh, there are?
I can finally rest.
Oh, I'm sorry I can't let you
get any rest tonight.
I have plans for you.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, yeah.
So settle in for
a nice, long night of...
catching up on "The Bachelor."
Oh, there's gonna be
limo arrivals
and rose ceremonies.
Sadly, lots of crying.
For every dream realized,
a hope will be dashed.
Honey?
Baby?
♪ ♪
If you don't want me to watch
ahead without you, just say so.
I love you too.
[upbeat hip-hop music]
♪ ♪
Damn it.