And just for safety,
place your hands
- on the hood for me.
- [ Sighs ] Damn.
Do you have any weapons
on you?
Anything that's
gonna stick me?
Yeah. I got a foldable knife
in my back pocket
- for self-defense.
- Alright. Uh,
just keep your hands
on the hood for me.
Don't reach for anything,
alright?
Yes, sir.
Ah. Thank you.
Oh, uh, and I have
a small knife around my neck.
You have a knife
around your neck?
In case I can't reach
the one in my waistband.
Right.
[ Blade scraping ]
♪ Look ♪
That's treacherous.
Two there.
Got those.
♪ I'm in the city, just
livin', you can't control me ♪
♪ Seeing all the phony homies
try to hold me ♪
Care... Careful with that one.
[ Keys jingling ]
♪ This road is lonely, huh ♪
Right.
♪ When you know the code,
you gon' need to prevail ♪
Nolan:
Anything else I'm missing?
Any more? Oh.
Oh, that's my balisong.
That... That one's
from the Philippines.
Oh. [ Chuckles ] Oh, that's...
That's... that's a neat one.
It looks like a money clip,
but it's actually a...
It's actually a knife.
[♪♪]
I hate to ask you
what's in your car.
No weapons in there.
♪ I'm-a live my life right ♪
- But, uh...
- But?
[ Growling, rattling ]
Uh, Nolan?
The trunk is growling.
[ Growling continues ]
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
*THE ROOKIE*
[♪♪]
Season 05  Episode 06
Episode Title: "The Reckoning"
Aired on: October 30, 2022.
Since the winner
of this little contest
gets to pick
where we get married,
I'mma just go ahead
and call it right now.
We're getting married
on the beach right here
in beautiful,
sunny Southern California.
Shh, shh. Shh, shh.
Listen. Do you hear that?
It's the smell of victory.
Correction. After I win,
you'll be smelling beignets
in the French Quarter after
our wedding in New Orleans.
[ Upbeat music plays ]
- Oh. Careful.
- Alright.
Here we go.
[♪♪]
Ten to seven.
I win.
My stack is clearly higher.
That is not the contest.
Fair enough. You win.
Alright.
It is...
20 to 20.
We're tied again.
We need another contest.
Bet I can eat mine faster.
Is it possible
we're too competitive?
If you want to quit,
just say so.
Say you're a quitter.
Fork me.
[♪♪]
Ready, set...
W... Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Without syrup?
What are we, animals?
Hey. The sitter's available
after all.
You still want
to go to dinner?
People on television:
♪ ...early in the morning ♪
Wesley?
[ Laughter ]
Sorry. Um, what was
the question?
You're not worried
about the deposition, are you?
The defense are just
throwing stuff against the wall.
Yeah. Well, the more
that they throw,
the more likely
something will stick.
And if something sticks,
Elijah could walk.
That won't happen.
They can depose me, Grey, half
of the Mid-Wilshire station...
It won't change
who Elijah Stone is.
I just wish I knew more
about the strategy.
I don't even know
who his defense attorney is.
And the DA's office
has a firewall
between me and anything
relating to Elijah Stone.
The RICO case against
Elijah is solid.
They're just desperate.
That's what worries me.
RICO means anyone involved
in the organization is on the hook.
I was a part
of the organization.
Under duress.
And his lawyers can't argue
that you were a mob lawyer
without admitting that
their client is a mobster.
You're right.
Of course,
because you're always right.
I'm going.
Think about where you wanna go
for our date night.
[ Smooches ]
Love you.
I love you, too.
[ Door opens ]
Take my advice...
you want to put a tennis racket
in her hand tomorrow.
Oh, I was hoping we had
a swimmer on our hands.
Whatever gets her
a full ride.
Trust me. You don't want to
know what we're paying
for Dominique's tuition.
What happened?
Leah okay?
- Leah's fine.
- Hey.
We had a minor accident
with the breast milk
you left in the fridge.
Oh, you mean the breast milk
that I woke up at 5:00 a. m.
This morning to pump?
That breast milk?
Yes.
Mm-kay.
Mama is gon' feed
her sweet little baby.
[ Smooches, laughs ]
Daddy... Daddy's gonna wait
in the hot car.
One more thing.
Uh, and I want to preface this
by saying
I'm just the messenger.
What is it?
Lila's best friend,
Jenny,
canceled trick or treating
tomorrow night.
Why? What happened?
Her mom didn't say,
but she left an awkward
message, though.
Okay. You have a theory.
What is it?
They may not be comfortable
with the whole law -enforcement,
gun-in-the-house thing.
You know, um,
just a wild guess.
You... You are
on one today.
[ Yawns ]
Nolan: The hours
take some getting used to.
Mm-hmm. My REM cycle's
all over the place.
I wasn't like this
at the academy.
Yeah, I had something similar
when I first started.
I know it's hard, but you got
to make sleep a priority.
[ Grunts ] Man, I'm, like,
wide awake
by the time my head
hits the pillow.
When Henry was a baby,
we tried everything
to get him to sleep...
Soothing music,
so many road trips
I'm sure we single-handedly
destroyed
the environment,
and a swaddling technique
I can still do in my sleep.
Hmm, I don't think any of this
applies to me.
Didn't a doctor just pull
a bullet out of you?
Like, shouldn't you
be resting?
It was an old bullet.
I'm fine.
What?
I overheard you talking
to Ashley
about picking up some
of your things from her place.
So look, if you want to talk
about it, we can t...
[♪♪]
[ Laughter ]
Hello. Good morning.
Chen. Sanford.
[ Telephones ringing
in distance ]
What's up with him?
He's just grumpy with
everything he's got going on.
Wait.
What... What's going on?
Nothing.
What?
He's fine. I'm fine.
We're just eager to protect
and serve.
Aaron.
I have to go. I'm so sorry.
What?
[ Police radio chatter ]
I, uh...
I found this checklist online.
No screens, thermostat at 68,
meditation, lavender oil.
No luck.
Red light. Red light.
Red light!
[ Tires screech ]
Sorry.
Dispatcher: 7-Adam-15.
Suspicious circumstance
at 12952 South Flower Street.
10-66. Female and
a bank transaction.
More to your box.
[ Sighs ] Copy that.
7-Adam-15, show us responding.
Switch places.
I'm driving.
No. I'm good. I'm good.
No. Not good enough.
When you are sleep deprived,
both your judgment
and your reflexes
are impaired.
It's no better
than being intoxicated.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
We switch.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
What's the problem?
Oh. Our alert system
flagged several bills
this young woman attempted
to deposit.
Counterfeit?
No, looks like they're
connected to some kind
of law enforcement
investigation.
Hi. I-I'm just trying
to make a deposit.
- What's going on?
- Uh, may I get your name?
Macy Tomkins.
And do you have any ID?
[ Pen clicks ]
And where did you get the
bills you were trying to deposit?
I had a garage sale
over the weekend.
Made $1,000
on a designer handbag.
Should've gotten more,
if you want to know the truth.
I don't suppose you got a name
or description
of the person who bought it.
Mm, Brent wood housewife.
Yoga pants.
Right. Any cameras around
where you live?
No.
Okay.
I'm just gonna have to get
a little more information
from you.
Celina, will you start
an FI card? We...
[ Snoring ]
Nolan: Officer Juarez.
[♪♪]
Welcome back.
[ Indistinct conversations,
telephones ringing ]
Monica.
What are you doing here?
Nobody told you?
Told me what?
I'm here for the deposition.
Elijah Stone is my client.
Um... that is a mistake.
You do not want to be
in his orbit.
I'm billing him
$800 an hour.
It's a nice orbit.
You read all the discovery.
You know what he did to me.
I know what you allege
he did to you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Uh, the court reporter
is still setting up inside,
but I could take you back,
if you'd like.
Great. I just need
to make a quick call
before we get started.
Yeah. Sure.
Excuse me.
[ Scoffs ]
You know Elijah's attorney?
We went to
law school together.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Is there anything in her bag
of tricks we should look out for?
She's smart, fairly ruthless,
and God forbid you leave
the toilet seat up.
We used to be engaged.
Maybe you should've led
with that.
Mm-hmm.
[ Police radio chatter ]
We're not talking
about it.
Look, I'm just saying
if you want to talk
about the breakup,
I'm here.
I don't.
Look, tomorrow's Halloween.
The crazies are gonna be out
in full force,
so let's just focus
on our job. Alright?
Alright.
Werewolf.
What?
She looks like she needs a hand.
We should stop.
[ Vehicles passing,
dogs barking ]
Morning.
Looks like you need some help.
I have to get this prop to set
or I'm screwed.
Okay. Well, uh, we'll get
your friend here loaded up,
and you'll be
on your way in no time.
Thank you.
So, what are you,
like, a P. A. Or...
I'm a director.
I'm shooting a short film,
but I lose my location
in an hour.
That is so cool.
You hear what she said?
- Tim: Hmm.
- She's a director.
- Oh. Yeah.
- Okay.
Help her get to set.
She's losing daylight.
Right.
[♪♪]
You know what?
I just need a better...
I need a better angle.
[ Walkie talkie chirps ]
7-Adam-100.
Show us Code 6
at Bronson and Rosewood...
- Stalled vehicle blocking traffic.
- [ Grunting ]
[♪♪]
Hang on.
Wait, wait. Hold on.
You shouldn't be lifting
anything.
I mean, you just had
major surgery.
You did?
I can handle this.
No, I didn't have major
surgery. I-I'm fine.
- Lift on three.
- Okay.
- Alright. One, two, three.
- Yeah.
- [ Grunting ]
- Lift.
[ Grunts ] Yeah.
- Let's go! Push!
- I'm pushing!
Do you want me
to call someone?
Both: No!
- I had back surgery, remember?
- Oh! My leg. My leg.
Oh! My knee. My knee.
My knee. My knee.
[ Groans ]
You good?
- [ Exhales deeply ] Yeah.
- Thank you. Both of you.
Yeah. Happy to help.
[ Cellphone ringing, click ]
Yeah. Bradford.
No.
I assigned Siega to that.
So, uh, what's your short about?
Like, werewolves versus zombies?
The lycanthrope is a metaphor
for the patriarchy's assault
on bodily autonomy.
Wow.
No, I never got it.
[ Engine starts ]
So, uh, you know,
maybe I can, uh,
take you out for coffee
and you can tell me more?
No, thanks.
[ Hand taps ]
No. No. Don't do anything.
I'll be right there.
Let's go.
Dispatcher: 7-Adam-15. Possible
arson at Elm and West Sixth.
[ Fire crackling,
indistinct talking on radio ]
Nolan: Just the firefighter
I wanted to see!
[ Vehicle doors close ]
I was thinking...
Since we are tied,
how about tonight,
we have a little
Lego-building
competition?
You were a contractor.
I didn't build houses
out of Lego.
I think we should do
something intellectual,
like learn a new language
and see who's more fluent
at the end of the month.
Oh.
Japanese?
You taught English
in Kyoto.
[ Sighs ] I was hoping
you wouldn't remember.
I remember everything
you tell me.
Uh-huh. What did I ask you
to pick up
from the store after work?
Milk. Eggs. Bread?
- Pops...
- Popsicles.
- Guys? See?
- I remember everything.
[ Sirens wailing ]
Looks like somebody
had money to burn.
[♪♪]
I'm very tired.
Maybe the money was cursed.
You know,
fire is very cleansing.
It's used in all sorts
of rituals.
Or it could be
something else.
Or someone was trying to hide
evidence of an old crime.
Tracking device.
Why old crime?
Well,
tracking devices nowadays
are all microchips
and GPS.
This thing's got to be
at least 10 years old.
I'm guessing... federal.
Maybe DEA or FBI.
So the money was part
of a law-enforcement sting?
That seems likely.
But why burn it now?
We figure that out by finding
out whose tracker this is.
Drive safe.
Hey.
Uh, I'm not sure
who to talk to.
Yeah.
What's the problem?
Um, these cops stopped
to help me,
and one of them
left his radio behind.
Yeah. I can take that.
Did you happen
to catch their name?
One of them looked exactly
like that guy
from that murder documentary,
but I think the radio belonged
to the broody one. Oh.
The broody...
Tim forgot his radio?
Tim Bradford, super cop?
You know, this guy will not
let me forget that I was once
three and a half minutes
late to roll call.
Can you believe that?
I... guess.
This feels like Christmas.
Thank you.
Cool. So you'll get it
back to him?
Yeah, I got it.
You have a nice day.
[ Engine revs ]
[♪♪]
[ Clicks tongue ]
How did you become involved
in the sting operation
against Elijah Stone?
I raised my concerns
about his criminal enterprise
to the LAPD.
Paint me a picture.
You went to the front desk
at Mid-Wilshire.
And then what?
Well, I didn't go
through the front desk.
Oh. I guess I'm confused.
In your own words,
describe the first time
you brought up Mr. Stone's
alleged crimes to the LAPD.
I raised my concerns
with Detective Angela Lopez.
At her desk?
In our living room.
They're married.
But you know that already.
- Oh. That's right.
- Mm.
It's in my notes.
Um, and this sting operation
was allowed to proceed
despite an obvious and
egregious conflict of interest?
Well, we had a mutual interest
in the truth.
Is it common for detectives to
work cases involving relatives?
No.
And why is that?
I think there's a concern
that the detectives won't view
the evidence objectively,
but I don't think that's
an issue here. Interesting.
Next question...
Uh, can I finish...
Moving on.
Let's just move on.
I'm telling you,
it's not in the shop.
Well, it didn't just
jump off my hip.
[ Sighs ] Let me check
this bag again.
[ Plastic crinkling ]
[ Hand thuds ]
The werewolf.
I put down my radio to
help you lift that dumb prop.
The director must have it.
Did you get her number?
Almost.
[ Hand thuds,
cellphone chimes ]
[ Sighs ]
[♪♪]
What the hell?
What is it?
[♪♪]
Who sent that?
Someone who's about to get
in a lot of trouble.
You know, uh,
you could just file
an incident report
and get a new radio, right?
And get written up?
That's one day's suspension
without pay.
[♪♪]
I think I know where this is.
Let's go.
Bailing on Halloween
is so passive-aggressive.
I mean, if you have a problem
with me being a cop
or having a gun at my house,
then just tell me.
Agreed.
But if that's the issue,
have James invite them over
for dinner tonight.
Show them your gun safe.
Everyone loves James.
People love me, too.
For sure.
I, for example, adore you.
Most people
find you terrifying.
Right back at you.
I know. It's why we're
so good together.
[ Chuckles ]
Alright. Fine.
I will have James invite them
to dinner.
Uh, hi. Nyla Harper.
We spoke on the phone.
This is Angela Lopez.
Xavier. Thanks for diving
right in on this.
Of course.
I can't believe we haven't
worked together before...
All the LAPD/DEA task forces
you were on.
Yeah. I never worked anything
that took me to the Midwest.
Smart. Undercover gets a whole
lot more uncomfortable
when it's negative 20 out.
[ Knock on door ]
Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
You wanted to see us?
Uh, yes. Officers Nolan
and Juarez.
They found the burned cash
and your old tracker.
Thank you. You don't know what
it means to finally have a lead.
We're happy to help.
A lead on what, exactly?
Ten years ago, my partner,
Robert Buckley, set up a buy
with a mid-level trafficker
named Winslow Harris.
Rob had been deep undercover
for months,
and this was a big break...
A chance to get real intel
on Harris' operation.
It sounds like it
didn't go as planned.
To this day...
I'm not sure what happened.
We found Rob's body
a week later.
The tracker failed,
the money disappeared,
and no one's heard
from Harris since.
[Quietly] Huh.
The money is cursed.
- I'm sorry. What?
- It's nothing.
Fast-forward to today,
when money from the old sting
set off alarms
at a local bank.
Okay. Wait.
The dumpster fire
and garage-sale chick
are connected?
Macy Tomkins.
I ran info on her...
Spotty employment history,
a few overdue parking tickets.
No criminal record.
It can't be a coincidence
that the bills were flagged
at the bank and the rest of
them were burned an hour later.
It seems clear Macy was lying
about where she got the money.
Question is, how does
she connect to Winslow?
Let's go ask her.
Man, this is one sketchy-ass
looking coffee truck.
This is where I get my coffee
every morning.
No Oat Milk Mafia hipsters
rewriting screenplays.
Buck for coffee
and you go to work.
You sound like
the old dude from "Up."
- Hey, Johnnie.
- Johnnie: Hi.
Anyone drop off this radio?
Nope. No.
Alright. Thank you.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
[♪♪]
Damn it.
They're running us
all over town.
[♪♪]
Okay. So, like,
what's the point?
I mean, they haven't asked
for money or anything,
and if they really wanted
to screw with the police,
they could do a whole lot more
with that radio.
I don't know.
We got to figure out
which studio lot that is.
[ Police radio chatter ]
Must have been hard,
all those years
not knowing what happened
to your partner.
Yeah.
He wasn't just your partner.
You loved him.
- What?
- Celina.
I'm sorry if I overstepped.
You're just so sad.
We met in intelligence.
Once he finished
undercover school,
we both ended up
in organized crime.
After-work beers
turned into dinners...
turned into... more.
No one we worked with knew.
It was a different time.
But... we had each other.
That was enough.
Then he was gone.
[ Car horns
honking distantly ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Seems a little upscale
for Macy's income bracket.
Seriously. I can't even afford
to park here.
[ Knock on door ]
Ms. Tomkins?
It's Officer Nolan.
We met at the bank earlier.
Security says she hasn't
left the building.
[♪♪]
Door's open.
Police! We're coming in!
[♪♪]
She's dead.
And we're sure
the money's not cursed?
[♪♪]
[ Camera shutter clicks,
zipper closes ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
I scrubbed through
the lobby security footage,
and this guy stood out.
Came in about two hours ago,
stayed for 20 minutes,
and then left in a hurry.
Not much to go on.
Does it feel like Winslow?
I don't know. Could be.
I can't see his face.
St. Brendan medal.
Patron saint of sailors.
Winslow smuggled drugs
up the coast.
Spent half his life
on a boat.
He wore a necklace
just like this 10 years ago.
Clasp is broken.
She probably ripped it
off
as she was fighting
for her life.
We'll get that checked
for DNA.
It's gonna come back to
Harris. I know it.
Okay. Let's say it does.
What's his relationship
with Macy?
If she lied to us in the bank
about where she got the money,
then it's safe to assume
she was covering for him.
Or she stole it from him.
Either way, when he found out
the money was flagged,
he panicked
and burned the rest.
Then came here
and killed her.
Macy's the key.
We need to tear her life apart
to find him.
[ Water splashing ]
Now, this
is my kind of coffee.
Wait, wait, wait.
My favorite movie was shot
right here on this lot.
[♪♪]
Wait.
Your favorite coffee place.
Your favorite movie.
Whoever's doing this
knows you really well.
[♪♪]
Chen.
Who is Arthur Andrews?
Arthur Andrews witnessed
a murder
committed by one
of Elijah Stone's relatives.
And you represented
this relative
as a favor to Mr. Stone.
Is that right?
If by "favor," you mean
your client threatened
to hurt me if I refused,
then yeah.
Now, you could have questioned
Mr. Andrews in your office,
but you chose to do it
in his home.
Why?
That was more
convenient for him.
Or you were trying
to intimidate him
and you didn't
want any witnesses.
No. No.
I went there
after your client ordered me
to find a way to undermine
Mr. Andrews' credibility.
He said, "Either you make this
witness go away or Moreno will."
And for the record, Moreno is
one of Elijah Stone's enforcers
who is currently in prison,
awaiting trial
on several charges,
including the attempted murder
of police officers.
Alleged enforcer.
But what we know for a fact
is that you called in a tip
about an illegal firearm
in Mr. Andrews' home.
Yeah. And that tip
saved his life.
According to you, yes.
But your client,
a man accused of murder,
went free because you
- damaged the reputation...
- [ Laughs ]
...of the only witness
against him.
[ Chuckles ] Yeah. No.
It's a good argument. It is.
And if I was on the other side
of that table,
I would be making it myself.
But it's B. S., and
you know it! Wes.
I know no such thing.
You just can't admit
that I'm outarguing you.
Yes, if you ignore
the truth!
Wesley, let it go.
You never won an argument in
the five years we were together.
What makes you think now
is going to be any different?
Uh-huh.
Why... Why don't we pick this
- up tomorrow? No.
- Yeah. That's a great idea.
- Of course.
- That's perfect.
[ Indistinct conversations,
telephones ringing ]
Hey. Wes. Hey. Hold up.
You can't let her
rattle you like that.
Yeah, sorry.
Just lost focus.
Won't happen again.
Okay. Well,
the facts are on our side,
so just focus on that.
Yeah. Right.
I have to ask you this...
how did it end between you two?
Are you asking
if I'm still hung up on her?
Or she on you.
I don't know.
I just need to know
where this thing could go.
Alright. Look. Monica and I
wanted very different lives.
Right out of law school,
she targeted
the most powerful law firms.
I rented a space next to
an aquarium-supply store.
Hm.
It was never gonna work.
Just took us two years
to figure that out.
Okay.
Look, take
the rest of the day,
but tomorrow, you come in
with your game face on, yeah?
Yeah.
Tim:
Where's my radio?
Did something happen
to your radio?
Oh, you know what?
Halloween is tomorrow.
Maybe a vengeful spirit
took it.
Why are you doing this?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Is holding my radio hostage
payback for how tough
I was on you
as a rookie?
Were you?
Gosh, I hadn't noticed.
Okay. But again, I don't
know what you're talking about,
but I might be able to help
you look for your radio
if you tell me
what's going on.
Nothing is going on
with me.
Please. I rode with you
long enough
to know when you are being you
and when you're upset.
I mean, are you okay?
[ Indistinct conversations ]
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Then I don't know
where your radio is.
Lopez: You were right about
Macy's finances.
Forensics got into her laptop
and found this.
"Sugar Be a us.com.
Opportunities await."
Lind:
"Anastasia Kennedy."
Macy had a sugar daddy.
Daddies... plural.
Warrant's in process
of getting their names.
That explains how she paid
for the nice apartment.
You think that's
how she met Harris?
Maybe.
Let me get a look at pictures
as soon as you have a list.
After staring at his face
for the past decade,
I could spot that guy
from space.
♪ You know I want it ♪
[ Cellphone chimes ]
[♪♪]
♪ I want it all now ♪
[ Cellphone clicks ]
[♪♪]
I think we need
more tombstones.
Uh, no,
I think we're good.
[ Chuckles ]
[♪♪]
What's wrong?
The Reeds have declined
our dinner invitation.
What, first trick or treating,
now this?
What... These people really have
a problem with me being a cop?
That's not why
they're avoiding us.
Honey, did... did Jenny say
something to you?
[♪♪]
[ Sighs ] Her parents told her
it's not safe here
'cause you hang out
with criminals.
Criminals.
M-Meaning my... my friends
from the community center?
Lately at school,
Jenny's been repeating
stuff her parents say about
"those people."
And worse.
Okay.
Which house is Jenny's?
I-I-I don't think
confronting them
is going to
be constructive.
Oh, you can screw
constructive.
Mom, it's okay.
Just 'cause we live close by
doesn't mean we have
to hang out with her.
[ Sighs ]
Alright. Honey, I'm sorry.
I know...
I know
Jenny was your friend.
Was.
I'm gonna go inside,
okay?
Okay. But listen,
you can talk to us
about anything, right?
Okay.
[ Smooches, sniffs ] Hm.
[♪♪]
It's not right.
It's not.
[♪♪]
Thirsty?
I'm fine.
Mm. I'm just saying...
130,000
is a lot of Scovilles.
You realize I've literally
been on fire before.
[♪♪]
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Grunts ]
Mm! Mm! Hm!
Yes!
Bailey 22, Nolan 21.
I've made
a terrible mistake.
I'm thinking
a wedding in May.
We'll miss Mardi Gras,
but the weather will be nice,
and we'll have plenty of time
to get out save-the-dates.
You still have to win by 2.
I think you should quit
while you're behind.
- [ Knocking on door ]
- Mm.
[ Knocking continues ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
I can't sleep.
As soon as I close my eyes,
all I could think about
is you warning me
how dangerous it is for me
to be on duty half asleep.
And I can't... I-I don't know
what else to do.
What do I do?
Uh...
Hey, come here.
There is no training
that could prep you
for the amount of stress
we are put under day after day.
It'll take some time,
but your body will adapt.
Okay? Why don't you
go sit on the couch?
Okay.
How about some tea?
Yeah. Okay.
Chamomile knocks me out.
So does music.
Uh, actually, valerian root
works better,
and don't play music.
That'll keep her up.
She wants white noise.
How is static gonna help her
get to sleep?
Not static.
Science.
You want to bet,
Professor?
Whoever can get Celina
to fall asleep first wins.
How is that even a contest?
Well, we take turns,
and if she falls asleep
on your turn, you win.
Yeah, but you can't separate
out the cause.
I mean, what if she gets
sleepy listening to white noise
but doesn't fall asleep
until she hears music?
Sounds like you're afraid
my way might be better.
I'm not afraid.
You sound afraid.
Okay. I see what
you're trying to do here.
- I see you.
- Mm-hmm.
She's trying to...
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Quietly ]
We'll call it a tie.
Yeah.
[ Indistinct conversations,
mid-tempo music playing ]
[♪♪]
Hey.
Whiskey?
When did you
start drinking whiskey?
I went to Vegas for the
weekend, and when I came back,
my fiancée
had cleared her things out.
Mm.
Maybe she was mad
that you cheated on her.
Oh. Is that why you took
this case?
To get back at me?
Wow. The narcissism.
I did not miss that.
Oh, I'm the narcissist?
Wesley, you think it's your
mission to personally save
all the downtrodden
of Los Angeles.
Mm-hmm. Well, at least I'm
trying instead of selling
my soul
for $800 an hour.
Okay. Some of us have to work
for a living.
I don't have a trust fund
to fall back on.
I didn't say
don't make money.
I'm saying Elijah
is dangerous.
I can handle him.
No, you can't.
He is a manipulator, and
he is always 10 steps ahead.
So whatever control you think
you have, that is an illusion.
And the second you stop
doing his bidding,
he will threaten
the people you love.
You'll live in terror,
and you will compromise
every principle
you hold dear
until you don't
even recognize yourself.
[♪♪]
Principles always were
your thing.
Hi.
[♪♪]
Oh. Detective Lopez.
It's a pleasure
to finally meet you.
And you are?
[♪♪]
Oh, she doesn't know.
Uh, well, then,
I should
definitely get going.
You two have some things
to, uh, talk about.
I'll see you at
your deposition tomorrow.
[♪♪]
Um, I'm gonna need
another one of these.
You're probably gonna
want one, too.
[ Clears throat ]
Wesley?
It's not a big deal.
Um, I just found out
that she's the lawyer
representing Elijah
- this morning.
- I was gonna tell you at dinner.
[♪♪]
We, um, used to date.
It was more than that.
We were engaged
for about a year.
But we were bad
for each other,
and I blew it up by cheating
on her with a co-worker.
[ Glass thuds ]
So much for date night.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Thanks for letting me crash.
I, um... you know,
I felt right at home.
My parents
would bicker back and forth,
just like you guys.
It always put me
right to sleep.
Oh, I don't know
that I would call
what Bailey and I do
bickering.
More like...
spirited debates.
Speaking of spirits, I was just
telling Bailey about my dream.
And here we go.
I dreamt Winslow was a
showgirl wearing a diamond bra.
We were dancing the tango,
and when I realized who he was,
he ran off.
And I tried to stop him,
but all of a sudden,
I was so thirsty, like,
I couldn't move.
And then I woke up.
So, what do you think
it means?
Me?
Are we... Are we are we really doing this?
Well, the tango is
the forbidden dance.
So it could represent
doing something
you're not supposed to do.
Like drug trafficking
or murder.
Okay.
What about the diamonds?
Diamonds are hard
and unchanging.
Clearly, that means Winslow
hasn't changed his ways.
And you dreamed
you were thirsty
because you think
he's near the water.
[ Snaps fingers ]
Yes.
[♪♪]
Is this really
how you solve crimes?
I guess we'll find out.
[♪♪]
My neighbors are trash.
That is something the home
inspection does not tell you.
And I wouldn't care,
but now they're dragging Lila
into the middle
of their narrow-minded B. S.
I'm sorry.
Wesley used to be engaged
to Elijah's new attorney.
You're kidding.
No. And it ended
because he cheated on her.
Oh, I did not know
he had that in him.
Neither did I.
And now I'm pissed because
he never told me
I have to go sit across
from his ex in a deposition
where she's gonna do everything
she can to get under my skin.
Uh, maybe leave
your gun here.
Maybe not.
I looked at every
sugar daddy Macy's had.
None of them are Harris.
Well, the DNA from the
necklace was a match to Winslow.
I've gone to bed every night
for the past 10 years
wondering,
"Did I screw up?
Am I the reason
my partner got made?"
Look, you have only ever been
on the outside
of an undercover op.
I have lived for years
on the inside.
And trust me, what happened
wasn't your fault.
Guys, Celina had
an out-of-the-box idea
that we did
our due diligence on,
and I think
it's worth pursuing.
From Macy's credit-card
statements, I mean,
you can tell she spent time
down in the marina district
during the last six months.
But none of her sugar daddy
clients are based there.
You think she
was meeting Winslow?
It makes sense. I mean,
he lived his life around boats.
Maybe he got back
into drug smuggling.
I'd have heard if he got
back in the game.
I mean, catching him
has been my obsession.
Well, then maybe he found
a legit job in the marina,
and that's where they met
and fell in love.
Love?
How'd you get there?
I felt it.
Uh, but... but
a-a romantic relationship
would explain how Macy got
close enough to Winslow
to try
to deposit that money.
And how he got into
her apartment to kill her.
Either way,
the marina is a big place,
and we are running out
of time.
He could be getting ready
to sail to Mexico.
Well, Macy's credit card
had a bunch of charges
at parking meters
near Pier 9.
Okay. I will call
the Port Police
and have them
meet you there.
Let's go.
[ Sighs ]
Detective Lopez.
I hope you and Wesley
had a lovely date night.
It was great.
Thank you.
Let's dig in,
shall we?
Mid-Wilshire station logs
shows your husband visited
a suspect in custody
by the name of Aiden Merritt.
If that's what's in
the logs.
What's not in the logs
is the fact that the next day,
Merritt was found dead in
his cell at the Twin Towers.
He'd been shanked
by a fellow inmate.
Were you aware that your
husband represented this inmate
that killed Merritt?
I don't keep tabs
on my husband's clients.
I'd keep a close eye
on him if I were you.
I don't have to.
I trust him.
Here's the thing...
Merritt's killer is prepared
to testify
that Wesley paid him
to commit the murder.
Lopez:
That didn't happen.
How can you be certain?
Maybe you don't know
your husband
- as well as you think you do.
- I know my husband is not a killer.
Elijah is.
Let me tell you
what it looks like to me.
It looks like your husband
tried to coerce Merritt
into pointing the finger
at my client,
and when he refused,
your husband had him killed.
I've dealt with a lot
of shady lawyers in my day,
but you are next level.
Please. The personal attacks
are so unprofessional.
[ Laughs ] Okay.
It's...
Unprofessional?
You're paying one of Wesley's
clients to give
false testimony.
I did nothing of the sort.
- Then Elijah did.
- It doesn't matter.
What matters is what a jury
will believe.
And the slipshod way you ran
this investigation
has provided ample
reasonable doubt.
Honestly, if Elijah goes free,
it will not be because of me,
it'll be because of you.
Okay. Let's just take
a break here, hmm?
Let's.
Great idea.
You and I should talk.
[ Folder closes ]
I get what you were trying
to do in there,
and that was clever,
but the fact of the matter is,
we caught your client
in a warehouse
filled with illegal narcotics.
My client was just as shocked
as the LAPD.
Elijah Stone is an upstanding
member of his community.
The only crime here
is that one of the people
he took under his wing
betrayed his trust,
exploiting
my client's goodwill
to further
their own criminal endeavors.
Do you really expect anyone
to believe that Elijah Stone
was oblivious to a massive
drug-smuggling operation
going on right under his nose?
It won't matter.
Okay.
We'll see about that.
Honestly...
the optics of your case
are a hot mess.
If you take this to trial,
I will drag the LAPD
and the DA's office
through five miles of mud.
You and your boss will be
lucky to survive the scandal
with your jobs.
So... do yourself a favor.
Walk away
while you still can.
[♪♪]
Hey. Hi.
What the hell
is going on with Tim?
Well, he lost his radio.
I will give you his radio
if you tell me
what's bothering him.
Honestly, I don't know.
He won't tell me either.
- What?
- Yeah.
Ready to roll?
Mm-hmm.
Hi. Good morning.
Morning.
Still missing your radio?
No. It's in the shop.
Dispatcher: 7-Adam-100,
officers on event.
7-99 are calling
for a supervisor.
[♪♪]
Copy. Show me en route.
Where is
your standard issue?
This is it.
That hasn't been standard
since the '60s.
Let's roll, Thorsen.
Well, wait. Let me get a photo
of you with it first.
[ Window whirring,
door closes ]
[♪♪]
[ Echoing ] 7-Adam-100, can
I get a radio check, please?
[ Static crackles ]
7-Adam-100, do you copy?
[♪♪]
Where's the guard?
Harper said
he'd meet us here.
God, this place is massive.
I mean,
Harris could be anywhere.
Or he could be
casting off right now.
[♪♪]
[ Grunts ]
Let's split up. Go that way.
[♪♪]
Wesley: I was a different
person back then.
I was trying to follow
in my father's footsteps...
The white-shoe law firm,
events at the country club,
Christmas in Mustique.
[ Sighs ]
And I was miserable.
This wasn't
about Monica or her co-worker.
It was a selfish and stupid
way to blow up a life
that was making me unhappy.
But I would never
cheat on you.
I know, 'cause
you're afraid of me.
Because I'm in love
with you.
[ Knock on door ]
Hey.
Uh... we're dropping the case
against Elijah.
What?
You can't be serious.
I'm afraid I am.
There's just too much risk
in trying
to take this thing to trial.
I put my family in danger
going after this guy.
Look, I get it's upsetting,
but we're just playing the
hand that you dealt us.
So you're just gonna
let him walk?
It became clear
after these depositions
that this case is a loser.
Look, take a few days,
you know,
get your head on right.
We'll talk about
what's next for you here.
[♪♪]
[ Exhales deeply ]
Winslow!
[♪♪]
Police!
Show us your hands!
[ Gunshots ]
[♪♪]
7-Adam-15. Shots fired
at 221 Whaling Way.
Suspect is fugitive
Winslow Harris...
Latino male, black shirt,
dark jeans.
Armed with a handgun.
Requesting airship and backup.
You got no move here,
Winslow! It's over!
- Nolan: You okay?
- Celina: I'm good.
Move. Move.
[♪♪]
You're finally gonna pay
for what you did.
You could just walk away.
That the deal you gave
Macy Tomkins?
[ Sighs ] That wasn't
supposed to happen.
She wasn't supposed to find out!
We were happy!
Tell it to her family.
Tell it to the family
of my partner
and the people who loved him.
Winslow: You won't believe
me, but I'm-a tell you this anyway.
The night at that deal...
the gun went off.
It just...
It went off in my hand.
I didn't know he was a cop!
None of that matters now.
[♪♪]
There are no second chances,
are there?
Not for you.
But I'm living one right now.
[♪♪]
Nolan: Drop the gun.
Do it now.
[♪♪]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gun clatters ]
[♪♪]
[ Groans ]
You're under arrest
for the murders
of Macy Tomkins...
...and Robert Buckley.
[♪♪]
So, how'd the debrief go?
To be honest, I checked out
after the words "Winslow Harris"
and "consecutive
life sentences."
I can't tell you
what it means to me,
knowing his killer
is behind bars,
what it means
to finally have answers
about those last moments.
Thank you.
Oh, it was our pleasure.
♪ It's okay if we lose
track of time ♪
Hey, happy Halloween.
You got any plans tonight?
Or should I just assume
you're gonna be inside,
hiding with the lights out?
I don't hide.
I leave a bowl of candy
on the porch.
- Oh.
- Hey.
Um... here.
I thought torturing you
would be more fun,
and getting your mind off
of whatever's been
bothering you.
But I should know better
than trying to get
into your personal business.
[♪♪]
Good night.
Ashley and I, uh, broke up.
[♪♪]
Well, I guess technically,
she broke up with me.
[♪♪]
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
Look, and just so you know,
I-I did appreciate
your whole radio gag...
a little.
[♪♪]
It took my mind off things.
Well, good.
[♪♪]
Lucy. Ready to go?
Uh, yeah. D...
Uh, do you want to join us?
We're gonna go grab
a bite to eat.
Oh, no, no.
I'm good.
I'm g... I'm... I'm beat.
[ Chuckles ]
You two have fun.
Mediterranean sound good?
Yeah. That sounds great.
[♪♪]
Children shouting
"Trick or treat" in distance...
Sweetie, I know that
trick-or-treating
with your parents
isn't cool,
but I happen to think
that our outfits are amazing.
They are.
And I'm actually
having fun with you guys.
Are you, now?
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, my God.
Someone TP'ed Jenny's house.
Constructive, huh?
[ Sucks teeth ]
Trick or treat.
[ Chuckles ]
- Bye! Happy Halloween!
- Girl: What'd you get?
You just have to admit
I wear it better.
Yeah, you wear everything
better.
No one's arguing that.
- I didn't agree to compete over this.
- [ Knock on door ]
Both: Hey!
Happy Halloween!
Oh, that is a brilliant
costume, young man.
You too, slightly older man.
I don't see many Philly fans
this side of the, uh, Rockies.
You from there?
Uh, Foxburg, actually.
Just moved here a few years ago.
God, you look remarkably
like that fella from CNN.
What's his name?
Jake Tapper.
No, that's not it.
Yeah, it is.
Here.
You guys want some candy?
Thank the nice people.
- Thank you.
- Roger that.
Have a great night.
- See you, guys!
- You too!
Celina:
Hey, yo, hey, yo.
Hey!
Can I, uh, sleep over again?
I don't know
that that's a great idea.
Didn't you say quality sleep
is important
for good police work?
Yeah, but I don't sound
like that, do I?
And you want your rookie
to do good police work.
Obviously.
Great. Come on in.
You can sleep here tonight.
I will get the chamomile.
Okay.
But this is the last time.
- Mm-hmm.
- And didn't we agree that valerian root
was better for sleep?
Chamomile is easier
on the stomach.
Where did you hear that?
[ Exhales deeply ]
[♪♪]
Wesley Evers,
attorney at law.
[♪♪]
I told you.
I always win.
[♪♪]
Oh, you really think
this is over?
Are you kidding?
You messed up my case so bad
that no one's gonna want
to touch me.
I figure I got
a two-year free pass.
You know, coming after me
before then would be unseemly,
given how compromised
you and your LAPD buddies look.
I wouldn't count on that.
Well, I think
I'm pretty untouchable.
[♪♪]
I have some business
to take care of, but, uh...
I'll be seeing you,
Counselor.
[ Engine starts ]
[♪♪]
Captions by VITAC...
Synchronized by srjanapala
[♪♪]