[Dog barking, train whistle
blowing in distance]
[Police radio chatter]
[Engine revs]
[Siren chirps]
[Car doors open, close]
I have so many questions,
I don't know where to start.
So I'll open with...
"Where you headed?"
To the bar on the corner.
I'm taking my brother
for one last drink.
I'm sorry for your loss.
As am I.
But y-you can't just
be transporting a...
There is a body in there?
Yes, sir.
My brother Kenny.
Uh, who knows the next time
I'll see him, if ever.
If you know what I mean.
Yeah. No, actually,
I don't know
what you're talking...
I'm sorry. Could you
open the lid for us, please?
Yeah.
Oh.
We there yet?
Your brother's not dead.
No, sir.
So why is he
in a coffin?
Oh, we just found it on the side
of the road a ways back.
Pretty cool, right?
Celina: Okay, but you said
it was the last drink
and you'll never see him again.
Yeah, well, he's moving
to the Valley tomorrow,
so who knows?
I just...
It's right
behind my eyes.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
It's like a hot knife.
♪ I'm gonna win for you
like I know you want me to do ♪
[Indistinct conversations,
camera shutter clicking]
Alright, so,
what do we have?
Ji-hoon Kim...
49, liquor-store owner.
Two gunshots to the head.
Also has a fractured jaw
and bloodied ear.
There were
broken bottles inside.
He fought off a robber?
Or tried to. Looks like
he tried to make a run for it.
Anyone see anything?
Hey, Detectives. A C.I. of mine
says Double R did it
because our victim
wouldn't pay up.
Double R?
Some new girl gang.
I'm sorry, did he just act like
girls aren't dangerous?
Yes, he did. In front of two
of the most dangerous women who
have ever walked this earth.
Who could have you assigned
to traffic control
on the surface of the sun.
Man: Officer Jan,
we need you inside.
Uh, yeah, Copy that.
I'm on my way.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You better run.
[Chuckles]
♪
Good morn...
[Whispering]
Oh. Good morning.
Sorry. Ignore me.
Please continue.
We need to talk.
That's never a good start
to a conversation.
So, I've been speaking
with Celina.
Oh! I just discovered
a worse one.
The energy in your house
is off.
Our house.
That's really sweet,
but not the point.
Okay. I'm excited to hear
what the point is.
Ever since the engagement,
whenever I'm here,
I feel off center,
if that makes any sense.
But I couldn't
put my finger on it.
But after talking to Celina,
we realized
that the wallpaper color
in the bedroom
doesn't line up
with your astrological sign
and the couch fabric
is completely counter
to your birth element.
Okay, see, the plan was
for you to rub off on Celina,
not the other way around.
What about the blocked energy?
Oh, don't you worry.
I'll talk to Celina today
all about that blocked energy.
Bye! [Smooches]
Love you.
Okay. That's it.
Be safe out there.
But before you leave,
one more thing,
what you've all
been waiting for.
So, I'll make this quick.
Pay raises from
the last union negotiation
have gone into effect.
- Yeah.
- Yay.
[Applause]
♪
Check your pay stubs,
and we'll see what...
You're interrupting a briefing.
Are you Sergeant Wade Grey?
No.
That'd be me.
You've been served.
"Elijah Stone vs.
The City of Los Angeles, LAPD,
Wade Grey, Wesley Evers,
and Angela Lopez."
♪
A civil suit
and a Pitchess motion.
Alright.
Briefing's over.
♪
Celina:
What's a Pitchess motion?
It's a request to see
a cop's personnel file.
Everything... IA complaints,
even the bogus ones.
It's a great way
to, uh, block energy.
Why don't you go set up the
shop. I'll meet you out there.
Lopez: Hey, union rep.
Anything you can do to help?
Not much I can do
about the lawsuit.
As far as
the Pitchess motion goes,
I can call the City Attorney's
office right now
and make sure they're
following POBR on that.
Thanks.
I've been hit with
20 Pitchess motions
and never had a judge
grant one.
Yeah, but if it is granted,
Elijah can use it
to support his claims
of "violation
of civil rights,
false arrest by a peace officer
with a warrant,
racial profiling,
civil conspiracy."
This is unbelievable.
I mean, the guy is
a major drug trafficker.
If he thinks he can sue
a defense attorney
turned prosecutor and win,
he doesn't know how badass
my husband is in the courtroom.
Damn straight.
Uh, you want to take a minute,
or should we ask
about Chen?
What about Chen?
We caught a D.B.
this morning,
a shopkeeper who refused
to pay protection money
to a street gang
called Double R.
Rowena Razors
out of Rowena Gardens?
Gang task force
doesn't have much on them
except their leader,
Shana Quelli.
She was released from Valley
State Prison three months ago.
She's been extorting
store owners on her turf.
Harper:
Our victim took a stand,
and the Razors made
an example out of him.
Harper and Lopez need you
to infiltrate the gang
to get some evidence,
murder weapon.
A confession
would be best.
Uh... they're not going
to let me anywhere near them.
You're U.C. now, right?
Gaining access and building
trust is the name of the game.
♪
You got it.
I'll figure it out.
[Car doors close]
Tim: Hello, ma'am.
We had a noise complaint.
Yelling.
Everything okay?
I was just arguing
with my son.
Ain't no need
for the police.
Okay, so what's
the problem, ma'am?
My son, Tabin.
Mm-hmm.
He won't listen.
He cuts school.
He won't pick up after himself.
And the mouth
on that boy.
And how old's your son?
15.
He threaten you?
He knows he better not!
Okay. Any drugs, weapons,
other criminal behavior?
Tabin?
Absolutely not.
I see him drifting.
He's running the streets
instead of doing schoolwork.
Told him he's gonna
end up like his sister.
I already lost one child.
I'm not gonna lose another.
And let me guess... He didn't
want to hear that, huh?
He says I don't know
what I'm talking about.
Starts yelling
and... and slamming doors.
I told him,
"You break my house,
I'mma break your head."
Okay. Well, we can't arrest him
if he hasn't committed a crime.
Ain't nobody asking you
to do all that.
You can't talk to him,
put the fear of Jesus in him,
help keep him
out of trouble?
I pay your salaries.
You know what?
We should defund y'all ass.
Look, um, I-I'll talk
to him, okay?
Is he inside?
Mm-hmm.
[Police radio chatter]
She did not
call the cops on me.
Ma!
Hey, hold on.
It's... It's alright.
Tabin, right?
Officer Thorsen.
Call me Aaron.
She's crazy, okay?
Your mom didn't call us, okay?
But she is worried about you.
What am I supposed to do?
Stay cooped up in here?
I-I want
to live my life.
Right,
and she wants you
to live a long and good life,
too. All moms do.
You know, it's just, sometimes,
they can trip about everything.
Listen.
I know how you feel, okay?
My mom,
she's a piece of work, too.
Sometimes I feel like
she's the kid and I'm the adult.
Yeah. Yeah. You know.
Right. But you still got to
show her respect, okay?
No matter how angry you get.
When I was your age,
I was angry, too.
Listen to her, right?
If you get upset or whatever,
just take a beat
before answering.
I mean, she changed
your diapers, man, okay?
You owe her that.
I hear you.
Anything else bothering you?
Kids at school?
Nah.
You use?
No, sir.
Good. Any gangs
pressuring you to join?
No, no.
Here's my card, alright?
It's got my cell on it.
Anything stresses you out,
you give me a call, okay?
But no more slamming
these doors. You feel me?
Yes, sir.
Alright.
Yeah, as their union rep,
I just wanted to touch base.
Thank you very much
for your time.
What'd they say
about the Pitchess motion?
That Lopez's
and Wesley's marriage
is going to
complicate things.
Elijah's gonna try
to prove prejudice.
He may actually
have a case.
Yeah, that's not good.
No, that's not good at all.
Uh, now, what was
Bailey talking to you about,
uh, our house's energy
being blocked?
Okay, look,
she came to me for advice.
And you suggested
redecorating?
[Chuckles] Okay, look,
it's more than that.
It's about having
your home's energy line up
as you build
a home together.
It's that couch.
She hates the couch.
Definitely the couch. It's like
a positive-energy black hole.
I'd start there.
"Start"?
Barista: Enjoy.
Have a great day.
Thank you.
Double latte,
cranberry scone?
[Sighs]
You know me well.
Damn.
He's taking the last one?
And if you real about it ♪
Hello, Wesley.
Elijah.
What, you following me?
Well, I heard you come here
every morning.
Well, the best scone
in town.
You know, I never
would have guessed
from your sad, little office
or that beater that you drive
that you're
old-money rich.
What's it like
having generational wealth?
I don't care about money.
I care about justice,
the rule of law.
Spoken like someone
with a ton of money.
Hmm.
Well, don't worry.
I'll be relieving you
of your burden.
Get in, get in ♪
It's been nice,
but you need to leave.
Your lawsuit's malicious.
I'm not leaving.
This is my spot.
Well, not anymore.
Given the fact that you
planted evidence on me,
are married
to a police detective,
and have the full force
of the D.A.'s office behind you,
it's easy to see
how you kept your job.
My only choice was to file
a restraining order against you.
The judge granted it.
This gentleman here
just served you.
I'mma be here every day,
which means you'd better not be.
♪
Wesley.
Take the scone.
That's all you're gonna get.
♪
[Wrapper crinkling]
[Cellphone chimes]
It's that kid Tabin.
[Police radio chatter]
"Took a beat
like you said.
Now Mom has me
grocery shopping.
Thanks a lot."
Smile emoji.
[Cellphone clicking]
"What time's dinner?"
I think that kid's
gonna be alright.
Be careful.
Puppies are a lot of work.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
What?
You just got a puppy.
Meaning I'm
blurring the lines?
Meaning protect
your personal space.
Lucy got a puppy over a year
ago. Now she's living with her.
I mean, as long
as his mom's a good cook.
♪
Lucy: Oh, hey. I ran
a record management search
on the Rowena Razors.
Here is everything
from the gang task force.
They are playing catch-up.
I...
This doesn't make sense.
I mean, criminal history,
arrest reports.
These girls
are heavy hitters.
They've all done time
for meth trafficking,
attempted murder, manslaughter.
Why is the current intel
so light?
Well, you said it. Girls.
Everyone dismisses
female gangs
as some sort
of throwback curiosity,
like the Pink Ladies.
And if they do
take them seriously,
they are written off
as drug mules or prostitutes,
not the ones who are actually
calling the shots.
This is what
I was trying to say earlier.
It's gonna be
tough to get in.
They'll be a tight-knit group,
you know?
Suspicious of outsiders.
Yeah. No doubt.
But don't make the same mistake
that men do
and write them off
as just little girls.
They're a real threat.
Well, so am I.
♪
[Chuckles]
Remember, those stop signs
are there for a reason.
Drive safe.
[Police radio chatter]
[Sighs] You know,
here's what's concerning me.
About what?
Bailey.
She's feeling off-center
ever since she proposed.
It's not you.
It's the energy in your house.
Let's just say,
for the sake of argument,
it's not about the couch.
Mm-hmm.
I just don't like
that she doesn't feel
comfortable in our home.
Gun!
Police! Drop the gun!
7-Adam-15.
Shots fired at our location.
I need assistance.
Check on the victim.
♪
[Dog barking]
[Dog whining]
♪
Good boy.
Police.
I know you're in there.
Throw the gun out.
♪
Now step out nice and slow.
Keep your hands
where I can see them.
[Hinges creak]
Turn around.
Hands on your head.
Step towards me.
Right there.
[Handcuffs click]
Alright.
Nice dog.
Code 4.
Suspect in custody.
[Tires screech]
[Police radio chatter]
He got what he deserved.
I'm sure you feel that way,
but no one deserves that.
He's dead.
[Sighs]
Yeah, well,
bullets will do that.
No, I mean, like,
he's a corpse.
Skin's cold and pale.
The vessels in his eyes
are trucking.
I mean, I'd say he's been dead
for at least an hour
before she shot him.
Why would she shoot someone
Nolan:
You'll see that little trailer
halfway down on the left.
That's where I found her hiding.
Hello, sir.
Our victim is Alvin Mitchelssen.
He's an M.D.
He was working at a urgent care
center in Woodland Hills.
This his residence?
Yes, sir.
Any family?
Uh, he's got a wife
we're trying to get ahold of.
She hasn't picked up yet.
I had realized
there was no blood
coming out of the bullet holes,
which was weird.
But then I saw blood pooling
on the seat,
and that's when I realized
he was already dead.
The M.E. found a stab wound
on his lower back.
They figure that's
the likely cause of death.
There was no blood
leading to the car.
So we figure he was stabbed
as he was entering the vehicle,
but he was losing blood
so quickly,
he passed out before he was able
to drive himself to a hospital.
Um...
Good work,
both of you.
[Scoffs] This guy must have
been a piece of work
for two people to set out
to kill him on the same day.
Uh, sir, would you mind
if Juarez and I continued
working this case?
I know you have your hands full
with the Elijah Stone stuff.
[Sighs]
I appreciate that.
Okay.
You two work this.
Just keep me in the loop
with any developments.
Yes, sir.
Head back.
Talk to the shooter.
If we can figure out
why she wanted him dead,
maybe we can
determine why
someone else would
want him dead, too.
Got it. Um...
What am I
charging her with?
Um, desecration
of a human corpse?
Right. But if she didn't know
it was a corpse...
Then it'd be
attempted murder.
But...
But without a victim...
Alright.
Give me a second.
Bradford,
we have a suspect
who fired into an already
expired individual.
Tim: Ooh, that's a tough one.
Could be murder one,
but maybe just
discharging a firearm.
They either get a trial
or a ticket.
Thanks for nothing.
Nolan: Uh, you know what?
I'll just call the D.A.'s office
when I get back.
I'm sure they've done this
a hundred times.
May...
Probably not a hundred.
That doesn't seem very...
Yeah.
I could pose as a store owner,
get them for extortion.
No. We need them for the murder.
Keep looking.
[Indistinct conversations]
Oh.
What is it?
One of the Razors,
Vina Cordon...
there was a 4-15 called
at her house today,
and Tim and Aaron took it.
Hey, you guys caught a 4-15
this morning?
Yeah. It was cute.
Cute?
All puppies are cute.
[Scoffs] Until they borrow
your earrings and they lose one.
Yeah, the mom asked us
to talk to her 15-year-old son.
He's a good kid.
Aaron's protégé has been
texting him nonstop.
"Who should I take to prom?
What's good on Hulu?"
Did the mom
mention a daughter?
Yeah,
she said she lost one.
Didn't want her son
to end up the same way,
and I thought she meant,
like, O.D. or something.
No.
Uh, Vina Cordon.
She runs with
the Rowena Razors.
R-2.
We want to put Lucy under,
but we can't find an in.
Your kid might be our ticket.
If your puppy vouches for her,
it can go a long way.
I don't know. Having a kid act
as a C.I. on his own sister?
I mean, they might not
even be in touch.
She doesn't have
any violent priors,
but we like the gang leader
for doing our shop owner.
Okay, so you're not
going after the sister.
The kid's a minor. We're gonna
need the mom's permission.
No,
I-I'm not feeling that.
Why would we put him
in this situation?
I get it.
But it's one intro.
It's not like
it's a buy or anything.
Yeah,
but it opens the door.
Isn't there another way?
There really isn't.
Alright, look, how about we keep
an eye on the kid ourselves,
make sure he's safe?
If we don't do this,
we risk letting a suspect
get away with murder.
♪
Understood.
Sure.
Whatever you need.
Great.
We'll set it up.
Well, do you want to tell us
why you shot Alvin Mitchelssen?
A few years ago,
my dad
hurt his back at work.
And Dr. Mitchelssen
gave him opioids for the pain.
And he just kept...
upping the dosage.
And I went and I told him,
"My dad is abusing the pills.
He needs help."
And Dr. Mitchelssen
just ignored me.
[Voice breaking]
My dad O.D.'d three months ago,
and he would
still be around today
if it wasn't
for that monster.
Well, did you report him
to the medical board?
I did everything
that you were supposed to do,
and no one cared.
I wasn't gonna just
let him kill my father.
He had to pay.
And that is why
I killed him.
And I am ready for whatever
consequences that may bring.
[Breathes shakily]
Well, Abby, I've got
some good news for you,
and I've got
some good news for you.
Dr. Mitchelssen was already dead
when you shot him this morning.
[Gasps]
Uh, I don't understand.
[Sighs]
So I'm... I'm not being
arrested for murder?
No. We will be charging you
with vandalism,
discharging a firearm in public,
and mutilation of a corpse.
So I'm not gonna be spending
the rest of my life in prison?
No. After we process you,
you'll be free to go,
and someone will explain to you
how you can get your gun back.
Keep it.
[Sniffles]
Having it in the house
in the first place
is what got me here.
[Laughing, crying]
Look, it's a big decision.
You know, we don't usually
involve minors,
but it's the only way.
I knew this Shana girl
was nasty.
I told Vina,
"Stay away from her."
Is it dangerous?
It's just an introduction.
One meeting. But we'll be set up
on surveillance.
You'll be there?
Yes, ma'am.
And what do you think?
Is this a good idea?
I think it's our best bet
to get Shana off of the streets.
That's not what I asked.
Do you think
he should do it?
[Inhales deeply]
Yes.
♪
If we can get Vina
away from Shana, then...
maybe she'll
come back home.
I hope so, baby.
Alright.
I'll do it.
Do I get a gun?
No.
Do I at least
get to wear a wire?
No.
You guys are
real cops, right?
♪
[Door opens]
Thank you for coming in.
We just had a few questions.
Would you like to sit?
Yeah.
First, uh, may I say
how sorry we are
for the loss
of your husband.
Oh. Thank you.
I-I'm still in shock.
I can only imagine.
When was the last time
you spoke with Alvin?
This morning.
I had a conference downtown,
so I left before him,
which is unusual.
He's usually
out the door first.
Can you think of anyone who
would want to harm your husband?
I don't understand.
What do you mean,
harm my husband?
W-Well,
he was stabbed.
Right before
he was shot.
Somebody stabbed him,
then shot him?
Two people, we think.
At the same time?
No.
So two different people
killed my husband?
No, technically,
just one.
None of this makes sense.
He's a doctor.
He... He dedicated his life
to helping people.
I-I knew he had
heart problems.
That's what I thought you were
gonna tell me killed him.
I-I don't understand why
someone would want him dead.
So there's nothing
you could think of
that could lead to this?
I mean, no arguments
with co-workers, patients?
All his patients
loved him.
Well, thank you very much again
for coming in.
And we are so sorry
for your loss.
[Door closes]
Uh, Rich, would you show
Mrs. Mitchelssen
back to the front desk?
If we have any more questions,
we'll be in touch.
Uh, please...
find whoever did this
to my husband.
Of course.
[Exhales deeply]
Sounds like she didn't really
know her husband.
Or he's
a really good liar.
♪ If you gon' do it,
do it right ♪
♪ So if I hit it once,
I know I can do it twice ♪
♪ Anything come up out my mouth,
I'mma back it up ♪
♪ Don't judge me cuz
[Camera shutter clicking]
Yeah, that's
the sister, Vina.
Lopez: I have Shana,
the shooter.
Tim:
Copy. Lucy, you're up.
[Engine revving]
[Camera shutter clicks]
Woman: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[Tires screeching]
[Hip-hop music playing]
[Dog barking in distance]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
[Scoffs] Yo.
You didn't invite me?
Shana: What you want?
You Vina?
Who are you?
UPS.
I got a special delivery
for you.
♪
What the hell you doing
with my brother?
Get over there.
♪
Put that gun away.
Is that how you're
gonna thank me
for saving your brother
from the cops?
You a'ight?
Yeah.
Man, you're wearing some
dumb genes in your family.
Got some nerve
to be talking like that. Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look,
cops saw me boost a six.
They chase you?
Two blocks.
They would have
caught him
if I didn't stop
and let him in my ride.
That's the last time
I help a kid in need.
♪
Can't blame her...
you rolling up
on a house like that.
Could've been
a drive-by.
Yeah. Well, I like
to make an entrance.
And exit, too.
[Door closes]
Stay good,
little man.
Peace.
Yo, chica.
Mm-hmm.
Chill.
Grab a drink.
Alright.
♪
Promise me
you're not gonna freak out.
I never freak out.
I'm a very calm person.
Don't even wo... Whoa.
This...
This is so... much.
Are we... Are you... Are we
redecorating the entire house?
You said you weren't gonna
freak out.
Listen, there are just
some samples I wanted
to look at together.
Okay, can we just talk about why
you're not comfortable at home?
I mean, this morning, you said
you've been feeling off-center.
I think we should try
to figure out why.
I want you to be happy everywhere.
I am.
Not entirely, though.
You know this has nothing
to do with you. I'm just weird.
Okay, well, maybe it doesn't
have anything to do with me,
and maybe it has something to do
with the house after all.
What do you mean?
There's nothing of yours there.
It's all my stuff.
Today we'll go get
some of your things,
bring it over to the house,
and then it'll be our place.
Thank you.
Oh, come on. I'm sorry
I didn't think of it sooner.
You know, there is
this one lounge chair
that I love
and I've been missing.
And every time you sit in it,
it feels like it's hugging you.
See? A hugging chair.
That sounds like
a wonderful addition.
[Door opens]
Oh, hey. Hey, girl.
How you doing?
Hi.
Yeah.
Oh, this is nice.
Ooh.
A-An investigation
had been launched
by the Medical Board
of California.
Dr. Mitchelssen was
racking up complaints,
mainly about
over-prescribing opioids.
He had all of his scripts filled
at just one pharmacy,
deep in the Valley.
That's not suspicious at all.
Mm-hmm.
Alright. Back to business.
Um, unless you two
want to handle the pharmacy,
and I'll get the chair?
[Laughing]
No, no. Go, go, go.
Don't worry
about the chair.
[Cellphone vibrating]
[Cellphone clicks]
What's up?
I got news.
Elijah's
Pitchess motion failed.
He won't be able
to get his hands
on all the B.S. IA complaints
in your file.
But?
But he decided
to file his own.
Against me?
On what grounds?
He claims you kicked him in
the nuts and slapped him around,
pulled his hair,
body-slammed him.
Never happened, although now
I'm regretting my restraint.
I know. Hey, it's his word
against yours.
He won't win.
We thought he'd spent
a lifetime in prison.
Now he's walking free.
Don't underestimate him.
[Cellphone clicks]
Listen, don't let Elijah Stone
get to you.
You got this.
[Hip-hop music playing]
You know, we keep it cool
like that. You want a beer?
Yeah.
♪ Money be da mission,
city slickin' ♪
♪ Back to back whips,
no penny pinchin' ♪
Appreciate it.
You from L.A.?
Phoenix.
My cellie at Valley State
lives here,
so I'm crashing
on her couch.
You were at Valley?
10 months.
I did 24.
Who's your cellie?
Shawty Ross.
I know Shawty.
You were cellies?
Hm.
That says something.
Tell her I said what up.
For sure.
Shawty's a C.I.
on D.O.J.'s payroll.
She'll confirm
Lucy's cover.
Okay. Good.
We should pull Tabin out now.
No, he's fine.
Sir, no, it's not.
You are endangering this kid
all because it's good
for Lucy's career.
Excuse me?
Lucy: ...time,
walk out a free woman.
I'm sorry.
Shana: Ain't no surprise.
Shawty don't play.
I shouldn't have said anything.
Vina: No, she don't.
So, what game you guys run?
Cars? Vike, goodfella, monkey?
What's the deal?
Drugs bring
too much attention.
Tabin: Yo, what'd you say
about my sister?
We stick to the shadows.
Yeah, let's just say
we in the security business.
[Indistinct shouting]
♪
Hey!
[Indistinct shouting]
♪
Oh, yeah.
You see it, huh?
You see it?
♪
Put that away.
[Crowd murmuring indistinctly]
Are you good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Good?
You just got your ass beat.
Hell yeah,
he got his ass whupped.
Hey, look, take this.
Settle up with him later.
Come on.
♪
Nah. I'm... I'm good.
Boy can't even
hold a gun.
Scared of a gun!
[Scoffs]
[Laughs]
"Nah. I'm good."
[Both laugh]
♪
Alright. She's in.
Let's peel off.
[Engine starts]
Roger.
[Seat belt clicks]
♪
Come on.
Aaron: Look, it may feel like
a big deal now,
but things like this always blow
over, okay? People will forget.
You're just saying that.
Nah, it's true, man. You know
how many times I been beat up?
Is that why you're so ugly?
Wow. Okay.
Althea: Get off me!
Get away from me!
Don't touch me!
Woman: Ma'am!
Where's my son?! Where...
[Sighs] I knew I shouldn't
have allowed this.
You said
it wasn't dangerous.
It was just a little dust-up
with another teen.
You call this a dust-up?
Well, I call it a screw-up.
And what about Vina?
You put her in danger, too?
Maybe I should tell her
what's going on.
Ma'am,
you can't do that.
You expose that we have
an officer undercover,
it'll jeopardize their life
and your son's.
He's right. As soon as
Tabin made his introduction,
I should have pulled him out immediately.
My son's done
playing cops and robbers.
You hear?
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, baby.
♪
With all those prescriptions
Dr. Mitchelssen was writing,
I mean, you'd think
this pharmacy would
be a little busier.
[Police radio chatter]
♪
[Van door closes]
[Siren wails in distance]
♪
Well, that's why
they don't look busy.
They're shipping in bulk.
♪
[Engine starts]
[Siren chirping]
♪
[Car doors close]
Nolan: License
and registration, please.
Uh, did I do
something wrong, Officer?
We'll get to that.
Alright.
You mind telling me
what's in the van?
Just, uh, making
some deliveries.
Show me.
Ta-da!
[Chuckles]
Just some boxes.
[Van door closes]
Why don't we open them up
and take a look?
Uh...
I don't think
I have to do that.
Do I?
Normally... no.
You wouldn't have to show me
what's in the boxes.
But, the fact is, your pupils
are the size of pinholes,
and you can't seem
to stop licking your lips,
which makes me believe you're
driving under the influence.
Now I can see
what's in the boxes.
The law is so confusing.
[Chuckles nervously]
Not if you
don't break it.
Step back.
Did you know it's illegal
to possess prescription drugs
assigned to anyone else?
"Janet Wilson."
I'm guessing that's not you.
That's my nana. Mm.
I'm her caregiver.
Mm.
"Thomas Jeffries."
Poor Thomas.
He's having such a tough time.
[Chuckles]
Hands behind your back.
[Handcuffs clicking]
What do you know about
Alvin Mitchelssen?
Never heard of him.
Dr. Alvin Mitchelssen?
Look, we've got a dead doctor
writing prescriptions
getting filled
out at that pharmacy.
And here you are, picking up
those very same scripts.
Whoa. Hold on.
You're not hanging that on me.
Then who are
we hanging it on?
Uh...
Look, I noticed
the ink on your hand.
Rolling Seventies?
That's a tough group of guys.
I'm guessing they're gonna
sell these pills on the street.
You're just a middleman.
Tell me this, though.
Any of those guys
willing to do your time for you
if they were here?
Mnh-mnh.
Come on, man.
Just tell us who's in charge,
and we'll keep your name
out of it.
[Sighs]
♪
Callis Caputo, okay?
He did the doctor.
Where do we find
this Callis?
This is a good party.
Except for my brother
getting his ass whupped.
Yo, my moms
got him so whipped,
he ain't ever gonna make it
on these streets.
I mean,
ain't that a good thing?
Maybe he'll get to live
a regular life.
Doing what?
Whatever he wants.
Yeah, what you know?
Don't disrespect me.
Shana: She ain't.
Sit down.
I told you,
you got to chill.
'Specially after you know.
What happened?
You nosy, you know that?
Step off.
[Laughs]
That's Shawty's girl.
[Indistinct conversations]
We got to make a run.
Want to come?
Yeah.
Soon as I finish this.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Man singing in Spanish]
[Door bells jingle]
I already paid you.
[Clatter]
We're gonna be by
twice a week now.
[Women speaking
indistinctly]
I-I can't pay that.
That's what the liquor store
owner said. You heard about him?
"I can't pay."
Even when I put a gun to
his head. He left me no choice.
[Breathing shakily]
Okay.
I'll pay you
whatever you want.
You know what?
Hey, man.
He said he could pay.
Don't interrupt me
when I'm doing business.
I already told you.
Do not disrespect me.
Stop.
The liquor store was enough.
We don't need more blood.
And I told you
to get rid of that.
It's my lucky piece.
Get rid of it.
[Clicks tongue]
See you in a few days.
[Man singing continues]
[Door opens]
♪
The City Attorney's offering
to pay you a settlement.
You should take it.
You know,
I lost everything
when I decided to help
you get your wife
back from La Fiera.
You turned me
into a pariah.
Now I have to start
from the bottom.
But it's all good.
I will win, and the damages
will be paid out
from everyone's
personal accounts.
Now, that may not hurt you,
Richie Rich.
But it most certainly will hurt
Nolan and Harper and Grey.
Where they gonna find a half
a million dollars each, huh?
I'll keep coming, adding more of
your little friends to my suit.
I'll take everything
away from you
until you say sorry for
taking everything away from me.
You want me to apologize?
To you?
Something along
these lines.
In public.
♪
And, Counselor,
make me believe it.
♪
Sir, we I.D.'d a suspect
for our homicide.
His name is Callis Caputo.
He's a member of
the Rolling Seventies.
Yeah, he's holed up at his shop,
surrounded by his crew.
We need to be smart with how
we go about bringing him in.
This could get ugly.
They've been itching
to start trouble for weeks now.
I don't want
to put a match to it.
Well, then, sir,
I think I have an idea.
♪
[Line ringing]
[Cellphone ringing]
Yeah?
You need to run.
The cops
are coming for you.
How do you know?
They picked me up earlier.
This is my one phone call, and
I'm using it to warn your ass.
Run!
[Siren chirping]
They're here already.
My car's parked
behind the repair shop,
halfway down the block.
Keys are in the wheel well.
Go now.
♪ Hit the breakers,
yeah, we're gone ♪
Stall the cops.
♪ I only do it for the chase
♪ To see the look
on their face ♪
♪ Big Electric
♪ Ultra Thesis
♪ Cut Express It
♪ Can you feel it?
Looking for these?
♪ Whoo
[Siren chirping]
♪ Can you feel it?
Hands.
[Handcuffs click]
Alright, come on.
Watch your head.
[Cellphone rings]
Yeah, this is John Nolan.
You're kidding me.
Oh, my God.
You're not kidding me.
No, I-I didn't
see that coming.
Alright, thank you very much
for the call.
What was that?
That was the coroner.
The tox report came back
on Dr. Mitchelssen.
It wasn't the shooting
that killed him,
and it wasn't the stabbing, either.
Before all that,
he was poisoned.
That's what
stopped his heart
before he bled out
after being stabbed.
Okay, so there's yet another
murderer out there?
Yeah.
But not for long.
Care for
a little overtime?
♪
Look who it is.
[Gearshift clicks]
What's up?
I just told Harper and Lopez
that I've made Vina
as the shooter
in the liquor store murder.
Tabin's sister?
Not the gang leader?
Vina: Look, I'm just
checking up on you
after your little
ass-whuppin'.
Man, I'm good. Fine.
Alright.
Look, I need you
to hold something for me.
N-No. No.
I'm sorry, Aaron.
She practically admitted to
pulling the trigger.
I'm pretty sure she's got
the murder weapon on her now.
Come on. No.
Just hold it.
Use it if you need to.
♪
Vina?
I don't want
to blow my cover.
[Engine starts]
Tim: We got it.
♪
You know anything about this?
[Tires screech]
Police!
Get on your knees now!
What the hell?
Vina,
you're under arrest
for the murder of
Ji-hoon Kim.
What,
you called them?
No, baby,
I swear I didn't!
Get on your knees!
Alright! Alright.
Gun!
Wait! No!
♪
Wait! What the hell
are you doing?!
Tabin, what are you doing?
Drop the gun.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You brought this mess
to my house.
Tabin,
give me the gun, man.
Put it down!
You did this!
Vina: No...
Vina, you did this.
Tim: Drop the gun!
[Muffled]
Tabin, look at me.
Althea: No!
Aaron: Give me the gun.
Put it down!
Give me the gun, man.
Give me the gun.
Give me the gun, Tabin, okay?
Just give me the gun.
Come on.
Give me the gun.
♪
You used me.
Vina: What you mean?
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
We just wanted you home.
[Handcuffs click]
[Dog barking in distance]
[Knock on door]
Officer Nolan.
Did you find out
who killed my husband?
We did.
And we're
looking at her.
What are you
talking about?
It struck me as odd,
but I couldn't quite
put my finger on why...
why you acted so surprised
when I told you your husband
was shot and stabbed,
as if you expected
something else.
Something like poisoning,
which would have presented to us
as a heart attack,
like you assumed.
And it would've worked,
had he not already been shot.
[Scoffs]
And stabbed.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Chuckling]
That's insane.
We put a pharmacy
out of business today.
They were filling
illegal scripts.
They have you
on video surveillance
using one of
Alvin's scripts
to purchase the drugs you used
to stop his heart.
[Scoffs]
♪ You can feel it
in the moment ♪
Did you know that he was
under investigation,
about to go to prison for being
a complete and utter idiot?
I thought I was at least owed
the life-insurance policy.
Mrs. Mitchelssen,
you're under arrest for murder.
Officer Juarez,
cuff her.
♪ Like it was your last
♪ Live extra ordinary
[Handcuffs click]
We matched Vina's gun.
It was definitely
the murder weapon
at the liquor store killing.
So thanks for the help.
Hey, how's your puppy?
I reached out a couple of times
to see how he was doing.
And? Did he respond?
[Clicks tongue]
Oh. Hey, you put a killer
in prison today.
Yeah.
It's his sister.
He'll get it someday.
♪ But you can't let up
I hope so.
♪ No, you can't let go
Good night.
♪ 'Cause you got that dream
♪ In your mind, oh
Hey, uh, I just wanted
to say I'm sorry
for what I said
about Lucy.
That was totally
out of line.
It was.
It's all good.
Look, sometimes
tensions get high,
but we get
the job done.
You had my back,
the way you threw yourself
in front of Mom for me.
Oh, yeah,
she was gon' lay you out.
Come on.
♪ 'Cause you could
never really hold it ♪
Wesley:
I don't have a choice.
Lopez:
Let's fight him in court.
You don't have
to do this.
Yes, I do.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Siren wails in distance]
From the heart, Counselor.
[Clears throat]
[Camera shutters clicking]
♪
Thank you for coming.
I'd like to apologize
to Elijah Stone
for some of my conduct while
acting as his defense attorney.
I made statements
to the LAPD
which broke
attorney-client privilege,
I misrepresented
the nature of his business,
and I cooperated
in an LAPD investigation
that involved wiretapping.
My actions have been reported
to the state bar,
and I have been reprimanded.
Mr. Stone's reputation
has been tarnished,
and for that,
I am sorry.
I'm relieved that
justice has been served.
Mr. Stone deserves
a second chance...
...and the full faith
of the community.
[Camera shutters clicking]
Thank you.
I accept your apology,
Mr. Evers.
I will also accept
an undisclosed settlement
from the City of
Los Angeles.
I'm glad to see
our elected officials working
to right
this egregious wrong.
I hope you all
have learned your lesson
and will strive
to do better.
Thank you.
[Camera shutters clicking]
[Sighs]
♪
[Camera shutters clicking,
reporters clamoring]
Smile.
[Clamoring continues]
♪
What are you
smiling about?
I did a thing.
What kind of thing?
Close your eyes.
I'll show you.
Oh, no.
[Chuckles]
Keep walking.
You trust me, right?
[Whimpers]
Walking, we're walking,
we're walking.
And...
open your eyes.
[Gasps]
I know we said we'd go
this weekend together
and get your stuff.
I thought
I'd surprise you.
Oh, thank you.
If I could wish upon a star ♪
Now let's put it
back in storage.
Yeah. Whoa, what?
I got your big hug chair.
I don't want that thing
hugging me.
It's hideous.
Oh, it's not...
that hideous.
No, really, it is.
Especially next
to all your furniture.
You have
such good taste.
Yeah, especially
in fiancées.
Aww.
Over the hills and far away ♪
Well, it can go back.
But this... has to stay.
[Inhales sharply]
I made it.
You don't say.
[Chuckles]
It spent an hour too long
in the kiln.
No, no, it's perfect.
This is excellent.
It'll live right here. Aww.
And he will
bring us luck.
There.
Now it's our home.
[Earthquake rumbling]
[Needle scratches,
music stops]
[Gnome shatters]
I'm sure that doesn't
mean anything.
Oh.
But you never
"gnome."
- Captions by VITAC...
♪