[♪ pensive theme music playing]
[♪ theme concludes]
[alarm blaring]
[alarm continues blaring]
[voice]
He's dead.
Who?
[breathing shakily]
I don't know you.
[clicks tongue]
Don't go in there.
- Stop it.
- I am telling you, go back.
No.
[sighs]
His brains are on the floor.
[faint sobbing in distance]
You're lying.
- [faint sobbing continues]
- [alarm continues blaring]
[alarm intensifying]
[fire crackling softly]
[shivering breaths]
- Hey.
Fuck.
[shivering]
You been out?
Yeah, thought about
setting up a watch,
in case one of those patrols
gets too close.
Made it about an hour.
[chuckles]
We'll do shifts.
I'll get you something
to warm up.
- Mm-hmm.
- Fuck.
It did not look like that
in the dark.
Shit. Hey, you two.
Hey. Come on.
- [groaning]
- Get up, get up, get up.
- Let me see.
- Well, it's alright.
Now that we know
what we're dealing with,
we can come up with a plan.
- Right?
- Definitely.
- [Mel] Fuck.
- [Nora] Oh, shit.
Wha-- It's-- it's a city, Abs.
I thought it would be like
a tent colony or something.
Well, we knew they had lights.
Yeah, I thought they were
from little generators
- like we use at the FOB.
- [Manny] Nope.
They got full
fuckin' power lines.
[Nora]
Oh, well, isn't that great?
[Owen]
Power lines aren't a problem.
Here are the problems.
They've got four main gates,
no other ins or outs.
Guard towers flanking each exit.
Mounted patrols, all heavily armed,
overlapping routes.
These guys are trained.
[Owen] Yeah, they've got
some vets down there, for sure.
But, okay.
Let's just say
we get past the gates,
the guards, the patrols--
[Manny]
Ah, they also got dogs.
'Kay. [chuckles]
And the dogs.
We still don't know
where Joel is in there.
Okay, how about this?
We ambush a patrol.
We tie 'em up.
- Make 'em tell us where Joel is.
- [Owen] Make them?
Yeah, we said that we weren't
gonna hurt anyone else.
- Just Joel. I'm not gonna--
- Mel, fuck. Relax.
I'm not saying we would.
I'm saying we bluff.
Scare 'em, you know?
And if they don't talk,
then what?
Yeah, it's not like
we could let 'em go.
I do have the beginnings
of an idea for a plan, maybe.
Just need some time.
I have to let it crystallize.
But you're onto something?
I'm onto something.
Okay. Then let's buy you
some time, then.
I'll take the next watch.
Where's the spot?
Up the hill.
A little outcropping.
You'll know it when you see it.
Okay.
Better be a good fuckin' plan.
[♪ tense music playing]
[wind whooshing loudly]
[shivering]
Oh, fuck.
Fuckin' hour out here?
[lighter clicking]
[gas hissing]
You don't actually
have a plan, do you?
No, I do.
The plan is to
convince her to go back.
'Cause if we don't,
the only people
getting killed out here are us.
[knocking]
[knocking continues]
I'm coming.
[sighs]
[groans]
- [scoffs]
- Hey.
Wow, you look like shit.
Dude, what do you want?
I want you to fulfill
your obligation
to the community
of Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
- Mm-hmm?
- 8:00 a.m. patrol.
[groaning]
It's eight?
No, it's-- 7:30.
But you're riding with me
and I like to be on time.
Okay, gimme a minute,
I'll get changed.
I heard you had quite
the night after I left.
Oh. Yeah.
Yeah, uh, she kissed me.
It was just Dina being Dina.
She was high,
she won't even remember it--
Uh, I was talking about
some fight
you had with Seth and Joel.
You kissed her?
- No.
- Wow, Ellie, come on.
We-- we've been
broken up one week,
- and you made a move on her?
- I-- I didn't.
- I didn't make--
- Seriously?
Dina-- you--
It didn't mean anything.
She was probably just trying
to make you jealous.
It didn't mean anything.
It didn't.
- I-- I wouldn't do that.
- I'm screwing with you, man.
I already know.
I don't care.
Come on, get dressed.
We gotta go.
You're the worst.
It's kind of fucked up
you did that, though.
- [scoffs]
- [slams door]
[Ellie]
What's everyone doing?
[Jesse]
Council put the town on alert.
Last night, Kylie and Max
found a pile of dead infected
near Seven Cabins.
- Frozen stiff.
- Okay?
They didn't think anything of it
until 30 live ones
broke through
from underneath the corpses.
They're using their own dead
like insulation.
Thirty? Fuck.
They okay?
Yeah, sprinted back
on their horses.
Sent a squad out
to clear the infected,
but now we're thinking
we don't know how many
are underneath the snow.
Could be 30 more.
Could be a thousand more.
A thousand?
Get the fuck outta here.
[chuckles softly]
Ah, yes.
Certainty masquerading
as knowledge.
- It's very Ellie of you.
- Suck my dick.
Also, somebody told
the council a ghost story
about the world's
smartest infected,
and now everybody's spooked
out of their minds.
It wasn't a ghost story.
You know, no offense, man.
I'm gonna do my patrol
with Joel.
Um, yes, offense,
'cause that's the one person
you've been avoiding
like the plague.
Well, we're better now, okay?
As of when?
'Cause last night I did--
Yeah, I know
what happened last night.
Can you shut the fuck...
[sighs]
My shit with Joel
is complicated.
I know that.
From the outside,
it probably looks really bad.
It has been really bad.
But I'm still me,
he's still Joel, and we--
And nothing's ever gonna
change that, ever.
So, you can all
stop talking about us,
worrying about us,
and thinking about us, alright?
So, you two hashed it out?
Uh... Alright.
Now, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna go on patrol with him
like fucking daddy-daughter day.
- Okay? Okay.
- He already went out.
What? With who?
Dina.
They left an hour ago.
For what it's worth,
he wanted to go with you,
but he said
we should let you sleep.
- Let's hit the restaurant.
- I'm not hungry.
Neither am I,
but Maria wants to talk to you.
And don't ask.
I don't know.
[Tommy] Now, the most likely
outcome is none of this
is necessary, okay?
You wanna remind me next week
how I made y'all
go through
all this crap for no reason?
- [townsperson] Ha. Yeah.
- Nothin' will make me happier.
But you know the drill.
Prepare for the worst,
hope for the best.
Now, half of y'all is hung over
and want me to shut up.
- [laughter]
- But, uh,
I'ma go through this anyway
'cause it's been a minute.
If you see flares,
if you hear bells,
stop what you're doin'.
You follow the plan.
What's the plan?
Vanessa, what's the plan?
We go to the forest?
- [laughter]
- To the forest?
Do not go
to the forest, sweetheart.
Be such a bad idea.
- [laughter]
- Now, young ones, old ones,
right quick into basements
and cellars.
You lock the doors,
you reinforce, shelter in place
'til we tell you it's safe
to come out.
Now, for the rest of us,
where do we go?
- [crowd] Up!
- Up, that's right.
Rooftops, second floors.
What do we bring?
[crowd] Guns!
- You wanted to--
- That means everyone is carrying
when we're on alert.
Sidearms, rifles,
take 'em with you.
Keep 'em on you.
Safeties, please.
Somebody shot themselves
in the leg last week.
- [laughter]
- [townsperson] Earl!
- Alright, don't be Earl.
- [laughter]
Now, bigger weapons,
security team will handle those.
For the rest of you,
if there's a breach...
God forbid,
stay off the main street.
Last place you wanna be,
trust me on that one.
Any questions?
Alright then.
Get with your group leaders.
Spread the word
to your neighbors.
- Let's get everyone in the loop.
- Go hug Daddy.
Tell him he did good.
[people chattering]
Come on.
This is bullshit, right?
It's just a drill.
Yep, it's a drill.
Unless we're attacked,
and then it's not.
Correct.
[whistles]
- Oh, fuck me.
- Stay where you are.
- [sighs]
- Thank you.
Seth, we have something to say?
Yeah.
Um, so last night,
I obviously had a few too many.
It happens to everyone.
People get drunk
and say awful shit
they've never thought before.
- Ellie.
- No, that's-- that's fair.
I shouldn't have said it.
I shouldn't even thought it.
I'm sorry.
I made you two some sandwiches
if you're going out there.
[clears throat]
They're, uh, steak.
Mm.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Well... [sighs]
- You be safe out there.
- [Ellie] Yep.
[guard]
Cottonwood run, moving out.
[horses snorting]
Are we worrying about that?
[Jesse] Nah, it'll just be
up in the mountains.
Fucking hope so.
Ten seconds in,
I already can't feel my ass.
[gates creaking shut]
[thunder rumbling]
[wind whooshing]
[shivering]
Goddammit.
[exhales sharply]
[shivering]
Fuck it.
[horses neighing in distance]
[people chattering in distance]
[chatter continues]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[wind whistling]
[townsperson 1]
We're runnin' out of rope.
One, two, three.
[chains rattling]
Whoa! Rope it.
[townsperson 2] Take those ammo cans.
Put 'em right there.
[people chattering]
[officer] [over radio]
This is mountaintop patrol.
Visibility dropping.
Mountaintop, repeat.
[radio cutting out]
Again, low visibility.
We're coming back to camp.
Repeat.
[radio static buzzing]
- June.
- Yeah?
Go find Amy in the radio room.
Tell her to crank the signal.
Call all the patrols back.
Okay, I'm on it.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[snow pelting,
metal sign clanking]
[Amy] [on radio] Cottonwood patrol,
return to Jackson ASAP.
[Jesse] What?
- Repeat.
- [Amy] Cottonwood patrol,
- return to Jackson ASAP.
- Yeah, alright.
But I think we're too far out
to make it back.
I know a spot,
we can hole up there.
[Amy]
Copy. Shelter in place
until we contact you.
Stay warm.
[Jesse]
Yeah, you too. Over.
- What spot?
- This way.
[horse snorting]
[banging]
[horse neighing]
- [Ellie] They gonna be okay?
- As soon as they eat.
- Okay, what about us?
- This way.
Okay.
[horses chomping, grunting]
[wind whooshing loudly]
[banging]
[heavy panting]
[Ellie] [whispering]
Fuck.
Am I fucking hallucinating?
[Jesse] Maybe.
Do you see
a 7-Eleven full of weed?
- Yep.
- Then no.
[stove door creaking]
How'd you know about this place?
Eugene.
He was my first patrol partner.
One day, he showed it to me,
said he found it a year earlier
when he was on a solo patrol.
Swore me to secrecy.
Said Maria wouldn't be
supportive of his, uh, farming.
[bag zipping]
You okay?
[♪ gentle, solemn music playing]
Yeah.
[fire crackling]
- Eugene was a Firefly?
- Yup.
Just early on, though.
- Quit back in 2010.
- How come?
He said he was tired
of killing people.
- I think he was in Vietnam.
- Oh.
[blowing]
That was a raw deal.
Joel having to put him down.
[sighs]
Fuckin' shame.
Guy makes it through a war,
end up going out like that.
What are you gonna do?
Couldn't be saved.
Yeah.
[grunts]
[people chattering in distance]
[wind whistling]
[exhales sharply]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[screaming]
[wind whooshing]
[groaning]
[panting]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[footsteps crunching]
[♪ ominous music continues]
[snow crunching softly]
[Abby gasping]
[snow crunching]
[exclaiming]
[infected snarling, clamoring]
[screeching]
[clamoring continues]
[panting and grunting]
[Abby yelling]
[♪ tense music playing]
[snarling and screeching]
[grunting]
[clamoring continues]
[Abby screams]
[Abby yells]
[grunts]
Fuck!
[panting]
[snarling]
[Abby gasping]
[grunting]
[growling and snarling]
[Abby whimpering]
[gasping and grunting]
[exclaiming]
[fence snapping]
[infected snarling]
[Abby grunting]
- [Abby yelling]
- [infected screeching]
- [shrieking]
- [gunshot]
[high-pitch ringing]
[muffled voice]
Give me your hand!
[Joel] [normal]
- Can you run?
- Yeah.
Run! That way!
[gunshots]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[door banging]
- [panting]
- [Dina] Joel?
Joel?!
[Joel] Up here.
I'm comin', I'm comin'.
[Abby breathing heavily]
- [Joel] You good?
- [gasping]
Hey, kid!
- Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
- Any bites?
[panting heavily]
Then let's go.
- [door banging]
- Now!
- [banging continues]
- [infected snarling]
- [Dina] What do we do?
- We leave!
Back to Jackson?
It's too far. We'll freeze before
we get halfway.
- I'm aware.
- Where the fuck did they even come from?
- Where did you come from?
- The mountain.
[banging continues]
[infected shrieking]
Okay, Joel, if we stay here,
we die.
If we go out there, we die.
[Joel] I don't know,
I don't know, I'm thinkin'!
The lodge.
My friends are holed up
in a lodge halfway up
the mountain.
Not far.
If the infected are down here,
maybe there aren't
anymore up there.
[banging continues]
Fuck it, it's all we got.
Are your friends armed?
- Yeah.
- Good.
We're gonna need 'em.
Get on.
[infected clamoring]
[radio static]
- [Tommy] How we doin'?
- Range is pretty compromised.
But you heard from all of 'em, right?
They're on their way back?
Or taking shelter, yeah.
Except Joel and Dina.
[static buzzing]
- Well, where the fuck are they?
- I don't know.
They're not responding.
Try 'em again.
Again!
Copper Mine,
this is Jackson, come in.
[static warbling]
Copper Mine, come in.
[static buzzing]
Joel, answer the goddamn radio!
[static warbling]
Fuck!
Every ten seconds, Amy.
You hear me?
Every ten seconds!
[Amy] Copper Mine,
this is Jackson, come in.
- [Ellie] [muffled] Jesse.
- What?
- [muffled] Check it.
- [scoffs]
[chuckles]
Did he make this?
- Yeah.
- I'm taking this with me.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
And as much weed
as I can shove into my pack.
- Nope.
- Dude, you're gonna be in charge
of Jackson one day, we all know.
But that day has not yet come.
[Amy distorted over radio]
[static warbling]
Repeat.
[Amy] [distorted over radio]
Copper Mine, do you copy?
This is Jesse,
you're barely there. Amy?
[Amy] [distorted] Jesse, have you seen
Joel or Dina?
[Jesse] Repeat.
[Amy] [distorted] Have you heard from
Joel or Dina?
No, why?
[Amy] They haven't checked in.
Are you near Copper Mine?
- [whispering] Fuck.
- Amy.
Amy, come back.
[static warbling]
Amy!
[exhales sharply]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
- [grunting]
- [Cordyceps rustling]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[Jesse] The route's an oval
around the mine.
We gotta split up
and come at it from both sides.
Northwest and northeast.
Meet up in the middle.
I'll take northeast.
How much time do you think we have?
If the wind holds steady,
maybe 20 minutes.
You gotta get
to the mine by then,
Ellie, whether you
find them or not.
- Yeah, you fucking too, Jesse.
- [horse whinnying]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Dina]
Joel, we gotta go faster!
[Joel]
I know! I'm tryin'!
[infected clamoring]
[Cordyceps rustling]
[grunting]
[distant screeching]
[gasps]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[snarling and screeching]
[people chattering]
Tommy!
[wind whistling]
Bell! Bell! Hit the bell!
[bell ringing]
[panting]
- They're coming!
- Raiders or infected?
Infected!
Five minutes out!
[Maria] Follow the plan.
I'll take the roofs.
You take Main Street.
- Go.
- [guard] Go! Let's go!
[Maria] Hey, you two with me!
Roofs! Let's go!
- [bell ringing]
- [people shouting]
[Tommy] [on bullhorn]
Basements and roofs!
Get off the street!
[bell continues ringing]
[panting] Okay.
[door bangs open]
[people panting]
[baby fussing and crying]
[thudding]
Hurry!
[metallic creaking]
[bell ringing]
[infected clamoring]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[growling and snarling]
[tank hissing]
[bell continues ringing]
[grunts]
[clamoring continues]
[motor rumbling]
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
[distant clamoring]
- Jackson Hole!
- [guards] Jackson Hole!
Get ready!
[barrels clanging]
[clamoring intensifies]
[loud banging]
[crunching]
- [banging continues]
- [wheels creaking]
Push! Push!
- Go, go, go!
- [Tommy] Go! Go!
Push!
[crunching]
[growling and snarling]
Rifles!
[gunfire]
[yells]
[bullets whizzing]
[gunfire continues]
[shrieking]
Now! Now!
[♪ tense music playing]
[Tommy grunting]
[explosions booming]
[infected screeching]
- [gunfire continues]
- [explosions continue]
[screeching continues]
- Whoa! Whoa.
- [horse neighing]
[all panting]
[Dina]
What? Oh, God.
- [Joel] I have to go back.
- [Dina] We won't make it.
- If I don't make it, I don't make it.
- We're almost there!
The lodge is just up ahead.
It's like a minute.
- Really?
- We've got blankets, ammo.
My friends can help you
get back.
We can fight.
Fast!
- [gunfire continues]
- [shells jingling]
[infected screeching]
- [fire roaring]
- [screeching continues]
[gunfire continues]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[distant roaring]
[distant roaring continues]
[Bloater roaring]
[guards shouting]
They're gonna breach.
They're gonna breach!
[loud banging]
- [deep growling]
- [wood cracking]
[heavy panting]
They're breaking through!
Get ready!
Get in there.
[flame thrower whooshing]
[♪ tense music playing]
[banging]
- [roaring]
- [infected clamoring]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[guns clicking]
[screeching]
[gunfire]
[growling and snarling]
[gunfire continues]
[clamoring continues]
[glass shattering]
- [muffled clamoring]
- [banging]
[door rattling]
[screeching and snarling]
[yelling]
- [screeching]
- [guard yelling]
- [flame thrower whooshing]
- [infected snarling]
[shrieking]
[screaming]
[guard whimpering]
[Bloater growling]
[gunfire continues]
[screaming]
[growling]
[roaring]
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Right here!
Hey!
[snarling and growling]
Come here! Come here!
[roaring]
[gunfire continues]
[infected screeching]
[guard grunts]
- You good?
- [infected snarling]
[guard screams]
[panting]
[♪ tense music playing]
No!
[grunting]
[panting]
Fuck!
[growling]
[shouting]
[deep growling]
[panting, yelling]
[growling]
- [shouting]
- [flame thrower whooshing]
[Bloater roaring]
[grunting]
- [growling]
- [flame thrower whooshing]
- [tank hissing]
- [Tommy shouting]
- [Bloater roaring]
- [footsteps stomping]
[Tommy shouting]
[tank hissing]
[shouting]
Come on, let's go!
[hissing weakening]
[yells]
[flame throwing clicking]
[snarling]
[roaring]
[flames sizzling]
[panting]
Jesus.
[grunting]
- [gunfire]
- [people shouting]
[grunting and snarling]
[screeching and shouting]
- [gunshot]
- [grunts]
[Maria panting]
[dogs barking]
Go!
[barking continues]
[gunfire continues]
[flames roaring]
[Tommy grunting]
[dogs barking]
- [infected snarling]
- [dogs growling]
[infected shrieking]
- [dog growling]
- [infected choking]
- [Mel] Abby!
- [Nora] Abby!
- [Manny] Abby!
- Abby!
- [Mel] Hey, horses!
- [Owen] Horses!
- Horses!
- We got horses!
[wind whooshing]
[Abby grunts]
Come on. Come on.
Inside! Inside!
[shivering]
[Nora]
Abby, you okay?
Oh, fuck.
[shivering]
- [Joel panting]
- [Dina shivering]
Help them too.
[bags zipping]
[Mel] No, no, no, uh, let's keep
your coat on, alright?
It's okay.
I think I see
just a little frostbite
on your wrist,
but it's not too bad.
I'm gonna take a look.
Easy.
We're gonna raise
your body temperature
up slowly, okay?
[shivering] What's the...
who are you?
Hang on. I gotta jump on this,
or you're gonna lose skin.
[Joel] Okay, everybody
grab blankets, ammo,
whatever weapons you have,
we're headin' out
- in three minutes.
- Uh, sorry.
I'm-- I'm Abby.
This is Nora, Manny,
Owen, and Mel.
Jackson, come in.
Tommy, come in.
Do you copy?
Her name's Dina.
- [Joel] Jackson, come in.
- Dina?
- [Joel] Jackson!
- [Abby] And he...
is Joel.
[Joel]
Hey, Jackson, do you copy?
Does anyone copy?
Any patrols, anyone?
- Tommy, if you can hear me, we've got these--
- Joel. Joel. Joel.
Ch-ch-ch, ah-ah.
[♪ tense music playing]
We're not gonna hurt her.
Not if you cooperate.
We're just gonna put her
to sleep for a while.
Trust me.
It's for the best.
Do it.
If you don't do it, I'm gonna smash her
in the fuckin' head.
You wanna rob us?
Fine, take what you want.
Do we look like raiders to you?
No.
What do we look like?
Military.
Fireflies?
Used to be.
Haven't you heard?
There are no more Fireflies.
They're all gone.
[♪ tense music continues]
- [softly] Okay.
- [Dina gasps]
[grunts] No, get--
Get that shit away from--
This is gonna put you to sleep.
This is going to put you
to sleep for one hour.
That is all, I promise.
I promise.
[Dina panting]
No. No. No!
[gasps]
[thuds]
[softly exhales]
[Abby]
See? Breathing.
That's a nice scar you have
on your right temple there.
I'd say you're about,
what, six feet?
In your 60s now?
[chuckling] You actually
are pretty handsome.
Congrats on that.
I'm gonna give you one chance
to tell the truth, Joel.
If you do... let's face it.
We'll all know.
I'll let her live.
- Wait, Abby, I thought--
- Shut up!
Where was the last place
you saw the Fireflies?
Salt Lake.
At least you're honest.
I saved your life.
What life?
[Joel screaming, grunting]
[sighs]
Tourniquet him.
Mel, let's just do
what we came to do.
[Joel gasping]
[belt rattling]
[Joel grunting]
[Joel breathing heavily]
[Joel screaming]
[♪ tense music playing]
You're tough.
I guess you probably have to be,
killing all those people.
Do you know how many
you killed that day?
Did you count as you went, or...
I guess maybe it just
didn't matter?
Eighteen soldiers.
And one doctor.
You remember that one.
An unarmed doctor
you shot in the head.
[inaudible]
Yeah.
That was my dad.
Guess you probably
already figured.
The nurses said you barely
even looked at him
when you pulled the trigger.
And then, you just walked
right past his body
and out the door.
But I looked at him.
I saw him.
I was 19.
[sobbing softly]
I've been in a militia
for five years now.
Seattle.
I'd warn you not to go there,
but little chance of that.
Anyway, our commander
trained us to follow a code.
We don't kill people
that can't defend themselves.
And right now...
that's you.
But I am going to kill you.
Because it doesn't matter
if you have a code like me,
or you're a lawless
piece of shit like you.
There are just some things...
everyone agrees
are just fucking wrong.
[sobbing]
[sighs]
[sniffling]
You know, it's funny.
I have waited so long--
[Joel] Oh, just shut the fuck up
and do it already.
[sighs]
[♪ tense music playing]
You...
stupid... old man.
You don't get to rush this.
[Joel screaming]
- [Abby grunting]
- [Joel screaming]
[panting]
- [shouting]
- [Joel screaming]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[horse whinnying]
[grunts]
- [Abby shouting]
- [fists thudding]
- [Mel sobbing]
- [Abby grunting]
[Abby continues shouting]
Abby.
- [Abby shouting]
- Abby.
[shouting echoes]
- [horse neighing]
- [Ellie] Whoa.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[wind whistling]
[muffled thudding]
[faint shouting]
[loud thuds]
[shouting continues]
[Owen]
That's enough!
- [Abby shouting]
- [fists thudding]
- [grunting]
- No!
- Ah! Fuck!
[grunting]
- [knife clatters]
- [Ellie crying]
- Stupid fucking bitch!
- No!
- [Ellie screaming]
- [Owen] No!
- Joel!
Joel! Joel!
Joel, get up.
Joel, fucking get up!
[whispers] Get up.
End it.
Joel, get up.
Please.
Please, get up. Get up.
[grunting]
Fucking get up!
[panting]
Get up. Get up.
[sobbing]
Get up.
No.
Please, no, please.
Please don't.
Please-- please don't.
Please don't do it! Please!
Please don't!
Don't!
Please don't! Don't!
[metal clangs]
[muffled screaming]
[high-pitch whistling]
[inaudible]
[muffled shouting]
[gasps]
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna kill you!
You're gonna die!
You're all gonna fucking die!
- [kick thuds]
- [gasps]
[wheezing]
Fucking pendejo.
[Ellie whimpering]
[♪ somber music playing]
[grunting]
[exhales sharply]
[panting]
- [grunting]
- [metal clanging]
[Ellie whimpering]
[fire crackling]
[♪ "Through the Valley" by Ashley Johnson
and Chris Rondinella playing]
♪ I walk
through the valley ♪
♪ Of the shadow of death ♪
♪ And I fear no evil ♪
♪ Because
I'm blind to it all ♪
♪ And my mind
and my gun ♪
♪ They comfort me ♪
♪ Because I know
I'll kill my enemies ♪
♪ When they come ♪
♪ Surely, goodness
and mercy will follow me ♪
- ♪ All the days of my life ♪
- [gunshot]
♪ And I will dwell
on this Earth ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
♪ Said I walk beside
the still waters ♪
♪ And they restore my soul ♪
♪ But I can't walk
on the path of the right ♪
♪ Because I'm wrong ♪
♪ 'Cause I walk
through the valley ♪
♪ Of the shadow of death ♪
♪ And I fear no evil ♪
♪ Because I'm blind ♪
♪ Oh, and I walk beside
the still waters ♪
♪ And they restore my soul ♪
♪ But I know when I die ♪
♪ My soul is damned ♪
[wind blowing softly]
[wind continues blowing]