[radio chatter]
[soldier] Did he try
to break it for you?
[chatter stops]
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
[door opens]
Your soldiers are loyal to you.
I think they're worried
we're gonna execute you.
If I was getting executed,
Isaac would've come himself.
There was a shooting
near the borderline
between us and the Scars.
Treaty might be broken.
He's dealing with that now.
If it's war again, we're gonna
need all the soldiers we have.
So he's wondering
why you apparently killed
some of your own men.
[Park] Including Leon.
Leon?
Leon.
[Hanrahan]
Jesus.
- [lighter flicks]
- What happened?
- My unit is responsible for--
- Securing the hospital.
I know your orders.
I gave them, Elise.
What happened?
We cleared the ground floor
up to the sixth.
A few scattered
infected here or there.
Nothing we couldn't handle.
All that was left
was the basement.
B1, B2, B3.
We were expecting the worst,
the kind of environment
they like.
Plus, the old-timers said
that down there
was where they brought the
first Cordyceps patients in '03.
On top of that,
we had an access problem.
These stairwells here,
here, and here caved in,
and all the elevator cars
were stuck in their shafts
just below ground level.
The only way in or out
of the basement
is here, this stairwell.
So yesterday, that's where
I sent a squad, down to B1.
- And?
- Nothing.
The whole floor was empty,
not even rats.
So today, B2,
hoping for more of the same,
I sent another squad down,
and I put Leon
in charge 'cause...
he's my best.
A few minutes in,
he radios back.
There's Cordyceps
on the walls, the floor.
Chances are,
they'll find infected next,
but that's what they
were down there for,
so I told him to proceed.
Five minutes later,
he radios again.
This time, he...
he was struggling to breathe.
He could hardly talk.
I thought maybe he had been bit.
I said, "Leon, were you bit?"
He said...
He said, "It's in the air."
[♪ Faint ominous music playing]
He said, "It's in the air.
Seal us in."
And I knew
it wasn't in the vents,
or we would've all
been infected weeks ago.
So, I scrambled my other team
and we locked
the only door to B2,
and we locked the only
door to B1.
And we did what Leon said.
We sealed them in.
[Hanrahan]
Nothing else has gotten out?
No one else has gotten sick?
Okay.
The hospital's a resource
we can't afford to lose.
I'll inform only the people
who absolutely
need to know, and no one else.
As far as I'm concerned,
Sergeant Park,
you resolved the situation
permanently
and heroically.
We owe you a debt.
I'm sorry about your son.
[♪ Pensive theme music playing]
[♪ Theme concludes]
[birdsong]
[distant explosion booming]
[distant gunfire]
[radio static]
[W.L.F. soldier] [over radio] Patrol
14 heading north to 13th and Bradford.
One mile out.
[W.L.F. soldier 2]
One mile out. Copy.
Mobile three.
[W.L.F. soldier 3]
[indistinct radio chatter
continues]
[W.L.F. soldier 1]
Possible movement
at the convention center.
- [electricity buzzing]
- [Ellie sighs]
Ta-da!
- What?
- Lights.
Oh, good.
They have a big-ass
generator down there.
Natural gas, baby.
- You figure it out yet?
- Gettin' there.
You'll find a safe way
to get us to the hospital though, right?
[chuckles]
Can I help?
Um... no.
Why, because I'm stupid?
That's not the word I would use.
Really?
What word then?
Non-school-oriented.
Fuck you, I went to school.
Let me help.
I'm triangulating.
- Do you know how that works?
- Yes.
With triangles.
It's pretty standard.
I get a bearing of
their troop movements,
and then triangulate
back to their bases.
I'm estimating angles, though.
I mean, if I had a protractor,
it would be a lot more accurate.
Oh, I actually brought
a protractor.
- You did?
- No.
I don't know what that is,
and I hated math.
I'm gonna leave you alone now
and go and explore
the rest of this place,
because you're smart as fuck
and you're figuring it out.
- Ellie.
- Yes?
[chuckles]
- [walkie beeps]
- [radio static]
[door opens]
[♪ Gentle music playing]
♪
[♪ strums guitar]
[tuning guitar]
[♪ Playing melody]
[softly singing]
♪ If I ever were to lose you ♪
[♪ stops playing]
[low rumbling]
[sighs]
[door opens]
Did you figure it out?
- I think so, yeah.
- [door closes loudly]
Good.
[Dina] We follow a safe path
west until this spot.
Here, let me show you.
They run a line of patrols
north and south, like this.
They're pretty evenly
spread out,
so they're watching
that entire area.
But there's a gap
between here and here.
Now, on this map,
do you see this long-ass building?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
So, we cut through and slip by.
What is that long-ass building?
No clue.
But it's set off
from the residential area,
so maybe it's a warehouse
or something.
It's a big fucking something
for them just to ignore.
Why aren't they patrolling it?
[Dina sighs]
- Infected.
- Probably.
If we make it through,
we pop out behind their patrols.
The hospital's maybe
a quarter mile from there.
Nora should be
on the first floor,
far end of the North Wing.
Wait, how the fuck
do you know that?
They never shut up.
I hear everything.
Morons.
Middle of a fucking war,
and they're just broadcasting
their positions.
Yeah, so I've been
thinking about that.
You know these people
they're fighting, the Scars?
We already know they use
bows and arrows, right?
And they seem culty,
or at least really religious.
- You ever hear of Amish people?
- Amish people? No.
Well, they were around back
in '03, Pennsylvania mostly.
But they chose to live
like it was the 1800s.
Maybe the Scars are like that?
No electricity or technology.
Because these motherfuckers
talk on the radio
like they know
no one's listening.
Yeah, and they didn't care
that a walkie was missing.
It's good.
They're overconfident.
- It gives us an edge.
- It does.
But what we're
doing is reckless,
so kind of a wash.
[indistinct radio chatter
continues]
If we were to leave now,
it'd be dark by the time
we got to the big
fucking something, right?
Mm-hmm.
[distant seagulls cawing]
[Ellie sighs]
Let's go be reckless.
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[distant explosion booming]
Are you sure this way is safe?
You don't trust me?
I trust you.
I don't trust Seattle.
Me neither, but let's just talk
like everything's fine
because if I get too anxious,
I'm gonna barf again.
[Ellie]
Alright, how 'bout this?
What are you gonna name it?
Huh?
Oh, uh, if it's a girl, Ellie.
If it's a boy, Elijah.
- Really?
- No.
Why?
It's a cool name.
What the fuck?
[insects buzzing]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
[Dina retching]
[insects buzzing]
We shouldn't be here.
We shouldn't have come,
I shouldn't have dragged you here.
You're having a fucking baby.
What am I doing?
Dina, do you wanna go back?
I'll take you back.
You don't need to do this with me.
Oh, I'm so fucking stupid.
[Ellie breathing heavily]
You know, you never asked me
about the first person I killed.
[Ellie] Huh?
Okay. Who?
When I was little,
we lived in a cabin
in a forest north of Santa Fe.
And there were
scattered families around,
but mostly it was just us alone.
And I would get so bored
cooped up with my mom
and sister,
I would just beg them,
"Just let me play outside."
But my mom was scared
and she wouldn't let me
go outside alone.
But one day, I just fucking did,
and I had a gun,
so who's gonna fuck with me?
Now, you already know
how this story ends
because I don't live in a cabin
north of Santa Fe anymore,
and I don't have a mom
or sister anymore.
But since everyone's
past is fucked
and we've all heard
everyone's fucked stories,
how do you think this one goes?
I don't know.
Uh, Raiders?
Just one.
And then?
Uh, you got home.
They were dead, he was gone.
Almost.
He was still there.
I heard them screaming
and I ran back with my gun out
but I was too slow
because I was fucking eight.
And when he heard me,
he turned around,
and he looked really startled.
And when I shot him,
he looked more...
startled.
Fuck, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know, I thought...
- How did you get to Jackson?
- It doesn't matter.
This is what matters.
Whatever reason Joel gave
those people to do what they did,
he didn't deserve that.
And I think,
what if I hadn't snuck out?
What if my mom and sister
were beaten to death
in front of me?
What if that motherfucker
made me watch as he did it?
Would it make a difference
if my family
had hurt his people first?
No.
And if I hadn't killed him...
if he had gotten away...
I promise you, I would have
hunted him down forever.
Forever.
[♪ Soft, melancholy
music playing]
I'll go back, if you want.
And I'll keep going,
if you want.
There's no right answer.
If I die, it's on me.
It won't be your fault.
So, what do you want to do?
[♪ Soft, melancholy
music continues]
[whispering]
Keep going.
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[dog barking]
- [Dina] Do you see anything?
- No. Let's go.
[Ellie]
Hurry! Down, down, down.
[vehicle rumbling]
Cover me.
[♪ Dramatic music
continues playing]
[metal rattling]
[rustling]
[banging]
At least we're not blocked in.
And there are
two more positives.
The search lights are up high
to scan the outside,
which means there'll be
no line of sight to the inside.
Good.
What's the other positive?
That door's open,
and nothing's come out
to kill us... yet.
- Great.
- Maybe.
- I'm gonna take a peek.
- Yeah, you should do that,
because you're the one
who can't get infected.
[Dina]
How's it look?
Haunted, but empty.
Oh, just like us.
Look, I'm not saying there won't
be infected somewhere in there.
In fact, there's no fucking way
this entire place is empty.
But simple logic, it's not
gonna be a horde, right?
We're not underground,
and the Wolves
are right next door
with their vehicles and lights.
A horde's not gonna
ignore that shit.
So what, we've got maybe
a few strays
and a couple clickers?
We can handle that.
We've done it like a million times.
Yeah.
We'll be okay.
But shooting
has to be a last resort, okay?
Because if the Wolves
hear gunfire,
- then we'll have a whole army up our ass.
- Fine.
- Ellie.
- What?
If it gets bad,
and we have to make a choice
between shooting or running,
we run.
Last resort, I got it.
Oh, you think
that no matter what happens,
I'm just gonna start firing?
Literally every single time.
Yes.
Don't get angry.
You're a little crazy.
And that's exciting.
It's one of the reasons
I love you.
But I do wanna
make it out of here.
You love me?
[♪ Gentle music playing]
- I re--
- Oh, I know.
So, tell me again,
what's the plan?
Knives or run.
Okay, Crazy.
- [knife unsheathing]
- Here we go.
[distant dog barking]
[door squeaking]
[♪ Tense, ominous music playing]
[water dripping]
So far, so good.
W-- wait.
[whispering]
Do you hear something?
No.
So, this way then?
Yeah.
[door squeaking open]
[Dina] Lots of windows in here.
Let's be careful.
Okay.
[♪ Tense music playing]
Dina.
[mysterious gasping]
[mysterious breathing]
What the fuck is that?
And why is it hiding?
I think it's a smart one,
like the one that stalked me
at the supermarket.
Okay, but you killed that one,
so we can kill
this one too, right?
Yes, I killed it.
Not before it got me.
- It fucking bit you?
- What was I supposed to do, tell you?
- You would've--
- [stalker vocalizing]
Listen, if it's like
the other one,
it's gonna be fast
and it's gonna be sneaky.
But this time, it's two on one.
Now, that fucker's
gonna try to flank us,
so I say we flank it first.
We split up.
Whichever one it follows,
the other one comes up
and takes it out from behind.
Plan?
Plan.
[stalker vocalizing]
[stalker grunting]
[screeching lightly]
[both gasp]
- What do we do?
- I don't know.
Let's go back the way we came.
If we run, they're gonna chase
so we have to go slow.
[stalker vocalizing]
[Ellie and Dina panting]
[infected grunting]
You see that fencing over there?
I'm gonna lure as many as I can.
You're gonna run in there,
secure the gate,
secure it however you can,
and stay in there.
Dina.
I can get bit a lot.
- [infected shouting]
- You can't. Do as I say.
Go!
- [infected shouting]
- [gunshots]
[Dina panting]
[infected screaming]
[Dina shouting]
- [gunshot]
- [infected grunting]
[infected continues shouting]
[gunshots]
[distant gunshots]
[grunting]
[stalker snarling]
[Ellie screaming]
[gunshots]
[gun clicking]
- [infected continue shouting]
- [Dina whimpering]
- [stalker snarling]
- [Ellie screaming]
[gunshots]
[gunshots continue]
[sound muffed]
[muffled panting]
- Did you get bit?
- What? No.
[Dina]
She's okay.
I was watching.
They didn't bite her.
- Jesse, I swear.
- [distant infected screeching]
We gotta go.
[♪ Tense music playing]
[W.L.F. soldiers shouting
indistinctly]
[W.L.F. soldier]
Move! Move! Move!
[Jesse]
Don't stop! Keep going!
- [gunshots]
- I'll shoot 'em! Go!
[W.L.F. soldier 1]
Heading west!
[W.L.F. soldier 2]
Over there! Over there!
[gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
[♪ Tense music continues]
[all panting]
[Jesse]
The park!
We can lose 'em in there.
Come on!
[gunshot]
- [panting]
- [bushes rustling]
[W.L.F. soldier 1] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stop. Stop.
We don't go in there.
[W.L.F. soldier 2] Looks like five...
three unknowns,
chased into the park.
Heavily armed.
- Not Scars.
- [Ellie] What are they doing?
[W.L.F. soldier 1] If they try
and come out, shoot 'em.
Not coming in the park.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Great.
More infected.
Maybe, but we can't
go back that way.
Come on.
[Ellie] Jesse.
Jesse.
- What?
- How did you find us?
The map you left in the theater.
Impressive triangulation,
by the way.
Thanks, that was all Dina.
Trust me,
I didn't think it was you.
How did you find the theater?
Do I look like I wanna
fucking talk to you right now?
You came alone?
No. Me and Tommy.
We split up when
we got to the city.
- Cover more ground.
- I can't believe they sent you after us.
They didn't, but you two
were gonna die out here,
so we snuck out the next night.
And it's a good thing we did.
You know what,
we were doing pretty fucking good
- up until--
- Up until what?
[owl hooting]
Until we weren't.
Is Tommy okay?
Hopefully.
We're supposed
to rendezvous in the morning.
- [Dina] So, what now?
- [Jesse] Find a way out,
get back to the theater,
shelter for the night.
Meet up with Tommy,
and then we all go home.
- No.
- [Dina] Ellie.
[whistling in distance]
[Dina] [whispering]
What the fuck is that?
[whistling]
[whistling continues]
[softly] Hey. Go.
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
[W.L.F. soldier]
No, wait, please.
Please, please, please!
I'm not-- I'm not
like the others. Please.
No, no, no, wait.
Wait, wait, I'll join!
- I-- I'll join you. I'll join.
- [Seraphite] Too late, Wolf.
[W.L.F. soldier] No, no. No, no, no, wait!
I know things.
I know what Isaac is planning.
I can help you. I can--
[gasping]
[Seraphite] We have
no interest in your words.
"For the corrupted soul
knows only lies."
So taught the Prophet.
[all Seraphites]
May She guide us.
No. No. No. No. No.
[whimpering]
No. No, no, no.
Please, please, please. No.
No. No.
[sobbing]
No! No! No!
[whimpering]
[sobbing] No.
[fabric tearing]
[soldier continues whimpering]
Oh, please, please, no.
[Seraphite]
He is nested in sin.
- No, no.
- [all Seraphites] Free him,
that he may know Her love.
No, no.
No, no, no, no.
Please, please, please, no.
[sobbing]
- [shouting]
- [flesh squelching]
[blood pouring]
[soldier gagging,
blood gurgling]
Now, he is free.
[whistling]
- [arrow whooshing]
- [Dina grunting]
- [Jesse] Oh, fuck!
- [Dina whimpering]
[whistling]
I'll lead them away.
Get her out.
Go! I'll meet you
back at the theater.
- Fucking go!
- [gunshots]
You won't get away, Wolf.
She sees you.
She watches over us all.
[♪ Tense, dramatic
music playing]
- [whistling]
- [arrow whooshing]
[Ellie panting]
- [whistling]
- [arrow whooshing]
- [Ellie grunting]
- [whistling]
[whistling]
[Seraphite]
He's not here.
[whistling]
- May She guide us.
[Seraphite] Alright, spread out.
Keep moving.
[♪ Tense music playing]
- [insects chirring]
- [dog panting]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[radio chatter continues]
[leaves rustling]
[dog growling, barking]
[barking continues]
[W.L.F. soldier] [over radio]
What do we got?
Not sure.
Checking it out.
- [dog growling]
- Come on, Bonnie.
[Bonnie continues barking]
[barking continues]
[growling and barking]
[W.L.F. soldier]
It was a critter or something.
- All clear.
- [Bonnie barking]
[distant barking continues]
[scissors snipping]
You're all set.
[people chattering quietly]
- [door closes]
- [fluorescent lights buzzing]
[Ellie]
Put that shit down.
Hands up.
Turn around.
You remember me?
Yeah, you remember me.
- What do you want?
- Where's Abby?
- I don't know.
- Yes, you do.
You shoot me, the sound will have
every soldier come running.
You'll still be dead.
Tell me where she is
and maybe I let you go.
- We could've killed you.
- Maybe you should have.
Or maybe you should've
stayed the fuck out of Jackson, Nora.
Where's Abby?
I'm sorry you saw it happen.
No one should ever have to see
something like that.
- Stop it.
- Sometimes at night,
I still hear his screams.
It was a terrible thing,
the way he died.
Yeah.
Yeah, the little bitch
got what he deserved.
[Ellie exclaiming]
Motherfucker!
Intruder!
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[gunshot, glass shattering]
Hey! Shoot her!
- [gunfire]
- [glass shattering]
[♪ Dramatic music continues]
[grunting]
Oh, no, no, no, no.
- Nora, you're gonna fucking die!
- [Nora grunting]
[Ellie] Nora!
[panting]
- [gunshot]
- [Nora grunting]
- [thud]
- [creaking]
- [grunting]
- [chains rattling]
[elevator banging]
[groaning]
- [gunshot]
- [gasps]
[gunshots]
[W.L.F. soldier]
Fuck, it's open.
The fucking shaft is open!
- Seal off the hallway!
- [soldier] Back, back, back!
[W.L.F. soldier] [indistinct]
The shaft is open.
[echoing thud]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
[♪ Ominous music
continues playing]
[infected gasping faintly]
[exhaling slowly]
[breathing raggedly]
[infected gasping loudly]
[wheezing]
[coughing in distance]
[coughing continues]
- [electricity buzzing]
- [coughing continues]
[coughing increasing]
[Nora coughing]
[straining]
You stupid bitch.
Spores.
[groaning]
We're breathing spores.
We're infected.
You killed us both.
Did I?
[wheezing]
You're... you're her.
The immune girl, you're...
[wheezing]
You're real.
Yeah.
Where's Abby?
Don't you know what he did?
- I don't care.
- You don't care?
He killed everyone
in that hospital.
Including the only
fucking person alive
that could make a cure from you.
That was Abby's father.
And Joel...
Joel shot him in the head.
That's what he did.
I know.
[gasps]
Oh...
[scoffs]
[♪ Ominous music continues]
Where's Abby?
[coughing]
No.
[shallow breathing]
[metal scraping]
Where is she?
No.
- [Ellie shouting]
- [Nora screaming]
[Nora whimpering]
Where is she?
[struggling] No.
- [shouting]
- [screaming]
Where is she?!
- [metal scraping]
- [Ellie yelling]
[birdsong]
[door opening, creaking]
Hey, kiddo.
[distant dog barking]
Hi.
[♪ "Present Tense"
by Pearl Jam playing]
♪ Do you see the way
that tree bends? ♪
♪ Does it inspire? ♪
♪ Leaning out
to catch the sun's rays ♪
♪ A lesson to be applied ♪
♪ Are you gettin'
somethin' out of this ♪
♪ All encompassing trip ♪
[♪ song fades out]