[boy breathing heavily]
It'll be fine.
He's gonna beat
the shit outta me.
I said, it'll be fine.
I'm-- I'm gonna get the belt.
No, you're not.
I will.
[distant dog barking]
[sniffling]
Just go to your room,
and stay there.
[footsteps receding]
- [dog barking]
- [vehicle approaching]
[door slamming shut]
[father sighs]
I'm back on patrol
in 30 minutes.
So, talk fast.
What happened?
You know what happened.
Yeah, well,
I wanna hear it from you.
I was buying pot
from this other kid.
He tried to rip me off,
and we got into a fight.
That's what you're going with?
- Okay.
- I'm telling the truth.
No. No, you're not.
I think Tommy was buying
the drugs, not you.
I think you happened to walk by,
saw what was going on,
- and started punching.
- Tommy didn't do anyth--
I talked to the kid
you beat up, Joel,
and the officers
who got called to the scene.
I'm not stupid.
And if you and Tommy
weren't my sons,
you'd both be in juvie
right now.
You're not gonna hurt him.
[scoffs]
- [refrigerator door opens]
- [bottles rattling]
[beer cans click open]
[slurping, sighs]
Did I ever tell you about
that time I stole a candy bar?
I was...
ten. [chuckles]
Grandpa found out,
made me give it back,
made me apologize
to the cashier.
And then, we went home.
Just before I got out
of the car, man, he just...
He broke my jaw.
There was blood everywhere.
Grandma thought I was dead.
My mouth was wired shut
for two months.
Everybody knew why.
It was humiliating.
If you know what it feels like,
then why?
That's not why
I'm telling you this.
Okay, yeah, I've hit you.
And I've hit Tommy.
But never like that.
[choking up]
Not even close.
I mean, maybe I go too far, I...
I don't know, I just...
[sighs]
I don't know.
But I'm doing a little better
than my father did.
[swallows hard]
And you know,
when it's your turn...
I hope you do
a little better than me.
[father breathes deeply,
sniffles]
[door opens, closes]
[♪ pensive theme music playing]
[♪ theme concludes]
[bottles clinking]
[patrons chattering]
[door opens, closes]
[knocking]
Oh. The new guy.
Been here two months, Seth.
[Seth] Like I said.
Got somethin' for me?
I'll be fucked.
[toys clattering]
My grandkids
are gonna love these.
- How'd you find 'em?
- Searched the old homes
out by Hoback.
I searched those homes.
Well, I know where to look
'cause I'm a smuggler,
and you're a...
I wasn't always this.
[toy blocks thud]
I was a cop.
Milwaukee PD.
[sniffing]
So, a trade's a trade.
We can make what you want
and have it to you by, uh...
Friday.
No, I need it by tomorrow.
Vanilla or chocolate?
Say vanilla, it's easier.
Vanilla.
Oh, I need one more thing.
Relax.
You got a lot of 'em.
[♪ light music playing]
[blowing]
[power tool whirring]
[♪ light music
continues playing]
[♪ strumming guitar slowly]
- [birds chirping]
- [distant dog barking]
- [door opens]
- [Tommy] Joel!
- What happened?
- Oh, where'd you come from?
Painkillers, she's alright.
Come on.
- [Joel] Painkillers?
- No, no, no.
No, no, no, leave it.
Leave it, don't touch it.
[Joel]
Tommy, what happened?
She was working KP
and she burned her arm.
Well, how?
I pushed it
right up against a pot.
You did this on purpose?
I was like, "Here we go,"
and then I fucking went.
- What? Why?
- No one saw. I was on my own.
And I took it off and
it was all red and melting
and gross.
You know what it smelled like?
Pork.
- Who let this happen?
- What do you mean, "let"?
- Who saw this comin'? I was eating my damn dinner.
- Ow! [wincing]
- Oh, it hurts.
- Okay.
- Ow!
- Easy, baby girl.
- Easy, easy.
- Dr. V ran over to the clinic.
He's gonna come by here
with another shot.
[Joel] Ellie.
[Ellie breathing heavily]
I just really wanted to wear
short sleeves again.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
[shushing]
It's okay.
You're okay.
[Joel kissing]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[sighs]
- [Joel] Goddammit, Seth.
- Hey.
Hey.
"Happy 15th Birthday, Eli."
[Joel groaning]
Well, let's hope Seth
bakes better than he spells.
[mouth full]
He does.
- [chuckles]
- It's really good.
[Ellie laughing]
Oh, right.
Uh, stay right there.
I got somethin' else for you.
Close your eyes.
- Keep 'em closed.
- [sighs]
Okay, turn toward me.
And... open.
- Whoa, what's this?
- Some folks call this a "gee-tar."
[Joel chuckles]
I borrowed one of your drawings
for inspiration.
Uh, took a bit of restorin'.
Real bone saddle here.
Lacquered the whole body
and, uh, used a Dremel
to carve the, uh--
Well, that's a rotary drill.
Or could be a saw,
dependin' on the tip.
But, actually,
it's a pretty versatile tool.
Anyway.
I had promised
I would teach you, so...
- Um...
- Oh.
Uh, well, if you want
a lesson later...
Let me hear something.
- What do you mean, play it?
- And sing.
No.
No, no, no, no.
No, I don't sing.
It's my fucking birthday, man.
Let's see what you got.
Hmm.
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
[softly] Shit.
[♪ playing "Future Days"
by Pearl Jam]
♪ If I ever were to lose you ♪
♪ I'd surely lose myself ♪
♪ Everything that
I have found dear ♪
♪ I've not found by myself ♪
♪ Try and sometimes
you'll succeed ♪
♪ To make this man of me ♪
♪ All my stolen,
missing parts ♪
♪ I've no need for anymore ♪
♪ I believe ♪
♪ And I believe
'cause I can see ♪
♪ Our future days ♪
♪ Days of you and me ♪
[♪ stops playing guitar]
Well...
- That didn't suck.
- [chuckles lightly]
[Ellie lightly chuckles]
[wincing]
I understand.
Your arm.
Happy birthday, kiddo.
[♪ light music playing]
- [Ellie] Is it a bow and arrow?
- [Joel] Nope.
[Ellie]
Is it water guns?
- [Joel] No.
- Is it... a dinosaur!
- You're not gonna guess.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is it a "lotter" of kittens?
A "lotter"?
You mean a litter?
A litter of kittens?
Really?
- Really. And no.
- Fuck.
Is it a convertible?
[Joel] The hell are you gonna
do with a convertible?
- [Ellie] Drive it.
- We cross here.
How do you even know
where we are?
I found it on patrol.
You know, Jesse was 16 when
he started going on patrols.
- Is that right?
- Don't get me wrong.
I love counting vegetables
and shoveling sheep shit.
I'm just saying, I think
I could be more useful
outside the wall.
You'll get on patrols
eventually.
You should enjoy
being a kid for now.
Oh, because childhood
has been such a joy for me so far.
You've been 16
all of four hours.
We're not sending you out
until you're trained.
You're gonna need
somethin' called patience.
Jesse said he'd train me
if you let him.
Is there somethin'
going on between you two?
Excuse me?
You spend a lot
of time together.
- [giggling quietly]
- Is it funny?
- [laughing]
- I see the way you look at him.
I got a keen eye
for these sort of things.
- Uh, I don't think you do.
- Alright, none of my business.
But, uh, has anyone
talked to you
about the birds and the bees?
Oh, you mean dicks and vaginas?
- Jesus.
- I tell you what.
I promise you,
I won't get pregnant
if you let me train
for patrols. Deal?
I'll see what I can do.
Okay, how much longer, man?
[sighs]
We're here.
Oh, my God.
It is a dinosaur!
- Joel!
- Like it?
[Ellie panting]
Yeah.
Likes it.
[♪ gentle music playing]
- [grunting]
- Whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
Ellie.
- [grunting]
- Ellie!
Oh, my God.
Careful.
I'm on a motherfucking
dinosaur! [chuckles]
- Joel, there's a museum!
- Yeah, I know!
If you don't fall off
the goddamn T-Rex,
I'll take you there.
[Ellie] [whispering]
This is so cool.
How long have you known
about this place?
A while.
Well, then what the fuck?
I was saving it
for a special day.
You see?
Patience.
Oh, yeah, I've heard of that.
Huh.
[water dripping]
[metal squeaking]
It works?
Somebody must have greased it.
[Ellie] Can you imagine
being up there?
- Would you like to?
- Like to what?
Go to space?
[softly gasps]
[birdsong]
[Ellie] [whispering]
Is it real?
It's real.
That one went up and back.
Apollo 15, 1971.
[♪ gentle music playing]
Well, open it.
[Joel chuckles]
[metal door creaking]
- [whispering] You got it.
- [Ellie sighs]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're going up to space.
You need a helmet.
[grunting]
Pick one.
[glass shattering]
[♪ gentle music playing]
How's it smell in there?
Like space, and dust.
Well, good.
Then, you're ready.
[grunting]
[hatch door thuds]
[Ellie imitating lasers firing]
[imitating static]
People of Discovery, set!
Abort!
[switches clicking]
They sat right here.
[Ellie chuckles]
- Happy birthday, kiddo.
- What's this?
This is something that took
a mighty effort to find.
Play it.
[seat creaking]
Close your eyes.
It'll be worth it.
[Walkman clicking]
[NASA Public Affairs Officer]
Thirty seconds and counting.
Astronauts report it feels good.
T-minus 25 seconds.
Twenty seconds and counting.
T-minus 15 seconds.
Guidance is internal.
Twelve, eleven, ten, nine.
Ignition sequence starts.
[spacecraft whooshing, rattling]
Six, five, four, three,
two, one, zero.
- [rockets booming]
- All engines running.
Liftoff!
We have a liftoff,
32 minutes past the hour,
liftoff on Apollo 11.
[rattling and booming
decreasing]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[birdsong]
I do okay?
Are you kidding me?
[both laughing]
[Ellie sighs]
This is nice.
- We should do this more.
- Yeah. In.
You okay?
Yeah.
[rain pattering]
[rain continues]
[Ellie] [giggling, muffled]
Stop.
[people laughing]
[laughter continues]
- [banging]
- [Ellie] Fuck.
Joel, what the fuck?
Exactly.
What the fuck?
- Get outta here.
- No, wait.
What-- what are you
even doing here?
You're supposed to be on patrol.
I came home early to...
surprise you for your birthday.
- [Ellie] [whispering] Oh, yeah.
- Seventeen, by the way.
Well, I'm 19, so...
I'm gonna go.
- Fuck is that?
- Fuck.
It's not done yet,
it's gonna look better when I fill in--
- [Joel] Leave.
- Right.
[Ellie sighing]
So, all the teenage shit
all at once, huh?
Drugs, and tattoos, and sex.
Experimenting with, uh, with--
[stammering] with girls?
It wasn't sex, and it
wasn't a fucking experiment.
You don't know
what you're sayin'.
We'll discuss this later,
when you're yourself.
- [door slamming]
- [sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain falling]
[thunder continues rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[heavy thudding]
[Ellie grunting]
- The hell are you doing?
- Moving into the garage.
The hell you are.
Ellie, let go.
It's the middle of the night.
It's pissin' rain out there.
Now, get this back on the bed.
There's no heat
or running water in the garage.
- You can't stay there.
- Okay, fine.
Okay, you want to have
this conversation? Fine.
You may not like the rules,
but this is my house.
No, it isn't.
You don't own it.
They gave it to you.
Sorry, to us.
You don't own anything.
[rain continues pattering]
Look, I'm s-sorry
that I got a tattoo,
and smoked weed,
and fooled around with a girl.
Except, I'm not.
Maybe, um...
Maybe it's a good thing
for you to have your own space.
Just give me a few days
and let me fix things up
a little out there.
Okay.
Come on.
[sighs] Thanks.
Sure.
Can I see?
- Did it hurt?
- Yeah.
But kinda good.
It's actually not bad.
Better than the, uh,
one I made on your guitar anyway.
I never did ask.
What is it with the moths?
Um, nothing. Just--
I just read about them
in a book on dreams and stuff.
It's kind of symbolic.
Oh, right.
Yeah, like change and--
and growin' and such.
It's late.
Yeah.
Well, good night.
Night.
[door creaking]
- [door opens]
- [people chattering]
[door closes]
[Joel] Hey.
You guys study, uh,
dreams and stuff, right?
Is there a "Doctor Is In" sign
on me like Lucy
from fuckin' Peanuts?
Yes, some doctors
studied dreams.
The dumb ones, mostly.
So, a moth.
That probably means
change and-- and growth?
No, that would be a butterfly.
Oh.
So, what's a moth?
Death.
If you believe in that shit.
Why?
[footsteps receding]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[♪ soft music playing]
[poster rustling]
Okay, so I've been thinking...
or wondering--
no, thinking,
uh, for a while now...
about Salt Lake City.
I just want to understand it.
So, I wrote down some questions.
Okay?
Okay.
One, if the Fireflies
spotted us a mile
from the hospital,
how did they get surprised
by an entire group of Raiders?
Two.
If the Raiders could
kill all those soldiers,
and Marlene, and you had
to carry me the whole time,
how did we get away?
Three, if there are dozens
of immune people,
- why hasn't anyone heard--
- [knocking]
[knocking]
[Joel] Ellie?
Uh, coming.
- [clearing throat]
- Whoa.
Already dressed.
I figured I'd be waking you up.
Uh, nope.
I had trouble sleeping.
Huh.
Well, guess what?
That works out great
for your birthday present.
You're 19
and you've been patient.
So, I told 'em
I was okay with it.
- With what?
- Your first patrol.
- I'll grab my coat.
- And a gun.
[crow cawing]
[horse chortling]
[Ellie] So, what's the record
for number of kills
on a training run?
Zero. This is
the safest trail we got.
Gotta start easy.
Ah, great.
Happy birthday to me.
- Come on, binoculars.
- Why? There's nothing out here.
I know, but this is about
learnin' the ropes.
So, pretend, okay?
It's part of the rules.
You stick with your partner,
scan the countryside,
be ready for anything.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
There's a little squirrel
fucking a big squirrel!
We should probably report that.
Fine, we'll skip
the scannin' for now.
But this is nice, right?
Reminds me of the old days,
just you and me on the trail.
I know you got stuff going on,
but it'd be nice
if we could do
this kind of thing more often.
Spend time together.
Yeah.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- It's just, you look...
- No, I--
- There's nothin' on your mind?
- No, nothing.
[dispatcher] [over radio]
Cache Creek, this is Jackson. Come in.
- Go for Cache Creek.
- Infected north of Pinnacle.
Eugene and Adam need backup.
You're the closest we've got.
- [horse chortling]
- I'll be there in ten.
Tell them to dig in.
- Go back to Jackson.
- No.
Ellie, it's not safe.
Go back.
I'm not your fucking kid, Joel.
I'm your partner.
We stick together.
[horse neighing]
[Joel clicking tongue]
[♪ ominous music playing]
We'll hike down from here.
Faster than the switchback.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
- [distant screeching]
- [distant gunshot]
You remember what I taught you?
I'm your back.
You're mine.
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
[mysterious noise approaching]
[horse whinnying]
Come on.
[leaves crunching]
♪
Oh, shit.
Eugene.
[Joel] Ellie.
You clean?
Uh...
No.
- Are there any more?
- Joel.
Are there any more?
Other than me?
No.
- Whoa.
- Okay, okay. Look.
Please, I-- I-- I figure
I got about an hour.
So, this is what we do.
We go back to the gate.
They let Gail out,
keeping her at a safe distance,
of course.
And I-- I say...
goodbye.
We can't do that.
Yes-- yes, we can.
- Yes, we can.
- You're empty.
[groaning]
No. [stammering]
Joel, I gotta go back.
I gotta see her.
I got things I gotta tell her.
Things.
- You don't understand.
- I do.
But we have rules,
and it can't happen.
Wait.
- Whoa.
- Hold out your hand.
Huh?
Hold out your hand.
Now, count slowly,
clearly, from one to ten.
One, two, three,
four, five,
six, seven, eight,
nine, ten.
He has time.
We tie him up
and we bring him back.
Joel, let him see
his fucking wife.
Please.
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
Get the horses,
bring them down the trail.
I'll start walkin' with him,
we'll meet up with you.
I promise.
Go ahead, ten feet.
Thank you.
[foliage rustling]
[Eugene panting]
It makes you cold.
The Cordyceps.
I didn't expect that.
[sighs]
Which, uh, way?
Head right.
[Eugene shivering]
It's beautiful.
[♪ ominous music playing]
Oh.
I need you to not turn around.
No.
Uh, you can't--
you can't do this to me.
Joel.
If you have last words for her,
I'll pass them along.
[Eugene]
Last words for her?
No, no, I need--
I need her last words!
For me!
I'm dying.
I'm terrified.
I, uh...
I don't need a view.
I need Gail.
To see her face.
Please.
Please let that be
the last thing I see.
If you love someone...
you can always see their face.
[♪ somber music playing]
[sighs]
♪
I see her.
[♪ somber music
continues playing]
[foliage rustling]
[hoofbeats]
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna radio ahead
and let them know.
When we get there,
I'll-- I'll tell Gail
what she needs to know,
and nothin' more.
It's the right thing to do.
Ellie.
I had no choice.
[crow cawing]
Uh, he was bit
when we found him.
And, uh...
Well, he wanted to tell you
that he loved you.
And, uh, he wished he could say goodbye
to you in person
but he didn't wanna
put you in danger.
[crying] No, no.
[Joel]
And he wasn't scared. He...
He was brave.
And he ended it himself.
[sighs]
[sobbing]
[Ellie]
That's not what happened.
He begged to see you.
He had time.
Joel promised
to take him to you.
He promised us both.
[softly] And then,
Joel shot him in the head.
[breathing heavily]
That's...
Get away. Please.
Get away from me, please.
You swore.
[Gail sobbing]
[Gail] [sobbing] No.
[♪ "Little Sadie"
by Crooked Still playing]
♪ Standing on the corner
reading a bill ♪
♪ And up stepped
the sheriff from Thomasville ♪
♪ He said,
"Miss, is your name Brown? ♪
♪ Remember the night
you shot Sadie down?" ♪
♪ I said, oh yes, sir,
but my name is Lee ♪
♪ And I murdered Little Sadie
in the first degree ♪
♪ First degree
and second degree ♪
♪ Got any papers,
will you read 'em to me? ♪
- [♪ song ends]
- [Dina laughing]
That was good, yeah?
[people cheering]
Oh, okay.
Yeah, he's fallin' apart.
I'm gonna get him to bed.
- You're gonna miss the countdown.
- I'll come back after.
[singer] Okay. The next one
is a little slower.
Save me some of that.
Say goodnight to Uncle Grumpy.
- Goodnight, Uncle Grumpy.
- [Tommy chuckles]
- Night, kiddo.
- See you next year.
See you next year.
[♪ "Ecstasy"
by Crooked Still playing]
- [Maria] You okay?
- Hm?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What I said today
about you being a refugee
probably came off as ungrateful.
- No, it's okay.
- Well, I am grateful.
You mean a lot to us.
To all of us.
But especially to me and Tommy.
What I'm trying to say is,
Uncle Grumpy is family.
And family helps each other out,
if you need it.
♪ Oh, when shall I see
Jesus and reign... ♪
Hey, it's a family event.
Sorry.
In a church.
Dykes.
- [Ellie] Fuck did you just say?
- [Dina] Ellie, no.
Ellie, hey. No.
[crowd gasping]
You get the hell out of here.
[Maria]
Seth. Let's...
- [Seth grunting]
- Let's take a walk.
Come on.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
What is wrong with you?
I don't need your fucking help.
Right.
[♪ gentle, somber music playing]
[♪ strums guitar]
♪
[♪ guitar continues
playing faintly]
[♪ stops playing]
What are you drinking?
Coffee.
- Where'd you get it?
- Um...
[smacks lips] The people that
came through last week.
- Mm.
- I'm a little embarrassed
for what I traded
to get it, but...
it's not bad.
I had Seth under control.
Yeah, I know.
And I don't wanna ever hear
about you taking me off patrol again.
Okay.
So, Dina.
Is she your girlfriend now?
No. No, she...
It was just one kiss.
Didn't mean anything.
I don't know why she did that.
But...
you do like her?
[sighs]
I'm so stupid.
Look, I don't know what
Dina's intentions are, but...
well, she'd be lucky
to have you.
You're such an asshole.
You lied to me.
You looked me in the eyes
and you lied,
and it was the same face.
Same fucking look.
But I think I knew already.
I knew this whole time.
So, I'm gonna give you
one last chance.
Tell me what happened
with the Fireflies.
If you lie to me again,
we're done.
Were there other immune people?
Were there Raiders?
Could they have made a cure?
[sniffling]
Did you--
And Marlene?
[sighs]
Making a cure...
would've killed you.
Then, I was supposed to die.
[sniffling]
That was my purpose.
My life would have
fucking mattered!
But you took that from me!
You took it from everyone.
Yes.
[sighs]
And I'll pay the price...
because you're gonna
turn away from me.
[breathing heavily]
But if somehow I had
a second chance at that moment...
I would do it all over again.
Because you're selfish.
[choking up]
Because I love you.
[whimpers]
In a way you...
you can't understand.
Maybe you never will.
But if that day should come...
if you should ever
have one of your own...
well, then...
I hope you do
a little better than me.
[Ellie sniffling]
[sighs deeply]
I don't think I can
forgive you for this.
But I would like to try.
[♪ gentle music playing]
[rain falling]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crashing]
[♪ soft music playing]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[♪ music fades out]