Swear to me that everything you said
about the Fireflies is true.
I swear.
Okay.
Why would he do this?
I heard rumors.
It was some kid he took
that was supposedly--
- That wasn't true.
- Supposedly what?
Something not true.
Because it isn't possible.
No. Probably not.
And even if it were,
it doesn't fucking matter anyway.
- Not without--
- Enough.
You want to worry about something,
worry about us.
So, what do we do?
Do we look for other Fireflies?
Where?
This place was the Fireflies.
Ed has a brother
who runs an outfit in Seattle.
A guy named Isaac.
Supposedly, he'd take us all in.
Not until we find Joel.
We're finding him. Yes, we are.
Yes, we are.
Alright, let's talk about how.
Because here's what we got.
He's a smuggler.
His name's Joel or Joe.
There's some confusion about that--
Fifties, graying, beard, six foot tall,
scar on his right temple.
Oh, yeah.
They say he's handsome.
I forgot.
With a three-day jump on us.
We should have gone right after him.
He drove away, Abby.
In our only working vehicle.
And we were trying to save the wounded.
But we didn't save anyone, did we?
- It's not fucking fair.
- No.
None of this is fucking fair.
Abby.
Maybe,
maybe the Seattle crew has resources.
They could help us get some sort of lead.
You'll help me find him.
Yes. We'll help you find him.
Then, we'll help you kill him.
Slowly.
What?
When we kill him,
we kill him slowly.
Get up.
Okay. Okay.
Ellie!
Boom, motherfucker.
First of all, "okay" means stop.
Sorry, I was in the moment.
Second, you can't
"Boom, motherfucker" people
who land the first hit on you.
Square in the face, by the way.
Well, I can obviously take a punch,
so who cares?
- Fuckin' hard, by the way.
- I pulled it.
- You pulled it?
- Yeah, he pulled it.
- Why?
- 'Cause I told him to.
- Otherwise, he would have knocked you out.
And I don't want to have
to explain that to Joel.
Don't do that again.
Okay.
I should've closed in faster on that one,
but the rest was good.
The rest was good.
Are you going to the thing tonight?
Don't we have to?
'Cause community and shit?
You're part of the community now?
Seriously, though, if you are,
we could use an extra pair of hands
breaking down firewood for the cookout.
Don't pull punches.
Oh.
Well, that's fucked.
Hey.
Hey, kiddo.
Somethin' go wrong out there?
Well, the main lines are clay,
all cracked to shit and full of roots.
We're not sure what we're supposed to do,
and our foreman isn't foreman-ing.
Yeah, sorry.
I'll be out there in a minute.
- Whatcha doin'?
- Fixing these breakers.
They were gonna chuck the whole panel
but all they need is new springs.
Teach me?
Okay.
Well...
First thing first,
before you mess with circuits,
you gotta check if the wires are live.
So, how do you do that?
I...
lick them?
Voltage tester.
Now, this right here
is the part that matters.
Bimetallic strip.
Too much current runs through,
heats up the strip,
it bends, releases the lever?
Circuit breaks.
Otherwise,
the wires get hotter and hotter,
lights the inside of your walls on fire.
There goes your house.
- Can I ask a question?
- Shoot.
Why is she angry at you?
- She said she was angry?
- No, but...
You're her best friend,
reckon she would have told you.
Nope.
Well, I figure it's normal.
Her bein' 19 and me bein' her, what I am.
No one likes their parents at that age.
I never got there with my own kid,
so we're both just figuring it out
for the first time, is all.
We'll get through it.
Yeah, that makes sense.
- So, the springs hold the levers back--
- The thing is, I try.
I know I'm a hard-ass
and maybe overprotective,
and she's
her, but...
I mean, what did I do?
I don't know.
Yeah, well.
I can't hold myself responsible
for another person's emotional state.
Are you in fucking therapy?
Holy shit, you're seeing Gail?
I'm not in therapy. Jesus, go,
go fix the main line.
Saw out the cracked parts,
pull the roots and we'll fill in the gaps
with some ABS.
Go on.
It'll be okay.
Dina.
Don't tell anyone I'm in therapy.
Oh, shit.
This scope is sick.
It ain't the scope, it's the shooter.
- You're gettin' good.
- Who's next?
Let's see.
Ah, okay.
There's a cluster of 'em up by the road.
- One's broken away, you see him?
- See him.
Alright, you wanna take your time
with this one.
It's further away, so more drop.
He's going uphill,
so you gotta compensate.
Head shot?
Always.
- Ah, fuck.
- Nah.
It's alright, you got him anyway.
I guess. A lot of them out there.
Yeah, I noticed.
Probably followin' down Route 89.
Maybe comin' outta Alpine.
We should head back.
I wanna get a patrol out there.
Cool, I'll do that run.
Actually,
I'm takin' you off patrols for a bit.
Puttin' you on gate watch.
Gate watch? What? Why?
'Cause it's an important job.
It's standing on a fucking fence.
He's concerned about you.
Unfucking real.
Well, you know, last run,
you were a bit reckless.
It was two runners and a Clicker
who barely had teeth.
I handled it. Isn't that the job?
You wandered off on your own, Ellie.
- We have rules for reasons.
- Oh, please, Dina does this shit
all the time, no one's putting her
on the fucking fence.
Tommy, I'm an adult.
He can't tell me what I can and can't do.
Yeah, well, he can tell me.
Look, I've been dealin' with him
my whole life.
Sometimes, easier to just go along.
I don't care if it's easier.
It's not fair.
And by the way, you know I'm the one
we should be least worried about
when it comes to infected.
Hey, no. You swore.
We don't talk about that.
I got bit on my arm.
Ellie, we don't talk about that.
- I got bit, everybody!
- Hey!
- I got bit!
- Hey! Hey, hey!
I'm immune!
Hey! Jesus.
Goddammit.
I swear, you and my brother?
Same goddamn fuckin' person.
Well, if we're the same person,
you know you're not winning this.
Put me on the patrol.
Alpine run leaves at 1300.
Now, you follow the rules.
You obey your captain.
No questions, no exceptions.
Well, that depends. Who's the captain?
- Ellie.
- Okay, fine. Whatever.
I'll do it by the book.
Easy girl. Come on.
Open it up!
These three will be done
by next day or so.
Then another day to hook up sewage.
Now, y'all wanted the library
and the school restored by spring.
But they both need new roofs.
With the manpower that we have,
I don't see any of this
gettin' done until summer.
This window isn't keepin'
the cold out anymore.
Yeah, yeah. Caulk.
It's high up on my list.
We've been using a ton of it
to restore the new--
- We need to build faster.
- Faster?
Sure. How much faster?
See, we got this dial
called the Constructo meter.
- Joel.
- The more you turn it, the faster we go.
We're running out of space
to put these people.
Yeah, I noticed.
Maybe your council
would stop lettin' so many of 'em in.
It's our council.
And those people are fleeing
collapsed settlements.
They're fleeing infected.
We're supposed to leave them out there?
If our lifeboat is swamped,
yeah, we leave 'em out there.
If I could, I'd let 'em all in.
And I'm workin' every damn day and night
to make more space, you know that.
But you got to look after your own first,
or you're no good to anyone.
- Uncle Joel.
- Hey, buddy.
- What are those?
- Come here.
Okay, we're lookin' at maps.
See? This is where we live.
- And what's that?
- The fence.
- And what's inside?
- People!
- And what's outside?
- Monsters.
That's right. And how do we keep 'em out?
- We shoot them.
- What do you mean, "we"?
Are you shootin' monsters?
- No.
- Are you shootin' monsters?
- You are. You are.
- Hey.
- You're shootin' monsters!
Daddy!
There he is! Killer!
Yeah. I missed you, boy.
Hey.
- What y'all up to?
- Well, your wife wants me to build faster.
Did you tell her about the big dial?
Yeah, he told me. Come here, baby.
Ah! You're getting so big.
- You huntin' or...?
- Infected.
What? By yourself?
Yeah.
I gotta go.
You keep gettin' those monsters, Benji.
Oh, you got me.
You got me.
Joel.
You were a refugee too.
It's open.
I'll be right there.
Do you want anything to drink?
What do you have?
Whiskey. Herbal tea.
But the tea's mostly
thistles and dirt, so.
What's the occasion?
It's my birthday.
Well, you wanna start or what?
Shake and stems.
What am I, in high school?
It's winter, Gail.
That never stopped Eugene.
January, February,
the man would grow buds
the size of pinecones.
Sticky as glue.
Payment accepted.
Didn't know psychiatrists were allowed
to drink in these things.
Psychotherapist.
Psychiatrists are the pill ones.
And, no, we're not allowed
to drink in these things.
But I woke up this morning feeling sad.
It's my first birthday
without my husband in 41 years.
Tick, tick, tick.
Well, I tried what you said. I backed off.
I stopped puttin' pressure on her.
Don't even make her sit down with me
for dinner anymore.
And what do I get for it? Nothin'.
She comes home,
shuts herself in the damn garage,
which I should never have
allowed her to move into.
And that's it. Not so much as a hello.
I see her around town.
Gives me a nod like I'm a stranger
or some asshole.
Even Dina asked me today,
"What's wrong with her?"
I mean, everyone can tell.
Now, that one.
That one treats me like a human being.
She talks to me, says "Hello,"
gives me a smile, looks up to me,
makes me feel like I'm a good guy,
which I am.
See, Dina understands me.
Like she's my kid or somethin'.
But she's not.
Neither is Ellie.
Tell you what.
Let's try something different.
- Like what?
- Like not pretending
you have the most boring
problem in the world.
"Oh, a 19-year-old daughter.
"She's acting toward me like
every 19-year-old daughter
has ever acted toward their dad, ever."
What is this, our fifth session?
Are you just gonna keep
grouching on like this every time?
Aren't you supposed to be
validating me or somethin'?
Oh, yeah, actually, I am.
But I'm not gonna do it anymore
because you're lying to me,
and it's exhausting.
Yes, you are, Joel. Yes, you are.
I've done this long enough to know
when somebody is leaving something out.
And you are definitely
leaving something out.
And you want me to validate that?
No.
In fact, fuck, no.
- That's not your first one of the day.
- Oh, no, it isn't.
And before, when I said I was sad,
that wasn't true either.
I'll just come back another day.
Should I say it out loud?
Yeah, I should.
You can't heal something
unless you're brave enough
to say it out loud.
I'm scared though.
I'm scared to say it.
Which is why I have to.
You shot and killed my husband.
You killed Eugene.
And I resent you for it.
No. Maybe a little more than that.
I hate you for it.
And, yes, I know you had no choice.
I know that. I know I should forgive you.
Well, I've tried, and I can't
because of how you did it.
And looking at your face
sitting in our home,
makes me so fucking angry.
There it is. I've said it.
I'm ashamed.
But it's in the air
and I can't take it back.
And now, maybe there's a chance
I can make things right with you.
Your turn.
Say the thing you're afraid to say.
I can help you.
Say it out loud, no matter what it is.
No matter how bad.
I promise, I will help.
Did you do something to her?
Did you hurt her?
No. No.
Then, what?
What did you do?
I saved her.
Coming.
Hi.
Came to pick you up.
Oh, you're on this run?
Give me a second.
Take as much time as you need.
Two minutes.
I heard you were getting stuck
on the fence today.
How'd you get out of that?
- Tommy.
Where'd you get the holster?
Dominique. Traded some old boots for it.
Should've kept the boots.
Here, let me help.
- I can do it.
- It's okay.
I got it. There we go.
Just like that. Hold on.
Let me get this part here.
Yep. 'Cause now-- There we go.
- Better?
- Yeah, better.
Look at you with all that hardware.
You're like Curtis and Viper.
You know those movies Joel likes?
Yeah, I know.
I was actually gonna maybe watch them
tomorrow night with him,
if you wanna join.
Patrol?
Yeah. Yeah, patrol.
- Why, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Yeah.
Hey, Shimmer.
Hi, girl.
Ellie.
There we go.
Okay, we're five minutes behind
because of one or two of you,
so I'll make it short.
You're doing the Alpine run.
I know a couple of you
are new to this trail, so listen up.
You're taking Route 191 down to Hoback.
- Yes, Dina.
- Hi.
Should we stick to the road,
scan the countryside, hit our checkpoints,
and sign the log books?
You know what? That sounds great.
But while you're doing all that,
we've got reports of strays.
So, be careful when you get into the town.
Now, I see Ellie over here
looking like Curtis and Viper.
- The fuck?
- So, let me remind you,
this is just a recon patrol.
If you see one or two runners,
that's fine, clear 'em out.
Anything more, anything worse,
you come on back and we send out a squad.
Understood?
You know you're only, like,
four years older than us, right?
Just say, "Understood."
- Understood.
- Thank you.
Your patrol leader is Kat,
so you will follow her orders.
When you're back,
today's all-clear sign is yellow.
Yellow, good. Green, bad.
Jokes aside, can you take things
a little more seriously?
The others look up to you two.
For some fuckin' reason.
Okay, Alpine run, moving out!
Alpine run! Moving out, let's go!
So, you going tonight?
Yes, I'm going.
Taking anyone?
- No.
- Why not?
- Kat's available.
- Why would I ask Kat?
Because she's the other one.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
You used to with her.
And she definitely left her mark.
Right, yes, thank you.
But no.
You're into someone else.
Tell you what. You can go with me.
We can get baked.
We can dance to the smooth tunes of--
what are they called?
Britney and the Jug Boys. It'll be fun!
We'll count down to the New Year together.
BFFs, 2029.
- Aren't you and Jesse?
- No.
Broke up.
Yes, again.
For now.
What is it with you two?
I don't know.
Let's go.
- Okay. We're on.
- Wait.
We should go back and report it.
We're recon, Kat. Let's fuckin' recon.
Wait, guys!
Hey, come on. Guys!
How many infected does it take
to bring down a bear?
Check out the van.
So, they've been sheltering in the market.
Yeah, it looks like at least one of them
made it back in.
Maybe needed a nap
after chomping that poor thing.
Yeah.
Hey,
what do you call a grizzly's ribs?
Bear-b-cue.
Did you just make that up?
- Yeah.
- Bear-b-cue?
- Seriously?
So, you think Hungry Boy
is still alive in there?
Fuckin' hope so.
Good.
Hi. Oh, hi there.
- Here comes fun.
- Hi.
Oh, my God.
Happy?
Hey, can we go back now, please?
Yeah, we will. Promise.
We're just gonna listen quick,
see if any are in there,
which is definitely recon.
Hey, you know,
maybe there's a regular person
who's trapped and needs help.
Yeah, what if there's a family in there?
What if there's a toddler? Or a baby?
There's no babies in there.
Hey, come on.
Rules!
Fine.
If you hear anything, you come right back.
Okay.
You just gonna let 'em go in?
I'll give 'em five minutes.
Two on one.
Okay, so one on one.
We've done that before.
If you'd rather let the men handle it.
Two.
The bottle.
Fuck yeah.
Did you get bit?
Do I have to shoot you in the face?
- Not today.
- Okay.
Nice.
Oh, my God, before we leave,
you gotta check out the employee--
Ellie!
Ellie! Ellie!
Ellie, are you okay?
I'm good.
Nothing's broken, I don't think.
Oh, shit.
Are you alone?
I don't hear anything.
I think we're good.
Alright, let's figure out
how to get you out.
I don't see a way out.
- A bunch of padlocked doors.
- Okay.
It's too far for me to drop down,
so I can find a stairway or something
and figure out a path back up here.
- Just stay put.
- Yeah.
Ellie?
Stay put.
- Yeah.
- Alright.
Run at me, fucker!
Run at me!
Fuck.
Ellie, are you okay?! Ellie, it's me!
Over here!
Oh, shit. You okay?
Yeah.
That was it?
- Just her?
- Just her.
So, you're saying it was, what?
Smart?
I'm not saying
it could do math or anything,
but it didn't run at me.
It did what we do--
took cover, planned, waited,
lured me in.
Stalking.
And you saw this?
It was exactly like Ellie says.
And how exactly does you two runnin' into
an uncleared building
qualify as following the rules
and obeying your captain?
Well, it wasn't like
this is our first time.
We've killed a lot of infected before.
And you're telling me, what,
if it were you and Joel,
you wouldn't have gone in?
- Well, that ain't the same.
- Why?
- 'Cause it's different.
- How?
Alright. Apologize to Kat
and log your report with Jesse. Go.
Do we believe them?
Dina was lying. She didn't see anything.
But I believe Ellie.
Maybe this smart one was a one-off.
Maybe.
But what about the other six
that brought down the grizzly?
Yeah, well, six ain't good,
but it's not exactly a horde.
Not yet.
I don't know, just lately,
I've had a feeling.
A feeling?
"Reality is nothing
but a collective hunch."
Lily Tomlin.
Four hours till New Year's.
We adjourned?
Adjourned.
Come in.
Ellie.
- Better?
- Nope.
Okay.
Just come to see if you were going
to that thing tonight.
Be good to show your face.
I don't know. Yeah, maybe.
I don't know.
You been playin' much?
Enough, yeah.
Strings are shot.
- Well--
- I'll put some new ones on for ya.
Oh, you don't have to do that, I--
I can get it back tomorrow.
Oh, sorry!
I hate these things.
Tell me about it.
Had to get half-drunk just to show up.
She's putting on quite the show.
Happy New Year!
You guys will be back
together in two weeks, tops.
Not gonna happen.
- Why?
- Ellie! Hey!
What took you so long?
Okay, this next one is a little slower.
- It's one of our favorites.
- Come on! Let's go!
Hey, don't forget, you got early patrol,
so get some rest.
Sir, yes, sir.
Okay, I have a very serious
question for you.
How bad do I smell?
Like a hot pile of garbage.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Gross.
You're so drunk.
I'm high. Smoked a lot.
Every guy in this room
is staring at you right now.
Maybe they're staring at you.
They're not.
Maybe
they're jealous of you.
No reason to be.
I'm not a threat.
Oh, Ellie.
I think they should be terrified of you.
Hey.
It's a family event.
Sorry.
Sorry!
You're in a church.
- Dykes.
- The fuck did you just say?
Ellie, no. Ellie.
Get the hell outta here.
Jesus!
Seth, let's...
Let's take a walk. Come on. Let's go.
Are you okay?
What is wrong with you?
I don't need your fucking help.
Right.
There ya go!
Cheers!
Happy fucking New Year!
- Same thing.
- I know.
We started at the party too, man.
I know.
Oh, my God. Wait up!
Come on, let's go.