- [soldiers laughing]
- [soldier] Now, the thing
about this one night,
and you guys know me.
Like, I'm fuckin' easy
on voters, right?
- That ain't what they say.
- Oh, yeah, well, fuck them
because they'd rather
have me than Greenberg.
- Oh, this is a Greenberg story.
- [laughter]
So, I got three voters
against the wall.
I caught 'em red-handed
disseminating pamphlets, right?
- WLF stuff?
- I thought it was.
Turned out later it was some,
like, religious crap,
but I didn't fuckin' know that.
So, I call for backup.
Guess who shows up?
- [soldiers] Greenberg!
- Greenberg!
- [laughter]
- He pulls up,
gets out of his truck.
He's in a fuckin' mood, okay?
I can already tell,
and he's all like,
"What are you
fuckin' calling for?
"What, you can't handle
three voters?
What did these
fuckin' pussies even do?"
- [laughter]
- I say, "I caught them
out here disseminating."
And he goes, "What?
You fuckin' perverts
are out here jerking off
and splooging on my streets?"
- [laughter]
- Holy shit!
I swear to God.
So, one of the voters turns back
to look at me like,
"Are you gonna tell him?"
I look back at him
like, "Fuck no."
And that's when the guy decides
to open his mouth anyway
and goes, "Well, actually,
the word 'disseminate' means..."
- And boom!
- Oh!
Greenberg slams his fuckin' head
against the wall.
There goes his teeth,
just blood fuckin' everywhere.
And-- and Greenberg goes,
"No one asked you, jizz boy!"
[laughter]
Wh-Why do you call them that?
The citizens, why do
you call them voters?
I don't know.
'Cause that's what we fucking call 'em.
Who cares?
'Cause we took away
their rights.
Took away their right to vote,
and somebody
started calling them
voters to mock them.
So, now you know.
I didn't mean
anything by it, Sergeant.
Of course, you didn't.
You're thoughtless.
- [driver] Sarge.
- [brakes squealing]
[engine idling]
[♪ Tense music playing]
Keep it running.
- [driver] Copy.
- How many?
[Sergeant Isaac Dixon]
A lot.
Could be WLF.
Lock and load.
- [Isaac] No.
- Sarge.
I'm gonna go talk to them.
Alone.
- But protocol.
- Protocol is to obey
your commanding officer.
Period. The end.
Now, if we go
out there in force,
this'll end up
the way it always does.
'Cause you're all Greenberg.
You wanna die?
Fine.
[♪ Tense music playing]
You.
Come with me.
Learn something.
[♪ Tense music continues]
You Isaac?
You Hanrahan?
[sighs]
- [metal pins clinging]
- [grenades bouncing]
[soldiers shouting]
[muffled shouting continues]
[explosions booming]
[birds squawking]
[driver gasping, wheezing]
[gunfire]
Welcome to the fight.
Now, make your choice.
♪
[♪ pensive theme music playing]
[♪ Theme concludes]
[rustling]
[grunting]
[Dina] [sighs]
No pain meds.
[Ellie] Anything else?
[Dina] Probably nothing
anyone wanted.
Ooh! You rockin'
a yeast infection?
[Ellie] Not today,
but gimme time.
Good news.
I found a gallon jug of milk.
Yum.
Make sure to smell it first,
just in case.
[Ellie] Alright, I give up.
I'm gonna stand watch outside.
Yeah, I'm done.
There's nothing else back h--
Hey, I'm gonna pee.
Gimme a minute.
[Ellie] Okay.
[♪ Gentle music playing]
- [Shimmer snorts]
- [bird cawing]
[Dina]
'Kay, good to go.
Thanks.
You okay?
Yeah.
[Dina grunts]
Alright, hit it.
People to kill.
Okay.
- [clicking tongue]
- [Shimmer nickering]
[♪ Gentle music
continues playing]
[Shimmer snorts]
[Dina] I don't understand.
I thought they bombed here.
Yeah, I heard that too.
Guess not this part.
[Dina] What's up with
all the rainbows?
[Ellie] I don't know.
Maybe they were all optimists.
[birds squawking]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
[insects buzzing]
[Ellie] So much for happy,
proud Rainbow Town.
[Dina] I've never seen
a tank this close.
Me neither.
- Ellie. Ellie!
- Just cover me.
I'm gonna check
if there's any ammo in there.
[insects buzzing]
[sighs]
[Dina] Man, FEDRA got
fucked up out here.
You think it was the WLF?
I don't know.
All these bodies
are in FEDRA gear.
Almost looks like they
were fighting each other.
Huh.
Good eye.
I wonder what that was about.
[metal lid banging loudly]
[birds squawking]
[birds cawing]
- Ooh.
- What is it?
Three burnt skeletons.
Like Apollo 1.
[Dina] What?
Grissom, White, Chaffee.
Early astronauts.
They were supposed to be
the first ones to go to the moon,
but they never made it
off the launchpad.
Burned up in their capsule.
Well, at least they died
for something worthwhile.
Yeah. [sighs]
These guys were just assholes
killed by other assholes.
Well, lookie here.
Check out the building
on the hill.
You've gotta be shitting me.
Fuck yeah, let's go.
You sure about that?
Oh, my God, are you
gonna fucking tell me?
If you paint a sign big enough
to be seen for miles away,
that means you want people
to know that you're there,
which also means more likely than not,
you're prepared.
And?
They're on a hill,
so they'll see us coming.
On horseback
in broad daylight, so...
just a little.
So, we wait until dark
and we head out on foot.
And right here
is the perfect place to hole up
because, well, no one's around.
Which you proved brilliantly
with your tank hatch maneuver.
Dick.
Alright, let's look for a door
we can fit Shimmer through.
Already found that.
[metal door creaking open]
[Shimmer grunting]
[♪ Gentle music playing]
♪
[cymbal tings]
[drum bangs]
[♪ Dina begins playing drums]
[Dina] Shout if something
tries to kill you!
That's the plan.
[♪ Drums lightly playing]
[breeze blowing]
[♪ Gentle music playing]
[sighs, kisses]
[strings glissing]
[guitar tuning in distance]
[tuning continues]
[♪ Ellie playing
"Take On Me" by A-ha]
♪ Talkin' away ♪
♪ I don't know what
I'm to say ♪
♪ I'll say it anyway ♪
♪ Today's another day
to find you ♪
- ♪ Shyin'... ♪
- [floor creaking]
[softly] Go on.
[softly] Okay.
♪ Shying away ♪
♪ I'll be comin'
for your love, okay ♪
♪ Take on me ♪
♪ Take me on ♪
♪ I'll be gone ♪
♪ In a day or two ♪
♪ So needless to say ♪
♪ I'm odds and ends,
but I'll be ♪
♪ Stumbling away ♪
♪ Slowly learning
that life is okay ♪
♪ Say after me ♪
♪ It's no better
to be safe than sorry ♪
♪ Take on me ♪
♪ Take me on ♪
♪ I'll be gone ♪
♪ In a day or two ♪
[♪ guitar stops]
Uh...
You've gotten pretty good.
Uh, thanks.
All those lessons from Joel.
He taught you well.
He did.
- You hungry?
- Starving.
Great. Come on.
I'll make us beef jerky.
- [both chuckle]
- Okay.
[footsteps receding]
- [birds chirping]
- [breeze blowing]
[footsteps approaching]
[gas hissing]
[match striking]
[flames whooshing]
[blows]
You know, when I was
a-- a younger man,
and I wanted to impress a woman,
well, you-- you have
to know your strengths.
And I was kinda shy.
I-- I didn't know
how to talk to women.
It made me nervous.
So, what I would do
is cook for them.
And I was good.
Good enough
to deserve quality tools.
Ah, but did I have
the money for that?
No, I did not.
I would go into Williams-Sonoma.
It's a cookware store.
You wouldn't know.
And I would stare...
at these.
Mauviel.
Best of the best.
French, of course.
And I would think, okay,
30 years to retirement
and pension, but one day,
I will own a Mauviel
sauce pan...
with lid.
And I was right.
Just not how I planned.
The strange benefits
of the apocalypse.
[clangs loudly]
Now, copper's a bit
of a pain in the ass.
You have to polish it a lot.
But it heats
faster than anything.
Highly conductive.
Of course, this means
it doesn't retain heat
the way cast iron does,
which of the two,
makes copper the inferior choice for
interrogations, but...
if you own Mauviel,
you use Mauviel.
She--
- She watches over me.
- Then she's been watching you
get your ass kicked.
You know there are even
Scars who don't believe
she's some magic fairy
in the sky, yeah?
Some of you actually understand
she was just a person.
Heretics.
Of course.
The steel handles stay cool.
It's the little touches.
[♪ Tense music playing]
Where are the Scars
attacking next?
[breathing heavily]
Seraphites.
Hold out your hand.
[breathing heavily]
- [sizzling]
- [Malcolm screaming]
Jesus.
This is so fucked.
[WLF guard] Shut up.
Isaac knows what he's doing.
[Malcolm whimpering]
[Malcolm] The blood!
[sobbing]
Yes, sir.
- [pan clanks]
- [Malcolm] She watches over me.
She fills my soul.
She watches over me.
- She watches over--
- She fills your soul.
You put an arrow
in a little boy's head.
Was she filling your soul then?
She tell you to kill children?
- You kill our children.
- Never by choice.
You trained them to shoot at us.
Because your Wolves kill them.
Because you trained
them to shoot at us.
Because you broke the truce.
- Because you broke the truce.
- Because--
Because you broke it
because we broke it.
I'm not playing your little
chicken-and-egg games today, Scar.
Where is the next attack?
[breathing shakily]
You're gonna lose.
[scoffs]
Are we?
Son...
we have automatic weapons
and hospitals,
and you lunatics
have bolt-action rifles,
bows and arrows,
and superstition.
So, tell me,
how are we going to lose?
[sighs]
[voice shaking] Every day,
one of your Wolves
comes to see the truth,
and takes Her into their heart.
Every day.
Every day, a Wolf leaves you
to take the holy mortification
to become a Seraphite.
And none of us ever leave...
to become a Wolf.
I will burn every part of you
until you tell me
what I want to know!
[labored breathing]
[♪ Tense music continues]
[pan clangs]
- [gunshot]
- [bullet shell clinking]
- [body thuds]
- [WLF guard] Good.
Scar got what he deserved.
Fucking animal.
[thunder rumbling]
No patrol.
- That's a good sign.
- Not always.
So, the front entrance
is like a security door.
There's a camera right over it,
which means we go
around the back.
Window.
Oh, boy.
Second floor.
[thunder booms]
[Ellie] So, somebody
hopped onto the shed,
climbed the downspout,
broke the window,
and got cut on the way in?
Well, I guess
that's our way in, too.
And if we run into Wolves
that weren't in Jackson?
Agreed.
[metal banging]
[Ellie grunting]
[whispering] You can do that.
You're good.
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
[door handle clicking]
[Ellie]
What the fuck is this?
[thunder rumbling]
- He isn't one of them.
- [Dina] No.
But we're definitely
in the right place.
[♪ Suspenseful music continues]
[door handle clacking]
[metal door creaking loudly]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[ropes creaking]
[Ellie gasps]
- [Dina retching]
- Dina?
[retching]
Ellie, g-- go.
[retching continues]
[Ellie] These aren't
any of them either.
- [ropes creaking]
- [thunder rumbling]
That group we saw in the woods,
they did this.
What the fuck is wrong
with Seattle?
[radio static]
[Dina grunts]
It's the same ones we use.
- If she called for backup--
- Yeah, we gotta get outta here.
- [people chattering in distance]
- Shit, get down. Down!
[banging]
[soldier]
Oh, my God.
Fuck me.
- Look at this.
- Who the fuck would do that?
Scars got all of 'em.
I don't see Brancaccio or Welsh,
but, yeah, it's the rest of 'em.
[commander]
You, cut 'em down.
[soldier] Shouldn't we secure
the station first?
[commander] I said cut them
the fuck down.
The rest of you, fan out.
And go slow.
If the Scars are still here,
find them and kill them.
[soldier 2] Isaac said he wants 'em
alive for questioning.
[commander]
Isaac's not here, okay?
With intestines all
over the fuckin' place.
So, I don't really give a shit.
I don't give a shit
if it's a woman or a kid.
I don't care
if it's a fuckin' baby.
Look what they did.
Now, fan the fuck out!
[soldier 1] Clear!
[♪ Tense music playing]
[soldier 2]
This side's clear.
[soldier 3] Clear.
[♪ Tense music
continues playing]
[soldier 4] Clear!
[distant clacking]
[soldier] Clear.
Stairs clear.
[♪ Tense music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
- [grunting softly]
- [clattering in distance]
[labored breathing]
[grunting]
[soldier grunting]
[soldier] We got one!
- [gunshot]
- [body thuds]
Shoot that window!
[soldiers shouting]
[soldier]
Move, move, move, move!
- [gunfire]
- [glass shattering]
Go!
[Dina] Come on!
[thunder crashing]
[grunting]
Come on. Get up!
[soldiers shouting]
[gunfire]
[thunder crashing]
[soldiers shouting in distance]
- Fuck!
- Shit!
[Ellie] This way!
- [Dina] Aw, shit!
- [Ellie] Fuck!
[soldier] We see them!
We see them!
Go. We can fit,
they can't.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
[Ellie grunting]
- [gunfire]
- [bullets ricocheting]
They're in the transit tunnel.
Circle the south entrance.
[water dripping]
[rustling]
[grunting]
[rocks clattering]
- [Dina grunting]
- [Ellie] [sighs] Okay.
- [Dina panting]
- You good?
Yeah.
Is this place gonna
fall down on us?
I'd rather not find out.
Let's go.
That way.
[loud bang echoing]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
[flare striking]
[footsteps crunching]
[distant screeching]
[distant clicking]
[distant screeching continues]
[whispering] I thought it was
supposed to be empty.
[whispering]
Yeah. It was.
[screeching continues]
[clicking, screeching
intensifying]
[screeching, clicking continue]
[screeching intensifies]
- [gunfire]
- [soldiers screaming]
[infected horde screeching]
This way!
- [infected snarling]
- Dina!
[gunfire continues]
- [soldiers shouting]
- [Dina] Ellie, fast!
[both grunting]
Shit!
- [infected screeching]
- [loud banging]
Go! Go!
[infected yelling]
Oh, my God!
Go, go, go!
[Ellie and Dina grunting]
[loud banging]
[infected screeching]
[Dina gasping]
[screeching]
[loud banging continues]
[glass shattering]
[Ellie exclaiming]
[gunshots]
- Fuck!
- Get it!
[glass shattering]
[gunshots]
Ellie!
Up!
- [gunshots continue]
- [Dina grunting]
Shit!
- [glass shattering]
- [infected screeching]
Ellie!
- [grunting]
- [Dina exclaiming]
- [glass shatters]
- [Ellie yells]
Jump!
[infected snarling]
[loud banging]
The fence!
[both panting]
[screeching]
[fence rattling]
[grunting]
Fucking open!
Fucking move!
[panting]
[screeching]
[Ellie shouting]
[screaming]
[gunshot]
[metal squeaking]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[both grunting]
[bodies crunching]
Dina.
Come on!
[grunting]
Dina, come on!
[thunder rumbling]
Maybe there.
Come on, we've gotta
get outta sight!
- [water dripping]
- [thunder continues rumbling]
[Ellie]
We can hole up here for now.
I'll bar the door.
[thunder crashing]
Okay, it's not perfect,
but if anyone tries to get in,
it'll buy us some ti...
The fuck are you doing?
[panicked breathing]
[softly] Okay.
Okay. Okay,
I know you're scared.
- Please, don't.
- But I need you to understand something.
[Dina] Please don't make this
any harder than it has to be.
- Wait.
- Why did you do that?
Why the fuck did you
have to do that?
Please listen to me.
I would die for you.
I would.
But that is not
what just happened.
Fuck. I'm immune.
I can't get infected.
[Dina crying]
Dina, do not fucking shoot me!
I've been bitten before.
I'm still here.
I don't-- I know you
don't believe me.
I get it, I wouldn't
believe me either, but...
Here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna walk over there
nice and slow,
to that big fucking chair,
and I'm gonna bandage my arm
and I'm gonna go to sleep.
You're gonna sit as far away
from me as you want,
and you're gonna keep
that gun pointed on me.
If I turn, shoot me.
But I promise.
[sighs]
A lot of the times,
I wish this wasn't true...
[thunder rumbling]
...I'm gonna wake up
exactly as I am right now.
Me.
[Dina panting]
[softly] Okay.
[sighs deeply]
[thunder continues rumbling]
[breathing heavily]
[water dripping]
[thunder rumbling]
[water drop plunks]
[groaning]
Uh, it's just water!
Rain fell on my face,
that's all.
[Ellie panting]
See?
No shaking.
I'm gonna stand up now.
[panting]
Can I show you?
[breathing heavily]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[flashlight clicks]
[breathing shakily]
[thunder crashing]
[voice breaking]
Ellie.
Yeah?
[both breathing shakily]
I'm pregnant.
What?
[♪ Soft music playing]
[both breathing heavily]
[Dina moaning]
[♪ Soft music continues playing]
[kisses]
[Dina groans softly]
Wait, no!
No.
Morning breath.
- [groaning]
- It's gross. Hold on.
[backpack unzipping]
I don't know if this
is gonna be better.
[Dina]
It'll be better.
Mm. Beefy.
[both chuckle]
Mm.
[blows, sniffs]
Mm!
How's it doing?
Wow, that's...
Is this where you
were bitten before?
Yep.
- You said it was a burn.
- Most of it is.
You did it to yourself?
[whispering] I really wanted to wear
short sleeves again.
[Dina chuckles]
It's a little thing,
but when you start
to hide little things,
they become big things.
You don't say.
Why now?
I thought you were gone.
And then all of a sudden,
this future I was imagining...
wasn't gonna happen.
Where we're together,
and we have a kid, and...
I don't even know
if you want that.
I want it with you.
I'm sorry it took so long.
I knew how you felt about me.
How?
I was hiding it really well.
No, you kind of fucking weren't.
- Oh.
- I'm sorry.
I wanted to.
Yeah?
When I was little...
I told my mother I liked boys
and I liked girls.
And she said,
"No, you like boys."
[Ellie] Hm.
And it just...
I got stuck.
Even after she died, it...
I tried to make things
work with Jesse
because I like him.
I do, I think he's a really good guy.
But he wasn't the one.
Still kept trying anyway.
Couldn't let myself just...
be.
You were scared.
Not everyone's as brave as you.
I'm not brave.
I'm just obvious.
[Dina laughing]
Shut up!
[both giggle]
[♪ Soft music playing]
[Dina chuckles]
How do you know
for sure that you're...
Oh!
I started wondering
after we saw the bodies
in the forest,
because I've seen fucked-up shit before
without barfing.
And I knew morning sickness
was a thing,
and I was late, which I--
I've never been regular,
but I was very late.
And then, I found
a pregnancy test
at the pharmacy,
and I peed on it.
- You pee on it?
- That's how it works.
I don't just randomly
piss on stuff.
Oh, okay.
That's good.
Here.
Two lines means pregnant.
This thing's pretty old.
- How do you--
- And here.
And here's a couple more.
So, we're having a baby.
I mean, we, and also
I guess Jesse are--
It was Jesse, right?
- [scoffs lightly]
- So, we're all having a baby.
Holy shit.
- I'm gonna be a dad.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
- [booming in distance]
- [both gasp]
[booming continues]
[soldier] [on radio] ...south of Pike.
Heavy fire.
Scars broke through
the north side of the FOB.
- [medical] Casualties?
- [soldier] At least two dozen.
We're falling back.
Bringing wounded to Lakehill.
- Tell Nora to get ready.
- [gunfire over radio]
Oh, fuck!
[radio static]
- He just said Nora.
- Yeah.
- She's gonna know--
- Where Abby is, yeah.
That's Lakehill
but I don't know
where we are anymore.
Okay, we go up high and we look around.
Come on.
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[explosions, gunfire
in distance]
Ellie.
See that white building
out there?
That's it.
That's Lakehill.
[distant gunfire continues]
You don't have to go.
You can stay here.
- Fuck you.
- No, I'm not saying...
[distant explosions continue]
- It's different now.
- Yes, it is.
Will you please
just think about it?
[♪ Ominous music playing]
[♪ Gentle music playing]
Together.
[♪ Soft music playing]