This picture is an assault
on Italian Americans
everywhere.
If I have my way, you won't
make this movie at all.
"The Godfather"
is becoming a problem.
We wanna give you
some help.
No.
One more thing.
Pacino.
Give him another shot.
No Pacino.
How many fucking times
do I have to tell you?
I got a script
the size of an encyclopedia,
a director in love with
the shortest unknown actor
on the fucking planet,
and Biaggi's making waves.
Am I forgetting anything?
No.
I'm pretty sure that covers it.
Joe Gallo's actions
led to our last war.
If Gallo comes gunning
for Colombo,
you get caught
with a stray bullet.
What do you got
in mind for him?
I'm gonna light his whole
fucking world on fire.
It's you and me now.
Your enemies are my enemies.
Please,
I don't want no trouble.
The Marlon Brando's house.
Ever since your letter,
I keep thinking about the Don.
Pacino and Brando
in the same frame.
I'm working on it.
Side with Francis.
Pacino's the guy.
Evans gave you your shot.
If I say yes,
he's gonna be pissed.
You stabbed me in the back.
I don't like Pacino!
I want to be with you.
All of you or none of you.
This is the life
that we've chosen.
We can only be around other
people who understand that.
You got the part, kid.
I'm doing "The Gang That
Couldn't Shoot Straight."
I signed a contract.
What are you doing?
Come on.
I like this song.
No.
You're sending
the wrong message, kid.
What fucking message?
Here we go.
That's good, no?
Whatever, old man,
I like this too.
Ah, fuck you
with the "old man."
Would you look at this jamoke?
The fuck?
Fuck that.
Come on!
What the fuck is he doin'?
Hey, buddy, you gotta move
this fuckin' car
before I move it for you.
Fuck.
Let him go.
What do you think's
in the truck?
Don't matter.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Oh, my God,
you smell like a sick dog.
What the fuck?
I just got off a plane.
I need your help.
Boy, did you come
to the wrong place.
You told me to do whatever
it takes to get my movie made.
You said to color
outside the lines.
I never told you
to fuck me over.
That was never
my intention, Bob.
Yeah,
and Yoko Ono never intended
to break up The Beatles.
I don't give a fuck
about your intentions.
It was for the movie.
It was for the good
of the movie.
Keep saying that to yourself.
Listen.
Pacino can't do the film.
He signed on
to another project.
Problem solved then.
I need you
to get him out of it.
You have got to be
fucking kidding me.
Come on, Bob.
You've never even
given him a shot.
He's got something special.
We need him.
What you need
is a fucking shower.
Mush.
Now, Paramount is just
one asset among dozens
in the Gulf and Western
portfolio.
Now, by God's grace,
we have a record-breaking hit
called "Love Story,"
but I won't pretend
that we knew
it was gonna hit like this.
And that is actually my point.
Making movies has become
too unpredictable.
Hollywood was founded by men
who understood
that the bottom line
of making movies
is to make money.
But gentlemen,
that system is broken.
The men with their hands
on the wheel now,
they are, quite frankly,
bullshit artists
who like to think of themselves
as the talent.
They know exactly
what to say to us
to get our money,
but they can give a damn
about making it back
because
they are not businessmen.
Now that we have finally
had some success,
we can get a much better price
if we offload Paramount now
and cash out.
So that's why we're here today.
We are here to seek
the board's approval
to begin the exploration
process because
we have already
had four suitors interested.
Charlie, anything to add?
Some of you think that
I have a sentimental attachment
to Paramount.
to many things,
which is why when I sell them,
I sell them for a lot of money.
Tessio, he's gotta be older.
He... he's like the oldest guy
in the whole family.
So what you're saying
is you want Clemenza to be
two or three years younger?
Yeah, that'd be good.
You got anybody in mind?
Hello.
Hi.
Where's Ruddy?
He's on his way back from LA.
His flight lands later tonight.
Why's he in LA?
Doesn't he realize
that the producer
is supposed to be here
for pre-production?
We have a sit-down
with Tavoularis and Gordy.
Did you tell him?
I was waiting
until Ruddy got back.
Tell me what?
What is wrong?
Pacino signed a contract
for another movie.
Come on, Francis.
Jimmy Caan's screen test
was good and you know it.
We just set him for Sonny.
And now you want me
to just make him Michael?
Francis, you know this shit
happens all the time.
Andrea,
this isn't musical chairs.
Caan is not even Italian.
Okay.
You're making a movie
with Marlon Brando.
And don't worry,
we'll find another Michael.
Will he just look
at Pacino?
Roll it back, would you?
Again?
How many times do we have to
watch "Panic in Needle Park"?
There's a scene in
"The Godfather" script,
Michael tells his
brother-in-law
he's not gonna kill him
but we know he's lying.
It's a shocking scene.
But it's gotta be played
in the subtext.
Pacino doesn't have
to say a word
and I can't take
my eyes off him.
"An ice-blue, terrifying film
about people you love."
Fuckin' Ruddy.
Hi.
Hey, Bettye.
Ooh, you smell nice.
Fancy hotel, fancy soap.
Gotta love the Waldorf.
How'd it go with Evans?
What did he say?
He said,
"Do whatever it takes
to get your movie made, Ruddy.
I support you."
So not well, I take it.
Have you...
have you seen this?
It's Carmine.
Fuck.
I liked that guy.
Al, this is really scary.
We're gonna be okay.
You got any good news for me?
Well, your buddy Jack Ballard
is waiting for you
in your office.
Shit.
You and I are gonna
need to have a little chat
about what exactly
constitutes good news.
Just the man I want to see.
Jack,
what are you doing here?
Anything you need,
Mr. Producer.
Have you met our editor?
Aram Avakian, Al Ruddy.
Aram, I thought you weren't
getting in until tomorrow.
Uh, Jack called me.
He wanted to get acquainted
a day earlier.
Oh, did he?
Mm.
Glad to be aboard.
Glad to have you.
Jack, did you see
"The Miracle Worker"?
Nah, missed it.
Aram cut it.
It's beautiful work.
Mm, thank you.
Al's gonna need a miracle
to bring us in on budget.
Aram, tell you what.
We'll have a drink,
take each other's temperature,
and solve the world's problems.
Sounds good to me.
Where and when?
Count me in.
For the second round, Jack.
I like to meet the team
on my own first.
Oh, sorry.
I wasn't sure about that
since you missed the meeting
with your production designer
and cinematographer
this morning.
Looking forward to that drink.
Charlie.
Question: why is Jim Aubrey
seated at my regular my booth?
I'm so sorry, Mr. Evans.
Mr. Aubrey got here early.
He insisted on sitting
at his usual table.
Aubrey runs MGM.
I run Paramount.
MGM just had an auction
to sell off
props and costumes
to pay the mortgage.
Come on.
How long has he been here?
About six minutes.
Son of a bitch.
You couldn't stall him for
six minutes until I got here?
Coffee.
Please.
Terry, looking good.
You lost weight?
Hi, Bob.
How are you?
Anabelle.
Hi, Bob.
Hi, dear.
Nice to see you.
Catch up later.
Jim, I'm so sorry I'm late.
You're still early.
Well, I grew up under the rule
that if you're
ten minutes early,
you're still late.
Hell of a job
you're doing at MGM.
It's all anyone can talk about.
Last year, we were in the red.
This year we're seeing
nothing but black.
How 'bout you?
Well, we haven't started
selling our props
and furniture just yet.
Nothing's too precious, huh?
Not even Dorothy's
Ruby Red slippers?
Thank you.
So we got a small piece
of business between us.
Let's make sure
we're on the same page.
This is about swapping actors.
It's Pacino and De Niro.
Two guys starting out
their careers,
getting paid scale plus ten.
Come on.
You're treating them like
we're trading an outfielder
for a shortstop.
Why not?
It's for the good
of both movies.
Each wants the other's part.
Simple.
You know, you make fun
of the MGM yard sale,
but I hear that Paramount's
getting spun off.
The whole show.
Gulf and Western
is getting tired
and they want out.
No.
If you didn't know,
I just did you a favor
and that's on top of the favor
you're here to ask me for.
I think I've done
both of us a favor.
You want this more than I do.
Personally,
I don't see such a difference
between Pacino and De Niro.
De Niro does "The Gang
That Couldn't Shoot Straight."
Pacino does "The Godfather."
Everybody wins.
Pass.
What else?
You have a couple of
Harold Robbins' books I want.
Can't do it.
Then we don't have a deal.
One book.
One book, my choice.
Wow.
That had to hurt.
You sure this is
really worth it?
You know, I'm a production
designer, not a magician.
Dean, what's the problem?
Well, having permits
to build sets
where I'm supposed to
build them would be nice.
We have permits.
They got pulled.
Some congressmen
is fucking with us.
Look, this should have been
handled a long time ago.
Take it easy, okay?
It's a misunderstanding.
Bettye, call that kid
in the film office I talked to.
Kevin something.
Yeah.
He'll sort this out.
Hi, I have Al Ruddy
on the line for Kevin, please.
Since when?
Okay. Thank you.
Kevin's been fired.
Because he gave us the permits.
We need to take Gallo out now.
No. No, not yet.
I gotta talk to Carlo
and the rest of the Commission
to get the okay to rip
this motherfucker's face off.
All right, in the meantime,
hit the streets,
make your collections.
Everybody pays today.
I want 20% kickback
to Carmine's widow.
FBI. Nobody move!
Keep your hands
where we can see 'em.
Well, this is nice.
Family reunion.
You bring presents?
We got warrants.
You know the drill.
Okay, okay.
Tear this place up.
What's this?
Go fuck yourself.
Teach your people
some respect.
I need that.
Congressman Biaggi
sends his best.
Hello?
Listen to me.
You're still a putz,
but I got Pacino.
He's in the picture.
Oh, Bob, thank you.
I can't tell you how much...
They can't breathe.
Huh?
The leaves.
Look, they're turning brown.
See? Caravaggio has the
light coming in from the top
and stopping on the edges.
I know. I love it.
It's beautiful.
I love the shadows.
It doesn't give the actors
much leeway
to move around though.
That's right.
Well, they have to have
freedom to move.
Well, they have
to hit their marks.
They need to be free to move
so we're gonna test it.
Sure. Yeah, if you want.
It's not an insult, Gordy,
to work all this out
before we get on the set
with 100 people.
You wanna test?
We'll test. It's fine.
It's fine.
Good. Great.
See it as an opportunity
to show off.
What? Is that what you think
that I'm doing here?
Uh-oh.
Are Mom and Dad fighting again?
Hello.
Can you give us a minute
because we're working...
Yeah, sure.
I just came by
because I had
a little piece of news,
a very small piece
of news to deliver...
Ruddy, what?
And I wanted to do it
in person.
No. You got Pacino?
You got him!
Are you kidding?
You did it?
How did you do it?
There's a certain shade
of yellow
and we're not making
this movie without it.
Oh.
Do I want to know
how this happened?
Nothing my mother
would be embarrassed by.
Okay.
What's with the suit?
You... you never wear a suit.
I gotta see a guy
about a thing.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Thank you for coming.
So good to see you.
Hey.
Sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
He was like a brother to me.
It's a fucking shame.
I'm sorry about Carmine.
Al.
They made it so he couldn't
even have an open coffin.
That way, the people
that... that love him
can't say goodbye
the right way.
It's just not done.
You did the right thing
by coming here.
I appreciate that.
Well, there's an old saying.
"Nobody should be invited
to a funeral
and everyone should come."
Carmine would've liked that.
He had a great sense of humor.
He was a funny motherfucker.
Come on.
How's the movie going?
Actually, Biaggi's making
more problems for us.
He pulled all the permits
from the film office.
I'm taking care of it.
I got my own issues
with that fuck.
I'm sorry to bother you
on a day like this.
It is what it is.
How's your son?
He's good.
He's really good.
He... he's thinking
about politics.
Politics?
Yeah, he's a smart kid.
He's smarter than me.
He's lookin' for
a less complicated life.
Well, what I do
is hardly uncomplicated.
But I wish you and your family
only the best.
Is that your way
of apologizing for the raid?
The raid?
Think twice about
lying to me, Congressman.
The League is now
over 200,000 strong,
and as we both know,
you have a campaign comin' up.
I got plenty of friends
who wouldn't mind taking a shot
at your seat,
and with the full backing
of every member in the League,
plus their big, fat
Italian families.
Joe.
There's been a misunderstanding
between us.
Oh. Maybe.
If I may,
I want a clean slate.
I'm listening.
We're both proud
Italian Americans
who want what's best
for our people.
So what can I do
to heal this rift between us
so we can, you know,
help each other?
Stronger together, is that
the tune you're singing now?
Good, good.
Get the feds
off my fucking back.
Consider it done.
And one more thing.
Film noir set in the '20s
about city politics.
Bob Towne wrote it.
It's called "Chinatown."
I read it over the weekend,
actually, in one sitting.
Is this the one with
the winning combination
of incest and water rights?
That's it.
I'll take a look at it.
Bob?
Hmm?
Something going on?
When I was negotiating
for Pacino,
Aubrey told me
that he heard that Paramount
was being spun off.
You heard anything about that?
No. Nothing.
Not since months ago.
I thought Bluhdorn said
he'd keep you in the know.
Yeah.
He told me "Love Story"
had to deliver.
It just passed $100 million.
I'd say that qualifies.
Aubrey's just trying
to get under your skin.
Ugh, it's too exposed.
It's too open.
It needs to be protected.
Well, maybe we can
build a wall.
How much?
Ballard's up my ass
about the budget, guys.
Um, it's... it's... it's cheap.
You know, it's Styrofoam.
We just paint it
to look like stone.
How tall is that wall?
Eight feet?
Well, it's going to cast
a shadow in the late morning.
You can light that out.
Maybe, if I get the lighting
package I asked for.
The... the shadows,
they help tell the story.
If that's the intention.
What the fuck is this?
A kitchen that costs $75,000?
Is this a joke?
They gotta cook.
We're not opening up
a restaurant, Francis.
They can pretend.
All department heads
in the conference room now.
No gangster film,
since the beginning
of recorded history,
ever needed a working kitchen.
It's not just
about the cooking.
This is the scene
where Clemenza
is talking to Michael
and he tells him
that the families
have to go to war
every ten years or so.
And while
he's telling them that,
they just happen to be making
tomato sauce,
and that's why the scene
is so important.
I love this scene.
You never see anything like it
- in a gangster film.
- It's essential.
You have to see them
making the tomato sauce.
It humanizes them.
Remember,
it makes them relatable?
If you want it so badly,
you can pay for it.
Francis, is that a propane
line with special effects?
It's practical gas.
Propane's fine. No.
Propane does not burn
like practical gas.
It does now.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just got off the phone
with the film commission.
We've got our permits back.
Why was that ever in doubt?
You guys meeting
about this budget?
Oh, God.
Yeah, we're making some cuts.
Good.
Then my timing is perfect.
Anna, where are we at
with costumes?
Over budget.
We know, Jack.
That's why we're talking it
through, buddy.
There's just nothing
quality in inventory
from the '40s,
so we're gonna
have to do a build
on most of the major players.
That's at least two suits
per player per scene.
And an additional 200 grand
we don't have.
Well, more because
we still have to dress
everyone at the wedding.
What if it's a small,
intimate affair,
maybe only family?
Stop!
It can't be a small affair.
She's the daughter of the Don.
There are a lot
of speaking parts.
Maybe you can combine
some of them.
Oh, I forgot.
We're doing
an off-off-Broadway play now.
Okay, look,
everybody just relax.
We are still making the movie
that we all set out to make.
Well, we're also still
about $2 million over budget
so unless you know something,
I don't know, Mr. Producer,
I suggest
you grab your scissors
and start making cuts
everywhere.
Where there's a will,
there's a way.
Hey, Al.
Got a sec?
Yeah.
So we've got a problem.
Look, Andrea,
I just want to say I think
you're doing an incredible job
casting this movie.
And it's obvious to me
that Paramount,
they knew what they were doing
when they hired you.
Thank you.
You're welcome. It's true.
And, uh, listen,
about the other night.
We both had a lot to drink
and I'm not...
I'm not saying I was drunk.
Obviously,
I knew what I was doing,
but, you know,
we're working together.
And for me personally, I just
got out of a relationship,
so, you know,
it's probably best if we just...
Al, stop.
That's not the problem
I was talking about.
Oh.
We still don't have an actor
to play Luca Brasi.
It's the last big role
we need to cast.
Don't worry about it.
We'll find somebody.
Just so we're clear,
I'm a grown woman.
We both know what it was
and what it wasn't.
Relax.
You know how we said
that we can make
this picture for 4 million?
Well, unless half the crew
works for free,
we're never gonna get there.
You gotta call Bob.
No, that's a check
I can't cash.
I used it all up on Pacino.
What... so what?
You just quit?
That's not fair.
What does fair have to do
with anything?
What's this?
A script.
It's called "Chinatown."
Any good?
A lot of talk about water
in the future.
You think it would be dull,
but it's oddly compelling.
Anything for me in it?
No.
Can we talk about something
that's important to me?
Yeah. What?
"The Getaway."
We passed on it.
Well, Warner Brothers didn't
and they're making it.
Steve McQueen just signed on
and there's a part
that I really want.
McQueen is in prison,
helps a crook plan a heist.
The crook betrays Steve,
and they take off across Texas
with the money,
running from the law
and the criminals.
A strong woman, quick thinker.
Walter Hill wrote it,
Peckinpah is directing,
and... and they want me.
It's not good enough
for you, Al,
and I really don't have time
for this right now.
I'm going to do it.
Starts shooting next week.
Do you want my opinion
or my blessing?
I want you to support
my opinion with your blessing.
How about I tell your agent
I'm not gonna work with him
if they let you do this.
How about that?
And destroy your marriage.
Ali.
Ali, come on.
Come back.
Hey.
What?
Look, I don't wanna fight,
but I'm under a lot of pressure
right now.
Thanks to you,
"Love Story" was a huge hit,
but if "The Godfather"
doesn't follow, I'm fucked.
I can't give Bluhdorn
a reason to sell, okay?
Bob still hasn't returned
any of my calls.
Sheila says
he's still pissed.
He needs time to cool off.
She said you should just
go to Bluhdorn yourself.
Remind me never to cross
the assistant pool.
It's more dangerous
in the mafia.
You have no idea.
You made any headway
with the budget?
Not unless you got a couple
extra million lying around.
Do you want me
to take a look at it?
The budget? Yeah, sure.
Knock yourself out.
You gonna take
Sheila's advice?
Yeah.
How is he today?
Mr. Bluhdorn
will see you now.
We're going in.
You want more money.
Charlie, come on.
We just came by
to see how your day was going.
Ah, it's all bullshit.
This being polite is a waste
of at least an hour every day.
How are you?
How's your kids?
How's your wife?
Well, what do you say?
She's got a suspicious mole.
Who gives a shit?
You're being polite.
That's your tell.
You want more money
and you agreed to do this film
for 4.5.
It can't be done for 4.5.
Low budget
specialist, my ass.
Look, Charlie, I got all
the actors to work for scale,
including Marlon Brando.
I'm getting tax breaks
from the city.
It's just still
not enough money.
Have you spoken to Evans?
He's not returning my calls.
Oh, and who's fault is that?
I warned you.
You made this bed
you're sleeping in, Ruddy.
I'm gonna make you an offer.
Take it or leave it.
Ruddy, you and Coppola
can get 6 million,
but you both have to
put up your fees
against any overages.
We'll have to talk
about that.
We'll take it.
He spoke. We're done.
Get the fuck out of my office.
We could've gotten to 6.5.
He said take it or leave it.
Let it go, Al.
The Corleones are expecting us
for dinner.
Hey.
We're in here.
Yeah, here we go.
Very nice.
Hello.
How you doing, Bob, Morgana?
Talia.
Oh, look at you.
Hey.
John.
How are you, sir?
Jimmy, come here.
Look who's decided
to show up, huh?
I guess you're the boss.
You're the boss.
How are ya? Good.
What's going on, buddy?
Hey, boss.
Diane, Al, beautiful.
Hey, look, it's Carlo.
The douchebag has arrived.
Here you go, Marlon.
Thank you.
Thank you for being here.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention,
please?
Oh, I want to thank you all
for coming out tonight.
This is very exciting.
You all look wonderful.
And I just thought it would be
really nice
to have the Corleone family
come together
for a real Italian dinner, huh?
Before we all start shooting
in a couple days.
That's it.
Just enjoy yourself.
Sit wherever you want
and let's eat.
Mangia.
Here you go.
I'm not the head
of this family.
Right.
I should help.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
She's got it.
Stay here with me.
No, no.
Your mother first. Always.
Are you gonna sit down
or what?
You get any eggplant?
No.
Well, you gotta try some.
You want me to get you some?
I... it's just I was gonna
get some anyway, you know?
So I... I thought
I... I can get you some.
I appreciate having
the whole family together
for my birthday.
Many things happen in life.
Celebrations, tragedies,
births, deaths.
But through it all,
what's right here
is what's important.
Family.
May you live forever.
- Ah, salud.
- Salud!
Ooh-hoo.
You make this?
Mm.
Mom's recipe.
Christ, it's the best
thing I ever put in my mouth.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, stuggatz,
you know how lucky you are?
I think she's the lucky one.
You don't know
what you're in for.
You're gonna need both hands
to deal with that one, right?
I only need one hand
to enforce my rules.
What did you just say?
Did you just threaten her?
Everybody needs a smack
once in a while.
Hey, hey.
Come on.
That's enough.
Who's this jamoke
think he is?
Has this man
laid a hand on you?
No, Pop. No, no.
It... it... it was my fault.
I didn't do nothing.
You know what the name
"Corleone" means?
"Heart of a lion."
So if I were you,
I wouldn't bring any attention
to the fact that
I'm the slowest in the herd.
If I offended you,
I'm sorry, godfather.
What do you have
to be sorry for?
You said you never hit her.
I'm just happy to be
in your family.
Kiss the ring.
Huh?
Kiss the fucking ring,
you fucking idiot.
Kiss it.
- Kiss it.
Kiss it, kiss it, kiss it.
Hey, kiss it.
Kiss it, kiss it.
Kiss it.
Kiss it, kiss it!
Everybody mangia.
Can you believe
this guy, huh?
You know what I'm thinking?
This is gonna be
a great film.
Yeah.
And they need a stove.
You had to bring that up,
didn't you?
Can't I just have
one good moment
without it being taken away
from me on this project?
I'm sorry.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
But food is so important
to this family.
Well, this family is gonna
have to get by with one burner.
Yeah?
Hey! Al.
I heard last night went well.
Your friend Gianni
didn't think so.
What a schmegege.
So I've been going through
the budget.
Uh-huh.
And?
And there seem to be
three men with
very Italian-sounding names.
They don't belong
to any department.
They're on payroll,
but I can't find them
on the crew list.
Al.
One of them is Caesar.
Caesar, I just saw him
at the wake.
He didn't mention anything.
Who hired him?
Probably one of the unions.
That's not weirdest part.
All three of these guys,
they have the same
social security number.
Really?
I don't know
why you find that funny.
Gulf and Western
is a publicly-traded company.
If they find out
we have mobsters on payroll,
it's over for all of us.
Look, get me Caesar.
I'll talk to him.
Caesar.
What's this about?
You could have finished lunch.
That's not how I like
to do things.
Never make the boss wait.
Right.
Let me ask you something.
What exactly do you do here?
I am a production assistant.
And who do you assist?
The production.
And what does production do?
Like, if there's a problem
with the unions,
I assist the unions
to not be a problem.
Moving right along.
These guys down here,
what do they do?
Those are my guys.
They're, um...
production assistant's
assistants.
Listen, you guys can't all
have the same
social security number.
Al, you know who you gotta
talk to about that.
You need anything else, boss?
'Cause, um,
I gotta take a dump.
Good luck with that.
How you doing?
Hi.
Al, there are two FBI agents
waiting for you.
Thanks so much for seeing us
on short notice.
I'm Agent Zabel.
This is Agent Richman.
What can I do for you boys?
What exactly do you do here,
Mr. Ruddy?
I'm the producer.
You mind telling us
why you were at
Carmine Vispiciano's wake?
He was a friend.
Where's this going?
Well, I guess
we were just wondering
how a man with
top security clearance
with the Rand Corporation
is now in bed with the mafia.
Well, fellas,
you know how they say that
truth is stranger than fiction?
I see nothing, nothing!
Exactly.
That's pretty good.
So why did you walk away
from "Hogan's Heroes"?
TV's too limiting.
You can't tell real stories
on TV.
It's fake.
And Marlon Brando
doesn't do TV.
Al, you seem like a nice guy.
Let me give you some advice.
These guys are a lot
more dangerous
than they first appear.
Look, honestly,
I'm just trying
to make my movie
and that's where
the association ends.
So I gave one of them a job,
hence the badge.
It's safer for him here
than working out there.
Not safer for you.
And we'd feel a lot better
if we can keep
a closer eye on you.
If you let us
put a wire on you,
we can protect you.
I appreciate it, guys, but
I'll take my chances on my own.
Yeah, she's gonna do
"The Getaway" next.
Well, Peckinpah
is a great director.
We just figured it was the
best move after "Love Story"
so she doesn't get typecast
as the shiksa goddess.
No, no, I... I've never worked
with McQueen.
What do you know about him,
Cary?
Look, I gotta go, Cary.
Thank you so much for the info
and I'll speak soon.
All right, bye.
It's Lapidus.
Barry!
How they hanging?
Guess what I'm calling about.
Another sock sale
at Brooks Brothers?
You were right about
"Love Story."
Well, thank you, Barry.
Maybe I do know what I'm doing.
You have made the board
very happy.
Gulf and Western's
stock price is up.
Nice work, Bobby.
Peter, I just had
a wacko call from Lapidus.
Aubrey wasn't bluffing.
They're trying
to sell Paramount.
And?
Tastes like fish bait.
But is too small
to slip on a hook.
Ugh.
That's impossible.
It's $200 caviar
from the Caspian Sea.
I don't care if it was $1,000
and came out of God's ass.
If I'm eating eggs,
I want 'em cracked, fried,
and covered in cheese.
I'm glad you could make
some time for me.
I know Ruddy
keeps you very busy.
Yeah.
Well, anything
for a free drink.
So tell me,
what does Bettye want?
I'm not sure what you mean.
What do you want
for yourself?
What do you want to do
with your life?
What is this?
Are you trying to be
my mentor now or something?
Do you enjoy
working as Ruddy's secretary,
pouring coffee,
answering phones?
Ah, is that
what you think I do?
Well, that's what
all secretaries do.
That's what
they're supposed to do.
I'm not all secretaries.
No, you're not.
No.
Come work for me.
Ah, for once,
she has nothing to say.
I work for Ruddy.
He works for me
so technically
you already work for me.
With all due respect, Charlie,
I love where I am.
They say movies are magic,
but they don't care
about magic.
They care about money.
And so do I.
You're selling Paramount.
I never said that.
I like you, Bettye.
Think about it.
Who else knows?
I assume the word
is already out.
Did he say anything
about the movie?
Not exactly.
You speak Charlie.
What did he say exactly?
He offered me a job.
I'll tell you
what they're doing, Peter.
They are using my success
against me.
Yeah.
Nothing's set in stone.
They fought me tooth and nail.
They told me not to make
"Love Story."
I put my balls on the line.
I knew people wanted a romance.
I knew that Ali was a star.
I knew people would
fall in love with her.
I fucking delivered
the biggest movie ever. Ever.
And now they're taking
my baby away,
selling her off
for spare parts?
I don't think so.
Fuck that.
What the fuck?
Hey!
What are you doing here?
We've got to work order to
map out the cemetery expansion.
Get the fuck off my lot.
Excuse me?
I said
get the fuck off my lot!
Hey, hey, hey.
This is exactly what I said
was gonna happen.
I heard you were
asking Caesar
a lot of questions.
No, no, Joe,
- I was just curious about...
- Hey, look, Al,
I don't like to talk business
over the phone.
Come by the League office.
We can talk about
whatever you want.
Joe,
I'm a little busy right now.
Great, I'll see you in an hour.
I gotta go see him.
Hold down the fort.
In the middle of all this?
He called for me.
I gotta go.
You sound like a gangster.
Be back in an hour.
If you're not, I'm gonna send
for your special agents.
I'm sure they'll be around.
Big day tomorrow.
You ready?
Yeah, I'm just going over
the scene, like,
a million times in my head.
Is the weather gonna be bad?
Clear skies, 45 degrees.
Perfect weather.
I just can't believe
that it's actually
beginning tomorrow.
I know.
You made it happen.
We.
We made it happen.
It's a miracle.
Everything that
we've been through.
They said that
this was not going to succeed.
They did.
And now it's up to me
to make sure that it does.
And it will.
And you're gonna
make it happen, Francis.
It's gonna be great.
Hey.
Good to see you, Al.
Come on.
He's inside waiting for you.
And it's because
of courageous men
like Congressman Biaggi,
who's willing to fight
for Italian Americans,
that we're able to make
any progress with civil rights.
That's why the League
wholeheartedly
throws its support
behind the Congressman
for his re-election.
Yes. Thank you, thank you.
Oh, oh, oh.
I'd also like to announce that
after intense negotiations
with Gulf and Western,
the League has decided
to allow them
to make the movie,
"The Godfather."
That's right.
And I... and I should say
that it's all because of this
man right there, Al Ruddy.
Al, come up here. Come up here.
He's the film's producer.
It's because of him
that we were able
to come to this agreement.
It was his brilliant idea
that Gulf and Western
donate the proceeds
from the premiere
to the League's hospital fund.
We can't thank you enough, Al.
This is the man
solely responsible
for the alliance
between the Italian League,
Gulf and Western,
and Paramount Pictures.
You're one of us.
Hey, come on, come up here.
Come on, take a picture.
How long have you
been working with Mr. Colombo?
Come up. Come on.
And what are the details
of this financial relationship?
Take a picture.
How does
Paramount Pictures feel
about this, Mr. Ruddy?
Is it true that the
movie is still about the mafia?
How does
Gulf and Western feel
about being in business
with Joe Colombo?
You're in bed with the mafia
for the whole world to see.
I did what I had to do.
They don't get it.
So make them get it.
You try to say no
to Joe Colombo,
let me know how that works out
for you.
We cannot have another war.
You should have stayed
in prison.
It was safer for you there.
Action!
We know people want...
violence...
Where's Ruddy?
Ruddy?
It wasn't personal,
it was business.
Just business, huh?
Unfortunate things
present opportunities.
Sometimes it is personal.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I
have your attention please?
The Patsy's cast dinner.
It's just a favorite
scene of mine.
It's a great scene.
Coppola had a dinner at
Patsy's for the Corleone cast.
I just thought it would
be really nice to have
the Corleone family
come together
for a real Italian dinner.
And he didn't tell them
to play their
characters or anything.
He just wanted to
have a nice dinner
with all the main characters
before they started shooting.
Bringing all of
these actors together
allowed for a subtle
alchemy to be present.
And at that dinner they
all started, weirdly,
assuming their parts.
Let's eat.
Mangia.
Talia Shire started
bringing platters over
to serve the table.
I'm not the head of this family.
Brando sat at
the head of the table.
No, no.
Your mother first, always.
The three sons started to jockey
for position to
sit next to Brando.
You get any eggplant?
No.
Well, you gotta try some.
You want me to get you some?
I think that this was the place
where the Corleone
family was born.
I appreciate having
the whole family together
for my birthday.
It's just a really great scene,
A great idea, to show
them being loose with it.
To show the family
becoming a family.
What's right here
is what's important.
Family.
There was a very
delicate balance
to allowing these
people to come to life
in a way where we began to see
not Al Pacino but
Michael Corleone.
You know what
the name Corleone means?
Heart of a lion.
Not Jimmy Caan, but Sonny.
The douche bag has arrived.
There was
something about that dinner
that always stood out to us
because you could see Coppola
and Ruddy sitting there
watching the dynamics of
the Corleone family play out
and understand that they
had something special.
You know what I'm thinking?
This is gonna be a great film.
- Yeah!
- Thank you, everybody.
You told me, do whatever it
takes to get my movie made.
You said to color
outside the lines.
I never told you
to fuck me over.
From Bob's standpoint,
he wanted a star.
He's like,
"I don't like Pacino!"
Ruddy goes to
Bluhdorn behind his back
and says, "We need Al Pacino."
I'm gonna make you an offer.
It was just brutally
difficult, but he had to do it.
He didn't want this
unheard of kid.
He already had Brando.
He's like, you know, it
was already exacerbating
going into a land of chaos.
But I suppose the sort of
Shakespearean part of that is
he felt like he'd been
stabbed in the back.
It was a sort of a Julius Caesar
moment for him.
It was for the
good of the movie.
Then his sort
of major confidante was Ali.
I love working with Matthew.
It's really no acting necessary.
He is a consummate pro.
I think I'm doing both
of us a favor.
Watching Matthew create
organically, take to take,
and his incredible range
as an actor,
but also having all of that
range fit so beautifully
inside of Robert Evans.
It's not good enough for you Al
and I really don't have
time for this right now.
So dependable
as a scene partner.
Working with him did feel
like I was always being held.
I'm going to do it.
He goes and watches
The Panic in Needle Park
and he sits in there with Ali.
Pacino doesn't
have to say a word
and I can't take
my eyes off him.
In the end, he's like, "Well,
he is actually really good,
this guy."
Which is wonderful, and then...
Listen to me.
You're still a putz,
but I got Pacino.
He's in the picture.