NARRATOR:
Previously on The X-Files...
MULDER: My name is Fox Mulder.
In the 1990s,
I began investigating
paranormal science cases
through a unit of the FBI
known as the X-Files.
My partner in this pursuit
was Agent Dana Scully,
a medical doctor
and scientist.
In 2001, we had
a child together...
William. ...but had to
put him up for adoption
to hide him from those
who wished him harm.
In 2002, the FBI
closed the X-Files.
Fourteen years later,
circumstances have arisen
which demand new X-Files
invesfigafions“...
Are you saying you
have alien DNA?
...bringing Scully and I
back together.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Good day, Dr. Sanjay.
Yeah. Good morning.
(METAL DETECTOR WHINING)
Sanjay! (CHUCKLES)
Oh, you okay?
Rough weekend?
A humdinger.
Work or pleasure?
I haven't known pleasure
for quite some time.
(CHUCKLES)
(HIGH-PITCHED
ELECTRONIC WHINING)
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
MAN: The Founder
looked at the data.
He sent a message
this morning.
"Do over."
Do over?
WOMAN: That's it?
We spent months
on those trials.
We've tried every new source
of pluripotent stem cells,
including samples
from amniotic fluids.
We need more than just
pronouncements from above.
We need direction!
What about a meeting
with the man?
MAN: You want the Founder
to tell you
how terrible your data is
face-to-face?
The guy is a recluse.
No one here's even
seen him for years.
(HIGH-PITCHED VVHINING) For all we
know, he didn't even read the stuff.
I can assure you that Augustus
Goldman is fully engaged.
(IN SLOW MOTION) But the
Founder has other interests
that keep him occupied.
Yeah, what about that?
WOMAN: Doesn't that
creep you out,
that he's referred to
as "The Founder"?
(CROWS CAWING)
(GLASS CLINKING)
...do it.
MAN: Now.
It's necessary.
Data is the key.
Don't hesitate.
Go.
Go now.
Go!
Go now...
(WHINING GETS LOUDER)
Can't anyone hear that?
(GASPS)
Sorry.
Excuse me.
WOMAN: Do it.
MAN 1: Now.
MAN 2: Data is the key.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Sanjay! Sanjay!
Sanjay, come on! Open up!
Open the door, Sanjay!
Sanjay!
Sanjay, open the door!
It's not opening!
Open the door! Sanjay!
Something's wrong with the system!
Open! Come on!
The certificate. Sanjay, open the door!
Sanjay, open the door!
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINING)
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Sanjay?
Sanjay! sanjay!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
What do you make
of this, Scully?
Well, it seems
that Dr. Sanjay
had a psychotic break
and committed suicide.
Note the letter opener
sticking out of his head.
Noted.
All the witnesses I spoke to
have consistent accounts.
I mean the room.
He chose the most secured place
in the building to kill himself.
He was trying to
access something.
These are isolated servers,
so the only way
to get to the data
is through this terminal,
which is also protected.
Is that why we're here?
You're interested
in the server?
What are you
looking for, Mulder?
Unhand the hard drive, sir.
This is evidence.
It's classified.
The reason why
we're investigating,
rather than the local police,
is because we have
security clearance.
To be in the room.
Not to look inside this.
This is property
of Department of Defense.
We need to conduct
a few more interviews, then,
before we conclude
our investigation.
The individuals
pertinent to this incident
have already been interviewed
by your colleague.
We'd like to talk to
Augustus Goldman.
That's impossible.
Dr. Goldman was not
even on campus
when this happened.
Well, if you won't let me
look at the drive,
then I have to
talk to Goldman about
what the deceased was trying
to access before he died.
I'm not authorized to confirm
that I have knowledge of the
whereabouts of the Founder.
Can you confirm that
you have security cameras
watching over
the entire complex?
There's that one, and I
saw a few more out there.
Yes. In that case, I'd like
to see all of the tapes.
As soon as possible.
All right.
I'll have those sent over.
But for now, remove this body
so we can secure this room.
Sorry, we're not finished...
Oh, we are finished.
We are finished.
Mulder, that's not
yourphone.
You know me, Scully.
I'm old-school.
Riley v. California.
The Supreme Court ruled that
you needed a warrant
to search a mobile phone.
That's for a suspect.
Sanjay's the victim.
Well, there is no victim.
He killed himself.
Well, then, I'm sure
he won't mind
me talking to
some of his friends.
Here's someone he talked to
every night. "Gupta."
Dr. Sanjay
is from western India.
Gupta's a Marathi word.
It means "secret."
How do you know that?
I'm old-school, Mulder.
Pre-Google.
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)
Gupta?
Thanks for meeting me.
My name is...
No. No names, please.
You're Sonny's friend?
Is that guy bothering you?
Not yet.
What do you want?
I want to talk.
Can we go somewhere
more private?
I don't know you
well enough.
I'm safe. You can trust me.
Come on.
Oh, whoa, whoa! No.
Well, you said
you wanted to "talk."
Yes. I don't think that means
exactly what you think it means.
Or I'm not...
You guys are all alike,
you know?
You say you want to
walk on the wild side,
but when it comes down to it,
you're repressed.
I finally let go
of all that,
that self-loathing and
thatjudgment and I'm free.
Stop tormenting yourself.
The truth is in here.
Yeah, I've heard
something like that.
Hey, listen,
I gotta tell you...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Sanjay is dead.
Deceased is a male,
35 years old,
five-foot-eight and three-quarters
inches, 180 pounds.
(SIGHS)
The probable cause of death
is the introduction,
self-propelled,
of a letter opener
into the cerebral cortex
by way of the ear canal.
Oh.
I will now commence with my
overall external examination.
The last couple of weeks,
he was...
He was distant.
He was troubled.
I thought it was me,
you know?
We hadn't gotten together
for a while.
I mean, he'd call me
every night,
but nothing physical.
Did he talk to you
about his problems?
About work?
Yeah.
Yeah, he said he was upset
about his kids.
He said they were dying.
His kids?
He was single.
I didn't push it.
I just tried to
make him feel better.
Well, I saw
where he lived.
There was nothing there.
He lived an antiseptic life.
He lived two lives.
In two separate places.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Mulder, you gotta see this.
I had to break his fingers
to pry them open.
But he wrote that on the palm
of his hand before he died.
"Founder's Mutation."
The Founder is what they called Dr.
Goldman at Nugenics.
Is that why you wanted
to talk to him?
I don't think that's the mutation
Sanjay was referring to.
Did you find anything else
on the autopsy?
Well, there were no abnormalities in Dr.
Sanjay's brain.
The opener destroyed
the acoustic nerve
and then went into
the cerebral cortex.
It's weird, because the
opener goes in at 9O degrees
and then it veers off at 6O degrees
up into his brain, like he was
hunting for something.
Yeah. It ended up
in the auditory cortex.
You know,
he blurted something out
at the meeting,
before his suicide.
He said,
"Can't anyone hear that?"
Mmm. But nobody else
could hear a thing.
Well, ultimately,
hearing is just nerve impulses
interpreted by the brain.
What if those same impulses
could be generated
without actual vibrations
striking the ear drum?
Hmm.
Anyway,
if he left a note on his hand,
maybe he left other clues.
But where?
We've checked out every
square inch of his apartment.
Well, he leased a place
that only Gupta knew about.
I think we should go to
where he actually lived.
It's hard to imagine,
in 2016,
that Sanjay had to keep his
lifestyle preferences a secret.
Being gay
wasn't his only secret.
(TIRES SCREECH)
Mulder?
I found something.
His kids.
Yeah.
Sanjay was afraid
they were dying.
These kids,
they look so young.
None of them
look older than 10.
Look at the backgrounds.
SCULLY:
It's a clinical setting.
It looks like
it might be a hospital.
(CAR DOORS CLOSING)
The police are coming up.
We must have triggered
a silent alarm.
All right, look around,
he's bound to have kept
some information
on them somewhere.
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINING)
(GROANS)
Mulder?
Mulder, are you okay?
They're coming. Mulder.
OFFICER: Police officer!
Lady, put your hands
where I can see 'em!
SCULLYI FBI.
Find her.
Help me.
Find her. Find her.
Do you have anything
to add to this, Agent Scully?
If you look at the files
that we found
in Dr. Sanjay's apartment...
No, I can't look at those.
They're right over there.
MURPHY: These
files are classified.
They're the property of
the Department of Defense.
Well, I've had
a look at them.
Those files
are the medical records
of children with
grave genetic abnormalities.
How those children relate
to Dr. Sanjay's suicide
is the object
of our investigation.
SKINNER: Well, considering
the fact that you just lost
access to those files,
your investigation is closed.
I'll submit the report
on the suicide
to the proper authorities.
We're done here.
(CLEARS THROAT) Let me remind
you, Agents Mulder and Scully,
dissemination of any
classified material,
either internally
or publically,
will be dealt with harshly.
I'm familiar
with Edward Snowden.
I assume you made copies.
I managed some top sheets
before the DOD took over.
I think those children
are failed experiments.
So you suspect the Department
of Defense is experimenting
with genetic modification
on humans?
What do you think?
I think there are many troubling
details to this case,
and if Agent Mulder
has nothing more to add...
I don't.
...then I think we need time
to prove his theory.
The bureaucracy in the FBI
has become
increasingly complex
and inefficient.
It might take days
for your incident report and
order to olose theinvesfigafion
to make it through
the proper channels.
Welcome back, you two.
Surveillance footage?
Yeah, from Nugenics.
I've been working on
syncing all the cameras
to the exact time code
of Dr. Sanjay's suicide.
There.
What happened to you at
Sanjay's apartment, Mulder?
I can understand why you
wouldn't want to tell Skinner,
but I was there,
I saw you
on your knees in pain.
I heard sounds.
It was a high-pitched
frequency,
like a steel spike being
driven through my head.
And then it focused
into two words,
"Find her."
There were no sounds.
I didn't hear anything.
Look at those birds.
Maybe they seeded
the lawn that morning.
Infrasounds, Scully.
Vibrations inaudible
to the human ear
but known to drive the
worms up through the soil
to the surface,
in response to them.
Mulder,
how are these connected?
The birds, the suicide, the
kids, the genetic: anomalies.
What are you hiding?
Augustus Goldman
is the only one
who might know
how it all fits together.
We gotta talk to him.
What are you hiding?
Sanjay heard sounds
right before
he committed suicide.
That could be you, Mulder.
This is dangerous.
Oh.
When has that
ever stopped us before?
I might know
how to get to Goldman.
WOMAN: Augustus.
Yes, I know him well, but
he's a very private person.
Some would say reclusive.
Without him, we wouldn't
have the resources
to help these women in need.
He's a true champion
of the unborn.
Dr. Goldman is a blessing.
That's why we're here today.
I've become aware
of a situation
that I wanted
to share with you.
Dr. Goldman
is under investigation.
ObamaCare.
We wanted to spare him
the indignity
of having the government knock
at his door unannounced.
I was wondering if we could
meet with him in private.
Dana, I'm afraid Our
Lady of Sorrows cannotbe
a conduit for the FBI
to one of our biggest donors.
Sister Mary, I've worked
here for seven years.
You know me.
Yes, and I know your heart's
in the right place.
I wouldn't ask
if it weren't important.
I have a number I can call.
I'll agree to relay
a message.
Thank you.
Ask Dr. Goldman
if he'll talk to us
about the Founder's Mutation.
Stay here.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
I got to get out of here.
What's your name?
Agnes.
You got a car?
Do you want to call someone?
You think if I could call
someone I would be asking you?
Just forget it. I knew you
weren't gonna help me.
Agnes. Wait.
I'm a doctor.
You can tell me anything.
I don't belong here.
Not with these sheep.
I don't care what I signed.
The hospital
is only concerned with
the health of the mother
and the baby.
My baby-
Of course, your baby.
I changed my mind.
I'm not giving it up.
I don't care if he's sick.
Sick?
My baby's not right.
They saw it
on the ultrasound thing
and I had a feeling, you know,
ever since I got pregnant.
But everybody here
has the same story.
Just don't say anything.
I was just
kidding around, okay?
If you ever want to talk.
I've spoken to Augustus.
He said he'd be happy
to meet you.
Thank you.
Sister Mary, how are the
patients chosen to be here?
They're homeless, damaged
in one way or another.
Alcohol, drugs,
no fathers in the picture.
Men and their lies.
No offense.
Desire is
the devil's pitchfork.
But as long as there's a
need and an innocent child,
we'll provide for each
and every one.
MULDER:
It's insidious, Scully.
A ward for pregnant women
paid for by Augustus Goldman,
the founder of a company with deep
ties to the Department of Defense.
This could be another phase
of the project,
their experiments
in eugenics.
Those women in there
could be incubators.
Mulder...
I'm not a fragile
little girl.
Scully...
This is what you
suspected all along,
but were afraid
to articulate.
Is this what you believe
happened to me 15 years ago?
When I got pregnant,
when I had my baby?
(SIGHS)
Was I just an incubator?
You're never "just"
anything to me, Scully.
Do you ever
think about William?
Yes, of course I do,
butPveH.lfeel like I've had
to put that behind me.
He'd be 15 years old now.
And I've missed every
single year of his life.
And sometimes
I hate myself
that I didn't have
the courage
to stand by him.
You did what you did
to keep him safe.
His adoption is secret,
his location is unknown
because you had to
protect him.
Do you believe
he was an experiment?
I don't know.
What if he's
out there somewhere,
like one of those kids
on Sanjay's wall,
fighting for his life?
All we can do, Scully,
is pull the thread,
see what it unravels.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
It's the first day of school.
You nervous?
Your hands are sweaty.
Ew! That's you.
(LAUGHS)
What's the most important
thing to remember?
Sit still, listen,
say "excuse me" if you fart.
(LAUGHS)
The most important thing to
remember is that I love you.
That's all you
have to remember.
Come on, let's go
say hi to your teacher.
Thank you.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Hi, Mom.
Bye, Mom.
Be home in time for dinner!
Will...
I'm scared.
You're gonna be fine.
You've just broken your arm.
Does it hurt anywhere else?
Okay, we're gonna get you to the
hospital, and take some x-rays
to make sure you don't have
a concussion, okay, honey?
WILLIAM: Mom!
Mom, please!
Mom!
What's happening to me?
DR. GOLDMAN:
Founder's Mutation.
Intriguing message.
It's what Sanjay
wrote on his hand.
Yes, before his unfortunate
act of self-destruction.
Very dramatic,
but meaningless.
I've read everything
you published, Dr. Goldman.
It seems your research deals primarily
with genetic: manipulation.
Let me try to explain
to you what we do here.
It's no secret.
We're trying to
save children.
I won't tell you their last
names, to protect their privacy,
but I can tell you what
they are fighting against:
Proteus syndrome,
Crouzon syndrome,
all kinds of
cancerous tumors,
epidermal dysplasia,
Pitt-Hopkins syndrome,
ichthyosis, Marfan syndrome,
among others.
We are a cutting-edge
research facility
for these
unfortunate patients.
There's absolutely no cost
involved to be treated here.
Would you like
to talk to him?
Sure.
Adam?
You have a visitor.
Hi, Adam.
My name is Dr. Scully.
How long have you
been here, Adam?
Forever.
And where are your parents?
I don't have any.
He was sent to us
as a baby.
Adam has a form
of Crouzon syndrome.
And why is he
in a sealed room?
All of the children.
He has a genetic disorder.
He's not contagious.
Thank you, Adam.
We are working
with therapies
unavailable anywhere
in the world.
We need to eliminate
the environmental factors
that could affect
the outcome.
I am searching for the key
that was the seed
to all of these terrible
genetic abnormalities.
Alien DNA?
Is that why the Department of
Defense is funding your research?
Dr. Scully,
I was told that you
were the rational one.
MOLLY: No! Let g0!
Molly!
Let go of me!
No!No!No!No!
I'm afraid that that is
all the time that I have.
Sarah will show you out.
This way, please.
He didn't answer
my question.
(CRASHING)
Let go of me!
Molly! Molly!
No!No!No!
No!
Did you see that, Mulder?
Interesting.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Something's happened
to Agnes.
(SIRENS WAILING)
We found the victim with
your card in her pocket.
Hit and run,
car was moving pretty fast.
Skid marks from back there
up to the point of impact.
We're checking cameras
in the area.
No witnesses.
What about the baby?
What are you talking about?
She was pregnant.
The baby's gone.
Mulder.
Mmm.
Agnes died from
blunt force trauma.
Most likely from
the impact of the car.
Her right ulna
was broken in two places,
her lungs were lacerated
by broken ribs,
and her skull was crushed.
What about the baby?
Surgically removed.
I couldn't tell
if the fetus was still alive
when it was taken
from her womb,
but they took it, Mulder.
To get rid of evidence.
Agnes wanted to talk.
She left the hospital.
That baby was the only proof
that she was part of
Goldman's experiment.
What if the baby
was still alive?
Mulder, that car hit her
so hard that an adult woman
with the benefit of
a mature skeletal structure
wasn't able to
survive the impact.
It's highly unlikely that
the baby would remain viable.
Unlikely for human fetuses.
In 1973, the Syndicate
was convened to assist
in a project to
colonize the world
by creating
alien/human hybrids.
The project was
ultimately unsuccessful.
I doubt they ever
stopped trying.
But what you're
talking about is
changing the genetic makeup
of a population.
That's the next step
in evolution.
Every new species begins
with a Founder's Mutation.
One child with the correct
combination of DNA
could be a start.
There was a study
pubfishedlastyear
in Nature Communications,
by Batini and Hallast,
that found that Y chromosomes
in the majority of European men
could be traced back
to just three individuals
from the Bronze Age.
I did some digging around
the police archives,
looking for anything
related to Goldman.
Seventeen years ago,
Jackie Goldman was remanded
to St. Elizabeth's hospital
as a forensics patient.
She was adjudicated
criminally insane.
Dr. Goldman's wife?
She was convicted
of murdering her baby.
That body also
was never found.
Mrs. Goldman,
we'd like to ask you
a few questions
aboutyourhusband.
About his work?
Mulder, she hasn't said
anything in 10 minutes.
(CAT YOWLING)
You don't like cats?
What do you want?
Can we ask you
a few questions, Jackie?
Not about my husband.
He is the one
still keeping me here.
Do you miss your daughter?
Molly.
You should see
that one, that one.
I love my daughter.
But there was something
odd about her.
I felt it from the day
she was born.
I didn't know for sure
until she was two.
Where's Molly?
She fell in the pool
and nobody noticed.
Molly was underwater
for at least 10 minutes.
She should've been dead.
I never told anyone else this.
Not only was she alive,
she was breathing
in the water.
The other moms
thought it was a miracle.
But I knew what it was.
My husband did something
to the embryo.
He used our own daughter
for his research.
I was nine months pregnant
at the time.
I was not about to let him
have my son.
I had to get away
from that monster.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Please, don't go.
I love you.
I want my daughter, Augustus.
She is safe, so are you,
right here with me.
What did you do to her?
Jackie! Jackie!
No!
He took Molly away.
He hid her from me.
So I got in the car
and I drove.
I just drove,
no idea where to go.
I knew there was no chance
they would leave me alone.
I had another baby
in my belly.
U-I-heyu?
The government.
Augustus worked for them.
I couldn't trust anyone.
Especially the police.
I was so scared.
I was going too fast.
And there was an animal
in the middle of the road.
I panicked and I crashed.
(GROANING)
(WHIMPERING)
I thought I was gonna die.
(GASPING)
But that's when
I heard the sound.
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINING)
(SCREAMING)
It was so loud
and piercing, it hurt.
It was in my head.
He was talking to me in the
only way that he knew how.
And I knew what I had to do.
They said I killed my baby.
I didn't.
I let him out.
Do you know what happened
to your son?
Passed out from
loss of blood.
Woke up in a hospital.
I never saw my boy again.
I think about him every day.
A mother never forgets.
All my training,
everything that I know
about psychology
tells me that
she's delusional,
but, Mulder, there's something
about her that I trust.
She heard a tone
in her head, a screech,
that's what happened to me.
Are you saying
that you think
the baby that
communicated with her
communicated with you?
Wouldn't be a baby anymore.
Excuse me.
You don't work for
the hospital, do you?
You're a subcontractor?
Yeah. A-1 Janitorial.
We're all over the city.
Thank you. Thanks.
A-1 Janitorial
also services Nugenics.
You'll recognize
the uniform.
He's cleaning the office directly
above the Secured Servers vault.
He's no more than 15 feet
away from Dr. Sanjay
at the time of his death.
Action, reaction.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
I made a request for the
name of the janitor on duty.
Turns out he also worked at
St. Elizabeth's last month.
High school dropout
Kyle Gilligan.
We got him.
I'm Special Agent Scully.
This is Special Agent Mulder.
We'd like to speak
with Kyle Gilligan.
I'm his mother.
Is he around?
We'd like to ask him
a few questions
about an incident at work.
The suicide?
You heard about that.
There's not a thing
that goes on
in my son's life
that I don't know.
Well, we'd still like
to speak with him.
He's got nothing to say.
Why don't you let us
decide that?
I don't like to expose my son
to stressful situations.
It's not good for him.
He doesn't understand it.
He's simple.
And he's a minor.
And I won't allow it.
You didn't give birth
to Kyle.
Mulder...
What did you say?
After the accident,
where'd you find him?
Get the hell off my porch.
Your son is unique,
have you ever wondered why?
Get out! Mulder, she's
making it pretty clear.
(BIRDS FLUTTERING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(SOFTLY) Bad things happen
when the birds gather.
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINING)
(GROANING)
Mulder?
Mulder! Mulder!
Where is he?
(SCREAMING)
Please, God, help!
Whatever you're doing,
stop right there.
(INHALES)
KYLE'S MOTHER:
Don't take him!
Don't!
Please don't take him!
He didn't know
what he was doing!
He was just trying
to protect me!
Is that true, Kyle?
That you don't know
what you're doing?
Why did you kill
Dr. Sanjay?
I didn't want him to die.
You made him kill himself.
No!
I would never.
He was helping me.
You got inside his head.
You got inside my head.
You can make people
hear things.
Like you just did,
like you did to me
in Sanjay's apartment.
But you can't control it.
I just want to find my sister.
Molly?
At the hospital,
where you worked.
You heard Jackie's story.
She told me that he has her.
And Jackie is
my real mother, okay?
I have to find my sister.
Kyle, nobody knows
where she is.
I know who knows.
Hmm.
Would you mind
if I took some blood?
Where's Molly?
How do you know that name?
NW
mother told me to find her.
And what would you do
once you found her?
I don't know.
I'm gonna let you meet Molly.
Molly?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
What's your name?
Kyle.
No.
You're not my sister.
No!
SCULLY: Kyle?
Molly?
You're Molly.
I didn't know
I had a brother.
I can hear you.
Are you ready?
Kyle!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
DR. GOLDMANI Molly!
No! No!
Daddy, just let me go!
Get the hell away from her!
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINING)
(GROANING)
Kyle!
(GRUNTING)
Scully!
(DR. GOLDMAN SCREAMING)
Skinner, keep your people
behind the red tape.
Department of Defense
has control of the facility.
It's now classified
as top secret.
We no longer have
jurisdiction here.
Have they found
Molly or Kyle?
You were the last one
to see them, Agent Mulder.
I blacked out after Goldman's
eyes popped out of the sockets.
Believe me,
you can't unsee that.
Well, they're gone. There's
no trace of them anywhere.
Kyle's blood.
A trace.
(MONKEY SHRIEKING)
Monkeys.
Yeah, that's...
Well, that's early man,
William.
That's the monolith.
What's a "momomyth"?
Some people think it represents
our first contact with aliens.
Other people think it represents
the beginning of human knowledge.
I think one day you'll probably
have your own ideas about it.
Dad.
Mmm.
My fin broke.
Space is hard.
"All great
and honorable actions
"are undertaken
with great difficulty.
"We choose to go to the moon
"in this decade
and do other things,
"not because they're easy...
BOTH:
"But because they are hard."
(CHUCKLES)
That's right.
Come on, let's light this candle.
We'll do yours first.
Okay.
There you go.
You ready?
Yep.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Ignition.
I'm gonna go
up there someday.
Dad!
William!
No!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)