NARRATOR: Previously
on The X-Files...
MULDER:
The countdown has begun.
Alien technology
being used against us
by a venal conspiracy
of men against humanity.
It's all part
of a conspiracy
dating back to the UFO
crash at Roswell in 1947.
How can we help you,
Mr. O'Malley?
I'm rattling
some pretty big cages
in the intelligence community,
but I'm prepared
to blow open
maybe the most evil conspiracy
the world has ever known.
I didn't know how my work
would be used.
They removed
your unborn fetuses?
They do everything
through here.
Even with the DNA.
Tell them about
your DNA, Sveta.
I have alien DNA. For sure.
MULDER". They police
us and spy on us,
tell us that makes us safer?
We've never been
in more danger.
Then do something
about it, Mulder.
What are they trying to do?
MULDER:
That's the missing piece.
Testing yourself
for alien DNA?
And I sequenced
my own genome
because of my history and because
we have a child together.
Scully,
are you saying
you have alien DNA?
I'm saying someone has to
stop these sons of bitohes.
Oh, no! (SOBBING)
No!
(EXPLODING)
SCULLY: My name is
Dana Katherine Scully.
I am a special agent with the
Federal Bureau of Investigation,
a career I chose
after medical school,
which promised a chance to
further my aim as a scientist
and as a seeker of justice
in a science-based world.
Soon after joining the FBI,
I was asked to review the work
of a fellow agent, Fox Mulder,
and to debunk the X-Files,
cases involving
what my superiors regarded as
science fiction and
a waste of resources.
I quickly came to understand
Mulder's work on the paranormal
wasn't such as I'd
been led to believe,
that the X-Files were worthy
of Mulder's investigations
and of mine, that a world
existed on the far fringes
of accepted science,
a world where a scientist
would have her strongly held
beliefs tested and retested.
I would also come to fear that
the institution I'd joined
and invested with my trust
was subject to the influence
of dark forces
outside the Bureau
and sometimes within,
forces threatened
by Mulder's work
and increasingly by mine.
Shortly after
sensing these threats,
I was abducted from my home
by unknown assailants
and returned without
a clear understanding why.
But intervening incidents
have led me to believe
that during my
short disappearance,
I was subjected to tests,
tests resulting in
a life-threatening disease,
its cure as mysterious
as the illness itself,
tests which I now suspect are
part of a larger conspiracy,
a conspiracy of men hiding
science for almost 60 years,
secrets kept from the American
people by a self-interested cabal
intent on the
consolidation of power
both at home and on
a perilously global scale.
But questions
remain unanswered
about their motives
and their final objectives,
when and where these men
(MARCHING) might play
out their dark plans,
and the significance
of a recent test result
of my personal genetic makeup
turning up DNA anomalies
that I can only classify
as alien.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Sorry I'm late.
The parking garage is locked
down for some reason.
You here, Mulder?
(ON VIDEO) Six weeks ago, we
went off the air due to threats
from outside forces
bent on controlling content
deemed dangerous
to their cause.
Today, we're back,
with facts threatening
these forces yet again.
The discovery of something
that's so shocking,
you'll want to sit down and
prepare yourself for the truth.
What may seem like science
fiction but is science fact,
(HEART POUNDING) the legitimate and
verifiable discovery of alien DNA
that's in virtually
every American citizen.
(PHONE RINGING) I know what
you're thinking right now...
Agent Mulder's phone.
MAN ON PHONE:
Who's this? Dana?
Yes. Who's this?
It's Tad O'Malley.
I was just watching your show.
You need to get over here.
Where exactly is "here"?
What happened here?
(SIGHS) I don't know
what happened.
What are you doing here
and where is Agent Mulder?
I don't know where he is.
You found it like this?
Door was open, unlocked.
We had arranged
an informal meeting.
A meeting about what?
About new facts surfacing.
I saw your report,
Mr. O'Malley,
and your
dangerous allegations.
Dangerous allegations, yes,
but not irresponsible ones.
Alien DNA lurking in
every American citizen.
I had my own DNA tested.
And what did you find?
We found anomalous DNA.
90% of everyone's genome is
anomalous DNA, Mr. O'Malley.
I have a doctor who says this is different.
And he's not a quack.
I'd like to be
the judge of that.
You found alien DNA yourself.
You found it in
Sveta six weeks ago,
just like we all
said you would.
And this has got
Mulder excited.
It should get anyone excited.
Who are you calling?
Well, first I'm calling
the police.
Still no word from him?
And he's not
picking up either.
You'd think he would've left a
note, maybe a voice message.
I'm afraid he
fears my judgment.
Fears your judgment on what?
On whether he's
crazy or not.
Then you do know something.
This man, Tad O'Malley,
has been making claims.
Claims about what?
That you and everyone you
know has a piece of DNA
in your genome put there
without your knowing it.
(SCOFFS) Put there by whom?
Well, that's
the question of the day.
This is an Internet lunatic.
You're not saying
you believe him?
Just hold on, Agent Einstein.
You're talking to a scientist.
AGENT EINSTEIN: Er, forgive
me, Assistant Director.
It may sound insensitive,
but the suggestion is pure
science fiction. (LAUGHS)
What I'm saying, Agent
Einstein, is that the facts,
as I understand them, cannot
be discounted outofhand.
No one has the right or the
ability to tamper with your DNA.
Unless we gave
them that ability.
Thank you for doing this,
Agent Einstein.
You didn't have to,
considering.
My prejudices are
only against pseudoscience.
If I can help to
clear up this nonsense
and find Agent Mulder,
I'm only happy to.
Can you help me?
Do you need
to sit down, sir?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Not sure of what?
What's happening to me.
Nurse, we need
some help here.
Dr. Scully?
I think this man
needs help.
As do so many
people today.
His left arm,
lateral deltoid.
Sir, can I see
your arm, please?
I don't know
how it got there.
Okay, you need to get
this man out of here,
get him to see
a doc immediately.
Can you do that,
Sandeep?
Yes, certainly.
Right away.
Can I direct them
in any way?
Just find out who he is and
what he's been exposed to.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(SIGHS) I'm not sure what
this is going to prove.
Well, it may prove nothing
or it may be negative.
I don't want to alarm you,
Agent Einstein,
but about six weeks ago,
I took my own blood,
and in sequencing my genome,
I discovered an anomaly.
What constitutes
an anomaly?
An aberration
in my sequence.
Something unexplainable
and, by definition, alien.
You can rest assured I don't
have alien DNA, Agent Scully,
if that's what
you're looking for.
Have you
sequenced your genome?
No. But has anyone?
MY Point precisely.
And why were you
even looking?
You know little of my
history, Agent Einstein.
And while we share
a faith in science,
I have come to
the understanding
that the science
that we were taught
takes us but a distance
towards the truth.
Yeah, but tampering
with our DNA?
I was given a smallpox
vaccine as a child,
as I'm sure
you were as well.
It was standard practice
in America at the time.
If you are suggesting
that there is
more in that shot
than a vaccine...
It's actually not that
far-fetched and within the realm
of accepted science.
Something entering the germ
line, something that would be
passed down hereditarily.
That would be an unprecedented
violation of the public trust.
And now you know
a bit more of the history
I was referring to.
For the purpose of what?
I don't know,
Agent Einstein.
And I don't know if
any of this is true.
But what I do know is that
the possibility exists,
and that is reason enough
to run these tests.
Hey. Been looking
for you.
A.D. Skinner asked me to come
down, help find Agent Mulder.
We know nothing, Agent Miller,
nothing more than this morning.
There's talk on the Internet.
What kind Of talk?
People are
freaking out about
reports on
The Tad O'Malley Show.
MR. O'MALLEY:
Now, I know this is
hard for people at
home to comprehend.
So what are we looking
at, Dr. Rubell,
the scale and scope?
A scale we've
never dreamed.
A scope that
quickly becomes global.
A massive contagion,
then?
Not one contagion, but a
variety of contagions.
If the flu doesn't kill you,
then something else will.
You're describing it
as a fast-moving
AIDS without the HIV.
Our immune
systems decimated
by the same tampering
to all our genomes.
(ON VIDEO)
Who Will be first hit?
The people we most depend on, the
police, health care workers.
Then people in
metropolitan areas.
Suddenly Tad O'Malley is the
singular voice of authority?
Is this at all plausible?
It's all too plausible,
and I think it's
already happening.
What have you
found out, Sandeep?
They're running tests now.
About the man,
who is he?
He's quite incoherent.
I think they've
determined he's military.
That man will die unless he's given
doses of intravenous doxycycline.
What do you suspect,
Dr. Scully?
Those lesions
are from anthrax.
Uh, someone's been
exposed to anthrax?
Willingly so,
in this case.
You better explain
this to me.
To me as well, Agent Scully,
because this is cause for alarm.
Soldiers deploying to Iraq
are given anthrax vaccines
to protect them in the event
of biological warfare.
But with compromised
immune systems,
it's the vaccines that are
attacking their systems.
Meaning we're
infecting them?
Thinking that
we're protecting them.
We don't know
that that's true.
Left arm is the site
of the injection.
That's where we saw the
lesions, Agent Einstein.
That's purely speculative.
Anthrax.
Why else would
there be an outbreak?
There were outbreaks
in 2001.
You don't understand.
Anthrax is the canary
in the coal mine.
It's a harbinger of
infections to come,
measles, mumps,
rubella, the flu.
We're all going
to be exposed.
This is happening now?
You are witnessing what may be the
advent of a global contagion.
You can't just say these things
when this is an isolated case.
Would you like
to wait and see?
Wouldn't you like to first wait and
see my test results, Agent Scully?
I don't think I need to
see your test results.
(AMBULANCE SIREN BLARING)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Mulder.
Pick up, please.
(ENGINE STARTING)
We're now getting reports
on law enforcement
dealing with soldiers
and military personnel
indicating symptoms
of exposure to anthrax,
a rolling first wave
of contagion set in motion
by our revelations of a
far-reaching conspiracy of men.
It's exact...
Spartanburg.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
This is just
the beginning.
You keep saying that,
ruling out all
other possibilities,
the possibility that they
were given a faulty vaccine.
The Department of Defense
was recently faulted
for giving
soldiers live vaccines.
That wouldn't cause this.
What do we do here
as doctors?
We ponder all
possible scenarios.
We don't have time
to ponder, Agent Einstein.
Well, I think
you're wrong.
I hope that I'm wrong.
I hope that there's
an explanation for this,
all of it, for Muldefls
disappearance, for everything.
But right now,
we are in deep trouble.
Consider what
you're saying.
Pathogens are
virtually everywhere.
Every cough, every sneeze, every
cut on the finger deadly.
That's not what I'm seeing
here, Agent Scully.
I am seeing one
class of people infected.
You're right.
You say they're
tampering with our DNA,
that they're able to shut
down our immune systems
by the addition of
something to our DNA?
Yes, but I don't know
how exactly.
Or how it's
being triggered.
I don't know
that either.
Or why it's
happening now.
No. It makes no sense.
Think about it.
Shutting down
the immune system
is a complex
biological process.
It would require something being
taken away from the genome,
not something
added to it.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
WOMAN ON PHONE:
Agent Scully? Dana?
Yes. Who is this?
I can explain
what's happening.
I'm sorry. Who is this?
Someone who was there for you.
There for me when?
When you also needed help.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Agent Scully.
Agent Reyes.
Monica.
(SIGHS) I wish this were
under better circumstances,
but I wish a lot of things
were different here today.
You have something
to tell me.
Something you need
to know.
I looked you up when I
went back to the FBI.
They said you'd
been gone for a decade,
that you left in a hurry.
I made certain choices.
You might not
approve or understand,
but they made sense
to me at the time.
Special Agent Monica Reyes.
Agent Reyes, someone would
like to speak with you.
Do not be alarmed
by his appearance.
He's expected to
make a full recovery.
He'd been near death,
so badly burned
they were having to
reconstruct his entire face.
Why would he summon you?
He had an offer to make.
Agent Reyes, please come in.
I think you know who I am.
I thought that
you were dead.
They haven't killed me yet,
as hard as they may try.
Is it hard
to look at me?
Considering what
I know about you,
the things you've done, the
people you've done them to...
I'm not an evil man, Monica.
And you're a liar, as well.
What did he want, Monica?
To make a deal with me,
one that left me
very little choice.
You changed
your whole life.
You have to
understand why.
How badly I want a cigarette.
Well, I can't help you
with that.
But you can
help me, Monica.
And for that,
I'd spare your life.
It's a federal crime to
threaten an FBI agent, sir.
You're hardly in a position
to threaten anyone.
You see a man lying here,
a seemingly weak man,
but I'm the most powerful man
in the world.
You must have a sense
of what's happening,
heard the reports.
How did he
threaten you, Monica?
With the ultimate weapon,
the ability to
depopulate the planet,
to kill everyone
but the chosen.
By tampering
with their DNA?
Science acquired in the '50s,
given to them by an alien race.
Alien DNA mixed
with our DNA.
It's not quite so simple.
That's excellent.
Just be quick. We don't
have a lot of time.
Merci.
Ahh. Thank you, Monica.
You're slowly
killing yourself
while you hold
the world hostage.
The world will go on.
Just in my image
instead of God's.
You think you
can play God?
Oh. Not God, certainly.
They won't know
what hit them.
That their fates
were sealed since birth.
They were simply puppets.
You will die
a lonely old man.
Oh. I don't think so, Monica.
Now that I have you
to light my smokes.
Why did you call me,
Monica?
To tell me what
a coward you are?
To tell you
you're protected.
What are you talking about?
Your abduction.
The tests. Your DNA, Dana.
You're safe.
You're one of
the chosen elite.
They tampered
with my DNA.
We are both
protected, Dana.
That's what he
was offering me.
But what about
everybody else?
Everyone else
is happening.
It's been in
motion since 2012.
Well, then we have
to stop it.
The science
is complicated.
And Mulder...
Where's Mulder?
He loves Mulder.
He sent a man to him
to offer Mulder a deal.
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GAGS)
Who sent you?
You sent for me.
I'm here.
This is so
unnecessary, Fox.
I don't come
when you call.
I've controlled you since
before you knew I existed.
So who's in control now?
The world
crumbling around us.
You set this in motion.
Now you're gonna
put a stop to it.
It's far too
late for that, Fox.
Too late for your
heroics or mine.
I don't believe you.
You don't want to believe.
You may not believe this,
but I really want
to save your life.
I don't make
deals with you.
So you can see
Scully again.
You harm her in any way...
(GROANS)
(LAUGHS) Every man
has his weakness.
Mine was always
just cigarettes.
You think it's power,
what you're doing,
but it's not.
It's sickness.
It's sickness not doing it.
Spoken like
a true psychopath.
I didn't set out to
destroy the world, Mulder.
People did.
You can't
justify your actions.
We have just had the hottest
year on record on planet Earth.
I didn't do that.
I'm not responsible for
the 40% loss of bird life
or the decimation
of the megafauna.
So just murder
all the people?
Aliens predicted all this.
They saw it
happening to themselves.
And you kept it
a secret.
Look at world
history, Fox.
Neither you nor I could save
mankind from self-extermination.
So you plotted
your endgame.
I just changed
the timetable.
Everyone still
dies in the end.
How's it feel now?
What good would it do?
You'll be dead
yourself within a week.
What are you offering?
A seat at the big table.
It would be
a shame without you.
I couldn't look at
myself in the mirror.
Let alone you.
We could start
the world anew, Fox.
You, me,
your beloved Scully.
Not a rat's chance
in hell!
You speak to me of hell?
(CHUCKLES)
When you look to be the one
who's hell-bound.
You appear a little feverish.
The plague?
Avian flu?
A nasty strain
of rhinovirus?
It's not too late, Fox.
MR. O'MALLEY: We have breaking
news of hospitals being overrun
and temporary
shelters filling up,
but the reality is all too clear.
It is a collapse.
The mainstream media
failing to cover the story,
failing to see
the writing on the wall,
as anthrax outbreaks
give way to an epidemic
of flu and bacterial diseases.
Now, if you see graffiti like
this in your neighborhood,
you can suspect
your DNA is being targeted
by a release of aluminum
into the atmosphere
through chemtrails,
a systematic
spreading of a substance
that triggers
a genetic response.
Cases in New York, California,
across the country,
while right here in Washington,
immunity to common germs
is breaking down and
flooding our city hospitals.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Dr. Scully, we are overwhelmed here.
We don't know what to do.
Yes, I can see that.
I'm trying to
figure it out.
Are we all just
gonna get sick?
I don't know,
Sandeep.
But right now, I need
to find Agent Einstein.
Yes, I'm gonna call
them next.
Agent Einstein, I was afraid
you left the hospital.
No, I'd be afraid to leave. It's
gone from bad to worse out there.
There's nothing to be done
for those people,
not yet anyway. Center
for Disease Control
confirms massive contagions.
They're at a loss
to contain them.
I'm gonna call
the W.H.O. next.
I need your help,
right here.
What can we
possibly do?
We need to act quickly.
You were right
about that.
Well, I was wrong
about the science.
I was wrong about what's causing it.
Dead wrong, in fact.
But it's clearly
a widespread failure
of our immune systems.
Through gene tampering.
What you're calling
alien DNA.
That's where
I was mistaken.
Alien DNA is what I have.
And alien DNA is
all that can save us.
But why is
everyone sick?
What they have, what you have,
what I have to presume
the entire population has is
something entirely different.
It's in the germ
line already.
It's in sperm,
it's in eggs.
It's a virus
within a virus
that was put there through
the smallpox vaccine.
It's what these men are
calling the Spartan Virus.
Where are you
getting this?
From a trusted friend who says that
it's not too late to change it.
Tell me what
I've got to do.
I'm gonna take a swab.
But what are we
looking to do?
To amplify my DNA.
Using alien DNA to
defeat the Spartan Virus
by creating
a vaccine against it.
You're gonna do a PCR,
using primers
from my sequence.
Okay, that shouldn't takelong.
Good, because
we don't have long.
This is no time
for pride, Fox.
I don't...
I don't want your help.
The ultimate irony.
The defeat of
the big-brained beasts
by the tiniest
unthinking microbes.
All thanks to
the Spartan Virus.
Musings of a madman.
You don't give up,
do you?
You'll be sorry
when I'm gone.
I'll miss you dearly.
You've made my life
truly worth living.
I'm on the king's throne.
Feels soft.
(PANTING)
Just like the king.
And yet,
I once cheated death.
(LAUGHS)
I wish Scully was here,
see what
a monster you've become.
I'm all she'll have left.
We'll have to move quickly
to extract more of my DNA.
AGENT EINSTEIN: First, we'll
have to see if it's there.
SCULLY:
It will be there.
It'll be on a band
next to the marker.
Thank you.
SCULLY: I don't believe this.
I don't believe this.
AGENT EINSTEIN:
There's nothing.
There's no alien DNA.
I saw it when I
sequenced my genome.
It was near the centromere
on chromosome 17.
It was there.
SANDEEP:
Excuse me, Dr. Scully.
The doctors are
all getting sick.
If there is
anything you can do.
We are getting our
first reports of deaths.
Soldiers from
anthrax and the elderly,
all succumbing to infections
because of immune systems
that have been
depleted or disappeared.
Launched by someone bent on a
biological attack on America.
New reports that
microwave radiation
is also being
used as a trigger.
And reports this may also be
global in scope.
Reports in from Europe.
Our advice is
to stay indoors.
My crew here
is suffering.
But we will attempt
to stay on
as long as there is still
hope of a turnaround.
(PEOPLE COUGHING)
(GROANING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
As if we're not
already in the dark.
We have to figure
this out.
What's wrong
with the science?
Okay.
The Spartan Virus removes
the adenosine deaminase gene
from your DNA.
Remove the ADA gene,
and your immune system
will simply vanish.
Yeah, but I'm not
getting sick.
It's only a matter of time.
Without alien DNA,
you don't stand a chance
against the Spartan Virus.
Okay. So how does it work?
How does the virus
remove the ADA gene?
A process
called CRISPR-Cas...
CRISPR-Cas9.
RNA and a protein cutting
genes at exact locations.
Exactly.
But in this
instance used as a weapon.
So how does your
alien DNA protect you
from this weapon?
I don't know.
The alien DNA must code for something
that targets the Cas9 protein.
It must somehow
deactivate the weapon.
But we should have
seen it in the gel.
Why didn't we see it?
They must have known that
someone would...
Would try to find it.
That someone would
attempt to find a cure.
But your DNA is different.
Yes.
What are you thinking,
Agent Einstein?
That this was
our mistake.
What was?
Our sample
was too small.
DISTORTED VOICE: Agent Mulder.
Agent Mulder.
Agent...
I'm getting you
out of here.
(COUGHING)
Save yourself,
Agent Miller.
No, I'm not just gonna let you die.
Come on.
There's nothing
you can do.
anyone can do for him.
Nothing to be done
for anyone.
Maybe nothing here, but
we're not staying here.
We're leaving.
And no one
is gonna stop us.
You think you'll get far?
You have no idea
how well we planned.
Come on. Let's go.
We need to do the PCR using a
larger extract of your cells.
Because my DNA
is different.
Because I have
extra nucleotides.
And we'll get
an amplification.
And this time,
I'm sure we'll see it.
(PANTING)
You're not
feeling well.
I'm just a
little feverish.
I'm not gonna
make it.
Well, I'm not giving up.
Save yourself,
Miller.
He's got the cure.
Ask him for it.
Why didn't you ask him?
'Cause that's
exactly what he wants.
Who the hell
are you anyway?
Before he dies,
tell him good-bye for me.
There it is.
Huh.
SCULLY:
There it is.
That's alien DNA
we're looking at.
You'll have
to centrifuge it.
Think I need
to lie down.
We're gonna cure you,
Agent Einstein.
We're gonna have a cure
here within a few hours.
Don't give up on me.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
SCULLY ON PHONE: Agent
Miller, where are you?
Driving north
with Mulder.
And what's
his condition?
He's not doing
so well.
And what's your condition,
Agent Miller?
Yeah, we could use
a couple doctors.
Help is on its way,
I promise.
Okay, we're gonna
keep driving,
but there's been
a run on gasoline.
We may just run
out of road here.
Keep your phone charged.
I'll come and
find you wherever you are.
It's okay,
stay right there.
Stay right there.
You're gonna
need my help.
Yes, lam, Agent Einstein.
I'm gonna need your
help getting these IVs
into all
the other doctors here.
They'll be able to make more of
this and help the suffering.
If this actually works...
It's not gonna fail.
“IhenlWlhave
alien DNA.
We should all
hope to have it.
It's the only hope
we have.
MR. O'MALLEY: Reports are
hard to come by now.
Lines of communication
are being cut,
as systems and infrastructure
are falling and failing
with no one to
man or operate them.
It would now appear
we go out
with a whimper,
a frightful,
deafening silence.
(HORNS HONKING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(GASPS)
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
Please, everybody,
get to the hospital!
Get to the hospital! Help
is on its way, I promise.
Just get to
the hospital.
I've just gotten
a text from a doctor,
saying now there is
a ray of light.
A vaccine that
could be a miracle.
Don't give up.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HORN BLARING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(HORNS BLARING)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
All I see are cars.
I don't know how
I'm gonna find you.
(SIGHS) I'm gonna get
out of the car,
stand in the road,
all right?
(GROANS)
I'm gonna get out, too.
I'm getting out.
I'm moving in your direction.
Yeah, I think
I see you. Just...
Just keep
walking straight.
Okay.
Where is he?
Mulder. I'm here.
He saved your life.
Old Smokey.
I suppose I should thank him.
We're gonna save your life.
Agent Miller
is also in trouble.
(COUGHS)
I'll take care
of Agent Miller.
But right now, we're gonna
get an IV into you, okay?
Okay.
He's worse off
than I thought.
Can you do
anything for him?
What I can do
might not help.
He needs stem
cells in him right now.
Stem cells from who?
We have a child together.
That child will be protected by
his inheritance and my alien DNA.
Then we have
to get to him.
I don't know where he is.
(WHIRRING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)