(MEN SHOUTING)
You people were
told this was coming.
This is the first phase
in a relocation project
that will see you transferred
to the old Franklin Hospital
in Bucks County!
Any personal items
collected tonight
by the U.S. Department of
Housing and Urban Development
can be retrieved
(WOMAN SOBS)
at our field office at 1804
South Walnut Street.
Which is where I'll be.
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
Hey, give me a ride
back to the field office.
(SLURP5)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Your street is next!
Tomorrow morning!
You've been warned.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
(RUMBLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
MAN: Hey! Hey, come on!
(RATTLING)
(BRAKES HISSING)
(TRUCK ENGINE IDLING)
Landry. Cutler.
You still down there?
Everything okay?
Any problems? (SNIFFS)
(GAGS)
(couemwe)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Oh!
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(CLANGING IN DISTANCE)
Somebody out there?
(CLANG)
(PANTING)
(DIALING)
This is Joseph Cutler.
I'm at 1809 South Walnut.
There's an intruder.
OPERATOR". Sir, we're notifying the police.
Are you in danger?
(PANTING)
Hello?
Sir, tell us
what's happening.
Hello?
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Sir, are you there?
(FLIES BUZZING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
I'm Special Agent Dana Scully, and
this is Special Agent Fox Mulder.
Detective?
How you doing?
I'm Aaron Dross.
I called the Bureau.
They said that you two have
experience with these, um...
Spooky cases.
Well, I don't want to be
confrontational here, but...
It wouldn't be Philadelphia
without a certain degree
of confrontation, right?
Look, all I'm saying is just
because I called for a hand
doesn't mean I'm looking to
pass off this investigation
to you.
I'm sure I don't have to
point out to you, Detective,
that the FBI has
jurisdiction over
the murder of
a federal employee.
Have you tried
polyvinyl siloxane
to try to lift the print?
It's not that I can't
lift a print, it's just...
There's no prints
to lift.
A footprint is here,
but there are no ridges.
Well, it looks like this person
was born without footprints.
Which is impossible,
by the way.
Where was
the victim found?
He's still here.
He's there.
And, uh, his head
is in a trash can here.
Not even in
the proper recycling bin.
Both arms
are gone, too.
Must have been
a sword or machete.
SCULLY: Hmm.
The supraspinatus
and the deltoideus
appear to be shredded
from the torso, not severed,
as do the other
points of separation.
So what are you telling me,
that he was pulled apart?
SCULLYI Well, I don't think
that would be
possible for a...
For a single
human being.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
You know, the homeless
out there,
they hate this guy,
this Cutler.
(VIBRATING)
See him as a reason for
them having to relocate
out to the old
Franklin Hospital.
When a medieval prisoner
was drawn
and quartered,
it took four horses
charging off
in four directions
at full speed
to tear him apart.
(RINGING AND BUZZING)
Bill, I'm at a crime scene.
ls everything okay?
Are you still
in Germany?
Okay.
Scully?
That was, uh...
That was my brother.
He just...
The EMTs found
his phone number.
My mom's just had
a heart attack.
She's in ICU in D.C.
You go.
Go.
Yeah.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
MULDER: Here are the four
mounted security cameras.
There's the first one
knocked out of position.
Then the second one.
And the third.
And I saw that
Cutler's was knocked out.
But Cutler's eye-line is
trained above the door,
about Tim Duncan height.
We can eliminate any 76ers, 'cause
those guys can't find the rim.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Oh.
Look at that.
The billboard
outside Cutler's office.
At the time of the murder, there's
no artwork on it or graffiti.
That street art
was put up this morning.
After Cutler's murder.
Maybe the artist
that put it up there
is saying something
or saw something.
I'm gonna
go see if it's signed
or if anybody
knows who made it.
Yeah.
(SHOE SQUEAKS)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
(AIR PUMPING RHYTHMICALLY)
(SOFTLY) Mom.
Are you related
to Margaret?
Yes, I'm her daughter.
I'm Dana Scully.
She regained consciousness
for a few moments.
She repeatedly asked for
someone named Charlie.
Charlie's my brother,
heryoungestson.
They're estranged.
Oh, I thought
you'd want to know.
She didn't ask for me or Bill?
Or her grandchildren?
Just Charlie.
Hi, Mom.
It's me, Dana.
I'm here.
I've been where you are.
I know that
Ahab is there.
And Melissa.
But, Mom,
I'm here.
Bill Jr.'s here.
And William.
William's here.
And Charlie is here.
(SNIFFLES)
Please, Mom,
don't go home yet.
I need you.
(INDISTINCT POLICE
RADIO CHATTER)
Hey, Officer?
Mmm-hmm.
I'm gonna need access to
the roof of that building.
OFFICER: Yes, sir.
All right?
WOMAN: Landry, I'm not
finished with you!
LANDRY: Look, look, this street
gets oleaned out tomorrow morning.
Not after
I get an injunction.
This street
is a crime scene.
LANDRY: Are you blaming these
poor people for Joseph's murder?
WOMAN: Doesn't his murder
convince you
how much these people hate
what you're doing to them?
Are you threatening me?
I've been threatening you
for six months.
Well, stop.
Special Agent Mulder
with the FBI.
And who are these
two fine representatives
of the City of Brotherly Love?
Hmm.
Daryl Landry. I've been
working with Joseph Cutler.
We've been
redeveloping this area.
Mmm-hmm. And you are? And why do you
think someone down here killed him?
Nancy Huff.
I'm the president of the Central
Bucks County school board.
And this douche bag
and Cutler are moving...
Oh. You guys married? No?
To him?
No.
"Douche bag."
I thought maybe...
Yeah, him and Cutler
are moving
these poor homeless
out of this area
in order to build a 10-story
apartment building
to kick-start gentrification.
The old
Franklin State Hospital
is in her district,
just sitting there empty.
We're taking these poor people out
of the downtown to that facility,
away from the drug bazaar, the
rats, the urine in the streets.
I want these people to be safe and
comfortable as much as anyone.
I come down here every Thanksgiving
and serve turkey dinners.
Oh. But?
But the Franklin Hospital is just two
blocks from Pennsbury High School.
If one of these
downtown people
killed Cutler,
would you want that person
moved near your children?
Okay, okay, okay, I hear
you speaking for them,
but really you're
speaking for yourself.
And I hear you
speaking for them,
but really speaking
for yourself.
What I don't hear is
who speaks for them.
The Band-Aid Nose Man.
"Band-Aid Nose Man"?
What is that? That's... Name of the artist?
Who is that?
You know where
I can find him?
(MONITOR BEEPING)
(AIR PUMPING RHYTHMICALLY)
I don't know if my being here
will help bring you back.
But I'm here.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Hey, Bill.
What time is it
where you are?
What time is your
flight from Frankfurt?
(RAPID BEEPING IN DISTANCE)
(MONITOR FLATLINING)
SCULLY'. Oh.
I think you should get
here as soon as you can.
Well, I can't...
How am I to know that?
I won't answer as to whether she's
going to die before you get here.
Bill, yes,
I'm a doctor,
but I'm also her daughter.
Well, we'll keep her
on life support.
That's... That's what
she wanted.
Yes. Mom and I talked about it
after my experience in a coma.
She said that
she wanted us to do
everything that we could
to keep her alive.
Her advance directive is on
the Living Will Registry.
Yes.
(SIGHS)
MULDER'. Clean'?
So clean.
There's nothing here.
You can confirm that there's no
presence of any pathogenic agents?
No, Mulder.
I mean, there's nothing.
Something's there.
Some material appears apparent,
but it's also not there.
I used backscattered
electron imaging
to separate and identify
inorganic particles
from organic materials,
and I found neither.
There's no organic material
on this Band-Aid,
but there's no inorganic
material either.
It's not alive.
It's not dead.
Nurse?
Is it wise to administer
a hypertonic saline
to a cardiac arrest patient?
Agent Scully,
we had to confirm
your mother's
advance directive,
and it indicates that
she not be resuscitated
if unconscious or requires
artificial respiration.
She amended it
lastyean
It's signed and witnessed
by two retired
naval officers.
(LABORED BREATHING)
Let's see what
we got here.
Whew!
This one's so big.
Yeah.
This is new territory.
It's not like him.
We should go to
Sotheby's on this.
Never knew you could make so
muoh money off the homeless.
(LAUGHS)
I'll call our
usual collectors.
Put that away.
Okay.
I got it.
Let's go, buddy.
All right.
(SIGHS)
(DIALING)
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
Hey.
You input that new guy's
number we met from last week?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(LAUGHS)
The waitress
from the bar?
(SINGSONGY)
She's got a friend.
What are you doing?
Why'd you turn it
around, man?
The slats will
mess up the paint.
(FLIES BUZZING)
Dude, what are
you doing?
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(DOORS CREAKS)
(GARBAGE TRUCK CLATTERING)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
We have to extubate her.
It's not necessarily
termination,
but we not only have to
honor the law, Dana,
we also have to respect
your mother's wishes.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(BEEP S)
Yeah.
MULDER: I'm here.
LANDRYI All right!
Time to go
to your new home.
Everyone on the bus.
NANCY: Excuse me.
This is an injunction against
this operation, Landry.
If any of these buses show
up at Franklin Hospital,
they'll be turned away
by Bucks County sheriffs.
MULDER: There was some
artwork displayed
outside Cutler's office
after the murder.
It was of a figure
the people on the street
believes defends them.
The street artist that made the
artwork goes by the name "Trashman."
No one knows
his real name.
Stays anonymous.
No one's ever seen him.
Isuspect the subject may be
a mission-oriented killer
who believes
he's helping the homeless
by eliminating those involved
with the relocation.
And I would stay,
but I suspect the subject
will kill again.
She asked for Charlie
before she fell
into the coma.
Your brother?
Yeah.
Just him.
Not Bill or me or...
I don't even know
where he is.
He hasn't bothered with her
or with us for years.
Why would she do that?
And why would she
change her living will
without talking to me?
And what's this?
I mean...
I've never
seen her wear it.
The date has
no significance.
It's not any of
our birthdays.
It's not dad's death
or Melissa's.
I mean, what is it
about that quarter
that she would frame it to
put it around her neck?
DOCTOR:
Are you ready to extubate?
NURSE: Yes, doctor.
DOCTOR: You have a stent on hand?
NURSE: Removing the tube.
On her next exhale.
MALE DOCTOR: Ready?
I don't care about the big
questions right now, Mulder.
I just want one more chance to
ask my mom a few little ones.
(sesame)
(ON CAR STEREO)
When you're alone
And life is making
you lonely
You can always go
Downtown
When you've got worries
all the noise and the hurry
Seems to help, I know
Downtown...
(CAR STEREO TURNS OFF)
MAN: Hey, honey, letting you
know I checked in at the hotel.
I'll call you on
the way to the meeting.
Kids are good. They're staying
at Ed and Melinda's. Love you.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WHIRRING)
(VIBRATING)
(BEEP S)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
When you're alone
And life is making
you lonely
You can always go
Downtown
When you've got worries
all the noise and the hurry
Seems to help, I know
Downtown
Just listen to the music
of the traffic in the city
Linger on the sidewalk where
the neon signs are pretty
How can you lose
The lights are
much brighter there
You can forget
all your troubles
Forget all your cares
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
So go downtown
Things will be great
when you're downtown
No finer place, for sure
Downtown
You're gonna be
all right now
(PANTING)
Downtown
Downtown, downtown
And you may find somebody kind
to help and understand you
Someone who is just like you
And needs a gentle hand
to guide them along
So maybe I'll see you there
(WHIRRING)
We can forget
all our troubles
Forget all our cares
so go downtown
Things will be great
when you're downtown
Everything's waiting for you
Downtown
Downtown, downtown
Downtown...
Back in the day,
did we ever come across
the ability to just
wish someone back to life?
I invented it.
When you were
in the hospital,
like this.
You're a dark
wizard, Mulder.
What else is new?
(LAUGHS)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Hello?
Charlie. Did Bill call you?
Yeah. Um...
Mom asked for you.
Charlie, can you just
say something to her, please?
Just anything.
I don't know.
Just“
Do what I can't do.
Bring her back to us.
Okay.
I'll put it
on speakerphone.
(PHONE BEEPS)
I've got Charlie here.
He's on the phone.
I know you can hear him.
(OVER PHONE)
Mom? It's me. It's Charlie.
I heard you were
asking for me,
so here I am, for once.
What do you
want to know?
What's the big mystery?
Anything? Any reaction?
Well, her pulse rate quickened,
but I didn't see her move.
Mom?
She just opened
her eyes.
Do you know
where you are?
Do you know your name?
My son
is named William, too.
Mom? Mom. Mom.
Mom, it's Dana.
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Mom, I'm here. I'm here.
(MONITOR FLATLINING)
Come back to us.
Mom? Mom?
CHARLIE: Dana? Dana?
Mom.
CHARLIE: What's going on?
(SOBS)
(WHEELS CLATTERING)
No. You get that
out of here!
Get that out of here!
MULDER: Scully, Scully.
ScuHy,no. Margaret's an organ donor.
And they need her right away.
You got to let her go.
(sesame)
Her last words to us
were about our child.
Her grandchild.
That we gave away.
Why did she say that?
Why did she have
to say that?
(SOBS)
(SNIFFLES) Mulder, let's
drive to Philadelphia.
I need to work.
No. No, no, no.
Yes. Right now.
No,lgetH, Scully, I do.
But not right now.
Mulder, right now.
I need to work
right now.
MAN: I broke down the paint
samples you chipped away
from the Trashman's
signature and analyzed it
with vibrational
spectography.
It defines binders, pigments and
additives that are used in spray paint.
The binder present
in this breakdown
was patented by
a brand called Cannonz
and used only in their
high-end spray paints.
Product locator indicates
that there's only one store
in Central Philadelphia
that carries it.
(WHISTLES)
Damn.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Federal agents!
(GRUNTING)
We're looking
for the Trashman.
Hey, just letting
you know, guys,
from here on down,
there's no light.
Power's out.
(GRUNTS)
What? I wasn't gonna
shoot the kid.
And I don't
do stairs anymore.
Mulder, back in the day, I used to
do stairs and in three-inch heels.
"Back in the day."
Scully,
"back in the day" is now.
(DOOR OPENS)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(RAT SQUEAKING)
(THUD)
What the hell?
Federal agents!
Open up!
If you're in danger,
we're here to help.
MAN: lam in danger!
But go away.
Put the guns down!
They don't work on them!
Put them away!
They don't work!
I tried.
I've tried to shoot them.
You the Trashman?
Turn down the light, man.
Turn down the light.
If they don't see me and I don't
see them, they can't hurt me.
The people on the streets,
the homeless, street people,
they ain't got
no voice, right?
They get treated
like trash.
I mean, actual trash.
It's like this.
You throw your grande cup
or your pop bottle
in the right trash can
under the sink,
recyclables here,
trash there,
you tie it in a bag,
you take it outside,
you put it in
the right dumpsters.
Pat yourself on the head.
You're a good person, yeah?
You did the right thing,
you fought global warming,
you love all
the little animals.
Well, Friday come,
Wednesday maybe,
garbageman takes
the trash away.
It's not your
problem anymore.
Magic!
But it is your problem, because
it piles up inthelandfifl.
And the plastics leak toxins
into the water and the sky.
But if you don't see a problem,
there's no problem, right?
People treat
people like trash.
So, what, you took care
of the problem?
I did my part.
By killing Joseph Cutler and Nancy
Huff and those two art thieves?
Nah, I was just trying to
give those people a voice
the only way I know how,
through art.
Not violence.
Something I can put around town,
so they wouldn't be forgotten.
A stencil that looked over
the Bad Suit Building Man,
looked down on the
Lawn Gnome Suburban Lady.
Well, Why'd you put up
the art after the fact?
The morning
of Cutler's murder?
I didn't. That wasn't me.
I only thought him up.
You know?
Those people who got
killed, that was only him.
"Him"? Who is him?
You saw those
things in the hall.
Yeah.
I made them.
I didn't mean to,
but I made 'em.
They'll go away, eventually.
They're fading.
But the Band-Aid
Nose Man...
He's different.
Tibetan Buddhists
would call him a Tulpa.
A thought form
using mind and energy to will
consciousness into existence.
Tulpa is a 1929 Theosophist mistranslation
of the Tibetan word "tulku, "
meaning
"a manifestation body."
There is no idea
in Tibetan Buddhism
of a thought form
or thought as form.
And a realized tulku
would never harm anyone,
let alone kill.
Okay. But I'm telling you.
I spend a lot
of energy in my art.
I meditated on it.
I willed it.
What I wanted him
to look like,
what I wanted him to be,
and why I wanted him.
(SCREAMING)
(BABY CRYING)
(GASPING)
Oh!
TRASHMAN:
I didn't bring him here.
He came to me.
(BABY CRYING)
But in the end, he told
me what he wanted to be.
All we do is
hold the pencil.
All we do
is hold the clay.
I think there must be spirits and
souls floating all around us.
And if you think real hard
or you want them so bad,
they come to you.
(BABY CRYING)
What are you
gonna call him?
William.
TRASHMAN: And then they become
alive with a life of their own.
My son
is named William, too.
(SOBS) Our son, Mulder.
I gave him up.
TRASHMANI This...
This is what came
to me in my dreams.
From some
other place, yeah?
But now it's alive
and it's out there.
Down to the Band-Aid I used
to hold the clay in place.
Who would copy this?
And did you smell it?
It smells like
nothing on this earth.
It has its own life.
Does what it wants.
I just wanted
to scare 'em,
scare anyone that took dignity
away from the homeless.
That's where the violent
idea popped in my head.
It was just an emotion
that ran through my head.
An idea is dangerous,
even a small one.
But now he uses
that violent idea.
He thinks that is what
he is supposed to do.
You are responsible.
If you made the problem,
if it was your idea,
then you're responsible.
You put it out of sight, so that
it wouldn't be your problem.
But you're just as bad as
the people that you hate.
If what you believe
is possible,
the last person involved in the
relocation would be Landry.
He got
the injunction lifted.
They're moving people out
to Franklin Hospital tonight.
All right, all right.
I'm paying a lot of good money
for all this. Let's get going.
Time to go home.
We're looking
for Daryl Landry.
Mr. Landry, this is Agent Mulder.
I need you to call me back.
SCULLY: Yeah.
It's urgent.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
MAN: I want my dog.
I said it.
I didn't want to be here if they
wouldn't let me have my dog.
Sir, go to your room.
The dogs have been
sent to the shelter.
I'm sure
you can find it there.
WOMAN: Mr. Landry, sir?
(COUGHS)
(DOORS CLOSING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(GROANS)
(EXHALES)
(FLIES CONTINUE BUZZING)
Somebody down there?
(COUGHS)
This area is off limits!
(GROANS)
Come back here
to the rooms.
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
(GRUNTS)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(GROANS)
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(GASPING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(GASPS)
(SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(GASPS)
There's one way
out of this room.
He just screamed
seconds ago.
How did we not see whoever did
this to him leave the room?
(SEAGULL CAWING)
I know now why Mom
asked for Charlie,
eventhough
he was out of her life.
She wanted to know before
she left that he'd be okay.
She gave birth to him.
She made him.
He's her responsibility.
And that's why she said
what she said to us.
She wanted to make sure
that we'd be responsible
to know that
William's okay.
Even though
we cam see 'rum.
I know that
as parents,
we made a difficult
sacrifice to keep him safe.
That it was for his own good
to put him up foradopfion.
But I can't help
but think of him, Fox.
I can't help it.
I believe that you will find
all of your answers.
You will find the answers
to the biggest mysteries,
and I will be there
when you do.
But my mysteries,
lWlnever
have answered.
I won't know
if he thinks of me, too,
or if he's ever been afraid
and wished that I was there.
Does he doubt himself
because we left him?
What questions
does he have of me?
The same that I have
with this quarter?
And I want to believe...
(SNIFFLES)
I need to believe
that we didn't
treat him like trash.