MULDER: My name is Fox Mulder.
Since my childhood,
I have been obsessed
by a controversial
global phenomenon.
Since my sister disappeared
when I was 12 years old,
in what I believe
was an alien abduction.
My obsession
took me to the FBI,
where I investigated
paranormal science cases
through the auspices of a unit
known as the X-Files.
Through this unit,
I could continue my work
on the alien phenomenon,
and the search
for my missing sister.
In 1993, the FBI
sought to impugn my work,
bringing in a scientist and
medical doctor to debunk it,
which only deepened
my obsession
for the better part
of a decade,
during which time that agent,
Dana Scully,
had her own faith tested.
In 2002, in a change
of direction and policy,
the FBI closed the X-Files,
and our investigation ceased.
But my personal obsession
did not.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
There are 10,000 sightings
each year
in North America alone,
and so it's been
since the dawn of time,
Stone Age and
even biblical references
into our modern age.
In 1947, Kenneth Arnold saw
nine unidentified craft
out the window
of his small plane,
followed by the historic crash
at Roswell
and its legendary cover-up.
In 1957, UFOs were spotted
over our nation's capital.
The Pentagon
held press briefings.
Multiple witnesses in 1967
at Malmstrom Air Force Base in
Montana see fighters scramble
but easily outrun by UFOs
that climb upwards
of 200,000 feet,
twice the service ceiling of
our highest-flying spy planes.
Dr. Edgar Mitchell,
the sixth man
to walk on the Moon,
cites secret studies
on extraterrestrial materials
and bodies.
Secretary of State,
Cyrus Vance,
and future president,
Gerald R. Ford,
validate the UFO phenomenon in
official government memoranda.
(SONIC BOOM)
But now people only laugh, and
only Roswell is remembered.
But we must ask ourselves,
are they really a hoax?
Are we truly alone?
Or are we being lied to?
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Can I ask how much longer?
Two shakes
of a lamb's tail, Doc.
Step quick.
NURSE: Excuse me.
Dr. Scully?
Yes.
You have a phone call.
I'm just heading
into surgery.
That's what
I told him, but...
But he said it was important.
Who is it?
He says his name
is Walter Skinner,
Assistant Director, FBI.
JIMMY KIMMEL ON TV:
If! was the president,
the moment I was inaugurated,
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
my hand would still be hot
from touching the Bible,
and I would immediately race
to, wherever they hold...
Have the files
about Area 51 and UFOs,
and I'd go through everything
to find out what happened.
The aliens won't let it happen.
(LAUGHTER)
My life's become
a punch line.
What's happening
out there, Scully?
A.D. Skinner's
looking for you.
Why doesn't he just call me?
He doesn't know
how to reach you, Mulder.
I barely know how myself.
What does he want, Scully?
He wants to know
if you've been watching
someone called
Tad O'Malley on the Net.
Apparently, he's reached out
to us from the FBI.
Hold on.
I'm bringing him up.
It comes down to this.
It's a mainstream
liberal media
lying to you
about life, liberty
and your God-given right
to bear firearms.
Why would I watch
this jackass, Scully?
9/11 was a false
flag operation.
It was a warm-up
to World War Ill.
Now, hear me on this.
It's all part
of a conspiracy
dating back to
the UFO crash at Roswell...
I thought you were done
with UFOs.
The stranglehold they put
on your very existence,
I believe is how you put it.
I'm just the messenger,
Mulder.
Apparently, this guy
is desperate to meet.
Tell Skinner to set it up.
Seriously?
And don't pretend
I'm going alone.
Uber?
Hitchhiked.
Relax, Scully. I'm kidding.
I just worry
about you, Mulder.
Not to worry, Doc. I'm
taking good care of myself.
It's good for you to get out
of that little house
every once in a while.
It certainly was good
for you.
I'm always happy to see you.
And I'm always happy
to find a reason.
Fox Mulder?
Yes.
Tad O'Malley.
And you must be
former agent Dana Scully.
Yes. That's quite
an entrance you make there.
She's shot men
with less provocation.
Funny. I heard
you were funny.
Join me for a little ride?
I'd be happy to talk to you,
Mr. O'Malley,
but right here is fine.
Allow me my small precautions.
Low-flying aircraft often employ
what they call "dirtboxes"
to record conversations
that I prefer private.
Aircraft employed by whom?
I'm afraid I can
only speculate.
Shall we?
Because...
Why not?
None for me, thanks.
Scully?
I take it
you have enemies.
Well, not always
of my choosing, Dana.
(MULDER CLICKING
WINDOW BUTTON)
Air's getting
a little hot in here.
Oh, I'm sorry,
those don't roll down.
I had the vehicle
bulletproofed.
'Cause you never know
when a gun-toting liberal
might go Hinckley.
You'll have to excuse him.
How can we help you,
Mr. O'Malley?
I'm not some
Johnny-come-lately
to the UFO phenomenon,
Mr. Mulder.
Like yourself,
I'm a true believer.
No, I only want to believe.
Actual proof has been
strangely hard to come by.
You ran the X-Files.
You were the X-Files.
You all but wrote the book.
I'm afraid
that book is closed.
As are the X-Files.
For better or worse, we've
moved on with our lives.
Yes, we have.
For better or for worse.
Well, that's beside the point.
What is the point,
Mr. O'Malley?
And how does a man with your
conservative credentials
count himself
a believer in UFOs
and 9/11 false
flag conspiracies?
I take it you think
my message is disingenuous.
Conspiracy sells. It pays
for bulletproof limousines.
You think I do it
for the ratings?
I think you're
The O'Reilly Factor
with a shopworn
little gimmick.
What Bill O'Reilly
knows about the truth
could fill an eyedropper.
The Kelly Cahill incident.
Kelly Cahill and her husband
were driving home
in Victoria, Australia,
when a craft appeared
overhead.
The Cahills lost
an hour of time,
and Kelly was hospitalized
with severe stomach pain
after discovering a triangle-shaped
mark near her navel.
As I said,
my interest is real.
What I need
is your expertise.
Our expertise for what?
I'm rattling
some pretty big cages
in the intelligence community,
but I'm prepared
to go all in,
prepared to blow open
maybe the most evil conspiracy
the world has ever known.
That's quite an assertion,
Mr. O'Malley.
What's stopping you?
If I'm putting
my ass out there,
I need to know it's hanging by more
than just a very slender thread.
Apparently, he has
something to show us.
MR. O'MALLEY: Something
and someone.
Aliens couldn't find
this place.
How did you, Mr. O'Malley?
A man in my position
finds himself contacted
by interesting strangers.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Everyone, meet Sveta.
Sveta, this is Dana Scully
and Fox Mulder.
Hi.
Hello.
Welcome to my home.
Sveta's who suggested
I call you.
And how would you
know to do that?
You probably
don't recognize me.
No, I think I'd remember.
You interviewed me
and my family
when I was
just a little girl.
Right after
my first abduction.
Please, come in.
These are from over 20 years.
You both probably recognize
the classic scoop-mark scars.
How many times have you
been abducted, Sveta?
I lost count.
And then there are the
screen memories they implant.
The memories implanted over actual
memories to make abductees forget.
I'm familiar
with the syndrome.
They aren't always effective,
and things come back
to me sometimes.
Like what kind of things?
Tests they do.
Harvesting and stuff.
(SCREAMING)
The aliens made you pregnant?
A number of times.
But they take the babies
before they're born.
Those are the memories
they can't remove.
They removed
your unborn fetuses?
(SCREAMING)
Through here. They do
everything through here.
Even with the DNA.
Tell them about
your DNA, Sveta.
I have alien DNA. For sure.
Have you had
a doctor confirm that?
No.
Something you could test?
Dana?
Oh, Lord. Oh, good Lord.
Damn thing
could be dangerous.
(GUN FIRING)
What are you doing?
(GUNS FIRING)
For God's sake,
what have you done?
I'm gonna take a swab.
If you'll roll up your sleeve,
I'll get some blood, too.
I know you're doubtful
about this.
What makes you
say that, Sveta?
I'm kind of a mind reader.
Is that a personal trait, or is
that what happens with alien DNA?
I can move things.
With my mind.
Would you care
to demonstrate?
I can't do it all the time.
So it just happens whenever.
I don't know
how to control it.
You were a couple before.
I'm sorry, what?
You and Mr. Mulder.
You were together,
but now you're not.
You reading my mind, Sveta?
He's been depressed.
What you diagnosed
as endogenous depression.
It's what killed
your relationship.
Oh.
And you have
a child together.
(MOANS)
That's enough.
You believe me now?
Why don't you tell me.
You don't know
what it's like to be abducted.
To be taken against your will.
You don't know.
Well, maybe you do.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
I was right about one thing.
Conspiracy's made you
a very rich man.
One way to look at it.
What's made me rich
is my pursuit of the truth.
My pursuit's
not been so lucrative.
I feel I need to warn you.
When we arrive
at our destination,
the people we're meeting
are very paranoid
about the work they do.
I want to prepare you for what
you're about to see, Mr. Mulder.
A Faraday cage? For what?
Do you know
what an ARV is?
That's what you
brought me here to see?
This is Garner.
He'll walk you through
the science.
That's an alien
replica vehicle?
Given your background, I would've
thought you'd seen one before.
No, never. Not like that.
What we're showing you,
we do at great risk.
Colleagues have had labs
burned to the ground
and work destroyed
by our own government.
(EXHALES)
(POWERING UP)
GARNER: It's running on
toroidal energy,
so-called zero-point energy.
Simply the energy
of the universe.
You're talking
about free energy?
That we've had
since the '40s.
No fuel, no flame,
no combustion.
A simple
electromagnetic field.
Technology kept secret
for 70 years
while the world
ran on petroleum.
Oil companies
making trillions.
GARNER: What I'm gonna show you
next is the most unbelievable part.
Gravity warp drive,
but how?
Element 115.
Ununpentium.
Where did you get it?
Where are you going
with that thing?
I'm a man of medicine, sir.
It's dead. It's done now.
Then why even
bring me out here?
Testing yourself
for alien DNA?
High cholesterol.
Sorry to barge in
on you like this.
It looks like
you've had quite a day.
The usual around here.
Doesn't look so usual to me.
It's a disease
called microtia.
Children born without ears.
You operate on these kids?
I assist the surgeons, who
are really doing God's work.
Giving kids what
their biology neglected.
So it's
a genetic deformity?
Possibly,
but not conclusively.
It's most common
in Navajo Indians.
What's so striking
is how alien it looks.
I assure you that is simply a
random coincidence, Mr. O'Malley.
You mean, unrelated to your
previous work experience?
Far, far from
that experience.
Do you miss it at all?
The X-Files?
As a scientist, it was probably
some of the most intense
and challenging work
I've ever done.
I've never felt so alive.
You mean
working with Mulder?
Possibly one of
the most intense
and challenging relationships
I may ever have.
And, quite honestly,
the most impossible.
Yeah.
I got that impression.
Are you here for a reason?
I needed to know
you weren't upset
by Mulder putting you
on the spot
with this Sveta business.
No, it's fine.
I'm used to it.
And I just wanted
to see you again.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
How did you get here?
Hitchhiked.
There was a moment you were being
asked about your abductions,
about your pregnancies, how
the aliens took your babies,
and before you answered,
you looked at O'Malley.
Why?
Because it's not exactly
the right question.
I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
Because I don't believe it's
aliens who were taking them.
But you said
you were abducted.
This is difficult.
These are
very difficult memories,
and this is very
dangerous answers.
Well, everything stays
between us, Sveta.
The things I've experienced,
they've affected my entire life.
They've made it impossible to have
anything like a normal existence.
What are you afraid of?
That it only gets worse.
Sveta,
who took your babies?
Men.
Men? Humans?
You saw their faces?
Yes.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
They took me
aboard their ships.
And...
I was afraid
they would kill me
if I ever told
anyone the truth.
It's why you didn't
see a doctor.
Who can I trust?
They would call me a liar
when they're the liars.
You can trust me.
You worked
for the government.
Technically,
but not for years.
But you always wondered
if they weren't
lying to you, too.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Mulder.
Scully, listen to me.
I've been misled.
We've been misled.
Mulder, hold on a second.
No, just listen
to what I'm saying.
What if everything we've been
led to believe in is a lie?
What if there is
no alien conspiracy?
Can we pull over a second?
I've got to get out.
Mulder, what are you
talking about?
I'm talking about everything
we've been led to believe.
Our work,
the X-Files, everything.
Can we talk about this soon?
I know why O'Malley
came to us, Scully.
And that girl
is the key, Scully.
Sveta is the key
to everything.
Couldn't you be
jumping to conclusions?
I can't do this over the
phone right now, Scully.
I got to go.
Mulder, where are you going?
Mulder? Talk to me.
Where are they, the files?
I don't know
where they are.
You said no one had been down
here, it hadn't been touched.
Not for 14 years since you
and Scully left the Bureau.
I need access to the X-Files.
Can you tell me
what this is about?
It's about controlling the
past to control the future.
It's about fiction
masquerading as fact.
Now, you owe me
some answers, Skinner.
You just calm
the hell down, Mulder,
before we both
get pissed off.
I don't take orders
from you.
No. Who do you
take orders from?
Why do you think
I called you?
Because I was
looking out for you,
like I've always
looked out for you.
A decade of my life
in this office.
And all the time,
I was being led by my nose
through a dark alley
to a dead end,
exactly as they planned.
You're blaming me for that?
No, I'm blaming myself.
I'm sure they lied
to you, too.
There hasn't been a day
since you left
that I haven't reached for my
phone to call you, Mulder,
wishing that you were
still down here.
Since 9/11, this country
has taken a big turn
in a very strange direction.
How they police us
and spy on us,
tell us that makes us safer?
We've never been
in more danger.
Then do something
about it, Mulder.
(DIALING)
(LINE RINGING)
Now you've got my number.
So if you own
a registered firearm,
you will actually
be targeted as an enemy
by your own government in the
likely imposition of martial law.
But I'd like to end the show
on a brighter note
by pointing out
the heroic work
being done
by a friend of mine.
Literally putting kids
back together
who are born without something
we all take for granted.
At Our Lady of Sorrows
Hospital in Washington, D.C.,
Dr. Dana Scully,
working to mend the lives
of unfortunate children.
Dr. Scully?
I've got your
test results back.
Thank you.
Nurse?
I need you to do something.
Of course.
I need
these samples retested.
Was there a problem
with them?
SURGEON: Dr. Scully?
We need you in here.
I just want them
retested, please. Thank you.
Oh, and I'm expecting
a call.
Well, I'm hoping for a call
from somebody named Mulder.
Is the hour
absolutely necessary?
It was important
that I see you.
We made an agreement about our
meeting in unsecured environments.
I took the usual precautions.
I'm assuming you did, too.
(AIRPLANE FLYING OVERHEAD)
I've been standing here for over an hour.
I haven't seen a soul.
I called you because you said if
I ever put the pieces together,
that you would confirm.
And have you
put them together?
I've met someone.
I've seen something.
'Cause you weren't
even close.
Warring aliens lighting each other
on fire and other such nonsense-
I was being
cleverly manipulated.
And what brings
this new clarity?
I saw an ARV running on free energy.
I saw it disappear.
That's what they all
seem to do.
But the technology exists.
It's existed since Roswell.
And it's been in use, being used
on humans in human testing,
the taking of men,
women and children
that's misreported
as alien abductions.
So you behave you have the how.
Yes.
And I think I know the why.
The why is more
complicated than
you may ever know,
Mr. Mulder.
Sixty years ago,
we were warned
about the military
industrial complex
gathering too much power.
This is old news.
The countdown has begun.
It began in 2012,
but no one knew.
Tell me something new.
Alien technology
being used against us,
not by aliens,
not with aliens,
but by a venal conspiracy
of men against humanity.
You're wasting my time.
What are the tests for?
You tell me, Mr. Mulder.
Ten years ago,
you came to me
saying you couldn't take
your secrets to your grave,
that you couldn't
live with it.
I'm a man of medicine.
I didn't know how my work
would be used.
The Hes are so great,
Mr. Mulder.
The truth must be
unassailable.
Well, let me tell the world.
They'll make
a mockery of us.
Then let me take that bullet.
And these men
are capable of that.
You're nearly there.
You're close.
Roswell.
That was a smokescreen.
So I've been told.
What are you
doing here, Scully?
Mulder, you hang up on me,
I don't hear from you all day,
you're on some jag
about the X-Files.
I figured it out.
It all makes complete sense-.
All these years,
we've been deceived.
I don't know what you mean.
I couldn't call you because
it's gonna sound crazy.
That's why I'm here, Mulder, as
somebody who cares about you.
As somebody
who's worried about you.
All right,
just listen to me, all right?
No, you listen to me, Mulder.
Scully, you got to
trust me on this.
I have seen this before.
You're on fire, believing
that you're onto some truth,
that you can save the world.
This will finally
be their undoing.
It'll be your undoing,
Mulder.
This is my life.
This is everything.
This is everything
I believe in.
You want to believe.
You so badly
want to believe.
I do believe.
I believe that
Tad O'Malley is right.
This is not
an alien conspiracy.
It's a conspiracy of men.
Tad O'Malley
is a charming man
full of charming BS, Mulder.
No, he woke me up.
How do you know
he's not playing you?
He's a player.
He's been a godsend.
What are you talking about?
The truth is out there,
Scully,
and Tad O'Malley's
gonna broadcast it.
Mulder, listen to me.
As your friend
and as a physician,
you are on
dangerous ground here.
I know what I'm doing.
SVETA: ls everything okay?
Yeah, everything is okay.
She's the key to everything.
Sveta is the key.
You know what you're doing.
Scully.
(KNOCKS ON WINDOW)
Hey.
Where you going?
You're not leaving, are you?
I just need to
get out of here.
Stay. It's important.
Don't tell me
what's important, please.
I just need to leave.
Wasn't she invited?
I would have invited you,
Scully,
but I didn't think
you'd come.
I shouldn't have come.
Then what are you
doing here?
Mulder, what are you up to?
The tentacles reach far back
into the last century,
but it wasn't until victories
in Europe and Japan
and the onset of the Cold War
that political
and economic conditions
became perfect
for actual execution.
A conspiracy bigger
and more secret
than the Manhattan Project.
More odious
and far-reaching.
MULDER: No sooner
had we defeated Germany
that a new threat started
appearing in skies over America,
drawn to Earth by the latest
threat to extinction,
the H-bomb.
Explosions acting
as transducers,
drawing alien life-forms
through wormholes
in spaceships using
electrogravitic propulsion.
Advanced extraterrestrial
species visiting us,
concerned for mankind and the
threat of our self-destruction,
forestalling our annihilation
through their own self-sacrifice.
And crashes at Roswell.
More importantly, places like Aztec.
(GUN FIRING)
World leaders signed
secret memos
directing scientific studies
of alien technology
and biochemistry.
Classified studies were clone at
military installations S4, Groom Lake,
Wright-Patterson and Dulce,
extracting alien tissue.
Tests were done
on unsuspecting human subjects
in elaborately
staged abductions,
in craft using
alien technology
recovered from
the downed saucers,
(SCREAMING)
including human hybridization
through gene editing and forced
implantation of alien embryos.
Why do such a thing
and lie about it,
our own government?
Your own government lies as a matter
of course, as a matter of policy.
The Tuskegee experiments on black
men in the '30s. Henrietta Lacks.
What are they trying to do?
That's the missing piece.
MR. O'MALLEY: But it's not
hard to imagine.
A government hiding, hoarding
alien technology for 70 years,
at the expense of human life
and the future of the planet.
Driven not only by corporate
greed, but a darker objective.
The takeover of America.
And then the world itself,
by any means necessary,
however violent,
or cruel or efficient.
By severe drought
brought on by weather wars
conducted secretly
using aerial contaminants
and high-altitude
electromagnetic waves,
in a state of perpetual war
to create problem-reaction-solution
scenarios
to distract,
enrage and enslave
American citizens at home
with tools like
the Patriot Act
and the National Defense
Authorization Act,
which abridged
the Constitution
in the name
of national security.
The militarization
of police forces
in cities across the U.S.
The building of prison camps
by the Federal Emergency
Management Agency
with no stated purpose.
The corporate takeover
of food and agriculture,
pharmaceuticals
and health care,
even the military,
in clandestine agendas,
to fatten, dull, sicken
and control a populace
already consumed
by consumerism.
And I encourage you all
to go shopping more.
A government
that taps your phone,
collects your data
and monitors your whereabouts
with impunity.
A government preparing to use that
data against you when it strikes
and the final takeover begins.
The takeover of America.
By a well-oiled and well-armed
multinational group of elites
that will cull,
kill and subjugate.
Happening as we sit here.
It's happening
all around us.
The other shoe
waiting to drop.
MR. O'MALLEY: It'll probably
start on a Friday.
The banks will announce
a security action
necessitating their computers
to go offline all weekend.
Digital money will disappear.
They can just
steal your money?
Followed by the detonation
of strategic
electromagnetic pulse bombs
to knock out major grids.
What will seem like an attack on
America by terrorists or Russia.
Or a simulated alien invasion
using alien replica vehicles that
exist and are already in use.
An alien invasion
of the U.S.
The Russians tried it in '47.
You can't say these things.
I'm gonna say them tomorrow.
It's fearmongering claptrap,
isolationist techno-paranoia
so bogus and dangerous
and stupid
that it borders on treason.
Saying these things would be
incredibly irresponsible.
It's irresponsible
not to say it.
Especially if
it's the truth.
Your test came back negative.
What do you mean, negative?
She has no evidence
of alien DNA.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
MR. O'MALLEY ON LAPTOP: I
promised you the truth today,
but that truth
has come under assault.
Tad O'Malley tried
to put words in my mouth.
He paid me to create stories
about alien abductions.
He is saying lies and stories
for his TV show,
so people will watch.
I am so sorry
if I misled anyone.
They got to her.
MR. O'MALLEY: These are the
depths our government stoops to.
We must be making them
very afraid.
Dr. Scully?
Your test results
came back in.
Sveta? Sveta?
Sveta?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
No, no.
Stop! You can't!
You have no right...
(BEEPING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(CAR UNLOCKS)
MULDER: There's something
called the Venus syndrome.
It's a runaway
global warming scenario
that leads us to the brink
of the Sixth Extinction.
Those with means will prepare to
move off the planet into space,
which has already been
weaponized against the poor,
huddled masses of humanity
that haven't been
exterminated
by the uber-violent
fascist elites.
If you believe
in that kind of thing.
You look exhausted, Mulder.
It was a long day
at the office.
I don't know
if you saw, but...
Tad O'Malley pulled the plug.
They're very good,
these guys, you know?
And what about Sveta?
Where is she?
I'm sure they scared her
to death.
We need to find her, Mulder.
We need to protect her,
no matter what.
Why?
You said her tests
came back negative.
Iran them again.
In fact,
l sequenced
her entire genome
because I didn't trust
the initial results.
Are you saying
she has alien DNA?
And I sequenced
my own genome
because of my history and because
we have a child together.
Scully,
what are you saying?
I'm saying
she's not the only one.
I'm saying someone has to
stop these sons of bitches.
(CELL PHONES CHIME
AND VIBRATE)
Skinner.
Scully, are you
ready for this?
I don't know there's a choice.
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
No.
Please.
Please don't quit. No.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
No.
No! (SOBBING)
No!
(EXPLODING)
Yes.
I see.
We have a small problem.
(EXHALES)
They've reopened the X-Files.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)