(PRAYING IN ARABIC)
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
(MIDDLE-EASTERN MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON
RADIO) You can call back home
Say you were wrong
Ahh.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
GIRL 1: Looks like
we got a visitor.
GIRL 2:
A little brownie.
MAN: Are we in
the wrong country then?
GIRL 1:
All right, all right.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
(CHUCKLES)
(MUSIC PLAYING
ON RADIO IN ARABIC)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(PRAYING IN ARABIC)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT INSTRUMENT
BLARING)
SCULLY: What am I
hearing, Mulder?
According to eyewitnesses
or "earwitnesses,"
as it were,
it sounded like
trumpets playing.
From nowhere
in particular?
No apparent source.
Music as if from the
heavens themselves,
as if God himself
was making music,
blowing his own horn.
Since when do you
believe in God, Mulder?
What makes you
think I do?
"God himself"?
I speak merely as
an investigator.
Reports from
Belarus to Canada,
France, Italy, Germany,
the Ukraine...
But as an investigator, you seem to
give this phenomenon credibility.
It's not important what
I believe, Scully.
It's important
what they believe.
The earwitnesses.
And what do
they believe?
"And I saw the seven angels
that stood before God,
"and to them were given
seven trumpets."
Revelations 8:2- A
herald of end times.
You know that prophecies like this
have been going on for centuries.
Failed prognostications of doom,
failed prophecy,
even in the Bible.
Yeah, God told Adam that if he ate
the forbidden fruit he'd die,
and he lived 930 years.
Top that.
You know that didn't
literally happen, right?
I'm just sayin'.
It's your book.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
AGENT MILLER: Hello?
Anyone down here'?
Nobody but the FBl's
Most Unwanted-
I've been waiting
23 years to say that.
How'd it feel?
Pretty good.
Yeah?
It's open.
Come on in.
Special Agent
Fox Mulder?
Speaking.
And to whom
am I speaking?
I'm Special Agent Miller. This
is Special Agent Einstein.
You're Special
Agent Einstein?
I claim a distant relation, if
that's what you're referring to.
MULDER: Forgive Agent
Scully's impertinence.
She wrote her dissertation
on Einstein's twin paradox.
Excuse me, but I was definitely
told you were a medical doctor.
I am. But I'm also a scientist.
Because I'm
a medical doctor.
Oh.
And you're a profiler,
obsessed with the paranormal?
That's why we're
here, actually.
When we should
be at the airport.
You both heard about
the terrorist bombing of
an art gallery in Texas?
Yes. Two young Muslim men protesting
the depiction of Mohammed.
Wearing suicide
bomber vests.
Can we get to the
business section, please?
Nine people killed in the act but
one of the bombers survived-
AGENT EINSTEIN:
Technically.
Medically, he's in a
persistent vegetative state.
He's dead except
for a heartbeat.
You must imagine
why we're here.
There have been
so-called practitioners...
I'm sorry. Forgive me, but I
can't imagine why you're here.
That would make
two of us.
Agent Miller, a man with a mind
obviously open to possibility,
would like to communicate
with the dead,
or the near-dead,
(SCOFFS)
as the case may be.
I believe he may have intel
on a larger sleeper cell
with an aim to commit
more acts of terror.
Which is where our energy
would be better spent,
trying to stop
live terrorists
rather than stopping to try
to speak with dead ones.
I have to say
I agree.
There have been noted divinators,
oracles, fakirs, necromancers
who have claimed
the ability...
Madame Blavatsky,
founder of Theosophism,
brought to America a
so-called Ancient Wisdom
gained from Tibetan
spiritual adepts.
Maybe I've been part of
the X-Files too long,
but I happen to know that
Madame Blavatsky's dead.
Which would make it
that much harder Oh-
to glean her
far-flung abilities.
Yeah. That's what
I thought. Miller?
You know of no
such practitioner
working now whom
we might consult?
None that I'd
waste your time on.
Miller, come on.
There's a 1 :30 flight
to Texas, and I
want to be on it.
Thank you
for your time.
Please call me when you think
of something.
He seemed like
a bright young man.
She calls him "Miller."
Hmm.
(ON TV) Using artwork to desecrate the
prophet of someone else's religion
just incites fanatical terrorists.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
It's just a painting.
Yeah.
Of Mohammed sitting on a toilet
defecating radical Islamists!
WOMAN". Do you know how absurd this all is?
It's just absurd!
MAN: It's not absurd to the victims
of this action and their families...
Wearing that vest, those last few
steps, knowing you're gonna die,
must be so strange.
How 'bout the victims?
Imagine not knowing.
That's even worse.
Where does all
the hate come from?
He's just a kid. A kid
needs to be taught
this hate. You wonder
who got in his head.
Well, he's not gonna
tell you, Miller.
And neither is
any necromancer.
Well, wasn't it at least worth a try?
(SCOFFS)
You think anyone takes
the X-Files seriously?
That's why they got them stuck
down in that basement office.
I pity that poor
Agent Scully.
That's, like,
my dream assignment.
No self-respecting
scientist
would spend
a career toiling away
in obscure realms
of science fiction.
Why else would
she do it?
She's clearly
in love with him.
You spent all of five minutes with them.
How do you know that?
Nothing else
would explain it.
Maybe he values
her open mind.
Maybe she
challenges his B.S.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(SIGHS)
Special Agent
Miller speaking.
(ON PHONE) Agent Miller,
this is Agent Scully.
Um. Hey. One second.
I'll meet you
on the plane.
MAN: Westboro Church is not
representative of all Christians!
WOMAN: Of course not,
but they have...
Hi.
You might wonder why I'm calling.
AGENT MILLER: NO-
Uh, well,
actually, yeah.
I was thinking
about your case,
and I have an idea
that might help you
communicate with
your terrorist.
That is good news.
What is it?
There's something
I'd like to try.
But I need to
meet you in Texas-.
Okay. Yeah.
That sounds great.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Special Agent
Einstein speaking.
Agent Einstein,
it's Agent Mulder.
You must wonder
why I'm calling.
No. I'm completely
baffled.
I have an idea
of how you might
communicate with
your terrorist.
Uh, I think it's Special Agent
Miller you're looking for.
No, no. I need to
speak with you.
I got your number from A.D.
Walter Skinner,
who sings your
praises, by the way.
Yes, I helped him
with his migraines,
which he claims
are due to you.
In any case, I was hoping
I might impose upon you
to delay your
trip out to Texas.
You can't just
tell me now?
It requires
some explanation.
You do realize the clock is ticking
on this case, quite literally.
I think it could
save lives.
Say no more.
I'm on my way.
Where are you going?
I'm catching the crazy train. I'll
see you down in Texas, Miller.
WOMAN: When did radical
Muslims become a protected
class in America?
MAN: When the Founding Fathers signed
the Constitution, that's when.
The same document
that's supposed
to protect my
freedom of speech.
MAN: But not your freedom to hate!
What is wrong with you?
WOMAN: It is not
a freedom to hate!
MAN: Why do you think these
guys are acting this way?
Why do you think
that guy went up
and shot five servicemen
in Chattanooga?
Because they
loved him?
Because we treated
him well?
Because we don't
plaster their names
as terrorists all
over the media? No!
Because we hate them.
WOMAN: We do
not hate them.
I will not...
MAN: Okay.
WOMAN: No, we do not hate them.
And I will not allow for that.
We are not going to continue to
spread lies about a people...
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Ah, come in, Agent Einstein.
Have a seat.
I came here in good faith, Agent
Mulder, but lives are at stake.
I'm all about that.
If there were another act of
terror, and I'm in here listening
to some woo woo treatise
on the paranormal,
I don't think I could
forgive myself.
(STUTTERS)
I don't do woo woo.
Okay, what's
your big idea?
How are we going to talk
with this terrorist?
Well, first, can we talk about the
nature of reality, as you perceive it?
My reality is new chatter on the
Internet about more suicide bombs.
But do you believe
that thoughts have mass?
That ideas such as faith and
forgiveness have weight
much the same way
this desk has weight?
Or any material,
really.
(SIGHS)
You are too much,
Agent Mulder.
It's a legitimate
question.
There's a legitimate answer. No.
How can you
be so sure?
Because when I stand on the
scale and think of ice cream,
my ass doesn't grow.
Need I
illustrate further?
Yes, but I'm sure you believe
that words have weight,
the weight to move people
to go kill other people.
People kill people.
Bombs kill people.
Words can incite people to kill
people as instruments of hate,
but are not lethal
in and of themselves.
Ever suck on a lemon,
Agent Einstein?
Do you feel a
sensation right now?
A quasi-measurable
effect?
lam getting a taste of what
Agent Scully must suffer.
Neo-Darwinists believe
that every word spoken,
every thought, every perception,
lest I misperceive,
is a step in the
evolution of mankind.
Yes. A butterfly beats
its wings in China,
but that butterfly won't be defusing
explosives in any suicide vests.
Agent Einstein, you have a terrorist
lying in a state of existence
somewhere between
life and death.
If he holds valuable intel
on other terrorists,
maybe in order to reach him,
you need to expand your mind
on the so-called
material world.
I got here as fast as I could.
Thank you.
Let me say, I'm blown away you
came down here to help me at all.
Well, I sensed
your frustration.
I just want to believe
there's some way
of reaching this young man and
learning what he might know.
Well, I believe there may be,
but not the way you think.
What way is that,
Agent Scully?
Well, not through an oracle
or a psychic or a seer,
but through science.
I don't know
how you mean.
This may sound heavy, but this is
a bit of a personal quest for me.
My mother was in
a coma recently,
and I wasn't able to
communicate with her, either.
I take it she's passed?
I wish I'd had
the presence of mind
to think of this when
she was still alive.
It might've solved a mystery
that I may never know.
Please enlighten me,
Agent Mulder,
how nine years of college, three
degrees, and two years at Quantico
has left me
such a simpleton.
Not a simpleton.
A mugwump.
I resent that
characterization,
and I don't even
know what it means.
It means sit down and shut up.
(GASPS)
You talk to Agent
Scully like that?
Only when she's
being a mugwump.
Please have
a seat.
I'll give you two
minutes, Agent Mulder,
and then I'm due
back on Earth.
Behold.
Psilocybe tampanensis.
I'm afraid where
this is going.
The so-called
magic mushroom,
the study of
which has begun anew
by respected
medical practitioners
from Columbia University to Oxford.
Oh. (SNICKERS)
Highly contested
studies.
Highly uncontested
results.
Test subjects
report experiences
that transcended space and time,
confrontations with the dead,
touching the very
face of God.
That's nice, Agent Mulder. You've
got about a minute and counting.
Test subjects
have also reported
that once the impediment of
the physical body is removed,
deep and lasting
truths are revealed
that the conscious
mind won't allow.
Feelings of ineffability,
sacredness, peace, unity, joy,
all without altering
brain chemistry.
Are you proposing,
Agent Mulder,
that we administer the magic
mushroom to the terrorist?
No. No.
I am proposing that you
administer it to me,
so that I can communicate
with the terrorist, (SIGHS)
learn what he knows, and
prevent future acts of terror.
To a technically
dead man?
Death is now viewed by some as
merely another plane of existence.
I don't think our terrorist
has even achieved that plane.
I believe he's still
reachable on this plane.
So you called me back here to
ask me to administer this drug,
this illicit
Schedule 1 substance.
As a medical
professional.
Which Agent Scully
is as well.
Agent Scully has recently had her
own life-altering death experience,
and I don't want to
bother her with this.
Oh.
Oh, so you want to just
keep it between us?
I would,
if you don't mind.
No.
No, I wouldn’t
mind at all.
Because there will be
absolutely nothing to say,
except maybe to
Internal Affairs,
if I were to go through with
this lunatic scheme of yours.
What is lunatic
about it, exactly?
Let me think about that.
Everything?
And rest assured, Agent Mulder,
when I walk out of here,
I will never again darken
your basement door.
So that's a maybe?
(EKG BEEPING)
It's hard to imagine there's someone
in there, when you really see him.
Research bears out a surprising
incidence of electro-activity
even in the most
severely brain-damaged.
What I want to try is a rather
novel but not untested protocol.
I'm open
to whatever.
I'm certain that
you are, Agent Miller.
I believe so many answers lie
beyond the pale of the known world
in realms of
extreme possibility.
I believe
that you believe.
So what are
you proposing?
Doctors recently achieved
the ability to communicate
with a man known as Patient 23
through magnetic imaging, MRI,
by prompting his
otherwise inert
and unresponsive
brain with questions
that triggered
electro-activity.
What kind
of questions?
Mundane questions about
housekeeping and tennis.
But they unexpectedly lit up
certain regions of his brain
that translated to
yes-and-no responses.
That is incredible.
Well, more incredibly, it can
be achieved rather simply
through the use of an ordinary
electro-encephalogram.
Why didn't someone
think of that?
But let me
caution you.
Even if we do
reach this young man,
it may be difficult to get the
intel that you're hoping for.
Who's Special
Agent Miller?
I'm Special
Agent Miller.
Gonna ask you to leave- FBI has
no more jurisdiction here.
Who has
jurisdiction?
Department of
Homeland Security.
I was assigned this case. Agent
Scully is a medical doctor.
We think we
can communicate...
Communicate?
To say what?
"You shouldn't
have done it, son"?
There's a chance to question him
about who was behind the bombing.
And you think
he's gonna tell you?
By any moral definition, this
body here isn't a human.
By my definition,
this terrorist is dead.
I'm sorry, but what's
your business here?
I suggest that you both
take a little breather
and call your superiors in Washington,
if you have any questions.
We're not leaving
this room.
(WHISPERING IN ARABIC)
I'm gonna ask
you to leave.
I'll give the orders,
Agent Miller.
Wrong. I'm giving
the orders now.
They've come here
for retribution.
Whoever you're calling,
this goes way beyond...
I'm not calling
anyone.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Special Agent Einstein.
I'm sorry, but I can't let you
in there without authorization.
I've been assigned this case with
my partner, Special Agent Miller.
Let me see that.
(CLEARS THROAT)
If you're his partner, then who
is Special Agent Dana Scully?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Agent Mulder,
it's Agent Einstein.
How soon can you
be in Texas?
Agent Mulder.
Agent Einstein.
For a second there, I thought
you were gonna punk me.
(SIGHS) I had a little trouble, uh,
procuring the illicit substance.
Wow.
Where'd you
get these?
Apparently, Texas is something
of a promised land.
As it turns out, one of the early
research pioneers is from here.
So this is the
real deal, huh?
I can't speak to the dosage, and
I certainly wouldn't take both.
Not till you've
experienced the one.
May I ask, Agent Einstein,
what changed your mind
on this whole
deal here?
I got here to find that Agent
Scully was here in Texas
working with
Agent Miller.
I sense some
professional animus.
Nothing professional
about it.
But you think
this misguided.
My loss is your gain,
Agent Mulder.
I'll deal with Agent
Miller about this later.
In the meantime, we must conduct this
business with a certain delicacy
where the consumption
of any potentially
dangerous and
psychotropic hallucinogen
must be undertaken
outside of a laboratory.
You mean hide it like a
couple of drug addicts.
While this may seem foolhardy,
I am anticipating results,
that you will actually be communicating
with the terrorist, somehow.
Now, what he may say to you,
or you to him, I have no clue.
How do you say "howdy,
pardner" in Arabic?
Thank you.
You Agent Einstein?
No, I'm Agent
Dana Scully.
Agent Miller? Yes.
ls there a problem?
I'm Special Agent Brem,
here to inform you
that this hospital is
under terror threat.
I've got a cordon of
agents near the building
as a precaution
against an attack,
but I need to clear
this wing until
we can bring in
the bomb squad.
You know where the
threat came from?
Mmm. An anonymous caller,
but a very clear guess,
there's a large and unassimilated
Muslim community in the area,
with one shared wish.
One shared
wish to what?
To wipe you and
America off the map.
To honor their hero,
Osama bin Laden,
whose picture we find all too
frequently on their refrigerators.
Not all Muslims are
extremists, certainly.
Feel free to stay here and take your
chances, if you don't believe me.
There are other people who want
to see this young man dead.
I'm not one of them,
Agent Miller.
Last thing I want
is for this
killer to die
and go to paradise
or to his 72 virgins in the sky.
(SCOFFS)
Sounds like
torture to me.
This boy can hear
everything you're saying,
and we're trying to win his
trust and talk to him.
Keep the
killer alive.
You do your job,
we'll do ours.
AGENT BREM: Time to evacuate.
Everybody out!
(EKG BEEPING)
(EKG BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(EKG FLATLINING)
(CLICKS)
(EKG BEEPING)
There's been a bomb threat.
They're asking us to leave.
We have special
authorization.
That's what
everyone says.
We'll just need the room for a
few minutes, to do research.
Yeah, that's what
everyone says.
You know, I've never seen a patient
receive so much attention.
Especially one who's
so unworthy of it.
Well, this is
a special case.
Just like all those
immigrant groups
coming over here,
taking all our jobs,
clogging up the health care
system and our schools,
and they don't
even speak English.
We're not gonna fix
that right now, so...
A church group brought 200
Arab refugees to our town,
and now they're saying that
they want to bring some more.
Maybe we need
to come back.
Or maybe we can
talk outside.
NURSE: It's all part
of a government program
paid for by
my tax dollars,
which means that I come
to work every day,
and I pay for
these people...
(CLEARS THROAT)
So I did
some research,
and I found out that this is all
part of a plot by the United Nations
to get these people
into the U.S.,
so that they can
form terrorist cells.
That sounds very suspicious.
Mmm. Yeah.
You turn your back on these
people, you're taking a chance.
No. No, we don't want
to turn our backs.
One more thing, you say
you're here doing research?
Yes. We'll just be a few
more minutes in the room,
and then we'll be
evacuating, as well.
Yeah. Well, your
partner already left.
(SOMETHIN' BAD PLAYING)
Stand on the box
Stomp your feet,
start clapping
Got a real good feeling
something bad about to happen
Pulled up to the church
but I got so nervous
Had to back it on up, couldn't
make it to the service
Grabbed all the cash
underneath my mattress
Got a real good feelin'
something bad about to happen
Stand on the box, stomp
your feet, start clapping
I got a real good feeling
something bad about to happen...
(WOMEN CHEERING)
(ACHY BREAKY HEART PLAYING) You can
tell the world you never was my girl
You can burn my clothes up
when I'm gone
Or you can tel! my lips
to tell my fingertips
(CROWD CHEERING) They won't be
reaching out for you no more
But don't tell my heart
My achy breaky heart
I just don't think
he'd understand
And if you tell my heart
My achy breaky heart
He might blow up
and kill this man
(CROWD CLAPPING IN UNISON)
Don't tell my heart
My achy breaky heart
I just don't think
he'd understand
And if you tell my heart My achy
breaky heart (CROWD CHEERING)
He might blow up
and kill this man
(HONKY TONK BADONKADONK PLAYING)
Left left left right left
Hustlers shootin' eightball
Throwin' darts at the wall
(CROWD CHEERING) Feelin'
damn near 10 feet tall
Here she comes,
Lord help us all
OI' T.W.'s girlfriend Done
slapped him outta his chair
Poor ol' boy, it ain't his fault
It's so hard not to stare
At that honky tonk
badonkadonk
Keepin' perfect rhythm
Make ya wanna swing along
Yee-ha! (LAUGHS)
There oughta be a law,
get the Sheriff on the phone
Lord have mercy, how's she
even get them britches on?
With that honky tonk
badonkadonk
Oh, that's what Pm talkin'
bout right there, honey...
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
ls this what you
wanted, Agent Mulder?
Your woo woo paranormal? (WHIPS)
Come on, say it.
Woo woo.
Say it!
Say it! (SHOUTS) Woo woo!
(INDISTINCT CHANTING)
(WHIP CRACKS)
(MISERY IS THE RIVER
OF THE WORLD PLAYING)
You want the truth,
Agent Mulder?
You've come to
the right place.
(WHIP CRACKS)
(THUNDER BREAKS)
There's no milk
at the bottom of the pail
Misery's the river
of the world
Everybody row
Misery's the river
of the world
Everybody row
(DISTORTED SPEECH)
Misery's the river
of the world
(THUNDER BREAKS)
Everybody row
Everybody row...
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
(CHANTING IN ARABIC)
Can you hear
my voice?
We don't even
know his name.
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
I was with
the Bureau in Iraq.
SCULLY: Keep talking,
Agent Miller.
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
AGENT MILLER: The
needles are moving.
SCULLY: It could be
a false positive.
Aberrant
neurological activity,
not a response
in and of itself.
How do we know
the difference?
Well, we need
to set up a baseline,
set up questions that
serve as yes-no answers.
It will be painstaking
and difficult.
I'm just certain
he hears us.
SKINNER: Agent Mulder?
Agent Mulder?
Where's your hat?
Rodeo's over, cowboy.
We're hanging up
your spurs for good.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
Dude, I was on fire.
Dude, you were
an embarrassment,
to me and to the Federal
Bureau of Investigation.
Agent Einstein? Agent
Einstein, tell him.
Tell him what,
Agent Mulder?
What we were doing was under
your medical supervision,
all on the up
and up.
It was until
it wasn't.
Well, it's not like
it was volitional.
What was it,
Agent Mulder?
It was the
magic mushrooms.
Maybe I took too much.
Maybe you didn't
take enough.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Agent Einstein informed
me that you requested
that she administer an
illicit substance to you
in your rather reckless attempt to
talk to an alleged mass murderer.
Yeah, and administer
them she did.
These are what I gave
you, Agent Mulder.
Yeah, that stuff,
that's potent.
This stuff is purchasable
at any corner drugstore.
Maybe in
Texas it is.
These are niacin
capsules, Agent Mulder.
What I gave you is a placebo.
No way-
No way.
That's impossible.
I was under the influence
of something powerful.
Yes. The power
of suggestion.
No, you were there.
And The Lone Gunmen.
The Badonkadonk.
Yeah, I was in Washington,
Agent Mulder.
This is what
I'm saying!
I think he's
still tripping.
Well, the placebo
effect has been known
to have a lasting
psychological outcome.
I talked to
the terrorist.
You talked to the terrorist?
Yes.
He whispered
in my ear.
Well, what did he say,
Agent Mulder?
I can't tell you
what he said.
It was in Arabic.
Well, I'm gonna
get you a wheelchair
so we can get you home,
partner, all right?
Well, you were
there, too.
And you were
50 shades of bad.
You know this
is ridiculous.
We don't want
you dancing away.
(STAMMERS)
So I did dance?
According to a whole bunch of very
frightened, middle-aged Texans.
(SIGHS) You're just
covering your ass.
Well, either way.
I'll be looking at
disciplinary action
over my own dismal
failure of authority.
Thanks to you, I'll probably be
banished to my own basement office,
consigned to a life of
ridicule and ignominy...
Stop! Stop.
(WOMAN SHOUTING)
WOMAN:
I'm begging you!
MULDER: Hey.
I know this woman.
It's okay.
Maybe you
haven't failed.
Agent Scully.
Miller.
This is Noora.
She's come here today to
talk to her son, Shiraz.
Mulder, where did
you find her?
Please don't
ask him that.
(GASPS)
It's okay.
(PANTING)
Got you.
(SOBBING)
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
We believe that
he can hear you.
Then my prayers
are answered.
Oh...
My beautiful
baby boy, Shiraz.
You could not
ever kill anyone.
This is not how
I raised you,
to worship Allah
through death.
To be a man
by following men.
Your heart is
too big for them.
You see the faces of the innocent,
and you lose your nerves.
You cannot go through
with the bomb.
Noora, how do
you know that?
Because my Shiraz
tells me so,
in my dreams
and in my prayers.
Who filled his
head, Noora?
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
I do not know how to help you
because I do not know their names.
(GROANING)
(EKG BEEPING RAPIDLY)
He's going into cardiac arrest.
(EKG FLATLINING)
Blood pressure's dropping.
AGENT EINSTEIN: I'm
gonna go get help.
No, no, I think
he's trying to tell us.
SCULLY:
Now we're losing him!
Shiraz, please, please.
(SOFTLY) I'm so sorry.
No, Shiraz!
(SOBBING)
SCULLY:
I'm sorry.
Let's give her some space.
NOORA: Oh, my Shiraz.
He talked to us.
NOORA: Oh, Shiraz.
He talked to me.
This is exactly
how I saw it.
Agent Mulder,
please...
He spoke to me.
Shiraz.
SCULLY: What do you
mean he spoke to you?
Spoke to you when,
Agent Mulder?
With the help of
Agent Einstein.
Ugh. Agent Mulder,
please stop.
Mulder, when could he
possibly have spoken to you?
I can explain.
Or I can't explain.
He spoke to me.
In Arabic.
In Arabic? In words I
didn't understand, yeah.
What words,
Agent Mulder?
(MUTTERING)
Babbel...
Babell.
(MUTTERING)
Babil?
Babil al...
Something.
"Babil" is "Babylon," the city.
Like in
ancient Babylon?
Just... Babil al...
I feel like I need
to explain.
Just let him
finish, please.
Babil al...
Babil...
Mulder,
are you okay?
(MUTTERING)
Funduuk.
Babil, a! funduuk.
Babylon
the hotel?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PUMPS SHOTGUN)
(CHANTS IN ARABIC)
(CLAMORING)
(SECRET HEART PLAYING)
Secret heart
What are you made of?
What are you so afraid of?
Could it be
three simple words
Or the fear of
being overheard'?
What's wrong?
Let her in
on your secret heart
Secret heart,
why so mysterious?
(SIGHS) Why so sacred,
why so serious?
Maybe you're
just acting tough...
Not staying
for the attaboys?
I didn't really do anything.
Huh.
Nothing but take down a terror
cell ready to kill untold numbers.
That was all
Agent Mulder.
That's not how
I understand it.
I'm told you kept
that boy alive,
that you kept him
safe from harm.
I translated a few words. It
was all you and Agent Mulder.
(CHUCKLES) Remarkably,
I did nothing.
And, remarkably,
it worked.
Although I'm at a loss
in explaining it.
Maybe some things are
unexplainable, Agent Einstein.
Hmm.
The most beautiful thing we can
experience is the mysterious,
the source of all
true art and science.
That's beautiful,
Einstein.
Yes, Einstein. That's
who said it, Miller.
The real mystery here
is your behavior,
bringing Agent
Scully down here
without bothering
to consult me.
Remarkably,
I did nothing.
It was you who abandoned me, Agent
Einstein, for the crazy train.
Ah.
Never again,
Agent Miller.
Although something is clearer to me
now, as a result of the experience.
The value of
an open mind?
The nature of reality.
I'm now convinced that words
and ideas do have weight,
the weight to move people to
do the most psychotic things.
Giving someone
magic mushrooms?
I was talking
about Agent Mulder.
Right.
(HO HEY PLAYING)
Ho!
Hey!
Ho! I've been trying
to do it right
Hey! I've been living
a lonely life
Ho! I've been sleeping
here instead
Hey! I've been sleeping
in my bed
Ho! I've been sleeping
Hey!
Ho!
Ho! So show me family
Hey! All the blood
that I will bleed
Ho! I don't know
where I belong
Hey! I don't know
where I went wrong
Ho! But I can write a song
Hey! One, two, three
I belong with you, you belong
with me, you're my sweetheart
Talk to me,
Mulder.
Where to begin?
Why didn't you tell me
about your little scheme?
You were on
your own mission.
And you would've
never bought that.
Absolutely
right.
I have to applaud her, though, on
her clever trick with the placebo.
Yeah. Yeah.
How did that work?
Wonders never
cease with you.
I saw things,
though, Scully.
Powerful things. I saw deep
and unconditional love.
I saw things, too.
I witnessed unqualified hate
that appears to have no end.
Yeah. But how to
reconcile the two?
The extremes
of our nature.
That's the question.
Maybe the question
of our times.
Walk with me,
Scully.
This whole thing
has got me thinking.
Thinking about God.
You, Mulder, thinking about God?
The angry God
of the Bible.
The Tower of
Babel and Babylon,
scattering people violently, so as
never to speak a common language.
Punishing man
for his hubris.
Well, that lesson didn't stick.
But the anger sure remains.
That's the same angry
God as in the Koran,
ordering death
to the infidels.
What exactly is
this God saying?
"Worship me and
my great anger"?
Well, that's a good
question, Mulder.
One for the ages.
Well, think about the immense
power in those prophecies,
the power in those words
to convince young men
to put on suicide vests today
and murder for their angry God.
What are you
getting at?
Those boys, they just
swallow the pill.
It's the power
of suggestion.
Is this received wisdom from
your magical mystery tour?
Yes.
Courtesy of
the shrooms,
something else, something
to trump all hatred.
Mother Love.
Whoa.
Now, I refuse to believe that
mothers are having babies
just to be martyrs.
I want to believe that mothers
have a greater purpose
for all of us.
I agree.
A child is not a tool
to spread hatred.
But where does the
hatred end, though?
Maybe it ends where it began, by
finding a common language again.
Maybe that's
God's will.
How can we
really know?
He's absent
from the stage.
Well...
Maybe it's
beyond words.
Maybe we should do
like the prophets
and open our hearts
and truly listen.
(CHUCKLES)
(INDISTINCT INSTRUMENT
BLARING)
What?
Did you hear that? What?
I belong with you, you belong
with me, you're my sweetheart
with me, you're my sweet... Ho!
Hey!
Come on, now
Ho!
The last one
Hey!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)