No, no, the engagement is low.
The engagement is low, it needs to be...
I am okay.
Take his belt, watch and any
other metallic object he's wearing,
and send him to the scan room.
Yes, I'll do it right away.
-And you sign this admission form.
-Yes.
What exactly is wrong with him, sir?
Nothing is wrong. We'll dispatch
him in the next couple of days.
Nothing is wrong?
Then why am I in so much pain?
Actually, you have a
problem with your L4 and L5.
There's a strain.
If you don't take better care of
yourself over the next couple of weeks,
then you can have a slipped disc.
What?
No need to worry.
I'll keep you under observation
for the next few days.
-Okay.
-Everything will be fine.
Thank you. Everything is fine.
I am okay. I am okay.
Very good.
I won't have a slipped disc either.
I am okay.
Thank you.
Naveen, I cannot stay here.
The product launched four days ago.
and we haven't seen any traction yet.
The real task of marketing begins now.
He'll say he's going home
but head straight to the office.
He's been staying at the office
for the last four days. Ask him.
Listen...
The hospital guys will
ask me to stay a couple of days,
and tell me to run a couple of tests.
It will add to the bill.
We already...
Not now...
Can you guys go out, please?
Nancy, thank you.
Tell everyone I am fine.
All is good.
How much is it?
2,15,000
Don't worry.
-I am sorry, guys.
-Don't be crazy.
Sorry.
I know we've a cash crunch, but
the company can reimburse half the bill.
No, Naveen.
We're already in a tight spot.
I cannot be a liability anymore.
Have you lost your mind?
What liability?
What do you mean by liability, Mandal?
Get well soon and all
the liabilities will be over.
I'm right.
And if you want to help,
then help with the marketing budget.
The tech team made a new product,
now let me do my job.
This is my job now.
Mandal, focus on your job right now.
No, Naveen.
We must focus on user growth.
That's the most important metric.
-Yes, we are...
-If we don't see a bump in user growth,
then we cannot close this round.
Get well first, otherwise,
you'll see a bump on your back.
I know we've faith in this product,
but even apple needs marketing.
Okay.
-I will figure it out.
-Yes.
Okay. Don't worry.
-You just...
-Yeah...
-Get some rest.
-I am alright. See, no stress.
-See, I am resting.
-No working.
-I am resting.
-Yes.
Get some rest. No talking either.
The doctor has said
that you have to do it.
We know this moron won't stop working.
Someone needs to stay with him.
Don't worry, sir.
I'll stay here and manage his workload.
Are you sure?
Call me if there is anything, okay.
Thank you.
-Come on, Pappi, let's go.
-Yes.
I'll send his favourite pillow.
We'll also buy some fruits on the way.
The changes in the social
media campaign, have they gone live?
-Yes, sir.
-Show me the graph.
Wha...
Shall we try influencer
marketing for promotions?
Sir, no 'blue-tick' guy
is agreeing to our budget.
Do you want me to google,
how to influence an influencer?
No.
Okay, this may be a long shot.
But have you seen the drone video?
To achieve something like that,
we'll need a marketing genius.
But just take a look.
Nancy,
a marketing genius is just
a marketing person with lots of money.
Sharks.
Pay attention!
Pay attention! Pay attention!
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Don't you want to make money?
Then skip if you can?
Skip... no wait.
We want initial traction, don't we?
We don't need any blue-tick guy for it.
Isn't he like a very down market?
Nancy...
I mean he is...
But we need to capture the market.
We'll think with up or down later.
But how are we going to
capture the market with him?
-He has only 150,000 subscribers.
-Nancy...
Nancy, he has 150,000 subscribers.
If we can get some of his viewers,
our user growth will start
walking instead of crawling.
Pappi got my stuff, didn't he?
Pass it.
It's time to work from the hospital.
To make a unicorn, sometimes
you got to stoop pretty low, Nancy.
But sir, after what happened between you
two, do you think Rastogi will agree?
People don't agree,
Nancy, they need to be convinced.
How am I looking?
I think Rastogi will agree.
After all, he was your friend.
I was your only friend.
Everyone in my group
thought you were a zero,
but I thought you were Zuckerburg.
And yet you came to Bangalore
and broke my laptop.
Blood Edwardo.
How can you forget why?
I wasn't happy about
stealing the pen drive either.
I went on a guilt trip as soon
as I got on the flight to Bangalore.
So, Mr. Rastogi, make just one video.
That will end your guilt trip,
and Pragati will get
a five-star rating as well.
Look...life doesn't give
everyone a chance for redemption.
I am not Shashank who needs redemption.
I need something else.
What?
If Pragati survives and you
get funding for the next round.
Then you will have to
become the angel investor
for one of my startups in the incubator.
It's been two years.
R-Cubator hasn't seen daylight yet.
If they don't show some results yet,
they will start thinking I am a zero.
Mandal, please.
I don't want to be
the Mandal of this group.
Just one post and one video, please.
Can't do it this time, Mandal.
Everyone says I am too accessible.
They are telling me to go exclusive.
Please, talk to my manager.
No, not Pragati.
Pragati is the name of my ex.
Okay, I'll do it.
But you must promise me one thing.
Every morning you'll
try anulom-vilom and pranayam.
Will you do it?
I love your product,
but I cannot do Amitji.
I am forwarding you everyone's number.
Call everyone.
Where did you get my number?
Forget how I got it,
let me tell you what
else I got from you.
So much of system, so much of knowledge.
Whenever I am lost,
I log on to YouTube and
watch a couple of your thumbnails.
And that makes me happy.
Our thumbnails are good.
I am also quite nice, bro.
Mandal, I really liked
the name of your product.
Very few startups
choose a name in 'Hindi'.
So congrats on that.
I am ready to make content for you.
I hope you're not making
any videos from RRR.
No.
Because 'Rastogi' is the
Shakuni of the startup world for me.
Well, my videos will have more views.
Girl power.
Do you have Ravish Kumar's number?
That's me, Raja Ravish Kumar.
Loyal to the youth,
hello I am Raja Ravish Kumar.
Okay, bro. Anything for
the Indian startup community.
Tell me about Pragati.
The app is called Pragati 2.0
Basically, our audiences overlap.
So what do you think?
I haven't even used your app.
So if you think I will
lie to my subscribers,
then I'll need more money for that.
What is your budget?
The teacher always gets his fee
for teaching his pupil.
So you do epic shit, I am with you.
We'll do epic shit together.
Okay.
In the start-up community,
Pragati launched like a superstar.
They have added several features,
that you'll run out of fingers.
Isn't it nice?
Mandal just nailed it.
This was just Rastogi.
He's collaborated with several
micro and nano influencers.
The product is receiving great traction.
Nice curves, bro.
Yeah.
It's working. It's working.
Good afternoon sir. Sir, Ashish Jain
here will manage our warehouse.
Sir, lovely to do business with you.
Sir, big fan. Sir, one selfie.
Sir, please...
My younger brother is into startups.
I'll send him this.
One second.
Thank you, sir.
The veneration is done, but
vacating the warehouse will take time.
But work has begun from today, sir.
I made a huge board outside
with your name on it.
What nonsense is he saying?
I will talk to him, sir.
Come with me.
Bhaati, how many
warehouses do you own now?
Don't ask.
Bhaati, daily active
users are growing decently.
But the engagement is tremendous.
-And the KAKS...
-Stop bullshitting me numbers.
Ever read in a newspaper,
"DAU of the startup is low,
or their KAK is high"?
But metrics are important, bro.
There are several stars in the sky,
they are all important.
But the ship only follows one star.
The North Star.
If you want to make Pragati
the biggest company in the world,
then you have to follow
only one North Star metric.
Valueship.
Bhaati, I feel if we do a good job,
it will automatically make us big.
You should have opened an NGO instead.
-Why start up?
-What...
If doing a good job could make you big,
then Tesla wouldn't be going bankrupt.
But only valuation alone doesn't cut it.
A valuation is just a number.
You say it yourself. Just a perception.
No one gives a fuck about reality.
Only perception sells these days.
That's not true.
It is.
There were several companies
whose valuation was millions of dollars.
They have all closed down,
and no one even asking about them. So?
I don't buy this.
Then don't.
Why are you asking?
Do what you want to do.
I am running a company
worth 100 billion.
-Don't mind.
-Fuck!
Why are the company trucks being used?
Did you smoke weed
before coming on the job?
-I told Raunak not to.
-Raunak who?
He's our sales AVP.
-Fire him right now.
-Yes, sir.
-Right now.
-Yes sir. I'm doing right now.
Move the truck.
Sorry, Bhaati. I didn't mean it.
You are my mentor.
That's why I come to you for advice.
I am not giving you advice.
I am saying this out of the experience.
Sorry, sorry.
Hello, Raunak. Can you hear me?
Asshole, you are fired!
Did you know what valuation
Uber got in the beginning?
Five billion.
They were told that they
are just an urban taxi company.
And the founder said they are not a taxi
company, they are a logistics company.
And very soon they went global.
What was Uber's valuation finally?
-How much?
-40 billion.
What? From five to forty?
The founder just pitched the
same product with a different story.
Startup valuations are
not just numbers, Naveen.
It's their story.
And your story is right before my eyes,
so according to me,
your valuation should be...
This much.
This much?
Go sell your story, understand.
I've a friend in Eagle Vision. Ashu.
I'll set a date if you want.
No, Bhaati.
We're already in talks with Prachi.
Plutus will make us an offer.
Are you going to plan
your retirement with them?
The world is dreaming about
Sequoia, Softbank,
and you're jerking off
on local investors like Prachi Meena.
That's not it.
She backs us. She has always backed us.
She believes in us.
That's why...
-Are you two having a scene?
-Of course not.
-No, we are just friends.
-With benefits?
No.
She saw it.
She saw the data and said this.
She said series A is almost done.
In fact, she is in
talks with the partners.
Of course, she will. You did your job.
You left her hanging till now.
The 'V' in VCs is silent.
They are all capitalists.
And what do capitalists want?
Speak up, asshole.
-Sir...
-What needs...
Sir's flight has landed.
We got to leave.
Think about it.
Bhaati, mail from Prachi.
-Again she left you.
-She sent a term sheet.
Take a look.
Glad to hear your offer...
...at a post-money valuation of...
This is nothing close to what you said.
Go on.
Go tie a friendship band to your friend.
Let's go.
You're signing your term
sheet and we're drinking coffee.
It's not on. We need to have whiskey.
We need to celebrate.
What happened?
Prachi, I am not happy
with the evaluation.
I mean, look at our turnaround.
We finished two years
of work in two months.
Naveen. Naveen. Naveen.
Don't get in the valuation game yet.
You just got on track.
This is not the time
to think about valuation.
It's not important right now.
It might not be important for you,
but it's very important for Pragati.
First of all,
it's very important for me.
And secondly,
we're an early-stage funders.
We don't sign big cheques.
This is the first time we're
getting into the series-A round. Right?
So if this is happening,
trust me, I know this is very-very good.
We must sign on this
and move on from here.
This will help us stabilise the ship.
It will help both of us level up.
No, it's a level-up just for you.
You will grow, and your firm will grow.
They will make you the partner.
This is not a level-up for me.
Sooner or later even
we'll need bigger funds.
Even we need bigger cheques.
Okay, Naveen. Wait a minute.
After increasing the valuation,
the pressure to perform
will be more on who?
On you? Right.
And if I become a partner,
who will benefit from it?
You will.
I'll be in a position of power,
to standup for Pragati.
For you. Right?
I think this is the wisest
thing we can do right now.
-Yeah?
-Okay... let's not even talk about it.
You... forget about it.
Take your time. Think over it.
Calmly and take a call.
I know the next time I meet you,
you would have taken a
good decision for both of us.
And then it will be my treat.
-Okay.
-You're good.
-I am good.
Okay.
Take care.
Yeah...
I am ready to meet
all the VCs I've to go to.
Set it up.
Use the term sheet like whiskey,
and see how high you go.
Go make it count.
Was the delivery okay?
-Is sister-in-law alright?
-Everyone is fine.
Just get well soon
and come see your niece.
-Yes.
-I saw that 'Rustomji' video.
-Rastogi.
-Yeah, that one.
He was selling it really aggressively.
Did you pay him?
That's the job of marketing.
Work from the hospital?
-No, I am at the office now.
-Okay, continue working.
Yogi, there are a
couple of dues pending.
-Office supply.
-AC repair and...
I already told you about the tax dues.
We've to pay our vendors as well.
HR was telling me if we could
have a meeting with you three,
that would be good.
-All three?
-Yes.
Mandal is still working in marketing.
And Naveen is busy with funding.
So we cannot trouble him.
Tell Hina we'll have a meeting.
Let's do it together.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Bro... how soon can
we close the funding?
I wanted to talk about my increment.
I am shifting home.
It's on track. The funding is on track.
After that everyone will get appraisal,
bonus, and Goa offsite.
-Goa offsite?
-Yes, of course.
A couple of guys were asking, so I
thought I should talk to you. Otherwise...
Let's all sit together and discuss this.
Okay. I'll solve this.
-Okay?
-Yogi.
What?
We need to talk.
Yes.
Can we go someplace else?
Come.
What is it, Chintu?
I didn't say it publicly.
But good work. You did a good job.
Thanks.
Speaking of which I wanted to ask,
what is your percentage of equity.
What?
Don't get me wrong.
Actually, I am still discussing
my equity with Naveen.
And...although I made the entire
product, but you are my co-founder.
I don't want you to
get a lower equity than me.
You know.
I mean even if Naveen asks me,
I will say no.
I mean...despite our contribution,
I think we should get equal.
And...we can think about Mandal's share.
I know it's confidential
information, but...
Just like privacy...
Confidentiality is also a myth.
So...
Asshole, we'll adjust that
'sattu' that you drink all day.
Ass...
Freakin' 21 but still no change.
Yeah, Naveen.
Do you and Mandal have your suits ready?
Suit?
I don't know. Mandal gets dry-cleaned.
-Why?
-Get ready.
We are setting out to pitch.
Great.
"I need a dollar,
dollar a dollar is what I need"
"Hey hey!"
"I need a dollar,
dollar a dollar is what I need"
"Hey hey!"
"I said I need dollar dollar,
a dollar is what I need"
"If I share with you my story
would you share your dollar with me"
"Hey hey!"
So apart from excellent retention,
our other user matrix
are also getting by the minute.
And, you know, we feel,
as we plan to grow and
scale up in our next phase,
we could use someone like you.
Yes.
So, what do you think, Ashutosh sir?
Please, call me Ashu.
That's what Bhaati calls me.
Okay.
And I've been looking to invest
in your sector for a long time now.
I did take a look at the matrix before,
but I wanted to meet
you guys personally.
It's a shame your CTO couldn't make it.
You know how these tech guys are.
Their job isn't done even
after the product is launched.
So Naveen,
this is what I can offer you right now.
Actually, I already have
an offer with this same valuation.
-Ohh...you do.
-Yes.
Yeah, like discussions
are still ongoing.
I feel the final
offer will be much more.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
I mean I have the term sheet,
if you want I can show you.
No, that's fine.
Bhaati trusts you, so okay.
This... This looks fine, I think.
Okay?
Yeah.
-Okay.
-It's fine?
-Yeah.
-Sure?
-Great.
-Thank you.
So... anything? Tea, soft drinks.
The money.
Naveen. Only you are
capable of doing this.
-That was quite a bluff.
-Yeah, I mean...
"...I reap what I don't sow"
"Well let me tell you something
all that glitters ain't gold"
"Hey hey!"
"It's been a long old trouble
long old troublesome road"
I like the smell
you are wearing, Naveen.
Thank you.
See, Naveen, the valuation
you are asking for, is a bit too much.
I don't know how long
will your business will last.
According to research from
the Rockerfella University of New York,
humans retain the memory
of 1% of what they touch.
2% of what they hear,
5% of what they see, but...
35% of what they smell.
Interesting.
Sir, great business
ideas are like fragrances.
They stay.
Similarly,
sir, our business idea and its impact,
is going to stay in each user's memory.
That much I can guarantee you.
Okay.
Everyone keeps on saying, go-big.
But I say... go-bigger.
If you want to expand or scale up,
I will help you.
I am on board.
"Hey hey!"
"I need a dollar..."
-Are you fucking blind?
-Sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
So, guys, I'll send you the mail.
You know, I always wanted
to work with you guys.
Because your idea and product
are quite relatable to me.
And this pivot is a great move.
And, as we speak, our marketing
team is pushing really hard,
to make these numbers better.
Pramod, I am so sorry,
I think I'll have to take this.
-Oh yes.
-I'll get back.
Sorry, who is this?
Infinity Capital, six million.
And at what valuation?
If we want to meet,
you have to tell me the valuation.
"Hey hey!"
Bro...
-You nailed it.
-He agreed.
-Touchwood.
-I told you.
Use the Helvetica bold
and the pitch gets bold too.
Yeah, all this is happening
because of your suggestion.
Any word from Prachi?
No, let's not wait for her.
I just saw the bank statement.
We have money for only 15 days.
Let's decide and close the round.
Don't stress so much, Mandal.
For the first time in
life even we have options.
Let's choose one of these offers, but...
-Yeah...
-But don't stress.
-Okay.
-Let's go to the office.
The king,
minister, and commander are out here,
the thief must be having a ball,
understood.
Who is the king?
You or me?
-I think it's me.
-Listen, Yogi.
God... again he gave a one-star.
He never wrote anything
nice about any of our updates.
He's the KRK of the play store.
Let's talk to Appu, she will fix this.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Appu.
-Some pages are loading slowly.
-Yeah.
Keeps loading forever.
Just fix this.
That's an issue from the front end.
I'll tell Dungeon.
Move. Move. I'm throwing grenade.
Move.
Hello, some pages...
Some pages are loading slowly,
can you just patch
it up at the front end?
I can, but I won't.
Please do it.
We're getting negative
reviews on the play store.
-EOD...
-EOD will be late.
EOD...end of discussion.
Stab him. Stab him.
What?
Why won't you do it?
It's your job.
It's my job to tell
you what everyone's job is.
You may be the CTO,
but I am with this company
since the early days.
So you won't know, but I
know how much is at stake right now.
And I am with this company
before it was a company.
You are right, there's a lot at stake.
But what about my stakes.
No one's talking about that.
You know, these guys...
These guys may be the stakeholders,
but you and me, we are the showrunners.
And if you can't see the
pride and respect in that...
What are you doing?
If you can't see the
pride and respect in that,
then maybe you are fucking blind.
Killed him.
I am not blind, Appu.
I can see everything.
How Naveen calls this product
'my baby' in front of everyone.
We made this product.
It's our baby.
You don't have to be the babysitter.
Come play CS with me.
Maybe you will know then,
when you have to storm the front,
and when you have to fall back.
Take him. Kill him. Kill all three.
Yes! Eat shit, bitch.
Not you, sorry.
I played a lot of CS in college.
But then I grew up.
And my favourite radio
command still is...
Stick Together Team!
I don't need a team.
The team needs me.
Because I am the fucking MVP.
So, if you will excuse me,
my team needs me for the second round.
Listen, dear.
I came here because the
front end is your domain.
But guess what,
when you became Pragati's MVP,
there were two coders.
And you were busy eating
fritters in the college canteen.
So when it comes to our product,
I can get it done with or without you.
And if you can find the time,
here's another game you can play.
Call of Duty.
Maybe you'll learn something from it.
Does anyone want to play Call of Duty?
I thought you wanted
to meet for a cup of coffee.
You ordered dinner.
Yeah, I thought you would be hungry.
Yeah, but,
how are we going to eat all this.
It's okay,
you're not supposed to eat all of it.
What's that? I didn't get it.
Don't worry, you will.
Okay.
Go for it.
-Last time that we met...
-Yeah.
I had said that the next time we meet,
we'll sign the term sheet,
and it will be my treat, right.
So let's sign it.
Yeah, let's wait.
Naveen, it's been a week.
Yeah, I know...but I just
need a little more time to...
You know...
Shop around?
What did you think, Naveen?
I wouldn't know.
The world of VCs is too small.
And not all VCs are sharks.
Most of them are like sheep.
They walk in a line.
They all follow where one goes.
Other VCs are giving
me updates on Pragati's deal.
Have you thought of
how that makes me look?
You think it's fair.
You take an offer from me,
and on the basis of my deal,
you're looking for a better deal.
Prachi, tell me something.
If Pragati's valuation grows,
won't that increase the
equity of Plutus as well?
So at the end of the day,
I am just making you more money.
So if anything,
I think you should be grateful to me.
Yeah, grateful. Like last time.
Remember what happened
in the KC partnership.
Yeah, how can I forget that?
I kept begging you for two million.
And Mehta swooped away KC.
So you are blaming me for your fuckup.
I am not blaming you for anything.
I am just doing what's
right for my company.
But you...only care about
your deal and your fucking growth.
My growth...
Here you go.
My growth?
If I cared about my growth,
I would have left Pragati
a long time again.
I any way get told at Plutus
that Pragati is a sinking ship.
You are wasting your time.
I don't think I am
wasting my time, but...
Unfair.
You know, you can still get out.
And I know if Pragati
shuts down tomorrow,
it won't make a difference to you.
Because we are not the biggest name.
We are just another
name in your portfolio.
But we have only one Pragati.
We are not that privileged.
Naveen, my name is Prachi Meena.
Trust me. I know a couple
of things about not being privileged.
I know what Pragati
is and I know what you are.
You know what we are,
but I know what we can be.
-Do you?
-Yes.
What do you...
What do you know?
I feel I am the only one holding
on to the vision of this company,
where you started this journey.
I am the only one holding
on to that vision.
What are you doing?
You've derailed yourself completely.
Instead of value creation,
you are running after valuation.
And you know how risky the valuation
game is at this point for you.
You are just...
Look, it's okay. It's your journey,
you do whatever you want to do.
But all I want to tell you is,
I am still on your side.
I am still on your side, Naveen.
You want to walk,
you want to run, you want to sprint.
Do what you want to do.
I am just going to make
sure that you don't fall.
I don't want to run, Prachi.
I want to fly.
And you are just holding me back.
-I am not holding...
-No, you are.
-I am not holding you back.
-You are.
I am just trying to keep you grounded.
If you can't tell the difference between
the two, it's your fucking fault.
Yeah, no, no, it's never your fault.
Mehta had backing from his investors,
so he must have given
a cheque to Mehta right there.
But all we could offer
was a fake promise.
But no, it's never your fault.
Every time we come to you for support,
why do you make it
an obstacle race for us?
Why do we have to deal with this
fucking nonsense bullshit all the time?
There are other fund managers.
They sell their portfolio companies
extensively. They pitch for it.
They fucking put their skin in the game.
You just say that you are on our side.
But where are you?
You stand on the sidelines.
You are sitting there.
If you don't want to
get on the playing field,
then sit outside and
give your commentary.
Because I've no interest in
sitting here and hearing your bullshit.
Excuse me, give him the bill.
Why? Wasn't this your treat?
It's good to have hunger.
But if you don't know your limit,
then you have to pay for it.
Cheque, sir.
Can you write down my phone number?
I don't have it right now.
Can I pay for it later?
Add some sauce please.
Yes, it's done. It's done.
Why go to an expensive restaurant
when he doesn't have money?
Must be meeting some
potential investors.
You got to lay the
cheese for the mouse.
The bill is 12,500.
Our entire office can
drink tea for a month.
12,500
Switch to green tea from tomorrow.
We'll say it's health awareness month.
Nancy wants her salary.
It's her wedding.
Hina needs her reimbursements.
He should have closed
the round by now.
What is Naveen doing?
Why are you stressed?
We'll get doughnuts for the team,
they will be okay.
What...
Do you remember when you
last disagreed with Naveen?
I am agreeing with you.
Bro, make your special coffee for him.
The best.
Neither hot nor cold.
Room temperature coffee.
This vada-pav isn't even hot.
Come on, give me the coffee.
Give me something hot.
Tastes like a mixture
of tea and coffee.
He makes tea in the
morning in the same vessel.
I am telling you.
Mom told me this.
There's no difference between
broccoli and cauliflower.
Mark my words.
Cauliflower is going
to be the next superfood.
I am telling you. Cheers.
Cheers.
Bro, we're all out of gobi Manchurian.
Why does Bhaati call these
small leaguers to the party?
They kill the entire vibe.
He just acquired them.
By the way, 7th drink.
9th.
Valuation 200 million.
Saif just invited me to lunch.
Bachchan sir invited me to Jalsa.
Saif Partners.
Please get my intro with him.
Listen, please...
Bhaati, get me a drink, man...
Bhaati?
Take him away. Come on.
He made a bet.
And after that he resigned.
How are you, bro?
I am great, Bhaati.
Why are you sulking?
No, it's just Plutus
nagging on my back.
Come on, let's play poker.
I'll show you.
I don't know how to, Bhaati.
I played only a couple of times.
It's not a big deal.
I don't have money either.
I will bankroll you.
Win or loss, all mine. Come on.
That's enough, Mehta.
Leave some for me as well.
Bhaati, it's a game of skill.
If there is anyone more
skillful than me, he will beat me.
Okay, guys, this is Naveen.
He just had a fight with his investor.
We got to fix the boy's mood.
He will play poker with us.
Naveen, that's Prabhas.
That's Dolly,
founder of the D2C brand.
Recently turned Unicorn.
Play amongst yourselves.
Harish.
Hi.
If you don't have a
fight with your investors,
then you're not running a startup.
Come on.
Come on, deal the cards.
Sit down.
Guys, this is Kevin.
Michelin star chef.
Do you guys want to order something?
Prawns, Sushi, bruschettas.
Cheese maggie for me.
And scrambled eggs for me.
Scrambled eggs.
Come on.
Raise.
What the...
You are in the mood
to raise these days.
I've been doing it for 10 days.
There are other players here.
But I am looking to
take only one guy down.
He took my KC deal.
God, it's not my fault if
you couldn't please your partner?
And don't take it personally, brother.
It's just business.
There are ups and downs like poker.
-But, Mr. Mehta--
-Don't fuck the mood.
You are at Bhaati's party.
Kids make startups
just to be here someday.
Just talk about the future here.
So... how high did you go?
If I show you the list of VCs,
you'll be shit-scared.
I see.
Who's on the list?
I won't show you my hand.
Someone else will take the cake.
Right, Prabhas.
You approached KC after reading
my Twitter thread, didn't you?
You want a ready pitch.
KC is the guy who
showed up the other day?
Yes, that same uncle.
You are safe. He's a moron.
Look, guys.
Poker is a zero sum game.
Someone's win is another's loss.
But... in business,
we can always have a win-win.
There is a lot of space in the market.
There's a lot of money.
If you play nice,
you can be Swiggy,
Zomato of your sector.
Hopefully, we can
deliver for each other.
We can be Ola and Uber as well.
If we can ride on
each other's success.
-See...
-Good shot.
Come on.
It's called all in, right?
Right?
Okay.
-All in.
-No.
Remember his story?
Fold. I am off.
Same. Fold.
Mehta.
I got to admit, man.
He's got fucking balls.
Respect, brother.
Not everyone has the
balls to take such a risk.
Chuck all.
Bhaati. Let it go.
You had one drink too many already.
You have to go all in.
Fucking 750,000 on
the table right now.
Hey Pablo Chekobar of Vikhroli.
Call it a showdown.
Showdown!
What showdown? See.
Full house.
-Nice hand.
-Congrats.
-Naveen.
-Bhaati, man.
-What are you doing?
-Make a drink.
What are you waiting for?
Did you have anything
or did you just blow it away?
What did you think
before going all in?
This.
Four of a kind.
Nice!
-Great.
-Beginner's luck.
What a great luck.
You had folded.
It was luck, Bhaati.
I was shit-scared.
If I had lost, how could
I have repaid 200,000?
You just raised 750,000.
Three times the money
in a little over an hour.
No start-up gives this
kind of profit these days.
Profit is the reward of risk.
And like poker...
We can't win without
taking risks, right?
Right.
Nice hand, brother.
-Thank you.
-You two are learning.
To bring excitement
to the game and the sector.
Close your round quickly.
Buy a penthouse.
We'll have the next poker party at
your house, and we'll all come over.
-But Invite me.
-Sure.
Cheers.
-Sure. Sure.
-Cheers. Cheers.
-Cheers.
I did not know you are from Delhi.
You are also from Delhi?
Yeah, Rajouri Garden.
-I am from Lajpat Nagar.
-Wow.
I miss Delhi food.
Then you must have tasted
Moolchand's parathas.
Don't remind me.
Crazy.
Naveen, regarding the term sheet.
It's a little dicey.
Ohh... what happened?
Okay, so honestly,
I think your CMO had
over-projected a few numbers,
like your engagement.
The time spent on the app is nice,
but the sample base is too small.
But you liked the user matrix.
Yeah, but the growth
matrix is too bloated.
I don't think we
can achieve that much.
We can't go that big right now, okay.
No, no, I think you
are right, actually.
I'll talk to the team
and we'll rework our numbers.
We'll represent everything.
So that's not a problem.
Yeah, but the investment committee.
They don't think it's the
right time to invest in your sector.
Okay.
Yeah, okay. Not a problem.
Thank you.
I mean, thank you for coming.
I didn't want to
do this over the phone.
No, that's okay. Not a problem.
Cool then, I'll take your leave.
Sure. Sure. Thank you.
Okay, Shreya, thank you so much.
Mandal, we'll have to
rework on the engagement, bro.
Hello.
Hi, this is Naveen.
I am trying to call Mr. Ahuja,
but he isn't responding.
One second, he was supposed
to mail me the term sheet.
You didn't send me the term sheet.
But what exactly happened.
You were very happy at the meeting.
You felt it worked.
Why?
So how long do we have to wait?
But we spoke about today?
So, are you going
to mail it to me, or...
Ashu, what exactly...
Has anything gone wrong?
Did something happen?
I am not getting it.
What happened?
Naveen,
you know a term sheet
is a non-binding document.
Right?
I can choose not to fund
you even after we sign a term sheet.
So...
maybe you're focusing
on the wrong piece of paper.
Sorry, what paper?
What are you talking about?
We shook hands.
And now you're backing out.
It's not fair.
Don't tell me what's fair.
You guys are not following
any compliances at Pragati.
This is how you guys work?
What compliances are we not following?
What are you saying?
Naveen,
my team did some digging,
and found out that your company
has a liability of three million.
And you haven't paid it for two years.
What?
Taxes are due.
And whatnot.
When there are such unethical
practices at Pragati,
so how can I trust you?
That you are running
the company properly.
Ashu, I think there has
been some miscommunication.
I don't think there
is anything like that.
I am not even aware
of what you are saying.
Ohh, that's perfect.
You are the company's CEO,
and you don't know what's
going on in your company.
We can't be associated
with such actions.
Only because Bhaati recommended you,
otherwise we never would
have had this meeting.
Seriously never.
And nothing personal.
It's not going to work out.
I am so sorry.
This is not done.
Hina still has one left.
Okay so we...
Pappi, come to my cabin.
I'll tell you later.
He's just come to the office.
I'll talk to him.
Please, please,
I'll call you back.
Naveen, Prachi sent a mail.
What is this?
-Wait a minute...
-We need to talk right now.
Naveen.
Are you deaf?
-I am calling you to my cabin.
-Sir, Jogi sir made me an employee.
Take it.
Leave this. Come to my cabin.
Please have it. Please.
-Can't you hear?
-Sir, please have one.
I said I don't want it!
Leave it. Leave it.
Did you get a notice
from the tax department?
Tax...
I got a notice for tax dues, sir.
Two notices for 250,000
each around a month ago.
-I told Yogi--
-What Yogi? What were you doing?
Let's talk inside. Come on.
Naveen.
Wait a minute.
What's there to talk about now?
We lost all the offers we had.
Because this 500,000
with interest and penalty
has escalated to three million!
Whose job was it to tell us?
Is it our job or yours?
Naveen.
What am I hearing?
Is this how you plan to become a CFO?
-Shall I demote you to intern again?
-Is this a joke, Yogi?
People are questioning my character.
Forget my character...
People are asking whether we are
following compliances at Pragati at all.
And you're promoting the
guy that screwed our company.
I will fire him today.
Right now. Right here.
You are fired. Right now!
Get out!
OUT!
What are you looking at him for?
Naveen, it's okay.
He made a mistake.
Let's go inside and figure it out.
Figure out what?
Whose fault is it?
Is Pappi to be blamed for it alone?
Who was looking after
the accounts department?
Who hired him?
Who is running the finance department?
Whose responsibility is it?
What kind of people have you hired?
Who are these guys...
There's a Pappi.
Then there's a Tau.
Are we running a company
or making your family film!
Trying to be the big brother,
you've hired morons.
And you are the biggest
moron of them all.
Naveen, Mandal, please don't...
Naveen, you're crossing the line now.
Why are you talking to Yogi like that?
-Prachi's mail--
-Wait a second, guys.
What? Why are you
giving your permission?
Do we need your permission?
You think I am Mandal
to be scared of you.
Let's go.
You really think they respect you.
Have you ever done anything
respectable to date?
Why do you hang around with kids?
Because you want their respect?
They respect you.
You are doing more damage,
compared to the very little
you achieved because of them.
Following up on the KC
deal was your responsibility.
What did you do?
Shat on it.
KC is a moron. Plutus is a moron.
Everyone is a moron.
You shit in every quarter.
So you are the bigger moron!
Naveen, you're the bigger moron.
The tax liability was just an excuse.
Three million is not a big amount.
If any of the VCs
was actually interested,
he could have managed it easily.
Do you know why all the
VCs turned on their offers?
Mehta beat us...
again.
Alpha1 has raised
40 million in series B.
Eagle Vision and all the
other funds that we went to,
are participating there.
So nobody wants to
back a losing horse.
Even our existing investors.
Prachi told me.
Plutus has also cancelled their offer.
You didn't know this, Yogi, did you?
Plutus had given us an offer,
which we could have
closed 10 days ago.
But this guy...
Now you tell us
why didn't you tell us this?
This was your job?
Tell you what?
Yes, they did.
Prachi gave us a term sheet.
She gave us the term sheet first.
But the valuation was too low,
So I didn't accept it.
I know the hard work
we did to get here.
Should we accept
any random value for it?
-That's why I didn't tell you.
-Why?
You bark every other
order in the group.
Reduce the KAK.
Increase engagement.
This metric isn't working.
Huh...
And such a big decision on which
the entire company is relying on,
wasn't communicated to us.
You made us run all over the city,
but still didn't tell us.
You came along with me, didn't you?
You saw we were getting more offers.
Didn't you see it for yourself?
If we had only Prachi's offer,
you would be the first to accept it.
I know that.
Listen to me, Mandal.
This might be brotherhood to you.
You are doing it for a friend's sake.
You might not be serious.
But I want to make Pragati the
biggest company in the world someday.
And valuation is the
real north star metric for it.
-What did you say?
-That's it.
I won't do it if I
don't get the valuation.
I am not serious?
Asshole...
that offer that you rejected,
we got that because I was fucking
working from the hospital. Understood.
You two have turned this into a joke.
Someone's celebrating
before we got the money.
Someone's not accepting
the money being offered,
because the valuation isn't right.
We are fucking doing business here!
And we need money to do business.
End of discussion.
I told you this before,
we have money to survive only 15 days.
The only north star
metric we had to follow
was money in the bank.
But no.
You...
You the visionary CEO,
fucking play your games.
Was I trying to fill my own pockets?
I know how we've slogged to get here.
I know our value.
Prachi was offering us much lower.
That's why I said no.
We were pitching together, weren't we?
Naveen, when will you understand?
It's not just us,
24 people are slogging with us.
You cannot flip a coin
anymore to make decisions.
Because your decisions
affect everyone.
And you've been doing
this from the beginning.
Forget asking, he doesn't feel
it's important to tell us anything.
You never realised that
Pragati had four founders.
You always thought that
you are in the driver's seat,
and we are passengers.
And thanks to this attitude
of yours there are just three left.
Good.
In fact, it will be better
if I am alone.
At least we'll get some work done.
Half the time is lost
in fixing your fuckups.
You guys make me inefficient like you.
Okay, leave. I don't want you.
I don't want any suboptimal people.
You came to me.
You wanted to come on board.
Get in the team.
Bloody freeloader.
You, and he's the bigger freeloader.
He's been a freeloader
since his college days.
He wouldn't have passed out
of college if it wasn't for me.
He would still be there.
Right, Yogi.
Wouldn't you still be there?
Am I wrong?
You are a burden.
I've been carrying
you around on my shoulder.
Good for nothing.
Still, I am carrying you around.
I don't know for how long.
Go on.
Fuck off.
"Everything is fine."
"It's just the effect of desires."
"The heart is stubborn."
"walks on fire though it knows."
"Let things get back on track."
"Let this night fade away."
"Let this storm pass."
"Let me convince my innocent heart."
"Everything is fine."
"It's just the effect of desires."
"The heart is stubborn."
"walks on fire though it knows."
"Let things get back on track."
"Let this night fade away."
"Let this storm pass."
"Let me convince my innocent heart."