♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪
♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BED, TWERP!
♪ THE DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY ♪
♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ WANDS AND WIGS ♪
♪ FLOATY CROWNY THINGS ♪
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD, PEA POD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪
♪ OBTUSE, RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE, GUAVA JUICE ♪
♪ GIANT SNAKE, BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES, CHOCOLATE SHAKE ♪
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE THE KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
YEAH, RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
NICE CATCH, COSMO.
THANKS. CAN I BE A BAT NOW?
GO FOR IT!
YAY!
THANKS FOR HELPING ME
WARM UP, GUYS.
THANKS FOR LETTING
US COME TO YOUR
LITTLE LEAGUE GAME
TODAY, TIMMY.
YEAH! I LOVE BASEBALL!
WHAT'S THE NAME
OF YOUR TEAM?
THE LOSERS.
HOW'D YOU GET
THAT NAME?
OW! OWIE!
OW! OOH, CHUNKY!
WHO ARE YOU GUYS
PLAYING TODAY?
Timmy: THE BURLINGVILLE
OVERACTIVE THYROIDS.
HARD TO BELIEVE
THOSE KIDS ARE 10.
OW!
COOL!
ALL WE NEED TO DO
IS GET HITS AND RUNS
AND NO OUTS AND WE
MIGHT HAVE A CHANCE!
[CROWD BOOS]
OH, NO.
IT'S CHESTER,
THE WORST PLAYER
ON THE TEAM.
THAT'S HOW HE GOT
THE NICKNAME:
CHESTER, THE WORST
PLAYER ON THE TEAM.
APPARENTLY
THE OTHER TEAM
DOESN'T SEE HIM
AS MUCH OF A THREAT.
DON'T LET 'EM
PSYCHE YOU OUT, CHESTER!
KNOCK IT OUT
OF THE PARK!
[SIGHS]
WAIT! IT BOUNCED
AGAINST HIS BRACES
AND SPLIT INTO
27 SEPARATE--
YET STILL IN PLAY--
PIECES OF BASEBALL.
LET'S SEE.
3 OUTS EACH,
TIMES 9 PLAYERS...
27 OUTS!
THAT'S 9 INNINGS
OF OUTS IN ONE SWING!
GAME OVER!
LOSERS LOSE!
[BOOING]
HE CAN'T RUN OR HIT,
BUT WHEN IT COMES
TO GETTING OUT
HE'S THE KING!
CHESTER, IT'S TIME
TO GO HOME.
COME ON, DUDE.
IT'S JUST A GAME.
YEAH, WELL,
TELL THAT TO MY DAD.
BUCKY McBADBAT
IS YOUR DAD?
HE WAS THE WORST
BASEBALL PLAYER EVER!
THAT'S WHY I
HAVE TO BECOME
A BIG BASEBALL STAR,
TO REDEEM MY FAMILY NAME!
YOU MEAN "McBADBAT"?
SHH! DON'T SAY
THAT NAME!
IT'S NOT SAFE
TO BE A McBADBAT.
MY DAD HAS TO HIDE
HIS FACE IN SHAME.
AW, COME ON.
I'M SURE NOBODY TAKES
THE GAME THAT SERIOUSLY.
[BOOM]
ISN'T THAT
YOUR MAILBOX?
NOT AGAIN!
OK. WE'RE PLAYING
3-YEAR-OLDS TODAY
SO WE MIGHT
HAVE A CHANCE.
ARE YOU READY?
ARE YOU IN
THE ZONE?
AAAH!
BATTER UP!
[CROWD BOOS]
STRIKE ONE!
HEY, MAYBE WE
CAN HELP CHESTER.
HOW? MAKE HIM
TAKE UP GOLF?
Umpire: STRIKE TWO!
[GIGGLES]
I WISH MY FRIEND WAS
THE BEST BASEBALL
PLAYER EVER!
Crowd: OOH!
YAY, CHESTER!
CHESTER, YOU'RE
THE GREATEST
BASEBALL PLAYER EVER!
YOU'RE TOTALLY ON FIRE!
LITERALLY.
WAIT TILL MY DAD
SEES ME NOW.
OW! OW! OW! OW!
[FIRE ENGINE SIREN]
OK. WINNING RUN
IS ON FIRST.
ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS HIT HIM IN,
AND WE'LL WIN THE--
CHESTER'S
STOLEN SECOND!
Cosmo: THIRD!
MY WALLET!
MY WATCH!
MY PANTS!
OH, YOU CAME HERE
WITHOUT THOSE, HONEY.
RIGHT!
Umpire: SAFE!
[CROWD CHEERS]
Timmy: I GOT IT!
FINALLY,
IT'S MY TURN
TO BE THE STAR--
TO MAKE
THE LAST OUT!
THERE'S NO WAY
CHESTER CAN--
BASEBALL SENSES,
TINGLING!
FLY BALL. I GOT IT!
I GOT IT!
I GOT IT,
YOU GOT IT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
SPORT?
I JUST--
I USUALLY DON'T MIND
OUR TEAM LOSING,
BUT I LIKE PLAYING.
BUT NOW THAT
CHESTER'S SO GOOD,
HE DOESN'T EVEN
NEED A TEAM ANYMORE.
WELL, IT CAN'T GET
MUCH WORSE, RIGHT?
Chester: DUDE,
BE MY PACK MULE
AND CARRY MY STUFF.
WELL, AT LEAST I'LL GET
TO TOUCH THE EQUIPMENT.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
OOPS! FEEDING TIME!
[MULE BRAYING]
OK. THAT'S IT!
I AM SO SICK OF BEING
CHESTER'S LACKEY
AND EATING THESE OATS.
EVEN IF THEY ARE
LOW IN FAT.
IT'S TIME TO GO BACK
TO THE WAY THINGS WERE.
COSMO, WANDA,
I UNWISH--
Chester:
LOOK, POP! ADMIRERS.
SON, I DON'T
KNOW HOW
YOU MAGICALLY GOT
GOOD AT BASEBALL
BUT...
I'VE NEVER BEEN
MORE PROUD OF YOU.
WILL YOU SIGN
YOUR OLD MAN'S BAG?
SURE, POP!
YAHOO!
I FEEL THE SHAME
LIFTING.
UH, YOU
WERE SAYING?
Dad: TIMMY,
IT SAYS HERE
THAT THANKS
TO CHESTER,
YOUR BASEBALL TEAM
IS SO UNBEATABLE
THE ONLY POSSIBLE
OPPONENTS REMAINING
ARE ACTUAL MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL PLAYERS!
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
PLAY THE NEW YORK BANKEES
IN THE WORLD SERIES!
WOW!
THESE CHESTER O's
ARE A GREAT PART
OF ANY WINNER'S
COMPLETE BREAKFAST.
DON'T YOU WANT
TO TRY SOME
TIMMY O's?
THAT LOSER CEREAL?
EW! THAT'S FOR
PACK MULES!
SON, I NEED
TO ACHIEVE!
HEY, THESE ARE
FOR PACK MULES!
Announcer: WELCOME BACK
TO WHAT IS SURE TO BE
A HISTORY-MAKING GAME
OF AMERICA'S PASTIME
AS THE DIMMSDALE LOSERS CONTINUE
TO SYSTEMATICALLY DESTROY
THE BEST TEAM OF ADULTS
MONEY CAN BUY.
[SOBBING]
GUYS, CHEER UP.
WE'RE WINNING!
WHY THE LONG FACES?
YOU PLAY
EVERY POSITION.
WE DON'T EVEN
GET TO PLAY ANYMORE.
I WAS BORN THIS WAY.
THEY'RE RIGHT,
CHESTER.
EVEN THOUGH YOU
ARE THE GREATEST,
YOU'VE BECOME A HOG!
YOU DON'T LET ANYONE
ELSE PLAY OR HAVE FUN.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
A GREAT PLAYER
DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE TO
BECOME A LOUSY FRIEND!
A LOUSY FRIEND?
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK?
AFTER I FED YOU,
BRUSHED YOUR COAT,
AND LET YOU
CARRY MY STUFF?
FINE! THEN I GUESS
I'M NOT YOUR FRIEND ANYMORE.
WELL, GOTTA GO!
MY DAD'S OUT THERE,
AND I'M GONNA WIN
THE WORLD SERIES!
HEY, WHAT
HAPPENED TO HIM?
REMEMBER WHEN
YOU WISHED
YOUR  FRIEND WAS
THE BEST PLAYER EVER?
"I GUESS I'M NOT
YOUR FRIEND ANYMORE."
THAT MEANS THE WISH
WAS CANCELED.
HA!
HE'S GONNA
STINK AGAIN!
OH, NO! HE'S GONNA
STINK AGAIN
RIGHT IN FRONT
OF HIS DAD.
Bucky: ATTABOY,
CHESTER! OK, BUDDY.
YOU GOT THAT
McBADBAT BLOOD IN YOU.
OH, MAN! YOU LOOK GOOD
IN THAT UNIFORM!
Crowd, chanting:
CHESTER! CHESTER!
CHESTER HAS TAKEN
THE PLATE.
LOOK AT HIM STANDING
THE WRONG WAY,
PRETENDING HE HAS
NO IDEA WHAT HE'S DOING.
OK. I'M GONNA HIT
THIS BALL RIGHT OUT--
Umpire: 3 STRIKES,
YOU'RE OUT!
THERE.
WHAT IN THE NAME OF
VERTICALLY CHALLENGED
NEWSCASTERS IS GOING ON?
MIGHTY CHESTER
HAS STRUCK OUT!
[GASPING]
[CHEERING]
LET'S MAKE
A SMALL BOY CRY.
I GOT IT!
[LAUGHING]
Timmy: CHESTER,
IT'S OVER!
YOU STINK AGAIN.
I CAN'T STINK AGAIN!
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO BRING RESPECT
BACK TO THE NAME
McBADBAT!
[BOOM]
DUDE, IT MAY BE
OVER FOR CHESTER--
THE GREATEST
BASEBALL PLAYER EVER,
BUT IT'S NOT OVER FOR CHESTER,
THE WORST PLAYER ON OUR TEAM!
AND THE BEST PART
OF YOU STINKING AGAIN
IS YOU'RE STINKING
WITH YOUR FRIENDS--
WHO ALSO STINK!
YOU MEAN,
TOGETHER WE'RE
A GIANT ODOR?
AN ODOR SO LARGE
YOUR DAD CAN'T HELP
BUT BE PROUD OF YOU.
YEAH!
[LAUGHTER]
STOP LAUGHING
AT MY FRIEND!
YOU'RE STILL
DOWN BY 29 RUNS
WITH ONE
INNING LEFT.
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU CAN CATCH US.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE ABOUT
TO CATCH US.
HEY, WE GOT TWO OUTS.
ONLY BECAUSE ONE GUY
LAUGHED HIMSELF
INTO A COMA
AND THE OTHER GUY
GOT TRADED TO BOSTON
AS HE ROUNDED
SECOND.
ONE MORE OUT
AND WE WIN, LEGALLY!
JUST PITCH.
I HAVE A PLAN.
Announcer: BASES LOADED,
BOTTOM OF THE NINTH...
ONE OUT TO GO.
I'M EXTREMELY HANDSOME.
Timmy: HEY,
BATTER, BATTER!
HEY, BATTER, BATTER!
HEY, BATTER, SWING!
HEY, KNOCK THAT OFF!
IT'S VERY DISTRACTING.
DON'T LET 'EM GET
IN YOUR HEAD, CORKY.
Kids: I GOT IT!
I GOT IT!
[CROWD CHEERS]
LOSERS WIN!
LOSERS WIN! LOSERS WIN!
[GRUMBLING]
WHOA, WHOA!
YOU'RE OUT, YOU'RE OUT,
YOU'RE OUT, YOU'RE OUT.
EVEN THOUGH
THEY'RE UNCONSCIOUS,
THEY'RE STILL MAKING
3,000 BUCKS A SECOND.
SON, I JUST WANT TO
LET YOU KNOW
HOW PROUD I AM OF YOU.
REALLY? OF WHAT?
I STINK.
YES, YOUDO... OUT LOUD.
BUT IN ALL MY YEARS
IN THE MAJORS,
I NEVER KNOCKED OUT AN ENTIRE
BASEBALL TEAM THAT FAST!
GEE, THANKS, POP.
HERE YOU GO, SON,
YOUR OWN BAG!
AWESOME!
CHESTER SEEMS
REALLY HAPPY NOW.
YEAH, TIMMY.
IT SURE WAS
NICE OF YOU
TO MAKE A WISH
FOR YOUR FRIEND
EVEN THOUGH IT
RUINED EVERYONE'S LIFE.
YEP, LESSON LEARNED.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I USE MAGIC TO HELP
ANYBODY BUT ME.
GEE, HONEY, I SURE WISH
I COULD HAVE SOME HELP
FINDING MY PANTS.
OK, GO AHEAD.
NEAT!
A COUPON FOR TIMMY O's?
THOSE ARE FOR PACK MULES.
Both: LAST TIME?
LAST TIME.
UH, ANY IDEA WHAT
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT?
Girls: BLAH,
BLAH--SHOPPING.
BLAH, BLAH--CLOTHES.
BLAH, BLAH--HAIR!
BLAH, BLAH--BOY BAND.
BLAH, BLAH--
WE'LL NEVER NOTICE YOU.
NOPE.
I DON'T
SPEAK GIRL.
Timmy: NO, RODERICK!
DON'T DO IT!
SHE'LL BETRAY YOU AGAIN!
TIMMY, SIR,
ARE YOU WATCHING
ONE OF THOSE DUMB,
GIRLY SOAP OPERAS?
HEY, THERE'S PLENTY
OF ACTION ON THIS SHOW.
TV Announcer:
WE'LL BE BACK WITH MORE
OF THE  KISSY KISSY,
GOO GOO ROMANCE HOUR,
RIGHT AFTER THIS!
[BLOWS KISS]
WHAT? I LIKE THE WRITING.
Girl: BLAH, BLAH,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH!
DUDE, WHAT'S SHE SAYING,
WHAT'S SHE SAYING?
HANG ON.
LET ME USE MY
GIRL TO GEEK TRANSLATOR.
Girl: BLAH, BLAH,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH!
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH--
WHO--BLAH, BLAH, BLAH--
DIDN'T--BLAH, BLAH--
GET INVITED TO MY
BIRTHDAY PARTY TOMORROW?
WELL, THAT'S EVERYBODY
WHO'S ANYBODY.
GREAT. ANOTHER YEAR,
ANOTHER TRIXIE TANG
BIRTHDAY PARTY
WE DIDN'T GET
INVITED TO.
NOT THIS TIME. WATCH THIS.
HI, TRIXIE.
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
BLAH, BLA-BLAH, BLAH,
BLAH, BLAH...
ANY IDEA
WHAT HE'S SAYING?
NOPE.
I DON'T SPEAK GEEK.
TOO BAD WE CAN'T
COME TO YOUR PARTY--
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
BECAUSE I GOT YOU A--
BLAH, BLAH--
REALLY GREAT GIFT.
I HEARD THAT!
HERE YOU GO, TOMMY.
THE PARTY'S TOMORROW.
AND DON'T FORGET
MY GIFT.
GREAT LIE, DUDE.
HE'S RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A GIFT FOR TRIXIE.
YET! NOW ALL I HAVE TO
DO IS IMPRESS HER WITH
THE RIGHT GIFT,
AND SHE'LL NEVER
FORGET MY NAME AGAIN.
Woman on TV: RODERICK,
CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?
I GOTTA GO.
RODERICK, NO!
[CRASH]
Timmy: I WISH I KNEW
WHAT KIND OF GIFTS
GIRLS LIKED.
HEY, DO GIRLS
LIKE STINK BOMBS?
NO!
WELL, HOW 'BOUT
DEAD FROGS?
[RIBBIT]
Timmy: UH, NO.
GIRLS DON'T LIKE 'EM
AND NEITHER DO I.
Wanda: SORRY,
SWEETIE.
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
LIKE A GIRL.
FACE IT, TIMMY,
THE ONLY WAY YOU
COULD THINK LIKE A GIRL
IS IF YOU WISHED
YOU WERE ONE.
HA! LIKE I'D WISH
I WAS A GIRL.
HA HA! WHAT
A WASTE OF A WISH!
[LAUGHING]
YEAH, WHAT A WASTE.
YOU'RE RIGHT!
HOW STUPID!
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREAM]
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I DIDN'T WISH FOR THIS.
WELL, YOU SAID,
"I WISH," AND "GIRL."
OH, YEAH?
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
WHO CARES WHAT YOU THINK?
YOU'RE A GIRL NOW.
HEY! I THINK
LIKE A GIRL NOW.
I CAN TOTALLY
USE MY GIRL BRAIN
AND FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO GET TRIXIE
FOR HER BIRTHDAY.
OH, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA,
LITTLE GIRLY-GIRLY.
CAN I GET THE DOOR
FOR YOU, MA'AM?
[LAUGHING]
MA'AM!
OH, I'M OFF TO THE MALL
TO FIND SOMETHING
TRIXIE WILL LIKE.
BUT JUST SO YOU TWO
HAVE SOMETHING TO LAUGH
AT WHILE I'M GONE:
I WISH YOU
WERE A WOMAN
AND YOU WERE A MAN!
Both: WHAT?
YOU'RE MY GODPARENTS.
NO CHOICE.
CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU'RE NOW
COSMA AND WANDO.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
HOW COME I
SUDDENLY KNOW
WHICH BOY BANDS
ROCK OUT LOUD?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHY AM I TEMPTED
TO SCRATCH MYSELF
AND NOT CARE WHO SEES?
SEE YA!
THINK LIKE A GIRL.
THINK LIKE A--OOH!
THE COMIC BOOK STORE!
DO I STILL LIKE COMICS?
MUSCULAR GUYS IN SPANDEX
FIGHTING CRIME,
COOL!
UH, RIGHT?
ARE YOU SEEING
WHAT I'M SEEING?
YEAH! DUDE--
A GIRL WHO ACTUALLY
LIKES COMIC BOOKS.
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I'M GONNA
STARE AT HER
UNTIL SHE FEELS
SO AWKWARD
SHE HAS TO TALK TO ME.
WHAT? A.J.,
SNAP OUT OF IT.
NO!
I'VE LOST HIM!
[SOBS]
A.J.,
COME BACK!
Timmy: COOL!
SKULL SQUISHER
NUMBER 3,
AND THERE'S
ONLY ONE LEFT!
HEY! THAT'S MINE!
LET GO!
IT'S MINE! MINE!
[LAUGHING]
TRIXIE TANG?
NO, I'M IN HERE
BY ACCIDENT.
UNDERSTAND?
ACCIDENT.
IF WORD GETS OUT
I LIKE BOY STUFF,
ALL MY FRIENDS
WILL THINK I'M WEIRD.
PLEASE, PLEASE,
KEEP IT OUR SECRET,
GIRL TO GIRL.
WELL, OK.
DEAL.
YOU'RE MY NEW
BEST FRIEND.
OW!
WELL, YOU KNOW ME.
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M TIM--ANTHA?
OK, TIMANTHA.
MEET ME OUTSIDE
SCHMOOKIEDALES IN AN HOUR.
WE CAN MALL AND STUFF.
WOW! SHE LIKES
BOY STUFF, TOO.
UH...HI.
DEAD FROG?
DON'T DO IT!
IT'S A TRAP!
UGH!
BOY OR GIRL,
THAT'S STILL GROSS!
[SIRENS BLARE ON TV]
[BURPS]
ARE YOU READY YET?
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
MEET TIMMY AT THE MALL
15 MINUTES AGO.
OH! WHAT DO YOU THINK,
THIS OR THIS?
WHICH GOES BETTER
WITH MY EYES?
JUST PICK SOMETHING.
OH, I GIVE UP!
[SPLASH]
[SCREAM]
WOULD IT KILL YOU
TO LEAVE THE LID DOWN?
TO LOOK BEFORE YOU SIT?
[BURPS]
Timmy: WOW,
THIS FEELS GREAT!
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE SCRUBBING
ALL YOUR TROUBLES AWAY.
AND THEY'RE SHOWING
MY FAVORITE SOAP OPERA.
THIS PLACE RULES!
IF ONLY I COULD MEET
A BOY CONFIDENT ENOUGH
TO ADMIT HE LIKES
KISSY KISSY, GOO GOO,
I'D GO OUT WITH HIM
EVEN IF HE WORE
A STUPID PINK HAT.
REALLY?
BUT I'LL BET HE'D
NEVER COME IN HERE.
WELL, HE SHOULD.
IF BOYS DID
MORE GIRL STUFF,
THEN GIRLS WOULD BE ABLE
TO DO MORE BOY STUFF.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
TRIXIE?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
COME ON!
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
WHERE GIRLS
FEAR TO TREAD.
Chester: GIRLS!
DEAD FROG?
YECCH!
COOL!
AAH!
NO, WAIT!
I'M DOING THIS
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
STOP RESISTING.
RUN!
Chester: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S UP WITH THOSE GIRLS,
BUT WE'RE SAFE IN HERE.
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'RE OVERREACTING?
DUDE,
BOYS LIKE COMICS,
GIRLS LIKE DOLLS.
BOYS LIKE VIDEO GAMES,
GIRLS LIKE MAKEUP.
WE'RE DIFFERENT!
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
DIFFERENT BATHROOMS.
[FLUSH]
UM...AM I
IN THE WRONG ROOM?
[SHRIEKS]
NOTHING MAKES
SENSE ANYMORE.
FROG?
IT WAS NICE
MEETING YOU, TRIXIE.
YOU KNOW, ALL WEEK
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN ASKING ME
WHAT I WANTED
FOR MY BIRTHDAY,
AND YOU'VE
GIVEN IT TO ME.
I HAVE?
YOU'VE GIVEN ME A FRIEND
WHO LIKES ME FOR WHO I AM.
THAT'S ALL YOU WANTED
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY,
A FRIEND?
YEP!
SOMEONE WHO
ISN'T AFRAID TO SAY,
"HEY, I LIKE
KISSY KISSY, GOO GOO
AND  SKULL SQUISHER!"
IF YOU WERE A BOY,
I'D TOTALLY DATE YOU.
SEE YOU AT MY PARTY. BYE!
OH, YOU'LL SEE ME,
ALL RIGHT.
[MUSIC AND LAUGHTER]
OK, IT'S PARTY TIME!
I WISH I WAS A BOY AGAIN.
HEY,
WHAT ABOUT US?
AREN'T YOU
GONNA CHANGE US?
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH!
BLAH, HAH!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
TRIXIE!
THANKS, UH...
WHO ARE THEY?
WHO CARES?
RIGHT.
SEE, I TOLD YOU FIREWOOD
WAS THE PERFECT GIFT.
IS SHE HERE?
DID YOU CHECK?
I'M SORRY, THAT'S ALL
THE GUESTS, MISS TANG.
NOBODY NAMED TIMANTHA
IS AT THIS PARTY.
Timmy: HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
TRIXIE!
TIMMY!
DUDE,
WHERE'S YOUR GIFT?
I BROUGHT A SPECIAL
KIND OF GIFT,
SOMETHING YOU CAN'T WRAP
UP AND PUT IN A BOX.
IS IT
A DEADLY GERM?
A GHOST?
NOPE, EVEN BETTER
THAN A DEADLY GERM
OR A GHOST.
TRIXIE, AHEM, BLAH--
WHAT YOU KNOW.
I LIKE YOU
FOR WHO YOU ARE.
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH--
NOT FOR WHAT EVERYONE
EXPECTS YOU TO BE...
A FRIEND TO YOU.
SOMEONE WHO ISN'T
AFRAID TO SAY,
"HEY, I LIKE
KISSY KISSY, GOO GOO
AND  SKULL SQUISHER."
OH, MY GOSH!
THAT IS SO SWEET.
[GASPS]
BUT, UH...
THAT'S WHAT
I HAVE GIRLFRIENDS FOR.
SECURITY!
HUH?
BYE, TIMMY TURNER!
HEY!
YOU REMEMBERED MY NAME!
TOLD YOU
SHE'D WANT A GIFT.
IT WORKED!
BECAUSE I TREATED
TRIXIE LIKE A PERSON
INSTEAD OF JUST A GIRL,
SHE REMEMBERED MY NAME.
BUT SHE CATAPULTED YOU
OUT OF THE PARTY.
YEAH, BUT SHE
DID IT WITH LOVE.
AND THAT NEVER
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
IF YOU HADN'T
MADE ME A GIRL.
THANKS. BUT DON'T EVER
DO IT AGAIN!
DEAL!
I WISH YOU GUYS WERE BACK
TO THE WAY YOU WERE BORN.
WHAT?
THIS IS THE NOSE
I WAS BORN WITH.
CAN'T A GUY
DO SOMETHING
TO MAKE HIMSELF
LOOK PRETTY?
BLAH, BLAH--
BLAH!
BLAH, BLAH--BLAH!
WELL, YOUR PARENTS
DON'T EXPECT YOU HOME
FOR A FEW HOURS.
WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO NOW?
AHH! IT'S LIKE THEY'RE
SCRUBBING ALL MY TROUBLES AWAY.
I'VE NEVER MET A BOY
SENSITIVE ENOUGH
TO WALK IN HERE
BY HIMSELF.
I TOTALLY WANT YOU
TO DATE MY DAUGHTER.
NO, HE SHOULD
DATE MINE!
I'M SO PROUD
OF TIMMY.
YEAH!
HE FINALLY
FIGURED OUT
THAT WOMEN LOVE
SENSITIVITY.
AW!
AND IF YOU CAN FAKE THAT,
YOU'RE IN! OHH!
Man on TV:
I'VE GOT BAD NEWS.
RODERICK ASKED FOR A RAISE,
AND HE'S OFF THE SHOW--
I MEAN, FELL DOWN
AN ELEVATOR SHAFT!
Women: RODERICK, NO!
HEY, WHO WANTS
TO WATCH WRESTLING?
Women: WE DO!
Announcer: AND RODERICK
HAS HIS EVIL TWIN RODERICK
IN A TOE HOLD!
All: RODERICK, NO!
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--