3 F1
♪♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪♪
♪♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪♪
♪♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪♪
BAD TWERP!
♪♪ DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪♪
♪♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪♪
♪♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO'LL GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪♪
♪♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY... ♪♪
♪♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE A KID ♪♪
♪♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
YEAH,
RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
NICKELODEON
AND U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
COCK-A-DOODLE...
WHATEVER.
[ALARM GOES OFF]
[YAWN!]
HERE WE GO.
ANOTHER BORING DAY.
SPORTS. SAME.
NEWS. SAME.
WEATHER. HEY!
WHAT?!
SAME.
SEE YA.
MAN, THIS TV SHOW
SURE IS BORING.
GUESS WHAT BORING MOVIE
WE RENTED?
THE BORING DOG
WHO COULD SHOOT
BORING HOOP.
Announcer:
DETECTIVE RYAN McCAIN
IS A LOOSE CANNON COP
WHO DOESN'T PLAY
BY THE RULES IN...
UH! EGAD!
IN MY ADVANCED STATE
OF LETHARGY,
I MUST HAVE GRABBED
SOMETHING INTERESTING
BY MISTAKE!
COME ON, GUYS!
CAN WE WATCH IT?
PLEASE! PLEASE! PLEASE!
WOW! THIS MOVIE IS
VIOLENT  AND STUPID!
I KNOW. I'D HAVE
SETTLED FOR JUST ONE.
AH! HAH! MY BRAINS!
BABBLE AND DROOL!
Timmy:
POW! PSSH! BOOM!
PSSH! BEE WOO WOO!
VRUH! BEE-WOO-WOW!
POWWAH-HAH!
TIMMY TURNER IS
A LOOSE CANNON COP ON THE EDGE,
WHO DOESN'T
PLAY BY THE RULES.
BOOM! HA HA!
ACTION MOVIES
ARE AWESOME!
I KNOW, BUT IT  WAS
JUST A MOVIE.
SO WHAT? IN THAT MOVIE,
LIFE WAS EXCITING.
ACTION EVERYWHERE
YA LOOK.
I WANT A LIFE
LIKE THAT!
BUT, TIMMY,
THAT WOULD BE DANGEROUS.
NOT TO ME!
I'D BE THE HERO,
AND NOTHING BAD
EVER HAPPENS
TO THE HERO!
I WISH MY LIFE
WAS EXACTLY LIKE
AN ACTION MOVIE!
ACTION...[YAWN]...
MOVIE...[SNORE].
COCK-A-DOODLE...AAH!
[ALARM GOES OFF]
GOOD MORNING,
MR. TURNER!
Cosmo's voice:
WE SCHEDULED YOU FOR
A DEATH CALL AT 7:00 SHARP!
COOL!
I MEAN...THAT WAS CLOSE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT YOU WISHED FOR.
YOUR LIFE IS NOW
AN ACTION MOVIE.
AWESOME!
HOLD ON, BIG GUY.
YOU CAN'T GO OUT
AND BEAT BADDIES
IN YOUR PJs!
BOOYAH! AWESOME!
I'VE GOT 5 O'CLOCK SHADOW!
AND IT'S ONLY 7 A.M.
THAT REMINDS ME.
HERE, TIMMY.
YOU MIGHT
NEED THIS.
A WATCH?
IT'S MORE THAN
JUST A WATCH.
IT'S A MULTIPURPOSE
WRIST COMMUNICATOR,
SO YOU CAN STAY
IN TOUCH WITH US.
WHOA!
I'M LATE FOR BREAKFAST!
SPORTS...ACTIONY!
NEWS...ACTIONY!
WEATHER...HEY!
WHAT?
A 100 PERCENT
CHANCE...
OF ACTION!
On tape: PASS THE BUTTER.
THIS TAPE WILL NOW
SELF-DESTRUCT.
IT'S BUTTERIN' TIME.
OH, NO!
I'M LATE FOR SCHOOL.
EXPLOSIONS, VILLAINS,
AND JET PACKS
OUT OF NOWHERE!
I SHOULD HAVE WISHED
FOR MY LIFE TO BE
LIKE THIS YEARS AGO.
IT'S QUIET IN HERE...
TOO QUIET.
TIMMY'S REALLY
WHOOPIN' TUSHY.
YEAH, BUT I GOT
A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
THINGS ALWAYS GO
FROM BAD TO WORSE
IN ACTION MOVIES.
REALLY? LIKE HOW?
LIKE THIS! AH HA HA HA!
COOL! I WISH I HAD
MORE NINJAS TO FIGHT.
COSMO! WANDA!
WHERE ARE YOU?
Wanda: TIMMY! TIMMY!
COME IN!
Cosmo:
ARE YOU CALLING TIMMY?
TELL HIM COSMO SAYS HI.
SHUSH. TIMMY,
YOU HAVE TO SAVE US!
COME ON, COME ON.
TELL HIM I SAID HI.
WE'VE BEEN
FAIRYNAPPED!
WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE WE ARE.
TIMMY? IS THAT YOU?
HI, TIMMY!
THERE ISN'T
MUCH TIME.
I'VE GOTTA SAVE THEM!
BOY, THIS MOVIE
JUST GETS BETTER AND BETTER.
LET'S SEE. IF I USE
THE COMMUNICATOR
TO TRIANGULATE THE SIGNAL
FROM THEIR TRANSMISSION,
I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO PINPOINT THEIR LOCATION.
AH-HA! BINGO!
NOW I JUST HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHO'S BEHIND ALL THIS.
LET ME SAVE YOU
THE TROUBLE, PUNY MAN.
I, JORGEN VON STRANGLE,
VERY TOUGH FAIRY
AND OBLIGATORY
ACTION MOVIE VILLAIN,
AND MY KITTY,
MR. TOOLITOES...
KITTY, KITTY, KITTY...
ARE GOING TO KIDNAP
ALL THE FAIRIES IN THE WORLD
AND THEN,
USING MY BRILLIANT
MAGIC SIPHONING INVENTION,
I WILL SUCK
THE MAGIC OUT OF THEIR
PATHETIC FAIRY BODIES...
AND TRANSFER IT
INTO MY WAND!
AH-HA HA HA HA!
TIMMY! HELP!
HE'S TAKING OUR MAGIC!
EHHHH, I LIKE
OLDER WOMAN...
BUT WAIT...WAIT...STOP!
AH-HA HA HA HA HA!
SOON THE WORLD
WILL BE MINE!
[COUGHING]
THE HORROR!
THE PURE, UNADULTERATED,
PG-13 HORROR!
Cosmo: YOU MUSTN'T
BLAME YOURSELF,
EVEN THOUGH IT IS
ALL YOUR FAULT.
Wanda: TIMMY, REMEMBER...
WE LOVE YOU...
Timmy:
NOOOOOOOOOO!
I GOOFED UP THIS WORLD.
NOW I'M UNGOOFING IT.
YES, THAT'S IT.
HEH HEH HEH.
DRAIN THOSE FAIRIES
OF EVERY LAST SPRINKLE
OF MAGIC
MY BEAUTIFUL MACHINE.
EH! OFF WITH YOU!
GO DO...KITTY THINGS.
I WANT TO BE ALONE
WITH MY WONDERFUL INVENTION.
HA HA!
OH, WHO IS
THE PRETTY MACHINE?
YOU ARE! OH, YES YOU ARE.
YES...
EGGGH! SOON ALL
THE WORLD'S MAGIC
WILL BE
AT MY DISPOSAL,
AND THEN I SHALL
RULE THE WORLD!
NOT SO FAST,
JORGEN VON POOP-HEAD!
[CRASH!]
SET THE FAIRIES FREE
AND GIMME BACK
MY GODPARENTS!
YOU FOOL.
BY DRAINING THESE FAIRIES
OF THEIR MAGIC,
I HAVE DONE
WHAT I THOUGHT
WAS IMPOSSIBLE.
I'VE FOUND A WAY
TO MAKE MYSELF
EVEN MORE POWERFUL!
OH, CRUD!
NOW-WITNESS-
MY-POWER!
PREPARE FOR YOUR...
DOOM!
OH, DOUBLE CRUD.
HE'S GONE MAD
WITH POWER.
PATHETIC HUMAN!
HE'S TOO POWERFUL.
I CAN'T DODGE HIM
FOREVER.
IF ONLY I COULD
GET TO THAT MACHINE.
OH, TRIPLE CRUD.
IT IS OVER, TURNER.
PREPARE TO CHANGE
YOUR NAME TO
THE LATE TIMMY TURNER.
AAHHHH!
AAHH! MR. TOOLITOES?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AH! GET OFF ME! AH!
MUSCLES-TOO-HUGE.
CAN'T REACH FACE!
HEY, JAR-HEAD.
LOSE SOMETHING?
NOOOO!
WHY DID I PUT
A REVERSE SWITCH
ON IT?
'CAUSE THIS IS
MY MOVIE.
UH-OH, IT'S OVERLOADING!
EEHH! MY MUSCLES,
MY BEAUTIFUL MUSCLES!
MY HEART,
SHE IS GLAD.
BUT MY ART...
SHE WILL SUFFER.
GUYS.
WE'RE YOUNG!
WE'RE MAGIC!
AND WE'RE NOT DUST.
THANK GOODNESS.
I WAS ALLERGIC
TO MYSELF.
GUYS, I'M SO SORRY.
MY SELFISH WISH
ALMOST...
NOOOOO!
RUINED EVERYTHING
FOR EVERYBODY.
[CRASH!]
CAN YOU EVER
FORGIVE ME?
ALREADY DONE, TIMMY.
WE LOVE YOU!
SO, TIMMY,
GOT ANY MORE WISHES?
I SURE DO.
NOOOOO!
I WISH THE WORLD
WAS BACK TO ITS
NORMAL, BORING,
SAFE SELF.
[CRASH!]
YOU'VE GOT IT!
COCK-A-DOODLE...
DOO?
WHEW!
COOL! SAME BORING HOUSE.
SAME BORING BREAKFAST.
SAME BORING LIFE.
HEY, WHERE ARE MY
SAME BORING PARENTS?
[GUNSHOT]
OH, NO!
[CAR SCREECHES,
CRASH!]
THAT RYAN McCAIN
IS A LOOSE CANNON COP
ON THE EDGE!
BOOM! YEAH!
THIS IS COOL!
I WISH MY LIFE
COULD BE AN
ACTION MOVIE!
TRUST ME.
NO, YOU DON'T.
THAT'S IT!
YOU'RE OFF THE CASE!
HIYA!
WHO'S UP FOR
A NICE, SAFE
DISEASE OF THE WEEK
MOVIE?
OOH! I AM.
I THOUGHT SO.
[BOOM!]
[BELL RINGS]
WELL, CLASS,
THE TEST RESULTS ARE IN...
AND, AS ALWAYS,
AJ GETS AN A.
ALL RIGHT!
ANOTHER A!
I'M GONNA ADD THIS
TO MY "A" COLLECTION.
[GROANS]
WHAT'S WRONG, TIMMY?
AW...I DIDN'T STUDY.
WELL, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE STUDYING
ALL WEEK WITH COSMO.
WHAT WERE
YOU GUYS DOING?
HEY! WANNA PLAY
THE "NOT STUDY GAME?"
HOW DO YOU PLAY?
YOU'RE ALREADY
PLAYING!
YAAAAAY!
F?!
MY PARENTS ARE GONNA
TOTALLY KILL ME!
GO AJ! GO AJ!...
UH-HUH, UH-HUH, UH-HUH!
ALL RIGHT,
I HEARD!
THE WHOLE SCHOOL
HEARD YOU!
GIVE IT A REST!
THERE'S NO NEED
FOR JEALOUSY, TIMMY.
I'M NOT JEALOUS.
I'M JUST SICK OF
CROCKER FAILING ME.
IF YOU STUDIED,
YOU PROBABLY
WOULDN'T FAIL.
I'LL BET I COULD
HELP YOU GET THAT "F"
ALL THE WAY UP
TO A "D".
GEE...
THANKS A LOT,
SUPERNERD.
BUT SHOULDN'T YOU BE
RESCUING A CALCULATOR
FROM A TREE?
SPELL "CALCULATOR".
C...A...L...Q...
LATER.
SON, DO YOU KNOW WHY
WE'RE DISAPPOINTED
IN THIS "F"?
BECAUSE I CAN DO
BETTER THAN THAT?
WHAT?
YOU CAN?
WHAT A RELIEF!
WE WERE GOING
TO BLAME OURSELVES.
YOU MARCH RIGHT UP
TO YOUR ROOM
AND APPLY YOURSELF!
CHAPTER ONE.
I'M DONE.
LET'S PLAY
THE "NOT STUDY GAME."
ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS GET THE TURBO LASER
HYPERBOLE GENERATOR
TO ACTIVATE ZARKON'S
PRINCIPLE OF THRUST
AND CREATE A WORM HOLE
LARGE ENOUGH
TO BREAK
THE SPACE-TIME CONTINUUM!
[PHONE RINGS]
DARN IT.
HELLO.
HI, TIMMY. I...
Crash Nebula video game:
GAME OVER!
BUT I SHALL RETURN.
ARE YOU PLAYING
THE CRASH NEBULA
VIDEO GAME?
SHOULDN'T YOU
BE STUDYING?
WHAT ARE YOU,
MY MOM?
HEY, GENIUS.
YOU MISSED THE RECEIVER.
NOPE, STILL OFF.
JUST 'CAUSE AJ
GETS As ALL THE TIME,
HE THINKS HE KNOWS
EVERYTHING!
BUT HE DOESN'T.
HEY, BUT I COULD.
RIGHT?
I WISH THAT I KNEW
EVERYTHING!
OK...
[APPLAUSE]
LET'S SEE
HOW SMART YOU ARE.
WHAT FLAMMABLE...
[BUZZ!]
PUDDING!
WHAT FLAMMABLE SUBSTANCE
IS THE MOST ABUNDANT
ELEMENT IN THE UNIVERSE?
[BUZZ!]
TIMMY?
HYDROGEN.
AND THE STUDY OF FISH?
ICHTHYOLOGY.
AND A CHINESE MAMMAL
WHO EATS MAINLY BAMBOO,
IS THE GIANT PANDA.
CORRECT. IT'S OFFICIAL!
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING!
[BUZZ BUZZ!]
I LIKE MAKING
THE BUZZY NOISE.
[BELL RINGS]
WELL, WE'RE TWO DAYS AWAY
FROM THE ACADEMIC BRAINATHON
AND I DON'T SUPPOSE
ANYONE OTHER THAN AJ READ...
ABOUT THE TEXANS' WAR
FOR INDEPENDENCE
FROM MEXICO?
REMEMBER? THE ALAMO.
YES, THE ALAMO!
CIRCA 1836. 13 DAYS.
IT GAINED TEXAS
ITS INDEPENDENCE
AND ADDED MORE THAN...
...A MILLION SQUARE MILES
TO AMERICA.
ACTUALLY A MILLION,
FIVE THOUSAND AND TWO.
HE'S RIGHT.
MAY I BORROW
YOUR "A"?
HERE YOU GO.
[KIDS CHEER]
GRRRR!
WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT?
LET'S SEE, HOW CAN I
PHRASE THIS ELOQUENTLY?
OH, YEAH!
JUST SMOKIN' YOU
AT YOUR OWN GAME.
GO TIMMY, GO TIMMY,
GO TIMMY!
YEAH, TIMMY, GO.
SO YOU'RE SMART
FOR A DAY.
YOU THINK
ANYBODY'S IMPRESSED?
WOW, TIMMY,
I'M IMPRESSED!
HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE TO BE IN OUR
ACADEMIC BRAINATHON?
WE COULD SURE USE YOU
AS A FIRST CHAIR.
BUT...I'VE ALWAYS
BEEN FIRST CHAIR.
OH, AJ, YOU'LL
STILL BE ON THE TEAM.
YOU'LL JUST BE
IN THE NOT-AS-IMPORTANT
SECOND CHAIR.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
ONE CHAIR. DUH!
[GIGGLING]
[FLIPPING TV CHANNELS]
OOOH! THE GAME!
DREK.
OOOH!
THE OTHER GAME!
GARBAGE.
OOOOH! GOVERNMENT FUNDED
TELEVISION!
AWWWW!
OH, TIMMY,
MY LITTLE PRODIGY,
I MADE YOU...
A HOT FUDGE SUNDAE,
TEEMING WITH CHOLESTEROL,
SATURATED FATS,
ARTIFICIAL PRESERVATIVES.
GEE, THANKS.
Wanda and Cosmo:
GASP!
UH...SON?
I WAS FILLING OUT
YOUR APPLICATION
TO HARVARD
LIKE YOU TOLD ME TO
AND...
YOU MISSPELLED COLLEGE.
WAY TO GO.
GASP!
WOW! IT SURE IS LATE!
TIME FOR BED, CHAMP.
GENIUSES GET
TO STAY UP LATE.
OH, NOT WHEN
THEY'RE 10 YEARS OLD,
THEY DON'T.
WELL, IF YOUR MATH
IS AS GOOD AS DAD'S
SPELLING,
I MAY ALREADY HAVE
TURNED 21 FOR ALL YOU KNOW!
GASP!
THOSE GASPING MICE
ARE RIGHT!
YOU ARE WAY
OUT OF LINE!
YOU CAN MAKE FUN
OF MY MATH SKILLS
UNTIL IT'S 13 O'CLOCK,
BUT YOU DO NOT ACT
LIKE A SMARTY-PANTS.
CAN YOU PROVE
I WAS A SMARTY-PANTS?
EEEHH WHA...?
IN AN INFINITE UNIVERSE,
WHERE REALITY IS
INTERPRETED THROUGH
OUR CONTINUOUSLY
FLUCTUATING PERCEPTION,
PROVIDING ANY KIND
OF ABSOLUTE DEFINITIVE PROOF
OF ANYTHING
BECOMES LITTLE MORE
THAN SPECULATION
BASED ON RANDOM DATA.
UH...IN AN
INFINITE WHAT?
ERRR...MY BRAIN HURTS.
[BELL RINGS]
WELCOME TO THE ANNUAL
DIMMSDALE ACADEMIC BRAINATHON!
TODAY'S COMPETITION IS
BETWEEN SNERD ELEMENTARY
AND DIMMSDALE ELEMENTARY!
[CROWD CHEERS]
HERE'S YOUR FIRST QUESTION...
THIS PACIFIC NORTHWEST INSECT
CAN GROW TO A LENGTH
OF 8 INCHES.
DIMMSDALE!
WELL, IT'S VERY OBVIOUS.
THE ANSWER IS...UH...
DUH?
UH, NO, I'M SORRY.
DUH IS INCORRECT.
[BUZZ!]
SNERD!
THE BANANA SLUG.
FIRST POINT
GOES TO SNERD!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UM...BUILDING
DRAMATIC TENSION?
NEXT QUESTION.
WHAT IS THE CAPITOL
OF IDAHO?
[BUZZ!]
DIMMSDALE.
UH...IT'S...
IT'S...UH...I GOTTA GO.
DIMMSDALE!
BOISE!
CORRECT!
POINT FOR DIMMSDALE.
COSMO...WANDA...
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ANYMORE!
WELCOME TO MY WORLD.
NOW THAT YOU'RE
IN A COMPETITION,
YOU CAN'T USE
THE KNOWLEDGE TO WIN.
THAT'S CHEATING!
THE WISH IS OFF!
WHAT? WHY DIDN'T
YOU TELL ME THAT?
WE FIGURED YOU'D KNOW,
MR. "I KNOW EVERYTHING
IN THE UNIVERSE."
I GOT HERE BECAUSE
OF A MAGIC WISH.
AJ WORKED HARD
FOR IT...
AND I TOOK IT AWAY
FROM HIM.
AND THAT COMPLETES
OUR FIRST ROUND
WITH SNERD LEADING
BY 8 POINTS.
WE'LL TAKE A SHORT INTERMISSION
AND THEN CONTINUE.
HEY.
WHAT? DID YOU GET
THE QUESTIONS WRONG
SO YOU CAN LOOK LIKE
THE BIG HERO
WITH A COME-FROM-
BEHIND-VICTORY?
I'M SORRY I WAS
SUCH A JERK TO YOU.
I WAS JUST JEALOUS.
AND, IN AN
IMPOSSIBLE-TO-
EXPLAIN WAY,
I SORTA CHEATED TO MAKE
MYSELF SEEM SMARTER
THAN I REALLY AM.
YEAH, WELL...
MAYBE YOU WOULD HAVE
LET ME HELP YOU STUDY
IF I HADN'T BEEN
SO BUSY GLOATING.
BUT YOU DESERVE
TO GLOAT!
EVERYBODY'S
GOT SOMETHING
THEY'RE GOOD AT.
YOU'RE GOOD AT
STUDYING AND I'M
GOOD AT...UH...
PLAYING VIDEO GAMES.
DID YOU SEE HOW MUCH
FASTER YOU WERE THAN ME
ON THAT BUZZER?
MAYBE, BUT IT
DOESN'T MATTER.
I CAN'T WIN
BY CHEATING.
I'M GONNA
DISQUALIFY MYSELF.
EXCUSE ME. I...
HE WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT HE WANTS TO
SWITCH CHAIRS WITH ME
AND GET BACK
IN THE GAME. RIGHT?
UH...YEAH!
WHAT HE SAID.
HE'S THE SMART ONE.
AND YOU'RE
THE FAST ONE.
I'LL BE THE BRAINS,
YOU BE THE REFLEXES.
DEAL?
DEAL!
WELCOME BACK.
THE SCORE IS 5 TO 13,
WITH SNERD IN THE LEAD.
LET'S BEGIN.
THE SCIENTIFIC NAME
FOR "SPIDER".
IT'S ARACHNID.
CORRECT!
[BUZZ!]
INFRALAPSARIANISM!
CORRECT!
ANOTHER POINT
FOR DIMMSDALE.
[BUZZ!]
GLUTEUS MAXIMUS!
CORRECT!
[BUZZ!]
THE ANSWER IS 1,952.
CORRECT!
NICE BUTTON-HITTING,
PAL.
DON'T THANK ME.
THANK THE "NOT STUDY GAME!"
WELL, WITH A DEAD-HEAT SCORE
OF 99 TO 99,
WE MOVE ON TO
OUR FINAL QUESTION.
THE CATEGORY IS...POTPOURRI.
A QUESTION
ABOUT SMELLY STUFF?
A QUESTION THAN CAN BE
ABOUT ANYTHING.
DESCRIBE THE PROPULSION
SYSTEM USED ON...
THE SPACESHIP
USED BY CRASH NEBULA?
I DON'T KNOW THAT!
[BUZZZZZ!]
AND DIMMSDALE!
CRASH NEBULA'S
CROSS-DIMENSIONAL
PROPULSION SYSTEM
USES A TURBO-LASER
HYPERBOLE GENERATOR
TO ACTIVATE ZARKON'S
PRINCIPLE OF THRUST
TO CREATE A WORM HOLE
LARGE ENOUGH
TO SHATTER
THE SPACE-TIME CONTINUUM!
CORRECT!
DIMMSDALE WINS!
Both: YES!
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS
AND CHEERS]
CONGRATULATIONS,
TIMMY TURNER!
ACTUALLY, I'D LIKE
THIS TO GO TO MY PAL AJ.
HE DID THE WORK.
I JUST MADE
THE BUZZY NOISES.
YEEEAH!
I GOTTA WORK
ON THE GLOATING.
[TIMMY SIGHS]
Wanda: WE'RE GLAD
YOU'RE BACK TO NORMAL,
TIMMY.
YEAH!
WE MISSED THE NICE,
LESS SMART YOU.
Dad: AH HA!
AFTER RE-READING
OUR PARENTING BOOKS,
WE THINK WE'VE GOT
A RESPONSE TO YOUR
SASSINESS.
YES!
WE HIRED A LAWYER!
WELL, THAT WON'T
BE NECESSARY.
I'M SORRY
I WAS A JERK,
AND I THINK YOU HAVE
THE GROUNDS TO...
WELL, GROUND ME.
I WAS A CREEP,
A BIG, SMART CREEP.
YOU FIGURED THAT OUT
ON YOUR OWN?
WELL, I STILL GET PAID.
WE GROUNDED
THE SMART KID!
GO PARENTS!
UH-HUH! GO PARENTS!
INDEED! MM-HMM!
NOTHING TO DO NOW
EXCEPT STUDY.
GOOD IDEA, TIMMY!
COSMO?
Cosmo: INDEED!