2 F1
♪♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪♪
♪♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪♪
♪♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪♪
BED, TWERP!
♪♪ DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪♪
♪♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪♪
♪♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO'LL GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪♪
♪♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY... ♪♪
♪♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE A KID ♪♪
♪♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
YEAH, RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
NICKELODEON
AND U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
[TWEETS]
OH, BOY! TWO MORE MINUTES
AND I'LL HAVE
THE VERY FIRST TICKETS
FORTHE  CRASH NEBULA MOVIE!
IT IS TIME?
DID WE SUCCEED?
YES, MY FRIENDS!
BEHOLD!
AFTER SUCCESSFULLY
CAMPING OUT ALL NIGHT,
WE WILL MAKE HISTORY
AS THE FIRST KIDS TO SEE
CRASH NEBULA, THE MOVIE!
AFTER ME.
HEY! WHO
THE HECK ARE YOU?
[TIMMY READING]
I DON'T CARE
HOW RICH YOU ARE!
WE WERE HERE FIRST!
FINALLY.
TICKETS, PLEASE.
HOW MANY?
ALL OF THEM.
(KIDS CHEERING)
OH! PUH-LEASE!
THEY'RE NOT FOR
YOU UNSEEMLY URCHINS.
I NEED ALL THE EXTRA SEATS
FOR MY PILES OF MONEY.
YOU'RE KICKING
VIRTUAL BUTT IN
THIS VIDEO GAME!
AND IF I GET THE HIGH SCORE,
I'LL FINALLY GET MY NAME
ON THE BATHROOM DOOR!
I WIN.
SOMETHING'S FISHY.
TROUT?
CATFISH?
SEA MONKEY?
HOW CAN THAT REMY KID GET
SO MUCH BETTER THAN ME--
AT EVERYTHING?
YEAH. AND
HE'S EVERYWHERE.
I KNOW ONE SPECIAL
PLACE WE CAN GO WHERE
HE COULD NEVER EVER BE.
AHH! JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
SOME GOOD, OLD-FASHIONED,
SUPERHERO, BASHING EVIL ACTION!
THE GOLDEN GUT!
ACTIVATE UTILITY CLEFT.
♪♪ THE CRIMSON CHIN! ♪♪
DON'T WORRY, C.C.
I'LL--
I'LL SAVE YOU.
WAY TO GO, CLEFT,
RICH BOY
CHIN WONDER!
AWRIGHT, LET'S SEE HOW
THE RICHER HALF LIVES...
WELL, UH...
UH...EEE...
SON.
OH, RIGHT! RIGHT.
IT CERTAINLY WAS THRILLING
SPENDING OUR DAILY
TWO MINUTES WITH YOU.
WELL, TIME IS MONEY.
MONEY? WHERE?
HAVE A NICE TIME WITH YOUR
ODDLY COLORED FERRET, SON!
I THINK I KNOW
HOW REMY'S PULLING
ALL THIS STUFF OFF!
REMY BUXAPLENTY HAS
A FAIRY GODPARENT!
YOU KNEW?
I'M SORRY, TIMMY.
IT'S IN  DA RULES.
WE CAN'T TELL YOU
ABOUT OTHER KIDS
WITH FAIRY GODPARENTS.
YA HAVE TO FIGURE
IT OUT ON YOUR OWN.
DO YOU KNOW THIS FAIRY?
NO! NO! NOPE!
NOT AT ALL.
NO IDEA. CLUELESS.
YOU KNOW HIM.
NUH-UH.
I WISH YOU'D TELL.
OH, DARN IT!
HIS NAME IS
WANDISIMO MAGNIFICO.
HE'S MY EX-BOYFRIEND.
SO!
TURNER HAS GODPARENTS, TOO!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
PERO, IT IS NOT PERMITTED.
IT IS IN THE RULES.
AND I AM A FAIRY
OF PRINCIPLES,
AND PRINCIPLES,
MUCH LIKE MY BICEPS,
ARE  MUY BONITO.
(REPEATS PHRASE IN SPANISH)
IF TURNER
HAS GODPARENTS,
HE COULD WISH HE
WAS RICHER THAN ME!
I WISH HIS GODPARENTS
WERE GONE!
I CANNOT.
FAIRIES CANNOT BE WISHED
AWAY BY OTHER FAIRIES.
FOR THAT WAY
LIES MADNESS.
AND MADNESS IS  MUY MALO.
GODPARENTS CAN
ONLY BE WISHED AWAY
BY THEIR GOD KID
OR IN A MAGICAL DUEL.
"GODPARENT
AGAINST GODPARENT.
"WINNER KEEPS
HIS FAIRIES, LOSER--"
AND BY LOSER,
I MEAN TURNER,
"FORGETS
HE EVER HAD THEM."
(LAUGHS)
TURNER.
BUXAPLENTY.
LET'S CUT
TO THE CHASE, SHALL WE?
YOU KNOW I HAVE
A FAIRY GODPARENT.
I KNOW YOU HAVE
FAIRY GODPARENTS.
WANDA, MY SWEET.
I HAVE MISSED YOU,
AS THE SUN MISSES THE DAWN...
WELL, THAT'S ALL
VERY FLATTERING--
BUT THAT'S MY HAND, PAL!
AND GUESS WHAT?
I DON'T NEED MAGIC
TO TURN IT INTO A FIST!
[GRUNTING]
WHEN I GET MY WAND,
OHH, YOU ARE IN FOR IT!
ARRGH!
YOU SEE HOW HE ALMOST
TURNED HIS HAND INTO A FIST?
I AM LUCKY TO BE ALIVE!
SO, HOW MUCH
WILL IT TAKE FOR ME
TO GET YOU TO WISH AWAY
YOUR FAIRY GODPARENTS? HMM?
YOU KNOW WHAT
STINKS ABOUT YOU,
REMY? YOU'RE RICH,
YOU HAVE GODPARENTS,
AND YOU'RE STILL
MISERABLE!
WHAT? YOU THINK
YOU'RE HAPPIER THAN ME?
DUDE, I  KNOW
I'M HAPPIER THAN YOU.
AND I'VE GOT
BETTER GODPARENTS.
WE SHALL SEE
ABOUT THAT, LITTLE MONKEY.
CALL IT.
I CALL "MAGICAL DUEL!"
[CHEERS]
All: DUEL! DUEL! DUEL! DUEL!
PUNY FAIRIES AND GENTLEMEN,
PREPARE FOR MAGICAL BATTLE!
(CHEERS)
THESE ARE THE RULES.
WINNER TAKES ALL.
LOSER WON'T RECALL.
BEST TWO OUT
OF THREE WINS!
WHAT? IF I LOSE,
I LOSE YOU FOREVER?
SO THERE'S
ABSOLUTELY NO PRESSURE!
YOUR VOICE.
IT IS LIKE THE CHORUS
OF A THOUSAND ANGELS.
YEAH, WELL, MY FOOT
IS GONNA FEEL
LIKE THE CHORUS
OF A THOUSAND--
REVENGE!
CHALLENGE ONE.
GODPARENTS MUST
BE ABLE TO RESCUE THEIR
KIDS FROM ANY DANGER!
IN THIS CASE...
A GIANT APE!
HAVE NO FEAR...
WANDISIMO IS HERE.
THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY
TO SOOTHE A SAVAGE BEAST...
YOU'RE GOING TO SING?
I MUST.
IT IS WHO I AM.
IT IS THE MAGIC
OF MY SOUL.
THE HANDSOME FAIRY HAS FAILED
TO RESCUE HIS GODCHILD!
[CROWD BOOS]
BUT HE IS STILL VERY SEXY!
[CROWD CHEERS]
THIS I CAN LIVE WITH.
AAAAAAAH!
MAKE IT STOP!
WE'VE GOTTA HELP TIMMY!
HMM. I NEED SOME THINKIN' FOOD!
GOOD JOB, HONEY,
DISTRACTING THAT APE.
HUH?
HEY! THAT MONKEY
ATE MY BANANA!
THE PUNY FAIRY HAS
RESCUED HIS GODCHILD!
TIMMY TURNER AND HIS
FAIRIES WIN ROUND ONE!
CHALLENGE TWO.
THE CHILD MUST NOW
HELP THE GODPARENTS
BY DISTRACTING A HUMAN ADULT
SO THEY DON'T SEE THEM
MAGICALLY DOUSE THIS FIRE.
NOW!
HEY, LOOK AT ME!
HEY, LOOK A UFO!
HEY, MISTER,
WANNA SEE A CARD TRICK?
UH-OH.
THIS IS PATHETIC.
WE WILL END THIS BEFORE YOU BURN
FAIRYWORLD TO THE GROUND.
NEXT CHILD.
LOOK! MONEY!
[SNIFFS, PANTS,
BARKS LIKE A DOG]
ROUND TWO
TO REMY BUXAPLENTY!
LOOK...WE CAN CALL
THIS A DRAW. RIGHT NOW!
I DON'T CARE IF
YOU HAVE A GODPARENT, REMY!
BUT I CARE IF YOU DO!
MY PARENTS
ARE NEVER HOME!
I NEVER GET TO SEE THEM!
WHY SHOULD
YOU GET REAL PARENTS
AND GODPARENTS
THAT LOVE YOU
WHEN I DON'T?!
IT IS TIME FOR THE TIE BREAKER!
[CHEERS]
EACH CHILD WILL DESCRIBE
AN IMAGINARY ANIMAL
AND THEN THEIR GODPARENTS
WILL TURN HIM INTO THAT ANIMAL.
THE GODCHILD WHO IS THE MOST
FANTASTIC ANIMAL WILL WIN.
I WISH I WAS A CRAB!
WITH TWO HEADS!
AHH!
TA-DA?
All: YAWN.
YEAH. GONNA
BE HARD TO BEAT THAT.
BUT JUST IN CASE...
I'VE GOT SOMETHING BETTER
THAN IMAGINATION!
HIGHLY PAID CONSULTANTS!
UH-HUH. YEAH?
HORNS OF A GOAT?
A BODY OF AN ANTELOPE?
HEAD OF A JACKELARF?
MM-HMM. V8 ENGINE.
ALL RIGHT!
WANDISIMO IS GONNA MAKE
REMY INTO AN AMAZING ANIMAL!
GUYS, DO SOMETHING!
IF ONLY THERE WAS
SOME WAY TO DISTRACT HIM!
OOH! OOH! I KNOW!
HEY, MUSCLES MAGOO!
LOOK AT ME.
I'M FANCY, AND MY LONG BLACK
HAIR FLOWS IN THE WIND.
STOP MAKING FUN
OF MY OUTER BEAUTY.
10 SECONDS LEFT!
WANDISIMO, DON'T LET
HIM DISTRACT YOU!
I'M STRONG, BUT I STILL
LOST MY WOMAN TO AN IDIOT!
5! 4!
HURRY UP!
CHUNKY HUNKY!
STOP!
MONKEY CHUNKY HUNKY!
I CANNOT CONCENTRATE!
3...2...
NOOOO!
Crowd: OOH!
[CROWD CHEERS]
HA! THE MOST
AMAZING ANIMAL EVER!
I WIN!
ACTUALLY, THE CHALLENGE WAS...
THE CHILD WHO
IS TURNED INTO THE MOST
FANTASTIC ANIMAL WINS.
SHE IS RIGHT!
TIMMY TURNER GETS
TO KEEP HIS GODPARENTS!
AND YOU LOSE YOURS!
ADIOS,
REMY BUXAPLENTY.
WE WILL NOT MEET AGAIN.
TIMMY, WHAT'S WRONG?
I FEEL SORT OF SORRY FOR REMY.
I WISH I COULD HELP HIM.
Both: WE CAN DO THAT.
I WISH REMY'S PARENTS HAD
MORE TIME TO SPEND WITH HIM!
WELL, WE COULD
BE HERE A WHILE.
I'LL COUNT THE MONEY!
AND I'LL COUNT THE MONEY!
AND I'LL FIND US
SOMETHING TO EAT!
HMM. GREAT IDEA, LIAM.
REMY. BUT IT'S A START.
WHY, HELLO THERE,
LITTLE FELLA.
YOU LOOK FAMILIAR.
LIKE A LONG LOST FRIEND
OR SOMETHING.
OH, WELL.
WHO WANTS TURTLE SOUP?
NO! I AM
TOO SEXY TO EAT!
Announcer: THE EVIL CLUTCHULACS
HAVE INVADED EARTH.
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
WHO CAN STOP THEM?
♪♪ CRASH NEBULA! ♪♪
Announcer:
YESIREE, FOLKS, IT'S...
THIS WEEKEND, ONE NIGHT ONLY,
AT THE DIMMSDALE DIMMADOME!
[ALL GASP]
Announcer: IT'S
A ONCE IN A LIFETIME,
SPACE-SKATING SPECTACULAR!
IT'S...
CRASH NEBULA
ON ICE!
WE SHOULD GET
OUR TICKETS RIGHT NOW!
HA!
DON'T SWEAT IT, GUYS!
I'VE TOTALLY
GOT IT HANDLED.
YOU SURE?
Announcer: YES...THERE
ARE THOUSANDS OF TICKETS
LEFT FOR  CRASH NEBULA
ON ICE!
SEE? NO PROBLEM!
LATER, TIMMY!
OK, GUYS,
TIME TO DO YOUR STUFF.
GONE FISHING?
BUT THEY ARE FISH!
HA! HA HA HA!
YOUR TURN!
THIS JUST IN...
I LIED.
THERE ARE ACTUALLY NO TICKETS
LEFT FOR  CRASH NEBULA ON ICE.
WHAT?!
HELLO, DIMMADOME
TICKET OFFICE.
HOW MAY I HELP YOU?
UH, YES, I'D LIKE
THREE TICKETS
FOR  CRASH NEBULA
ON ICE, PLEASE.
HA HA HA HA! ARE
YOU CRAZY? HA HA!
TICKETS FOR
CRASH NEBULA ON ICE.
HA HA! I'M SORRY, KID.
WE'RE SOLD OUT.
[BELL RINGS]
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T
GET OUR TICKETS, TIMMY!
DON'T WORRY, GUYS.
THERE'S ALWAYS A WAY
TO GET TICKETS.
FRANCIS' TOILET
OF TICKETS.
HOW MAY I HELP YOU?
THREE OF YOUR BEST SEATS
FOR  CRASH NEBULA.
ON ICE?
YEP.
$1,500.
THANK YOU VERY...WHAT?
WE DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF MONEY!
THAT'S FOR FREE.
WE CAN'T MISS THAT SHOW.
DUDE, RELAX.
I WILL GET
US THOSE TICKETS.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
MAKE THREE TICKETS
APPEAR BY MAGIC?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
I CAN'T JUST MAKE
THREE TICKETS
APPEAR LIKE MAGIC?
TIMMY, IT'S SOLD OUT!
IF WE GAVE YOU THREE
OF THE TICKETS,
IT MEANS WE'D BE TAKING
THEM AWAY FROM SOMEONE ELSE
WHO ALREADY HAS THEM!
AND THAT WOULD BE STEALING...
WHICH IS BAD.
I HAVE TO BUY THOSE
TICKETS FROM FRANCIS!
I WISH I HAD $1,500.
THAT'S COUNTERFEITING.
WHICH IS,
OF COURSE...
BAD.
HOW DO MOST
10-YEAR-OLDS MAKE MONEY?
A LEMONADE STAND.
OH, NO.
THERE IS NO WAY...
NO WAY I'M SELLING...
LEMONADE!
25 CENTS!
HOW'S THE LEMONADE
BUSINESS, TIMMY?
TERRIBLE.
NOBODY'S BUYING ANY.
WELL, I WOULDN'T WANT YOUR
SELF-ESTEEM TO BE CRUSHED.
I'LL BE YOUR FIRST CUSTOMER!
CHEERS!
TO MY FIRST
CUSTOMER!
[COUGHS]
AND YOUR LAST!
THIS STUFF YOU MADE
YOURSELF IS HORRIBLE!
GIVE ME THAT BACK.
I'M AFRAID I'LL BE TAKING
MY BUSINESS ELSEWHERE...
LIKE HERE.
HELLO, MRS. TURNER!
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO TRY SOME
OF GRANDMA VICKY'S
OLD-STYLE COUNTRY LEMONADE
AND HELP ME RAISE MONEY
TO SEE  CRASH NEBULA...
ON ICE?
YEAH...HE'S
A HUNK-SICLE!
HE SURE IS.
OK, ONE LEMONADE
COMING RIGHT UP.
THE LIGHT...IT BURNS!
HERE YOU GO,
MRS. TURNER!
MMM-MMM!
IT'S DELICIOUS!
IT'S SO MUCH MORE TASTY
THAN THAT RANK BILE TIMMY MADE!
VICKY WANTS
THOSE TICKETS, TOO.
THAT DOES IT!
I'VE GOTTA MAKE
BETTER TASTING LEMONADE!
I'LL SAY! THIS BILE
TASTES LIKE FISH!
FINALLY,
I THINK I'VE FOUND
THE SECRET INGREDIENT
THAT WILL
MAKE MY LEMONADE
THE TASTIEST EVER.
BLECH!
OK, CHEESE IS NOT
THE SECRET INGREDIENT.
[CRASH]
UH...NEITHER IS TACO SAUCE.
OR PEAS.
DARN IT, I'M RUNNING OUT
OF INGREDIENTS!
SO, THAT
WOULD BE A "NO" ON
THE CHOCOLATE LAXATIVES?
LISTEN, YOU--
BATHROOM!
WELL, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
FIND IT IN THERE!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY HE DOESN'T JUST WISH
FOR SWEETER LEMONADE?
OH! I CAN DO THAT!
WOOO HOOO!
AAAH!
I SAID SWEETER,
NOT SWEATIER!
REALLY?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID,
"DUNK YOUR SWEATY SOCKS
IN TIMMY'S LEMONADE!"
THAT WAS THIRSTY WORK!
[DING]
HEY! THIS IS GREAT!
I WISH I HAD
A PITCHER OF THIS!
I DIDN'T DO THAT.
THE SECRET INGREDIENT
IS FEET!
COOL!
SO? WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
STUPENDOUS.
THIS LEMONADE IS SO GREAT
I WISH EVERYBODY
KNEW ABOUT IT!
[CAR SCREECHING]
I'M CHET UBETCHA
SAYING MY TIRE IS FLAT
AND WE'LL NEVER GET BACK
TO THE STUDIO IN TIME.
THIS IS CHET UBETCHA
SAYING...
I'LL DO THE NEWS
FROM RIGHT HERE.
GOOD EVENING, DIMMSDALE,
I'M CHET UBETCHA
WITH BREAKING NEWS.
AFTER PULLING HIS CREW
FROM THE TWISTED METAL
OF HIS BURNING NEWS VAN,
ACE ANCHORMAN,
CHET UBETCHA,
WAS REPORTED TODAY
AS SAYING THAT...
THIS LEMONADE IS FANTASTIC!
EVERYONE WITHIN THE SOUND
OF MY VOICE
HAS REALLY GOT TO TASTE
THIS ASTOUNDING LEMONADE
MADE BY DIMMSDALE'S OWN,
TIMMY TURNER.
All: TIMMY TURNER'S LEMONADE!
TIMMY TURNER'S LEMONADE!
I WISH I HAD MORE.
NOW THAT'S SERVICE!
SO, HOW
ARE WE DOING?
♪♪ WE'RE GOING
TO SEE  CRASH NEBULA ♪♪
DUDE, AT THIS RATE,
WE'RE GONNA OWN
CRASH NEBULA.
YOU MAN THE FORT,
I'M GONNA GET SOME MORE
SWEATY SOCKS FOR MY LEMONADE.
WHAT?
UH, I MEAN I'M
GONNA MAKE SIX MORE
SWEATY PITCHERS OF...
LOOK, A MONKEY!
I HAVE DREAMS,
TOO, YOU KNOW!
LESS TALKIE!
MORE SWEATIE!
MAN, THIS WAS A GREAT IDEA!
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW FAST
WE'RE MAKING MONEY!
I WISH MY DOG
WAS HERE!
HE USED
TO LOVE LEMONADE.
SPEEDY!
IT'S A MIRACLE!
WOW!
ONCE PEOPLE
DRINK COSMO'S SWEAT,
THEIR WISHES
GET GRANTED!
BAD!
DAD, NO! PUT THAT DOWN!
ARE YOU MAD?
THIS LEMONADE'S TANGY
AND REFRESHING!
IF ONLY THERE WAS
SOME WAY I WOULDN'T HAVE
TO GO BACK TO WORK,
I'D STAY HERE AND
DRINK IT ALL DAY LONG!
[ROARING]
THAT'S MY OFFICE!
COOL! I'M UNEMPLOYED!
COME ON, HONEY,
LET'S GO FROLIC
WITH THE OTHER
UNEMPLOYED PEOPLE!
OK!
[ROARING]
THIS IS CHET UBETCHA
WITH BIG NEWS!
I'M THE TALLEST
NEWSCASTER ALIVE!
DETAILS AT 11!
OH, MAN!
GOTTA FIND COSMO.
EVERYBODY'S WISHES
ARE COMING TRUE!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
EHHH...ONLY...
ENOUGH
BODY FLUIDS TO MAKE
ONE MORE GLASS...
[CRASH]
I'M GONNA FIGHT LEMONADE
WITH LEMONADE.
[BOOM BOOM BOOM]
[ROARING]
HELLO THERE, LITTLE FELLA.
NOT SO TOUGH NOW, HUH?
[ROARING]
GOTTA WATCH THAT.
I WISH THAT WAS
BACK TO NORMAL...
AND THAT...
I WISH ALL THAT
WAS BACK TO NORMAL.
THIS IS CHET UBETCHA
SAYING,
I'M SHRINKING.
AW...
I WISH THAT EVERYTHING
WAS BACK TO NORMAL
AND NOBODY REMEMBERED
ANY OF THIS!
WELL, EVERYTHING
IS BACK TO THE WAY IT WAS.
WHICH MEANS I STILL
HAVE NO MONEY
TO BUY FRANCIS' TICKETS.
HUH?
THERE'S STILL
A LITTLE BIT LEFT.
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
VICKY HAS KEPT ME
LOCKED UP FOR SO LONG
I-I-I GOTTA HAVE
SOMETHING TO DRINK.
HERE, DRINK THIS.
I WISH MY FATHER
WAS HERE.
♪♪
[SCREECH]
HELLO, SON!
TIMMY TURNER, MY NAME
IS DOUG DIMMADOME.
OWNER OF THE DIMMSDALE
DIMMADOME.
THANK YOU FOR LOCATING
MY LONG LOST SON,
DALE DIMMADOME,
HEIR TO THE DIMMSDALE
DIMMADOME FORTUNE.
IF THERE'S ANYTHING
I CAN EVER DO TO REPAY
YOU FOR YOUR KINDNESS,
ALL YOU NEED
TO DO IS ASK.
DOUG DIMMADOME?
THE OWNER OF THE
DIMMSDALE DIMMADOME?
THAT'S RIGHT,
DOUG DIMMADOME,
OWNER OF THE
DIMMSDALE DIMMADOME.
THE SAME DOUG DIMMADOME,
OWNER OF THE DIMMSDALE DIMMADOME
WHERE THEY'RE SHOWING
CRASH NEBULA...
ON ICE?
YEAH!
THAT'S RIGHT.
THEN YOU CAN GET ME
THREE TICKETS
TO SEE  CRASH NEBULA
ON ICE, RIGHT?
NOT RIGHT.
NOT RIGHT?
RIGHT! I'M AFRAID
IT'S SOLD OUT.
OH, RIGHT.
HOWEVER,
THERE IS ONE WAY
I CAN SEE TO IT
THAT YOU AND ALL
YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS
CAN SEE THE SHOW.
WELL, GUYS, I TOLD YOU
I'D GET YOU IN TO SEE
CRASH NEBULA ON ICE.
LEMONADE!
GET YOUR LEMONADE!
ON ICE!
WELL, AT LEAST IT'S
BETTER THAN VICKY'S JOB.
AAAAAGH!!!!
DON'T YOU JUST LOVE
CRASH NEBULA...
ON ICE?
HE'S A HUNK-SICLE!