♪♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪♪
♪♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪♪
♪♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪♪
BAD TWERP!
♪♪ DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪♪
♪♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪♪
♪♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO'LL GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪♪
♪♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY... ♪♪
♪♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE A KID ♪♪
♪♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
YEAH,
RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
NICKELODEON
AND U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
[SNORING]
[BEEP]
GOOD MORNING, DIMSDALE!
DO YOU KNOW WHY IT'S GOOD?
BECAUSE TODAY'S
MY BIRTHDAY!
RIGHT?
NOPE,
BECAUSE TONIGHT'S
THE NIGHT
OF THE BIG CHIP
SKYLARK CONCERT!
AND HERE'S
HIS NEW HIT SONG--
"MY SHINY TEETH
AND ME."
♪♪ WHEN I'M FEELIN'-- ♪♪
HA HA HA!
♪♪ SAD AS I CAN BE... ♪♪
CHIP SKYLARK?
THAT LAME, PRETTY BOY,
DORK SINGER?
HE STINKS!
DOES NOT!
I WISH CHIP SKYLARK
WAS AROUND WHEN
I HAD A BAND!
WE WOULD'VE
ROCKED OUT LOUD!
DID YOU KNOW
I USED TO PLAY
THE ELECTRIC TRIANGLE?
BUT YOUR BAND STUNK!
HA HA HA!
BUT WITH CHIP
WE WOULDN'T HAVE.
AHEM!
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING SPECIAL
YOU WANT TO SAY TO ME?
CONSIDERING
WHAT DAY IT IS?
YEAH, PIPE DOWN!
SO I CAN JAM TO THIS
AWESOME CHIP SONG!
AAAHHH!
THANK YOU, KARMA.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT MOM MADE ME
FOR MY SPECIAL
BIRTHDAY DINNER!
COOKIES FOR DINNER!?
WITH OUR PHONE NUMBER
ON THEM!
SURE, TONIGHT'S
THE NIGHT OF THE CHIP
SKYLARK CONCERT.
YOUR MOM AND I
ARE GONNA THROW
THESE
TO CHIP WHILE
HE'S ON STAGE!
AND MAYBE HE'LL
CALL US AND OFFER TO BE
YOUR BIG BROTHER!
YOU GUYS ARE GOING
TO THE CONCERT?
TONIGHT OF ALL NIGHTS?
WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT CHIP SKYLARK?
OPEN YOUR EYES, SON.
THAT TEEN'S DELICIOUS.
[GIGGLING]
UHH! GOOD GOSH, SON!
WE HAVE A SPECIAL
SURPRISE FOR YOU!
A SURPRISE?
WHAT IS IT? WHAT?!
IT'S VICKY!
HELLO, MR.
AND MRS. TURNER.
HELLO, KID WHO'S
NOT CHIP SKYLARK.
SHE'S BEING PAID
QUADRUPLE TO BABY-SIT
SO WE CAN GO
TO THE CHIP SKYLARK
CONCERT TONIGHT.
AND THERE'S
EXTRA MONEY IN THERE
SO YOU KIDS CAN
WATCH THE CONCERT
ON PAY-PER-VIEW!
HAVE A FUN
CHIP-FILLED NIGHT!
[EXIT MUSIC PLAYS]
WELCOME
TO  CHIP WATCH TONIGHT.
I'M YOUR HOST
CHET YOU-BETCHA.
AND WE'RE
MERE HOURS AWAY
FROM THE LIVE BROADCAST
OF THE BIG CHIP SKYLARK CONCERT!
MOVE IT, TWERP!
IT'S PAY-PER-VIEW,
WHICH MEANS
IF I DON'T VIEW,
THEN SOMEONE'S GONNA PAY!
ARE YOU OK, NOT CHIP?
EVERYBODY FORGOT
ABOUT MY BIRTHDAY
BECAUSE OF CHIP
STINKING SKYLARK!
HEY, IT'S NOT HIS
FAULT HE TURNED OUT
SO DELICIOUS! MMM!
YEAH, WELL!
YOU KNOW WHAT I WISH?
I WISH SOMETHING BAD
WOULD HAPPEN TO HIM!
OK, BUT YOU JUST
CAN'T WISH HIM MAIMED.
OK, THEN I WISH--
OR INJURED.
THEN--
OR BEATEN.
OR DEAD.
FINE! I WISH THE WORST
POSSIBLE NON-LETHAL THING
WOULD HAPPEN TO
CHIP SKYLARK RIGHT NOW!
[CRASH]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
WHO IN THEIR RIGHT MIND
WOULD THINK OF INTERRUPTING ME
WHEN I'M ABOUT TO WATCH
TEEN SINGING SENSATION--
[ANGELIC MUSIC]
CHIP SKYLARK?!
AAAAAH!
HI!
[MUSIC PLAYS]
I WAS JUST IN A
NON-LETHAL ACCIDENT,
IN MY RECORD
COMPANY'S CAR.
ALL OF A SUDDEN
I HIT THIS TREE
WHICH SEEMED TO
POP OUT OF NOWHERE.
TOTALLY WEIRD.
THE ALBUM COMES
OUT JULY 24th. CAN
I USE YOUR PHONE?
SURE!
USE MY SPECIAL PHONE.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
AWESOME!
TUESDAY IS APPLE SAUCE DAY.
[SNORING]
EVEN UNCONSCIOUS,
HE'S DELICIOUS!
MMM-MMM-MMM!
HA! THE WORST
POSSIBLE THING
THAT COULD HAPPEN TO CHIP
IS THAT HE'S STUCK HERE
WITH VICKY LIKE ME!
[SNORING]
DO YOU LIKE THIS ONE
THAT MAKES ME LOOK LIKE
MRS. CHIP SKYLARK?
OR THIS ONE THAT
MAKES ME LOOK LIKE
MRS. CHIP SKYLARK?
I REALLY DON'T
THINK IT MATTERS.
I THINK YOU'LL MAKE
A GREAT MRS. SKYLARK,
MRS. SKYLARK.
AAH! I LOVE YOU,
CHIP SKYLARK!
I'M GONNA CALL ALL
MY FRIENDS AND INVITE
THEM TO THE WEDDING!
FIRST, I GOTTA
FIND SOME FRIENDS.
[SIGH]
ANOTHER DAY,
ANOTHER WACKADOO HOLDING
ME AGAINST MY WILL.
HI, CHIP! I'M TIMMY!
HAVING A CRUDDY DAY
LIKE ME?
THE ONLY CRUDDY DAY
I EVER HAVE
IS A DAY WHEN
I DISAPPOINT MY FANS.
W-W-WAIT! I DIDN'T
DISAPPOINT YOU, DID I?
BECAUSE OF YOU,
YOUR FAME AND YOUR
STUPID CONCERT,
EVERYBODY FORGOT TODAY
WAS MY BIRTHDAY!
OH, I'M SORRY TO HEAR
THAT, LITTLE GUY.
REACH INTO MY COAT POCKET.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING THAT
MIGHT MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
OH, MY GOSH!
IT'S THE BRAND-NEW
CRASH NEBULA
ACTION FIGURE!
SIX PACES TO FUN!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, TIMMY.
THIS HASN'T EVEN
BEEN RELEASED YET.
HOW'D YOU GET IT?
I GOT IT AS A GIFT
FROM THE RECORD COMPANY.
TODAY'S
MY BIRTHDAY, TOO.
REALLY?
YEAH.
WHAT A JERK!
YEAH, BUT THEY
SCHEDULED MY CONCERT
ON MY BIRTHDAY,
SO I HAVEN'T
EVEN HAD A CHANCE
TO CELEBRATE IT.
SOMETIMES IT'S HARD
TO BE FAMOUS...
AND TALENTED.
AND DELICIOUS!
WHAT?!
MY DAD SAID THAT.
[LAUGHING]
[COUGHING]
SORRY. I WOULD'VE
LAUGHED HARDER,
BUT THESE CHAINS ARE
CRUSHING MY LUNGS.
SORRY, CHIP.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
LITTLE PAL.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU WISHED
FOR THIS TO HAPPEN.
WOW. I THOUGHT CHIP
WOULD BE A BIG JERK
BECAUSE HE'S A BIG STAR!
BUT HE'S NOT SUCH
A BAD GUY AFTER ALL.
I WISH CHIP WAS FREE AND
OUT OF VICKY'S CLUTCHES.
[SPLAT]
OH, GREAT.
THE WAND-NOT-WORKING
[SPLAT] NOISE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW
THE RULES SAY
WE CAN'T USE OUR MAGIC
TO DESTROY TRUE LOVE?
SO?
HELLO, MY LOVE.
MY TRULY LOVE WITH ALL
THE LOVE IN MY HEART.
LOVE!
OH.
YOU CAN WATCH THIS
WHILE I FIND SOMEONE
WHO'LL PERFORM A MARRIAGE
CEREMONY BETWEEN A CRAZED FAN
AND A CELEBRITY
TEEN HOSTAGE.
TO THE INTERNET!
Chet: IT'S A SCENE
OF MASS CHAOS HERE AT
THE DIMSDALE DIMMADOME!
WHERE EVERYONE
IS ANGERLY ASKING
THE SAME QUESTION--
WHERE
IS CHIP SKYLARK?
IF CHIP DOESN'T SHOW UP,
I'M GONNA PUNISH
OUR CHILD FOR NO REASON!
TIMMY, IF YOU'RE
WATCHING THIS, RUN!
OH, NO!
FANS!
HUNDREDS OF 'EM!
DISAPPOINTED!
MY FAULT!
GUILT GROWING!
TEETH ARE BECOMING
LESS SHINY!
HAIR...
LOSING SHEEN!
AAAAAH!
OH, MAN! I'VE GOT TO
GET CHIP TO THE CONCERT
BEFORE ALL THOSE
WOMEN--AND MY DAD--
TEAR THE TOWN APART!
YOU AND I HAVE
TO GET CHIP OUT OF HERE.
COSMO, YOU GOT
TO GET TO THE CONCERT
AND STALL BY ANY
MEANS NECESSARY.
COOL! I'M GONNA GET MY OLD
BAND BACK TOGETHER.
All: WE WANT CHIP!
OR ELSE.
WE WANT CHIP!
HELLO, DIMSDALE!
ARE YOU READY
FOR CHIP SKYLARK?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WELL, HE'S NOT HERE YET,
INSTEAD, PLEASE PUT
YOUR HANDS TOGETHER,
FOR YOUR OPENING ACT--
ON THE FLUTE...PAN!
AND ON DRUMS...SANTA!
YOU BETTER WATCH OUT.
AND ON THE ORGAN...
BEETHOVEN!
WHAT?! WHAT?!
AND I'M COSMO!
AND TOGETHER,
WE'RE THE FAIRIES!
[BOOING]
[SKY SIGHS]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
FEEL BETTER?
YEAH, I DIDN'T HAVE
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM,
BUT THE SOUND OF FLUSHING
CALMS ME DOWN.
I'M SORRY YOU HAVE
TO SPEND YOUR BIRTHDAY
WITH VICKY.
OH, THAT'S OK, LITTLE PAL.
YOU HAVE TO SPEND
EVERY DAY WITH HER.
I'M JUST HERE
UNTIL SHE SNAPS OR
THE SWAT TEAM ARRIVES.
THAT'S VICKY FOR YA.
ICKY WITH A V.
HEY! ICKY VICKY.
I CAN WRITE
A SONG ABOUT THAT.
♪♪ ICKY VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ ICKY ♪♪
♪♪ VICKY ♪♪
I WAS TOTALLY WRONG
ABOUT YOU, CHIP.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
RICH AND FAMOUS
DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'RE A JERK!
ACTUALLY, I'M NOT
ALL THAT RICH.
THE RECORD COMPANY PAYS
FOR EVERYTHING.
I'M BROKE,
BUT IF THE FANS
KNEW THAT,
THEY MIGHT NOT
LOVE ME ANYMORE.
BUT NEITHER WOULD VICKY.
WELL, THERE'S THAT.
SHE WOULDN'T
LOVE YOU ANYMORE.
HI, CHIP, DARLING.
LOOK WHO I FOUND
ON THE INTERNET.
THE ONLY JUSTICE
OF THE PEACE ON EARTH
WHO WILL MARRY SOMEONE
AGAINST THEIR WILL.
WHEN VICKY FINDS OUT
THAT CHIP'S NOT RICH,
SHE WON'T LOVE HIM ANYMORE.
Timmy: YEAH, BUT HOW
DO WE LET VICKY KNOW?
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY
TO FORCIBLY BOND THESE
TWO TEENS AGAINST THEIR WILL.
IS THERE ANYONE HERE
BESIDES THE GROOM
WHO HAS A REASON THESE
TWO SHOULD NOT BE WED?
HE DOES!
OH, MY GOSH!
IT'S THE GUY FROM
THE RECORD COMPANY!
THANKS FOR THE TIP,
PINKHEAD MYSTERY WOMAN.
I REPRESENT CHIP'S
RECORD COMPANY.
SINCE YOU'RE GOING TO
BE CHIP SKYLARK'S WIFE,
YOU GET CHIP SKYLARK'S
DEBTS.
AND THIS IS FOR THE CAR,
THIS IS HIS CELL BILL.
THIS IS FOR THE PAGER
AND THIS IS FOR, UH...
WELL, EVERYTHING ELSE.
6 MILLION BUCKS?!
BUT, CHIP, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE RICH!
NOPE. HE'S JUST
PRETTY AND TALENTED.
NOOOO! YOU BROKE,
LOSER CREEP!
I DON'T LOVE YOU!
THIS WEDDING IS OFF!
NERD!
[ANGELIC MUSIC]
♪♪ I'M FREE ♪♪
♪♪ YES, SIREEE ♪♪
♪♪ I'M FREEE ♪♪
OH, NO! I'LL NEVER GET
TO THE CONCERT IN TIME!
HERE YOU GO, CHIP.
USE THIS! LET 'EM KNOW
YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY!
THANKS, LITTLE DUDE.
THE ALBUM COMES OUT
ON JULY 24th.
[BOOM]
I WISH WE WERE
AT THE CONCERT.
[CROWD BOOS]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
STAY BACK!
HEY, THEY LIKE US!
THEY REALLY LIKE US!
[CROWD BOOS]
LADIES...AND
TIMMY TURNER'S DAD!
HEY, THAT'S ME.
ARE YOU READY TO ROCK?
[CHEERING]
THEN GET READY FOR...
CHIP SKYLARK!
[SNORING]
HUH? WHAT?
DUDE, HOW'D WE GET
HERE SO FAST?
UH...THE POWER OF MUSIC?
ROCK ON! HIT IT!
♪♪ V-I-C-K-Y ♪♪
♪♪ THE SOUND OF HER NAME
IS THE LITTLE KIDS' CRY ♪♪
AAAAAAH!
♪♪ HEY, VICKY,
YOU'RE SO, SO ICKY ♪♪
♪♪ JUST THE THOUGHT
OF BEING AROUND YOU ♪♪
♪♪ MAKES ME OH, SO SICKY ♪♪
♪♪ HEY, VICKY, WON'T
YOU PLEASE EXPLAIN ♪♪
♪♪ WHY YOU GET
SO MUCH ENJOYMENT ♪♪
♪♪ OUR OF CAUSING
KIDS PAIN ♪♪
♪♪ OH, OH, OH ♪♪
♪♪ A CHICK WHO'S
JUST PLAIN MEAN ♪♪
♪♪ A SOUR SWEET 16 ♪♪
♪♪ SHE'S A FIRE-BREATHING
DRAGON ♪♪
♪♪ IN A PAIR OF BLACK JEANS♪
All: OOH!
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT FORGETTING
THAT MY BIRTHDAY WAS
TODAY, MOM AND DAD.
IT'S OK.
WHAT? FORGOT YOUR BIRTHDAY?
WE'D NEVER FORGET
YOUR BIRTHDAY, TOMMY.
YOUR BIRTHDAY ISN'T
UNTIL TOMORROW.
WHAT?
HAPPY ALMOST
BIRTHDAY, TIMMY!
All: OOH!
♪♪ HEY, VICKY, WON'T
YOU TELL US TRUE ♪♪
♪♪ HOW'D WE EVER
GET THE BAD LUCK ♪♪
♪♪ TO BE STUCK WITH YOU ♪♪
♪♪ OH, VICKY,
CAN WE SAY ONE THING ♪♪
♪♪ IT'S YOUR SUPER,
TOTAL YUCKINESS ♪♪
♪♪ THAT MAKES US
WANT TO SING ♪♪
♪♪ ICKY VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ OOH, OOH ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I HATE MUSIC.
♪♪ ICKY VICKY ♪♪
[CHEERING]
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
HOUSTON, WE HAVE
A PROBLEM. OVER.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M SCARED
OF THE BIG RAMP.
SO YOU AND
YOUR FRIENDS PAY
TO FALL ON YOUR FACE
AT THE SKATEBOARD PARK?
AAH!
SOMEONE'S COMING! QUICK!
I WISH YOU GUYS WERE
MY SKATEBOARD GEAR!
AAAH!
HIS WHOLE FACE HIT
AT THE SAME TIME!
HE MUST
BE REALLY GOOD.
DOES YOUR DENTIST
BUY YOU TICKETS
TO THIS PLACE?
YEAH. WHY?
DARN IT!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS,
WATCH AND LEARN.
I LIKE TO LEARN!
WOW! WOW! I'VE NEVER
BEEN THIS GOOD BEFORE!
WELL, SWEETIE,
YOU'VE NEVER HAD MAGIC
SKATE GEAR BEFORE.
WOW! LOOK AT TIMMY ROLL
NIMBLY BACK AND FORTH!
I MEAN...SHRED!
BEAT THAT!
THAT'S A LITTLE TRICK
I LIKE TO CALL...
SCRUNCH
OF THE MUNCHKINS!
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
THE BEST SKATER HERE
DOESN'T MEAN YOU GET
TO BOUNCE OFF OUR HEADS!
ACTUALLY, TWERP,
IT MAKES ME QUEEN
OF THE SKATE PARK,
AND AS QUEEN,
I DECREE...
...TO RIDE THIS RAMP!
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
SO...WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
I CHALLENGE YOU
TO A SKATEBOARDING
CONTEST TOMORROW!
AND WHOEVER WINS GETS
TO BE THE NEW QUEEN!
KING.
GOOD CATCH.
DEAL. BUT TOMORROW,
WHEN I KICK YOUR BUTT
ON ALL THREE RAMPS,
YOU AND EVERY OTHER
PUNK UNDER 16,
IS BANISHED
FROM THE SKATE PARK FOR GOOD!
SEE YA ON
THE BIG RAMP, SQUIRT!
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SKATE THE BIG RAMP?
AREN'T YA SCARED?
A LITTLE, BUT WITH
YOU GUYS HELPING ME,
I'VE GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
Both: UH...
OH, NO! NOT THE GROUP "UH."
THAT'S USUALLY FOLLOWED
BY BAD NEWS LIKE...
UH...
ACCORDING
TO THE RULES,
WE CAN'T HELP YOU WIN
A CONTEST, TIMMY,
THAT'D BE CHEATING.
WE CAN HELP YOU SHOW OFF,
BUT FOR FUN, NOT PROFIT.
I'D NEVER HAVE
CHALLENGED VICKY
IF I'D HAD KNOWN THAT.
ALL THE KIDS ARE
COUNTING ON ME!
I STILL HAVE
A SHOT THOUGH, RIGHT?
ACTUALLY, YOU'RE
PRETTY UNCOORDINATED.
I AM NOT! UHH!
I'M DOOMED!
WHAT YOU NEED IS SOME
DEATH-DEFYING TRICK
ALL YOUR OWN!
TIMMY, WHAT YOU NEED
IS SOME DEATH-DEFYING
TRICK ALL YOUR OWN!
YOU NEED THIS.
IT COMBINES
A 1400 DEGREE TURN
WITH FOUR AERIAL
FLIPS.
I CALL IT
THE 1400 DEGREE
IN FOUR AERIAL
FLIPPY TRICK.
YEAH, THAT ROLLS OFF
THE TONGUE, POINDEXTER.
WHAT ABOUT CALLING IT
THE TIMMY TUCK?
[CRASH]
OH, DARN IT!
CALL IT IMPOSSIBLE!
I CAN'T DO THIS!
Vicky: BUT I CAN!
I CAN'T WAIT TO TOTALLY
STEAL THAT TRICK
AND MAKE IT MINE!
[MANIACAL LAUGH]
IT'S GOOD TO BE QUEEN.
[SCREAMING]
HE'S NOT VERY GOOD,
IS HE?
NOPE, BUT THIS
GARBAGE ROCKS!
[SCREAMS]
SORRY.
I'LL NEVER GET
GOOD ENOUGH IN TIME
TO DO THAT TRICK.
I KNOW YOU GUYS
CAN'T HELP ME CHEAT,
BUT CAN'T
YOU TRAIN ME?
YOU KNOW,
TAKE ME SOMEPLACE
WHERE I CAN GET
REAL GOOD REAL FAST?
WHOO-HOO!
ZERO GRAVITY IS PERFECT
FOR PRACTICING SPINS!
HOUSTON, WE HAVE
ANOTHER PROBLEM, OVER.
IT'S ALWAYS PROBLEM,
PROBLEM, PROBLEM
WITH YOU GUYS.
DON'T YOU EVER CALL
JUST TO SAY HI? OVER.
SKATING IN THE JUNGLE
IS A GREAT WAY TO LEARN
HOW TO SWERVE.
LEARN TO SKATE IN DIFFICULT
ENVIRONMENTS, YOU MUST,
BECAUSE SCARED
OF GORILLAS AM I!
RAMPING DOWN A PYRAMID
IS A GREAT WAY
TO LEARN HOW
TO PICK UP SPEED!
AAAAAH!
HEAVENS! THIS SPECIMEN
IS PERFECTLY PRESERVED.
AM I? I'M STILL
USING THIS.
UH! THE MUMMY'S CURSED!
OH, MAN! I'M
STILL BEEFING IT
ON THE SIMPLEST
OF TRICKS!
DON'T WORRY,
TIMMY!
WHEN OR LOSE,
YOUR FRIENDS WILL
STILL LOVE YOU!
REALLY?
TIMMY BETTER WIN OR WE'RE
NOT GONNA LOVE HIM ANYMORE.
WELCOME TO THE SKATE PARK
AT THE BIG
SKATEBOARDING CONTEST!
TODAY'S THE BIG MATCH
BETWEEN EVIL 16-YEAR-OLD
BABY-SITTER,
SKATE PUNK VICKY...
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
AND TIMMY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WAIT!
WHERE IS TIMMY?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
ABRUPTLY STOPS]
HA HA! I KNEW IT!
I KNEW HE'D PUNK OUT.
I WIN BY DEFAULT.
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS!
WHERE COULD HE BE?
OH, MAN. IF I GO
DOWN THERE,
I'M GONNA LOSE AND HAVE
TO GO ON THE BIG RAMP.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GONNA
HUMILIATE MYSELF. NO WAY.
ALL RIGHT, TWERPS! LINE UP!
SAY BYE-BYE!
NOT SO FAST, VICKY!
YOU WANNA WIN,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
IT THE OLD-FASHIONED WAY!
BY BEING BETTER THAN ME!
Both: IT'S TIMMY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
GOOD LUCK, TIMMY.
THANKS, GUYS.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
YEAH, JUST REMEMBER,
IT'S NOT WHETHER
YOU WIN OR LOSE,
IT'S WIN OR WE DON'T
EVER GET TO COME
BACK HERE AGAIN.
[GULP]
[DONG]
BREAK A LEG,
TWERP!
THANKS, VICKY.
NO, REALLY. I MEAN
BREAK A LEG!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YEAH, WELL,
WATCH THIS!
[LAUGHTER]
AND TIMMY ACTUALLY
WINS THE FIRST ROUND.
[DONG]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HA! BEAT THAT, TWERP!
AND VICKY...
UNFORTUNATELY...WINS.
[DONG]
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO THIS!
THE SUPER,
COLOSSAL, GIGANTIC,
FREAKISHLY LARGE,
RAMP OF DEATH!
DON'T WORRY, TIMMY.
JUST DO THE TIMMY TUCK,
AND YOU'LL BE THE NEW QUEEN.
KING!
WHATEVER.
I, VICKY,
AM ABOUT TO DO
THE TOTALLY ORIGINAL,
AND COMPLETELY MINE, TRICK,
THE VICKY TUCK!
WHAT?! WHAT?!
SHE STOLE YOUR TRICK!
OH, THIS CALLS FOR SOME
DRAMATIC BACKGROUND MUSIC.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
AAAAAH!
NOW ALL TIMMY HAS TO DO
IS SURVIVE THE BIG RAMP
AND HE WINS!
OH, NO. THE BIG RAMP!
I CAN'T DO IT! I WON'T!
TIMMY! TIMMY!
TIMMY!
ALL RIGHT! ALL RIGHT!
WELL, IT'S BEEN NICE
KNOWING ME.
SKATING ON THE MOON,
RAMPING DOWN
THE PYRAMIDS,
SKATING IN THE JUNGLE,
I CAN DO THIS!
HE CAN DO THIS!
UNLESS!
[BOOM BOOM BOOM]
OH, NO! I'M DOOMED!
SHE'S TOTALLY CHEATING.
I MEAN...CHEATING.
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
AND NOW FOR SOME
ZERO-GRAVITY SPINS!
LOOK AT HIM GO!
A 1400 DEGREE SPIN
WITH ONE FLIP...
TWO...
THREE! AND--
WHAT'S AFTER THREE?
FOUR!
RIGHT!
AND THAT'S WHY IT'S
CALLED THE TIMMY TUCK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
NO WAY, TWERP!
HOW CAN YOU DO THAT
WHEN I COULDN'T?
BECAUSE TIMMY'S
SMALL AND NICE.
YOU'RE TALL
AND WEIGHTED DOWN
WITH TOO MUCH EVIL,
WHICH THREW YOU
OFF BALANCE.
HA HA! WELL,
THAT'S SUPER.
YOU'LL
BE GOING NOW!
OH, NO! I WON!
I'M THE QUEEN NOW!
KING.
RIGHT!
GIMME THAT CROWN!
OH, YOU WANT
THIS CROWN?
YOU'VE GOT
A BETTER CHANCE
IF SOME LOSER
12-YEAR-OLD WASTEOID
FALLING FROM THE SKY
AND PLOWING ME
INTO THE GROUND!
AAAAAAH!
HERE YOU GO.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
AND AS THE NEW QUEEN
OF THE SKATE PARK,
I DECREE...
LET MY PEOPLE SKATE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
TIMMY WON! VICKY'S
IN A CRATER,
AND THE KIDS
ARE FREE TO SKATE!
PRETTY GOOD DAY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I WANNA A HOT DOG.
IS IT HALF-TIME YET?
YOU DID IT, DUDE!
YOU BEAT--I MEAN...
THRASHED VICKY
AND SAVED THE PARK!
AND BEST OF ALL,
I DID IT ALL BY MYSELF--ME!
THE MOST COORDINATED
SKATER EVER!
UH!
AND BEST OF ALL,
TIMMY LEARNED SOME
GREAT NEW TRICKS!
AAAAH!
UH! AND ONE
NOT-SO-GREAT...ONE.