♪♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪♪
♪♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪♪
♪♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪♪
BAD TWERP!
♪♪ DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪♪
♪♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪♪
♪♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO'LL GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪♪
♪♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY... ♪♪
♪♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE A KID ♪♪
♪♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
YEAH,
RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
NICKELODEON
AND U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
PULL!
E EQUALS MC SQUARED...
BYE, ALBERT.
THIS SURE WAS
A GREAT IDEA
TO DESTROY
OUR OLD STUFF,
TIMMY.
HEY!
LAUNCH MY RETAINER.
YEAH. NOW THAT
WE'RE 10,
WE DON'T NEED OUR DUMB
9 YEAR OLD STUFF.
HEY, LET'S
LAUNCH THIS!
BUT TIMMY, THAT'S
YOUR FAVORITE CRIMSON CHIN
ACTION FIGURE!
YOU CAN'T LAUNCH THAT.
HE EVEN HAS
18 CHIN-TASTIC
ACTION PHRASES.
Doll: QUICK!
TO THE HYDROFOIL!
BUT IT'S
LAST YEAR'S MODEL.
I AM SO BEYOND HIM
AND HIS LAME PHRASES.
Tootie:
TIMMY! TIMMY!
OH, NO!
IT'S VICKY'S
LITTLE SISTER...
TOOTIE.
QUICK! TO THE
ANTI-GIRL FORTRESS!
ENEMY ON SCREEN,
CAPTAIN.
PREPARE TO
FIRE PHASERS!
[BUZZING SOUND]
PHASERS LOCKED,
CAPTAIN.
I LOVE WHEN
THE PHASERS GET LOCKED.
TIMMY! CAN I COME
UP AND PLAY!
FIRE!
WAAAAAH!
I'M SO WET!
YOU CAN'T EVEN SEE
HOW MUCH I'M CRYING!
CAN I AT LEAST
COME UP AND DRY OFF?
FIRE!
WHAAA! WHAAA!
WHY WON'T YOU
GIVE MY LOVE A CHANCE?
DARN IT. WE'RE
ALL OUT OF BALLOONS.
LET'S GET SOME MORE
AND STRAP THE CRIMSON CHIN
DOWN TO ONE!
YEAH! WE CAN HIT
TOOTIE WITH A BALLOON
AND A PLASTIC DOLL!
WELL, I GUESS
THIS IS GOOD-BYE.
YOU'RE MY BEST PAL!
IF YOU USED TO
LIKE IT SO MUCH,
WHY ARE YOU
GOING TO DESTROY IT?
BECAUSE I DON'T NEED
THIS DOLL ANYMORE.
I HAVE YOU GUYS!
STILL,
HE WAS PRETTY COOL.
YOU KNOW, I WISH
I COULD PLAY WITH HIM
ONE MORE TIME.
HEY! I'M TOY SIZED!
THERE'S EVIL AFOOT!
I MEAN...A-CHIN.
WOW! YOU MADE HIM ALIVE!
SURE! STANDING NEXT
TO A LIFELESS DOLL
WOULD HAVE
BEEN BORING.
AND YET...
SOME HORROR APPROACHES!
QUICK!
TO THE CHIN CAVE!
TIMMY! WHERE ARE YOU?
NEAT! FAIRY DOLLS!
I CAN ADD TIMMY'S
DOLLS TO MY TIMMY
LOVE SHRINE.
MAYBE IF YOU TOOK US
TO YOUR HOUSE,
TIMMY WOULD FOLLOW YOU
AND TRY TO GET US BACK.
WHAT? CAN'T I HAVE
AN ACTION PHRASE?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
THE COMMISSIONER
IS MISSING.
AND LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THESE PIPES.
OH, NO! I'M STUCK
TOY SIZED
AND MY GODPARENTS
ARE BEING TAKEN
TO VICKY'S HOUSE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE
THING TO DO.
WOW! A TIMMY TURNER
ACTION FIGURE.
WITH THUMB SUCKING
ACTION! YO!
AND LOOK, HE'S GOT
KUNG FU OVERBITE.
OW!
WHAT SHOULD WE
DO WITH IT?
WELL, IT IS
AN UNCANNY LIKENESS
OF OUR BEST FRIEND.
LET'S LAUNCH HIM
INTO MRS. O'LEARY'S YARD!
YOU MEAN THE LADY
WITH THE PET BEES?
WE CAN'T DO THAT.
[BEES BUZZ LOUDLY]
NOW WE CAN DO IT.
AAAAAHHH!
NOW I HAVE TWO
OF TIMMY'S DOLLS
TO ADD TO MY
TIMMY COLLECTION!
WOW. SHE REALLY
HAS A THING FOR TIMMY.
WELL, SURE.
HE'S THE BOMB!
I READ THAT
IN A TEEN MAGAZINE.
LET'S PLAY
TIMMY AND TOOTIE
IN THEIR
JUNGLE HOME.
YOU'RE ME...
AND YOU'RE TIMMY!
COOL! I'M THE BOMB!
MWAH! MWAH!
I LOVE YOU, TOOTIE!
HEY! I LIKE THIS GAME.
AAAHHH!
I'M DEAD!
DID SOMEBODY SAY
JUSTICE?
AAAHHH!
♪♪ HERE COMES
THE CRIMSON CHIN ♪♪
OOF! THANKS,
CRIMSON CHIN DOLL.
YOU TOTALLY
SAVED ME!
WONDER WHY
I GOT SO BORED
WITH YOU.
CHECK OUT MY DIMPLE!
IT'S HUGE!
NOW I REMEMBER.
YOUR ACTION PHRASES
STINK!
COME ON. WE GOTTA
RESCUE COSMO AND WANDA.
I EAT EVIL
FOR BREAKFAST!
MWAH! MWAH!
WELL, YOU'RE JUST
A DUMB GIRL.
THAT'S OK, TIMMY.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
FOREVER.
FINE! I'LL BE OVER HERE
THROWING WATER BALLOONS
AT YOU.
THIS DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
ARE YOU NUTS?
I'M HAVING A BLAST!
AND LOOK HOW CLEAN
YOU'RE GETTING.
WELL, TIME TO DO
MY CHORES.
YOU TRIM MY HEDGES,
AND YOU CUT MY LAWN.
BUT THESE ARE
YOUR CHORES.
AND THESE ARE
HIGH DEFINITION PHOTOS
OF YOU TWO SNEAKING INTO
AN "R" RATED MOVIE.
AAAAAAAND...ACTION!
HAAH! ALL THIS
BLACKMAILING IS
MAKING ME THIRSTY.
[TOOTIE GIGGLING]
MY DORKY LITTLE
SISTER IS LAUGHING
WHEN SHE SHOULD BE
DOWN HERE DOING
MY CHORES!
I'LL FIX THAT.
QUICK! WHILE
SHE'S DISTRACTED.
WE'VE GOTTA GET
INTO THAT HOUSE.
I HAVE GOATS
IN MY PANTS!
OH, NO!
RUN!
OOF!
HEY. THAT'S
CHESTER'S RETAINER.
MAN, THAT
GOT SOME DISTANCE.
[LAWN MOWER
LOUDLY APPROACHES]
WITHOUT GRAVITY,
WE'D FLOAT
INTO SPACE!
JUSTICE,
THY NAME IS CHIN!
ALL FINISHED!
GOOD THINKING,
CRIMSON CHIN!
OF ALL MY MUSCLES,
MY BRAIN IS
ONE OF THEM!
YOU'RE A COOLER DOLL
THAN I THOUGHT.
TOGETHER,
NOTHING CAN STOP US.
GRRRRR!
AAHHH! IT'S
VICKY'S DOG!
[CHOMP!]
[CLANG! CLANG! CLANG!]
DO YOU, TIMMY,
TAKE YOU, TOOTIE,
TO BE YOUR
LAWFULLY WEDDED WIFE?
WELL, WELL, WELL...
WHAT'S THIS?
TWO NEW TOYS?
WELL, GUESS WHO
THEY GET TO MEET?
NOT MISTER HAMMER.
MISTER HAMMER?
YES. MISTER HAMMER!
AND HIS FRIEND,
MRS. SAW.
HI, MRS. SAW!
I'M COSMO
AND THIS IS WANDA.
DON'T YOU WANT
TO BE A GOOD HOST?
NO! THOSE ARE
TIMMY'S DOLLS!
OH, THAT CHANGES
EVERYTHING.
HEY! MR. FIRE!
HAVE YOU MET WANDA?
OH, NO! HE'S
BEING TORN APART!
CHEW ON YOUR BUTT,
NOT MY FRIEND!
[CRASH!]
WHAT WAS THAT?
BAD DOG! YOU KNOW
YOU'RE ONLY SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT OUTSIDE,
OR AT TIMMY'S HOUSE!
CHIN! CHIN!
SPEAK TO ME!
I'M SORRY I GOT YOU
INTO THIS MESS.
I PROMISE...
I'LL NEVER LET
ANYTHING HURT YOU AGAIN.
[REPEATS OVER AND OVER]
YOU'RE...YOU'RE...
OW! YOU'RE MY
BEST PAL.
COSMO! WANDA!
I WISH I WAS
NORMAL SIZED!
COME ON, TIMMY.
LET'S GET YOU
AND YOUR STUPID DOLL
AND GET OUT OF HERE!
HE'S NOT STUPID!
HE'S MY FRIEND.
AND I SHOULD HAVE
TREATED HIM BETTER.
NO!
VICKY'S STOLEN
TIMMY'S DOLLS.
NOW HE'LL NEVER
COME OVER,
AND HE'LL
NEVER LIKE ME.
WHY DOESN'T HE LIKE ME?!
WAAAAHHH!
MAYBE HE'S NOT
THE ONLY ONE YOU
SHOULD TREAT BETTER.
YOU KNOW,
SHE MIGHT BE CREEPY,
BUT SHE DOES HAVE
TO PUT UP WITH VICKY
MORE THAN YOU DO.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
VICKY LIVES HERE.
I GUESS WHEN
SHE'S NOT TORTURING ME
AT MY HOUSE,
SHE'S TORTURING
TOOTIE HERE.
THAT'S GOTTA BE
THE WORST.
UH...HI, TOOTIE.
TIMMY! HI!
I...
WAIT. YOU'RE ONLY
HERE TO TAKE BACK
YOUR STUPID DOLLS
AND THEN HIT ME
WITH ANOTHER
WATER BALLOON!
ACTUALLY, I WANTED
TO SAY I'M SORRY
I WAS MEAN TO YOU.
YOU SEE,
I'M JUST...
A STUPID
10 YEAR OLD BOY!
RIGHT. AND I'M NOT
INTERESTED IN GIRLS.
AND I WON'T BE UNTIL...
HE'S A STUPID
11 YEAR OLD BOY!
THEN...THERE'S HOPE?
THERE'S HOPE!
I SHOULD DO SOMETHING
NICE FOR HER.
MAKE UP, YOU KNOW?
SHE'S NOT MEAN.
SHE'S JUST A GIRL.
IT'S NOT HER FAULT.
I'M TOTALLY INTO
THE IDEA OF YOU
GIVING ME TO TOOTIE!
THIS WAY, SHE'LL
ALWAYS HAVE A LITTLE
PIECE OF YOU
SHE CAN SMOTHER
AND CHOKE WITH LOVE.
WOW! THAT WAS
AN ODDLY SPECIFIC
ACTION PHRASE.
I'M GONNA MISS YOU,
PAL.
I PUT THE "MAN"
IN MANDIBLE!
TOOTIE, I WANT YOU.
TO HAVE THIS.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
I WANT YOU
TO HAVE THIS
AND NEVER, EVER, EVER
FOLLOW ME HOME AGAIN.
OH, TIMMY!
THIS IS THE BEST
GIFT EVER!
AND IT WILL BE
OUR LITTLE SECRET,
OF LOVE...
[WEAKLY]
OH-OH!
[BANG!]
Vicky: NOW, WHERE WAS I?
EVIL SISTER!
GOTTA GO! BYE!
ANOTHER TOY?
WOW, WHEN IT RAINS...
IT MELTS!
I WISH THE CHIN DOLL
WAS INDESTRUCTIBLE
AND HAD 12,000
"I HATE VICKY"
ACTION PHRASES.
YOUR ICKY, RED-HEADED
YUCKINESS
CANNOT PIERCE THE SHIELD
OF TOOTIE'S LOVE!
EVIL REDHEADS MAKE
BOY-BANDS SAY "EW!"
WHY WON'T THIS
STUPID TOY BREAK?!
I WISH WE WERE
BACK AT THE TREE HOUSE.
THAT WAS REALLY
SWEET OF YOU,
TIMMY.
YEAH, WELL...AS LONG AS
CHESTER AND AJ
DON'T EVER FIND OUT
ABOUT ME BEING NICE
TO A GIRL,
I'M SAFE.
Chester:
HEY, TIMMY.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
TIMMY! TIMMY!
LOOK! THIS DOLL IS YOU,
AND THIS DOLL IS ME.
MWAH! MWAH! MWAH! MWAH!
I LOVE YOU, TIMMY!
I LOVE YOU, TOO,
TOOTIE.
MWAH! MWAH!
OH, TIMMY!!
I GOT YOU SOMETHING, TOO!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LOVE STINKS!
AND IT'S WET, TOO!
HA HA HA HA!
BRUSH YOUR CLEFT
EVERYDAY!
HONEY,
YOU'VE OUTDONE
YOURSELF AGAIN.
WHAT DO YOU
CALL THIS?
COLD CEREAL AND MILK.
IT'S MARVELOUS!
I'M FALLING
IN LOVE WITH YOU
ALL OVER AGAIN.
Reporter Chet Ubetcha:
GOOD EVENING, DIMMSDALE.
I'M CHET UBETCHA.
THIS JUST IN.
SHOPLIFTING RAMPAGE CONTINUES
AT THE WALL 2 WALL MART.
ITEMS STOLEN INCLUDE
A COMPUTER...
A BASKETBALL...
A SNOWMOBILE
AND A FULL-SCALE WAX REPLICA
OF THE CRIMSON CHIN.
HONEY, DID YOU NOTICE
ALL OF THOSE NICE THINGS
TIMMY HAS?
I DON'T REMEMBER
GETTING HIM THOSE
NICE THINGS.
WHY DON'T I HAVE
NICE THINGS?
I WANT SOME
NICE THINGS!
IF YOU HAVE ANY INFORMATION
ON THE SHOPLIFTER,
GO UP TO YOUR SON'S ROOM
AND CONFRONT HIM IMMEDIATELY!
THANKS FOR GETTING
US READY FOR FAIRY
INSPECTION DAY, TIMMY.
ALL THIS EXTRA
WISHING YOU'VE
BEEN DOING
IS PUTTING US
IN TIP TOP SHAPE
TO IMPRESS
THE FAIRY INSPECTOR
WHEN HE GRADES US
ON OUR "FAIRYNESS!"
NO PROBLEM, GUYS.
AND LOOK AT ALL
THESE NICE THINGS
I'VE GOTTEN
OUT OF THE DEAL.
[LOUD KNOCK ON DOOR]
YOUNG MAN...WHERE
DID YOU GET ALL
THESE NICE THINGS?
UH...
INTERNET?
AND WHERE DID YOU
GET THE INTERNET?
UH...UH...
OOH, HE'S STAMMERING!
OUR SON IS
THE WALL 2 WALL MART
SHOPLIFTER!
[SCREAMS
LIKE A GIRL]
WHAT? YOU DON'T THINK
I STOLE THIS STUFF,
DO YOU?
AAAHHH!
THAT'S A YES.
BUT I DIDN'T DO IT.
AAAHHH!
THAT'S IT,
YOUNG MAN.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO MAKE
YOUR DAD SCREAM
LIKE A GIRL 3 TIMES
IN ONE DAY.
WHEN HE WAKES UP,
YOU'RE IN A LOT
OF TROUBLE.
GREAT. NOW MY PARENTS
THINK I'M A THIEF.
I WISH YOU GUYS
WOULD GET RID OF
ALL THIS STUFF.
I CAN'T HAVE
MY PARENTS THINKING
I'M A SHOPLIFTER.
AND I CAN'T TELL
THEM YOU GUYS MADE
ME ALL THAT STUFF.
LOOK, NO MORE WISHES
FOR AWHILE, OK?
BUT YOU HAVE
TO MAKE WISHES!
THAT'S WHAT FAIRY
INSPECTION DAY IS ABOUT!
WELL, THIS STINKS!
WHEN'S
THE INSPECTION?
Jorgen's voice:
IT BEGINS NOW!
[BANG!]
Timmy: OH, NO! IT'S
JORGEN VON STRANGLE!
THE TOUGHEST FAIRY
IN THE UNIVERSE!
HE'S THE FAIRY
INSPECTOR?
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THAT?
All three: UH...
GOOD!
THERE ARE THREE PARTS
TO THE INSPECTION...
RESPONSIBILITY,
NUMBER OF WISHES,
HAPPINESS.
IS THAT THE FACE
OF A HAPPY CHILD?
WELL...UH...
NOT "HA HA" HAPPY,
BUT...
F!
IF YOU GET AN "F"
ON TWO OF THESE
THREE TASKS,
I WILL SEND YOU BACK
TO THE FAIRY ACADEMY
FOR 1,000 YEARS
OF TRAINING!
LOOK, UH...
THIS IS A REALLY
BAD DAY.
WHY?
UH...
Parents: TIMMY!
COMING!
BUT TIMMY, WE NEED YOU
TO MAKE WISHES!
JUST STALL HIM.
AS SOON AS I SORT THIS OUT,
I'LL COME BACK.
Parents:
TIMMY!
[FOOTSTEPS]
Dad:
WE'RE GOING TO ASK YOU
POINT BLANK, SON.
ARE YOU A SHOPLIFTER?
NO. IN FACT,
IF YOU DON'T
BELIEVE ME,
USE MY NEW
LIE DETECTOR.
HEY, WHERE'D YOU
GET THIS NICE LIE
DETECTOR?
UH...INTERNET?
HUHHHH!
OH, TIMMY.
THIS CALLS FOR
DRASTIC MEASURES!
[FOOTSTEPS]
AJ! CHESTER!
FRANCIS?
WHERE AM I?!
YOU'RE IN
A POLICE LINE UP.
YOUR MOM AND DAD
ARE TRYING TO SHOW YOU
WHAT KINDS OF BAD THINGS
HAPPEN TO SHOPLIFTERS.
AND YOU'RE IN
MY SPOT, TURNER.
HEY!
LOOK! THIS WAS STOLEN
FROM THE WALL 2 WALL MART!
IT EVEN SAYS
IT'S NOT PAID FOR.
HE'S THE SHOPLIFTER,
NOT ME.
YOU'RE MY PARENTS.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
TRUST ME AND BELIEVE ME.
BUT WE DO BELIEVE YOU.
BUT WE BELIEVE
HIM, TOO.
AND HE'S GOT
A NICE BADGE.
HEY, WHY DON'T I
HAVE A NICE BADGE?
FINE!
IF YOU WON'T
BELIEVE ME,
I'VE GOT NO CHOICE
BUT TO PROVE I'M INNOCENT.
CHESTER! AJ!
EVASIVE MANEUVER 12!
FIND THAT PUNK
AND GET HIM BACK HERE
DEAD OR ALIVE!
WHAT?
DUH...SORRY.
ALIVE, NOT DEAD,
ALIVE.
HA. I GET A LITTLE
CARRIED AWAY.
[SIREN]
CHESTER, AJ,
COME IN! OVER!
TIMMY? TIMMY,
WHERE ARE YOU?
WE WANT TO HELP
PROVE YOUR INNOCENCE.
THANKS, GUYS!
WE'LL ALWAYS
BE THERE FOR
YOU, DUDE.
Cops:
FREEZE!
IT WAS HIM!
THANKS, GUYS.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
Cosmo: AND THIS IS US
ON VACATION IN EGYPT.
COSMO HAD
FOOD POISONING.
AND THIS IS US
IN PARIS.
FOOD POISONING.
FANCY FOOD POISONING!
AND THIS IS ME
GETTING FOOD POISONING
IF PIDDLEYLAND.
YOUR PUNY SLIDE SHOW
DOES NOT AMUSE ME!
WELL...UH...
WE COULD JUST SIT HERE
COWERING IN FEAR
OF YOU.
OOH! I'LL GET
MY CAMERA!
[SIRENS]
THIS IS TIMMY CALLING.
WHERE ARE YOU?!
WE'RE IN FRONT
OF THE STORE,
TIMMY.
BUT THE COPS
HAVE GOT IT
SURROUNDED.
THERE'S NO PLACE
FOR YOU TO SNEAK IN.
MOVE IT, GEEKS.
Cops:
HEY, FRANCIS!
SUCH A GOOD BOY.
Timmy on walkie-talkie:
LISTEN CAREFULLY.
HERE'S WHAT
I NEED YOU TO DO.
AND THIS IS US
COWERING IN FEAR
TWO MINUTES AGO.
AND THIS IS US COWERING
IN FEAR 3O SECONDS AGO.
AND THIS IS US...
STOP!
TIME IS ALMOST UP!
GET YOUR GODCHILD
AND PREPARE TO BE
INSPECTED! NOW!
WHO WANTS SOME
NICE TV?
WE NOW RETURN TO
SHOPLIFTING SHAME--
THE TIMMY TURNER STORY.
WE'RE LIVE AT
THE WALL 2 WALL MART
WHERE SHOPLIFTING FIEND,
TIMMY TURNER,
HAS BEEN CAPTURED
RETURNING TO THE SCENE
OF THE CRIME.
CAPTURED?
AUTHORITIES SAY
THE PINK-HATTED
SCOUNDREL...
SO, TIMMY WAS
NOT HERE AT ALL!
YOUR BUMBLING
HAS CAUSED
THE PUBLIC TO THINK
HE'S A CRIMINAL!
YOU HAVE FAILED IN
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY
AS FAIRY GODPARENTS.
SO WHAT?
IT'S JUST A STUPID
INSPECTION!
YOU WANT TO SEND US
BACK TO THE FAIRY
ACADEMY, FINE.
BUT RIGHT NOW,
TIMMY NEEDS
OUR HELP.
DON'T KILL ME!
[CHICKEN SOUND]
THEY STOOD UP TO ME
AND MY AWESOME MUSCLES
TO SAVE THEIR GODCHILD.
RESPONSIBILITY...A!
BUT THEY ONLY HAVE
15 MINUTES LEFT
BEFORE THE END OF THE INSPECTION
AND I FAIL THEM!
HA HA HA HA HA!...
WE'VE CAPTURED YOUR SON.
IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
BUT...WE ONLY
HAVE ONE SON.
AND NEITHER OF
THESE TWO KIDS
ARE HIM.
YOU TWO KIDS
ARE IN BIG TROUBLE!
IT WAS HIM!
CHESTER AND AJ
DID A GREAT JOB
OF DISTRACTING
THOSE COPS!
[SIRENS]
TIMMY!
PLEASE DON'T
SHOPLIFT!
ESPECIALLY NOT TWICE
AT THE SAME PLACE!
I'M NOT A SHOPLIFTER!!
AND I'M GONNA
MAKE YOU BELIEVE ME!
[BEEP BEEP]
WOW! THIS PLACE IS HUGE!
HUP HUP HUP HUP!
AH HA! SEE! FRANCIS
IS THE SHOPLIFTER!
[WHISTLING]
THAT'S IT!
I'M OUTTA HERE!
ALL RIGHT, FRANCIS!
ADMIT IT!
ADMIT YOU'RE
THE SHOPLIFTER!
DUH!
OF COURSE I AM.
BUT WHO CARES?
NOBODY BELIEVES YOU.
[SIREN]
ALL RIGHT, SON.
LEAVE THIS LAW ABIDING,
GRAY CHILD ALONE.
KEEP AN EYE ON TIMMY.
YOU GOT IT,
LAMB CHOP.
OOOOH! LOOK!
THERE'S A SALE ON LARD!
A COSMO CAM!
GO FOR THE DVD PLAYER.
IT'S NICE!
HUP HUP HUP HUP HUP!
I WISH I HAD A PARACHUTE!
HUP HUP HUP
HUP HUP...!
PLEASE, TIMMY.
WE LOVE YOU
AND THEY JUST
WANT TO HELP.
OH, YEAH?
DO YOU LOVE ME ENOUGH
TO GIVE ME A CHANCE
TO SHOW YOU THAT
YOU'RE WRONG?
WELL, OK.
ONE CHANCE.
BUT IF YOU'RE WRONG,
IT'S OFF TO
THE CLINK.
WHICH I HEAR
IS NICE.
WHY DON'T I GET
TO GO TO THE
NICE CLINK?
HAH! A LARD SALE!
[EVERYONE GASPS]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I KNOW. WHY DON'T
I HAVE LARD LIKE THAT?
UH...
I GOT THAT STUFF
OFF THE INTERNET?
RIIIIIGHT.
GOSH, SON.
I GUESS JUST
BECAUSE YOU HAD
NICE THINGS
DIDN'T MEAN
YOU STOLE THEM.
WE SHOULD HAVE
TRUSTED YOU MORE.
WE LOVE YOU,
TIMMY.
AND WE'RE SORRY.
CAN YOU EVER
FORGIVE US?
WELL...OH-MY-GOSH!
TWO MINUTES LEFT!
Speaking very quickly:
OK. I FORGIVE YOU.
OK, I LOVE YOU, BYE!
ONE MINUTE LEFT.
THE PUNY FAIRIES
WILL NEVER...
I WISH FOR A ROCK AND ROLL
LASER SHOW.
A UNICORN.
A BEAR ON A UNICYCLE!
A TANK.
A CASTLE AND A DRAGON!
A TEAM OF
SUPER HEROES!
AN ATOMIC SUBMARINE.
IRISH DANCERS!
CLEANING PRODUCTS!
FRIED CHICKEN,
A BEAUTY PAGEANT!
AND TO WRAP IT ALL UP,
THE CHINESE OLYMPIC
GYMNASTICS TEAM.
[PANTING]
HAPPINESS...
REVISED TO AN "A!"
RESPONSIBILITY...A!
AND WISHES...
A!
WOO HOO!
YOUR DELAY TACTICS
WERE OBVIOUSLY PART
OF YOUR OVERALL
PRESENTATION.
UH...SURE.
WE'LL GO
WITH THAT.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
HIGHLY ORIGINAL.
DON'T DO IT AGAIN!
WE PASSED!
YEAH! AND MY PARENTS
TRUST ME AGAIN.
BUT I'M GONNA HAVE
TO BE SMARTER ABOUT
WHERE I KEEP THE
STUFF I WISH FOR.
[RUMBLING SOUND]
WHERE DID YOU GET
THE NICE TANK, SON?
UH...INTERNET?
[GIGGLING] WORKS FOR US!
Mom:
HEE HEE HEE!
THIS IS FUN!
MMMM!
WAS THAT
THE DINKLEBERG'S CAR?
I HOPE SO.
THAT'S WHAT
I WAS AIMING FOR.
[MOM AND DAD LAUGH]