3 F1
♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ AND NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY
ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BIG TWERP!
♪ THE DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY
THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
WANDS AND WINGS!
FLOATY CROWNY THINGS!
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD, PEA POD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪
OBTUSE, RUBBER GOOSE
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE A KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
YEAH, RIGHT.
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
ALL RIGHT! THE WEEKEND!
NO SCHOOL.
NO VICKY BABY-SITTING.
JUST A NICE, FUN WEEKEND
WITH MY PARENTS.
YOU'RE LEAVING?
Mom and Dad:
ON A WEEKEND
BUSINESS TRIP.
Dad: TO OCEANSIDE
RESORT SPRINGS BEACH.
THEY'VE GOT GOLFING,
NOT BUSINESS,
FISHING,
SNORKELING,
NOT BUSINESS,
DEEP SEA
NOT BUSINESSING,
AND 8 DIFFERENT
RESTAURANTS.
WHERE'S THE BUSINESS?
WELL, UH,
THEY'VE GOT A COPIER...
THAT MAKES
FOOFIE LULU DRINKS!
YOU'RE GOING
FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND?
WE'RE ALL BUSTED UP
ABOUT IT, TOO, SON.
BUT YOU'LL BE PROTECTED
BY VICKY.
I HOPE OUR
FISHING BOAT--
I MEAN, BUSINESS MEETING--
DOESN'T DO THAT.
DARN IT! VICKY'S GONNA
TORTURE ME ALL WEEKEND
UNLESS WE CAN FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO GET RID OF HER.
COME ON, GUYS.
THINK OF SOMETHING--
SOMETHING THAT'LL TAKE
VICKY A MILLION MILLION
MILES FROM HERE.
I'M ON IT.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MARK.
HEH HEH.
OPEN IT UP, PAL.
IT'S FROM
YOUR MOM AND ME.
RADIOACTIVE WASTE!
DUDE, THAT'S THE
MOST AWESOME KIND
OF WASTE THERE IS.
MY PARENTS ONLY GOT
ME MEDICAL WASTE.
WHATEVER.
IT DOES NOT MATTER
HOW HORRIFYINGLY BAD
THESE GIFTS ARE!
NOTHING CAN FILL THE HOLE
IN MY HEART
LEFT BY LOSING MY ONE TRUE LOVE:
VICKY OF EARTH.
1,999,999. ONE MILLION,
ONE MILLION. PHEW!
WHO DARES TO INTRUDE ON
MY PATHETIC WEEPING?
FEDERATION EXPRESS.
I HAVE A MESSAGE
FOR MARK CHANG
FROM VICKY OF EARTH.
HELP ME, MARK CHANG.
YOU'RE MY ONLY HOPE.
I, LIKE, MISS YOU
AND STUFF.
WON'T YOU TAKE ME AWAY
FROM THIS PLANET FOREVER?
AND EVER...AND EVER...
JEFF...
ERIC...
ROAD TRIP!
YOU! I REMEMBER YOU.
YOU'RE TIMMY'S GEEK
FRIEND FROM EUROPE
WITH THAT STUPID
ALIEN COSTUME.
IS THERE AN IDIOT
CONVENTION IN TOWN?
DUDE, SHE'S ON TO US.
DO SOMETHING.
[COUGHING]
IS THIS SOME SORT
OF FRENCH PERFUME?
I'M SLEEPY.
CAN'T FORGET THE GOOD
OLD BOOGIE BOARD.
BOOGIE BOARD?
I MEAN, BUSINESS
BOOGIE BOARD.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
WAIT FOR IT.
[DING DONG]
I'LL GET IT.
YES?
UH, HEY, EARTH GUY.
I JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
I HAVE TO GO TO,
UH, EUR--EUR...
EUROPE?
YEAH! RIGHT. THAT.
OK, LATER.
NO BABY-SITTER MEANS
YOU GUYS CAN'T GO ON
YOUR BUSINESS TRIP NOW.
WELL, YOU'D
THINK THAT, SON.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO
THE SAFETY AND WELFARE
OF OUR BUSINESS TRIP,
WE ALWAYS HAVE A PLAN B!
FLAPPY BOB'S PEPPY
HAPPY CAMP LEARN-A-TORIUM?
THAT'S PLAN B?
HEY, PLAN C WAS
MILITARY SCHOOL.
WE LOVE YOU, TIMMY.
WHOA THERE,
SPECIAL GUEST.
YOU CAN'T JUST
DIVE HEADFIRST
INTO THE PEPPY HAPPY
BALL PIT.
AND WE'RE GOING TO
EXPLAIN WHY IN SONG.
♪ I'M HAPPY PEPPY GARY ♪
♪ I'M PEPPY HAPPY BETTY ♪
♪ WE'RE PEPPY HAPPY HAPPY PEPPY
PEPPY HAPPY HAP ♪
♪ ASK PEPPY HAPPY GARY ♪
♪ THAT BALL PIT'S
KIND OF SCARY ♪
♪ SO BEFORE YOU LEAP
YOU MUST PUT ON ♪
♪ THESE HELMET
BALL PIT PADS, YAY! ♪
AM I HAVING FUN YET?
BELOVED SEMICONSCIOUS VICKY,
BEHOLD YUGOPOTAMIA.
HA HA!
MOST FEARED PLANET
IN THE GALAXY,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
CAN I HAVE A COOKIE?
DO YOU NOT SEE
WHY I LOVE HER?
SHE IS UNAFRAID OF
ONE OF THE MOST LETHAL
OF ALL POISONS
FOUND ON OUR PLANET.
SHE ROCKS!
STUPID GARY. STUPID BETTY.
FINALLY! SOMETHING
MINDLESS AND VIOLENT
I'M TOTALLY
EXCELLENT AT.
STOP.
YOU MUST LEARN.
HOW TO SMACK?
NO, SILLY WILLY
WALNUT HEAD--
ABOUT THAT MOLE
AND HOW IT FEELS
ABOUT BEING SMACKED.
I'M CHET UBETCHA,
NARRATING  THE MOLE:
SMACK ME TO EXTINCTION.
LET'S START
AT THE BEGINNING.
6 MILLION YEARS AGO,
THE DREADED MOLASAURUS
RAN RAMPANT
ACROSS THE CONTINENT.
...WHICH SPELLED THE END
FOR OUR FURRY LITTLE
FRIEND THE MOLE.
NOW, WHO WANTS
COOKIES AND ICE CREAM?
I DO!
NO, YOU DON'T.
THEY'RE NOT APPROVED
FOOD GROUPS.
WHO WANTS SOY CUBES?
I DO!
WELL, I WANT TO GO HOME.
YOU CAN'T.
YOU DON'T HAVE
ADULT SUPERVISION.
AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO STAY HERE
UNTIL YOUR BABY-SITTER
RETURNS FROM EUROPE.
BUT SHE'S NEVER
COMING BACK.
YAY! WE'RE GOING
TO BE FRIENDS FOREVER!
AAH!
GUYS, I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D SAY THIS,
BUT I WISH
VICKY WERE BACK.
OH, MAN, LET ME GUESS.
THAT ALIEN KID
LOVES VICKY AND...
OUR MAGIC CAN'T
GOOF UP TRUE LOVE.
EXACTAMUNDO.
I WISH WE WERE
ON YUGOPOTAMIA.
WHY AM I IN MY CRASH
NEBULA SPACE SUIT?
IT'S SPACEY
AND FORMFITTING.
YOU WORE IT LAST TIME
YOU WERE HERE.
YOU THINK THEY'LL
REMEMBER ME?
IT'S TIMMY TURNER,
THE EARTH WARRIOR WHO ATE
THE DREADED CHOCOLATE!
[SCREAMING]
I'D CALL THAT A YES.
Queen: MARK WAS SO
DISAPPOINTED WITH HIS GIFTS.
I HOPE THIS SURPRISE
BIRTHDAY PARTY CHEERS HIM UP.
HE'S COMING. HE'S COMING.
SURPRISE!
AAH!
WE LEFT YOUR PLANET
IN PEACE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
WITH US?
I DEMAND THE RELEASE
OF THE EARTH GIRL VICKY.
HE'S COMING.
HE'S COMING!
AAH!
SURPRISE!
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
YOU HAVE BROUGHT
THE WRATH OF
EARTH UPON US.
GIVE HIM
HIS MATE BACK.
MATE?
IT IS MY BIRTHDAY,
AND I AM A MAN NOW.
I WILL NOT RELINQUISH
MY LOVE.
I CHALLENGE THE EARTH
PUNK TO DIJIFAT.
I ACCEPT. WHAT KIND
OF CHOCOLATE-EATING,
COOKIE-CRUNCHING,
FLOWER DANCING
HORROR IS DIJIFAT?
[SNIFF] I'M SORRY.
I SNEEZED.
I MEANT TO SAY
DEATH COMBAT!
EXCUSE ME?
EACH WARRIOR MAY
CHOOSE THEIR OWN
ARENA OF COMBAT.
AND SINCE IT IS
MARK'S BIRTHDAY,
HE MAY CHOOSE FIRST.
ALL RIGHTY THEN.
I CHOOSE THE YUGOPOTAMIAN
WAR ARENA.
LET THE BATTLE BEGIN!
I WISH YOU WERE
AMAZINGLY COOL
HIGH-TECH PROTECTIVE
SPACE WEAPONS.
BRING IT ON,
SOAP SCUM.
ALIEN SCUM.
WHATEVER.
AAH!
FEATHERY SOFTNESS!
PILLOWS?
YUGOPOTAMIANS HATE
FLUFFY AND NICE
AND GOOD AND SWEET.
YEAH, TIMMY.
ON THIS PLANET,
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT
FIRE WITH FUN.
CHECKMATE, DUDE.
[GASP]
WHOA! I MISSED.
THAT IS THE END
OF THE FIRST ROUND.
YOU MAY NOW CHOOSE
THE BATTLE ARENA.
[THINKING]
THINK, TIMMY, THINK.
FIGHT FIRE WITH FUN.
THEY HATE GOOD,
AND NICE IS ICKY.
GOOD AND NICE
COMBINED?
AAH! THOSE COLORS!
THOSE ANIMALS!
AAH! IT'S ALL
SO FUZZY AND NICE!
HEY, MARK, I GOT
A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
FAT-FREE SOY CUBES.
AAH! WAY TOO HEALTHY.
I'M PINK THE POLAR BEAR.
CAN YOU SAVE ME
FROM EXTINCTION?
AAH!
HELLO, THERE,
FUNNY HEAD.
AAH! NO!
MY HEAD
IS NOT FUNNY!
AAH!
♪ YOU HAVE A FUNNY HEAD ♪
THE LAUGHTER
OF CHILDREN!
I CANNOT TAKE
THE LAUGHTER
OF CHILDREN.
I SURRENDER.
YOU WIN THE DIJIFAT.
EARTH CHILD, ONCE AGAIN,
YOU HAVE WON FAIR AND SQUARE.
HERE. TAKE YOUR WOMAN
AND KINDLY SLAY OUR SON.
HEY, MAN, SHE'S
NOT MY WOMAN, OK?
SHE'S MY BABY-SITTER.
AND ONCE I'M 16,
YOU CAN HAVE HER
BACK FOR GOOD.
6 YEARS?
THIS BIRTHDAY STINKS.
WELL, I DO FEEL BAD ABOUT
SPOILING YOUR BIG DAY,
SO I WILL GIVE YOU
TWO GIFTS.
ONE, I WILL SPARE
YOUR LIFE.
'K.
AND TWO--
Jeff: DUDE, THAT EARTH
KID ISN'T SO BAD.
YEAH, CHECK OUT
HIS AWESOME PRESENT.
FOOLISH HUMAN!
WHEN I AM DONE WITH THIS
COMBAT TRAINING DEVICE,
I WILL RETURN FOR VICKY
YET AGAIN.
SOY CUBE?
AAH!
WELL, MARK'S GONE.
VICKY'S BACK
IN BABY-SITTING,
AND I'M NOT IN
HAPPYTOWN ANYMORE,
AND EVERYTHING'S
RIGHT WITH THE WORLD.
AND YOU'RE NOT DEAD!
I--UH--HEY, WHERE AM I?
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
WHY AREN'T
YOU MISERABLE?
YOU'D BETTER--
[SNORING]
COCK-A-DOODLE-DOO!
IT'S SATURDAY!
YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT
SATURDAY MEANS.
CARTOONS!
OUTDOOR ACTIVITIES LIKE
GARDENING AND BIRD-WATCHING.
OR CARTOONS.
OR VICKY.
WAIT. THAT'S NOT
A GOOD THING.
OR VICKY!
NO!
NOW, TIMMY, YOU KNOW
YOU CAN'T COME WITH US
TO THE ANNUAL MOTHER FATHER
NO KIDS ALLOWED COOKOUT.
BUT IT'S SATURDAY.
SATURDAY!
WE HAVE A DEAL.
IT SAYS HERE QUITE
CLEARLY, AND I QUOTE...
WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT, SON.
AND THIS IS
A LEGAL DOCUMENT--
A REALLY NICE
LEGAL DOCUMENT.
AND NOW IT'S FISH WRAP--
REALLY NICE FISH WRAP.
OH, DON'T FEEL BAD,
SWEETIE.
IT'S JUST ONE SATURDAY.
YOU'LL HAVE A LOT MORE
FUN HERE WITH VICKY.
[CAT SCREECHES]
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
WELL...
BYE!
BYE, MR. AND MRS. TURNER.
STAY AWAY FROM ME,
VICKY.
OH, DON'T WORRY,
TWERPY.
I BROUGHT ALL KINDS OF FUN
THINGS FOR US TO DO TOGETHER.
REALLY?
NOPE! THESE ARE MY SHOES
THAT NEED TO BE SHINED,
THESE ARE MY CLOTHES
THAT NEED TO BE WASHED,
AND THIS IS MY HOMEWORK
THAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
AND THIS IS MY BUTT,
WHICH WILL BE IN THAT CHAIR
WHILE I WATCH YOU
DO IT ALL.
AND IF I REFUSE?
THEN I LET YOUR PARENTS
LISTEN TO THIS RECORDING
I MADE OF YOU.
Timmy's voice: HI.
I'M TIMMY TURNER AND I--
Gruff voice:
CHEATED ON MY MATH TEST.
I NEVER CHEATED
ON MY MATH TEST!
Timmy's voice: HI.
I'M TIMMY TURNER. AND I--
Timmy's voice:
CHEATED ON MY MATH TEST.
I'LL GET TO WORK.
WAIT.
I'M NOT DOING CHORES
IN A DRESS.
HI. I'M TIMMY TURNER,
AND I'M...
IN A DRESS.
[SIGH]
OH, MAN,
I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
WELL, AT LEAST
NOBODY CAN SEE YOU
UP HERE ON THE SECOND
FLOOR, RIGHT?
SEE THE BOY
IN HIS UNDERWEAR.
5 BUCKS.
I WISH THE TRAMPOLINE
WAS GONE.
AAH!
[CRASH]
I HATE BEING
BABY-SAT BY VICKY.
SHE CAN DO ANYTHING
SHE WANTS TO ME,
AND I CAN'T
STOP HER.
Wanda:
WELL, KIDDO,
THAT'S KIND OF
WHAT THE BABY-SITTER
GETS TO DO.
YEAH. AND IF I WAS
THE BABY-SITTER,
SHE'D HAVE TO LISTEN
TO ME, RIGHT?
OOH. OOH. I KNOW
WHERE THIS IS GOING.
YEAH. I WISH I COULD BE
VICKY'S BABY-SITTER.
MAYBE I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THIS IS GOING.
HUH? HUH?
HEY! WHAT HAPPENED?
WHO ARE YOU?
AND WHERE AM I?
EVERYTHING
LOOKS BIGGER!
HI, VICKY.
YOU'RE 5, AND I'M
YOUR 10-YEAR-OLD
BABY-SITTER TIMMY.
YOU'RE IN
FOR A GREAT DAY.
REALLY?
NOPE!
WELCOME TO THE CORNER
OF PAY AND BACK.
I CAN'T CUT THE GRASS
WITH JUST A PLUNGER.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
TWERPETTE. MY BAD.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
BUT I--
AH! YOU WOULDN'T
WANT YOUR MOMMY TO
HEAR THIS, WOULD WE?
Vicky's voice:
HI, I'M VICKY, AND I...
Gruff voice: STOLE
FROM MY MOM'S PURSE.
I NEVER STOLE
FROM MY MOM'S PURSE!
HI, I'M VICKY,
AND I...
STOLE FROM
MY MOM'S PURSE.
THIS IS GREAT.
FEAR THE POWER
OF THE NEW BABY-SITTER.
HA HA HA HA HA!
YOU KNOW, HONEY,
BEING MEAN SHOULDN'T
MAKE YOU THAT HAPPY.
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT,
WANDA.
REALLY?
NOPE. I'M GONNA
GIVE VICKY
THE MOST MISERABLE DAY
OF HER LIFE!
SO DECLARES EVIL
BABY-SITTER TIMMY.
HA HA HA HA HA!
HEY, WANDA, CAN YOU
TURN INTO A FIREHOSE?
GONNA HELP VICKY
WATER THE PLANTS?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
MAN, I DON'T
EVEN LIKE HER,
AND I FEEL
SORRY FOR HER.
I THOUGHT
GETTING BACK AT
VICKY WOULD BE FUN,
BUT MAYBE I
SHOULD APOLOGIZE.
WAY TO GO, TIMMY.
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH
REVENGE FOR ONE DAY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH, TIMMY,
JUST REMEMBER
ALL THE GOOD
TIMES YOU'VE HAD
WITH VICKY.
YEAH. I GUESS.
HEY, VICKY, I WANTED
TO SAY I'M SORRY.
REALLY?
I WANTED TO, BUT
I CHANGED MY MIND!
HA HA HA!
WAH!
AH HA! SIGH.
THAT'S ODD.
WHAT?
I THOUGHT THIS
WOULD BE HILARIOUS.
WHY ISN'T IT HILARIOUS?
I JUST GOT MY ULTIMATE
REVENGE ON VICKY,
EVIL VICKY,
ICKY WITH A V.
NO, ALL YOU DID
WAS USE OUR MAGIC
TO TORMENT A 5-YEAR-OLD
GIRL TILL SHE CRIED.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULD WISH HER
BACK TO NORMAL. I--
REASSIGNMENT ORDERS
FOR WANDA AND COSMO.
SHE'S WANDA
AND COSMO.
YOU'RE BEING REASSIGNED
TO A SAD LITTLE KID
WHO NEEDS YOUR HELP.
WHAT? WHO'S
THE SAD LITTLE KID?
HER.
WHAT?
WE DON'T WANT
TO BE HER GODPARENTS.
SHE'S MEAN!
YEAH. WE LIKE TIMMY.
HIS HAT IS PINK.
SO? SHE'S A KID.
SHE'S MISERABLE.
YOU'RE FAIRIES.
MAKE HER HAPPY.
BECAUSE UNLESS
SHE SAYS...
...YOU TWO
ARE STUCK WITH HER.
BUT--BUT THIS IS ALL
A HUGE MISUNDERSTANDING!
SO? WHO CARES
WHAT YOU THINK?
YOU'RE A MEAN
BABY-SITTER.
[SOBBING]
I'M COSMO.
AND I'M WANDA.
AND WE'RE YOUR...
NEATO. I HAVE
FAIRY GODPARENTS?
WELCOME TO THE CORNER
OF PAY AND BACK!
AAH!
OK. MAYBE SHE WON'T
FIND ME HERE.
BUT IN CASE SHE DOES...
I, TIMMY TURNER,
BEING OF SOUND MIND
AND NO GODPARENTS,
DO HEREBY BEQUEATH--
SORRY ABOUT THIS,
TIMMY.
AAH! A BAT! A BAT!
A BAT! A BAT!
ALL RIGHT, VICKY.
YOU'RE GETTING
YOUR REVENGE NOW.
FINE.
I DESERVE IT.
HEY, TIMMY,
LOOK AT ME.
I'M TERRIFYING.
AAH!
I WISH YOU HAD PIMPLES.
AND LOOKED LIKE A PIG!
STOP GRANTING HER
WISHES, YOU GUYS!
WE CAN'T, TIMMY.
WE'RE HER GODPARENTS NOW.
YOU TWO HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING,
BECAUSE IT'S ONLY
A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SHE
TOTALLY KILLS ME.
OH, SHE CAN'T DO
THAT, TIMMY.
IT'S AGAINST
THE RULES.
WHAT? THERE'S RULES?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
THERE'S RULES?
[SNAP]
WELL, YEAH,
UH, YOU SEE,
WITH EVERY PAIR
OF GODPARENTS,
YOU GET A NIFTY
RULE BOOK.
THERE'S LOTS
OF RULES, VICKY,
BUT THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING
IS YOU
CAN NEVER SAY
THIS SENTENCE
RIGHT HERE.
LET ME SEE THE RULE BOOK.
[READING ALOUD]
WHY WOULD I SAY THAT?
ALL RIGHT.
WHO SAID "I'M HAPPY
AND I DON'T NEED MY
GODPARENTS ANYMORE?"
Wanda and Cosmo:
SHE DID! SHE DID! SHE DID!
OH, YEAH? PROVE IT.
Vicky's voice: I'M HAPPY
AND I DON'T NEED
MY GODPARENTS ANYMORE.
INCONCEIVABLE.
YOU MADE THIS KID
GO FROM MISERABLE
TO CONTENTED
IN NOTHING FLAT.
HEY!
YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND,
ARE A MISERABLE,
MISERABLE KID.
MISERABLE KID,
FAIRY GODPARENTS.
MAKE WITH THE HAPPY.
I LOST MY
GODPARENTS ALREADY?
NOOOO!
HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU GOING TO DO
TO HER, TIMMY?
HEAD LIKE A TOILET?
FACE FULL OF ZITS?
OH, NO, BETTER THAN THAT.
BUT I'M MISERABLE.
WHY WON'T ANYBODY
BELIEVE ME? I'M--
OOH, VANILLA.
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO NICE TO VICKY?
WELL, IF IT WEREN'T
FOR HER MAKING ME
SO MISERABLE,
I WOULDN'T HAVE
GOTTEN YOU GUYS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SO I'M GOING TO
GIVE HER THE BEST
DAY OF HER LIFE.
AND BEST OF ALL,
WHEN I WISH HER BACK TO 16,
SHE WON'T REMEMBER
A THING.
YOU SEE, TIMMY?
TWO WRONGS DON'T
MAKE A RIGHT.
YEAH. BUT 3 RIGHTS
MAKE A LEFT.
AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR THE SHOW.
♪ LA CUCARACHA ♪
♪ ENCHILADA
BLAH BLAH BLAH ♪
♪ LA CUCARACHA,
LA CUCARACHA ♪
WANDA?
♪ AND A BURRITO
BLAH BLAH BLAH ♪
OH!