2 F1
♪♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪♪
♪♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪♪
♪♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪♪
BED, TWERP!
♪♪ DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪♪
♪♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪♪
♪♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO'LL GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪♪
♪♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY... ♪♪
♪♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE THE KID ♪♪
♪♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
YEAH,
RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
[ROOSTER CROWS]
MUST...
KEEP...
FOOD....
ON...
TABLE.
[BEEP BEEP!]
YAAH!
[WATCHES BEEP]
YAAAAHHH!!
MOM, DAD...
CAN YOU CHECK MY HOMEWORK?
EH--YEP, THAT'S
HOMEWORK, ALL RIGHT.
EH-HEH!
UH...VERY GOOD, TIMMY.
HERE YOU GO, SWEETIE.
TUNA SALAD FOR LUNCH.
UM...MOM?
THESE ARE DAD'S SOCKS.
HEY, THESE HAVE
ABSOLUTELY NO
ARCH SUPPORT.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR PARENTS?
THEY'RE ALWAYS
IN SUCH A RUSH.
THEY BARELY
HAVE TIME FOR ME!
BYE, SCHOOL.
HAVE A NICE DAY
AT TIMMY.
HURRAY, THEY'RE HOME!
SO-MUCH-JOY-
IN-MIDDLE-MANAGEMENT.
MUST-OVERPAY-
BABYSITTER.
THANK YOU!
Parents: OW!
[SNORING]
MOM, DAD, I CAN'T WAIT
TO TELL YOU ABOUT MY DAY.
I...I...
[SNORING]
THIS IS SO UNFAIR!
I'M SURE THEY'RE
DOING THE BEST
THEY CAN, TIMMY.
I KNOW, BUT
THEIR OVERACHIEVING
IS KILLING THEM  AND ME.
THEY JUST CAN'T
GIVE IT UP.
WELL, THEY ARE
ONLY HUMAN.
[KA-CHING!]
YOU'RE RIGHT!
THE CRIMSON CHIN.
HE'S A SUPER HERO.
HE CAN DO EVERYTHING
WITHOUT EVEN BREAKING
A SWEAT!
BEING A SUPER HERO
WOULD MAKE ANY DAY EASIER!
EXACTLY. WHEN MY PARENTS
WAKE UP TOMORROW,
I WISH THEY HAD
SUPER POWERS!
WHICH ONES?
ALL OF THEM:
INVULNERABILITY...
SO NOTHING CAN HURT 'EM
AND THEY'D NEVER GET TIRED,
FLIGHT TO GET TO WORK,
SUPER STRENGTH
AND SUPER SPEED
TO FINISH
THEIR WORK FASTER.
AND TIMMY SENSES,
SO THEY'LL ALWAYS KNOW
WHEN I NEED THEM.
OH, AND
HEAT VISION TO...
UH...HEAT STUFF WITH.
AND TOSS IN WHATEVER ELSE
YOU GUYS CAN THINK OF.
YOU WISH IT...
WE DISH IT!
[BEEP BEEP!]
MEAT PRODUCT!
AND...
[SUPER HERO MUSIC]
WE HAVE AMAZING
SUPER HUMAN ABILITIES,
LIKE THE HERO
IN THIS BOOK.
IT SAYS HERE THAT
PEOPLE WITH SUPER POWERS
HAVE TO HAVE
SECRET IDENTITIES
BECAUSE THEIR ENEMIES
WOULD HURT THEIR
FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
DO WE HAVE ENEMIES?
[WHISTLING]
DINKLEBURG.
Both: AHH!
TIMMY SENSES TINGLING!
TIMMY NEEDS OUR HELP!
BUT REMEMBER, WE NEED
TO HIDE OUR POWERS.
TIMMY'S A SHARP KID.
HI, GUYS.
WHAT SUPER POWERS?!
WHAT'S WITH
THE SUITS?
EH...IT'S, UH...
TAKE YOUR MILD-MANNERED
SUITS AND HORN-RIMMED GLASSES
TO WORK DAY!
REALLY!
ANYTHING WE CAN
HELP YOU WITH?
I NEED A LITTLE HELP
WITH THIS HOMEWORK.
SEE, IT'S ABOUT...
HEP, HEP!
DON'T TELL ME!
YOU NEED TO DO A REPORT
ON THE EXACT DISTANCE
BETWEEN THE EARTH
AND OUR YELLOW SUN!
I'M ON IT!
I'LL GET YOUR BREAKFAST,
TIMMY!
LOOK, A MONKEY!
HEY, I HAVE
MEAT VISION, TOO!
I'M BACK...
FROM THE SURFACE OF THE SUN!
I MEAN, SURFACE
OF THE...LIBRARY!
AND THE SUN IS EXACTLY
186,413,671 MILES
FROM THIS KITCHEN.
WELL, GOTTA WORK.
OK, YOU GUYS.
HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
HO HO HO HO HA HA!
GOOD JOKE,
HEY, TURNER?
I'M ONTO YOU,
DINKLEBURG.
THANK YOU,
MYSTERY HOME SELLER!
DON'T THANK ME.
JUST INITIAL IN
ALL THE RIGHT PLACES!
SO, HOW WAS SCHOOL?
I HAVEN'T LEFT YET.
YOU'VE ONLY BEEN
GONE A FEW MINUTES.
RIGHT. I TOTALLY FORGOT
THAT TODAY'S A FEW MINUTES
LONG DAY, TOO.
YOU WORK A FEW MINUTES
AND THEN YOU'RE DONE!
HEY, HEY!
SO, EH...WHADDYA WANNA DO?
WELL, THE BUS
DOESN'T COME FOR
30 MORE MINUTES.
WANNA JUST TALK?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA,
SON!
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT
ABOUT MY SECRET IDENTITY,
I'M FINE!
SO, UH, WHAT WOULD
YOU LIKE TO TALK
ABOUT, SWEETIE?
AND THAT'S ALL YOU NEED
TO KNOW ABOUT WHERE
BABIES COME FROM.
BUT WHAT'S
THE MACHINE FOR?
I'LL TELL YOU
WHEN YOU'RE OLDER.
THERE'S THE BUS.
GOTTA GO!
LOVE YA! BYE!
WOW!
WHAT A COOL KID!
IT'S NICE THAT WE GOT
TO SPEND THIS TIME
WITH TIMMY.
BUT NOW WE'VE GOT
THE WHOLE MORNING
TO DO ANYTHING WE WANT.
YOU THINKING
WHAT I'M THINKING?
OH, YEAH!
IT'S TIME
TO FIGHT CRIME!
IT SAYS SO
IN THE BOOK.
OH. WELL...OK.
I AM...
MIGHTY MOM!
AND I AM...
DYNO DAD!
♪♪ MIGHTY MOM
AND DYNO DAD! ♪♪
AAAAHHHH!
UGH!
HEH HEH HEH!
GOODNESS! IT SURE
IS DRAFTY UP HERE.
MMM. YOU'D BETTER
BUTTON UP OR YOU'LL
CATCH YOUR DEATH...
OF JUSTICE!
WHO KNEW THIS TOWN WAS SUCH
A CRIME-INFESTED RAT HOLE?!
I KNOW!
WE HAVE TO KEEP
FIGHTING BAD GUYS
AND KEEP THE CITY
SAFE FOR OUR SON!
EH EH! OH!
[WHOOSH! OF
TIMMY'S PARENTS]
HI, VICKY.
WE'RE HOME!
SAY THE WORDS,
"VICKY, YOU CAN
GO HOME."
YOU CAN GO...
BACK TO WATCHING TIMMY
FOR THE REST OF THE NIGHT!
LOOK OVER THERE!
MOM, DAD. OH, NO!
GUESS WHAT
TIME IT IS?!
[TOILET FLUSHING SOUNDS]
THEY'LL BE BACK.
I KNOW THEY WILL.
THEIR TIMMY SENSES WILL BE
TINGLING ANY MINUTE!
MY TIMMY SENSES
ARE TINGLING!
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR TIMMY.
I'M TRYING TO MAKE
THE WORLD SAFE FOR TIMMY!
NOW THAT THEY'RE
SUPER HEROES,
THEY'RE BUSIER THAN EVER!
HO HO HO! I CAN DEFEND
TRUTH AND JUSTICE ALL NIGHT!
LET'S!
THIS STINKS!
I WISH THEY DIDN'T HAVE
SUPER POWERS ANYMORE!
LET ME GUESS...
All: THEY'RE SO SUPER POWERFUL
THEY'RE INVULNERABLE
TO MAGIC.
MAN. THE ONLY WAY
TO GET THEM TO CHANGE BACK
IS IF I MAKE THEM
VULNERABLE AGAIN.
HOW ARE WE GONNA
DO THAT?
WELL, IT SAYS HERE
TO CHANGE A SUPER PERSON
BACK TO NORMAL,
THEY HAVE TO WILLINGLY
GIVE UP THEIR POWERS
ON THEIR OWN.
THAT'S IT!
THEN I'LL MAKE THEM!
I'LL BECOME THE BIGGEST,
BADDEST, MOST POWERFUL
SUPER VILLAIN EVER!
I WISH I WAS...
GALACTIMUS,
THE EATER OF PLANETS!
EVERYTHING SEEMS QUIET.
Both: SUPER GASP!
BEHOLD,
MY MIGHTY VICTIMS!
I, GALACTIMUS, WILL
NOW EAT YOUR PLANET
LIKE A MEATBALL!
Both: NEVER!
[COUGHING]
FORM OF A GIANT SHARK.
SHAPE OF
A BUCKET OF WATER!
UM...
BEWARE MY POWER?
SORRY, HONEY.
[LOUD FOOTSTEPS]
MMM! TASTY!
NICE SNOT,
MIGHTY MOM!
THANKS, DYNO DAD!
HE'S TOUGHER
THAN HE LOOKS.
AND HE LOOKED
PRETTY TOUGH
TO START WITH!
YOU CANNOT WIN!
TO ME, MY FAIRIES!
HEY!
WHERE ARE MY PANTS?
SURRENDER
YOUR POWERS TO ME,
OR I SHALL
DESTROY THE EARTH...
AND YOUR SON!
THEY'VE GOT TIMMY!
I LOVE YOU, MOM.
GIVE UP YOUR POWERS.
I LOVE YOU, DAD.
WE DARE NOT ENDANGER
TIMMY OR THE EARTH.
IT'S MY FAVORITE
OF ALL PLANETS,
AND HE'S MY FAVORITE
OF ALL SONS!
YES, IT SEEMS
WE ONLY HAVE
ONE CHOICE.
WE MUST MAKE
OURSELVES VULNERABLE
AND RELINQUISH
OUR MIGHTY ABILITIES!
AW!
I'M GONNA MISS YOU,
MEAT VISION.
Both: GALACTIMUS!
WE GIVE YOU OUR POWERS!
I WISH THEIR POWERS
WERE GONE!
FAREWELL, POWERS.
MOM, DAD!
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU
BACK TO NORMAL!
HEY, NOW THAT
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS BARREN,
BATTLE-SCARRED WASTELAND
ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF TOWN,
HOW ABOUT A PICNIC?
MMM! PICNIC-VISION.
YOU DON'T SUPPOSE
TIMMY HAS...
OH! DON'T BE
RIDICULOUS!
LET'S JUST ENJOY
OUR LUNCH
WITH THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING
IN OUR LIVES...
TIMMY!
RIGHT. THIS IS
A BORING TOWN ANYWAY.
HA HA HA HA HA!
[SIREN]
OH, BOY!
THE 595th
ANNUAL DIMMSDALE
CAMELOT FESTIVAL!
WHERE YOU GET
TO DRESS UP
AND ACT LIKE PEOPLE
FROM THE MIDDLE AGES!
LOOK!
I'M MIDDLE-AGED!
YOU KIDS
GET OFF MY LAWN!
NO, I MEAN
THE LONG AGO TIME
OF KNIGHTS AND DRAGONS
AND WIZARDS.
THIS SHALL BE
MOST AWESOME.
BUT I'M GONNA NEED
THE BEST KNIGHT COSTUME EVER!
COME ON. LET US
SALLY FORTH INTO YONDER FAIR!
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[LAUGHTER]
[CRUNCH!]
GREETINGS,
FELLOW KNIGHT!
SHALST WE QUEST
FOR THE GRAIL?
UM...
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M JUST HERE
TO POINT TO WHERE
THE PORTA-POTTIES ARE.
OVER THERE.
THANKS FOR THE INFO,
SIR "LANCELITTLE."
THEY ALWAYS
CALL ME THAT HERE.
WELL,
THAT STUNK.
MAYBE WE CAN AT LEAST
FIND A WIZARD.
WOOOOOH!
DID SOMEBODY SAY
"WIZARD"?
WHAT KIND OF WIZARD
ARE YOU?
I'M...
THE CLEANING WIZARD!
HOW MANY TIMES
HAS THIS HAPPENED
TO YOU?
YOU'RE RIDING
IN THE FOREST,
WHEN SUDDENLY...
HEY!
YOU GET COW MANURE
ON YOUR TALKING SHIELD?
WELL, THE CLEANING
WIZARD MAKES ALMOST
ALL OF IT
GO ALL AWAY!
AH! THIS IS NO WAY
TO TREAT A MAN MY AGE!
VERILY!
AN ACTUAL DRAGON!
[ALL GASP]
WOW, THAT'S REALLY...
PATHETIC.
MAN, THIS FAIR STINKS!
Dad's voice;
MOOOOVE OVER, TIMMY.
Mom's voice:
WE CAN'T SEE
THE DRAGON.
MOM? DAD?
ISN'T THIS
A GREAT FAIR?
LOOK WHAT I BOUGHT.
THE CLEANING WIZARD!
AND THIS MANURE
ALMOST COMES ALL
THE WAY OFF!
[COUGHING]
THIS IS THE WORST
CAMELOT FAIR EVER!
[CLANG!]
CAMELOT? I THOUGHT
THIS WAS THE STATE FAIR!
WELL, I'M GONNA WIN
A BLUE RIBBON ANYWAY.
BYE, SON.
THE KNIGHT'S SHORT,
THE WIZARD'S A SALESMAN,
THE DRAGON'S FAKE...
AND...PEOPLE ARE THROWING
MANURE AT US!
WHADDYA MEAN US?
KNOW WHAT?
I WISH WE WERE ALL
IN THE REAL MIDDLE AGES.
[DING!]
THIS IS GREAT!
WE'RE ACTUALLY
IN THE MIDDLE AGES!
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
YOU WISHED FOR,
SIR POINT-OUT-
THE-OBVIOUS-A-LOT.
YEAH, BUT HERE
IT'S JUST CALLED
"THE AGES".
[LOUD FOOTSTEPS]
WHAT HO!,
TINY KNIGHT
WITH A SHIELD THAT SMELLS
LIKE A HUNDRED HORSES' BUTTS?
I AM ON MY WAY
TO PULL THE SWORD
FROM THE STONE
AND CLAIM MY RIGHTFUL
PLACE AS KING OF ENGLAND.
AND YOU ARE?
I AM MANY NAMES.
THE SHINING KNIGHT,
THE HAMMER OF FURY.
BUT YOU,
MY FELLOW WARRIOR,
MAY CALL ME...
SIR FINKLEBURG.
FINKLEBURG?
WHAT KIND OF DUMB NAME
IS FINKLE...?
COOL! I GOT POUNDED ON
BY SIR FINKLEBURG!
[DING! DING!]
HELLO, TIMMY.
WOW! THIS PLACE
SURE IS AUTHENTIC.
IT LOOKS
JUST LIKE CAMELOT!
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
I HAVE TO GO
TO THE CAN...
A LOT!
I SURE HOPE
THIS COSTUME
HAS A ZIPPER!
WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
YOU WISHED FOR
ALL OF US TO COME BACK.
I CAN'T HAVE
MY MOM AND DAD
RUNNING AROUND
IN THE MIDDLE AGES
IN A COWSUIT!
GET THEM
OUT OF HERE!
I TOLD YOU TO GO
BEFORE WE GOT
IN THE SUIT.
I'LL ONLY
BE A SECOND.
I JUST
HAVE TO MOVE
THIS UDDER.
[ZIP!]
[DRAGON ROARS]
HI, TIMMY!
OH, MY GOSH!
MY PARENTS ARE GONNA
BE EATEN BY A DRAGON!
I NEED A WEAPON
OF SOME KIND!
HEY, HOW ABOUT
THE BIG GLOWING
MAGICAL SWORD
OVER THERE?
I, SIR FINKLEBURG,
DOTH CLAIM THIS SWORD
EXCALIBUR
AS...AAH AAH AAH!
MY ARM! MY ARM
THAT HAS SLAIN
A THOUSAND MEN!
HOO AH!
BUT YOU GAVE IT
A GOOD TRY!
AND WE HAVE
A LOVELY PARTING
GIFT FOR YOU.
THE SWORD-IN-A-STONE
HOME GAME!
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERS]
I CLAIM THIS
TOY SWORD AS...
AAH! AAH!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR HIM,
FOLKS, HUH?
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERS]
NEXT UP, NUMBER 897.
PLEASE GIVE A ROUSING
15th CENTURY WELCOME TO...
ARTHUR LEBOWITZ!
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]
THAT'S KING
ARTHUR LEBOWITZ TO YOU.
OK, ARTIE,
I'VE ALREADY CAST THE SPELL.
THE NEXT MO
WHO YANKS THE SWORD
IS GONNA BE
THE KING OF ENGLAND!
YOU GOT IT?
WHATEVER YOU SAY,
UNCLE MERLIN.
I'M OVER HERE, KID.
AND ONCE
YOU GET THE SWORD,
I CAN HOCK IT FOR GOLD
AND GET US OUT OF THIS
RAT HOLE TOWN.
SORRY. NO TIME!
DRAGON TO SLAY!
GOTTA RUN!
'TIS THE NEW KING
OF ENGLAND!
WE MUST FOLLOW
HIS GLORIOUS...
AAAAHHH!
All: ALL HAIL KING...
Man: WHAT'S
THE NAME AGAIN?
[COUGHING]
ARTHUR.
All: ARTHUR!
KING ARTHUR!
BUT UNCLE MERLIN,
I'M NOT THE KING.
NOT YET, ARTIE,
BUT I WANT PEOPLE
TO GET USED TO THE IDEA.
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU KING,
A GREAT KING!
AND THEN MORE IMPORTANTLY,
I'LL BE A GREAT, RICH UNCLE
OF A GREAT KING!
BUT I CAN'T EVEN SEE.
CAN'T YOU USE YOUR MAGIC
TO MAKE SOME SORT
OF GLASS THING TO PUT
IN FRONT OF MY EYES
THAT'LL IMPROVE
MY VISION?
WHAT?
THAT'S CRAZY TALK?
YOU WANT THEM TO
BURN YOU LIKE A WITCH?
COME ON, WE GOTTA
GET YOU "KINGAFIED".
[DRAGON ROARS]
SO, ARE YOU
ENJOYING THE FAIR?
[DRAGON GROWLS]
WHAT A GREAT,
REALISTIC DRAGON RIDE!
I'LL SAY.
PICK US NEXT!
ALL RIGHT, WE MIGHT
HAVE MISSED THE SWORD,
BUT IF WE FIND
THE HOLY GRAIL,
YOU'RE SURE TO BE
KING OF ENGLAND!
BUT I CAN'T
SEE ANYTHING.
GEEZ, YOU'RE A WHINY
LITTLE TWIT.
MY MAGICAL POWERS
WILL LEAD US TO THE GRAIL.
GOSH!
MY FEET HURT!
NO WONDER METAL SHOES
NEVER CAUGHT ON.
LET'S REST
AND GRAB SOME WATER.
OW! HUH?
A CUP. HEY,
DID SOMEBODY DROP THIS?
OH-SAH! HE HAS FOUND
THE HOLY GRAIL!
HE IS EVEN MORE THE KING
THAN HE WAS 5 MINUTES AGO!
AAAAHH! AH-AH-AH-AH!
DAGNABBIT!
WELL, THERE'S NO CHOICE.
THE ONLY WAY TO GET YOU
TO BE KING OF ENGLAND
IS FOR YOU TO
SLAY THAT DRAGON.
YOU MEAN, YOU USE
YOUR MAGIC TO HELP ME
SLAY THE DRAGON, RIGHT?
NO. DRAGONS ARE
IMPERVIOUS TO MAGIC.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN,
SPORT.
WHAT?!
HEY! WE WERE HERE FIRST.
WELL, THIS RIDE
LOOKS WORTH THE WAIT.
I WONDER WHERE
IT LETS OUT.
THINK WE'RE CLOSE
TO THE DRAGON'S LAIR?
AS THEY SAY
IN THE MIDDLE AGES,
THAT'S A BIG 10-4,
GOOD BUDDY.
Dad: YAY!
WE'RE NEXT!
MY PARENTS!
YOU GOTTA HELP ME
FIGHT THE DRAGON!
UH...WELL,
ACTUALLY, TIMMY,
DRAGONS ARE
IMPERVIOUS TO MAGIC.
SO WE'LL BE WITH YOU
IN SPIRIT...
WAY OVER HERE!
HI, TIMMY!
GUYS!
MOM! DAD!
THIS IS SO REALISTIC!
I KNOW!
IT ACTUALLY LOOKS AND FEELS
LIKE I'M GETTING
THIRD-DEGREE BURNS!
OW! I MEAN, NEAT!
Timmy: HEY, YOU BIG,
STUPID LIZARD!
LEAVE MY PARENTS
ALONE!
WELL, THAT WAS
ANTI-CLIMACTIC.
LET'S GET SOME
CAMELOT PIE.
OW! THE BLISTERS!
I MEAN, NEAT, THE BLISTERS!
WOW! THIS MAGIC SWORD ROCKS!
EXCUSE ME,
HAVE YOU SEEN
A DRAGON AROUND HERE?
GET DOWN!
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
UH...I DON'T SEE
VERY WELL.
WELL, I CAN'T DO THIS
BY MYSELF.
HANG ON, DUDE!
THERE YOU GO.
WHEN WE DIE A HORRIBLE,
FLAMING DEATH,
YOU DESERVE
TO SEE IT, TOO.
EVERYTHING'S SO CLEAR!
I--I CAN SEE!
I CAN FIGHT!
HERE YOU GO.
I PICKETH THEE...
I SHALL CALL IT
THE...
THE SHINING BLADE
OF LEBOWITZ.
UH, HOW ABOUT EXCALIBUR?
THAT WORKS, TOO.
AT THE FIRE DEMON!
HEY! SIR POINTS-OUT-
THE-OBVIOUS-A-LOT,
YOU'RE NOT DEAD!
HOW'D THE BATTLE GO?
IT WAS AMAZING!
ARTIE'S GONNA
KICK THAT DRAGON'S...
UH...GUYS?
WELL, WE CAN TAKE
A CRACK AT IT.
I CAN BREATHE!
I CAN FIGHT!
AAAAHHHH-HA!
HE HATH SLAIN THE DRAGON!
HE IS THE TRUE KING
OF--
AAAAAAAAH!
All: FOOD!
All: ALL HAIL KING ARTIE!
THAT'S ARTHUR!
All: WHATEVER!
I THANK THEE.
PRAY THEE,
WHILST THOU STAY
AND BE ONE OF
MY KNIGHTS OF THE
PENTAGONAL OTTOMAN?
UH, YOU MIGHT WANNA GO
WITH A ROUND TABLE.
I LIKE IT!
ARTIE, PAY DAY!
I KNEW
YOU COULD DO IT!
All: OH, BOY! SECONDS!
AND SO, ARTIE LEBOWITZ
BECAME KING ARTHUR.
SIR FINKLEBURG,
WITH HIS ONE ARM,
BECAME THE WORLD'S
FIRST SLOT MACHINE,
AND THE DRAGON NEVER
BARBECUED ANYONE AGAIN!
THE END!
MMM, THANKS
FOR READING
IT TO US, SON.
YOU KNOW,
WITH MY BURNT HANDS
AND BAD EYES,
I COULDN'T HAVE
HELD OR READ
THAT BOOK.
ALL IN A NIGHT'S WORK.
YOU GUYS MIND?
I'M LOOKING FOR
A NEW GIG.