♪♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪♪
♪♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪♪
♪♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪♪
♪♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪♪
BED, TWERP!
♪♪ DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪♪
♪♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪♪
♪♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO'LL GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪♪
♪♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY... ♪♪
♪♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
WANDS AND WINGS.
FLOATY, CROWNY THINGS.
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ REALLY MOD, PEAPOD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪♪
OBTUSE,
RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE,
GUAVA JUICE.
GIANT SNAKE,
BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES,
CHOCOLATE SHAKE!
♪♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
♪♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOU ARE A KID ♪♪
♪♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪♪
YEAH, RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
[BELL RINGS]
HELLO, STUDENTS!
WE HAD TO DECIDE BETWEEN
PRINTING FULL-COLOR BALLOTS
FOR THE UPCOMING
STUDENT ELECTIONS
OR PURCHASING FOOD
FOR THE CAFETERIA.
SO, THERE WILL BE
NO LUNCH TODAY!
ENJOY YOUR BALLOTS!
[CHEERS]
WHY IS EVERYBODY
CHEERING?
WAIT FOR IT...
ALL WE HAVE IS DESSERT
AND GRUEL.
SO, WE'RE DECLARING TODAY,
CAKE AND GRUEL DAY!
[CHEERS]
COME ON, GUYS!
LET'S GO BEFORE THEY RUN OUT
OF CAKE AND START SERVING GRUEL!
BUT I LIKE GRUEL.
LIFE IS SWEET
AND SO IS LUNCH!
ONE SIDE!
STUDENT BODY PRESIDENTS
COMIN' THROUGH!
FORGET IT!
WE WERE HERE FIRST!
CO-PRESIDENT CHAD,
DO YOU HEAR SOME NON-STUDENT
BODY PRESIDENT TALKING?
NO, I DON'T
CO-PRESIDENT, TAD,
BUT I DO KNOW THIS:
STUDENT BODY
PRESIDENTS GET FIRST
IN LINE PRIVILEGES.
OH, YEAH?
WHAT ABOUT ME?
THE COMMON STUDENT?
WHAT DO I GET?
AAAAAAAHHH!
DARN IT!
THIS STINKS!
I'LL SAY!
IT SMELLS LIKE FEET IN HERE!
NO, IT STINKS
BECAUSE TAD AND CHAD
ARE THE STUDENT BODY
PRESIDENTS.
THEY GET TO DO
ANYTHING THEY WANT!
IT'S TIME SOMEBODY
RAN AGAINST THEM.
SOMEONE WITH VISION.
SOMEONE WITH IDEALS.
SOMEONE WITH...
FAIRY
GODPARENTS?
EXACTLY.
BUT, TIMMY...
TAD AND CHAD,
I, TIMMY TURNER,
AM RUNNING AGAINST YOU
FOR STUDENT BODY PRESIDENT.
WOW, YOU'RE
.001% MORE OF A PERSON
IN MY EYES NOW, TIMMY.
TRIXIE?
YOU--YOU ACTUALLY
GOT MY NAME RIGHT.
SURE! I'M POLITICAL REPORTER
FOR THE SCHOOL NEWSPAPER!
YEAH!
SHE HAS TO KNOW THE NAMES
OF ALL THE TOTAL LOSERS!
COOL!
IF I'M PRESIDENT,
TRIXIE'LL HAVE TO TALK TO ME!
AND WITH YOU GUYS HELPING
MY CAMPAIGN, I CAN'T LOSE!
INCOMING!
[SCREAMS]
OH, BOY! GRUEL!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
I CAN'T WISH MYSELF
STUDENT BODY PRESIDENT?
I TRIED TO WARN YOU.
YOU CAN'T WISH YOURSELF
INTO WINNING A CONTEST.
IT'S AGAINST  DA RULES.
YOU HAVE TO WIN
THE OLD-FASHIONED WAY!
BUY YOUR WAY IN!
BUT WE COULD BE
YOUR POLITICAL ADVISORS
AND HELP RUN YOUR CAMPAIGN!
RIGHT INTO THE GROUND!
YEAH! IT'LL BE GREAT!
THE MASS MARKETING
OF TIMMY!
BALLOONS!
CONFETTI!
AND A MONKEY
ON A UNICYCLE,
WEARING A NEON HAT
THAT GOES WHEEEEE!
[EEP EEP EEP EEP]
YOU'LL GET
TONS OF VOTES!
COOL! I SHOULD WRITE A BIG
CAMPAIGN SPEECH FOR TOMORROW.
TIMMY, THIS IS
WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE.
HE'S A WRITER.
MAYBE HE CAN HELP!
EVER WON AN ELECTION?
UH, NO.
BUT I HAVE WON THE HEARTS
OF MILLIONS WITH MY POETRY.
AND IN--
WHATEVER.
JUST START WRITING,
PUFFY PANTS.
ALL: FOUR MORE YEARS!
FOUR MORE YEARS!
THEY'RE GOING FIRST!
WHO KNOWS
WHAT KIND OF AWESOME
AND IMPRESSIVE SPEECH
THEY HAVE LINED UP!
[CHEERS]
THAT'S IT?
A SMILE AND
A POINTING GESTURE?
AND NOW...TIMMY TURNER!
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
"YAY AND VERILY?"
OH, FORGET IT!
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU KIDS?
WHAT KIND OF
SPEECH IS...?
EVERY YEAR
YOU ELECT THESE GUYS
AND THEN THEY USE THEIR POWER
TO BULLY YOU AROUND!
NO, THEY DON'T!
PIPE DOWN.
OH, OK.
IS THAT WHO SHOULD
BE REPRESENTING YOU?
THEY THINK
WE'RE THE LOSERS!
AND MAYBE WE ARE!
BUT THEN SHOULDN'T YOU BE
REPRESENTED BY A LOSER?
I'M TIMMY TURNER,
AND I WANT TO BE...
"OR NOT TO BE..."
OH, I LOVE THAT LINE.
THAT LOSER!
[CHEERS]
TIMMY, THAT WAS
AN AMAZING SPEECH!
REALLY?
YEAH. I...
WAIT!
WE'RE EXTENDING CAKE DAY!
EVEN FOR THE
LESS POPULAR KIDS
LIKE YOU!
All: TAD AND CHAD!
TAD AND CHAD!
TRIXIE?
AW, TIMMY, IT'S NOT OVER
UNTIL THE FAT LADY VOTES!
CAN THE PRINCIPAL VOTE?
YOU STILL HAVE
A CHANCE, SWEETIE!
NO, I DON'T!
EVERYBODY WHO COMES
TO SCHOOL TOMORROW
IS GONNA VOTE
FOR TAD AND CHAD!
I'LL LOSE AND
TRIXIE'S NEVER GONNA
TALK TO ME AGAIN.
I TOLD YOU, YOU SHOULDA
STUCK WITH THE MONKEY!
[EEP EEP EEP]
WHEE!
[WOLF HOWLING]
HEY! WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
PUKING, PROBABLY.
FOOD POISONING!
FROM TAD
AND CHAD'S CAKE!
THE ONLY REASON
I'M HERE IS BECAUSE
I'M FROSTING INTOLERANT!
WHAT ABOUT THE ELECTION?
IF EVERYONE'S SICK,
WHO'S GONNA VOTE?
POLLS ARE OPEN!
I KNOW WHO I'M VOTING FOR!
WHO?
POLLS ARE CLOSED!
WE MUST COUNT
THE BALLOTS!
I MEAN BALLOT!
AND THE WINNER IS...
TIMMY TURNER!
WE SWEAR
YOU IN TOMORROW!
CONGRATS!
DO YOU ACCEPT
YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES
AS STUDENT
BODY PRESIDENT?
PIECE OF CAKE!
AND GUESS WHAT?
I'VE ALREADY PICKED
MY OWN SECRET-SERVICE DETAIL.
WE HAVE THE PACKAGE
IN OUR PERIMETER!
AFFIRMATIVE!
PROTECT THE PACKAGE
AT ALL COSTS! OVER!
COME ON, GUYS!
LET'S CHECK OUT SOME
OF THOSE PRESIDENTIAL PERKS!
MAKE WAY! MAKE WAY!
PRESIDENT
COMIN' THROUGH!
NO WAY!
WE WERE HERE FIRST!
PRESIDENTIAL PRIVILEGE.
WHY, HELLO,
MR. PRESIDENT.
I LIKED THE WAY
YOU USED YOUR AUTHORITY
TO CUT IN LINE!
SHE'S TALKING TO ME!
IT'S WORKING!
I WAS HOPING
WE COULD DO A LONG,
IN-DEPTH INTERVIEW
FOR THE SCHOOL PAPER.
OH, YEAH...
WELL, I STILL THINK
TIMMY TURNER IS A LOSER CREEP!
LUNCH!
PROTECT THE PACKAGE!
GO GO GO GO!
AAAAGH!
NO! WAIT!
TRIXIE! I...
[TOILET FLUSHES]
THE PRESIDENTIAL
STALL, SIR.
I CAN'T GO WITH
YOU WATCHING ME.
WE CAN'T STOP WATCHING
UNTIL YOU GO, SIR.
THAT BELL!
THE PACKAGE IS LATE
FOR HIS PRESIDENTIAL DUTIES!
KEEP THE PACKAGE'S
APPOINTMENTS AT ALL COSTS!
GO GO GO GO!
HI, PRESIDENT TIMMY!
TRIXIE, WAIT UP!
Boy:
FOREIGN OBJECT!
GET HER!
AAAGH!
AND I PLEDGE
THAT ORGANIZATIONS
LIKE THE FUTURE PHLEGMERS
WILL GET THEIR
FAIR SHARE OF FUNDING
FROM STUDENT GOVERNMENT.
THE TURNER ADMINISTRATION
WILL NOT TOLERATE BIAS
AGAINST THE SINUS IMPAIRED!
[CHEERING, SNEEZING,
SNORTING, WHEEZING]
AH-CHOO!
CODE YELLOW!
THE PACKAGE MUST
REMAIN GERM-FREE!
AJ! AJ!
SPEAK TO ME!
IT'S OK...AH...
IT'S ONLY...
A COMMON COLD...AH-CHOO!
AH-CHOO! AH-CHOO!
NOOOO!
HOW'S OUR LITTLE
MR. EL PRESIDENTE?
MISERABLE!
I DO BORING STUFF ALL DAY,
CAN'T GO TO THE BATHROOM
BY MYSELF!
HEY! NEITHER CAN I!
AND NOW THAT TRIXIE WANTS
TO TALK TO ME, WE CAN'T,
BECAUSE I GET YANKED AWAY
BY MY SECRET SERVICE!
WELL, TIMMY, NOBODY
EVER SAID BEING A LEADER
WAS GOING TO BE EASY.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE A LEADER,
I JUST WANTED
TO BE PRESIDENT.
I WANT OUT.
YOU HAVE
TO BE IMPEACHED.
YEAH! YOU HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING SO BAD
THE WHOLE SCHOOL
WANTS YOU OUT!
I'LL GET THE MONKEY!
NO, WAIT!
I'VE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
WELCOME TO THE LIBRARY
ASSISTANT'S CLUB,
PRESIDENT TURNER!
DO YOU SWEAR
TO ALWAYS RE-SHELVE
ACCORDING TO THE DEWEY
DECIMAL SYSTEM
AND TO DEFEND THE LIBRARY
AGAINST THE LOUDNESS
AND GUM CHEWING
OF ALL OTHERS?
YOU BET!
[GASP]
IT CAN'T BE TRUE!
IT IS TRUE!
PRESIDENT TIMMY TURNER
LIKES BOOKS AND PERIODICALS!
SILENCE!
OH, YOU'RE RUINED, TURNER!
RUINED!
TIMMY TURNER,
YOU STAND ACCUSED
OF GEEKINESS WHILE IN OFFICE!
HOW DO YOU PLEAD?
GUILTY!
[GASP]
SO WHAT?
I LIKE BOOKS.
I LIKE MATH, TOO.
AND I'D JOIN
THE FUTURE PHLEGMERS
IF I HAD
A BAD ENOUGH ALLERGY.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO ABOUT IT?
IMPEACH ME?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
IMPEACH! IMPEACH!
ALL IN FAVOR?
All: AYE!
TURNER IS OUT.
TAD AND CHAD ARE BACK IN!
HEY, NOW THAT I'M NOT
THE PRESIDENT ANYMORE,
I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU AND I COULD FINALLY
HAVE THAT TALK.
3 WORDS.
"NOT" "PRESIDENT" "ANYMORE."
SO? WHAT'S FOR LUNCH?
NOT CAKE!
WELL, THAT'S POLITICS!
YOU WIN A FEW,
YOU LOSE A LOT!
WELL, I'D RATHER BE
A NORMAL GEEK
THAN STUDENT
BODY PRESIDENT ANY DAY!
[DOOR OPENS]
HUMANS!
TIMMY?
YOU STOOD UP FOR US!
NOBODY EVER
STANDS UP FOR US!
REALLY, GUYS...
IT WAS NOTHING.
All: ONE OF US!
ONE OF US!
NOOOOOO!
AW!
LOOK HOW POPULAR HE IS!
ALL'S WELL
THAT ENDS WELL.
I WROTE THAT!
HEY, TIMMY!
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
SHE DID IT!
NO, SHE DIDN'T,
I DID.
I FORGOT I HAD
TO DO A MASSIVE REPORT
ON THE AMERICAN REVOLUTION!
AND IT'S DUE TOMORROW!
I'LL NEVER GET ALL
THE INFORMATION I NEED
TO DO THE REPORT IN TIME!
[CRASH]
[CAT SCREECHES]
DON'T WORRY, TIMMY.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS APPLY YOURSELF SERIOUSLY!
OR YOU COULD DO
A TALK SHOW!
AND BRING THE FOUNDING FATHERS
HERE TO INTERVIEW THEM!
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
THAT'S A HORRIBLE IDEA!
YOU CAN'T JUST YANK PEOPLE
OUT OF THEIR TIME PERIODS!
THEY MIGHT BE DOING
SOMETHING IMPORTANT!
OR THEY MIGHT JUST
BE ON THE TOILET!
I SAY GO FOR IT!
I'M WITH
THE LIGHT-BULB FAIRY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Cosmo: LIVE!
FROM TIMMY'S TREE HOUSE,
IT'S TIME FOR...
JOIN TIMMY
AND HIS SPECIAL GUESTS
AS HE TRIES TO COMPLETE
THE BIG HISTORY REPORT
HE BLEW OFF!
AND NOW,
HEEEEEEEEERE'S TIMMY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
HEY, WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW
FOR YOU TONIGHT!
HERE TO HELP ME
WITH MY REPORT
ARE 3 OF THE FOUNDING
FATHERS THEMSELVES...
PLEASE SAY HELLO
TO THE FATHER
OF OUR COUNTRY,
GEORGE WASHINGTON!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU, THANK YOU...
I...MUST...NOT...
CAN'T...FIGHT IT...
MUST CHOP WOOD!
HEY! THAT'S MY DESK!
DON'T CHOP...
MY DESK.
MUST CHOP WOOD!
LET IT GO, LAD...
AAH!
HE CAN'T HELP HIMSELF.
IT STARTED
WITH THE CHERRY TREE
AND IT'S BEEN
CHOP CHOP CHOP EVER SINCE.
BENJAMIN FRANKLIN,
EVERYBODY!
STATESMAN, INVENTOR,
AND THE MAN WHO
DISCOVERED ELECTRICITY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANKS! AAH!
I'VE DISCOVERED
IT'S GREAT TO BE HERE!
AND LAST, BUT NOT LEAST,
THE GUY WHO WROTE
THE DECLARATION
OF INDEPENDENCE,
THOMAS JEFFERSON!
HEY! WRITE ON!
YOU GET IT?
WRITE! WITH A "W"?
I WRITE?
[CHIRPING]
NOT SO EASY, IS IT?
BUT I'M FUNNY!
SOMEBODY KEEPS CUTTING
MY BEST LINES
FROM  THE DECLARATION
OF INDEPENDENCE!
I DON'T SEE WHY
THE DECLARATION
OF INDEPENDENCE
SHOULD NEED
A JOKE ABOUT
MY WOODEN TEETH.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
AFTER THIS!
TIME-TRAVEL ARRANGEMENTS
FOR  THE TIMMY TURNER SHOW
ARE MADE POSSIBLE BY TIMMY'S
MAGICAL TIME SCOOTER!
TIMMY, WE NEED
TO WRAP THIS UP
AND GET YOUR
GUESTS BACK FAST
BEFORE WE SCREW UP
TIME...AGAIN.
RELAX! I ASK
A FEW QUESTIONS,
GET WHAT I NEED
FOR MY REPORT,
DO THE VACUUM CLEANER
SALESMAN SKETCH
AND I'LL GET
'EM BACK RIGHT AWAY.
OH, MAN! THEY'RE GONE!
WE BETTER FIND THEM FAST!
LET'S GO!
THE TIMMY TURNER SHOW
WILL BE RIGHT BACK
AFTER THESE MESSAGES!
BLAST THIS TV!
I CAN'T SEE ANY
OF MY 300 CHANNELS!
WHERE IS THAT REPAIRMAN?
THIS GLOWING BOX...
SO LARGE AND MADE OF WOOD...
OH, MOMMY!
HEY! IT'S FIXED!
I SHOULD PAY YOU!
YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO TOUCH THE MONEY, DEAR!
AWWW.
HEY!
YOU'RE THE GUY
ON THE MONEY!
WOULD YOU SIGN THIS?
WHO AM I, JOHN HANCOCK?
HANCOCK!
THAT'S FUNNY, GEORGE.
HOW DO YOU GET LIGHTNING
INTO THESE SMALL CONTAINERS?
OW!
HONEY! LOOK!
IT'S THE GUY ON THE NICKEL!
HA! NICKEL!
I'M ON THE DOLLAR.
I'M WORTH 20 OF YOU.
HA HA HA!
AH! AND THAT'S THE GUY
ON THE 100!
IF I CAN'T TOUCH THE MONEY,
CAN I AT LEAST TOUCH HIM?
EXCUSE ME?
THAT'S IT!
YOU KNOW HOW
YOUR DAD GETS
WHEN HE'S AROUND PEOPLE
WHO ARE ON MONEY!
OUT! OUT! OUT!
AWWW.
AND THAT'S HOW I CAME UP
WITH THE FIRST FIRE DEPARTMENT.
OW! AND THE LIBRARY!
INTERESTING! OR SHOULD
I SAY "ENLIGHTENING"?
TIMMY! WE NEED
TO TAKE A BREAK.
WE GOTTA GET THESE GUYS
BACK TO THEIR TIME PERIOD!
THEY'VE BEEN HERE
TOO LONG ALREADY!
RELAX, WANDA!
WE'RE STILL OK!
BESIDES, I THINK
IF HISTORY HAD CHANGED,
WE'D HAVE NOTICED NOW.
RIGHT?
[SHAKING]
[ENGLISH ACCENT] RIGHT?!
RIGHT?
[NORMAL] I MEAN RIGHT?
[SHAKING]
[NEIGH]
OH, NO! EVERYTHING'S
TURNING...BRITISH!
[ENGLISH ACCENT]
OW! BLIMEY, SON!
LOOK!
I'M TOUCHING
A POUND NOTE!
I'LL TAKE THAT, LUV.
'OI...
OH, NO!
BECAUSE YOU GUYS
WERE GONE TOO LONG,
AMERICA IS STILL
A BRITISH COLONY
AND DEVOID
OF ELECTRICITY!
DON'T FORGET ABOUT TAXATION
WITHOUT REPRESENTATION.
HUH?
'ELLO!
TAXMAN HERE!
WAND TAX.
TAW! TAW!
[NEIGH]
[ENGLISH ACCENT] OH, NO!
WITHOUT OUR WANDS,
WE CAN'T USE
OUR MAGIC TO CHANGE
EVERYTHING BACK!
[ENGLISH ACCENT]
I SAY. THIS IS A BIT
OF A STICKY WICKET.
[NORMAL] I MEAN...
DUDE! THIS STINKS!
I CANNOT TELL A LIE.
KID, YOU MESSED UP BIG TIME!
HEY, THAT'S MY JOB!
GIMME A SECOND.
I'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
WAIT FOR IT. WAIT FOR IT.
[DING]
HEY, I'VE GOT AN IDEA!
WHY DOESN'T
HE TAKE EVERYBODY BACK
ON THE TIME SCOOTER?
GREAT IDEA, COSMO!
BOY, THERE'S 3 WORDS
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D SAY IN A ROW.
HOP ON, EVERYBODY!
[RINGING]
All: WASHINGTON, FRANKLIN,
AND JEFFERSON ARE MISSING?
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
HA HA HA HA.
NOW THAT WASHINGTON,
FRANKLIN AND JEFFERSON
HAVE MYSTERIOUSLY VANISHED,
JUST AS THEY WERE ABOUT TO DO
SOMETHING REALLY IMPORTANT,
I, BENEDICT ARNOLD,
WILL BE ABLE TO BETRAY
THE AMERICAN REVOLUTION!
WELL, HELLO,
JOHN HANCOCK!
IT IS I,
YOUR LONG-TIME PAL,
GEORGE WASHINGTON!
SEE MY WHITE HAIR,
WOODEN TEETH,
AND LOVE
OF ALL THINGS FREE?
ANYWAY...I BROUGHT
YOU A PRESENT TO SIGN!
IT'S CALLED
"THE DECLARATION OF
SURRENDERPENDENCE."
"WE THE PEOPLE
OF THE UNITED STATES...
GIVE UP?"
WELL, I DUNNO...
COME ON, HANCOCK,
SIGN IT!
I MEAN, UH...
SIGN IT REALLY BIG.
I LIKE SIGNING
THINGS REALLY BIG!
[SHAKING]
OW! MY HAND!
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM!
I CANNOT TELL A LIE!
I AM THE REAL
GEORGE WASHINGTON!
CAN'T YOU SEE
MY WHITE HAIR AND
THE WOODEN TEETH
AND THE LOVE
OF ALL THINGS FREE?
HEY! THAT'S MY LINE!
[GRUNTS]
OH, NO!
ONE OF THEM IS GONNA
TURN THE FUTURE AMERICA
INTO A YELLOW TOOTHED,
ELECTRICITY-DEPRIVED RAT HOLE!
YEAH! AND THE OTHER ONE
IS GOING TO TURN IT
INTO A BRIGHTLY LIT,
DEMOCRATICALLY RUN RAT HOLE!
BUT I CAN'T TELL
WHICH IS WHICH!
THINK, TIMMY, THINK.
HERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
OW!
I'VE GOT AN IDEA!
AND WAX BURNS!
A COAT RACK?
NOT JUST A COAT RACK!
A BEAUTIFULLY CARVED,
TOTALLY PRISTINE,
WONDERFULLY
LACQUERED, SOLID OAK,
WOODEN COAT RACK!
SO WHAT?
AAH! OH, NO!
MUST CHOP WOOD!
All: THAT'S WASHINGTON.
DARN IT!
All: BENEDICT ARNOLD!
I KNEW
HE WAS A TRAITOR!
YEAH,
THE BIGGEST TRAITOR
IN AMERICAN HISTORY!
AND I WOULD HAVE GOTTEN
AWAY WITH IT, TOO,
IF IT WEREN'T FOR
THAT MEDDLING KID!
OW!
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WE SHOULD
DO SOMETHING NICE
FOR
THE PINK-HATTED LAD!
HEY! WE COULD
PUT HIM ON THE DOLLAR!
[NERVOUSLY LAUGHS]
WELL, ALL YOU GUYS
GOTTA DO IS SIGN
THE DECLARATION
OF INDEPENDENCE
AND WE CAN BE ONOUR WAY!
WE CAN'T!
GEORGE WASHINGTON'S
FAKE TEETH
AND LOVE OF ALL THINGS
FREE BROKE MY HAND!
NOW WE'RE ONE SIGNATURE SHORT!
GIVE ME THAT!
YOU CALL
THAT A SIGNATURE?
AWESOME!
WE'RE NOT BRITISH...
AND WE HAVE
ELECTRICITY!
UH! BLAST THIS TV!
I CAN'T SEE ANY
OF MY 300 CHANNELS!
WHERE IS THAT REPAIRMAN?
OK, I GOT IT.
HEY! YOU FIXED IT!
I SHOULD PAY YOU!
AH AH AH!
AW...
HEY!
YOU'RE THE KID
ON THE DOLLAR!
HEY! CAN I HAVE
YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
WHO AM I,
JOHN HANCOCK?
[BELL RINGS]
PLEASE WELCOME
MY FIRST GUEST...
GEORGE WASHINGTON!
HE DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE A WASHINGTON.
SURE I DO!
CAN'T YOU SEE
MY WHITE HAIR,
WOODEN TEETH, AND LOVE
OF ALL THINGS FREE?
AND YOU,
BEN FRANKLIN,
INVENTED
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT
AND DISCOVERED
ELECTRICITY, DIDN'T YOU?
AND THE LIBRARY!
I INVENTED THAT, TOO!
AND IF I HAD
ANOTHER FRIEND,
WE'D TALK ABOUT
THOMAS JEFFERSON!
YOU KNOW, TURNER,
SOME PEOPLE WOULD
FIND THIS STYLE
OF DELIVERING A REPORT
IMAGINATIVE AND
DESERVING OF REWARD!
THANKS!
UNFORTUNATELY, I AM
NOT ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE!
YOU FAILED!
I'M HISTORY!