♪ TIMMY IS AN AVERAGE KID ♪
♪ THAT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ MOM AND DAD AND VICKY ♪
♪ ALWAYS GIVING HIM COMMANDS ♪
BED, TWERP!
♪ THE DOOM AND GLOOM
UP IN HIS ROOM ♪
♪ IS BROKEN INSTANTLY ♪
♪ BY HIS MAGIC LITTLE FISH
WHO GRANT HIS EVERY WISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN REALITY ♪
♪ THEY ARE HIS ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ WANDS AND WIGS ♪
♪ FLOATY CROWNY THINGS ♪
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ REALLY MOD, PEA POD,
BUFF BOD, HOT ROD ♪
♪ OBTUSE, RUBBER GOOSE,
GREEN MOOSE, GUAVA JUICE ♪
♪ GIANT SNAKE, BIRTHDAY CAKE,
LARGE FRIES, CHOCOLATE SHAKE ♪
♪ ODDPARENTS,
FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
♪ IT FLIPS YOUR LID
WHEN YOUR THE KID ♪
♪ WITH FAIRLY ODDPARENTS ♪
YEAH, RIGHT.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
IT'S QUIET.
TOO QUIET.
AND IT'S WET,
TOO WET.
AAH!
Wanda: OH, YOU GOT ME.
EVERYTHING'S GOING...
PINK.
HEY, NICE
SHOOTIN', TEX!
I'LL SAY.
[KNOCK KNOCK]
Dad: TIMMY?
OH, SON OF MINE?
OH, NO!
IT'S DAD!
WHERE IS THAT BOY?
I WANT TO
GIVE HIM A GIFT
FOR NO REASON
WHATSOEVER.
WELL, TOO BAD.
I'LL JUST GIVE IT
TO THE NEIGHBOR KID.
HUH?
DID HE SAY GIFT?
THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
EMERGENCY ANTI-WISH
MANEUVER NUMBER 74, NOW!
HELLO, GIFT, BUDDY,
WONDERFUL GIFT DAD!
GIFT!
TIMMY! DO YOU KNOW
WHAT WEEKEND THIS IS?
YEAH, THE ANNUAL
DIMMSDALE FATHER-SON
BIKE RACE.
RIGHT, AND I HAVE
A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
OH, BOY!
IS IT A BIKE?
WHO TOLD YOU?!
IT'S NOT JUST A BIKE,
IT'S A BIKE I MADE.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE?
HA, BUT
I DID ANYWAY.
CHECK OUT
THE WOODEN FRAME, HMM.
IT'S LIGHTER AND MORE
FLAMMABLE THAN TITANIUM.
ARE THESE HANDLEBARS
MADE FROM RUSTY PIPE?
YOU BET THEY ARE.
AND CHECK OUT
THOSE PEDALS.
FUZZY TOE LOOPS FOR
EXTRA POWER AND COMFORT.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, UH...
TAKE YOUR TIME ON
YOUR UNDYING GRATITUDE,
I CAN WAIT.
OK, ANY TIME NOW.
Mom: AAH!
SOMEONE REPLACED MY SLIPPERS
WITH BIKE PEDALS!
HA HA!
GOTTA GO!
IF YOUR MOM ASKS...
I DID IT!
YOUR A GOOD BOY.
NIFTY BIKE, TIMMY.
I CAN'T RIDE THIS BIKE
AT THE BIG RACE.
IT STINKS!
I NEED A BIKE
THAT'S AS COOL AS I AM.
TIMMY, THIS BIKE
IS AS COOL AS YOU ARE.
BESIDES, YOUR DAD
MADE IT FOR YOU
WITH HIS OWN TWO HANDS.
[POP]
YEAH, WELL, HE MADE
A CRUDDY BIKE.
I WISH I HAD
A SUPER BIKE!
Oddparents: NO!
WE HAD AN AGREEMENT
ABOUT SUPER WISHES.
REMEMBER SUPER KITTY?
[DOGS YIPPING]
[ROAR]
AND DON'T MAKE HIM
RELIVE SUPER TOILET.
IT TOOK THE PLUNGER,
THE WHOLE PLUNGER!
HOW 'BOUT THIS, THEN?
I WISH FOR A SMART BIKE
THAT'S UNSTOPPABLE,
UNBREAKABLE,
TOTALLY MODERN
AND COOL,
AND JUST FOR ME!
[GASPS]
IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
HELLO, TIMMY.
SHALL WE GO
FOR A RIDE?
Both:
CAN WE COME?
SUPER TOILET.
AAH!
3...2...1...
HANG ON, TIMMY!
DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
Dad: OH, SON?
WHO WANTS A RIDE
TO CHESTER'S?
NOT ME!
I'VE GOT
A REALLY COOL BIKE!
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
TIMMY FINALLY
APPRECIATES HIS OLD MAN.
[CRASH]
THIS CALLS FOR
A CELEBRATION!
WHO WANTS
A FRUIT SHAKE?
OH, OH,
ME! ME! I DO!
DAD: THAT'S NOT
THE BLENDER I MADE YOU.
OH, OH...
WHY YOU'RE RIGHT.
SILLY ME.
LET ME GET
THE GOOD BLENDER.
ALL RIGHT!
FRUIT ME UP, BABY!
Timmy: BYE, GUYS.
I'M GOING OVER
TO CHESTER'S.
Both: HAVE FUN!
[ENGINE STARTS]
LET ME GIVE YOU
A RIDE THERE, TIMMY.
HE'S PERFECTLY
CAPABLE OF WALKING.
HA HA HA!
SUPER TOILET.
AAH!
COME ON, TIMMY.
I'LL TAKE YOU.
WELL, I GUESS
IT'S OK. LET'S GO.
THERE'S CHESTER'S HOUSE,
BACK THERE!
HEY, CUT THAT OUT!
WHAT WAS
ALL THAT ABOUT?
SORRY, TIMMY.
I JUST DON'T
THINK THIS
IS A VERY GOOD
NEIGHBORHOOD IS ALL.
YEAH, RIGHT.
JUST STAY HERE.
THAT'S AN ORDER.
[BOOM]
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU UH--DIDN'T PUT
MY KICKSTAND DOWN
ALL THE WAY?
YOU LOOK OK TO ME.
BESIDES, YOU'RE
INDESTRUCTIBLE.
MY MIRROR!
SUPER BIKE!
GO...HAVE FUN
WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
ARE YOU OK?
I'M FINE. [COUGHING]
JUST LEAVE ME HERE
ON THE COLD GROUND.
I'LL RUST
IN SILENCE.
NO, REALLY, IT'S OK.
I CAN GO TO
CHESTER'S ANYTIME.
LET'S GO HOME.
CAN WE GO THE LONG WAY?
UH, SURE.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
[BELL RINGS]
WERE COULD TIMMY BE?
HONEY, CHECK
THE WATCH I MADE YOU.
IT'S--
NOON.
IT'S A HALF HOUR
TILL RACE TIME.
HE'S PROBABLY STILL
POLISHING THE BIKE.
HE LOVES THAT BIKE
SO MUCH.
[HORN HONKS]
HEY, DAD.
WHA--WHERE'S
YOUR BIKE?
THIS IS MY BIKE.
YOU MEAN YOU'VE BEEN RIDING
THIS BIKE THE WHOLE TIME
AND NOT THE ONE I MADE YOU?
YEAH, I MEAN,
DID YOU SEE HOW FAST
I WAS JUST GOING?
WE'RE GONNA WIN.
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT, SON, FINE.
I'LL BE RIGHT OVER HERE
DOING MY PRE-RACE
DEEP BREATHING EXERCISES.
DON'T BE ALARMED
IF IT LOOKS LIKE I'M SOBBING.
OH, AND IF MY EYES
START TO WATER,
THAT'S NORMAL, TOO.
[SOBBING AND WHIMPERING]
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH DAD?
TIMMY, DO YOU
KNOW WHY I USE
THE CLEARLY DANGEROUS THINGS
YOUR DAD MAKES FOR ME?
IT'S BECAUSE
I LOVE YOUR DAD
AND IT MAKES HIM HAPPY
TO SEE ME USE THEM.
[STILL SOBBING]
JUST...
DOING...DEEP BREATHING.
I WON'T MAKE YOU RIDE
THE BIKE HE MADE,
I'M JUST SAYING
IT WOULD MAKE YOUR FATHER
HAPPY IF YOU DID.
OH, MAN!
Bike: COME ON, TIMMY!
WE'VE GOT A RACE TO WIN.
WOW! I...
I CAN'T!
I WANT TO WIN,
BUT NOT IF IT
MAKES MY DAD SAD.
YOU KNOW,
IF HE REALLY
LOVED YOU
HE'D LET YOU
RIDE ME!
HEY, DON'T SAY THAT!
MY DAD LOVES ME.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
HE'S NOT LYING?
HOW DO I KNOW
YOU'RE NOT?
WELL, I'M A BIKE!
YEAH, AND YOU'VE BEEN
MANIPULATING ME
TO KEEP ME AWAY
FROM MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY!
COME ON,
WE'RE GOING HOME.
NOT A LOT OF TIME!
YOU RIGHT, ME WRONG.
JUST BECAUSE I CAN
WISH FOR SOMETHING
DOESN'T MEAN I SHOULD.
BUT TIMMY,
I'M YOUR BIKE!
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE
NOT A VERY NICE BIKE.
AND I DON'T WANT
TO RIDE YOU ANYMORE.
THAT'S IT!
BYE-BYE, PSYCHO-BIKE!
HEY!
WHAT THE--
I'M INDESTRUCTIBLE,
REMEMBER?
WAIT.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
OUTSIDE?
SURE, TIMMY!
BUT, TIMMY!
SSH!
WHAT'S THAT
REFLECTIVE THINGIE?
Timmy:
SUPER BIKE'S MIRROR.
IT BROKE.
BUT HOW?
WELL, IT'S JUST
A STUPID MIRROR.
THAT'S IT!
IF THE MIRROR FALLS OFF
THE SUPER BIKE
IT'S NOT A SUPER MIRROR
ANYMORE.
IT'S JUST A PLAIN OLD,
REGULAR MIRROR.
IF I CAN TAKE
THE BIKE APART
THEN IT JUST BECOMES
A BUNCH OF REGULAR PARTS.
FOLLOW MY LEAD.
HEY, HEY!
I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE BEST
BIKE EVER.
OH, MY GOSH!
IS THAT A SCRATCH
ON YOUR FACE?
WHERE?
RIGHT THERE,
ON YOUR NOSE.
CAN I GET THAT FOR YOU?
THE BEST BIKE
IN THE WHOLE WORLD
SHOULDN'T
HAVE A SCRATCH.
WHAT WAS THAT?
NOTHING.
THERE IT IS AGAIN.
YOUR CHAIN
IS SO DIRTY.
I CAN'T HAVE YOU WIN
WITH A DIRTY CHAIN.
Bike: HEY,
THAT'S NOT MY CHAIN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M JUST TIGHTENING
A LOOSE BOLT.
I KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE.
FINE!
IF I CAN'T
BE YOUR BIKE,
NOBODY CAN!
Wanda: TIMMY!
HURRY, TIMMY!
TIMMY, DON'T GO!
HI, SUPER BIKE!
MEET SUPER SCREWDRIVER!
SUPER TOILET.
AAH!
SO MUCH CLOGGING!
HEY, WANDA,
CATCH!
P.A.: TAKE YOUR PLACES
AT THE STARTING LINE,
DADS AND SONS.
HEY, DAD!
HEY! WHERE'S
YOUR COOL BIKE?
I'M RIDING IT.
WHAT COULD BE COOLER
THAN A BIKE MADE BY MY DAD?
YE--REALLY?
YEAH, ANY DAD CAN
GO OUT AND BUY A BIKE.
YOU LOVE ME ENOUGH
TO MAKE ONE YOURSELF.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT COOL.
AW, YOU'RE
JUST SAYING THAT.
SO.
RIGHT! LET'S GO!
WE'VE GOT
A RACE TO WIN!
P.A.: ON YOUR MARKS,
GET SET,
GO!
[STARTER'S PISTOL FIRES]
[LAUGHING]
ISN'T THAT SWEET.
GRRR!
SUPER BIKE,
MEET SUPER TOILET.
NO!
HEY, I CONQUERED
MY FEAR.
OH, OH!
[GURGLING]
Cosmo: HUH! IF I COULD
JUST LIGHT THESE CANDLES,
WE COULD EAT.
DID IT EVER OCCUR
TO YOU WE'RE IN
A FISHBOWL
FILLED WITH WATER?
THAT'S WHY I'M TRYING
TO LIGHT THESE CANDLES.
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO DRY UP
ALL THIS WET FOOD.
HEY, GUYS. WHAT'S NEW?
UH, THE LAWS OF PHYSICS.
I GOT A REPORT ON
DINOSAURS DUE TOMORROW.
I WISH MY ROOM WERE
A PREHISTORIC FOREST.
[SHRIEK]
[THUMP THUMP]
COOL. THANKS, GUYS.
WHEW. WE'LL HAVE TO CLEAN
THIS ALL UP BEFORE WE LEAVE
TOMORROW MORNING, TIMMY.
WHAT? WHERE ARE
YOU GOING?
WE'RE GOING
TO FAIRY WORLD.
WE NEED TO GET OUR
CROWNS CERTIFIED,
AND OUR WANDS
ARE DUE FOR THEIR
3,000-WISH TUNE-UP.
AND I'M GETTING MINE WAXED.
[SHRIEK]
SORRY WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO ZAP TO YOU SCHOOL
TOMORROW, SWEETIE.
THAT'S OK.
MY DAD CAN DRIVE ME,
PROVIDED HE HASN'T
DONE ANYTHING STUPID
TO THE CAR.
YOU TRIED TO MAKE
A GIANT FIGHTING ROBOT?
SO? THE DINKLEBERGS HAVE ONE.
BESIDES, YOU CAN TAKE THE BUS.
WAIT!
DARN IT.
WELL, AT LEAST
IT'S A NICE DAY.
[THUNDER]
I HOPE COSMO AND WANDA
ARE HAVING FUN.
Man with German accent:
BEFORE WE TUNE UP
YOUR WANDS,
WE MUST TUNE UP YOUR
PUNY FAIRY BODIES.
IT IS TIME FOR WAND-UPS.
1, 2. 1, 2. 1, 2.
HEY! I MADE A MONKEY.
SO DID I.
MONKEY
WAND-UPS, NOW!
1, 2. 1, 2...
[YELLS]
I ALREADY MISSED
FIRST PERIOD, BUT I'M
STILL IN TIME FOR...
[BELL RINGING]
GYM? WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE'RE PLAYING
DODGE BALL.
IT'S DRIES
VERSUS WETS.
THINK FAST.
[TIMMY GROANING]
OOH, MY ACHING WINGS.
WELL, AT LEAST TIMMY'S SMILING
FACE AND CHEERFUL DISPOSITION
WILL MAKE THE PAIN GO AWAY.
I DON'T SEE
A SMILING FACE.
THERE IT IS.
OH, SORRY, SWEETIE.
WE WERE GONE LONGER
THAN WE THOUGHT.
OH, WELL, GREAT.
BECAUSE YOU GUYS HAD TO POOF OFF
TO CAMP HAPPY CROWNYVILLE,
I GOT RAINED
AND VOLLEYBALLED ON.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW HARD IT IS TO BE A KID.
YEAH. HAVING US GRANT YOUR
EVERY WISH ALL DAY LONG
MUST REALLY TAKE
A TOLL ON YOUR NERVES.
BEING A FAIRY IS NO DAY
AT THE BEACH EITHER.
OH, RIGHT, HAVING UNLIMITED
MAGICAL POWERS AND ACTING
GOOFY ALL DAY LONG
WOULD DEPRESS ANYBODY.
HOW DO YOU STAND IT?
WELL, IF YOU THINK IT'S
SO EASY BEING A FAIRY,
WHY DON'T YOU TRY IT?
YOU'RE ON.
I WISH I COULD BE
YOUR FAIRY GODPARENT.
[GULP]
HEY! I'M TIMMY!
AND I'M TIMMY.
AND I'M A FAIRY.
AND I CAN FLOAT.
[CRASH]
Mom: WOW, HONEY.
YOUR GIANT FIGHTING
ROBOT REALLY WORKS.
AAH! IT'S YOUR PARENTS.
GET IN THE FISH BOWL.
RIGHT, RIGHT!
OLD FISH.
NOT SO EASY IS IT, SPORT?
LET'S TUCK
TIMMY IN...
WITH MIGHTY, FIGHTING
ROBOT ACTION.
[ALARM SOUNDING]
THINK FISH ME FISH--
GOLDFISH!
[TIMMY SIGHS]
COOL! I'M A GOLDFISH.
I'M--AARGH!
I FORGOT TO GIVE
MYSELF GILLS!
[GAGGING]
AH, SWEETIE,
YOU FEEL WARM.
AND YOU LOOK
POSITIVELY
GREEN.
WARM? GREEN?
THOSE ARE ALL THE SYMPTOMS
OF STEAMED BROCCOLI!
GET THE THERMOMETER
AND THE SALAD SHOOTER.
I'D BETTER GET THE FISH
A THERMOMETER, TOO.
GOOD NEWS, HONEY.
I'M FIGHTING THE DINKLEBERG'S
ROBOT CAR TOMORROW.
Mom: TIMMY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING UP THIS LATE?
IT'S WAY PAST YOUR BED TIME.
BUT, UH, BUT...
NO BUTS.
STRAIGHT TO BED, YOUNG MAN,
AND DON'T MAKE ME GET
THE GIANT ROBOT IN HERE.
TIMMY? WHAT ARE
YOU DOING IN HERE?
YOU WERE
JUST IN THERE.
UH, NO I WASN'T.
WELL, THAT SETTLES THAT.
BUT YOU KNOW
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO EAT SWEETS
THIS LATE AT NIGHT
OR CHANGE FROM
PINK TO GREEN.
Timmy: SEE? I'VE GOT
A RULE BOOK, TOO.
IT'S CALLED
"MOM AND DAD."
NOT SO EASY BEING
A KID, IS IT?
JUST WAIT. YOU'RE IN FOR YOUR
OWN RUDE AWAKENING TOMORROW.
OOH! LET ME GUESS.
I HAVE TO USE
MAGIC TO SOLVE
ALL MY PROBLEMS.
NOT YOUR PROBLEMS.
OURS.
TOMORROW'S SATURDAY,
AND THAT MEANS WISHES,
WISHES, AND MORE WISHES.
AND AS OUR FAIRY GODPARENT,
YOU HAVE TO GRANT THEM ALL
NO MATTER HOW STUPID.
AND, MAN, AM I ALL OVER THAT.
GOOD NIGHT, INKY BUTT.
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[RINGING]
♪ GOOD MORNING, TIMMY ♪
HEY, GUYS, LOOK.
I FINALLY GOT
THE FISH THING DOWN.
CHECK IT OUT: GILLS.
WELL, THAT'S
JUST GREAT, TIMMY.
I WISH YOU WERE A PUPPY.
BUT--
WE WANT A PUPPY!
DARN IT!
I STILL CAN'T
GET THAT RIGHT.
[GASPING]
CAN'T...BREATHE.
NEED...WATER.
[YELLING]
AND I WISH I HAD
A HOT FUDGE SUNDAE.
COME ON,
LET'S PICK IT UP, KIDDO.
Vicky: HEY, TWERP.
GUESS WHO?
VICKY!
Vicky: YOUR PARENTS ARE
IN A GIANT ROBOT FIGHT,
AND I'M IN CHARGE.
GUESS WHAT RHYMES
WITH "CHORES"?
MORE CHORES!
LOOK AT ALL THIS STUFF
SHE'S MAKING US DO.
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE
FOREVER WITHOUT MAGIC.
BUT LUCKILY...
Both: WE'VE GOT
A FAIRY GODPARENT.
WHAT?
OH, GODPARENT.
WHAT NOW?
I WISH THE TRASH
WAS SOMEWHERE ELSE.
OK.
HA! PICK UP
THE TRASH AND
THE OCTOPUS, TWERP.
[HEDGERS CLIPPING]
THERE! ALL NICE
AND SYMMETRICAL.
WOW! I DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW I KNEW
THAT WORD.
[MOTOR ROARING]
[DAD GASPS]
MY HEDGES!
CURSE YOU,
DINKLEBERG.
HA! TAKE THAT,
[POUNDING]
MAN, AM I GLAD
YOU'RE HERE.
I WISH THE HEDGES
WERE FIXED.
WHEN DO I GET TO HAVE ANY FUN?
Dad: COME BACK HERE,
DINKLEBERG.
HEY! WHAT--WHOA!
MAN, I JUST CAN'T
GET THE HANG OF
THIS FAIRY BUSINESS.
I NEED TRAINING.
THAT'S IT.
I'LL GO TO FAIRY WORLD
AND LEARN HOW TO BE A BETTER
FAIRY THAN COSMO OR WANDA.
FAIRY WORLD?
SCARY WORLD.
YOU'RE NOT THAT SCARY.
YEAH? WELL,
HERE'S A PHOTO
OF YOUR
GRANDMA'S FEET.
[SCREAMS] IT BURNS.
FAIRY WORLD?
HAIRY WORLD.
[MOOING]
DAIRY WORLD?
HAIRY WORLD.
OH, DARN IT.
FAIRY WORLD!
I DID IT.
YOU FAIRY WITH
SILLY, PINK HAT.
YOU MUST DO
WAND-UPS--NOW!
1, 2, 3...
Wanda: OH, WOW.
THIS REEKS.
WHERE'S OUR
FAIRY GODPARENT?
WHAT DIFFERENCE
DOES IT MAKE?
AS LONG AS VICKY'S AROUND,
WE CAN'T MAKE WISHES.
WOW! IT'S SO CLEAN,
I CAN SEE MYSELF.
AND NOW I CAN'T.
GOOD THING
THE GARBAGE
DISPOSAL'S BUSTED.
START SHOVELING!
I'LL BE BUSY
SLEEPING.
SHE'S WORSE
THAN JORGEN.
Timmy: AND HOW DOES THIS HELP
ME IN BEING A FAIRY GODPARENT?
TO HONE THE MAGIC
REFLEXES.
A NEEDY CHILD COULD
WISH FOR ANYTHING AT
ANY GIVEN MOMENT.
YOU MUST BE READY.
BIG DEAL. I CAN FLY.
[SCREAMING]
SAVE YOURSELF,
NEW FAIRY.
THINK FAST.
I--I--WAIT, THAT'S IT.
THIS FAIRY STUFF
IS HARDER THAN I THOUGHT.
AND I'M SICK
OF THESE THINGS.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE
IT, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GO BACK TO BEING
A PUNY, LITTLE
HUMAN BOY.
YEAH. I'M NOT MUCH
OF A GODPARENT.
BUT BEING A KID IS ONE THING
I KNOW I'M REALLY GOOD AT.
BUT BEFORE I GO...
[MOO]
Jorgen: OOF.
DAIRY WORLD?
FAIRY WORLD.
OH, DARN IT.
[LAUGHING]
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU
HAVE JUST AS MUCH JUNK
TO DEAL WITH AS I DO.
JORGEN'S A CREEP.
YEAH, WELL, VICKY AIN'T EXACTLY
A TRIP TO CHERRY WORLD EITHER.
AH! OOH! CHERRY WORLD!
CHERRY WORLD!
CAN WE GO THERE.
I WISH HE HAD A MUZZLE.
PUZZLE? CLOSE ENOUGH.
I THOUGHT BEING
A FAIRY WOULD BE FUN.
BUT I LEARNED IT'S
MORE FUN TO BE A KID,
BECAUSE I HAVE YOU GUYS
TO MAKE IT BETTER.
SO, UH, I'M, UH...
APOLOGY ACCEPTED, SPORT.
WE WISH YOU WERE
A KID AGAIN, AND WE WISH
WE WERE FAIRIES AGAIN.
DARN IT.
[MOOING]
FINALLY. DAIRY WORLD.
[CRASH]
Dad: AH, FINALLY.
I CAN USE
THIS FOR MY
MILK-POWERED ENGINE.
MOO?
[THUMP THUMP]
DON'T BLAME ME.
I'M JUST A KID.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND NICKELODEON
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--