Deep in the Alaskan wilderness.
This year, we got
something to prove.
- Extreme gold miner Dustin hurt...
- Let's go.
- Leads his crew of fearless miners...
- Whoo!
To the most remote
claims on earth
I feel like the guys
are hungry right now.
Hunting for nuggets where
no one else would dare.
Really hungry. I'm loving it.
Good to go.
Diver in.
Risking everything...
- Get out of there!
- Watch the swing.
Do or die, amigo.
He would have been dead.
This is still not how I die.
- For the big score...
- There's gonna be giant nugget
just about 10 feet down.
This season, they
finally hit the jackpot.
- Nugget!
- My god!
Everything we've heard is true.
There is so much
gold down there.
Breaking the record books...
That's the biggest
nugget in gold rush history.
But face a catastrophe...
Hey, guys, I have some bad news.
No one is ready for...
Never known life
without Fred hurt.
- Yeah.
- You guys ready for this?
- We don't have to set up camp.
We don't have to move anything.
We go in there,
open everything up,
get the dredge out,
get up creek and go.
In remote southeast Alaska,
veteran gold miner Dustin
hurt and his band of brothers
are heading deep into
the Alaskan wilderness.
Let's get some good gold, guys.
On a mission to start mining
operations earlier than ever before.
And I can't find the
tent or the camp.
Did you see it?
By the way, you can't
see anything right here.
I got to figure out how
to get on top of this stuff.
We can find the right ledge.
We can probably do that.
Y'all ready for that?
Yeah.
We're probably going to run
over a whole bunch of rocks,
so everybody don't trip over.
Whoa!
Come on.
Whoa. What the was that?
- We're not going to make it!
My god! That was insane!
That's not my intention.
I thought hopefully I could
get up on top of the snow
and maybe it would go.
All the ledges, look how
tall all the ledges are.
We're so close to camp.
30 miles north of
the nearest town
lies Dustin's mining
camp at nugget creek.
He sunk his life
savings into buying it,
but getting there is a risky
nine-mile journey up the sercu river.
The dangerous access
is why it's rumored
to still have legendary
chunky nuggets.
We have to freaking take
all this snow out, dude.
All right, let's get the
shovels, and we got
- to get some of the weight out.
- Yeah.
We're trying to find a water track for the
air boat to ride on all the way to camp.
And what it looks
like is it got too narrow,
and we started busting
through snow, and I got us stuck.
The whole point of
getting up here early
was so we could get digging before
the rain comes and floods us out.
But right now, we can't
even make it to camp.
I knew we'd be digging
snow, but I didn't think
- we'd be digging snow out of the boat.
- No.
Dude, that was
crazy even for me.
My god.
Sorry, guys, I tried.
We got most of the way.
If we can just get this out.
Well, it was too
narrow, obviously.
We got no choice, man.
We have to follow this.
It's not looking good
for us making it to camp,
which we could see camp,
but I can't get up on these banks.
I'm going to keep
trying, though.
So I'm wondering if I should
cut y'all loose, go by myself,
and try to jump up on
top without killing us?
Yeah.
And then try to come get
you if I can ride on the snow.
You ready to push out?
Let's go for a shove.
All this is just
gonna slide off.
We're gonna turn it on and...
There we go. Ready?
Yep.
- All right, up.
- Watch yourself.
- We made it!
- Holy, we made it.
We made it! Yeah!
- No way!
- Yeah!
I knew I should have stayed on.
- What are you doing, Carlos?
- Trying to get up on the shelf.
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
- Hell yeah!
- I didn't think I was going to make it.
Let's go jump some.
Yeah, Carlos.
Woo!
Let's get to the other side now.
I agree.
All right, let's get a camp.
Look, we were so close
to the gold last year.
It's driving me crazy,
knowing what we left out there.
I just grabbed the dredge
and just yank it up there
and start dredging.
That's all I want to do, too.
Woo-hoo! We got this down.
We're crash-test dummies.
- Whoo!
- We're here, boys!
Back at nugget creek.
Let's get in the water.
Last year, Dustin shifted
his focus to the remote
and inhospitable
nugget creek claim,
rumored to hold nuggets
worth up to $50,000 apiece.
The word is that nugget
creek has more gold up there
than I can handle.
More gold and bigger gold.
That's promising.
With a little bit of luck, this
could change our entire lives.
But those dreams quickly
turned to nightmares
when his two crews were annihilated
by a series of ferocious storms.
That is so loud.
You can hear the boulders
rolling down the creek.
Sound like I'm in a Texas
thunderstorm right now.
We're about to lose everything,
and there's nothing I can
do but watch it happen.
This place is destroyed.
I'MMA call in the
season. That's it.
We're done with this.
Mother nature beat us last year.
After all that flooding, it
destroyed my bank account,
- I can tell you that.
- Yeah.
And it was a choice between
completely stopping this
or basically going
to debt to do this.
So I went into debt to do
this, and this is where we're at.
Couldn't afford to bring
everybody back, so this is it.
This is us. We either
weren't going to come back,
or we're going to have a
single crew, and that's it.
And I decided on us.
We're going to have to
hit it as hard as we can
- because we know the rains are coming.
- We got to.
We got to make up for
what we didn't do last year.
That's true.
Dustin is down to
just a five-person crew.
And to make matters
worse, he will have to face
the season ahead without
his most trusted ally.
I have to find out
how Fred's doing.
They just diagnosed him
with severe brain cancer.
Quite frankly, I think
that this is probably going
to be the last time I see him.
Um...
We'll see.
It's pretty sad to
say that out loud.
I think that's the first time I've
really, really said that out loud.
Mining legend, Dakota Fred
brought his son, Dustin, to
Alaska over 10 years ago.
They can go on by, baby.
The two mined side by
side, sharing good times
- 280 ounces of gold.
- Yeah!
Hell yeah.
And bad.
What the hell are you doing?
That does not sound like
condescending bull to you?
But nothing could stand
between father and son
and their dream of
a bonanza in gold.
Hey, Fred, can you believe it?
We're both diving in
McKinley creek together.
Double the dredges,
double the hurts.
But Fred's recent diagnosis
changed everything.
- Hey, Fred.
- Hey, what's up, man?
How's it going, man?
- Good to see you.
- Yeah.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
So how you doing, man?
I guess you know I got...
Good old brain tumors right now.
My balance is down a little bit.
A little bit of blurry vision.
It's progressing every day.
Sorry to hear that, brother.
That's too bad.
So how long did they give you?
They don't know.
I mean, anywhere from a
few months to six months.
I know you're concerned,
and I know it bothers you.
Hell, I've lived a good life.
Yeah.
We're gonna miss
you up there, man.
Everybody likes
having you around.
I want you guys to go up there
and have one hell of a season.
I know you got a good plan,
and I'll be rooting for you.
Hopefully, you
make it long enough
to where we can
show you some gold.
- I'll be looking forward to it.
- Okay.
That's my goal.
To hold out long
enough to see some gold
come out of nugget creek.
So, bring me some.
I'm gonna try with all
my might, but, yeah.
- All right.
Love you. You take care.
I love you.
Hope we get to see you again.
Pretty damn sad.
I've never known
life without Fred hurt.
Nobody's ever ready
to let somebody go.
You just deal with
it when it happens.
That's it.
- Love you, hon.
- I love you, too.
I'm heading up to
Alaska with his blessing.
He wants me to succeed.
He wants me to find gold.
He wants me to have adventure.
He doesn't want me sitting
here watching him die.
So, it's gonna
be a little rough.
Snow's a little deep.
The things that we
do to go for this gold,
it's a 1,000-foot hike through
deep snow to their camp,
which they left under wraps
through the harsh
Alaskan winter.
. He found a spot.
Gotta catch a breath.
That's destroyed.
That's not good.
That's not what I wanted to see.
To give themselves
a head start this year,
the crew left all
their mining gear
in a steel-reinforced tent to
protect it from the elements.
Everything is under snow.
Our tent, our buggies,
the dredges are buried.
This mother was
supposed to be snow proof.
This was a big setback.
Yet again, I messed up.
I bought the wrong
tent, obviously.
And now we're set back.
Um...
The most perfect day to
go out and start dredging,
and I'm not out there.
I'm picking up the damn mess.
Did we lose everything?
On our first day, it's a
rescue mission for all our gear.
Phase one, find out
what's in this destroyed tent.
At Dustin's nugget camp,
the collapsed storage tent
threatens to derail their
early start to the season.
We had an idea right
before the end of last season,
put up a nice tent rated for freaking,
kind of, buku snow, like arctic snow.
And we thought we would
come back this season
with all our gear
nice and toasty,
obviously,
snow wins.
That's slick. Whoa.
- Dang it.
- It's like a maze in here.
I can't move.
I'm literally stuck.
Solid ice down here, too.
- We need this snow out.
- Gotcha.
There's a shovel
right here, James.
- Boy.
- Can you get over here?
Can you reach it?
You have to bring it back
to where you were before.
Okay.
Good job, dude!
Get out of town!
It's not even about
trying to beat the rains.
I need my gear to be okay.
If it's smashed and all of
my dredges are destroyed,
we're done. We're done here.
We got to just go,
because I can't afford
to replace all this stuff.
It's just not going to happen.
All right, I'm going to see if
I can get the dozer running
and start cleaning out some
of the snow around the camp.
Hell, yeah. There's a lot.
I mean, we can
work at it and get it.
- Yeah, man.
- Arnold.
Yeah!
Yeah! Fired right up!
Well, the dozer
started right up,
so that's a good sign already.
That means we
can get rid of snow.
It's a big deal here.
Getting rid of snow
is always a plus.
Dustin gets to work clearing
the snow, while inside the tent,
there's a
search-and-rescue mission.
There's a lot of snow on top.
I'm going to go
to the other end.
- Jeep got up, too.
- Did it?
Yep.
Yeah, the windshield.
Dude, it popped the tires.
- Yeah.
- Bad.
Holy.
- That crushed in the whole roof.
- My god.
I don't even know if
we should be in here.
They're crushed.
Holy moly, dude.
That's not good, bro.
That's not going to happen.
The tires are popped...
- All our vehicles are done for.
- From all the weight.
Well, they're going
to need a lot of work.
Who's going to be the
first one to tell Dustin?
Not me, amigo.
- How's it going over there?
- It smashed everything.
They digged up the
atv. It's smashed too.
Somewhat.
The whole bed is
crushed to the ground.
I can't tell on the axles yet.
I can't get over
there to actually see.
We'll just have to assess it once
we can get some of that off of there.
Let me take a look. I
haven't looked in here yet.
Yep. Okay.
I've been out here
playing in the mud.
The excavator's fine, but
I need to take that bar off
down there before I
can get the excavator out.
Can we maybe get
it out of the tent, or...
- Yeah.
- Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Don't you think it's smashed up?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
It took it pretty roughly.
Don't get in here.
There ain't no reason.
- Just let it happen.
- Okay, gotcha, gotcha, gotcha.
Don't get in here.
Ooh, it's got me pinned.
- Wow.
- What do you need?
- Balls.
- There you go.
- Um...
- It might come.
Just let us get out
of the way and...
Okay, you're good.
- Free at last.
- You got it.
All right. Let's
pull this Jeep out,
see what's left of it.
Sit tight.
Keep driving.
- Watch your fingers and toes.
- Go for it.
- I'm about to bounce on you.
Ooh.
. Wow.
She's in there.
Carlos, James, come hang
off the back of this thing, man.
Yeah!
- Okay. Here goes.
- There it goes!
Yeah!
Thank you, guys.
, man, it's so
apocalyptic, dude.
That poor Jeep.
Let's get the atvs out.
We might have a flat tire.
It's alive!
Yeah!
You don't even
need to tow it, dude.
- It works.
- Holy.
- That's a good sign.
- Yeah, it is.
I thought that thing
was trashed completely.
It's all wonky, but
god, man, it still goes.
That tire flat on the front?
Man, I bet you
that ice came down,
just pushed the air out of that.
- Yeah.
- We're trying to get to this dry spot.
That thing was pancake.
You couldn't tell if it
was going to drive or not.
It looked like it was toast.
Now we got an atv we can drive.
We'll be able to get
around in the snow.
That's a huge win
for us right now.
- So...
- Yes, it is.
- Takes a licking, keeps on ticking.
- Right.
How are the dredges
looking over there?
Did they make it?
You know what?
All the dredges
are on this side,
and they all look just fine.
I cannot believe that made it.
That is awesome, man.
The one thing that it
didn't smash is my dredges.
They made it, and
it was just blind luck.
- That was it.
- Hang on, hang on.
The dredges got pontoons
and we've got snow.
Why don't we try to
stage that dredge?
- You want to drag it up on the snow?
- Drag it up with the atv.
Then it's just a short
jog to get it to the site.
Yeah, we can stage it.
Tell you what, right now, we need
to finish getting our cabins fixed up.
Yes, then we can
go check it out.
So first thing tomorrow,
we'll get the tracks on that atv,
and we'll drag that
dredge up to the creek.
That's a great idea, Paul.
Hopefully, we can
get minin' real soon.
Well, you slept hard, cos
I could hear you snoring.
- Yeah, I slept hard.
- You didn't wake up at all?
I woke up at 1 o'clock.
It was still dark. I
had to take a piss.
Then that freaking light,
Paul's light came on.
I said, thank you, god, man.
Check it out. I've got
something cool to show you.
It's in a map.
- And it's from 1928.
- Wow.
This is the known
perimeters of our claim
if you go on the online stuff,
it is different than
the original stuff.
I got a hold of
the original stuff,
and this is... This
is our boundaries.
And what I've been told is
we, and this kind of proves it,
that we're about 200
to 300 feet upstream,
too far, what we thought
was our property line.
Dustin spent the
whole of last season
battling at what he thought was
the southernmost limit of his claim.
But the 1928 survey map
has revealed that his boundary
extends 250 feet further down creek,
gifting him the potential
of new gold-rich territory.
So I'm pretty psyched
about this map, guys.
- Yeah. Me too.
- And what it did for us,
I think it's a good spot to dig.
Last year, we had
to walk right by it,
because I thought it
wasn't on our property.
Yeah.
But it's within our
reach to dig there.
It's a good settling area for
ancient gold that came down.
Yep.
And it settled there,
and everything else
smoothed off on the other side.
- That's freaking awesome, dude.
- Come on.
You see, the way I see it,
too, big boulders, big gold.
You know, if the big
boulders stopped right there,
the big gold's gonna
drop out right there.
It's gonna be it, man.
Nugget patch, bro.
Just picking them up and
putting them in your basket.
I haven't seen any damn gold.
- Man.
- There's no speculation until I see it.
- Yeah.
- Right, right, right.
This is not real until we
actually hold it in our hands.
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
So we can talk about
how much we're gonna get,
but the truth is, if
we don't beat the rain,
it's all for nothing anyways.
So we have to beat it.
Yeah.
We have to be to the
bottom of this thing.
No time wasted. We
have to get up there.
We have to smash this.
Just absolutely dig it out.
Just... Just everything you can.
And then when it's flooding,
you can take your break.
- All right?
- Yep.
All right. Everybody know
what they were doing?
All right.
Man, I can't wait to go mining.
Last year, we found out
how hard it was to drag
these dredges up to the creek.
So we need to put
tracks on this atv.
We're going to put these
dredges on the snow
and slide them right up.
We want to take
advantage of the snow
so we don't have to drag
it over all the boulders.
Come on.
Yeah, a little bit more.
Yeah, there you go.
- Back on.
- That's it. Yeah.
That is almost it.
Hold on. Stay right there.
Stay right there. That's it.
I just got to tighten
this up, but it's over with.
It shouldn't be a
huge accomplishment,
- but it really is right now.
- It really is.
All right. That's
it. Tracks are on.
Let's move the dredge
up to the cul-de-sac.
All right.
We're way ahead of
the game right now.
- Yes. Absolutely.
- I love it.
Just ride in.
Just make sure we
don't hook anything.
Yeah, we'll have to
watch those boards.
I'll walk behind it
to help us guide it.
Yeah, baby.
That's no problem, dude.
Get on top of it, Paul.
There you go.
Look at the mountains
behind him. That's badass.
How badass is this, dude?
Looks like a freaking
dog musher, dude.
So we're going to beat one
of the all-time honors this year.
They did it in the fall and the
winter when there was snow.
Get it set up,
things melted down,
their equipment
was sitting there,
and they were ready to go
as soon as the snow melted.
The frenzy for Alaskan gold
began over 120 years ago when
the discovery of gold in the Yukon
sparked the original gold rush.
Thousands of intrepid adventurers
raced to the chilkat mountains,
eventually digging out more
than 80,000 ounces of gold
worth over $160
million in today's money.
It's estimated there's
200 million ounces of gold
still in the ground in Alaska,
but only in the hardest
to reach locations.
We made it!
My gosh, it's so
bright out here.
We're weeks ahead now.
Dude, we're way ahead, man.
- That saved a lot of time.
- Good job on the idea
of dragging it up in the snow.
It's better than trying to
carry it out here by hand, man.
- My god.
- Let's get this going.
We're just one step closer.
We need to be in that
water yesterday, all right?
Yesterday.
All right. Let me go
look at this creek, man.
Just see what we
were dealing with, right?
Yep.
- It sounds mild right now.
- Man, look at that water.
Look how clear! Whoo!
Man.
Holy, dude.
Do you remember how
hard of a time we had just
getting across from here
over to there last year?
Yeah, I do.
One of the things I'm
worried about right now
is last year when we
went up there, it was ice.
Giant slabs of
15-foot thick ice.
And you can't see up
there to see what's going on.
So I'm going to
grab my little drone.
I'm going to fly it up there
and see what we're going to see.
Hopefully, when the
drone goes up creek,
he can locate our dive site.
Best case scenario,
we can set shop up
and start dredging tomorrow.
Let's just tilt this
straight down, shall we?
I am so confused at what
I'm looking at right now.
That's got to be big-ass
Boulder right there.
That's all that ice that we
were looking at last year, isn't it?
Whoo. Look at that.
So let's back up.
All right, where's
my new property line?
Let's look up.
There it is. That's
it right there, look.
That looks perfect, actually.
So do we have to go through
that ice bridge to get up there?
I think so.
It's the snow Bridges
that freak me out, man.
That's stopping us from
dragging that dredge up that creek.
That is a big snow bridge, man.
I got to make a plan.
In order to pull our
dredge all the way up
to our dig spot, there
is one snow bridge.
And we have to melt
through this stuff really quick.
Not like last year.
We spent so much
damn time cutting on ice.
I'm not having it this year.
We need to be in
this water yesterday.
You guys ready to melt some ice?
Hell yeah. That
snow bridge has to go.
Desperate to get a
jump start on the season,
the crew waste no
time getting to work
on the 20-foot snow
barrier blocking their path
to the new section
of their claim.
- Yep. Got it.
- There we go.
Going for the drop.
This year, they've
come prepared with
a new weapon in their arsenal.
Right now, what
we have is kind of...
Convoluted.
We have a water pump.
It's gonna pull
out of the creek.
It's gonna pump it
into a high-pressure
water pump over to a
heater that's gonna convert
the water into really hot steam.
Dustin's plan?
Use the bush fix
device to create a jet
of pressurized hot water
capable of slicing through
the 20-foot-high snow barrier
like a hot knife through butter.
- Ready to run?
- Yeah.
Man.
Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Nice!
Yeah!
Good pressure!
Look how quick that
is! Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
That thing works great!
This thing's working perfect!
Look what we got now!
No, no problem.
Big boulders, no problem.
Flood?
We're working on that.
Dude, this water is
scorching hot, dude.
- Yeah.
- Scorching hot. Holy moly.
I can see the steam
coming out underneath it.
So the hot water helped, right?
My gosh.
That's a game changer, man.
This is cheating, dude.
I love it.
Dude, I bet you can get
that big chunk to come off.
- I bet you can get that.
- That's what I'm trying to do.
Nice.
The hot water and
the pressure together
cutting right
through ice Bridges.
That's pretty awesome.
That's a win for me today.
It's going to cut
weeks of snow cutting
the way we were
doing it into hours.
It's nice that it worked, but I've
accepted that it's going to work.
And now I've already
moved on to the next stage,
which is decision
making and where to dig
and how to dig it.
And what are you doing and...
And the only person to
blame when this is over with,
if I fail, is me.
But if I succeed,
I get that too.
Hopefully I succeed this year.
This is where
we're going to dig?
This is what I want.
While James and Carlos battle
the mammoth snow barrier,
Dustin, Paul, and Wes head
upstream to inspect the ground
inside their new
claimed boundary.
Yeah. Check it out, man.
Our property line,
just so you know,
- okay.
- Is right the here.
This is our property line.
It goes right through here.
The fact that this is going
down, and as wide as this is,
it makes a great gold
catch, because the canyon
narrows back down, it's
going to slow the water down,
and this is a fallout area.
Yep.
- That would be the inside bend.
- I think that's so close.
- That's tough.
- Yeah.
Fifty feet up from the ice bridge lies
Dustin's newly extended boundary line,
containing a section of
prime ground as it lies just
below a steep, narrow
drop-off in the river.
Capable of carrying
the largest and heaviest
material on the creek,
it runs directly into the
slower-moving waters
of the inside bend
where gold, 19 times
heavier than water,
can settle and could have
deposited the monster nuggets
this creek is famous for.
We're going to start right here.
Where the snow patch is, we're
going to go right through that.
Matter of fact, while
he's cutting that ice,
we can start popping
some of these rocks, man.
Why not?
They're going to be
done with that soon.
I need these rocks.
That one, that one, that
one, anything that'll crack.
All right. I'll do that.
Don't get hurt. Don't die.
To quickly remove
the heaviest boulders
from their dive site,
Paul will blast them
into smaller pieces
using targeted
rock fracturing technology.
So the mission for
today, drill and crack
as many big rocks as I can find.
It's the perfect time for me to
come over here and break rocks.
The more rocks we get
broke now, the better off
it'll be when we get
the dredging spot.
Years past, there's no way
we'd be busting rocks right now.
We'd be still trying
to set up camp.
It's so nice being ahead
of the game right now.
What?
Don't need no frickin' blanket.
I'd like to see
the rocks explode.
You guys are so
frickin' sappy, man.
Everybody ready?
Fire in the hole!
Perfect! Whoo!
That did more than
I thought it would do.
- Yeah, George, it's a lot more.
- -Holy
right now it's working great.
We're making big
boulders into pebbles.
That looks like bedrock
underneath this one.
That might be interesting.
I'm seeing that bedrock.
It could be a good thing
because it might just be a fin
that comes across,
and if that's the case,
we've got a plunge
pool up there.
There's a plunge pool.
The gold's not going
past that plunge pool.
There's going to be
a lot of gold up there.
So hopefully, that's just
a fin that's going across.
I think we're going to cut
through this ice like nothing.
This is going to be
easy for us this year.
Paul has already busted
rocks to clear space
for our new dive site.
Fire in the hole!
This is awesome.
- James, look at the water.
- I see that.
Look at this water,
dude. Cave-in, dude.
We're about to have a landslide.
Holy we got to get out of here.
Every so often,
we get that steam
coming underneath the ice.
That's a telltale sign
that we broke through.
For this crew to
succeed in the untamed
wilderness of Alaska,
they must operate in the zone
between craziness and insanity.
- Okay, that's getting a little scary.
- Yeah, dude.
It's starting to scare me, man.
Oh, there it goes.
- Woo-hoo!
- Man.
Yeah!
It scared the out of me.
We need gold.
Everybody needs gold.
- James, look at the water!
- I see that.
At nugget creek, a landslide
upstream has turned the creek
into a raging torrent
of murky whitewater.
Holy!
We must have had a landslide!
With all these snow
Bridges that we have, just like
the one we're trying to cut,
there's a bunch of them upstream,
so anytime one of them lets go,
it puts a lot of dirty
water and debris...
It closed up. We
gotta get out of here
because that means it
dammed up the creek
and when it melts that snow,
it's gonna be a wall of water.
Keep an eye on that for sure.
It's not doing nothing, dude.
It's not even cutting, man.
Yeah, we did get some
chocolate milk in the water,
meaning that we got a
landslide up above us.
That's a big, big problem with
any machinery that uses hot water
or any kind of water filtration.
We went from 100%
destroying down to 50%.
No heat.
What the is up with
that pressure washer?
They have no pressure.
- They have no pressure.
- No pressure.
What's going on?
Yeah.
Look, you see? Hey,
you see the steam?
Getting this out of
the way will mean
that we'll be dredging
way faster than last year.
So that's great. That's
frickin' awesome.
We can now bring
the dredge up here.
I think what we have is
about a month and a half
before all hell
breaks loose here.
Can we get enough gold
in that month and a half
to stretch out?
We're here already,
man. We're already here.
I know.
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
This place is for real.