- Mornin', fellas.
- Mornin'.
In remote southeast Alaska,
Dustin hurt and his crew
are on the richest
gold streak of their lives.
- Hell of a day, James!
- Yeah, man.
These guys, they worked so hard.
We're getting gold and
we're getting it early.
But we're not just getting
regular gold, we're getting big gold.
Like, huge gold for this area.
James went down and
found more gold in one day
than we've had in entire seasons.
On his last dive,
James delivered the biggest
single day gold haul ever.
So, we're gonna weigh this gold up.
All right.
My god! 1.19.
- I told you! I told you!
- Holy moly, dude!
Put some of them other ones on there.
That's absolutely the
biggest one we've ever had.
- My god!
- 3.87 ounces.
- Wow.
- -Almost four ounces in one day, James.
Yeah, man!
Look at the size of those
nuggets you got, dude.
- Look at that...
- I'm gonna have a heart attack... Nuts.
That's a $3,000 nugget. That
one nugget is worth three grand.
Well, maybe more.
James, you've had
the best dive so far, man.
- Ever. Ever!
- We've been ever doing
just about half an ounce
per dive until today.
Yeah.
Everybody, just look at
this, feel this, and enjoy it.
James found a bunch of nuggets.
We found the gold line, finally.
It's probably only about this wide.
But it's an actual line that
goes straight up the damn creek,
and we just need to follow it,
and there's gonna be plenty of this.
Now we gotta put in the work.
Put in the work, get the gold,
and it's going to change our entire lives.
That wall is coming down on you.
Gonna fall on your head and
crush you like a damn bug.
Holy crap, man! You couldn't
be in a worse place in the world.
Get out of there!
Right back!
Watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it!
I have visions of it being the worst day.
Is the gold worth it?
I just don't want to die.
We spent seven years
just killing ourselves.
We stuck it out. We put in the effort.
We got this.
Whoo-ho! Look at that.
Black gold...
My god!
Look what you just found, buddy.
There we go.
That's the biggest
nugget in gold rush history!
Another day, another dollar. I'm excited.
Just 12 hours after their
best day of mining ever,
the crew is ready to pick
up right where they left off.
We know that there's gold here now.
We just gotta go get it.
- I wanna see it.
- I gotta hold it.
And then you gonna see
that hoop and hollering.
You know what I mean?
The jig, you know...
Doing the jig and all that.
I gotta get focused for the gold.
Over two months ago
the miners were
handed the ultimate test.
Whoa!
Mother nature beat us last year.
We couldn't afford to
bring everybody back.
So, this is us.
We're gonna have to
hit it as hard as we can
because we know the rains are coming.
The scaled back operation
has meant double the work.
- Keep going.
- Keep going. Keep going.
Keep going. Keep going.
It's going underwater.
Pull, pull, pull, pull, pull, pull, pull.
And a relentless fight to overcome
a never-ending barrage of obstacles.
Watch out behind you!
Carlos is pinned!
Get him out of there!
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
Whoo. Okay, got it.
Every time mother nature
tried to knock 'em down...
Carlos!
- You all right?
- Something popped.
The crew fought back
with everything they had.
Holy moly, man!
Whoo! I kicked its butt!
And their determination paid off.
- , a nugget!
- No way!
It's a nugget?
First gold ever this early!
Until a bombshell rocked
Dustin and his crew.
I got a message this
morning that, Fred died.
And he went peaceful in his sleep.
He said he wasn't in any pain.
- I'm sorry, man.
- -Sorry to hear about that.
Try to be patient with me.
- Just lost my father.
- Yeah.
And he'd give you the shirt off his back.
That's enough of that.
That's too much.
Driven to honor Fred's legacy
I wish Fred was here with us.
Maybe from above, he's helping us out.
The crew refused to back down
from their toughest season ever.
That just drops off, man, to oblivion.
Holy moly!
I hit the jackpot today. Big nuggets!
My first thought was to call to tell Fred.
Everybody wants to be that
person to come up with nuggets.
It's a contagious disease.
Once I see the gold,
the excitement's just gonna... Boom!
Change everybody's future for the best.
Gold, gold, gold, man.
- All right, here's the deal.
- You're gonna dredge.
All right.
- You're gonna find gold.
- -Dredge, find gold.
- All right, guys.
- Going in the water.
All right.
- Nice deep hole, guys.
- You guys did a great job.
Right about where you're at, Carlos,
on that shelf, is where I was
seeing nuggets yesterday.
- Gotcha, man.
- I'm looking. I'm looking.
I'm looking.
Can I get that sprayer
down here, please?
- I got it right here.
- Thank you.
Looking for James' nuggets.
The gold.
Carlos uses the high-pressured hose
to break up the centuries old hard pack
and free the ancient gold locked inside.
You know what, like, seven
years we've been burned,
so we all got that feeling of, like,
"is this actually gonna happen?"
And it still doesn't feel like it.
- Yeah, I know.
- -Well, let's see how this goes.
I know it seems too good to be true.
It might be that we blow this out and...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
- Yeah.
I know there's nuggets left
behind because I didn't finish it.
- Yeah.
- I wanted it so bad.
I'm like, "you know what? I'm gonna
let Carlos get some of that glory."
In this hole, and I am
finding the small gold
in the layer and the hard pack.
Yeah, yeah.
- All right.
- Yeah.
And it seems it's going toward the Weir.
So, it's the Weir.
So, I mean, it's going down.
I'm at hard pack.
- All right.
- I like to hear that.
Following the deepest
part of the bedrock
on the center line,
Carlos found an anomaly.
Instead of going up, the
creek bed is dropping down
into what could be the
perfect nugget catch.
Carlos is finding gold.
Which I love.
He said this bedrock's
coming up on the right side,
and it looks like it's going
deeper towards the Weir.
Whoo!
That's the color I wanna
see coming across right there.
The red and the black both, that's
absolutely what we're looking for.
That's what I call acing nuggets.
We've gotta keep an eye on the
blocks on that one rock right there.
I don't like that.
Those aren't so bad, but that one,
well, that one's too, but...
He might be able to pull it off
the wall and pull it right behind him.
The more he comes into the Weir,
the steeper the wall
gets, the more chance
of some of these rocks
falling in on top of him so...
Following the nugget-rich center line
is taking Carlos straight into the Weir,
where towering 12 ft above him
are a thousand boulders that could
come crashing down at any time.
I come over here periodically,
check 'em, make sure nothing's moving.
If they move, I'll get them out of the way.
We do not wanna crush the divers.
Man, that's pretty good.
This is a little bit deeper spot.
Getting a lot of material out, for sure.
It's a crack, man.
It goes underneath the hard pack.
Carlos, get out of there!
- What happened?
- I don't know.
Come get him.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Did you get clipped.
Yeah. Right there.
That was a close one,
dude. How big was it?
That big. It just took off my index finger.
- You good?
- It's good. It's good. I got this.
Despite being hit by falling rocks,
for three hours Carlos fights on,
determined to cash in
on their golden hot streak.
What's the story, Carlos?
It's time to double
down and check the box?
Yeah, it'd be good time
to double down, man,
and check the box.
- I'm at bedrock right here.
- It's just bedrock right here.
I'm just curious.
Did he get all of it...
They found... Hey!
My god! Carlos.
I gotta see it.
I gotta see it!
My god.
Let me go show him.
- Holy!
- -I gotta see it!
Carlos, you ain't gonna believe this.
You ready for this?
Look what you just found, buddy.
My god!
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay. Don't, don't, don't...
Holy!
Don't lose that
my god!
Can you believe that?
- You found it.
- Holy!
Let's see it. Let's see it.
My god.
That ain't no joke right there.
That is no joke.
Wow!
That's the biggest
nugget in gold rush history.
Yup.
My god!
- Carlos, Carlos.
- I gotta see it!
You ready for this?
Look what you just found, buddy.
My god!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
At nugget bend,
Carlos has just uncovered a nugget
that could change the
course of their lives.
- Look at that big piece of gold.
- -Wow!
That's at least four ounces, man.
That's the four ounce
nugget we're all looking for!
- Yeah!
- -No, that's bigger than four ounces.
That's the biggest nugget in
gold rush history right there.
Now, we were talking
about, like, a $2,000 nugget,
- that's about a $15,000 or $20,000 nugget.
- -Yeah, dude.
That's gonna be a hard one to beat, man.
Yeah.
Damn it, it's got Clay on it, doesn't it?
Yeah, it still does.
- My.
Nugget bend, man, it's owned its name.
- This is real, real.
- Yeah.
- This is happening for us.
- This is happening.
- My god. I mean... yeah.
- About damn time.
Holy stinkin' moly, man.
You see the size of that nugget?
I wish Fred was here to see that.
I literally do.
Amen. Amen. Amen.
Double amen.
Wow.
Good livin's comin' from here on out.
Got too excited with that big one,
forgot about all the babies?
- Yup. It's gonna be a good cleanup.
- Should be.
- Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
We lost Fred.
He's the one that got us all here,
- but he's still here with us.
- He's helping us out.
I know he'd be so proud right now, so...
This is definitely the
high that we needed today.
We spent seven, eight
years just killing ourselves.
And now, we got this
badass nugget that just...
Kinda like a trophy.
We stuck it out. We put in the effort.
We finally figured out
where the right place
and the right technique to get down here.
We got this.
Now, let's do great.
Hell yeah. We freaking did it.
Hell yeah, fellas. Not a bad haul.
Not at all.
After nearly a decade of mining
in the harshest environments,
Carlos' discovery is proof
there's ancient gold here for the taking.
Good job, everybody. Way to stick it out.
They say that, definition of a winner
is someone that didn't
let losing stop them.
- Yup.
- And...
- Like that.
- We've lost a lot.
Yeah, we have.
- Not giving up.
- It's about damn time.
Set that baby on there
and let's see what it weighs.
Moment of truth.
Dun-dun-dun-dun dun-dun-dun.
- Wow.
- 5.8.
- Yeah!
- Dude, that's freaking... man!
Wow. Almost six ounces.
Hell yeah!
That might be $20,000, guaranteed.
For a specimen like that?
Yeah.
No, you don't get gold
like that for a gold price.
- That's gonna be almost double.
- Wow.
A nugget this big
is worth far more than its weight in gold,
and could be just the beginning
of what nugget creek has to offer.
Well, I went completely broke last year,
so this is a great start.
- It's a great start, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
That one nugget is more gold
than we did at our site last year.
There's no way there's
only one nugget like that
- in that whole freaking creek.
- No.
The whole deal is there
were stories up until today.
- Yeah.
- But it's reality for us now that
- there are big nuggets in this creek.
- -Yeah.
I absolutely guarantee it.
- I couldn't say that before.
- That's true.
Well, soak it up.
- We earned it.
- Yup.
I've gone bankrupt twice, almost,
trying to do this.
It's finally gonna pay
for itself the right way.
- We're at the very beginning.
- The first 200 ft of the claim.
I got a mile to go.
- This is it.
- We found it.
We have arrived.
I live for this.
Up ahead... Holy, man.
He's flanked by rock.
Hey, hey!
Everything above it.
Watch it. Watch it. Watch
it. Watch it. Watch it.
Watch, watch, watch, watch, watch!
He would've been dead!
Today, I'll be getting in the water.
Hopefully, I can get back
down to where Carlos was at.
Clean up that bedrock wall,
and see if we can't put a few more
of them six-ounce nuggets in the box.
At nugget camp,
on the heels of their
biggest gold find ever,
expectations for another
record-breaking day are high.
We are on the gold line right now.
We keep following it and,
get as much gold as we possibly can.
I have a good feeling
about the dive, dude.
We'll see gold.
We'll see lots of it today.
It should be something.
We'll get so much done today.
We're gonna get a lot done.
Whoo...
Hey, Paul?
Yeah?
You got a couple solids on the bottom,
but everything on top is
getting dangerous, man.
Yeah.
So, I'll work all this,
we'll do some box checks,
and then I'll go over to the Weir.
The promise of more giant nuggets
means Paul is ready
to put his life in danger
as he follows the center line up creek,
undermining the Weir, that
could trigger a fatal rock fall.
All this undercut.
All this comes down, those
rocks are coming down right here.
This is where the diver's at.
It's always been one of my biggest
fears, is being trapped underwater.
So, if I end up undercutting it too much,
that'll be my permanent
home. I don't wanna do that.
Something lands on you,
- grab your mask and keep it on.
- Yeah.
- If that don't... Knock me out.
- If you can keep your mask on,
- we can get you out.
- Yeah.
I'll be right there.
Be certain of it.
- You tight?
- Nope, that feels good.
All right, brother. Good luck, man.
Sense that six ounce!
- I know, you set the bar high.
- I got my work ahead of me now.
All right, man. Let's
find some more nugs?
Yeah.
- All righty.
- Where's the hole at?
All right, here we go.
Little bit of overburden down here, but...
- It'll go back.
- Yeah, I think so.
Need you to think about big nuggets.
If you get that image in your head, baby,
maybe you'd be, you know, direct into it.
All right.
I've got a vision of a big black nugget.
James, is that bedrock right there?
- Right here?
- Yeah.
- It sure is.
- That is.
- Paul.
- Yeah?
That bedrock comes straight up this wall.
- Right up.
- Really? That's a waterfall.
This is a little waterfall and
that's the bottom of it right there.
- So this is a big Boulder?
- -Yes, that's what's going on.
I think we'll really get
gold catch. Whole nuggets.
Yeah?
Every gold diver dreams of a plunge pool
beneath an ancient waterfall.
Hope it goes down deep.
And spotted with gold.
Yeah.
Paul, this is all wanting to slide right now.
- Copy that.
- It's moving by itself.
- And it's getting dangerous.
- All right.
Paul, just so you know,
Carlos is going to be
permanently on your line right now.
- Copy that.
- Got real, bro. It got real.
You know.
Things got crazy...
When you had to put a
tender on a diver's hose.
So when something happens, in an
instant, I have to pull the diver back.
Holy, man.
He's flanked by rocks.
Go! Go!
Damn it.
Stand back for a second. Hold on.
It's being undermined.
Let it settle for a second.
- All right.
- He's good to go?
- We're good to go.
- Yeah.
I'm on the bedrock wall, but
I might almost be at the bottom.
He's exactly on that
bedrock on that slope.
- Is he?
- That's where I was at.
That's where you
were getting the nuggs?
That's exactly where I left off at.
Hey, Paul, whatever that
is, it looks good in the box.
That's the color we're
looking for right there.
The next color after that is jet black.
So when we get this red and
jet black, there's always gold in it.
Come on, Paul. You can do it, baby.
You can do it, Paul.
- Yeah, man.
- That was the first good material
you look like you put
across the box so far.
- I've had it.
- -Do we look at the box?
- Go for it.
- Double it down.
Yeah, there's a piece right there.
Yep. Yep, yep, yep.
You got a few pieces for sure.
They're just underneath
the screen right now.
We gonna keep
adding. Just keep adding.
Do this, come back up.
- Copy that.
- You're on it.
You're on again. That's it.
Come on, man.
- Seven ounce nugget.
- Holy.
What are you doing?
Wow.
That's a weird color.
- It's root beer. Red root beer.
- Look at that.
Whatever you're doing,
just keep doing that.
- Copy that.
- Here's the black. Look at the black.
- The black... -holy.
- There it is.
- Black.
- Look at that.
Black gold. Check to see.
Watch it, watch it,
watch it, watch it, watch it.
Watch, watch, watch,
watch, watch, watch, watch...
You gotta be kidding me.
Sorry. You gotta back
up, back up, back up,
back up, back up. That
wall's coming down on you.
Just as he's getting on to something.
Finally, right?
- All right.
- Back at it.
Come on, Paul. Get me
some gold. Get me some gold.
Hey, Paul. Hey, Paul. The
whole thing's gonna go, dude.
That big Boulder, man,
it's starting to come down.
Paul, Paul, Paul, come on.
It's gonna fall in, man.
It's just getting more
and more dangerous.
This is about to get out of hand.
I gotta pull him out.
If they're gonna fall on your
head, it'll crush you like a damn bug.
Another three feet in there I can't see.
It's just too fast. It'll
be on you. We'll just go,
this is just freakin' freaking me out.
Let's double down.
Let's get the nozzle out.
Yeah, man.
That thing's coming
down right there, dude.
They know the gold is here.
But it's just out of reach.
Less than two hours in,
Dustin won't let Paul push any further.
At least there's two pickers.
You didn't see much?
- Anything?
- Nah.
Two little pieces. What a waste of a dive.
I didn't get a chance to do anything.
Frustrating...
To get pulled out every five minutes.
I guess they seeing a rock move, but...
It's annoying.
He's upset that we pulled him.
But, better than getting squashed.
It's that black rock up there. It
looked like it sagged a little bit
to that whole wall.
That might be one we
can knock in the morning.
Yeah.
Make it, safe for James.
I don't wanna dive in that.
- Kidding me?
- That unstable.
Are we that stupid or what the going on?
- Try not to get so frustrated.
- Yeah.
You get upset with something
and you gonna get yourself killed.
And you'll be like, "that's
what they were bitching about."
- And here we go.
- Holy.
That would have killed you.
That would have got your legs. You
legs were up. Your legs were there.
Yeah.
We'd be trying to pull it
off your legs right now.
A half ton widow maker
just dropped under the spot
right where Paul was diving.
I'd rather you be mad
than dead or pinned.
- I get it.
- -Go ahead and get mad.
Yeah, man. You would
have been peg legged, dude.
That was like some,
wild ass timing right there.
That ain't no lie.
You could have kept dredging
and that would have happened.
He would have been dead.
And now they're laughing about it.
Is that rock on top of this?
- I bet you that rock...
- that rock was on top of it.
- That rock's on top of it.
- All right.
Great call, guys. Great call.
He'd have been on
the end of that nozzle,
right there pinned, and we'd
have been trying to get him out.
I never saw that danger.
Not once.
You guys had my back. I appreciate that.
- You saved my life, dude.
- Dude. Man.
- That's... that's us.
- Yeah.
It's nice knowing as a diver that you
can trust your team to keep you safe.
We're just... we're one
big family here, so...
Credit to those guys. They saved my life.
White water gold mining is
like a game of high-stakes poker.
The chance of life-changing
gold could cost you everything.
I ain't diving in that hole tomorrow.
No. He could fire me.
It's my turn in the rotation to dive.
And, I did not sleep at all last night.
I knew that rock was gonna come down.
I'd just seen it. I had visions of it.
Visions of it being the worst day...
Of him getting crushed
and we can't get him out.
Broken ribs, smashed head.
That was all going through my mind.
I just don't want to die.
Is the gold worth it?
Dustin and his crew have proven
there's life-changing
gold in nugget creek.
But to get to it, they'll have
to put their lives on the line.
We got to a place where we
can no longer be safe and dive.
The guys are scared.
They should be. Paul almost died.
Well...
Now I'm filling in the hole that
we've been digging for days.
This sucks.
To move forward at nugget bend
and clean out every ounce
of gold from the plunge pool.
Dustin and his crew must
take a major step back.
Hole's getting filled in. Hell lot of work.
Start, start, start again.
But the upside... it's safer.
That sound is the
scariest sound in the world.
Especially, when the
diver's at the receiving end.
My job is to keep everybody safe here.
I'm not the safety guy.
, I've become the safety guy. My
god, I've become the safety guy.
How the hell did I
become the safety guy?
I gotta keep these guys
alive. That's all there is to it.
We'll anchor this one back to that.
- To that chain?
- We'll tie that one off.
- Maybe tie that one off.
- That one?
We'll anchor this one back
and then that big one down there,
we'll anchor it back as well.
We're gonna start pulling all
those boulders back downstream,
so, we can get a diver in
and get back on the gold.
Dude, we can put the basket
there and drop them right in.
There you go.
Woo-hoo.
Friggin' send it.
- I love it, dude.
- That thing's badass.
Run another cable here,
up over that way, makes the perfect y.
Should hold this rock in place
and all this will stay right there.
Better to be too safe than not safe.
What do you think, James?
- That one is not a big risk but...
- -Nope.
These three are all tagged up.
All right. Well, I'll get suited up.
If gets in there, he can get to the
bottom where I was at yesterday.
We gotta remember
it's gonna rain tonight...
Yup.
So, we have no idea
what to expect tomorrow.
That's true.
This might be the only
chance we get for that thing.
Now that it's mitigated, Boulder's
all tethered up, I feel safe.
That six ounce nugget is stirring
up gold fever for everybody.
We can't leave the
hole without finishing it.
I need to do this by the numbers.
I need you to do yardage.
Get the yardage out of
there, make sure it's clean.
Slick it, slick it, slick it and when
we run out we run out, all right?
Okay, copy that. Yup.
I appreciate you going in.
All right, James, you're
good to go, amigo.
- How is your vis?
- It's about a foot.
- Foot-and-a-half.
- All right.
Top get back to the pay layer
that held the six ounce nugget.
James must first remove all the material
they washed into their hole.
Also, don't forget, you're gonna
have a giant black rock down there.
- That's the rock that almost got him.
- -Man.
That's your rock, Paul.
- Yeah.
- The rock's pretty big.
I can't even get my arms
all the way around 'em.
What are you thinking?
- How about a choker?
- Choker?
Yeah!
- Good wrap, James.
- Good wrap.
Holy.
Holy moly, Paul. That's yours.
I'll get it right here to the shore.
- My god.
- Holy moly.
Holy.
That's half my body.
- Wow!
- That is half of my body.
Hey, man, that would've
hurt, I ain't gonna lie.
- Yeah.
- I don't think he would've felt it, man.
That would've had me from head to tail.
Hey, you remember the
rock that almost killed you?
- Yeah.
- This is it.
At nugget bend Paul comes
face-to-face with the widow-maker
that nearly ended his life.
That's the goddamn meteorite
- that killed the dinosaurs, bro.
- -Yup.
That would've ended my life.
I would still be in the bottom of that hole.
There would be a
body recovery going on.
Holy.
So, I need dredge a little bit
right here till I find that wall.
Over five hours into his dive.
James is still searching for
more of the six ounce nuggets
that nugget creek has proven to hold.
Let's find the bottom of that bedrock wall.
It already warmed up today and
that water's gonna come up again,
and then that wall's
gonna start caving in again.
Let's get...
Let's get everything
we can get done today.
Not sure but.
James, you find gold?
Sitting in the crack on
the side of the bedrock.
My god! Whoa!
Look at that.
I love it.
- That's the pretty stuff?
- It is.
- I love that patina on there.
- Ruby gold, man.
That's beautiful.
- That's amazing.
- We're on to it now.
Hopefully, there's more.
Make it spotless, man.
And, I see everything down there now.
- Lick it all, man.
- Lick it all.
I know.
- He's just like, "hey. Look at this."
- "Look."
"Yup, there it is."
Good looking stuff.
I just... I think what I'm looking for now is
- that pile of six ounce nuggets.
- -Yeah.
We're spoiled.
All right, I'm just about
done with that hole.
I got one minute left.
James was freaking out all yesterday,
but as soon as he gets
in the water, man, it just...
- It all goes away.
- It does.
I think that's it.
The bedrock channel rises up
in front of me just before the Weir.
It's a dead-end, man.
Over the last two months.
Dustin and his crew have dredged
through 100 feet of prime
big nugget real estate
and cleared nearly 200 tons of boulders
as they chase the gold line.
Now, James has dredged the hole clean
and the rising bedrock
signals the end of the line.
The hole's done.
This hole is done.
- Good deal.
- Can we do a double down right quick
and check and see what's in there?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'd be blown away if
there's nothing in the bottom.
I don't see anything in here.
- Wow.
- Gold does weird things.
I don't get it, man.
Well, I'm glad you got that six ounce
nugget out 'cause it shows something.
I think we tap this thing out, man.
- Yeah.
- -That might be all of it, man.
If you're good, I'm good.
- I'MMA call it then. Good?
- Yeah.
I need to hear it.
Do you think there's
any more gold down here?
No.
All right. Time to move on.
- Let's pack, then.
- All right.
Good dive, man. Good dive. Tapped out.
On to bigger and better gold, man.
- That's true.
- That's it. Moving on.
It's beyond me why there
wasn't a pot of gold at the bottom.
Gold is where you find it.
I think we can leave this spot knowing
that we didn't leave anything behind.
After eight hard weeks,
dredging 12 ounces
of the biggest nuggets they've ever found
the empty sluice box shows it's time
to move on to the next opportunity.
Finally getting gold.
The only thing that's
been missing in my life
is more gold and we're getting there.
Not as much as I wanted but nugget
bend produced a six ounce nugget.
I can only imagine what's
about to happen for us.
- This is gonna be our best year, ever.
- It already is.
It's already our best year.
This is awesome.
Up ahead, this season...
We're done with you!
Time for us to move on!
This is gonna be a challenge again.
This is the rematch.
We got a solid plan.
And we have to win or
else we're done for, y'all.
Welcome to my nightmare.
Almost got killed just now.
- Hurry up. Come on.
- Lift. Come on.
Help me lift this mother.
This place is trying to kill us... Holy.
Are we gonna let it?
- You all right, man?
- You look beet red.
I'll let you know.
I'd like to see what our future's gonna be.
I swear I can hear a waterfall.
Now, that's a waterfall, man.
Holy, dude.
Looks like it's holding a bunch of gold.
Get that gold! Woo-hoo!
There it is!
Holy.
What would you sell this for, man?
$60,000 or $70,000.
About damn time, man.
We know there's big gold.
All we gotta do is go get it.
We're dredging!
I got something for ya.
This place is gonna pay
for the rest of my damn life.
My god!
That's beautiful.
Finally, we made it.