SUMMARY
In my job you can't help but notice
how unfair society is.
I heard from him again.
It's immigrants this time.
- What are you doing here?
- He slept over.
Saga's my colleague, you're my son.
- He's published something.
- Why Henning, not the others?
- Has he got Henning?
- He disappeared in the night.
- There was a letter by the door.
- I won't get my brother back!
- Why were you with that Charlotte?
- To interview her.
Have you slept with her?
Get up and pack your bags.
Leave, I don't want to look at you.
I died in the night.
I didn't see a tunnel or a light.
- We need a search warrant.
- How did the blood get there?
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
I'm going to find you.
- It's me. Stefan.
- Charlie walked along the street...
- Who poisoned you, Sonja?
- I saw him.
- The police car was stolen.
- Maybe it wasn't stolen.
What if he's one of us?
What if he's a police officer?
EPISODE 7
What the hell...
THE BRIDGE
Hi, this is Mette.
Please leave a message.
Hi, it's me. I understand
that you're hurt and angry.
You know we'll have to talk.
Can you please call me?
I'll try to get home tonight.
Have a nice day... today. Bye.
If he's a police officer,
it explains a lot.
He hasn't left a single trace.
- Hardened criminals avoid that.
- They're only in it for the money.
- Why does he do it?
- It's personal.
He selected people he wanted to die.
This time it was Henning.
- But why a police officer?
- He knew we were looking for Anja.
Only the police knew
that she was in the parking garage.
He took a police car
and no one noticed.
He's got riot gear. The stun gun
was stolen from a police office.
The shots
were fired by a professional.
He's very organized.
He can handle
weapons and explosives.
- He's in the military.
- A police task force.
We have to be very careful if we
pursue that line of investigation.
We're looking for Danish officers,
so we'll run the investigation.
- Why Danish officers?
- Danish police car and riot gear.
- He speaks fluent Danish.
- I'll single out the few it might be.
None of them
would have shot their colleague.
Have you got
an opposing theory, Martin?
So?
I'll send you what we've got.
We'll talk later.
- How about some breakfast?
- No thanks.
- Why not?
- I haven't got time.
It seems to upset Martin
that it might be a colleague.
- Or has something else happened?
- He's annoyed with me.
- Why?
- His son spent the night with me.
- Did he miss his train or something?
- No, he likes me.
- How old is his son?
-18. I don't see why he's upset.
- August can do as he wants.
- That's irrelevant.
You can't have sex
with your colleagues' children.
We didn't have sex.
I said that he spent the night.
You should tell Martin.
He probably thought what I did.
- That's not my problem.
- Do it as a favour to me.
OK.
A school bus with five children
has disappeared.
BODY FOUND IN SKIP
Sonja? Sonja?
Sonja! It's Stefan.
Do you recognize me?
Charlie walked along the street,
he found a parcel.
He thought it was tobacco,
it was dynamite.
- Is this a long time ago?
- It's the present, sister.
- She's awake.
- Yes, she's awake.
- Don't leave me.
- Listen. I'll never leave you again.
I'll never leave you again.
- Hi. I didn't think you'd come.
- You were right.
It was wrong to expose
the psychiatric patients.
- I'm sorry.
- OK.
You're a good guy, Åke.
I didn't appreciate you enough.
I have to go.
A school bus has disappeared.
- Five children missing. It's big.
- Congratulations.
- Hi. Åke said you were ill.
- I feel better now.
He killed
that police officer, Henning.
Any news about the fifth problem?
Have you checked your e-mail?
- Are you going to?
- I don't think so.
- It doesn't make a difference.
- What?
All of this. Everything I write,
everything he sends me.
In the end everything is meaningless.
- Nothing really matters.
- What's happened, Daniel?
- What does he want?
- I'll be damned if I know.
Lillian sent us these,
they match the criteria.
He died this winter.
He's dead as well.
It's been years.
Why didn't they check?
We've received new data.
I didn't sleep with your son, Martin.
August and I didn't have sex.
You clearly wanted to know.
- Listen.
- What is it?
Communication between a police
helicopter and the stolen car.
HK4 to car 319. What's your status?
HK4, this is 319.
Zebra, zulu. Zebra, zulu.
- Car 319, repeat.
- Nothing to report.
Car 319, message received.
"Zebra, zulu" means "all well".
ZZ is a snore.
It's used by officers in the US
with task force training.
- Does that match any of the profiles?
- They're all trained by the FBI.
Did he find "zebra, zulu"
on the Internet?
- John?
- No hits from the big search engines.
Do any Swedish officers
match the profile?
- John? Any Swedes?
- There are seven.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Right, thank you. Bye.
Sonja Lindberg
has come out of the coma. Martin?
There's a school bus
and 15 officers to investigate.
- Sonja saw him.
- We don't know why he's got the bus.
John? Can you get us pictures
of the seven Swedes?
She doesn't answer.
I've tried to reach Mette all day.
- Why do you keep calling?
- She kicked me out.
- Why?
- I cheated on her.
Didn't she know
that you don't believe in monogamy?
What? What makes you think that?
- I do.
- Then why do you sleep with others?
- Have you been in a relationship?
- That depends on the definition.
I don't mean sex
with guys twenty years younger.
- August and I didn't have sex.
- Right. So what did you do all night?
- Talked, watched a film, ate, slept.
- In the same bed?
Is it unthinkable to spend
the night together and not have sex?
- I can see why you're cheating.
- Give it a rest.
- OK.
- Thank you.
It's all your fault. You waved
my wallet in front of Mette.
Did you sleep with
Charlotte Söringer?
What was it like?
It's Mette Rohde.
I'll be right down. Thank you.
- Hi. Is Sebastian Sandstrod here?
- Yes, over there.
- Hi, I'm Mette Rohde.
- Sebastian Sandstrod.
- What's this all about?
- I want to show you my software.
I don't purchase IT systems.
- But you use them.
- Yes, the ones the company buys.
They only think of the company.
I think of what's good for you.
Lots of salesmen
try to revolutionize my life.
I'll be the first to succeed.
- How?
- The long or the short version?
- The really short one.
- A better overview of the profits.
Less coordination, so less overtime.
More time with the family.
- Too long?
- No, but is it true?
The short version is that it is.
You have my full attention
for five minutes.
- That's not much.
- You have to earn more time.
This way.
Is it my fault that Mette's angry?
You could have
given me the wallet at work.
So the problem isn't that you cheat,
it's that Mette found out.
No. The problem is I want her back.
Do you get that? I love her.
- You should have thought about...
- ...that. I'm fully aware of that.
- What are you doing here?
- I've got some questions, Sonja.
- She just woke up. Can't this wait?
- No. I'm Saga Norén.
Look at these pictures. Did you see
who left the bottles of wine?
You said that you recognized him.
- Sonja? How are you?
- Fine.
- That's good.
- Yes.
- Look at them.
Concentrate, look at every picture.
- Focus, Sonja.
- She only just woke up.
- Do you want to tell me something?
- No.
- Are you OK, Sonja?
- Sonja, Sonja...
It's OK, Sonja.
We're not all equal before the law.
That's a problem.
Not just for the police.
People should take it seriously.
- "Equal before the law."
- "People should take it seriously."
Jesper Andersson,
born 1969, bilingual.
Danish mother.
He lived there until he was 12.
He graduated in 1995 and was given
training with the FBI 1998-2000.
He was in the national task force.
Two colleagues were killed in 2003.
He went on sick leave
and got divorced in 2005.
Then he became a regional
coordinator against organized crime.
He's good at youth work
and well-liked.
We need
a connection to the victims.
No one but the investigation team
should know about the surveillance.
- Should we talk to him? He's here.
- Do it.
Ask Pilkvist to give me a call.
- Is Jesper Andersson here?
- No.
- Do you know where he is?
OK. We just wanted to talk to him.
Do you want to leave your name?
Hello?
- He's Swedish. You said Danish.
- Things indicated that he was Danish.
- But Jesper Andersson is Swedish.
- Yes.
- What are you getting at?
- Nothing.
- He wasn't there.
- He isn't at home either.
- Gry is searching his home.
- I'll go, she might miss something.
If it's him, he's busy. I'll show you
in John's office. Come here.
Millions of children
around the world are exploited.
If a product is very cheap,
someone has been made to pay.
We don't care, they're not
our children. But these are.
- Where's this from?
- Truth.se and the Danish page.
Each child represents
a line of business.
There are companies in our region
that contribute to child labour.
I want their premises torched
before the time is up.
One fire saves one child.
All can survive, it's up to you.
A list of the companies
will soon be made public.
Bloody hell.
The companies.
They're not just any companies.
Should we assume it's true?
- Are they involved in child labour?
- He hasn't been wrong yet.
If we print it,
there'll be consequences.
Five fires. Insurance companies
will make less of a profit.
- Five children will survive.
- It's not that easy.
I thought it was. Does it matter
that they're important advertisers?
- We can't encourage arson.
- We won't. We pass information on.
- As we've done for a week.
- We won't print it.
- We'd instigate crime.
- You've spoken to the lawyers.
We'll send the list to the police.
This is police business.
Because it affects
those that pay your wage?
I've put up with your crap,
but you're almost crossing the line.
- I'm not killing five children.
- Oh, you just crossed it.
Thanks.
The five minutes were well spent.
- Or how long? An hour and a half?
- That's including coffee.
Your software sounds interesting.
I'll talk to my colleagues.
Thanks. It's simple, really.
It's like life itself.
Figure things out and sort them out.
How do you sort your life out?
If I knew, I would have been
on tour giving well-paid lectures.
Do you need to sort your life out?
Who doesn't?
I'm sorry. That's too personal.
- It's too soon. I'm sorry.
- That's OK.
- Your five minutes are up.
- Yes.
I'll send you some info.
You can forward it to colleagues.
- Thank you.
- No, thank you.
Navid? Have you found a link
between Andersson and the victims?
Kerstin Ekwall
used to be a prosecutor.
- They might have met.
- Here's the list of companies.
We can't watch
all warehouses, offices and shops.
We have to try. Excuse me.
Anne? Look for a link between
the companies and the children.
- John has a list for you.
- OK. Thanks.
- John? The sounds in the room?
- None are from the surroundings.
- What have you done?
- I assume it's a rhetorical question.
- I said no.
- Yes, and I didn't give a damn.
The list is everywhere,
in case you take it off our web page.
It's gone already.
Like you'll be in less than a minute.
- Labour laws aren't like that.
- Get out of my editorial offices.
Here's an update on Andersson.
- The ex-wife says he's a loner.
- That matches the profile.
His mother in Båstad hasn't seen him.
He's got a cottage in Småland.
We're in touch with colleagues,
but have to tread lightly.
- Have you spoken to Gry?
- Nothing of interest in the flat.
We're no closer to him
than we were this morning.
Excuse me. We've found
the body of Sören Holmgren.
His wife Veronika has disappeared.
Their social worker is
Stefan Lindberg.
- Do you know where he is?
- He's at the hospital.
- His sister's there.
- Good. Thank you.
He did it. Stefan Lindberg did it.
There's blood between
the floorboards in his bedroom.
Saga? The school bus
was found after a tip-off.
Five fires in two hours.
It's as if he wants them to die.
He wants people
to act on instinct, not think.
Children affect people's emotions.
Just like kittens.
Isn't this the worst thing he's done?
He'll kill five children.
They're five small persons,
he killed more homeless.
They don't know they're in danger.
Bjørn Rasmusen knew he was dying.
- So you have no maternal instinct?
- No. Why do you ask?
The windows are covered up.
No movement.
He used explosives before.
We'll send in the bomb crew.
- Are you ready, Milos?
- Yes.
- Hi, Saga.
- Hi.
The children aren't in the bus.
They're not filmed inside a bus.
- Maybe he moved them.
- He wouldn't.
The transmission might be recorded.
We have to expect the worst.
Can you hear me, Milos?
That's good.
You can follow Milos' camera here.
- What kind of a warehouse is it?
- We're looking into it.
What kind of a warehouse is it?
It's urgent.
- Yes, Milos?
- The outside of the bus is OK.
It's not wired on the outside.
- Back up.
- Can you back up a little?
- What does it say?
- Can you improve the picture?
Wait.
"Thanks for helping out."
- "Thanks for helping out"?
- Yes?
OK, thanks. It's a furniture company.
- Which company?
- Hulbos Möbler.
- We have to get him out.
- I've opened the door.
The company's on the list.
Get him out!
- Now!
- Abort and come out now.
- I'm in..
- Abort now!
A warehouse is on fire.
The missing school bus is there.
The police bomb technician
narrowly escaped the explosion.
It's not known whether
the five children are in the bus.
There's reason to believe
that they're not.
"Thanks for helping out."
Now it's on TV.
Five fires will save them. We don't
know if this company is on the list.
The building is engulfed in flames.
It'll take a while to...
- Saga Norén.
- Hi, it's John.
"Furniture" was taken off the list.
A child is saved.
- Yes. Thank you.
- OK. Bye.
- Did the police get hold of you?
- What?
The uniformed ones
were looking for you.
Yes, yes. We've...
We're done. Thanks.
- You were gone a long time.
- I'm sorry.
We're going away.
- Where to?
- I don't know. Away.
- Together?
- Of course. We'll always be together.
- Come on.
- Now?
We'll make a fresh start.
A fresh start. Do you hear me?
We'll walk away from this shit.
Come here.
OK? OK.
OK?
Sonja, come here.
We'll go the other way.
Hang on, I have to sit down.
Listen to me, Sonja.
I've messed up. Do you hear me?
I'll take care of you and make sure
you're fine. I love you.
- Stefan!
- Listen to me, Sonja.
Do you remember when you were
taken away? I said I'd wait for you.
Can you promise me the same thing?
Wait for me.
- You said we'd be together!
- We will be. Wait a little longer.
Stefan! Stefan!
- "Clothes" was taken off the list.
- Some kids torched a clothes store.
- Have they been arrested?
- Yes. People called them heroes.
There are three left. Excuse me.
- Has he got children?
- His son just turned two.
I'm here with Erik and Anna.
Their boy has been kidnapped.
Companies are on fire.
- How does that make you feel?
- It's terrible, but...
It only affects material things.
It's more important to get
my son back. They have insurance.
My boy can't be replaced.
I need the number
for Gladans Choklad in Malmö.
Can you transfer my call? Thank you.
Hi, my name's Daniel Ferbé.
Yes, that Daniel Ferbé.
Your company
has been tied to child labour.
I'd like to interview you
to get a more balanced coverage.
Who should I talk to?
Can you transfer my call?
- And Jesper Andersson?
- I might issue a wanted notice.
- He'll disappear.
- He already has.
- Have we got anything on him?
- Navid? Have you found anything?
I compared his working hours
to the perpetrator's activities.
He often works nights.
He's often in Denmark.
No one knows where he is.
- Is there a link to the children?
- They seem to be randomly selected.
A toy store's warehouse is on fire.
Another clothes store as well.
There are three minutes
and two fires left.
- You want it to succeed.
- Yes, and so do you.
"Sport" just disappeared.
How is this personal?
There must be a link to Andersson.
It might be a parent.
Five fires will save five children.
The companies must be connected.
Navid? Look for a link
between the companies.
There's a small fire at Gladans.
One minute and thirty seconds left.
They're saved.
- Do you think it's a good thing?
- To avoid the death of a child, yes.
Yes, but what if he puts people
up against each other?
If five disabled people die,
five children are saved.
- Or five immigrants have to die.
- That's not what he did.
- People obey him. Aren't you worried?
- There's something new.
- GPS coordinates.
- Find out where it is.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
- Did he lock you up?
- I don't know.
- Didn't you see him?
- Yes.
Look at the picture, concentrate.
Was it him?
Maybe.
He had a beard and an eye patch.
- He looked like a pirate.
- I found these.
They're all saying the same thing.
Thank you.
That was
the last of his five problems.
- He's done.
- Maybe.
Let's issue a nationwide
wanted notice for Jesper.
He doesn't know we're looking
for him. That's our only advantage.
There'll be no wanted notice.
- What are you doing here?
- I need clothes.
- I want to see the children. August?
- He's not here.
- Will those children be all right?
- Yes, but we haven't caught him.
- I would like to tell you...
- Fetch your clothes and leave.
I love you.
Saga Norén.
What? Now? Yes. Thanks.
Hi. I was just passing by.
- Where were you going?
- Nowhere. I just wanted to see you.
You want to spend the night
at my place.
- If you'll let me.
- No. Your dad doesn't like it.
- Who cares what he thinks?
- I do.
- Really?
- Yes. I have to work now.
- Good night.
Thanks for a lovely day. Sebastian.
- I'm leaving.
- OK, fine.
- How long do we carry on like this?
- I don't know.
- We need to talk to work things out.
- I don't want to see you right now.
- Saga?
- Lithium aluminium hydride.
It was on the floor around the bus.
Water makes it catch fire.
- August slept over at your place.
- Yes.
- Does Andersson know chemistry?
- So you have a camp bed?
Don't you know, or doesn't he know?
- I don't know. You have a camp bed?
- Do you want to sleep over?
No, I was thinking about
someone else.
Who?
Don't touch that.
- It's brand new, isn't it?
- Yes, it's not been used.
- So August slept in your bed?
- Yes.
He stopped by the police station.
August.
- What did he want?
- To sleep over. I said no.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Do you want some food?
I'll cook something.
Is this cooking?
- Isn't it hot?
- Yes, it's perfect.
- Have you always lived alone?
- I lived with my sister a while.
- And with a boyfriend?
- No.
- Why not?
- I'm no good as a girlfriend.
You can't know without trying.
- Is it because of your sister?
- What do you mean?
Do you worry about something
that you should be able to predict?
Many commit suicide
without prior suicidal tendencies.
Of course.
- Do you expect visitors?
- No.
Hi. Come on in.
Martin Rohde is
from the Copenhagen Police.
His wife kicked him out,
he's staying over.
This is Anton.
We have sex now and then.
- Hi.
- Do you want to go to bed right now?
- Maybe I won't stay.
- Why? Martin will take the camp bed.
Yes, but I was thinking...
- We can do it another day. OK?
- Sure.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye. Nice to meet you.
- That was a nice guy.
- Yes.
- I should have left you two alone.
- No, we have to work.
- What's that?
- Jesper Andersson.
- Shit. It's just you.
- Yes, just me.
- What are you doing?
- I'm copying some stuff.
I've put too much time into this
to let Carina take over.
- What are you working on?
- The children that were released.
I know who torched
Gladans chocolate factory.
- Who?
- Just a part of the main office.
- Have you lost your mind?
- I saved a child.
You can't report me.
You have to protect your sources.
- What are you going to do?
- I don't know.
To save a child was intense.
Or maybe I enjoyed
setting fire to the place?
- I thought you'd changed.
- Maybe I have?
- It doesn't seem that way.
- So sue me.
- I thought you were done.
- Thank you for cooperating.
- I was fired because of you.
- What a shame.
You helped me, so I'll help you.
The paper will take you back
if you get an exclusive interview.
- Do you want to meet up?
- We meet up and talk.
And then you get to
hand me over to the police. Daniel?
- Are you pulling my leg?
- No. I never intended to walk free.
I wanted to create awareness
among people.
- I'll face the consequences.
- OK.
- How do we do this?
- I'll give you driving directions.
I'm here.
- Do you get a feeling of déjà vu?
- It wasn't funny the first time.
Do you know what else isn't funny?
To give the truth second priority.
Journalists that can be bought.
Cowards.
People like you, Daniel.
That's really good.
- We're through with each other.
- You're right.