SUMMARY
- Thank you for your cooperation.
- We're through with each other.
One fire saves one child.
All can survive.
- "Thanks for helping out."
- Get him out now.
I didn't sleep with your son, Martin.
August and I didn't have sex.
- You have no job. What's your plan?
- Not to have a plan.
- I'm pregnant.
- Come here.
Did you sleep with
Charlotte Söringer? How was it?
Do you need to sort your life out?
I'm sorry. That's too personal.
I love you, Mette.
- Have you always lived alone?
- I'm no good as a girlfriend.
You can't know without trying.
I'm Emil.
If he's a police officer,
it explains a lot.
He's got riot gear. He took
a police car and no one noticed.
The stun gun was stolen
from a police office.
Did you see
who left the bottles of wine?
- Look at the pictures.
- Sonja, Sonja.
EPISODE 8
- Mind the traffic next time.
- Yes.
- Why did he kill Daniel?
- He doesn't need him anymore.
That's not enough. Kerstin, Monique,
Emil, Henning, Bjørn, and Daniel.
There has to be a connection.
- Hi.
- Jesper Andersson is in. We're ready.
- Hi, Jesper.
Lie down! Lie down!
THE BRIDGE
- Is this why I'm here?
- Why did you think?
I don't know, but I know
what happened at these times.
- You were there.
- I'm in the police.
I know what you're working on.
Do you need DNA or fingerprints?
- I'll agree to anything.
- Fill in the form.
- Check Jesper Andersson's alibi.
- I'll do it right away.
Double check. If he's our guy,
it'll seem to be in order.
Have John check
Daniel Ferbé's computer.
- "If he's..." Are you unsure?
- We mustn't lose our objectivity.
I had a closer look
at Jesper Andersson.
Two colleagues were shot.
He saw a psychologist.
- Emil Fernskog.
- He took him out of active service.
Look for a link to the other victims.
We'll try to get his medical records.
Are you ready? Come on.
Is Mette OK with
you staying at my place?
- She doesn't think we'll have sex?
- Hell, no. You're not my type.
Have you got a type?
Charlotte and Mette are dissimilar.
- Will you get a divorce?
- No, it'll work out.
- Have you worked it out before?
- Yes.
So you've cheated before?
- What the hell are you up to?
- I'm chatting.
- As colleagues do.
- Don't. You're no good at it.
- Am I annoying you now?
- No.
- Sometimes I do?
- Yes, you can be very annoying.
- More than others?
- Much more.
Why do you ask? You don't care
what people think of you.
No, it's important
what you think of me.
- Does Mette cheat as well?
- No.
In unhappy relationships both
often seek happiness elsewhere.
- We're not unhappy!
- Then why do you cheat?
- Do you really care what I think?
- Yes.
Then give it a rest. Thank you.
- Hi.
I've hardly slept since it happened.
I keep picturing all the blood,
the guy and the sword.
- How can I work here?
- We want some medical records.
He doesn't have any.
It was his first appointment.
Not Lars Jönsson,
but Jesper Andersson.
- I don't recognize the name.
- It's been a couple of years.
Jesper Andersson stopped
seeing Emil five years ago.
- Before my time here.
- We want his records.
- I can't give them to you.
- Yes, you can.
The privilege is waived if a crime
has a minimum sentence of a year.
A medical secretary must know that.
- You still don't think it's him?
- I didn't say that.
- You don't want to be overly sure?
- I want to be sure when I'm sure.
If it's him, he knows we don't have
DNA or fingerprints. There's no risk.
There are links to Emil and Henning,
two of the victims.
- That leaves three.
- He might have met Ekwall.
Andersson is on his way back.
His lawyer's coming.
A lawyer? The perpetrator's
in control. Everything's succeeded.
- Why would he need help?
- We're really clever.
Not the way he sees it.
Why would he kill homeless people,
a politician, a prostitute-
- manipulate schizophrenics,
and threaten children?
Tell us about
when your colleagues died.
That's OK, I'm happy to tell you.
It was a bilateral operation
against a motorcycle gang.
We'd surrounded the building
and were waiting for the go-ahead.
The Danish hadn't secured
the building across the road.
Well, we were fired at.
Two of my colleagues died.
You blame the Danish officers
for the deaths. They messed up.
- They should have died instead.
- No, I've never said that.
You said it to your psychologist
on 23rd August.
That was less than a month
after the shooting.
Jesper saw a psychologist
to deal with such thoughts.
- So you were transferred.
- Yes. It was the right decision.
- You didn't think so back then.
- No, but I do now. With hindsight.
With hindsight,
how do you feel about your divorce?
I can see why Maria couldn't take it.
I was angry and hateful.
I turned selfish and mean.
And now you're a middle-aged man
in touch with yourself.
- Do you live with anyone?
- No.
- Why not?
- Is there a point to all of this?
Henning Tholstrup was one of those
that didn't secure the building.
And he was acquitted for negligence
a week ago in Copenhagen.
- I know, I was there.
- Then you also know...!
Then you also know that Henning
was shot and killed the other day.
You commented the verdict on TV.
- In Danish.
- Yes, I'm bilingual. It's useful.
You said we're not
equal before the law.
As illustrated
by the killer's first victims.
- Don't you think it's a problem?
- Yes.
A number of editorial writers
wrote the same thing.
Are they here as well? Then I assume
you've got something else.
Like a motive or a piece of evidence.
Three alibis have been confirmed.
When Kerstin Ekwall was abducted,
he was at a meeting in Copenhagen.
The poisoned wine was left outside
while he was at a youth club.
Staff and youngsters confirm it.
The morning Bjørn was abducted
he worked at a school.
We don't know exactly when Bjørn
was taken. Jesper was there at 7:30.
Bjørn was left alone
just after seven.
Jesper worked with Lennart Fransson
during the gun amnesty in 2001.
We can't prove that Fransson
passed the stun gun on.
- And Ferbé's computer?
- We didn't find it.
The lock was damaged. A break-in.
- Were we too quick to arrest him?
- He matches the profile.
He focuses on a single project.
He's single. He's successful.
- He had a traumatic experience.
- We're getting nowhere.
One more try.
Sonja Lindberg identified you.
How do you explain that?
I don't know who she is.
- She's one of the poisoned homeless.
- Well, I don't know.
- She made a mistake.
- There were 15 photos.
She didn't make a mistake,
she didn't hesitate.
- She made a mistake.
- No. You know each other.
- Did she just come out of a coma?
- Yes, yesterday.
- Can you rely upon her?
- Her eyesight's fine.
She's been homeless
for quite a few years.
Pardon the expression,
but she's a complete nut job.
Jesper has an alibi
for when the wine was left.
I'm sure you've checked it.
- Hans is quitting.
- Why?
He wants to go back to Gothenburg,
closer to children and grandchildren.
It's one hour by plane,
three by train.
How close do you have to be? So?
- So you'll miss him?
- I don't know.
He'll be placed in custody.
- On what grounds?
- Focus on how to spend the 72 hours.
The prosecutor's given us three days.
No stone will be left unturned.
Whatever you've done, we'll find out.
No district court
would ever have detained you.
Isn't that what you said
about the prosecutor?
It'll be harder to clear my name.
The press is having a field day.
You'll be out in 72 hours.
We'll find a way to handle the media.
Three days. They'll rip me apart.
If you want to tell me something,
this is a good time.
No. Nothing.
Thank you.
Can I use the bathroom?
Thanks.
- Hi.
Unlock. Unlock!
Get in.
Get back!
Go!
- How did he manage to escape?
- He had an inside helper.
He used a key card.
- Where did he get the weapon?
- He went to the bathroom.
Someone left him a weapon
in the bathroom.
Check payments, computer traffic,
calls, ex-wife, friends, and family.
Stop all other work.
Make sure you find that bloody car.
- Knock, knock... Am I disturbing you?
- No.
Or maybe a little.
I was going to e-mail you some info,
but I was in the neighbourhood.
- They're nice.
- Yes, they're for my mother.
Oh... right.
I'm just joking, they're for you.
- For showing up unannounced.
- Thank you.
- I'll fetch a vase. Coffee?
- Yes, please.
No blood or sign of violence.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Jesper established a foundation that
supports youth that counteract crime.
- What about it?
- The office is at Jesper's.
- There's no separate address.
- It's his foundation.
But it rents
part of a property in Frihamnen.
- What the hell have they been doing?
- They filmed it.
There's no computer and no camera.
Let's check the flat again.
Isn't it weird to keep
photos of your ex-wife on display?
I don't with any of mine.
Look at this. Look at the best man.
Kent Hammar.
Look at this. This is a few seconds
before Jesper arrives.
We thought that Kent just happened
to arrive. But look at this.
This is 45 minutes earlier.
- He's waiting for him.
- They're cooperating. Anne?
Kent Hammar's born in 1975.
He started working here in 2000.
He left Växjö and rented a room
at Jesper's. That's how they met.
Jesper recommended Kent
for the task force twice.
He failed the tests.
He was Jesper's best man. It's been
confirmed that they're close friends.
- They're two, so Jesper has an alibi.
- We're checking Kent's time sheet.
So we had the right guy.
So that's what I can offer you.
Call me if you're interested.
Thank you, it seems very interesting.
Thank you.
For seeing me, if nothing else.
- Are you OK?
- Yes.
- Hey... What's going on?
- It pinches, I've got cramps.
- Has it happened before?
- No. It's just... I'm pregnant.
OK, that settles the matter.
You're going to the hospital.
I've got my car downstairs. Come on.
Saga?
Kent Hammar used his credit card.
- Where?
- A service station. He rented a car.
- Do they know the number plate?
- There's a tracking device in it.
- You know where they are.
- Yes.
Hi, darling.
Where are you? I'll be right there.
Mette is on her way to the hospital.
She's pregnant.
I have to go. Good luck.
- Didn't he have a vasectomy?
- Yes.
They're in the third lane,
the third car from the front.
Space is tight.
There are lots of people. Let's wait.
I have to take a leak.
- Kent Hammar is leaving the car.
- Anne and Navid, get him.
- Jesper will wonder where he went.
- OK, let's get him.
Drop your weapon.
Drop your weapon!
- Send an ambulance.
- He's alive. Take him to the car.
A man has been shot.
It's the police! Don't worry.
An ambulance is on its way.
Hi.
- How do you feel?
- It's painful.
- What happened?
- We'd had lunch.
I just collapsed. It hurts like hell.
- What about...?
- I don't know.
I'm here now. It'll work out. OK?
- Hi. Who are you?
- Martin, Mette's husband.
Hi, I'm Tom. I've been her doctor
the last couple of hours.
The ultrasound gave us two answers.
The children are fine,
and you have kidney stones.
- The children? As in twins?
- Yes.
There are two of each.
Two children, two stones.
- What do we do about the stones?
- It might be enough to drink a lot.
They'll pass out with the urine.
We can't crush them now.
If necessary we'll remove them
through a small pipe.
Drink a lot, pee, take painkillers,
and keep your fingers crossed.
- Is that OK? Good.
- Thank you.
Two more. How will we manage?
Can we talk when I don't have
a jabbing pain in my back?
- How old is she?
- Sixteen or seventeen, perhaps.
Jesper received a reward
for his youth work two years ago.
Yes, he did a good job.
He didn't do it to find victims.
He was trying to compensate.
Both take part, they're sadistic.
Jesper more so than Hammar.
The one we're looking for
doesn't enjoy tormenting anyone.
- They're not the ones.
- No.
- Are we absolutely sure?
- Yes.
- Back to square one.
- I'll go tell the others.
- They're not the ones.
- How do you know?
There's no link between Andersson
and the rest of the victims.
- Maybe they're linked to Hammar?
- What doesn't make sense?
The perpetrator operates alone.
It's risky to have a partner.
How do you know?
Sonja Lindberg identified him.
She's in the films.
They sexually abused her.
The case isn't over.
- Why are you still here?
- We're taking a break.
- Really.
- A coffee break.
- What are you talking about?
- Nothing, we're just chatting.
Really.
I got my period this morning.
- How is Mette?
- Better.
They're keeping her there
for some tests.
- She'll be home tonight.
- That's good.
- How's it gone?
- Fine. They're watching TV.
- Nikolaj's asleep.
- That's good. Thanks for helping out.
- There are sandwiches and coffee.
- Thanks.
- Will you get a divorce?
- No.
This is how it started with mum.
You didn't sleep at home.
I don't know whether you
didn't want to or weren't allowed.
I was a year younger than the twins.
You returned with a bike
on my tenth birthday.
No. I was there from time to time.
Not that I can remember.
I kept my distance. You were angry,
your mother was angry.
Then I had Julie
and made a fresh start in life.
It felt as if I wasn't allowed
to get involved.
You could have let me decide.
Do you know why you didn't?
You always choose the easy way out.
That's just the way it is.
It's how you are.
So am I.
- Did you want me there?
- Yes. For a while.
Later I didn't care about you.
I threw the bike in the canal.
- Did you?
- Yes, the following day.
If you really love Mette,
why do you cheat on her?
Because... I thought...
I thought I needed to.
And I wanted to prove something.
I wanted to be sure
that I'm with the right person.
- Have you worked things out?
- Yes, I have.
In some ways you're a fool.
- So why did you move here?
- To see if you still didn't care.
- Did you?
- You just moved on.
I'm glad you moved here.
I'm happy about this.
Yes?
I spoke to Frida about it online.
She said that I had to
talk to you about it.
That's a clever girl.
Saga? Kerstin Ekwall
used to be a prosecutor.
I've checked her cases.
All that were won, lost and dropped.
One is interesting.
- Are you listening?
- Yes.
There was an accident on the bridge
in 2001. A woman and her son died.
A car got away.
They suspected drink-driving.
The car was reported stolen. There
was no proof that the owner drove it.
I remember.
They suspected Sixten Rockstad.
- Kerstin Ekwall dropped the case.
- Carry on.
The dead woman's husband was
a Danish task force police officer.
Yes, Saga? I'm at home.
You have to come.
It wasn't Jesper Andersson.
- We may have something.
- Mette is fine. It was kidney stones.
- I thought maybe you wanted to know.
- Yes, I want to know.
- When can you come?
- Now, soon, straight away.
- Was that Saga? Saga and I...
- You don't have to say anything.
She told me nothing happened.
- Everything's fine.
- OK.
- "OK"? You sound surprised.
- No, it's just that...
- I went to see Saga at work.
- I know.
She threw me out because you
don't want us to see each other.
- I have to go. Will you guys be OK?
- I just thought you should know.
Saga, there's a visitor for you.
Anton something.
- Hi.
- Hi. What do you want?
- How are you?
- Fine. What do you want?
- These are for you.
- Why?
We got off to a wrong start
with the sex.
And I want to...
- I want to rewind, get to know you.
- Why?
Because I've got a feeling
you're worth getting to know better.
Can we have dinner? Just dinner.
- No sex, you mean?
- Yes, no sex.
- Didn't you like it?
- Yes, I did. That's not it.
I want to see
if we can have something more.
- Hi again.
- Hi.
- Think about it.
- Think about what?
- Do you know who this is?
- Jens. We worked together for years.
- Was he a good police officer?
- The best. He could have gone far.
- What happened?
- His wife and child died.
He never got over it. He was fired
and lost absolutely everything.
Why are we talking about Jens?
- Could he avoid leaving traces?
- Yes, definitely.
Deepfreeze a body for a year?
Start a riot?
- It's not him.
- Kerstin Ekwall dropped the case.
OK, but he's dead.
He blew his head off years ago.
He's in Charlotte Söringer's files.
They evicted him in October 2004.
He threatened them.
- Gry didn't follow up, he's dead.
- She made the right call.
- Are you serious about this?
- Why shouldn't I be?
He's dead. He blew his head off
in his caravan. I saw him.
Did he literally blow his head off?
- Why?
- Was his face missing?
- A friend of Jens is taking revenge.
- After more than five years?
It was bad enough to investigate
the police, but his...
No fingerprints were checked.
No DNA either.
He was in his caravan. He'd blown his
head off. There was a suicide note.
- Isn't there an autopsy report?
- There was no autopsy.
- Why?
- Didn't we know the cause of death?
- Is there no autopsy after a suicide?
- This was a colleague.
Let the poor man rest in peace.
- I'll take these with me.
- I spoke to August earlier.
- Did something happen between you?
- No.
Do you remember our talk with Anja's
mother? Sometimes we tell white lies.
- Is that what you're doing?
- No. Not now either.
You'll discover
that his wife Mikaela was Swedish.
She and the boy
were going to see her parents.
They were pushed against a lorry
and off the side.
The boy wasn't found. There was
no proof against Sixten Rockstad.
- If Jens wants revenge...
- Or someone else.
Why doesn't he
go after Sixten Rockstad?
Yes. Thanks for telling me.
Sixten Rockstad died in Monaco.
Probably drink-driving.
That's what you call poetic justice.
Jens repeatedly asked
if he could investigate the accident.
Or his colleagues, at least.
Sweden refused.
There's a report against Jens.
"...tardy, puts colleagues at risk,
unreliable..."
"...suspected substance abuse...
Relocation and psyche evaluation."
It's signed by a union rep.
- Do you know who it is?
- Yes. Henning Tholstrup.
Daniel looked into the accident.
He was at the same party.
- With whom?
- Sixten Rockstad, in Copenhagen.
He spoke to the staff about how much
Rockstad had to drink.
If he left in his car,
or if someone else did.
- Did he get anywhere?
- I don't know. He received an offer.
A good job, well-paid, free housing.
He left the same day.
- He was paid off.
- It's not unlikely in Daniel's case.
As far as I know he had
no moral scruples whatsoever.
- I'll miss him.
- Thanks.
Thanks for your help.
Saga? Martin?
I've read what we've got on Jens.
A psychological evaluation
advised against active service.
It questioned his suitability
as a police officer.
- The evaluation itself is lost.
- Do you remember the psychologist?
- When was it?
- In the late fall of 2003.
In the end he wasn't with it at work.
He'd given up.
They referred to the evaluation
when he was dismissed.
It doesn't say who carried it out.
- What was Emil Fernskog doing?
- He had an office in Copenhagen.
- He moved to Sweden the year after.
- Jesper Andersson saw him.
Had Fernskog worked with
traumatized officers before?
We've found Sonja Lindberg.
She'll be here in five minutes.
- Should I put these in a vase?
- Yes.
- What did Anton want?
- To take me out to dinner.
He brought flowers
and asked you out.
- Yes, isn't that strange?
- Why do you think it's strange?
Guys ask girls out when they want to
have sex. We're already having sex.
- Isn't that the case?
- No. Well, yes, sometimes.
- What are you going to do?
- When Sonja Lindberg...
- With Anton.
- I don't know.
- Have dinner. He likes you.
- He doesn't know me.
No, he doesn't.
Do you know who this is?
He was like a brother to me.
Stefan saved me.
- Stefan... my brother... is coming.
- Yes.
- I'll wait for him where I live now.
- Jens?
This guy. What did he save you from?
Someone took my stuff.
He kept doing it.
He took my stuff.
He told him to stop.
- He hit him.
- Jens hit the guy that took stuff.
But... he was beaten up later.
Badly, much worse than I was.
All the time.
- What was the guy called?
- His name was Bjørn. It means bear.
Him?
He hit him. He hit everyone.
Thank you. You've really helped us.
- When is my brother coming?
- I'm afraid we don't know.
Go ahead.
Do you want a name? The companies
that were torched are part of Pica.
- Who's the chairperson? Martin?
- I have no idea.
Ida Rockstad,
Sixten Rockstad's mother.
- I spoke to my father.
- Did it go well?
- Better than expected.
- Did you stir his conscience?
Not really. It was good.
Thanks for suggesting it.
Thank me by taking me to dinner.
- Deal! Where and when?
- It'll be somewhere expensive.
I thought you were asleep.
I checked on the children and stayed.
Are you OK?
- Do you remember Jens?
- Yes, what about him?
- Saga thinks he's alive.
- He can't be.
It might sound insane,
but the investigation points to him.
- Well, I'll leave now.
- You can stay.
- Do you mean that?
- Yes.
I thought I would lose the children,
and I was almost relieved.
I'm not sure
I want more children with you.
It felt as if I didn't
have to make a decision.
- Can we get by with more children?
- If our relationship gets by.
Can we get by?
We should publish that photo.
Let's paste it on every wall.
It wouldn't help. He's probably
changed his appearance.
- Do you know what's worse?
- No. What?
He staged his suicide five years ago.
He's planned this longer.
Would gassing Daniel Ferbé
be the end?
Why not?
It's not enough. He's not done.