SUMMARY
- T.T.?
- They call him The Truth Terrorist.
Agree to his demand.
He doesn't like to improvise.
If we force him to,
he might make mistakes.
The property investors
haven't agreed to the demands.
He's saying: A...1...
And then three letters.
- A, J, B.
- Bjørn can see a power meter.
There are three meters
in the same empty building.
Bjørn! Bjørn! Can you hear me?
He shot two from the task force.
- How are they doing?
- One dead, one critically injured.
Sören! Stop it!
- Why are you doing this?
- Because I can.
- Don't walk away!
- Let go.
Or what?
Or I'll have an awkward fall?
He was unconscious.
I watched. Then I walked away.
- Aren't you going to open it?
- I'm not allowed. Not yet.
A samurai fasts
the day before he goes into battle.
EPISODE 5
Lars Jönsson? Hi, I'm Emil.
- You haven't been here before.
- No.
- Did you struggle to find the way?
Emil? No!
THE BRIDGE
Thank you. The best way
to honour our colleague Mats...
is to catch the bastard.
- How are you doing?
- Fine, I'm on painkillers.
Did they find anything
where Bjørn was?
A shoeprint, size 9.
I haven't identified the make yet.
Let's bring in
all men that take size 9.
- That was a joke.
- Yes, I got that.
- Hi, Lillian.
- Henning.
- When are you due in court?
- At one o'clock.
- What are you going to do?
- I don't know.
You want to tell them who did what.
You didn't do anything.
If I tell them...
If that's true, what will happen?
There will be a new trial.
Some colleagues will freeze you out,
most will back you up.
- Can I be charged with perjury?
- That might happen.
- If I'm sentenced, I'll lose my job.
- I would do my best to avoid that.
- That's not good enough.
- Henning... The boy died.
Four officers
will be sentenced today.
They're charged with
bodily harm leading to death.
24-year-old Hadi Hurani died
during an arrest.
Saif? Let's go.
- What are you doing?
- I don't want to go.
- Do it for your brother's sake.
- We both know what'll happen.
- They'll do the right thing.
- Do you really believe that?
- I have no choice but to believe it.
- Right.
Come on.
- Saif...
- You know they'll make fools of us.
A postman and a psychologist
were killed this morning.
The postman's killer
committed suicide.
- Don't you want to take it on?
- Definitely, it's big.
- All the more reason to do well.
- Of course. Let me just...
He's so cute when he gets excited.
It's like throwing a ball to a puppy.
- Daniel Ferbé.
- A miserable front page.
I'm trying to make people
aware of problems.
- That stuff steals attention.
- Then stop shooting police officers.
- They came too close.
- Are you getting sloppy?
- Do you really want to annoy me?
- No, I'm sorry.
- Let's focus on the third problem.
- Which is...? Hello?
"A pat on the shoulder and pills
is the help mentally ill receive."
Åke? Run everything by Daniel,
he decides what we'll use.
- This was my case.
- It isn't anymore, things happened.
You've heard about the murders,
three of them followed by suicide.
A postman in Malmö
was killed with a machete.
A psychiatrist
was assaulted with a sword.
In Copenhagen an axe was used
on a bus and a knife in a stairwell.
According to Daniel Ferbé
T.T. has claimed responsibility.
It's his way of criticizing
the cuts to psychiatric programs.
- That's the third problem.
- How did he do it?
Both perpetrators in Malmö
suffered from paranoid schizophrenia.
He must have spent months
coaxing them into this.
So four murders,
but only three suicides?
The psychiatrist's colleagues
overpowered the perpetrator.
- Is he here?
- The first interview gave us nothing.
This is the second interview
with Lars Jönsson.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police,
and Martin Rohde are present.
You killed Emil Fernskog.
Someone told you to do it. Who?
Did you meet him?
What did he look like?
Can you describe him? Lars?
Look at us, Lars.
Lars! Try to look at us.
- Hi. Do you want something?
- What?
I don't know. Are you thirsty?
- Hungry? Are you a smoker?
- Some green tea.
Green tea? OK.
You can have some green tea
if you give me something.
- What?
- Just answer a few questions.
- Not about him.
- About whom?
- Who?
- No One.
Are you scared of him, Lars?
He won't come here. He can't get in.
Do you know, you ought to be
more scared of me than him.
Do you get it? You can't decide
whether you're going to talk or not.
You killed for him.
You make me furious
when you don't talk.
Do you get me?
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
Stop defending him!
- Martin!
- Yes. Stop protecting him.
The interview is stopped at 09:57.
- Don't say anything.
- What?
- About this.
- How you handled the interview?
When I tell you not to say anything,
I really mean it.
- Do you get it, Saga?
- But it's inappropriate...
- What are you doing?
- We're always one step behind.
It's not a race
where we're chasing someone.
We're in different places.
When we get enough information,
we'll be in the same place.
If you're chasing someone,
he decides which road you go down.
Martin?
Stefan Lindberg was here yesterday.
Was he here yesterday?
And we weren't told until now?
You've got our mobile numbers.
What if he had important information?
He didn't. I asked him to stop by.
- She doesn't know that.
- Have a nice day.
Yes.
He was going to get help a couple
of days a week. I don't know.
I can go see him this afternoon.
Absolutely.
That doesn't matter.
Hang on a second.
Sorry.
OK, I'll get in touch
when I've been there. Bye.
Was that Veronika?
- No, a colleague.
- Really.
I want
Veronika and my children back.
Certainly.
Let's go down to the office.
- We can find out where they are.
- No, you're going to tell me now.
Where are they?
Stefan?
This is Martin Rohde.
I saw you, so please open the door.
- Yes?
- What are you doing?
I was about to go to bed,
I worked the night shift.
Can I come in?
Sure. Come on in.
What... What do you want?
- We bump into each other too often.
- Really.
I guess we frequent the same places.
- Are you nervous?
- No.
We wouldn't have met if Ekwall
or some other VIP hadn't been killed.
- Do you dislike VIPs?
- That's not what I meant.
So what did you mean?
In my job you can't help but notice
how unfair society is.
But violence isn't the answer.
- What is the answer?
- I don't know.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, why do you ask?
Do you know any of these?
- Are they homeless or drug users?
- No.
Why do you think I know them?
- Maybe you've met them.
- No.
- I'd like to see his medical records.
- It was his first visit.
- But he had an appointment?
- Yes, he called eight weeks ago.
- How many psychiatrists are there?
- Five, but not at the same time.
So he just happened to get Fernskog.
No, he asked to see Emil,
and it had to be today.
I remember.
Emil had two cancellations.
Both times I called Lars Jönsson.
He could have had an earlier
appointment, but insisted on today.
- It's Martin.
- Are you in the office?
I'm with Stefan.
- Can you go there?
- I'll be there in fifteen minutes.
See you. Bye.
We have to talk some other time.
- Don't leave town.
- Sure. No, no.
- My sister's ill, I'll stay here.
- OK, see you.
- What did Stefan Lindberg say?
- Nothing, but something's wrong.
We'll have him followed.
Take a look at this.
The two schizophrenics
in Copenhagen lived here and here.
They committed murder
here and here.
The postman in Malmö
was killed here.
It's the killer's stairwell.
But Lars lived here.
He walked to the bus stop
and got on the bus.
He got off, walked through the park-
- came to the surgery,
and stayed in the waiting room.
He killed Emil Fernskog
in the consulting room.
He booked the appointment
eight weeks ago.
It was planned.
Bjørn recognized his kidnapper.
Maybe Brammer and Ekwall
weren't just symbols?
- Did he pick them for a reason?
- Possibly.
Gry's looking for
links between the victims.
- And Lars' apartment?
- Forensics are checking it.
The police officers were acquitted.
There were protests.
In a trial last year-
- four immigrants were found guilty
without proof of who did what.
Jesper Anderson,
you're a regional coordinator.
You work against recruitment
into organized crime.
- What effect will the verdict have?
- It's very unfortunate.
It's giving out the wrong signals.
- How?
- It affects our youth work.
We have to establish
some sort of trust.
This verdict
takes us back to square one.
It's been compared to
the one against the four immigrants.
I can understand that.
We're not all equal before the law.
That's a problem.
Not just for the police,
but for the general public.
- They should take this seriously.
- Thank you.
- I'm glad I wasn't there.
- We'll appeal. It's all we can do.
It's all you can do.
We have to take action.
- What are you up to?
- I'm going out with my friends.
No, stay away from them!
Stay here.
- We're trying to find the sender.
- That won't get us anywhere.
- What else?
- Navid?
- He's been taking his clozapine.
- Have it analysed.
- This was in the apartment.
- It's a good likeness.
He didn't make it himself.
The pens, and the flat, are covered
in someone else's fingerprints.
- It's a small hand, a youngster's.
- Someone with the initials A.B.
- It's Martin.
- This is Charlotte Söringer.
I found something for you
amongst Göran's things.
Records. It's easier to explain
if you take a look.
- I'll be right over.
- Good.
Charlotte Söringer
found something interesting.
- Records. I'll go there now.
- Good.
He called them his black files.
They're complaints.
Legal documents. Tenants'
associations, the authorities...
People who have sued,
appealed, all sorts of things.
There's a folder of hate mail.
Thank you.
- Is it of use to you?
- I'll have someone check it.
- Do you have to hurry back?
- Yes.
He's on the move. We'll follow him.
This is Martin.
I'm with Charlotte Söringer.
- Still? Why?
- I'll be there in twenty minutes.
- Did she have something for you?
- Records.
Does it take that long
to fetch some records?
What's it like to cheat on your wife?
I wonder how Göran felt.
- This isn't your first time, is it?
- It was a long time ago.
Take care, Martin.
- Have I missed anything?
- The cameras don't show the gate.
We can't see Lars at all,
he doesn't seem to leave the house.
Our guy could be anyone on there,
but he's avoided the cameras before.
Stop. Stop. Rewind.
There! She sees the police officer
and turns around.
Is that Lars Jönsson's lodger?
- He's not talking.
- I got the lab results.
All four were given placebo drugs.
They haven't taken drugs
for schizophrenia for months.
These are Goran Söringer's records.
See if you can find any names
connected to the investigation.
Show me again.
Can you see the sign?
"Ellborns Päls".
The shop window's been smashed
three times. Red paint everywhere.
- What does the police do?
- Property crime is not a priority.
- Not the way I see it.
- No, but we do.
- Is that all?
- Only the last 48 hours are kept.
A colleague will stop by
with a formal complaint.
- The camera's illegal.
- You have to be joking.
- Was she joking?
- No. I'll see what I can do.
Are there any rules you don't follow?
- Why do you ask?
- I just wonder. Are there?
Rules are rules,
unless they're only recommendations.
Are you thinking about the camera?
It's illegal.
- He helped us.
- We don't know that.
What else should we ignore
if people are helpful?
That's not what I mean. You don't
have to say you'll report them.
- Why not?
- It's an unwritten law.
I don't know any of those.
Hi, it's me. I'm on my way home.
Can we have dinner together?
All of us, for once.
That would be nice.
I'll head home now.
Saga sends her regards. Bye.
- Why did you say that?
- What?
I didn't send my regards.
Should I have?
Is that an unwritten law?
Call me if John finds anything
on the tapes.
"A killer could be living
in your neighbourhood."
Addresses for psychiatric patients.
What's wrong with you? Is this legal?
- I had to write "could".
- He wants to spread fear.
He wants to tell the truth
and point to problems.
To call all psychiatric patients
potential killers is not the truth.
It was true
in four cases this morning.
I spoke to
one of the killers' parents.
They've tried to have him admitted
for weeks, he's been very ill.
- That's what we should write about.
- You don't get to decide.
Nor do you, T.T. is in charge.
You're just a useful fool.
It's better than being just a fool.
Don't you think?
If you update it,
remove my name from that crap.
I got this from
the guy in the fur shop's camera.
Lars Jönsson isn't here either.
But the girl that lived with him
is in these three. Here.
- That's all that's of interest.
- It's of no use without her identity.
It's Anja Björk, she's missing.
Should we issue her description?
Yes, but don't tie her to this case,
that could put her in danger.
This could be done
by the time we get home.
Is it so difficult
to place demands on him?
- Maybe he struggles to adjust.
- Should the rest of us adjust to him?
- You can hardly tell he's here.
- Yes, even the twins help out more.
What would happen
if you placed some demands on him?
I don't know.
Can't we just give him some time?
OK. In the meantime
Hotel Rohde stays open.
This is new for me as well.
Give him a chance.
Is dinner ready?
August! The doorbell rang.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Is Martin Rohde at home?
- Yes, yes.
- Are you here?
The girl is 14-year-old Anja Björk.
She ran away from home.
- Would you like some food?
- We haven't got time.
Yes, we do.
It's quicker than going to 7-Eleven.
We've got bubble and squeak.
It's a kind of hash. Come on.
This is Carl, Johanne, and Nikolaj.
The young man staring at you
is August. You've met Mette.
- Can you say hi to Saga?
- Hi.
You lost this at Charlotte Söringer's
place. She handed it in.
Well, take a seat.
- Would you like the recipe?
- No, it wasn't tasty.
- You don't have to finish it.
- I don't want to either.
You have to.
- Why are you looking at me?
- What? I'm not.
- August is a big fan of T.T.
- Not his actions, not the killings.
But he points out important issues.
- And he's a genius.
- Yes, he's well-organized.
- He's not a genius.
- That depends on your definition.
I've never come across
anyone like him.
He's Michelangelo,
the others do fingerpainting.
- That's a good comparison.
- Are you in the fan club as well?
I understand his reasoning.
We'll be right there.
Anja Björk's mother is on her way.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry you didn't like it.
Yes. Thanks.
See you later.
I'm afraid I can't help you.
- She'll be back, right?
- She'll be home soon. I promise.
You can't. We'll do our best,
but can't promise that she'll return.
- I guess I'll hear from you.
- Yes.
Are you aware of the things you say?
Are you?
We can't promise that she'll return.
She might be dead.
She was caught on camera
eight hours ago.
Everyone is alive eight hours before
they die. 30 percent never return.
I'm fully aware of that.
And so is she, I think.
Sometimes people need to hear
something, even if it's not true.
Martin? Wait.
- So people want to be lied to?
- Yes, Saga. Sometimes.
What if she dies?
What will we say then?
- You're annoying me how.
- Really?
- You know, Anja...
- What about her?
- She's not the only witness.
- But he's not talking.
Maybe we asked
the wrong questions?
I want to talk about Anja.
She stayed with you.
Did you like her?
She made this drawing of you.
The guy that told you to kill,
has done this.
And this. And this.
And this. He'll do it to Anja if we
don't find her. Do you want that?
What? Do you want that?
If we catch him, he can't hurt Anja.
But we don't know what he looks like.
Can you tell us?
What does he look like?
He's tall and has blue eyes.
Chequered coat, hat, and gloves.
- What did you say?
- Tall, chequered coat, scarf, gloves.
- You have to speak up.
- Tall, blue eyes, scarf, and gloves!
I said he's tall and has brown hair!
He's tall and has a scarf and gloves!
He's tall and has blue eyes,
chequered coat, scarf, and gloves.
- It's him, she saw him.
- He's not on the other tapes.
- He avoids the cameras.
- He didn't know about this one.
- We have to find her.
- All officers are looking for her.
- Did Anja's father know anything?
- No, nothing.
- We have to find her.
- You can't search both cities.
You can't, and you're not going to.
Do you understand?
- Are you Daniel? Daniel Ferbé?
- Yes.
- What the hell is this?
- They threw it through my window.
I'm Markus Bolin.
You printed my address today.
So? There's no need to be scared,
I won't hit you.
I just wanted to show you
what might happen.
It's sad, but I'm just a writer.
I can't take responsibility for
people's reactions.
How nice.
You don't give a damn
about the consequences.
Good luck with your life. Good luck.
- One more!
- Have you got something stronger?
- Hi.
- Don't you recognize me?
- Yes, we had sex.
- Anton Cederlund.
- Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
- Would you like something?
- I need to eat first.
If we're going to have sex.
I didn't have dinner.
So you got to meet Saga Norén
from Malmö's criminal police.
- She's different.
- Yes.
She drives me mad sometimes,
but there's something about her.
We work well together.
Good thing
she stopped by with your wallet.
- Didn't you know that you'd lost it?
- No, clearly not.
Who's Charlotte?
One of the property investors.
She put up twenty million kroner.
You're so hot.
Do you know who was here tonight?
Saga fucking Norén.
From TV? How was she?
- Cool. Very pretty.
- So you're into MILFs now? :)
- LOL! I won't say what she told me.
- PLS. I promise I'll be good.
We've spotted Anja Björk where
Adelgatan crosses Östergatan.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Yes. I'll be right there.
- I have to go.
- What?
Henning?
- Are you drunk?
- Yes, somewhat.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
I heard about the verdict.
Did you speak to Lillian?
- Yes, I spoke to Lillian.
- What did she say?
She had nothing to say,
nothing that matters.
That's enough, Saif. It's late.
You're disappointed.
- We did the right thing.
- I didn't do anything.
We can appeal and have a new trial.
- We can talk to the media.
- It won't make a difference.
It has to. We live in Denmark,
it has to be better here.
You lost a son, I lost a brother.
They were let off.
Hate and vengeance
will lead to nothing.
I want you to put this behind you.
You're everything to me.
Your brother wouldn't listen.
We lost him.
I'm not my brother,
you won't lose me.
Sometimes it feels
as if I've lost you.
- Saif...
- I have to go.
Anja?
Hi.
Do you remember him?
Was he the one that shot you?
Draw him and I'll catch him.
Am I going to die?
No.
Carry on.
Anja? Anja?
There are no traces
in the parking garage.
- How is Anja doing?
- She died twenty minutes ago.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- She drew this.
Can you see who it is?
It's Stefan Lindberg. Can you see?
He's got that look in his eyes.