SUMMARY
The lights on the bridge went out.
It went black for 45 seconds.
- Saga Norén.
- Copenhagen Police.
Is she in Sweden or Denmark?
Two women killed a year apart.
Dismembered and assembled.
- Someone wants to make a statement.
- I can identify the lower body.
The father changed his mind.
We can't have the heart. Göran!
I've got the car's license number.
- It belongs to Daniel Farbé.
- The journalist?
- Do you know Kerstin Ekwall?
- Who?
It skipped a minute. What did you do?
Come back! Where are you going?
Daniel? Are you still there? Hello?
- It's clean.
- Sorry about the drama.
I assume I have your attention now.
This is only a beginning. We've got
interesting times ahead of us.
EPISODE 2
What the hell are you doing?
No! Step back!
I've got her, I've got her.
THE BRIDGE
Can we deal with it
when we get back? Which address?
- There's info on truth.se.
- What is that?
It's an Internet address.
Someone knows more than us.
What if you were in a car with a bomb
and had five minutes left to live?
- He didn't have five minutes left.
- But imagine thinking that.
- I'd try to get out.
- It would have gone off.
Five minutes don't make
much of a difference. Look.
"Equal Before The Law - a Myth."
In Swedish and Danish.
- "The Women on the Bridge."
- In the plural.
- Have we said that there were two?
- No. "They were just a beginning."
"Message to the police. Listen.”
Sorry about the drama, it's hard
to make oneself heard today.
I assume I have your attention now.
He says it's just the beginning.
Will there be more killing?
- Don't you ever have breakfast?
- Sometimes.
- Do you plan to eat at all today?
- Maybe later.
- There's a web page.
- Two, truth.dk has the same content.
It's from Daniel Ferbé's car.
Check the content.
- Can we eat before we interview him?
- We're not handling it.
- Why not?
- We've got specially trained staff.
- Interrogators? Not you?
- No.
Aren't you curious?
Which number is he in?
- Number three.
- Come on.
- Hi.
- Why am I here?
- Your car was used in a murder.
- I worked all night.
- Ask the editorial staff.
It's not random
that your car was involved.
I know nothing about Kerstin Ekwall
or bodies on the bridge.
You might know more than you think.
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
- I have a ticket to Berlin.
- You're not going anywhere.
- Are you kidding?
- No, I'm not kidding.
- I nearly died in that car.
- No, you didn't.
There was dynamite in the backseat.
Why don't you try to catch
the one that put it there?
I didn't do anything.
I just want to get out of here.
Please.
A lunatic stole my car,
it's not my problem.
But the drugs in your apartment are.
- Personal consumption.
- You're still in possession.
We just want to know why.
- It was used in a double homicide.
- I have no bloody idea!
Let's try to find out why.
- Interrogators never lie.
- I'm not an interrogator.
- He might never trust us again.
- He doesn't trust us anyway.
- How do you know?
- I know his type.
- Based on the clippings you read?
- No, I'm clever.
- Am I annoying you?
- No, not yet. Why do you ask?
- I'll get a search warrant.
- Or we can just go have a quick look.
No. The breakfast room is downstairs.
You've got ten minutes.
Excuse me, where's room 3234?
Thank you.
- Is this Christian?
- Yes.
- I'm Charlotte Söringer.
- I'm Ole.
- Are you the psychologist?
- No, but...
My husband's very ill.
He'll die without a new heart.
Your son's heart.
My son is breathing.
His heart is beating. You can tell.
- I understand, but...
- I want him here. Do you understand?
But he's not here.
What was your son, is gone.
I don't want you to take his heart.
I can't imagine what this is like,
but I love my husband.
Without your son's heart he'll die.
Then he'll have to die.
- Do you call this lunch?
- Come here, you guys. Come listen.
- John.
- The next listener is Jørgen.
My name isn't Jørgen,
but that's irrelevant.
Have you heard about
the two bodies on the bridge?
One was Danish,
Monique Brammer.
A drug user and a prostitute.
I killed her 13 months ago.
The investigation lasted two weeks.
Will they drop
the Swedish politician's case?
- This isn't the right forum.
- The right forum is truthnow.dk.
It was on the radio
an hour and a half ago.
- Have we traced the call?
- Cash card.
- It's not the same voice.
- Is it a group?
No, he says: "I think", "I killed".
Groups spread fear
by saying that they're many.
- What now?
- I'll reopen Monique's case.
We'll put a tail on Daniel Ferbé
and hope that he's contacted again.
- And the web pages?
- We're trying to locate the server.
Both links are
on newspaper websites and blogs.
There's info
only the killer could have.
- What does he want?
- There's a message.
- We're not equal before the law.
- That's true.
- Many would beg to differ.
- That doesn't make it less true.
What are your thoughts?
- The women were just the beginning.
- He wants to point out five problems.
Unequal before the law.
There are four left. What are they?
The second body
was a Danish prostitute.
She disappeared 13 months ago.
- You contacted the donor's father.
- His dead son can save my husband.
- That wasn't a good idea.
- Nothing's happening.
He's brain dead,
can't you just pull the plug?
Your husband isn't our only patient.
What if your son was lying there?
I don't have children.
I don't want to lose Göran.
The medical examiner
should finish today.
I'll check on Ferbé's car.
What's your email address?
Hi, darling. I'm still in Malmö,
but heading home soon.
This evening, I have to stop by
the station. Ask August to help you.
It's after noon, just wake him up.
I promise to talk to him tonight.
Bye, darling.
Saga sends her regards. Bye.
- My wife. Have you got a boyfriend?
- No. What's your email address?
- August is my oldest.
- Saga!
The server's in Copenhagen.
Here's the address.
- That can't be right.
- The IP address leads to the server.
The guy may not be there,
but the server is.
That's Copenhagen Police Station.
- It's impossible. It can't be.
- That's what I said.
He switched off
the lights on the bridge.
I'll be darned.
They're right, he's using us.
- How can he?
- He might have hacked in.
Even if I knew how,
you wouldn't understand.
- Can we trace him?
- We can try.
He disconnected.
- Martin.
- Saga Norén.
- Is he closed down?
- He disconnected.
- Can you still trace him?
- Can we trace him?
Maybe, but he won't still be
using his computer.
- We might find the computer, but...
- I heard her.
He wanted us to find it. Why?
He closed it down when we traced it.
That defeats his object.
- He wants it out in the open.
- It already is.
Everything's on the Internet.
The source isn't necessary anymore.
Saga? A visitor says that he recorded
the message on the Internet.
Turn around, face the wall.
- Why?
- Face the wall, spread your legs.
I was shocked when I heard
the message on the radio.
- I've recorded it.
- How come?
I sometimes work for Ljudgrottan.
I do radio commercials and dubbing.
- I'm with Malmö City Theatre.
- You're an actor.
- Maybe you've seen me perform?
- No.
- The recording?
- Ljudgrottan called about a job.
The client wanted
a Standard Swedish speaker.
Did you meet the client?
No, the script came in the mail.
The tape was sent to a P.O. box.
We joked about it,
it was like a spy film.
- Wasn't the work a bit odd?
- No.
I thought it was for a performance
or an art installation.
It sounded ominous. I didn't know
that it would be used for this.
- Have you still got the script?
- No.
Maybe the studio has,
and the P.O. box number.
You could give them a call,
but I would be very surprised.
It was recorded
three and a half years ago.
You're not taking my son away.
My son stays here!
I haven't seen you here before.
It's important to look nice.
It's important
to make a good impression.
Last year I had two new teeth put in.
A beautiful smile opens up doors.
- Charlie walked along the street...
- What did you say?
- Charlie?
You have nice legs,
if you don't mind me saying.
Nice to meet you. I have to go now.
Charlie walked along the street,
he found...
Hi.
- Have you sold her anything?
- No.
- Try a bit harder.
- Maybe, but it's a long time ago.
- Who did she work for?
- I don't know. I can't remember.
I'm tired, hungry, and my dick hurts.
I have a very short fuse.
- I wish I could help you, mate.
- My fuse is getting shorter.
Her name is Monique.
She disappeared a year ago,
what's taken you so long?
- Did she say something back then?
- No.
She's dead.
- Did she bring customers home?
- No, that would have been stupid.
We found blood in her apartment.
- Did any customers threaten her?
- Not as far as I know.
- Where did she work?
- In Absalonsgade.
- Can I talk to someone there?
- Pernille. I'll give her a call.
- How old are you?
- Old enough. Do you want a blowjob?
- Thanks for your help.
- I worry about them. Keep me posted.
I'll give you my full attention
when this case is over.
- You're going to Berlin, but...
- The police won't let me go.
Do you know that he confessed
to the murders on Danish radio?
This is turning into a big case.
We have a unique angle.
- I'm supposed to be off work.
- We can discuss the matter.
Daniel, who's negotiating his salary.
Can I call you back? Who is this?
- Do you understand my Danish?
- Yes.
- Who are you?
- A protector of the truth.
- Why are you calling me?
- We need each other, Daniel.
I don't need someone
that places bombs in my car.
I need a voice,
they're trying to silence me.
- Why do I need you?
- You're negotiating your salary.
- I'm not for sale.
- Really?
I'm giving you facts,
use them as you please.
What facts? Hello?
(UN)EQUAL BEFORE THE LAW
- What's this?
- Crime statistics.
"Investigations depend on
where the crime is committed."
Statistics don't reflect everyone
Social groups...clear-up rate...
- ...resources... What do we do now?
- What do you want to do?
Excuse me. Veronika Holmgren
has been given a secret address.
- Can you register it?
- OK.
She was here a lot,
she needed the money.
- She was an amphetamine user.
- I know.
- Was that the reason?
- What?
- Was she killed because of debts?
- No, that wasn't why.
She wanted to quit.
She met a man that she cared about.
- Who was he?
- Jørgen something. He wasn't here.
- Was this her room?
- No, it's next door.
- It's empty, I've taken her things.
- What things?
Her diary.
- Why haven't the police got this?
- They were never here.
Thank you.
I'll make sure it's returned to you.
No fingerprints
apart from the owner's.
He must have had
someone in the car before.
- There were very few fibres.
- It's been cleaned.
Thoroughly.
With a steam cleaner, I think.
Have you really checked everything?
Have you?
- We need each other, Daniel.
- I don't need you.
- What's this?
- The killer called a reporter.
- Why do I need you?
- You're negotiating your salary.
I'm not for sale.
- Hi there!
- Why didn't you call?
- It didn't occur to me.
- He's a criminal.
If he contacts you again,
call us straight away.
- What's that?
- The relevant act and penalties.
- I said I'll call.
- I don't believe you.
Where's your boss? Here's her copy.
- Saga Norén.
- Hi. We've found Ekwall's car.
It's on a surveillance tape.
It was in the town hall car park.
He avoids the cameras.
- Is that the only camera?
- The other one's of no use.
The window's covered up.
- And when he entered?
- The same side faced the camera.
- Do you recognize this woman?
- No.
I'll pay whomever helps me find her.
- Yes?
- That guy knows her.
Charlotte?
It went well.
In spite of some complications.
He's in the recovery ward.
You can go see him.
Thank you, Anders.
Kerstin Ekwall was strangled,
like you said.
Cause of death can't be determined
for the other woman.
We can only rule out poisoning.
There were traces of amphetamine.
She was chopped in half after death.
It took a lot of force,
it wasn't done by hand.
The cut is perfect.
- A sawmill, then?
- The blade wasn't made for timber.
You can tell that it's fine-toothed.
I think they used the right tool
for the job. A meat saw.
- A slaughterhouse?
- Possibly. Definitely a meat saw.
Hi! Careful, careful.
Let's go in and eat. Take a bag each.
Nice! Bloody hell.
- No, without that thing on. Hi.
- Hi. Can you fetch August?
- Where is he?
- He's gardening...
Food's ready. I've bought Thai food.
You have to eat well
when you're this active...
August! Come on, food's on the table.
We're waiting for you.
It's... It's important
to have a family meal.
I've eaten without a family
for 15 years.
- What kind of bullshit is that?
- I'll be there in a little while.
Turn it off.
Stop it, come on.
We're not equal before the law,
that's a lie.
- So he's right?
- Of course not.
- It's growing bigger.
- The planning took over three years.
Ekwall's computers, phone and car
gave us no clues.
We haven't traced the power cut
or websites. The voice was distorted.
Martin Rohde found
Monique Brammer's diary.
She met someone called Jørgen,
the name used on the radio.
- How are things with Martin?
- Fine.
- Does Karin call you for no reason?
- Sometimes. Why?
Martin's wife called.
What a waste of time
to call just to hear someone's voice.
- Do you want a lift?
- No.
EQUALITY BEFORE THE LAW
Hi.
- Are you waiting for someone?
- No.
- Can I buy you a drink?
Right. OK.
Listen, why did you walk away?
- I just didn't want a drink.
- OK.
Do you want to have sex
at my place?
- Yes, definitely.
- Good. Let's go.
- What are you reading?
- A diary.
Are you upset?
It's been a long day.
There's something about this case.
The women on the bridge...
- The guy that called...
- What?
I just have this feeling.
Get some sleep.
Tomorrow is another day.
Hi, darling.
We did it!
Did the father change his mind?
The son was a registered donor.
The father didn't matter.
- It didn't matter.
- No.
Charlotte.
I thought I was about to die,
and it made me think.
"If I make it"...
"I'm going to treasure life more."
- We'll take care of each other.
- No.
I neither can nor want to anymore.
Things haven't worked since...
It's been bad for so long.
Life's too short not to be happy.
- I am happy.
- But I'm not.
- I haven't been for a long time.
- Do you want a divorce?
- I love you.
- I know. I know.
Do you have any idea
what I've done for your sake?
Göran? Göran?
What's happening?
Do you need help?
Sonja!
Listen to me. It's me.
Stefan.
Charlie walked along the street,
he found...
...a parcel. He thought
it was tobacco, it was dynamite.
He filled his pipe and lit it.
Then Charlie blew up with it.
We'd chant it that summer.
Didn't we, sis? Do you remember?
It didn't rain a single day
that summer. It's me.
I could kill him over and over again
for your sake.
He'll return. He lives within me.
Sonja? Sonja? Sonja!
Did you get a chance to talk?
We talked about the future.
About our time together.
We were grateful to have each other.
- He really loved me.
- Yes. I know he did.
- What's that?
- Work.
- What do you do for a living?
- I'm with Malmö County Police.
- Do you want me to leave?
- Do you want to stay?
- Do you want me to stay?
- Yes. You can sleep.
What the hell is that?
- It's a corpse.
- Oh, OK. I think I'll...
- Well... Bye, then.
- Bye.
Thanks!
AEB...STAEB...
...STA...
- Yes? Hello?
- Is "staeb" something in Danish?
They thought it was part of a tattoo
on Monique Brammer.
It might be printed or stamped on.
The body might have been
pressed up against something.
Doesn't it mean something to you?
It's not the whole word.
Think in the lines of
an autopsy room...
- ...meat...
- Kødbyen.
It's a slaughterhouse area.
There's a huge one in Staebogade.
- I'll go there now.
- See you there.
- Can you unlock?
- Yes.
- Can the lights be turned on?
- Martin! A dog is alerting.
Clear!
I need a list over those
that have access at night.
- Are there any surveillance cameras?
- No.
I need a list over those
that can switch the alarm system off.
And the alarm log
from the last couple of days.
VISIBLE, YET INVISIBLE
- What did you find?
- The other half, a lower body.
- Ekwall.
- This was attached to it.
"...there would have been
no victims."
He knew that we would find
the stamp and this place.
- Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
- It's Daniel. I've been contacted.
The subject is:
"Visible, yet invisible."
The email reads:
"If you had cared..."
"If you had cared, there would
have been no victims." Go on.
There's a number of attachments,
just like last time.
- What's in the attachments?
- More statistics.
Something's increased
in Copenhagen and Malmö.
- What's increased?
- "...little funding for..."
Homelessness.
It's about the homeless.
- He contacted Daniel Ferbé again.
- Six people have been found.
They seem to be poisoned
and have been brought to hospital.
- He's going to kill homeless people.
- He's started already.