SUMMARY
- Daniel Ferbé.
- A miserable front page.
I'm trying to make people
aware of problems.
T.T. is responsible. He's criticizing
the cuts to psychiatric programs.
You can't decide
whether you're going to talk or not.
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
Stop defending him!
There! She sees the officer
and turns around.
Is that Jönsson's lodger?
I want to talk about Anja.
The guy that told you to kill,
has done this. And this.
And this. He'll do it to Anja-
- if we don't find her.
Do you want that?
It's him, she saw him.
We have to find her.
Stefan? I saw you,
so please open the door.
- What did he say?
- Nothing, but something's wrong.
If I'm sentenced, I'll lose my job.
The police officers were acquitted.
There were protests.
In a trial last year-
- four immigrants were found guilty
without proof of who did what.
- We have to take action.
- What are you up to? Stay here.
EPISODE 6
Henning?
Are you out here?
THE BRIDGE
- Good morning.
- Good night. I'm going to bed.
Have you only just come home,
or are you leaving?
I'm leaving.
- Can you help out around the house?
- With what?
All that needs doing
when the others get home.
- She's never asked for help.
- She shouldn't have to.
- Will you see Saga today?
- Yes.
- Do you have fun together?
- Fun?
She's a really good police officer,
but fun...
Well, yes. We have fun,
but she's very different.
- In what way?
- In every way.
Is she single?
- What?
- I'm just asking.
- What are you asking?
- Is she single?
Yes. I don't know what type of person
that could stand to be with her.
See you later.
Sorry to disturb you,
but I'm very worried.
Someone could be after revenge.
You hear about gangs.
There's nothing in the apartment
that indicates that.
It's just that he's
never disappeared before.
He probably needed some time alone.
The trial was strenuous.
I'll ask around. I'll call you
as soon as I know something.
Good, thank you.
Maybe he's home already?
He must be wondering where I am.
- Thank you for your time.
- Don't mention it.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Bye.
- Hi. Where have you been?
- The cemetery.
- Why?
- My sister's there.
How did he know
that we were looking for Anja?
Only we knew
why we were looking for her.
- Do you think we have a leak?
- I don't know.
- How similar are they?
- Very.
- No.
- Yes. He keeps popping up.
He didn't leave the apartment
when Anja was shot.
He'll only reveal
what he wants us to see.
- It's not enough.
- Let's add to it, then. Come on.
We need a search warrant.
- Will I be arrested for breaking in?
- No, but we need a search warrant.
Be a law-abiding Swede
and get one, then.
- Did you change your mind?
- The public prosecutor approved it.
- Where do you want to start?
- In the kitchen, you do the bedroom.
Saga? I'm in the bedroom.
It's like a Red Cross warehouse.
Or maybe he likes to play doctor?
An identical one
was used to drain Bjørn's blood.
- None of this will be sent to Africa.
- It's still not enough.
Are there any dressings?
Thanks.
You're late.
- What did you do last night?
- Nothing. I was out.
- Until four o'clock?
- I was out.
- Were Yassir and the others there?
- Yes.
Listen. Stay out late,
and go wherever you want to.
As long as there are no calls from
the emergency room or the police.
Do you get it?
Do we have an agreement?
There was a letter by the door.
- Did you see who put it there?
- No.
- What's in it?
- Nothing.
- What'll you do afterwards?
- Later today, you mean?
No, when this is over.
When the calls stop.
You'll just be a regular reporter.
- That'll never happen.
- It won't?
I'll always be the guy that was
the link to our worst killer ever.
- People forget.
- Not if you remind them.
I'm going to write a book.
Maybe two or three.
- Why do you ask?
- You look beat.
I care, is that so strange?
- Yes.
- That's just how it is.
The police arrested someone,
it could be him.
- They found someone?
- A social worker.
- Who is he?
- I'm not the one you're looking for.
What do you need
the medical equipment for?
- Have you been in my apartment?
- Yes.
It's useful. People get hurt.
- Do people around you get hurt?
- No, but what if they did?
- Do you know who this is?
- Should I know?
Where were you
from ten until midnight yesterday?
- I was at home watching TV.
- What did you watch?
I was flicking the channels.
- Can't you name a specific program?
- No, I can't remember.
- Do you speak Danish?
- No. I'm not your guy.
This wine is from a crime scene,
this is from your apartment.
It's the same type of wine.
So I see.
- How did the blood get there?
- What blood?
- We have to take a blood sample.
- Of course.
- Can I leave afterwards?
- No.
- There you are. Bye, see you soon.
- Yes. Bye.
CLOSED
What's going on?
What's going on? What?
What do you want?
- The thing with your brother...
- Don't talk about him.
I can explain.
- Your brother...
- Don't talk about my brother!
- Listen to me.
- What are you doing down here?
What are you talking about?
Haven't you put me here?
Help me get these off.
- Can you help me get these off?
- Help you?
Help me. We'll sort out
the thing with your brother.
When we get out of here
we'll explain the whole thing.
- We'll explain the whole thing?
- Listen, I didn't do it.
I'm sorry about your brother.
You won't get your brother back.
No, I won't. That's just it,
I won't get my brother back!
- When did your sister die?
- Fifteen years ago.
- Older?
- Younger than me. She was fourteen.
- Just like Anja.
- Yes.
- Why did she die?
- She killed herself.
- Were you close?
- I guess so, she lived with me.
- Why not with your parents?
- She didn't want to.
- Suicide?
- Yes. She jumped in front of a train.
Were there signs of depression?
I don't pick up on signs.
He asked to see you.
I help people.
Beyond what my job requires.
I help the weak
that have been let down by society.
It can be food, money, clothes,
medication, or a place to live.
- How can you afford that?
- There are many ways.
There are many ways
to fool the system.
- Name someone you've helped.
- I can't, you know that.
- There's a priest you can talk to.
- What about the blood?
Well...
I can only think of one thing.
A refugee was at my place,
he was being expelled.
He cut himself severely.
I dressed the wound.
- Where is he now?
- I don't know.
- Any news about the blood?
- It doesn't match the victims'.
- Is there another victim?
- No, he would never kill in his home.
- I don't believe there was a refugee.
- Stefan isn't our guy.
The priest confirms
that they've worked with refugees.
- The perpetrator cares about society.
- No, that's just a diversion.
- Should we spend time on Lindberg?
- No.
- I'll request his release.
- Wait a little.
I want to talk to Daniel Ferbé first.
I need your help, Gry. Come on.
If you object to people being named,
discuss it with my boss.
- It's not him.
- What?
Stefan Lindberg isn't our guy.
He'll soon be released.
- Have you gone public with that?
- No, you can have the exclusive.
- Why?
- It's useful to the investigation.
You can quote anonymous sources.
Add that he doesn't speak Danish.
- Doesn't Stefan speak Danish?
- No.
- Well?
- What do you want?
Write that we were wrong.
I'm giving you this
because Saga likes your writing.
Daniel. Bloody hell!
I'm really sorry.
There's a bathroom out there.
- Are you all right?
- It looks as if I've wet myself.
Yes, it does.
I think it'll wash off. Now then...
- When will you go public?
- How much time do you need?
- An hour.
- You can have two.
- What's that?
- Daniel's SIM card.
- How did you get hold of it?
- I grabbed it.
- Did he give it to you?
- Not exactly.
You can talk to the killer.
- That's misconduct.
- So you don't want it?
He's published something new.
- Why just Henning, not the others?
- I don't know.
Have you seen it?
Has he got Henning?
I'm afraid so. His wife was here,
he disappeared in the night.
- We'll move in.
- There'll be riots.
- Have you got any better ideas?
- No.
- Saif? Why did you close the store?
- I had to fix something.
One of the police officers
has been kidnapped.
- They think he's here at Nørrebro.
- OK.
- There'll be riots out here.
- Hello, it's Saif. Can we meet up?
- Has something happened?
- I can't talk now.
- Have you heard about the cop?
- That's what I want to talk about.
- Come on over, I'm in the square.
- OK.
- Hi, Daniel. Beers tonight?
- No, he'll call you later.
- It's No One.
- No, this is Saga Norén.
- Hello?
- Yes.
Why not talk to us directly?
- Hello, are you still there?
- Yes.
- What do you want to talk about?
- Why couldn't Anja live?
How did you know
that we were looking for her? Hello?
- Daniel?
- I'll skip lunch.
It's for you. It's for you.
- Daniel Ferbé.
- What are you up to?
- I wonder what you're up to.
- Nothing.
Why do the police
answer your phone?
- Why would they do that?
- Saga Norén answered your mobile.
I've got it right here.
I don't... Bloody hell.
The Danish guy took my SIM card.
We're aware of it now.
Let's carry on working together.
Immigrants receive tougher sentences.
Ban of burkas - a matter of time.
A stricter immigration act.
Nationalist parties join forces.
The police arrested the wrong man
- Hello?
- You've got something that's mine.
- I was just reading your article.
- I didn't expect that move you made.
- No, me neither.
- My boss would have blown her top.
She takes protection of sources
quite seriously.
She would have attacked
the entire police force.
I'll do you a favour,
I won't say anything.
- But you'll owe me one.
- OK.
- Send it over, I'm expecting a call.
- Lots of people have called.
- Did you make a note of their names?
- No.
I heard from him.
He called the office.
I've sent you everything.
- Hey, what's up?
- Have you seen Yassir? See you.
- Hi, Yassir!
- There you are, where did you go?
- I have something to show you.
- Not now, come on.
What? What?
He's at my place, the bloody cop.
- He's in the basement.
- Are you serious?
- Will you help me?
- Of course, but let's go.
OK. You're not our guy,
but you've done something.
I've compared the blood
to all the bodies this week.
I'll find out whose blood it is
and catch you.
The police have arrested 17 people.
Three officers
have been injured in the riots.
Henning Tholstrup
hasn't been found yet.
We know what the fourth problem is:
Integration has failed.
- He says that we've failed.
- We don't want to succeed.
"Those in power will always be
unwilling to share their power."
Here's the acquittal
of your colleagues.
Statistics show that immigrants
receive longer sentences.
Pia Kærsgård, crime statistics,
and The Sweden Democrats.
- It's all here.
- It doesn't matter, it's personal.
It's all about Henning,
like the other cases.
He tells the police where Henning is.
He's supposed to die.
He helps the gang find him.
Where does the victim's family live?
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
This is Martin Rohde.
- Do you know where Saif is?
- No.
- A police officer disappeared.
- It's got nothing to do with my son.
- How do you know?
- Because he's my son.
Violence and vengeance
isn't tied to genetics.
- What's in here?
- The staircase.
It leads up to our apartment
and down to the basement.
Fuck!
Stop it. Stop it.
Be quiet. Shut up!
Shut your mouth.
- What's in here?
- A boiler room.
The others aren't ours.
They're all locked.
I haven't got the keys.
I think we're done here.
He wants Henning to die.
Focus our assets where the gang is.
- There's nothing more for us to do.
- You can always do more.
Would you like to talk about it?
Your sister.
- What would you like to know?
- Nothing.
That wasn't why I brought it up.
If you need to talk...
- Why would I need to?
- You didn't save Anja.
She was your sister's age.
It might have upset you.
I miss her sometimes, but she's gone.
- So you're all right?
- Yes.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
- Saga Norén.
- You're working late.
- What do you want?
So now you want to talk?
Were you surprised
when I answered Daniel's phone?
- You want to be in charge.
- You talk as if you know me.
- I understand you.
- It takes one to know one.
How did you know about Anja?
- I'm going to find you.
- Perhaps.
Do you still want to know
how I knew about Anja?
Do you feel responsible
for her death?
- There was nothing I could do.
- It's horrible to Feel inadequate.
- How did you know?
- You ought to know.
Me personally
or me as part of the investigation?
You're clever,
I'm sure it'll come to you.
Hello?
Are you awake?
- Why were you with that Charlotte?
- To interview her.
- I keep thinking about your wallet.
- My wallet.
Yesterday it fell out of your pocket
when you took your pants off.
- Did you use her bathroom?
- I don't know. I can't remember.
- You can't remember?
- Well, yes...
I did use her bathroom.
Have you slept with her?
I don't know why. Maybe it had
something to do with the operation.
- I had to prove something to myself.
- Prove something?
Yes. Is there something wrong,
can I still do it, or...?
Is my manhood affected?
I really don't know.
- You got me pregnant not long ago.
- Yes, I know.
- Isn't that proof enough?
- I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
Get up and pack your bags.
Leave, I don't want to look at you.
Saga Norén.
What do you want?
Thirsty?
Let me go, I'll tell them everything.
There'll be a new trial.
Bo did it. It was Bo and Luffe.
I'll tell them everything.
- It's too late now.
- I can testify. You'll get justice.
- I'm telling you, it's too late.
- No, there'll be a new trial.
- Listen...
- Shut up!
Last night's riots are subsiding.
They were massive.
Many are injured.
Cars and containers were torched.
The police officer Henning Tholstrup
has not been found.
- You're up early.
- I couldn't sleep.
Me neither.
- Why?
- I had a dream.
I was with your brother.
We met the police officers.
They started hitting him.
There was nothing I could do.
I just watched.
They left him there.
I turned him over.
It wasn't him anymore.
He had your face.
My face?
Was there any blood in your dream?
- No.
- There wasn't.
Then it was just a silly dream.
Don't think about it.
- Why are you giving me that?
- Rats need to eat as well.
- Don't they?
- What's this? What are you doing?
- Saif? What's he doing here?
- Just listen...
- I found him here.
- You found him?
We can have a whole new trial.
We'll fix this. I promise.
What? You and your colleagues
have caused so much pain.
I can testify.
If I testify, it'll work out.
Work out? How can it work out?
I lost my son.
- Can you get me my son back?
- No, I can't. Let me go.
- We'll work this out.
- No, you don't get it!
You should have
told the truth in court!
You killed my son!
He's not coming back!
Let go of him, father.
Take it easy. Easy.
Help him.
- Saga Norén.
- It's Martin.
- What do you want?
- Let me in.
I thought you might like some coffee,
so I brought croissants.
- Are there enough for August as well?
- Who's August?
- August.
- My August?
- I've borrowed one of your towels.
- That's OK.
What the hell are you doing here?
- What does it look like?
- He slept over.
I'll wait by the car.
What the hell is this?
Saga's my colleague, you're my son.
- I do as I please.
- No, you don't.
If you live in my house,
you follow my rules.
I don't know what your rules are.
You were never there.
Is this your revenge
because I was a bad father?
Not everything is about you.
Why Saga?
- Are you jealous, or what?
- Shut up.
- Are you going home?
- No.
- You can make your own way back.
- That's really mature of you...
- Hi, Lillian.
- Martin.
- We've found Henning. He's dead.
- Bloody hell.
What's wrong?
- You and my son are wrong.
- He's 18, he doesn't need permission.
- You just can't do that.
- Why not?
- You might be a bit odd, but still...
- Why is it such a problem?
We won't mention it again.
I don't want to hear about it.
Don't say anything at all just now.
You found him, hid him, released him,
and watched him get shot?
- Yes.
- By a police officer.
- What did he look like?
- I can't remember.
- How tall was he? What build?
You must remember something
about him. Try again.
- What?
- I got a letter with a key in it.
- Where's the key how?
- Here.
- Have you got anything else?
- Not really.
- What is it?
- It's just typical.
You must know what I mean.
My brother was killed.
I asked for justice,
and you dismissed me.
When one of your own is killed,
it's a completely different matter.
You run around
and turn the earth upside-down.
- The Danish police operate that way.
- Can you shut up? Shut up!
What does he look like?
- The colour of his eyes and hair?
- He looked like a cop.
Was he as tall as Martin?
OK.
He was in uniform. He was as tall
as Martin, maybe a bit taller.
He was of slender build.
- That's all I know.
- OK.
Daniel?
- How did you know where I was?
- I read the police reports.
Young man, overdose, your local club.
And you didn't show up at work.
You don't have to be Einstein
to understand.
- That must have been a highlight.
- It wasn't, actually.
- How are you doing?
- I'm OK.
- I slept the whole time.
- You haven't heard what happened.
Henning Tholstrup
was shot this morning.
I'm going to work.
I'll drive you home first.
I died in the night.
I was lifeless for
two minutes and thirty-three seconds.
- I didn't see a tunnel or a light.
- I'll drive you home.
There was only darkness, Åke.
Complete darkness.
The preliminary examination
confirms that Henning was there.
Had Saif told us,
Henning would have been alive.
He didn't have much faith
in the police.
Maybe he dragged Henning out
and killed him.
- He made up a story.
- There was no gun residue.
Maybe it was a gang member.
There were no traces.
That sounds like our perpetrator.
- What do you think, Saga?
- It's him.
It was risky to let someone else
kill Henning, so he stayed close.
- But why Henning?
- I don't know.
There's a link between the victims.
Yes? Thank you.
We've found the car.
- The car's from Helsingør.
- OK.
Saif saw him leave in a police car.
It was stolen for 24 hours,
but there are no traces.
- Maybe it's not stolen.
- What do you mean?
What if he's one of us?
What if he's a police officer?