SUMMARY
The report you filed
against Martin...
He let an ambulance through.
No life was in danger.
-Should I take the gun?
-You can't be armed in Sweden.
What the hell have they been doing?
Lie down! Lie down!
Get back!
Knock, knock...
Hey... What's going on?
-It pinches.
-You're going to the hospital.
The children are fine.
You have kidney stones.
-The children? As in twins?
-Yes.
Drop your weapon!
They're not the ones.
Back to square one.
The girl is 14-year-old Anja Björk.
She ran away from home.
Saga Norén was here.
You always choose the easy way out.
That's just the way it is. So do I.
-He's in the military.
-Police task force.
It's Jens.
We worked together for years.
His wife and child died.
They were pushed against a lorry.
-He blew his head off years ago.
-They took no fingerprints or DNA.
-Saga thinks he's alive.
-He can't be.
EPISODE 9
-Hi.
-Are you allowed to sleep here again?
-Yes.
-You're good together.
-Yes, we are.
-Are you going to work?
-I'm going to Malmö.
-I thought he was done.
-Yes, but we're not done chasing him.
Saga thinks he'll carry on.
-With what?
-I don't know.
When this is over, maybe we
could do something together.
-We could go somewhere.
-The two of us?
-Where would we go?
- I don't know.
-Think about it until tonight.
-OK.
It's too risky,
someone might recognize him.
-He's changed his appearance.
-We have to assume so.
Bjørn recognized him,
but only the eyes.
Look for something to do with plastic
surgeons after the staged suicide.
-Anything in particular?
-Deaths and missing persons.
-Hi, everybody. Hi, Saga.
-I thought you'd sleep at my place.
-I was allowed to sleep at home.
-Right.
-We're not seeing each other.
-He cheated, his wife threw him out.
-He slept on my camp bed.
-Now you all know.
-Why was Jens' wife out driving?
-Mikaela. Her name was Mikaela.
-Why was Mikaela on the bridge?
-She was going to see her parents.
At 2 a.m. midweek?
What a strange time to visit
your parents with a 7-year-old.
THE BRIDGE
Can you look after
the children a while?
-When?
-Around 11 o'clock.
-Why aren't they in school?
-They're off. We're going to the zoo.
-What are you doing first?
-I have a meeting here.
-I thought you were on sick leave.
-We're just preparing a presentation.
I don't want the children to disturb.
-Can you take them out?
-No, I'm going to town.
It's difficult to move in with me,
you don't see much of Martin.
So I've not asked anything of you.
You use our home as a hotel.
But now I need your help.
What is so important
you can't help me?
I've got a job interview.
A job interview? About a job?
Yes, so that I can pay
the hotel bill.
OK. I'll work something out.
-The job's a good thing. Good luck.
-Thanks.
-Think aloud.
-You and Jens were friends.
-That's why he didn't shoot you.
-Probably.
Is your relationship
relevant to the investigation?
I don't know.
Jens was a good police officer.
He was a good person.
He wanted to change the world.
-This is different.
-That night on the bridge...
-She wasn't going to her parents.
-Where was she going?
They said that her friend
Josefin Samuelsson might know.
-Mikaela was on her way to see her.
-Yes.
-Why was Mikaela on her way?
-She and Jens had a row.
She asked
if she and Rasmus could sleep over.
-What was the row about?
-She wanted a divorce.
She'd met someone else.
Jens went furious
and didn't want to see her again.
She didn't dare to stay.
She was coming here with Rasmus.
-Did she tell you who she'd met?
-No.
-Did she tell Jens?
-No, only that she'd met someone.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I asked her if she ought to
warn him against Jens.
-But Jens didn't know who he was.
-Did she say anything else?
-Excuse me.
-No, we were going to see each other.
Why are you asking about this now?
They were mentioned
as part of an investigation.
-Jens is dead, he committed suicide.
-Yes, we know.
Martin? Why did you leave?
The man that Mikaela met...
It was me.
I wasn't married.
It was long before I met Mette.
Susanne and I were divorced.
She and Julie left me.
Mikaela was having a hard time.
-You weren't married, but she was.
-Yes.
-With your best friend and colleague.
-Can we keep this to ourselves?
I don't want
the rest of the team to know.
If it affects the investigation,
they have to be told.
-Did you know that she'd tell him?
-No.
It must have been hard to see him.
Could you have remained colleagues-
-if you and his wife had become
a couple? Maybe you didn't plan to.
I certainly didn't plan
to cause her death.
-You didn't.
-Yes.
She chose to tell him.
He became angry.
Without me there would have been
nothing to tell.
Without a bridge
she wouldn't have crashed.
-You can't think like that.
-No, but I do.
-Let's go.
-OK.
-Have you got anything?
-Well...
It's cost a lot to do these things.
We looked for
properties and transactions.
We checked
unsolved robberies and break-ins.
It's brought us nowhere so far.
Do your colleagues know
that Jens is alive?
-Yes, a few chosen by Lillian.
-What did the friend say?
Mikaela told Jens that she was
leaving him. She was scared to stay.
-Why did she leave?
-She'd met someone.
Do we know whom?
No. She didn't know, nor did Jens.
-And it doesn't really matter.
-OK.
Saga? Karl-Erik Hermansson
was a plastic surgeon.
He died in a car accident.
His practice was close to Triangeln.
-Did he have any colleagues?
-A nurse called Elsa Dahlberg.
-Saga, you're doing a good job.
-Yes.
If this leads to anything...
You're good.
And...if anyone's going to catch him,
it'll be you.
-Yes, I think so as well.
-Yes.
-Do you ever praise the others?
-No.
-Why not?
-I just tell them what to do.
-They're good.
-Yes, that's their job.
-Don't you want praise?
-No, that's not necessary.
-Do you think it's important?
-Yes, very. Most people do.
-Do you want me to sing your praise?
-Sure.
-What do you want me to say?
-It doesn't work like that.
That's like telling someone
to say "I love you".
It has to be spontaneous.
Did you miss me yesterday?
When I didn't show up in the evening?
Yes, a little.
Karl-Erik...
They said that he killed himself,
but I never believed that.
-Why not?
-We worked together for 11 years.
I would have known
if he was planning suicide.
No, many that commit suicide
don't display suicidal tendencies.
And then there was that fire.
Something wasn't right.
-What fire?
-At the practice, after his death.
-The entire house nearly burnt down.
-Was he one of your patients?
Yes, yes...
Jens something. Danish.
I wouldn't have been surprised
if he'd committed suicide.
-Why not?
-Such extensive changes indicate...
...problems beyond your appearance.
-What did he have done?
-The hairline, the nose...
...the mouth, the teeth,
changes to the bone structure.
But he became really handsome.
Karl-Erik was good at his job.
Do you have any medical records?
There were medical records
and computer back-ups.
It was in the same room in the fire.
Can you describe him
if we bring in a sketch artist?
-I think I've got a photo of him.
-Of him? After the operation?
I kept paper copies
of some of my patients' records.
I worked from home at times,
my husband was ill.
-So you might have some here?
-Yes, in the attic.
-Do you know where you put them?
-In a box.
-Is it marked?
-I can't remember.
It should be a bit further in.
-How far in?
-A bit further that way.
It might be next to a typewriter.
There it is.
It's marked "office".
-Is it marked "office"?
-Yes, that's it.
There.
-Hi.
-Sorry I'm late.
-Flowers to make you feel better.
-Thank you.
Come in.
This is what he looks like now.
-What do we do?
-I'm trying to find his name.
Should we distribute the picture?
He doesn't know
that his appearance is known.
If no one but us know,
he won't be recognized.
None of us will run into him.
To catch him everyone must know.
-He'll find out and go into hiding.
-If there's a leak.
He somehow receives
info we distribute.
We'll keep it to ourselves
for a while.
-For how long?
-We'll distribute it in the morning.
A nationwide alert in both countries
and Europol and Interpol.
-Martin? I don't like lying to Hans.
-What have you lied about?
I haven't mentioned
your affair with Mikaela.
You just haven't told him.
That's not a lie.
To not tell the truth
is the definition of lying.
-Has he asked you?
-No.
-Did he ask if you're hiding info?
-Then you haven't lied.
-He'll find out sooner or later.
Say that you knew,
but that it wasn't relevant.
I'd be lying.
-Is it relevant?
-Not so far.
-What a nice house.
-Thanks, we like it here.
-What does your husband do?
-He's a policeman.
How exciting. What kind
of crime does he work with?
He's an investigator.
He's working on
the killer from the bridge, or T.T.
-Or whatever you call that madman.
-He has his hands full then.
-They seem unable to catch him.
-No, they're closer than we think.
-Mum, when are we leaving?
-Later, if I'm up to it.
-You promised.
-That was before I fell ill.
-You manage to work.
-If you disturb me, it takes longer.
-Then I'll be more tired. OK?
-Ok, then...
-Where are you going?
-To the zoo.
I'll bribe them
with a film and sweets instead.
-The zoo sounds more fun.
-That's what they think.
-Do you want me to join you?
-No, I'll manage.
I'm sure you will,
but I can help out.
-If you want me to.
-No, that won't be necessary.
I haven't been there for ages,
it'd be fun.
Well, thank you. That's nice.
Thanks for coming,
we'll get back to you.
"Thank you for your interest.
The position has been filled."
-Excuse me?
-If you need help with the wording.
-As I said, we'll get back to you.
-Thank you.
August!
-Why are you here so early?
-What?
You were to arrive this afternoon.
-We were supposed to meet up.
-Were we?
-That's what we arranged.
-When did we do that?
Online the day before yesterday.
-We've never chatted online.
-Knock it off.
-We haven't.
-You have to be joking.
-We've chatted every night.
-No, we haven't.
Someone must have been
pulling your leg.
-I hope you haven't revealed too much.
-Oh, fuck.
-Do you regret something you said?
-Not really.
I don't know. I thought it was you.
Yes, well...
We met anyway, as it turned out.
-Am I disturbing? Where's Martin?
-On a coffee break.
-Should I fetch him?
-No, no.
I want you to know this before
the others. I asked for a transfer.
-Yes, to Gothenburg.
-It's going to happen.
-When?
-I want to finish this first.
-And they have to find a successor.
-How long does that take?
I don't know, maybe a month.
-Do you know who it'll be?
-No.
You'll be fine,
you're a wonderful police officer.
-Not everyone thinks so.
-Then they're wrong.
All aren't
as understanding as you are.
-I just wanted you to know.
-Thanks.
A meeting at John's.
OK, we've got a name.
Sebastian Sandstrod.
I found a link between Jens'
bank accounts and Sebastian.
-He runs an IT consultancy firm.
-Where?
There's no office,
just a PO box and a mobile.
We've got his card details,
driving licence and address.
-Where does he live?
-Outside of Copenhagen. Hellerup.
-Did Jens live there?
-No.
Well done. Well done, everybody.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
-Do you want to go with me?
-No, I'll go with Martin.
OK.
-Who are you calling?
-Mette.
-Does she know about Mikaela?
-No.
Maybe you shouldn't
tell her just now.
You weren't together
when you did Mikaela, but...
-Thank you.
-Yes.
That's it. You can wait outside.
It's my husband,
I'll call him later.
-There. Where's your hat?
-I don't know.
-Did you tell your husband about us?
-What about us?
-That I'm going with you to the zoo.
-I left a note.
That's it, I think we're ready.
-You're not having second thoughts?
-No, I look forward to it.
The house is cleared!
I'm ready, we'll go in.
Martin? Saga? Down here.
I need Gry, Navid and Anne here.
They know what to look for.
-We've got Danish officers.
-Let's put politics aside.
You've got nothing to lose.
-I'll go see someone that knew Jens.
-You knew him.
-Not recent years.
-I'll get the team here.
-I withdrew the report against you.
-The one from the bridge?
-Yes. I thought you should know.
-Thanks.
-But you made a mistake.
-Thanks anyway.
Did she talk about me
on the way here?
-No, was she supposed to?
-Not really.
-I've resigned, I'm going to move.
-Yes, I know.
It's definite now,
and I wonder how she is.
-Saga doesn't share her feelings.
-You're most likely to hear about it.
-Can you ask her?
-Yes, of course.
-She means a lot to me.
-You mean a lot to her.
-Do you recall my colleague Jens?
-Yes, he stayed here.
Did he mention other places?
Places where he felt safe?
Well, he didn't talk much.
He kept to himself.
-I need something, Olsen.
-He got that caravan.
Other than that? No.
Why do you ask?
It wasn't suicide.
-Was he killed?
-He's alive.
-What?
-He's called Sebastian Sandstrod.
-Do you know him?
-No, no.
Try to remember.
Is there anything at all?
Hang on... He...
-He got a parcel just before he left.
-What was in it?
His family had
a summer house in Sweden.
When they sold it, they sent him
some of Mikaela's things.
-What was it?
-I'm not sure.
Note books, letters, personal items.
Something made him angry.
-What?
-I don't know.
He wanted someone dead.
He broke furniture,
he really lost it. I threw him out.
He got that caravan where he...
Well, he never came back.
-Yes?
-Hi, it's Saga. He knows it was you.
Hello?
Come on. For God's sake, answer.
-It's August.
-Hi, is Mette at home?
No. I'm alone.
-Where is she?
-She spoke about going to the zoo.
-I didn't think she went.
-There's a note.
She did go, someone joined her.
-Who?
-Sebastian Sandstrod.
Everyone knows what he looks like.
There's a nationwide alert.
Gry, Navid and Anne are checking
his basement. He planned this.
-Did he succeed with everything else?
-Yes.
-Does that mean...?
-Stop it. Don't even think it. OK?
The zoo was searched,
they're not there.
Why is he after you?
You were friends.
Do you think I can read his mind?
-And Mette's mobile?
-Barbara is working on it.
Just go.
I've got it. It's in that area.
-Can't you narrow it down?
-No, but it doesn't seem to move.
-What's that?
-The zoo.
-Then how could they miss them?
-It's not correct.
-The sound might be switched off.
-He let Mette write his name.
He knows we'll find out
who he is and where they are.
-Yes, but this is our best lead.
-Then how about a thank you?
A team arrives in five minutes.
-No uniforms. We're leaving now.
-Good.
Aren't we leaving? What is it?
OK. We'll go in now.
Go that way.
-Saga Norén.
-Hi. He used his credit card.
-Five minutes ago at a zoo café.
-He used his credit card here.
-Where?
-It's called Provianten.
-Provianten.
-Come on.
Excuse me...
It's the police.
Show me the credit card you used.
It's not mine, it was given to me.
He told me to use it here.
Are you Martin?
He said you'd show up.
Take it easy, take it easy.
It's just this.
He said it was for you.
Right.
Catch me, if you can!
-Let's race each other.
-Haven't you got any children?
No.
I have had. A son.
-What happened?
-A car accident.
-Oh, I'm sorry. How terrible.
-Yes.
It took a while, but...
I got back on my feet.
The worst thing is the anger.
You need an outlet for your anger.
I work on it every day.
-I don't know what I'd do.
-No.
-What about your wife? Was she...?
-She'd met someone else.
She wanted a divorce. I lost her
even before the accident.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to pry.
-That's OK.
-Martin cheated on me.
It's not relevant,
but I know what you've been through.
It hurts.
We should...
-Children? We're leaving now.
-We're coming.
Yes!
Thank you,
it's been a really nice day.
-I want to show you one more thing.
-Yes!
-We should go home, they're tired.
-It won't take long.
-You won't regret it.
-OK.
We drove far
to get to Legoland as well.
-The door is open.
-Yes! Yes!
There's a surprise for you inside.
The light switch is by the door.
-Is it yours?
-It belongs to a friend.
-What do you think it is? A rat?
-I think so too.
Rats aren't that small.
I think they're bigger.
What is it?
-I'm sorry.
-I don't know, it's just...
I'll get the children.
Come on. We're going home.
-Look, a hamster.
-Yes.
I have something for you as well.
Close your eyes. Close your eyes.
Give me your hand.
Hold on to this.
-What is it?
-I'm almost done.
Squeeze it. That's it.
You can look now.
What is it, mum?
What is it?
Sit down, please sit down.
Do as I say. Sit down!
Help!
I spoke to my father.
-Did it go well?
-Better than expected.
Yes?
-Have you found them?
-No.
I thought about something.
Do you remember Frida
that I've been chatting to? My ex?
-Yes, what about her?
-It wasn't Frida.
Let's go, Saga.
She's not on the chat line.
It's someone else.
-When did she contact you?
-A week ago.
It's Jens. You wrote
that we were looking for Anja.
Did it matter?
-Anything else?
-He doesn't know that he met Frida.
-We can contact him as August.
-He didn't answer about today.
-What's happening today?
-I was meeting Frida, I thought.
-Fælledparken in an hour and a half?
-Yes.
-Have you got a hoodie?
-Will he show up?
-He's been true to his word so far.
-I'm going.
-I'll stay here and check this.
-I'm in position.
-Received.
Give me your status, 1 to 4.
Unit 1 is ready.
I can see the target.
Unit 2 is in position.
Unit 3 is in position.
I can see the target.
-Unit 4 is in position.
-Received. Stand by.
A man is approaching the target.
-What's happening?
-A man with a dog is approaching.
All units,
move slowly towards the target.
It's not him. Continue the operation.
Return to initial positions.
I'd like to report
some strange sounds.
A woman and some children
are screaming.
-You write a lot about me.
-Yes, maybe...
-MILF.
-Yes. It was just a joke.
-It means...
-I know, but I don't have children.
Did it matter that I mentioned Anja?
He didn't know
that we were looking for her.
It was my fault that she died.
We shouldn't have spoken about her.
It was unprofessional.
-I didn't know it was him.
-I know. He's smart and dangerous.
Will he kill Mette and the children?
Give me a straight answer.
Probably,
if he hasn't done it already.
-Nothing yet. What do we do?
-Hang on.
-He's twenty minutes late.
-He's not coming. Call it off.
-Abort! He's not coming.
-Abort the operation.
-Pack up, we'll see you at home.
-Yes?
Martin? The central received
a call about cries for help.
-A woman and some children.
-Morten, you drive.
-Why is he doing this?
-His family died in an accident.
He feels that there were made errors.
He's taking revenge.
All the talk
about opening people's eyes...
-...was just talk?
-Yes.
What was my father's error?
-You have to ask him.
-But you know?
Did he let him down?
He let me and my mother down.
And my half sister and her mother.
And Mette. That's just the way he is.
Wait here.
Mette? Mette!
What's happening, Martin?
Lillian! Listen to me.
Lillian is coming, go with her.
There's a grenade.
I'll stay with mum.
Get the children out.
-I'll stay with mum.
-Come on.
-Help me.
-I'm with you now.
I'll hold here. I'll help you.
Come, darling. You've done
really well. Let's do this together.
-We're ready, Martin.
-Yes.
To the left, the ruins are cleared.
Come on.
Come on. I'm with you.
On the count of three you let go.
OK? On three. Raise your hand.
On three you open your hand
and let go. Ready?
One, two, three.
OK. Yes. Thank you. Bye.
John didn't find anything
on the chat line.
-Who's John?
-The IT manager in my unit.
Isn't that typical? Just when things
are getting better...
Frida made me...
or the guy I thought was Frida...
He made me see my father
in a new light.
He got me closer to him.
He gave good advice,
but it was just some psychopath.
-Are you listening?
-The park...
-Have you heard anything?
-Mikaela was lost to him already.
He didn't want to see her again.
-So he lost a son.
-Who?
You and Martin were to grow closer,
so that it would hit him harder.
What are you talking about?
He's not after the others.
He's after you!
-It's Saga Norén. Do you read me?
-What's going on?
-Why don't they answer?
It's Saga. Do you read me?
What are you doing?
He's here.
-Haven't you got your gun?
-No. Hush, come on.
Wait here.
No!
Turn around.
Put your hands behind your back.
Translated by: Elisabeth Carrera
www.sdimedia.com