SUMMARY
The lights on the bridge went out.
- The women were just the beginning.
- He wants to point out five problems.
Unequal before the law.
There are four left. What are they?
- Is he a psychopath?
- He's willing to make sacrifices.
- Are you sure it's the same man?
- Yes. Two dismembered women.
- Nine dead homeless people.
- Ten now.
Daniel Ferbé has joined us.
He's been in contact with
the perpetrator or perpetrators.
- Which is it?
- I've been in touch with one person.
He's done more for the homeless
than the politicians.
- Stefan! Stefan was there.
- Stefan? Do you know him?
Do you know who brought
the bottles? Who poisoned you?
You can't stay, Anja.
We haven't got space.
I'm just about to have some tea.
You can have some.
What are you doing?
- Has he been in touch?
- He wants 20 million to stop it.
- After another litre the heart stops.
- OK, so five or six hours.
- Let's contact the four men again.
- Did he do that with his eyes before?
Wasn't he in the merchant navy?
It's Morse code.
EPISODE 4
THE BRIDGE
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes, pretty well.
- And you?
- I keep having dreams.
- About dad?
- About anything.
Was he happy?
Yes. Why do you ask?
We had a wonderful relationship.
I want to see him.
- Is that a good idea?
- I don't know, but I want to.
Will you come with me?
It's the police.
They want to talk to you.
- Charlotte Söringer is on her way.
- And the Danish?
- They're coming, albeit reluctantly.
- Let me know when they're here.
- How are things going?
- This is Kjell-Åke Jönsson.
He used to be a telegraph operator.
So far he's found:
"Recognize the eyes."
- And then "near".
- Does he know him?
- From the merchant navy?
- T.T. doesn't know Morse code.
- T.T.?
- They call him The Truth Terrorist.
Here's something new.
Men... Men's...
...home...is...
- ...te...
- Istedgade.
The Men's Home on Istedgade.
I'll go there.
August? Dammit, August!
I'm warming milk. Keep an eye on it.
- What's going on, brats?
- We're not brats.
Yes, you are.
- What's wrong with mum?
- It must be something she ate.
- What?
- I don't know. A car?
She did it yesterday as well.
She was sick.
Four police officers are charged.
There is no proof
of police brutality.
It's uncertain who did what,
when Hadi Hurani was injured.
Experts believe...
I don't care
what they say on the radio.
Nice coffee.
- What are you doing?
- Did I wake you?
No. Do you know what time it is?
- Why are you here?
- What?
- What are you doing here?
- I came yesterday. I stayed over.
Don't you remember?
I had a row with my mum.
It was raining.
You let me stay here.
Have you got
some bread or something?
A samurai fasts
the day before he goes into battle.
I have an important
assignment tomorrow.
- But... can I have something to eat?
- Sure.
Bread is in the other cupboard.
- Why are you so grumpy?
- I'm scared of my wife.
Does anyone want this?
A former sailor, a nasty man.
We banned him five years ago.
- Why?
- He was aggressive and unstable.
He nearly killed
a man that changed the TV channel.
- So he fell out with everyone.
- Yes.
- Do you know where he went?
- I don't know.
I need a list of staff
while he was here.
Do you realize how many there were?
What do you need it for?
Bjørn met his abductor here.
Lindberg! Stefan Lindberg.
- This is quite a coincidence.
- I work here.
- I'm the Swedish contact person.
- Maybe you know Bjørn, then.
- Who?
- The guy that's bleeding to death.
No.
Were you here five years ago
when he was banned?
I never met him,
so I probably wasn't.
- How's your sister?
- Still unconscious.
- When will you be back in Malmö?
- This afternoon.
Stop by the police station.
I want to ask you some questions.
- About what?
- We'll talk about it then.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
We weren't given much of a choice.
- Why are we here?
- Agree to his demand.
- Why?
- He doesn't like to improvise.
If we force him to,
he might make mistakes.
- Does he assume we won't pay?
- Of course.
You stockpile your money
and take no social responsibility.
We need to discuss our next step.
- If you give in, he'll take action.
- It might save Bjørn Rasmusen.
- And then what?
- I don't know.
Now we know what you think.
Can we discuss the matter in private?
- Could you excuse us?
- Of course.
There's nothing to discuss.
Is there? Do you want to give
a madman 20 million?
We could agree to it,
but then stop the payment.
- I don't think we should pay.
- "They can afford to save Bjørn."
9454 group members so far.
And then there's that.
Charlotte is right.
Bjørn knows the abductor.
All of these people
were there when he was.
- Is it personal?
- I don't know.
- Is he in Denmark?
- I don't know. I don't know anything.
We need a happy ending.
Tomorrow won't be easy.
- I heard they might be acquitted.
- The press is drawing comparisons.
Four immigrants were sentenced,
but only one or two were guilty.
- Is this the same thing?
- Yes. Yes.
- But they're police officers.
- Yes, exactly.
- I'm going back to Malmö.
- Martin? A happy ending.
- Hi, Henning.
- Hi, Martin.
- How are you?
- Fine.
- The trial must be stressful.
- Yes.
- We'll be acquitted.
- So I hear. Can I have a cigarette?
- Why are you protecting them?
- I'm not. He fell.
- His arm broke and an eye ruptured.
- He had an awkward fall.
How do you rupture your eyeball
in an awkward fall?
- He's dead. Don't walk away!
- Let go of me.
Or what?
Or I'll have an awkward fall?
You're going through hell.
Why are you going down with them?
Hey, hey... Hi, Henning.
- What were you talking about?
- Nothing.
One day. Right?
Keep your mouth shut one day more.
- Do you get it?
- Yes.
We'll get through this.
The property investors
haven't confirmed...
that they'll agree to the demands.
There's no time to lose.
Medical experts say-
- that Bjørn Rasmusen will lose
consciousness within the next hour.
His life will be at stake
as a second hour passes.
Thank you, Karin.
Journalist Daniel Ferbé is with us.
He's in contact with the killer.
- How's it going?
- We don't know where Bjørn is.
I didn't find any clues, but I met
Stefan Lindberg in Copenhagen.
- What was he doing there?
- Working. I told him to stop by.
- Why?
- He keeps popping up.
- They won't pay.
- Didn't they hear what we said?
- Are they still there?
- You can't have your way this time.
He's saying something.
He's saying: A...1...
And then three letters: A, J, B.
- He repeats it: A1.
- It's some sort of code.
- No, he must be looking at something.
- He can see the camera.
Maybe.
Gry and Navid,
search for A1AJB everywhere.
Product numbers, the land registry...
Everything!
Ask Copenhagen to do the same.
- He might change the number.
- He won't. He's unconscious.
THEY'RE KILLING BJØRN
- Can you see well enough?
- It's a bit more complicated.
- To negotiate with terrorists...
- Write an editorial.
- I mean...
- Have you seen the competition?
- It's all about emotions.
- That's what he wants.
How do you know what he wants?
Are you his contact?
- You're just jealous.
- For once I'm not, actually.
The four property investors
have made a decision.
They won't pay the 20 million.
- Do you regret this?
- Not yet.
- We can go back home.
- No, I want to see him.
- Are you OK?
- Yes.
- Who are you?
-I'm sorry. I'll leave.
Who are you? Why are you here?
My name's Emilie Hanson.
I was a close friend of Göran.
Well... I'm sorry,
I shouldn't be here. I'll leave.
Em? You're Em.
You were together.
I'm sorry for your loss, Maja.
I didn't know that she was here.
- Think out loud.
- He hasn't made a single mistake.
He didn't expect that Bjørn
would be able to communicate.
He's in an abandoned factory.
What's in an abandoned factory?
Machinery.
- He would have told us what kind.
- Pipes, doors.
Doors with serial numbers.
A barrel of chemicals.
Behind the camera.
It's filming continuously. Filming...
Bjørn can see a power meter.
He isn't giving us
the last two digits.
There's a letter, a digit,
three letters, and two digits.
The last two digits
must be hidden from view.
- Are there 99 possible places?
- 100, there's 00 as well.
- We've found it.
- It's a fuseboard.
- Some aren't used, there are 89 left.
- That's 88 too many, he's dying.
37 are in apartment buildings
and 30 in houses.
- That leaves 22.
- Martin, Saga.
I'll pay. I'll pay the entire sum.
- Why? On your own?
- Yes.
If he demands that the others pay,
we can pretend they did.
- Your husband would have refused.
- Yes.
- Are you sure? It's a lot of money.
- Yes, I'm absolutely sure.
- He'll go there to stop the bleeding.
- I'll contact the press.
This way.
- What made you change your mind?
- Revenge.
I'm sorry. I don't have noble motives
or a guilty conscience.
- It's revenge.
- On your husband.
- I feel as if I've wasted 19 years.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
Don't be.
I can break down or get my own back.
I'll get my own back.
- Are you married?
- Yes.
And faithful? Good.
I'd like to drive you home,
but I'm needed here.
I've got my car, and I'm in no hurry.
I'll let Maja leave the house.
My stepdaughter.
Who will inherit 20 million less.
- They'll pay 20 million.
- To save the tramp?
- Can you handle it?
- To quote a press release? Use Åke.
- What is he doing?
- Åke? He's licking his elbow.
- The killer, I mean. T.T.
- He said he would stop the bleeding.
- So he has to go there.
- Yes, but no one knows where it is.
There are three interesting meters
in the same empty building.
The power station says
that one is in use.
The task force is on its way.
We've got him.
- If he sticks to his word.
- He will.
Do you think he's dead?
- Are you expecting visitors?
- Open the door.
It's locked.
- Lasse Jönsson?
- Yes, he lives here. I'll take it.
I need your signature there.
Thank you.
I don't want you to lock the door.
- Why not?
- I'm locked in.
No, I'm locking things out.
The end result is the same, isn't it?
- Take the keys. Is that better?
- Sure.
- Don't let anyone in.
- No.
- Aren't you going to open it?
- I'm not allowed. Not yet.
- Says who?
- No One.
I might call mum.
I'm sure she's worried.
That serves her right.
Dad's much nicer.
But he's got a new, fantastic family.
He doesn't have time for me.
- Who are you?
- Are you kidding?
Anja. I came yesterday.
I spent the night here.
The rain.
- I'm going out for a while.
- Will you come back?
- If you let me.
- Of course. Just knock three times.
They're on their way.
We can enter in ten minutes.
The fuseboards are in three places.
- Ten minutes is a lot of time.
- 9 minutes 47 seconds.
- Where are you going?
- I'm doing my job.
We have to wait for the task force.
The most important task
is to protect your colleague.
Let me make this clear,
I'm your colleague.
Turn left.
- It's this one.
- Hans calling Saga. Where are you?
Hans calling Saga.
Saga? Over.
What the hell are they doing?
Police! Stop!
- Stop!
- Don't kill me! Please!
The other fuseboard is over there.
Don't.
Calm down. We're from the police.
Calm down. OK?
- What's your name?
- Mange. I live here.
- Have you seen anyone here?
- No, I'm alone.
I'll check the other fuseboards.
Can you bring him upstairs?
- Are you OK?
-I'm OK.
Saga calling Hans.
We've arrested a person.
- What are you doing? Who is that?
- A homeless person.
There was nothing
at Sorgenfri and Dalvik either.
They're other industrial areas
with the correct meter numbers.
- I was absolutely sure.
- He might have stopped the bleeding.
That doesn't matter
if we don't know where.
- Saga Norén.
- It's Gry. We discovered something.
There are two of some fuseboards.
- What does that mean?
- There's that new area at Sorgenfri.
Numbers from buildings due
for demolition have been reused.
- Every fuseboard is in two places.
- We checked the new ones.
Send me everything you've got.
Get everyone out there.
- Should I take the gun?
- You can't be armed in Sweden.
- I don't like this.
- Don't worry, I'm a good shot.
All the way down the corridor.
- Are you OK?
- Yes.
Bjørn! Bjørn! Can you hear me?
Saga calling Hans.
I found the victim.
T.T. is going out onto the roof.
He's armed.
- Hi. How are you doing?
- Me? Fine.
- What did he look like?
- He was taller than me and athletic.
He was fit and good at close combat.
I don't know more.
- Is that it?
- She meant to say: How are you?
It's been patched up nicely.
What about Bjørn?
His heart stopped.
He never regained consciousness.
He had stopped the bleeding.
He sticks to his word.
- He must have had an escape route.
- He shot two from the task force.
One dead, one critically injured.
Did you see anything?
- What?
- I just got this feeling.
I don't know what it means.
I'm sorry.
- I'll be back tomorrow.
- Are you sure?
Your wife is outside,
I'll send her in.
Are you Mette Rohde?
Your husband's in there.
- Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
- Nice to meet you.
- Martin has told me a lot about you.
- What?
- You're working together.
- Nothing else?
- Do you do something else together?
- No. What do you mean?
We'll let Mette go inside. I'm Hans.
I'm the one that called.
You can go in.
Maybe we can meet
under better circumstances?
Come here. I need a kiss.
Come here, sit down.
- Ouch, what are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
The bastard kicked the stitches open.
It hurt as bad as giving birth.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Was it him? Why didn't you
shoot him? Why let him get so close?
- Because I'm not armed in Sweden.
- You're chasing that lunatic unarmed?
- Saga is armed.
- OK, what did she do?
She was knocked over.
- Are you off the case? Why not?
- I can't stop.
Of course you can.
You're in hospital, for God's sake!
I can't. I'm going to find him.
This is no different
from what I've always done.
Normally you're
able to defend yourself.
Yes.
How are the twins and Nicholai?
August is watching them.
He's been very helpful today.
- It will work out.
- Yes.
Saga Norén will be back tomorrow.
- Martin Rohde?
- Same thing, tomorrow.
- Can you leave them a note?
- Certainly, I will.
- What was your name again?
- Stefan Lindberg.
Stefan Lindberg.
I'll take care of it.
- Stefan Lindberg.
- Where's Veronika?
- What Veronika?
- She can't leave with the children.
I'll find her! Do you get it?
If I can't find her, I'll find you.
Bloody hell...
- I can do this.
- Sorry.
Thanks.
- Hi. Are you home already?
- I may as well lie here.
- Thanks for looking after the kids.
- That's OK.
- What did T.T. look like?
- I don't know.
But he's the hell of a kicker.
I'm off to bed. Don't stay up late.
Maybe I should get
one of those user accounts?
- I could stay in touch with people.
- You're good at that...
- Who is she?
- Her name's Frida.
- Is she your girlfriend? A friend?
- If you cared, you would have known.
She's my ex. We were together
my first year in high school.
- Can you remember my first year?
- No...
- And then he left his son's room.
- Sleep tight.
Bloody hell...
What is it? What's on your mind?
What?
Is something wrong?
- What is it?
- I'm pregnant.
It happened before your operation.
- It's yours, in case you wonder.
- No, I don't.
We weren't going to have any more.
What?
- We can't.
- I don't know.
What if it's twins?
It could be twins again.
We'd have five children!
No. We haven't got enough space.
- No. We... Can we manage?
- Can we manage?
Come here. Come here.
- We don't have to decide yet.
- No.
- I'm leaving now.
- Hans?
What's a police officer's
most important task?
To solve crime,
arrest the perpetrator.
To protect your colleague?
Martin thinks so.
- It wasn't your fault he was injured.
- I helped Bjørn.
To save lives must be
most important. Martin is alive.
- Exactly.
- It must be most important.
I've double-checked,
they prioritize the same way.
The Nordic countries
have the same instructions.
There's no difference.
You did the right thing.
Why do you sit in the dark?
Darling?
He resisted a body search.
Bo kneed him in the face.
His eye burst.
Luffe tried to stop the screaming
and broke his arm. It hurt.
He tried to get up,
but they sat on him...
until he calmed down.
He was unconscious.
I watched. I watched,
and then I walked away.
You should tell someone else.
I agree.
I'm sorry. Thanks.
Hello? It's me.
Hello?
Did you run into No One?
He just left.
- How can I run into no one?
- That was his name. A master.
He revealed the truth. Tomorrow
the sword of justice will swing.
OK.
- Good night, Anja.
- You're odd, but in a good way.
Listen, I... called mum.
I thought she would cry
and tell me to come home.
She went absolutely crazy.
So I'll stay another night,
if that's OK?
Stay as long as you like. From
tomorrow on the apartment's yours.
- What? Mine?
- Good night.
- Don't forget to lock the door.
- No.
- Hi, Saga.
- How's your scrotum?
Small talk isn't your strong side.
I was thinking about
what happened today.
He aimed at you, but didn't fire.
Why didn't he shoot you?
- I don't know.
- He shot two from the task force.
Maybe I wasn't a threat to him?
Maybe.
Or he's trying to tell us something.
- What?
- Maybe he needs you?
- Why?
- I don't know.
Think about it. Good night.