SUMMARY
The lights on the bridge went out.
- Saga Norén.
- Copenhagen Police.
Two women killed a year apart.
Dismembered and assembled.
- Someone's making a statement.
- Do you understand my Danish?
- Who are you?
- A protector of the truth.
Why are you calling me?
Sorry about the drama.
This is only a beginning.
I was shocked
when I heard the message.
It was recorded
three and a half years ago.
- What do you do?
- I'm in the police.
- It's a corpse.
- Oh, OK.
- Can the lights be turned on?
- Martin! A dog is alerting.
I thought I was about to die.
- I neither can nor want to anymore.
- Do you want a divorce?
I've been contacted. Homelessness.
It's about the homeless.
Six people have been found.
They seem to be poisoned
and have been brought to hospital.
Sonja? It's me.
- He's going to kill homeless people.
- He's started already.
EPISODE 3
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Do you know anything
about the poisonings?
- Saga Norén. Do you know...?
- No.
Go... over there.
- In there?
- Go over there.
THE BRIDGE
I'm going back to Malmö.
- Are you sure it's the same man?
- Yes.
Two women, the car bomb.
- Nine dead homeless people.
- Ten now.
- Is your Swedish colleague clever?
- Saga Norén?
- Her clear-up rate is fantastic.
- She's very efficient.
She's found time to report you.
I'll stall as long as I can,
but try to make her withdraw it.
- Show some finesse.
- Finesse? What do you mean?
The two of you are colleagues.
Just colleagues.
- Am I here because of this?
- No, no. I'll walk you to your car.
We want to attract businesses
and families to our region.
It's bad enough that we've got
homeless people, now they're killed.
We have to handle
a trial against five police officers.
The Monique Brammer case
was never mine. I'm not involved.
- What are you trying to tell me?
- Solving the case has top priority.
- And your second priority?
- We need some positive publicity.
It seemed to be going well.
He woke up. Suddenly... well...
I wasn't there when mum died either.
Your father
loved you very much, Maja.
Very much.
- Hi.
- Stefan Lindberg.
- This way.
- Thank you.
We're running tests, but don't know
what she's swallowed.
- Should we contact anyone?
- No, I'm all she has.
- OK.
- Thank you.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Sonja.
- It's mine!
- Let go!
What the hell are you doing?
They want us to leave.
- Who?
- The welfare office. There's a bus.
- Aren't you coming?
- I take care of myself.
What are you doing?
- Any news about the survivors?
- Two in Denmark, one in Sweden.
Didn't anyone see
the cases of wine be put there?
- Do we know which poison it was?
- Not yet.
And he doesn't leave traces.
The spasms suggest an alkaloid.
The rigor mortis implies strychnine.
But vomiting blood
isn't typical for strychnine.
- Get yourself a hobby.
- What?
The bottles and cases
gave us nothing.
It's been more than 24 hours,
and we have nothing.
We'll start from scratch again.
The reporter Daniel Ferbé
has joined us in the studio.
He's been in contact with
the perpetrator or perpetrators.
- Which is it?
- I've been in touch with one person.
12 people have died in 24 hours.
What do they want?
They, or him,
want to point out five problems.
Five truths about society.
He's a truth terrorist.
They questioned whether we're
equal before the law. What now?
We shouldn't be so upset.
The same number of homeless
freeze to death every year.
They're his words, not mine.
- Why did he contact you?
- I don't know. Maybe he trusts me?
He's pointed out two problems,
what are the three remaining?
I have no idea. He'll let me know
when something happens.
Do you write what he wants?
I'd be done as a reporter.
- I decide what I write.
- Aftenposten's circulation is.
Saga? Congratulations, Gry!
He's broadcasting again.
It's on truth.se and truth.dk.
He's covering his tracks better.
- Can't you trace him?
- I'll find the server, not him.
What does he want?
A man tied to a chair?
Do you know who he is?
It could be a three year old recording.
Martin. Yes, we're looking at it.
Who? Are you sure?
We'll be right over.
We know who he is.
I had a meeting with my boss.
She's under pressure.
Five of my colleagues face trial for
murder.
- Are you listening?
- Yes.
It's difficult to tell. Try to say
"oh" or "yes" now and then.
I'm in the car next to you.
How can I not listen?
She needs positive publicity.
She'll try to demonstrate
good police work.
- Do you catch my drift?
- No.
When we solve this, she'll make it
look as if Danish police did it.
- We should both take credit for it.
- Fine, if that's important to you.
It should be important to you.
It must have occurred to you
that this might lead to a promotion.
Yes, it occurred to me.
- You improve your career.
- It doesn't matter.
I can't climb higher up the ladder.
I'm not cut out for management.
- Who's told you that?
- No one.
I wanted to let you know.
- Thanks a lot.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Move!
- Let go of me!
- Calm down. Please! Stop it!
- Show me your bag. Let me see.
- No, you can't.
- Let go of me!
- Stay still, show me the bag.
Please, let go of me.
- What's wrong with you? Stay still.
- Let go.
Show me the bag.
Hello? I have to check it.
I didn't mean to do it.
- I still need to check the bag.
- I'm sorry.
- Have they got their own beds?
- It's first come, first served.
- But not for Bjørn?
- He was violent towards the others.
- And that pays off?
- In the end no one took his bed.
- Who's the girl?
- His daughter.
She lives in the US.
- Was he a sailor?
- He was in the merchant navy.
Has he clashed with anyone else?
Apart from neighbours, businesses,
associates, parking attendants...
and most others in the world?
Hi. You don't have to look hard
to find someone that bears a grudge.
- I know where Bjørn is.
- Or was, at least.
- That's the dart from a stun gun.
- OK.
The cartridges contain tiny notes
with the production number on.
You can tell who fired,
for how long, and how many times.
- A note?
- No, tiny notes.
We need people to search for them.
I'm sorry.
Yes, that's it.
- What's on your mind?
- Why he's there.
- What's in it for the perpetrator?
- We'll find out, he's keen to talk.
I spoke to Lillian
about another matter.
You filed a report. What can I do
to make you withdraw it?
- Nothing.
- What?
- What did you do last night?
- We both worked.
- I know. Before that?
- Why do you ask?
It's what colleagues do, they talk.
I'm just making conversation.
- I had sex as well.
- What?
- How did you find time for that?
- It doesn't take long.
- What's his name?
- I can't remember.
- So he stuns Bjørn.
- Yes.
He ties him to a chair
and posts it online.
Why?
He killed the others straight away.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
When?
We'll head straight there. Bye.
She's awake.
She woke up a short while. She slips
in and out of the unconsciousness.
- Unconsciousness.
- Pardon?
- It's without the definite article.
- Thank you.
Let's have a quick look
so the trip isn't wasted.
Sonja? Can you hear me, Sonja?
- I'll fetch a doctor.
- Wait.
- Sonja? Can you hear me, Sonja?
- Stefan.
I'm Saga Norén
from the County Police.
- Stefan was there.
- Stefan?
- Do you know him?
- Everything's fine.
- Did you see who brought the bottles?
- Stefan!
Did Stefan bring them?
Fight it, Sonja. Stay awake.
Who poisoned you? Did you see him?
- I saw him.
- Did you recognize him?
What did he look like?
- Who are you?
- And who are you?
- I'm her brother. Is she awake?
- No.
I'm Saga Norén. This is Martin Rohde
from the Copenhagen Police.
- What's your name?
- Stefan Lindberg. Why are you here?
Have you got an ID?
- You found her and drove her here.
- Yes.
How long has she lived on the street?
I don't know.
We lost contact when I was 15.
We were in separate foster homes.
So... I found her yesterday.
I didn't know she was alive.
You find your sister after years,
on the day she's poisoned?
- What? What's wrong with that?
- How unlucky.
- Where were you when we arrived?
- I had some things to sort out.
They were more important
than your dying sister.
- I can show you where I found her.
- There's no need, we know where.
Let me know if I can help you.
Can I go be with Sonja? Thank you.
- I'll get some flowers for Gry.
- Why?
- It's her birthday. Didn't you know?
- Just go, I'll wait here.
- Have you got any Swedish money?
- Yes.
- Can I borrow some?
Aren't you going back to work?
Mum...
I said I'm sorry.
- Take a painkiller.
- I did an hour ago.
It's from a stun gun.
Can you trace it?
- Do we know which make?
- No.
Here you are. Happy birthday.
They're from Saga and me.
I didn't buy any flowers.
You said they were from both of us.
- They still made her happy.
- How is that relevant?
Something's happening.
I understand, but I can't make it.
We can do it over the phone.
OK. Call me later. Bye.
- You did well on TV today.
- Thanks, Åke.
- Your opinion means a lot to me.
- No, you're being ironic.
- No. Irony is dead, Åke.
- Sure.
- It went well, we all think so.
- I know.
- This guy will be my Sankara Stones.
- What?
"Fortune and glory, kid.
Fortune and glory." Indiana Jones.
- Daniel Ferbé.
- I like your "truth terrorist".
- I don't give a damn.
- I can stop calling.
- I can find someone else.
- No.
Good. I saw you on the air,
have you seen what I sent?
- I'm looking at it.
- You're not the only one.
- What's with the pictures?
- And you're a journalist?
I can find out who they are,
but it's easier if you tell me.
Who are they? Hello?
What the hell...?
Dad's on TV.
He's called Bjørn Rasmusen.
Four property investors are shown.
- From Malmö and Copenhagen.
- I'll answer.
Daniel Ferbé is
in contact with the killer.
The four can save Bjørn Rasmusen.
It's unknown how.
- They're chosen to save Bjørn.
- How?
- What have they got in common?
- All four are property investors.
We're receiving loads of tips
about Bjørn's location.
It's impossible to tell where it is.
Otherwise he wouldn't be there.
Danish police is on its way
to Lorentzen and Beckgård.
We'll take Söringer,
send Anne and Navid to Hodell.
- How did it go with Sonja?
- She saw someone.
- Saga! Martin! He's dead.
- Who?
- Goran Söringer died in hospital.
- Who owns the business now?
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
We need to talk to you.
- Do you remember me?
- Yes.
I won't talk to you. I'm happy
to help, but I'll only talk to you.
- Have you got a name?
- Martin Rohde.
Come in.
- Aren't you coming in?
- Didn't you hear what she said?
- Can't you just listen?
- Yes.
Stop! Hey!
- Get out! Get out!
- Bloody drunk.
What the hell do you want me?
What the hell do you want?
I'm hungry as well.
You've only got yourself to blame.
All police officers in Malmö
and Copenhagen are looking for him.
Then the camera's switched off.
- If he escaped, won't he contact us?
- Let's hope so.
- When was this?
- Nearly an hour ago.
Our colleagues
in Copenhagen report-
- that the Danish property investors
don't know Bjørn.
He's not been evicted, had a lease-
- or had any other connection
to Hodell's properties.
- Charlotte Söringer doesn't know him.
- They're chosen for a reason.
- So what? He doesn't have Bjørn.
- Nor do we.
A psychological profile is useful,
but we don't know if it's one person.
- There's only one.
- How do you know?
There's something about the wording.
Hi, Salvatore.
This is Martin Rohde from Denmark.
Why would someone mispronounce
their colleague's name?
It might be a means of suppression.
- Did you hear that, Saga?
- Yes.
Well, well...
- My name's Martin Rohde.
- Salvatore Johansson.
I haven't had much to go by.
But... it's some type
of psychotic condition.
- Saga? We've found...
- You have to wait.
This person is extremely focused
on a single project.
He's not in a relationship.
He is or has been...
very successful professionally.
I think that he's experienced
something traumatic.
His conception of the world
is warped.
He's trying to regain balance
and make sense of the world again.
Is he emotionally numb
or a psychopath?
He's got a clearly defined target.
He wants us to see things his way.
He's willing to make sacrifices
to achieve that.
- A psychopath, the way I see it.
- No. What are his weaknesses?
Everything is
meticulously planned and executed.
He planned this
for more than three years.
That's his weakness.
If someone or something
upset his plans...
he'll start to lose grip on things.
In short,
he doesn't want to improvise.
- Daniel Ferbé.
- Who's the woman?
Why did you remove
Goran Söringer?
He's dead. He died yesterday.
It's his wife.
Maybe you should read
the entire article?
- Should I find someone else?
- No, no!
What will happen... to Bjørn? Hello?
The technicians found the ID number.
The stun gun was registered.
- It was handed in to us in 2001.
- To us?
It was handed in for destruction,
but that never happened.
I thought it went missing,
but it was signed for.
- By Lennart Fransson.
- He's a retired police officer.
He's 58
and has an apartment in town.
- What was he like as a policeman?
- He did well.
No reports against him.
He was well-liked.
- How can he be involved in this?
- He might not be.
Stay here, Gry.
It's the police, Lennart.
It's Hans from the County Police.
I'll be back.
- Hi. Is dad here?
- No, he just left.
We're having guests tonight.
It's Oscar's birthday.
My brother and my parents
are coming.
- Well...
- Can I wait for dad here?
- Here?
- Yes.
- He'll be gone a while, he just left.
- That's fine, I can wait.
- Well, you can sit there.
- Thanks.
- Does your mother know you're here?
- No. Can you call her?
Tell her that I'll spend the night.
Something happened,
I can't go home.
You can't stay, Anja.
I'm sorry, it's impossible.
- You can't just show up.
- What now, then?
Filippa's brother and his family
are coming. Her parents.
- We haven't got space.
- I don't have to come to the party.
- I can find somewhere to...
- Sweetheart.
That would have been fine,
but there's nowhere to sleep.
Apart from the neighbours,
they're all spending the night.
- It can't be...
- Some other time.
You're always welcome here.
You know that.
I haven't got time
to drive you all the way home.
- I can drive you to the train.
- No, that's OK.
Hey... Is everything OK between us?
They haven't found anything
in Fransson's apartment.
- Nothing? What happened to Bjørn?
- He got him back.
If not we would have found him.
He needs Bjørn for something.
- Bye.
- Why did he pick Bjørn?
- Why not?
- He's big and strong, that's risky.
- He had a stun gun.
- Even so, why did he pick Bjørn?
- Did he take the first he could find?
I would have picked a weak person.
- Listen, Hans...
- Bye.
- Are you going to move?
- Do you want to get rid of me?
Nothing's decided.
Karin is looking for a house online.
We feel a bit homesick.
- Do you want to take over?
- No.
Whoever takes over,
will appreciate having you here.
Extremely focused. Single.
Successful. Clearly defined targets.
- Good at planning.
- Exactly.
- What?
That's the perpetrator's
psychological profile.
Go home and get some sleep.
- How did it go today?
- Fine.
The children are asleep in your bed.
Ask your oldest son why.
- What did he do?
- Showed them the man that's tied up.
They're afraid.
What's going on?
- What is it?
- What do you think?
You showed your siblings some shit.
- It was reality.
- It's not for them to see.
- That's the problem he points out.
- Who is he?
Him, the truth terrorist.
He's done more for the homeless
than the politicians.
- He killed ten of them.
- But everyone's talking about them.
- Do I need to worry about you?
- No. Why?
You've taken a year off
and moved here. You have no job.
- Help me out here, what's your plan?
- Not to have a plan.
- You can't only think about yourself.
- You do.
- You're going to help out more.
- Yes, yes...
- Help Mette out. Stop it.
- Yes, I said!
- Why is he called a truth terrorist?
- A Swedish reporter used it.
It works well online: T.T.
- Turn it off. Come join us.
- I'll be right there.
- What happened?
- Dad was nagging.
- Did I ever meet him?
- No. Me neither.
- Hi.
- Are you visiting someone?
- No. You see...
- It's raining outside.
- I know. I took the rubbish out.
I'm just about to have some tea.
You can have some, if you like.
Oh... sure.
Come on in.
- I've only got green tea.
- That's fine.
- Nice place.
- Thanks. Take a seat.
- Where are you from?
- Copenhagen.
- Why are you here?
- It sounds really childish.
I ran away from home.
- Why?
- I had a row with mum.
That's how it is sometimes.
- Can I stay here a little while?
- Sure. Stay as long as you like.
- Cool. I'll stay a while, then.
- OK.
Dad?
There something you have to see.
- What time is it?
- Five o'clock.
- Come on.
- What's going on?
- Hello?
- He's got Bjørn. You should come in.
- What's happened? Is he dead?
- Not yet.
I'll be right there.
- Saga Norén.
- He's broadcasting again.
- Has he been in touch?
- He wants 20 million.
Five million from each
of the four men, to stop it.
If they refuse, we'll know
what a human being is worth.
- How much time have we got?
- He started at five.
He's lost half a litre of blood.
He weighs 80 kilos.
7 percent is 5 litres. He'll pass out
when he's lost 40 percent of that.
- That gives us four hours.
- After another litre the heart stops.
- OK, so five or six hours.
- Let's contact the four men again.
- Did he do that with his eyes before?
- His tics.
Wasn't he in the merchant navy?
It's Morse code.