There's a burnt cornea.
Let me see.
Yeah, like ice burns.
Why are they naked?
It doesn't make any sense.
It's a ruptured eardrum.
- See that blood?
- Yeah, but how?
Pressure?
It could be.
Over here, too.
Yeah, that's Lund.
Look at that.
Oh, god.
This guy scratched his own eyes out.
You think?
This case...
it's gonna be a shitbowl.
No answers,
just bunch of angry people.
We don't even have
a forensic technician.
We should send this thing
back to Anchorage.
I thought that's what we were doing.
Yeah, we're keeping it.
- Fuck Anchorage.
- Really?
Hey!
Three feet! Three feet.
Need to tie it down.
Hey! No photos!
- Delete that right now!
- Sorry.
Come on, Liz.
They're just blowing off steam.
All right, shut up, Hank.
All right, everyone.
Everyone, stop fucking around!
All right, this is a crime scene.
I want you to pretend like you know
what you're doing.
Fuck's sake.
You should go home.
I can't.
Maybe leave this one
for someone else, Missy.
It's tied to Annie's case, Rose.
Then you're screwed.
Come and see me later.
No, don't use that.
You're gonna damage the tissue.
- What do I use?
- Yeah, just go back to the brush.
You get a little air pocket in there
and then you can just slide it
into the side.
All right.
- Just don't touch the skin.
- Oh, shit!
That's it. Wilson!
What the fuck?
It's not looking good, ma'am.
We'll have to amputate
at least one leg.
How soon can we talk to him?
Definitely not today.
He's in an induced coma.
- Chief?
- Thank you, nurse.
- Just hold on. Hold on.
- Chief? Over.
Prior? Did you fit him in?
No, they're kind of in a weird shape.
Unless you want us
to break them apart? Over.
No, don't break anything.
Ma'am? I have to go.
We're starting surgery.
- Chief?
- Okay.
Just... just hold on
one second, nurse.
Prior, go ahead.
I know how we can move 'em.
The heart?
No. That's...
That's not an emoji, Haydn.
Try again.
Merry Christmas, kids.
Class dismissed.
Hey, hey. No, no.
Guys, class is not dismissed.
I assure you, class is not dismissed.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna call your mom.
- I'll call your father...
- Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas.
- And yours, too. I promise.
- Merry Christmas!
- Yeah, call her.
- I promise I will.
Carla? You too? Really? Really?
Sorry.
You gotta be kidding me.
I told you to stay away.
I work here, and I meant it.
I work here.
Oh, come on, Bryce.
I'm not here for that.
I need you to explain to me
what Tsalal Station does.
Tsalal?
Why?
And why not just go out there
and talk to Lund
and the rest of them?
That's not gonna be possible.
Do you see him often?
Travis?
No.
Death didn't change him.
The fucker only comes
when he wants something.
Did he say goodbye?
Before he went into the ice? Yes.
He knew he was dying.
He didn't want the leukemia
to take him.
He brought me croissants.
Fucking croissants.
He had made them himself.
We ate them.
He sang a little.
We fucked a little.
He didn't say much.
He was so tired.
But then...
we talked so much
all those years he came to me.
Then he left.
And then I found him.
Yeah.
One last gift from Travis Cohle...
I got to meet you.
Can I ask...
you seeing the dead...
when did that start?
With Travis.
But I know people
who are born with it.
And then, of course, there's Ennis.
It happens around here all the time.
I think the world...
is getting old
and Ennis is where the fabric
of all things...
is coming apart at the seams.
And when you see them...
hear them...
how do you stay okay?
The thing about the dead
is that some of them come and visit
because they miss you.
Some come
because they need to tell you
something that you need to hear.
And some of them
just want to take you with them.
You need to know the difference.
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ.
What do you...
What do you think happened to them?
That's what we're trying
to figure out.
So, what were they up to at Tsalal?
I'm a geologist,
so not really my field
but they were madmen.
Very reclusive.
They didn't come into town,
and received no visitors.
Other Arctic Stations
rotate crews but not Tsalal.
They... No one comes in,
no one goes out.
And what were they doing?
They spent decades
trying to sequence the DNA
of an extinct microorganism
that potentially
could stop cellular decay.
All right, try it in English, nerd.
Well...
If you want English,
you should have...
Fucked?
Yeah, fucked the English teacher.
He wasn't my type.
Neither were you.
But, you know, desperate times.
So, what were you saying?
I'm saying the work they were doing
could end up curing cancer
autoimmune diseases,
genetic disorders.
Just an absolute
fucking game changer.
So, what was taking them so long?
I mean, they've been out there
like forever.
I mean,
it's not making hot dogs, Liz.
Ice-coring
for that type of microorganism
is extremely difficult.
It requires delicate robotics,
careful digging.
You know, drills break.
Deposits run dry.
The fact is...
the permafrost is too hard
and it damages chromosomal material
upon extraction.
So, it was never gonna work.
Like... like never.
Chief. I think you wanna
come by the station.
Over.
Copy.
My sister sees people following her.
She... she can't sleep.
She has these breakdowns.
She says my dead mother
is calling her.
I brought her to Ennis last year
to keep her close.
But...
I'm worried.
Don't confuse
the spirit world
with mental health issues.
Sounds to me
like she needs treatment.
Have you talked to the people
at The Lighthouse?
She doesn't wanna go
to The Lighthouse.
Doesn't even want to talk about it.
She went to a place in Nevada
like four years ago
and they medicated
the shit out of her.
She fucking hated it.
You sure don't want something to eat?
No. I've got a shift coming.
Hey...
Did you see that thing
on his forehead?
I've seen that before.
Years ago.
What is it?
It's old, Missy.
Older than Ennis.
It's older than the ice probably.
Yep. We got the cellphone records.
There's nothing there.
- Radios?
- Yeah.
- Radio logs, nothing there either.
- Chief, how are you today?
Hey, Lulu.
What's this?
Liz! How you holding up?
What a fucking mess.
But don't worry.
I'm moving it out to Anchorage.
You don't have to do a thing.
Oh, great.
That is Chief Danvers's specialty.
You know what?
The families need to be notified.
Hank, can you get
Chief Danvers the...
No.
No?
No, you're not taking
my case away from me
Captain Connelly Sir.
- What are you doing?
- My job.
All those men died
in Ennis jurisdiction.
- Unless you want to call State...
- Stop...
You don't want this case.
I know you.
What's that thing you say?
Shitbowl?
This is a shitbowl.
Well, it's my shitbowl.
You don't have any resources.
No forensic department, no fucking...
You're doing it just to fuck with me,
aren't you, Lizzie?
You sent me to Ennis.
Actually, no.
You... appointed me to Ennis.
You gave me this nice office
in this lovely ex-dental building
so that I could handle
the unique issues
that arise in an isolated community
during the sunless season.
- I'm here to serve.
- Cut it out.
Those bodies are going to Anchorage.
Hank, get the guys
to rig the chopper.
We're flying the bodies.
- Section nine, chapter four.
- Hello?
Proper handling of frozen remains.
What is that?
Don't worry.
That is the Alaska Forensic
Crime Detection Laboratory Manual
that you gave to me along
with the regulation bibliography
for my promotion, Captain Sir.
It says, "Frozen bodies
are not to be manipulated
beyond the absolutely imperative
until properly thawed at a constant
temperature of 38 degrees
or the forensic results will be
compromised and useless in court."
Right.
And how long do they take to thaw?
48 hours.
Where are you even gonna
put 'em, Chief Danvers?
Liz!
Hey.
Did you see me play?
No. Did you see the manager?
Hank?
Hank, did you find him?
Even better.
Hello.
Hi, good to see you.
Janet, how are you?
Hi, Henry.
Ma'am.
How's Pete?
He's good.
You need to get that son of yours
to do some private skating coaching
for my boys.
Good money in it,
you know, for a young dad.
I'll try and talk some sense
into him.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, god.
Kate.
Liz.
You wouldn't come talk to me
unless this was really serious,
would you?
Nope.
Hey, Mom!
Go get dressed.
Wait in the car, okay?
Is this about those poor scientists?
Yep.
So horrible.
Yeah.
They're frozen into a giant
block of flesh as we speak.
Christ.
We need some place to thaw the bodies
that's big enough, at the right temp.
And since the mine owns the rink
and the rink fits the bill...
Well, just so we're clear
I'm doing this
because I love this town.
Oh, yeah. Of course.
Careful when you lift it.
Lift it up. High as you can.
- Oh, a little higher here.
- Higher.
Up.
Don't damage the soft tissue.
Good.
Jesus.
God.
That fucking bitch!
Trooper Navarro.
Hey, Chief?
That's teeth marks.
I think they bit their own hands.
What the fuck?
Hey. Get out of here!
Well, I just wanted to tell you...
Now! Go!
Fine.
I'm gonna be
at your place, all right?
Okay.
All right.
Let's have a little dig
around the autopsy files in the area.
You know, look for similar injuries.
The burnt eyeballs, the busted ears
and the self-inflicted bite wounds.
Yeah?
That one's Molina.
Yeah. Jie is here.
And Merens.
This one? This one's...
Kotov?
No, that's Kotov.
See with the ring?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he's... he's Russian.
They wear it on the right hand.
How many do you count?
Five heads and nine feet.
The rest of them are buried.
Why are they climbing
on top of each other?
It's like there was
something chasing them.
Well, hate to break it to you, kid.
There's no Yetis.
Hypothermia can cause delirium.
They panic, they freeze,
and voila, corpsicle.
Hey, we still got that retired guy
up in the North Bay?
The forensic tech?
Get him down here. We...
Prior?
Yeah, I have an idea.
What ide...
Okay.
That mine bitch hates you
even more than she hates me.
I might've dated her husband.
Before or after the divorce?
What do you want?
This tattoo was on Annie's body.
- So?
- It was on the forehead
of one of your guys.
I don't know. Maybe.
- So what?
It's the same case.
We can work together
and figure out Annie.
No. I'm not working
with you again ever.
You think I want to work with you?
I do, actually. Yeah.
Take a look in the mirror, Liz.
No one can stand you
except for that poor kid Prior.
But you'll be breaking
his heart real soon.
Get out of my scene.
Go on.
Fuck off.
You know where to find me.
Prior?
Take a look at this. Go show it...
Hey, hey, what are you, what are...
Yeah.
Hey, baby girl.
Oh, hey. Want some lunch?
Nah. Bachelor later?
- Evangeline.
- Qavvik.
Hey, Ryan. You got a sec?
Sure.
So, no?
No.
I don't think I ever saw him.
You sure?
Yeah. I don't know.
If she was seeing him,
she never introduced him.
Hey. Can I talk to you?
Chuck, come on.
No. She's bringing up all that shit.
You understand I'm trying to find
who killed his sister, right?
You know this man?
No. Never seen him.
Fuck you! We ain't poisonin' nothin'!
Hey!
- You motherfucker!
- Hey! Bob!
Hey. Shit, man.
Hey, no, fuck you!
You think my kids don't drink
the same water?
You mining people
are poisoning your own kids
and we're sick and tired of you
pretending you don't see it!
We fucking feed your kids!
- Come on, man.
- Fucking moron!
- Chuck. Come on.
- We pay for that school!
Go, get out, man.
Fuck.
What? Hey!
Fuck you all, motherfuckers!
Fucker didn't even pay his tab!
- Did you get the lab report back?
- Yeah.
- The DNA on the clothes?
- Yeah, that's gonna be a while.
How 'bout the prints?
Here you go.
It was on one of the shoes
and we didn't come up
with any matches.
All right.
All right, so we know
that a sudden drop in pressure...
can rupture eardrums,
damage soft tissue.
We know that hypothermia
can cause delirium
and irrational behavior
and that could explain
the self-inflicted wounds.
They drop everything,
run out there in the first place.
Why?
- Gas leak?
- Nope.
No gas at the station.
It's all electric.
- Then what?
- Well, I don't know, kid.
Start asking questions.
'Kay.
Polar bear?
The doors don't lock, right?
- To avoid accidents.
- Okay.
It comes in, the men panic,
they run out.
And they undress. Why?
Paradoxical undressing.
People with severe hypothermia,
they feel hot, they undress.
You've been studying.
All right, keep asking.
'Kay, who drew the sign
on Lund's forehead?
Wrong question.
Okay.
When was it drawn?
Was it before they ran out,
or was it after?
Well, if it's before,
it could be a prank or a game.
If it was after?
Then someone was out there
on the ice with them.
No one stops to draw
on their own forehead
while they're freezing to death.
That's right.
Keep asking.
'Kay, what about the clothes?
I mean, they don't even match
the bodies.
There's only five pairs of pants.
Three shoes are missing.
Okay.
Maybe they weren't fully dressed
when they ran out.
What's the question?
Why weren't they fully dressed?
No. Ask again.
How scared do you have to be
to run out on the ice
without any shoes?
And?
And why are the clothes
folded like that?
So?
So maybe the killer folded them.
A killer.
Why would he fold them?
I don't know.
Was he taunting them? Did he...
Did he make 'em fold them?
It doesn't make any sense.
Oh, no, it does.
We're just not seeing it.
Not asking the right questions.
I told you this was a shit case.
Yeah, you did.
Then you went ahead
and made it your shit case.
I won't even ask why.
- Yeah.
- Ma'am?
The station supply guy
and the cleaning ladies
are ready for questioning. Over.
Thanks, Lulu.
You get the supply guy.
I'll get the cleaners.
- Mayonnaise, a lot, okay?
- Chief.
Guys, a lot of mayonnaise.
Like that, yes.
Do you want to see
the final product? Yes?
- Look at this, are you ready?
- Now that's... that's the 17th.
That's the day they died.
Hey, Clark, are you okay?
She's awake.
That's a good girl.
You stubborn lady, ain't ya?
Picking fights with those big boys,
you dummy.
Homebrew in here?
No.
And what homebrew?
Qavvik's is a respectable
food service establishment
with an FF1 license.
And that's why
you have drunken fights in it.
Drunken fight, singular
was because of the bad water
in the Villages.
Nothing to do with illegal spirits.
The water thing's getting bad, huh?
Yeah.
The whole thing
went to shit last week.
It turned black in some homes.
Poor fuckers
are too close to the mine.
Now there's talk of protesting.
Again?
How's my sister doing?
She's doing all right.
I mean, it's only one in town
that doesn't love my pancakes.
Hey...
Cut it out.
One of these days,
those dogs are gonna eat you.
Nah.
Me and this girl, we go way back.
Huh, gorgeous?
She thinks she's real tough,
you know?
You come close, she snaps at ya
but deep down, she's a softy.
Yes, she is.
She just needs
a little love and affection.
Then she's gonna melt.
For fuck sakes, Qavvik. Cut it out.
- Will I see you tonight?
- No. Busy.
Great. I still need my toothbrush!
So, you do the cleaning
at Tsalal Station, is that right?
Yep, two shifts a month.
Did you ever see Annie Kowtok there?
Annie K?
No, never saw her at the station.
But then, why would she, you know?
She was a midwife, right?
What about this?
What is that, a cult sign?
No. Witchcraft?
Hey, Blair.
You ever seen anything
like that devil sign?
No.
So, when you were
cleaning at the station
- you never saw this?
- No.
They were weirdos, all right?
I mean, you have to be a little off
if you wanna spend
your life out there
locked up in the ice,
you know what I mean?
Very quiet boys.
Played video games.
But they were all very obsessed
with their work.
Dr. Lund once screamed at me
for moving his notebooks.
Well, were they acting strange at all
the last time you saw them?
Did they say anything weird?
Say?
They never spoke to us.
We're just the cleaning ladies.
Clark was weird. He was always weird.
But last couple times
I went out there
he... he was talking to himself.
He was staring into nothing.
You know, I just,
I... I don't think the guy was right.
And once,
I saw him hanging out au naturel
skinny ass just hanging out.
He would be locked in his room.
We couldn't go clean in there.
He wouldn't come out.
I heard him crying.
What did the other men do
when he was acting off?
They just ignored him.
It was sad.
I thought I saw somebody
when I got to the station yesterday.
But it couldn't be, right?
Wait, you saw somebody
at the station?
No, I didn't see no one. Nope.
Bill, come on, this is serious.
If you saw somebody
- you got to tell me.
- This is Ennis, man.
Yeah, you see people sometimes.
Know what I mean?
Jesus, Pete, you grew up here,
you know this.
You see people
who are gone sometimes.
It's a long fucking night.
Even the dead get bored.
Hey, have you seen this before?
Yeah. Clark had that thing.
Had it?
He had it tattooed on his chest.
The guy you're looking for
is Chuck Mosley.
Block 16C, room 43,
Silver Sky Mining Barracks.
I texted you the location. Over.
Thanks, Lee. Owe you one. Over.
Oh, shit!
Hey, Jules! You hear that, sis?
It's our song, baby girl!
I wanna, I wanna, I wanna really
Really, really wanna zigazig...
Fuck.
I told you I don't know him.
You're lying.
Don't make me arrest you
for stiffing the bill at Qavvik's.
He bought my cousin's trailer.
A Golden Eagle from the fucking '90s.
But my cousin made
this idiot shell out ten grand.
Guy paid in cash, right there.
Boom.
And when was this?
I don't know.
Seven years ago?
Can't you ask your cousin?
Dead.
Bone cancer.
This fucking town.
Write the description of the trailer
and your cousin's name.
Why didn't you tell me when I asked?
'Cause I don't like you, ma'am.
No.
It's because you didn't
like Annie, isn't it?
You're okay
with what happened to her.
Don't worry, babe.
I've still got a little cash left.
I'll send you some more
for your mother's medication.
Can't wait to see you.
All right.
Wallis said he had
the spiral tattooed on his chest.
Why was Wallis looking at his chest?
Clark was walking around naked,
talking to himself.
Yeah.
He was not okay.
I don't get why the other guys
were putting up with him.
That's exactly the question.
All right, well,
did you get a hold of the family?
Yeah. I spoke to his mom in Dublin.
She hasn't seen him for 10 years.
Says he's dead to her.
Well, he is dead.
Jesus.
Okay.
What did we learn about the money?
So, who's paying Tsalal's bills?
'Kay, so the NGO
that funds the Station, right?
If you follow the taxes
you can trace it back
to a shell company
called NC Global Strategies
which in turn
belongs to Tuttle United.
Tuttle United, what do they do?
Oh, everything.
I mean, glass, tech, video games
shipments, palm oil, cruise lines.
Okay, thanks, Petey, 'cause that...
that was really not helpful.
I'm here to serve.
All right, okay.
Chief, can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
What did Navarro do to you?
You worried
you're gonna fuck up, too?
Well, don't fuck up.
Go watch the corpsicle.
I'm gonna go pick up Leah
at your place
- and I'm gonna go back to work.
- No, I... I gotta go home.
I can't. I... I promised
I'd put Darwin to bed.
Kayla will kill me. I...
You're not going home tonight.
What did I just say?
Don't fuck up.
What do you mean, no?
You said you were giving Darwin
a bath tonight.
Well, can't you...
No. He wants you doing it, not me.
Come on, help me out here.
I don't know
what you want me to tell you.
I promise I'll do it next time.
Yeah, that's what you said last time.
Well, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you want me
to tell you. He's waiting for you.
- Hey, hi, Darwin.
- Hey, your boss is here.
Making Legos?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry, babe.
- Whatever.
- Whatcha making?
- A house.
- A house for the fish?
So, you taking my man again tonight?
You don't know this, Kayla,
but I'm doing you a big favor.
Pretty soon, you're gonna get sick
of having the husband around.
Thanks, but you can save
your favors for your family.
She's in the kitchen with my grandma.
Come on, baby. Bath time. Let's go.
Leah, we gotta go. I gotta get...
Hi, Liz.
Leah wanted to see how kakiniit
looked like on her beautiful face.
Hey! Wash it off.
- No.
- It's just marker.
- It'll come right off.
- Go get in the car.
Go!
Ah-ha ah-ha nah-kooo nah-kuh-nookh.
You don't get to doodle
on my kid's face.
She's 17.
And she wants
to understand her heritage.
Ee-eh tabbur-lah.
What? So, she can be
a night nurse like you?
- Zrah nah-naahng kay-mehm...
- Yeah, don't... don't give me that
Laundromat Grandma.
You need to leave my house.
Now!
Ayh nohhh loopay-ah-tak
ah nahnaahng kay mehm.
Really?
I mean, since you're paying,
I'm getting my nutrients.
Nutrients.
Twenty for some damn cookies?
Arctic prices, babe.
Remind me again why we're here.
Good job benefits.
Hey, so I've been thinking.
That place, The Lighthouse?
Maybe we should go by
and talk to someone.
I'm not going back into a hospital.
Those pills...
- You don't get it.
- Hey... Listen. Listen.
Hey, look at me. It's not a hospital.
It's a community center
for addictions and other issues.
Okay? I think we should
go check it out.
I mean, there's other meds. And...
No.
Listen, I'm not Mom.
- Please, Angie.
- Okay. Okay.
You got to let me live
like a normal person.
Okay.
Of course, baby girl.
Lee! Help me put up
this stupid fucking Christmas tree!
You do it! I'm in bed!
Hey, get in here.
This place is crazy.
- Hey.
- You did it.
- No, they're just temporary.
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
Fuck.
I see you.
I'm the one eye.
I see you. I see you.
Fuck.
- Hey, Chief.
- Pete.
Did you get the scientists'
credit history?
Yeah.
All right. Send me Clark's.
As far back as you can go.
Okay. You want me to include the...
You don't go into my house to steal.
You know better.
Look at me.
Even your mother didn't steal from us
when she left.
Now, listen.
Danvers doesn't own you.
You have a family, and she's not it.
Blood is blood, Peter.
Remember that.
So, you fuck me with the bodies
then you come to actually fuck me.
You want to or not?
Yeah.
Knew you didn't stay in town
for the lovely weather.
- I can't!
- No, no, don't you dare.
Don't you dare. No, wait...
You're sweating on me.
Do you wanna say it first
or should I?
That's the last time we do this.
That's 15 years of last times.
Nineteen.
What? No.
Nineteen years ago,
I just got married, and...
Nineteen years.
You were with Jake?
Yeah, we were on a break.
One of them.
Fuck.
This is the last time we do this.
Yeah.
What are you doing
with the Tsalal thing, Liz?
Really.
I know you don't want the case.
I know you.
Oh, you do?
What am I thinking right now?
You're thinking,
"Know why I want the case?"
- Why?
- "'Cause fuck you. That's why."
I guess you do know me.
- You sent me to Ennis so that...
- No, I gave you a promotion.
For whatever reason.
I... I mean, mostly because
you're an insecure asshole
and because you're scared of me,
but whatever.
I'm just doing my job.
You're not "doing your job."
You're messing with me.
Why are you so hellbent
on keeping a lid on it?
Well, I just don't want it
to turn into a fucking disaster
for no reason.
Weird circumstances?
Dead bodies?
Come on.
Let's run it out of Anchorage.
No.
I'm gonna keep control of it.
- I've got control.
- Yeah. Well, I don't think you can.
- Well, I can.
- You can't.
- Says who?
- Me.
- And I swear, if you don't...
- What?
Are you fucking threatening me?
Fucker.
Yep. I'm looking at it right here.
It's a 600-dollar charge...
Fairbanks Ink Tattoo, April 22, 2017.
Clark, you said, yeah?
Yeah, Raymond Clark.
This tattoo was on his chest.
It's a spiral.
I can send it to you right now
if you want.
No need. I have it right here.
Yeah, I remember him.
Weird guy. English, right?
- He was Irish.
- He cried a little when I finished.
Not because it hurt, you know?
Just sentimental, maybe?
Was he alone?
He was alone, yeah.
Did he tell you what it meant,
the... the tattoo?
That I don't remember.
Wait, I can send you
a photo of the tattoo.
I keep them for my records.
And here's one showing
the model for the work.
Lady? Hello?
Guess I should start locking.
He took this photo
to a studio in Fairbanks.
He got the same tattoo as her.
That's four days after she died.
Here's the DNA results.
That was Annie's tongue at Tsalal.
Tissue has some unusual
cellular damage.
Possibly from freezing.
Did you change
where you put the cans?
Where do the cans go?
Well, it looks like
your case is my case.
What are you doing here?
Well, you know Annie better
than I can get from the files.
And now it matters
because it's a bunch of white men?
You want in or you just wanna
go fuck yourself?
Listen, The Wheeler thing was...
Shut up.
No. We did exactly
what we needed to do...
No, we're not doing that, all right?
We're just doing this one thing.
We're gonna crack it, close your case
I close my case, and then
that's it for the two of us.
It is.
Fuck!
Hi.
Jesus Christ, Leah. Fuck.
Oh, dude, you got the...
- Oh, yeah. They're temporary.
- Yeah?
- Temporary?
- Yeah.
Oh. They look cool.
So...
Liz make you stay and watch them
in case they wake up?
Don't.
Don't, you don't want that shit
in your head.
Seriously, Leah.
What happened to you?
Fuck, Prior.
He's an animal.
Yeah, well, he was raised by
an animal to be an animal, so...
It doesn't matter.
I mean, you come from the same shit
and you managed to be nice.
A fucking dork.
But nice.
- A dork? Really? A dork?
- Yeah, you're a dork.
- Yeah.
- Ah, you're a dork.
You know, my dad and Liz
used to dance to this all the time.
- What?
- Yeah.
Nah. No way.
Yeah.
My dad was, like, a stoner.
Like a wannabe artist.
And he was so chill.
And they used to love
to dance together.
I'm pretty sure
that Liz smoked weed, too.
Nah.
- Nah, Come on. Fuck.
- I'm so serious.
- Can you imagine?
- No.
I don't wanna.
You know, Hank was a musician.
What?
He played the guitar.
- No.
- In a band.
- Yeah.
Well, was he any good?
I don't know.
I've actually never heard him play.
Yeah, not once.
My mom said he wasn't
good enough to have a career
but she kinda felt he wasn't...
Good enough. Period.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
That sticks with you, doesn't it?
Not being good enough.
Fuck. Gee, you said
you weren't coming!
Hey, Qavvik.
You could've given me a heart attack!
Changed my mind.
Want to fuck?
Oh... you jerked off.
- Watching porn?
- I'm... No! I was just...
What kind of porn were you watching?
Can we just, like,
watch a movie and...
A porn movie?
Get out. I'm getting dressed.
And now she wants me on the case.
But I don't have anything.
That can't be true.
If you didn't have anything
she wouldn't want you,
so you have it all.
Yeah. I mean, I know everything
about Annie, every single detail.
Somehow, I had no idea
about the Clark thing.
I mean, they kept it a secret.
Well, why?
That's not the right question.
What?
That's what Danvers would say.
The right question is...
The right question is how.
That's why he got the trailer.
To keep it a secret.
Fuck.
Yes. Where do you keep
a trailer to fuck in secret?
- The Nook.
- Nook.
Talk to me, Raymond Clark.
Danvers.
You have to see this.
Jesus.
Are those bones?
Yeah. Animal.
Seal.
Caribou.
I think.
How'd you find this place?
My Spirit Animal showed me
in a dream, remember?
Hey.
Yeah.
That's her phone.
I checked.
It was not with her body.
Holy fuck.
- Danvers.
- Chief?
We have a problem.
Hey.
There's only six of them.
See?
Jie, Merens...
Molina, Kotov...
Mehta...
Emerson.
He's not here.
Clark's not here.
Maybe he got separated.
No. He didn't.
He's alive.
He's out there.