I found it.
My name is Annie Kowtok.
If anything happens to me, please...
Kowtok.
If anything happens...
All right, Petey, talk to me.
I'm at the ice rink, Chief.
And they're early, packing up
the bodies to Anchorage.
Of course, they are.
All right, I'll be there right away.
Well, Captain Connelly is here
to supervise, so...
What? He's there?
All right, I'll be there in five.
- Okay.
- Wait... fuck.
Chief?
Oh, shit. Hey, call Navarro,
and tell her that...
to meet me at the police station.
- Chief?
- Right away. Okay?
Okay. Well, what should I say
it's about?
- Hey.
- Chief?
Hey, hey, Julia.
- Chief, can you hear me?
- Julia.
It's Liz Danvers,
I... I've worked with your sister.
Okay, I'm just...
- I'm just gonna come towards you.
- You can see me...
- Okay?
- Oh, no.
Yeah, we need to...
we need to get you inside.
Okay, let me put that on you.
Fuck!
It's okay...
I know...
You know what?
I'm gonna put this on you.
There you go. There you go.
That's it, that's it.
I'm gonna keep you safe.
Just gonna get you safe, baby.
It's all right.
I got ya. I got ya.
Okay.
Yeah.
You ready?
Come on.
Hi. Hey.
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
Hey, can you wait for me downstairs?
It'll just be a minute, okay?
Thank you.
She gonna be okay?
Bodies off to Anchorage yet?
Yeah. You know, Prior's handling it
and, you know,
Connelly's supervising, so...
- The fuck is he here for?
- I... I got it, I got it.
He better not be trying
to take this case away from us.
Nobody's taking
the case away from us.
Just go be with your sister.
That video...
We need to talk about it.
Yeah.
Hey, Prior.
- So, how'd it go?
- Yeah.
Anyway, I... I think
I got something for you
with medical records
on folks with similar injuries
to the Tsalal men.
Yeah. Good... Okay, get it together.
- Talk to you later.
- Okay.
That kid's gonna be good.
It's a miracle of overcoming
shitty genetics.
What the fuck are you doing here?
- Oh, it's good to see you too.
- No, I'm serious.
Why are you here
for a routine body transport?
I'm gonna stick around for a while.
- Fucking knew it.
- Look at me.
I'm not here
to take the case away from you.
Why are you here?
You have protests around the mine.
You had a shooting that ended
in a fight in the hospital.
You got six dead bodies
in the local ice rink
and a still missing
person of interest.
You need to get
this shit under control.
I need to show up.
So you could look good
for your mayor campaign next year?
I'm fucking helping you here, Liz.
Besides, you like having me in town.
Fuck off.
Listen...
Look, just to get you up to speed.
Those men died before they froze.
How do you know that?
We haven't done forensics.
Oh, 'cause I did a independent
pre-forensic evaluation.
I don't want to know what that means.
Look, I'm treating
this like a murder case.
You saw the Annie Kowtok video
I sent you?
You keep that
on a need-to-know basis.
- All right?
- All right, copy.
It's good to see you.
What, you want to come in here
and take my office, too
or can you find
yourself someplace else?
Yeah, okay.
And, fuck you.
Yeah. Fuck you, too.
This is to fill out
your insurance information.
Thank you.
This isn't gonna be
like the other places
I promise, okay?
I'm right here in town.
I'll come visit you every day.
And you can keep your cell phone,
so you can call me.
I'm good.
I'll be here tomorrow for Christmas.
I'll bring presents and virgin eggnog
and, you know, 20-dollar cookies.
I can do this.
You knew.
That you were gonna stay here,
didn't you?
I'm so sorry.
- You're perfect, okay?
- I'm so sorry.
No, you're perfect, okay?
I love you so much, baby girl.
I love you, too.
Thank you.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Merry Christmas, Chief.
His name is Otis Heiss.
White male.
Admitted to St. Joseph's, April '98.
Burns on both corneas
ruptured eardrums,
self-inflicted bites.
You're... you are
not terrible, Prior.
He's a German national.
No records of employment,
no bank accounts
no credit card numbers.
Social security's been inactive
since November 2006
and no registered address
for the past eight years.
- So, no wife, no kids?
- Nope.
It's like no trace.
Like Oliver Tagaq.
Yes, but this guy has a long history
of disorderly conduct, all right?
So, breaking and entering,
petty theft.
He's been in and out
of rehab forever.
- Possession.
- Okay, move.
And if you look here
he was picked up by a trooper
in Noatak two months ago.
Zero sightings since.
- So, he's a junkie?
- After the accident.
What was the cause of the accident?
That's the thing. There is no cause.
It's not out there.
All right.
Let's get the units out there
looking for him.
Motels, hostels,
flop houses, dealers.
The men are out there
looking for Clark.
We don't... don't have anybody left.
What about your dad?
He is at the airport.
Picking up his fiancée.
Fine.
Well, get the men out there
looking for Clark and Otis.
Maybe they're in the same place.
Who knows?
Okay, but I... I mean,
I'm gonna have to put out an APB.
That's... that's updates, links.
- Go for it then. Do it.
- Gonna take...
Chief, it's Christmas Eve.
Well, get on it. Fast. Chop, chop.
I really hate you.
I hate you, too.
Yeah?
There's no ice caves in the area.
Fuckin' Hank.
Hey.
What do you mean,
there's no ice caves?
Annie's video.
There aren't any ice caves
near where her body was found.
You know what that means?
It means she was killed in one place
and then they dumped
her body in town.
Send a message.
You said it, not me.
What about those bones in the walls?
In the video. Fossils?
Yeah, maybe.
Where's Julia?
In The Lighthouse.
I'm hanging outside. I...
You should go home.
I don't want to go home.
It's Christmas Eve.
Fuck Christmas Eve.
Good. I got an idea.
How bad is it with Julia?
I don't know. She's...
Remember when you asked me
earlier if I pray?
Well, she prays a lot.
That's not a good thing?
Praying a lot?
I don't know.
When my mom died...
my dad told us to pray.
He said...
pray with our hearts
and she'd be fine.
And you prayed?
Oh, yeah. I prayed.
From the bottom of my...
sorry ass little seven-year-old
broken heart.
I prayed so hard, day and night.
My knees turned black.
Couldn't even walk at the funeral.
Maybe you didn't pray hard enough.
Fuck you.
Still no God though.
All right, you might wanna
step in front of me.
- Why?
- Well...
Just forget it.
Danvers.
Hi.
Can I help you with something?
Good evening, ma'am.
We're really sorry to bother you.
We just need to speak with
your husband for a few minutes.
Oh, you didn't.
Is there anyone in this town
you haven't fucked?
No, you can't be serious.
Wait, we just need five minutes.
- This is my home.
- Okay, three.
It's Christmas Eve.
This is a recording of a murder, sir.
My name is Annie Kowtok.
- We do need your help.
- If anything happens to me
please...
- Well?
- Yeah. Those are...
Those are definitely whale bones.
Monodontoides.
Probably prehistoric.
How do we find this cave?
There's no caves in the region.
Actually, there are.
There's a whole ice cave system up
bordering the Brooks Range.
But it's a death trap.
There were a bunch of accidents
up there years ago
and it was closed.
Where are they exactly?
I could pull the maps.
But it's gonna take some time.
Everyone's out for the holidays.
Even if you had the maps
you'd still need
an expert to guide you.
There's... there's fissures
everywhere.
One wrong step and the whole bottom
could drop out from under your feet.
So, what then?
We need to go there.
Please.
Other way to do this
would be to track down
whoever mapped the cave system.
You got a name?
One second.
Heiss.
Otis Heiss.
- Wait. Heiss, Otis Heiss?
- You know him?
Yep. I asked Prior
to check the medical files
for anybody that had similar injuries
to the Tsalal men.
Only got one ping...
- Otis Heiss.
- Fuck.
Adam?
You... guys... you guys need to go.
You're gonna get us
those maps, right?
Yeah, I'll get it to you.
Get 'em to you. Get you the maps.
Hey.
What are you still doing here?
We are just putting out an APB.
I'm communicating
with the men in the field
and nearly done.
That wife of yours
is gonna kick your ass.
Yeah.
Did Irina get in okay?
Alina? She wasn't on the plane.
Did she call?
No, I think there's some problem
with her cell service.
Something musta happened.
Her mother's been sick.
Maybe some emergency.
Something like that.
Yeah.
Listen, you didn't send her
any money, did you?
I was thinking,
seeing as I'm all freed up
maybe I can come over tonight
for Christmas Eve.
Yeah...
That sounds...
Yeah, that sounds really nice.
Obviously, just gotta finish up here
and talk to Kayla, but...
Take your time.
I got nowhere to be,
no hurry to get there.
Damn.
Merry Christmas, Missy.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I just stopped by
to say Merry...
Christmas.
Jesus, did you make all this?
'Course, I did.
All of Santa's elves drowned
in global warming, darling.
And the rest are all meth-heads.
This is amazing.
What were you, Rose, before?
You mean before I was old and crazy?
No. I mean, before Alaska.
Your name isn't Rose Aguineau, is it?
You never talk about it.
Well, I was a very serious professor
in a very serious school...
writing very serious ideas.
Why'd you leave?
One Tuesday morning, after coffee...
I sat down to polish
some pompous, useless article.
And I just had enough.
I had enough.
Every damn word I had written
in my entire life
was meaningless.
Making so much noise.
So much noise.
It is a little quieter here.
Mostly.
Except for all the fucking dead.
Liz, this is Kate McKittrick.
We need you to come
to the mine offices now.
We have a problem.
That is unacceptable.
Great.
You, talking about
what's unacceptable.
What do you plan to do about it?
Well, first, I'm gonna go home
'cause it's Christmas Eve.
And then I'm gonna call a couple guys
to come over here
and clean this up so that...
it's gone before
your employees get back.
I wanna press charges.
- No!
- No?
- Yeah, no.
- You don't get a say in this.
- If I wanna press charges, I will.
- Well, well...
You don't get to fuck up
my kid's life
just because you're pissed at me
and you feel like
maybe this will make us even.
Because, you know,
it won't do the trick, Kate.
Look, it's Christmas.
Please.
Yeah, I ought to strangle you.
Why do you always take their side?
Just get in the fucking car.
Hey. Just checking in.
How's the room?
It's okay.
Quiet.
Good, good.
Get some rest, okay?
I'll see you tomorrow morning?
Yeah.
I love you, Angie.
I love you too, baby girl.
Really?
Where are you gonna spend the night?
What? Priors'?
Why... why don't you just wait
until after dinner?
I'm making the turkey.
Come on.
I'm not gonna make you
pretend anymore. All right?
Fine, go.
Go to Priors'.
Go, get out.
My name is Annie Kowtok.
If anything happens to me, please...
Wha...
She's awake.
- Hello?
- Someone cut the power.
What are you talking about?
Molina. The... hot one?
The Tsalal guys, Molina.
Okay, I thought
it was a glitch in the video...
but the power goes out.
Are you drunk?
Well, it's... it's the same
in the Annie video.
You're gonna see it,
that part where the power goes out.
It's the same MO in both cases.
Why would there be power
in an ice cave?
I guess...
that is the right question.
Okay, where does that get us?
Someone put a generator there. Ol...
You got Oliver Tagaq
the fucking equipment engineer guy.
He's got access
to the emergency generator.
And he was defensive
and... and hostile
when we went to see him, right?
I can hear you thinking.
It's not crazy.
I'm gonna come pick you up in five.
Hell no. You're not going anywhere.
You're wasted.
I'm not... I barely drink.
Yeah, clearly.
All right.
You pick me up then.
I'm not going to a suspect
with my backup armed and shitfaced.
Well, you stay where you are
and I'm gonna get Prior
to come pick you up.
Liz, come on, give the kid a break.
It's Christmas Eve.
Prior's gonna come pick you up
in ten minutes.
All right, should we hit it?
Yeah.
Hey, you want me to bring this gal?
She's still got a little life in her.
Nah, we're good.
- Yeah.
Hey, Chief, I put out the APB.
We got everybody
looking out for Otis Heiss.
- Okay, I need you
- Is that Danvers?
- To go to Navarro's.
- Let me talk to her.
She's headed to the Nomad camps.
Suspects could be armed and dangerous
- and she needs backup.
- Jesus Christ, Liz.
Kid's got a family.
It's Christmas Eve,
for Christ's sake.
I wouldn't ask you
unless I really needed you.
Yeah, I know.
That's my boy.
Anyway, so they just disappear.
- Oh, my.
- So, all the... all that for...
nothing, really.
Make these, too.
- Push, and then...
- Like that?
- Like that.
- Yeah.
Sorry, freshman.
She was drunk, right?
Hammered.
She was so fucking drunk.
Jesus. Why are we even doing this?
She's onto something.
Mr. Tagaq?
Evangeline Navarro. Alaska Police.
Open please.
Mr. Tagaq?
This feels a lot like...
You need an order
to go into a man's house.
When did he leave?
The day after you came.
We were supposed to go seal hunting.
Do you have any idea what this is?
Fuck.
One sec.
Bye, guys.
What is that?
Hi.
Are you drunk?
So what?
You drive here?
Don't judge me.
Come here.
- Hi.
Have you been working on
your Hollywood smile?
Is this for your...
your campaign posters?
- Stop it.
- Or what?
Where are you gonna send me
that's further away than Ennis?
Or to the North Pole with Santa?
That's funny. When I sent you here,
I was trying to help you.
You were a fuckin' mess.
That's not why you sent me here.
You were scared
I was gonna take your job.
Okay. You want the truth?
You were a better cop than me.
From day one.
But you were terrible with people.
And after...
What?
Go on.
Say it.
Jake and Holden, it got worse.
Bullshit.
What, are you saying
I got... I got too emotional?
No. You just got fucking shittier.
Told people
they sucked at their jobs.
It's 'cause
Nobody wanted to work with you, Liz.
Nobody wants to work with you now!
You're still a fucking mess.
Take a look around.
It's Christmas Eve
and you're here, busting my balls.
Yeah. You're here, too,
busting mine, aren't you?
Liz. Liz!
Do not fucking drive.
Fuck off, Ted.
I ought to say, "No, no, no sir"
Mind if I move in closer?
At least I'm gonna say that I tried
What's the sense in hurting my pride?
I really can't stay
Baby, it's cold outside
- Hello?
- Evangeline Navarro?
This is Lieutenant James Ingram
of the Alaska Coast Guard.
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Go be with your family.
You sure?
Yeah, go.
I'm sorry.
You're not.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to let me sleep.
Why don't you just say it?
That I ruined your life
and you didn't want to have the baby.
Bitch!
- Why the fuck you let her leave?
- What?
Ma'am, you can't come in here
after hours.
My sister.
Julia Navarro.
We checked her in earlier today
and you just let her
walk out the fuckin' door.
If... you want, I...
Here, let me check in the system.
What are you checking?
She's not fucking here.
Are you... Are you listening?
I'm... sorry, ma'am.
You don't even know
she's fucking gone.
Are you kidding me?
On your computer,
does it say how the fuck
a mentally unstable patient
just fucking disappears?
Ma'am, this is...
this isn't a detention center.
It's a... it's a voluntary facility.
Well, it's a shit fucking facility.
You just let people fucking die!
What the fuck?
You're fucking kidding me?
Hey! We done nothin'!
- Just having a nightcap...
- Hey!
You motherfucker!
Hey, hey, fuck!
Fuck you!
Get up.
Evangeline?
Jesus fucking Christ!
What the fuck happened?
Nothing.
But you should see the other guys.
Shit. Slow...
Holy Christ.
You lost a fucking tooth?
Just stay still.
Just... just stay still.
All right. Let me see.
How's this?
What, let me see that hand.
Oh, what's going on here?
No, don't.
What is this?
I don't know what it is.
Fuck!
Oliver Tagaq left it for us.
- Wait...
- I'm just...
It's gonna sting.
Okay. Yeah.
Stay still.
Okay.
Why are you alone?
My brother went to Disneyland
with all the kids, so.
In life.
I'm... I'm not.
Yeah, you are alone.
I'm alone.
Danvers is alone.
Rose...
Hey. Hey!
Gee...
Baby, baby.
You're not.
You're not alone.
Okay?
Nah.
Yeah.
Forget it.
Fucking Christmas, right?
Since you're here...
I knew that you were gonna come.
And I've been thinking,
you know, you and me...
Oh, no.
- No... Qavvik, listen.
- I really think that we could do...
- Fuck!
- You're, it's good.
- It's done. It's done.
Fuck you, Qavvik!
Fuck you!
Fuck!
- Fuck...
- That's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Baby. It's good. It's good.
It's okay.
Peek-a-boo!
Baby
Twist and shout
- Twist and shout
- I see you!
I see you...
Oh, your face. What happened?
What happened to you?
Was it... Was it Tagaq?
Hey, is Prior okay?
He's good.
Hey, what the fuck,
with the boots in the house?
Oliver Tagaq is gone.
He was gone when we got there.
Think he knew we were coming?
He left this.
- Fuck.
- What?
It was a stone.
With the spiral on it.
You lost it?
Yes, I did, all right?
And I also had a rough night, okay?
All right. Here, sit down.
Did you sleep down here?
- Maybe.
- Where... Where's Leah?
Oh, fuck sake.
Tell my mommy...
What?
Is this his?
Holden's?
I don't know what
weird-ass shit you're thinking
but just stop it.
Dead people are dead.
Danvers...
No! There's no heaven,
there's no hell...
there's no ghosts fucking beyond.
There's nobody out there
just waiting for us, watching us.
Then why do you keep that around?
There. Happy?
Okay, there's nothing except us.
We're here, Navarro.
Okay? Alone.
The dead are gone.
Fucking gone.
My sister killed herself last night.
What?
Just walked out into the sea.
Just walked.
Just kept going until she fell
into the freezing ocean.
And drowned.
Oh, I'm so sorry. I'm...
Her body is coming today.
Her dead body.
They diagnosed her with
schizophrenia, bipolar disorder
borderline personality.
You wanna know
what was really wrong with her?
Oh, yeah, don't...
It takes us one by one.
And you know who's next?
Hey, listen to me.
You're an intelligent woman.
You don't have to believe that stuff.
I failed her, Liz.
You don't understand.
It's a curse.
My mother had it, too.
Something calls us, and we follow.
- Stop it.
- And it's calling me now.
- Stop it! Stop it!
- She's calling.
All right, you're doing the thing
that you did with Wheeler!
Okay, where... where...
You're... you're seeing something
you saw something in that room.
No, I didn't.
Yeah, you did.
I was there.
And you saw something in that room.
It was a ghost,
or some kind of spirit.
You saw something.
I saw nothing.
You're a liar.
- What, Prior?
- Hey, Chief.
We just got a call in.
Some fishermen spotted
something near the dredge.
Wait, I... I'm gonna send you
the photo.
We already checked the dredges.
Clark wasn't there.
He's probably been moving around.
A dredge is a good place to hide.
You ever seen them
when they were still working?
When you were little?
The dredges?
Yeah.
They were amazing.
Then the fucking things
just got abandoned.
Still out there rotting...
forgotten.
Aren't we all?
Clark!
Stop!
Evangeline...
Navarro?
Stop where you are! Ennis Police!
Fucker.
Raymond Clark?
Hands over your head.
Let me see your hands.
Slowly.
Otis?
Otis Heiss?
Leave me alone.
Who gave you that coat?
Was it Raymond Clark?
Otis? Did he give you that coat?
Otis.
Talk to me.
Where is Raymond Clark?
He's gone!
He went back down to hide.
Where is he hiding?
Navarro?
Navarro.
Where you been?
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Otis! Where is he hiding?
He's hiding in the Night Country.
We're all in the Night Country now.