Here she is, hon.
Thanks for letting me stay close.
Absolutely.
Just please don't tell anyone.
Sign here.
Be careful. It's hot.
The doctor says we have to
limit contact to ten minutes.
He's still in withdrawal,
so go easy on him. Okay?
All right.
Did you know Clark from before?
Otis?
Did you know him?
No.
I knew about Tsalal
but I didn't know the men there.
What did he want with you?
He was asking
how I survived my injuries.
And how did you?
Fuck, man, does it really
look to you like I did?
All right.
Where's Clark now?
I don't know.
But you said...
You said that he was...
he was going back
to the Night Country.
- I did?
- Yeah. At the dredge.
- What'd that mean?
- I don't know.
He was crazy as shit, man.
All right. What else did he say?
"She's awake."
She's awake.
He said that a bunch of times.
He said, "I have to hide.
She's out there."
Creepy motherfucker.
All right.
Let's talk about back then.
What happened
on the day of your injuries?
Shit was 30 years ago.
What does it matter?
It matters.
Tell me.
There was a cave in.
Men died trapped in the ice.
We ran out for help
but there was a blizzard.
I heard...
Otis?
Something...
Screaming. Howling.
The other men started
following the sound.
I tried to go after them, and then...
Nothing.
Nothing? What does that mean?
I woke up in the hospital.
My eyes were burned.
My ears, all gone to shit.
All right.
So...
this the cave system
you were mapping?
Can you point to
where the entrance is?
It's right at the end of Bear Creek.
Here. But you can't go on your own.
The caves collapse.
That ice,
it's like crawling on thin glass.
Yeah. Well, you're gonna
take us there.
I can't like this.
You're gonna be better in a few days.
That's not what I'm saying.
You can help me get well.
I can't get you heroin.
You know that.
Your time's up.
I found the entrance.
You sure you're up for this?
Yeah.
You want to talk about it?
No.
All right.
What's this?
That's your bag.
Please don't come back tonight.
- No. Hold, Kayla, you can't...
- Please, just go.
No... Kayla.
You can't just kick me out, Kayla.
This is my fucking family, too!
So, this cave is
on Silver Sky property?
Yeah, they own the entire region.
How's Leah?
She's got a girlfriend.
So? I've had a bunch of those.
Yeah, I guess.
Girlfriend thing is okay.
It's just...
Lee's turned into one of these...
crazy radicals.
Splashing the black paint
all over the place.
They're not crazy.
It's the fucking water.
- It's poisoning them.
- I know, all right? I know.
Is this it?
Probably. It looks like
somebody blew the entryway shut.
Because, of course, they fucking did.
- Fuck!
- Hey!
Fuck this shit!
There is no love
None lost, none found
There is no God
No hallowed ground
You are forever bound...
To lose
So what's...
The use
We were here before!
Gonna stay when you're gone!
We were here before! Gonna stay...
We were here before!
Gonna stay when you're gone!
- Land back! Water back!
We were here before!
Gonna stay when you're gone!
Stand back!
Land back! Water back!
Stand back! Get back!
Don't touch me!
- Get off of me!
- Get off me!
Hello?
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey.
Hey.
What... what are you doing?
Oh, I'm just doing some work
on my truck.
What's... what's going on?
Kayla...
she thinks we need
a little time apart.
And...
I was wondering
if it's not too much trouble
could I... could I crash with you?
Yeah.
It ain't exactly the Radisson,
but come on over.
Okay. Great.
Probably like five minutes away.
Okay.
- Land back! Water back!
Hey! Move! Let him go!
Let him go, now. Move back.
Get down. Move.
Hey. No. Break it up.
- Land back! Water back!
Get over here, you fucking bitch!
Get off of me, you fucking pig!
Sheri!
Stay back!
Hey! She's a fucking kid!
You okay?
Fuck the police!
What the fuck, Navarro?
Come on, Ted.
It was a protest.
What do you want from me?
Kate's fucking furious
and wants answers.
Well, why me?
It's not even our jurisdiction.
It's the troopers' job.
She wants you there.
You're the Chief of Police,
for Christ's sakes.
Fine, I'll go to her office.
- I'll see you there.
- Wait.
You're gonna be there?
What the fuck is going on, Ted?
Just fucking be there.
Fine.
- Navarro.
- I got some shit news for you.
Really?
'Cause I fucking will.
All right.
What'd she say?
How's your head?
Fine. Stopped bleeding.
That's a shame.
Put on your seatbelt.
What the fuck were you doing there?
I mean, whose side are you on?
Liz, I get it. But you know the shit
that's happening in this town.
What were you thinking?
Jesus Christ, I'm actually
feeling for Danvers right now.
Just take me home.
You're not going home.
What are you talking about?
She wants me to take you in.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Fucking pigs. All of you.
- Hey.
- Hey. I was looking for you.
Did you know that Leah
was going to that protest?
- No... Is she okay?
- 'Cause if you're covering for her
- I swear to God...
- No, no.
I'm not... in the house.
Kayla kicked me out.
Wow, that's...
That's... that's hard.
Do you need a place to stay, or..
No. No, moving in with you
would basically fast track me
to a divorce, so...
It's not all bad, though.
Here. Take a look at this.
What's this?
That is the thing
you've been looking for.
Liz.
- Don't look. No.
- What's going on?
- Coop!
- Yeah?
- Book me, will you?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Seriously?
- Hey. What am I looking at?
The LLC that paid the grants
that fund the station.
- Yeah.
- I followed their tax returns
and they trace back to Tuttle United.
You remember them?
Yeah, the palm oil,
video games, cruise lines.
Yeah. And four deals in Canada
and two in China
with Norbank Securities
which is a founding partner of...
Silver Sky Mining.
This is evidence.
That means...
the mine bankrolls Tsalal
and then Tsalal pushes out
bogus pollution numbers for them.
It's definitely possible.
Hey, sorry about the divorce.
- It's not a divorce, Chief.
- Whatever.
You know I hate Pepsi, Prior.
Yeah, well, the machine
was out of Mountain Dew, so...
Fine.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thanks.
What about Sheri?
- She okay?
- Fuck Sheri.
Fuck Sheri? Why?
Heard you got kicked out.
You knew?
She couldn't stop crying, Prior.
You're an asshole.
You know, she told me about
when she first fell in love with you.
She saw you play.
Senior year? Finals?
No. This game you lost.
You fell on your ass
- and then...
- Huey Larson scored.
She said that
everyone gave you so much shit
and you just had this stupid,
idiot smile on your face.
And then she found out that
Huey's dad had had a stroke.
You fell on purpose, didn't you?
No.
She just misses that guy, Prior.
Don't let Liz ruin that guy, okay?
She's not good
with people she cares about.
You're not really keeping her
in there, are you?
She needs to get
how vulnerable she's making herself.
I mean, come on, Liz.
She's just young.
She's trying to do the right thing.
No, she's not.
She's just doing it to piss me off.
You know what? Don't come
telling me how to handle my shit.
You know how many
phone calls I had to field
about you kicking the shit
out of another trooper today?
That asshole hit Leah.
Yeah. He's fucking suspended.
You okay?
Not okay.
Where are you going?
Going to meet Kate McKittrick
and Connelly about the protests.
What? Why?
That's the troopers' job.
Exactly.
You know what?
I'm kind of glad that
I'm going over there
'cause I have something
I want to discuss with her.
Look at that.
You're gonna like it.
Hi.
- Can I take you to the...
- I'm good, thanks.
Liz. Thanks for coming.
Yeah, so first of all
we all know that...
the mess at the protest,
that's on troopers.
Running a shitty outfit.
Not on APF. It's not on me.
- So, as long as we're here...
- As long as we're here...
Shall we?
So, this came from
our security cameras up north.
It's 9.15 this morning,
during the lead up to the riot.
Why are you and Trooper Navarro
in a remote section
of Silver Sky land?
It's just a question, Liz.
It's police business.
It has to do
with the Tsalal investigation.
On Silver Sky property.
What led you to that location?
Well...
we got some intel about the area.
There's an abandoned cave
and we located an engineer
who had some information
about Raymond Clark.
The missing scientist.
Who's the engineer?
Otis Heiss.
Well, the good news for you
and Mr. Heiss is that
it turns out,
this isn't a murder case after all.
All right, what do you mean?
What does she mean?
Forensics came back.
It was a weather event.
Slab avalanche.
They're sudden and can move
at a hundred miles an hour.
An avalanche? Come on.
It was the last sunset
before the long night.
Theory is they went outside
to watch it.
What about the ears
and the eyes and...
Ruptured eardrums
and damaged soft tissue
are common during a flash freeze.
- Yeah, okay...
- And... And...
fatal hypothermia
causes hallucinations.
You're... you're saying
the official word from Anchorage
is they froze to death?
Well...
I know it's a relief for all of us
that there's not some killer
out there on the loose.
Well, that's convenient, isn't it?
'Cause the mine bankrolls Tsalal.
Well, of course.
I mean, we donate to a lot of
worthy research projects
and Tsalal is in our own backyard.
You know what?
Their work was an incredible...
Yeah, incredible work.
But the funding
is for an independent outfit that
verifies your pollution numbers.
You don't think
that's a conflict of interest?
Well, I'll have to look into it,
but I...
I don't see what possible relation
it could have with a weather event.
Oh, fuck you
and your fucking weather event.
You know what? I'm gonna have to...
I'm gonna leave you two alone.
Yeah, I'm... I'm sorry
Bill's such a terrible lay.
You have my sympathies.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
The Annie K case, remember?
Look, that location, the cave
that's where she was killed.
The two cases are linked.
We're almost there.
Three years ago,
you and your partner
Evangeline Navarro
responded to a domestic violence call
in Linden Village.
William Wheeler, 43, white male.
It was a murder-suicide.
Except there was no suicide,
was there?
- I don't know what you're talking...
- Stop.
This case is closed, Liz.
What happened to you?
A woman was murdered.
Go home to your daughter.
- Hey, Henry.
- Hey.
How's Peter?
Well...
Kids shouldn't be getting married
that young, you know?
Danvers is not gonna let this go.
She's looking for the location
of the Kowtok murder.
She can't find that cave.
I don't know
what I can do about that.
The engineer, Otis Heiss.
He could take her there.
You should take this to Connelly.
Connelly is a political animal.
He's weak.
And he's fucking her.
Okay, well, I did something for you.
- You broke your promise.
- Yeah. We paid you well.
That money's gone.
You promised me chief of police.
Look, I couldn't have known
Danvers was gonna be exiled here.
The bureaucracy was a mess.
I had no control.
This time it's different.
I'm not a killer.
I didn't say those words.
Do you understand me?
- I need to hear you say it.
- You didn't ask me to kill anyone.
Otis Heiss is a drug addict.
Drug addicts get lost.
I don't need to know the details.
I don't know where to find him.
So, you follow Danvers.
She'll lead you to him.
You do this and the job is yours.
I'm counting on you, Henry.
You okay?
Yeah.
Your grandma okay?
Yeah. I'm just covering for her.
She went to the dentist in Fairbanks.
What about you? Are you okay?
Kenny, she's here.
I found her. Come here.
Evangeline.
Kenny, tell her what you told me.
- Tell me what?
- Well, my grandpa
he told me to walk away
when I saw those.
People would leave them
as a warning for hunters.
What kind of warning?
Places where the ice
would swallow them whole.
Underground ice caves?
Yeah.
Truth is, sometimes we kids
would crack the ice on purpose
to go down into the caves.
My grandma, she was so pissed
when she found out.
Said the Night Country
was gonna take us.
I know how to get us in the caves.
It's so obvious. We just have to find
the highest point on the cave maps.
That's how you get into
an underground cave system.
- Navarro...
- You find the place
closest to the surface,
and you crack in.
Otis can point it out for us,
and we can just...
- Listen... to me.
- You listen.
This is big, Liz.
This connects everything.
People call those caves
the Night Country
- and then every...
- No. It's over.
What are you talking about?
Forensics came back
on the Tsalal men.
It was a freak weather event.
What?
- Are you kidding?
- Look.
It doesn't matter what you believe.
Connelly's shutting us down.
Fine.
Fuck Tsalal.
- Annie's a whole separate case.
- He knows about Wheeler.
What did he say?
He knows.
All of it.
I don't even know how.
You know what? I don't even care.
If I can find where Annie died...
What do you think you're gonna find?
A signed confession on the wall?
A murder weapon, DNA
- anything that's gonna
- Even if you found something
- help us find...
- he's gonna block it.
No, you gotta stop now!
Stop?
What are you even saying?
It ends here, all right? It's over.
No.
I'm gonna go talk to Otis.
- He can point it out on the map
- No.
- And he can find it for us.
- You're not gonna go to Otis
because The Lighthouse isn't gonna
let you in after what you did.
You just gotta...
please, you just... it's over.
Just let it go.
Just let her go.
It's time.
No.
You carry her now.
Like I did, all this time.
You carry Annie.
Every day.
You're leaving her. Alone.
In that cave.
In the dark.
You.
She's yours now.
Is Liz letting me go?
Fuck Liz.
- Hey.
What the hell was that all about?
It's just family stuff, you know?
You...
You need anything?
Me? No. I'm...
I...
I was thinking about that time
when you were nine
when you were skating
and you fell through the ice.
You know, I...
I don't really remember
a lot of that. So...
You don't? Oh, I do.
I wake up dreaming of it sometimes.
One second you were there,
I turned around
and boom, you were gone.
Under the ice. Current took you.
I had to run on ahead of you
and try to break through
with an ice axe.
I kept hacking until I got through,
and then I pulled you out.
Then on the way to the hospital
I knew I had to keep you awake.
Just keep you awake.
Felt like we were
driving for days. Just...
I was...
Family stuff, right?
Fuckin' family.
There!
I think that... that should do it.
Thanks, Rose.
Do you want me to stay with you?
Well, the weather is shit,
so don't be long.
They're saying we're getting
a category four.
Here you go, baby girl.
I thought if you wanted
to be in the ocean...
Evangeline...
Listen...
Lie down!
Towards me.
Lie down.
Slowly.
Towards me.
Take that.
You're all right.
You're okay.
What the fuck were you doing
walking into the sea like that?
I called you back.
Didn't you hear me?
Peter's not here.
I'm looking for Leah.
She doesn't wanna talk to you.
Please.
Lee?
What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
Just to mess with me?
Not everything's about you, Liz.
What the fuck?
- Is that bruises?
- Don't worry about it.
You could've been killed.
Don't be dramatic.
It's not like you.
I'm working on this case.
Annie K?
Everything she fought for
is still happening.
Do you know how many
stillbirths there were
in the villages
in the past three months?
- I know about Aviaq Carter's...
- Nine.
That's nine moms, Liz.
Leah...
will you please just come home
for New Year's?
Come on. Please.
Liz?
You know, I haven't given up on you.
It'll be another three months
before we can dig any graves.
So, they're stuck here.
At least they keep
each other company.
Especially the little ones.
You want me to stay?
No, I'm fine. Thanks.
Hey, Chief.
Did you talk to Connelly?
In my office.
Bring that thing, now.
Close the door.
Who'd you talk to about Wheeler?
No one.
Well, Connelly knows,
'cause your father knows.
What's the password to your computer?
- Is it your birthday?
- No.
Oh, let me guess. It's Darwin's.
How many times I gotta tell you?
Your father only seems
like an idiot. Sit.
Sit!
What do you think you know
about Wheeler?
Fine.
You want to do it differently?
You make up the questions.
You just had to know, right?
You had to keep digging.
That's what Hank found in there.
I bet he was asking you.
What do they know about the mine?
And then bingo,
his kid gives him a little present.
- I wasn't digging for anything...
- Yeah, go.
- Ask me questions. Question me.
- I don't wanna do that, Chief.
- Ask me questions.
- No. I don't want to.
You wanted to know.
Ask me the fucking questions.
Ask the questions, Prior!
All right, fine.
How many times did you and Navarro
visit the Wheeler household?
I'm not sure.
- Three.
- Ten.
Ten times you were there.
And what was the situation
- on those visits to the Wheeler?
- Wrong question. Ask again.
Ask again.
- Did Wheeler ever show any signs...
- Wrong question.
Did you think Wheeler was capable...
Wrong question. Ask again.
Did you know
Wheeler was left-handed?
No.
I did not.
What direction are the blows in?
Right to left. All of 'em.
This is her senior yearbook photo.
You see the birthmark, right?
Someone flipped
every single photo in her file.
That bullet wound...
on his right-hand side.
Everything else, the ballistics,
forensics report
it's all gone in the flood.
Ask the real question, Prior.
Go on.
Did you and Navarro
shoot William Wheeler
and make it look like a suicide?
You see?
Smart as you are...
you need to learn
when to stop asking questions.
You can't stay at Hank's.
This is to the shack
in the backyard of my house.
I don't have to see you.
You don't have to see me.
Just don't be stupid. Stupider.
Take the key.
- Pete?
- Get the fuck away from me.
Hey.
Do not fucking touch me.
Thank you.
Fuck! No! No!
Come on. You're coming with me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I got you what you wanted.
All right, we're gonna
get you feeling better
and you're gonna guide us
through those caves.
Come on.
Show me.
Give it over.
I'm not letting you get high
in my truck, in public.
Then fuck you and fuck your cave.
Hey, you walk out that door
and I'm sending your ass
right back to jail.
What's it gonna be?
All right.
- Hello?
- Hey. Meet me at my place.
We're going to where Annie died.
I thought you said
the case was closed.
I was wrong.
You're not gonna stop me?
Just come back. Okay?
Come back.
The bathroom's over there.
Show me.
Here. Off Niksik Pass.
That's the highest point.
Take it easy.
And don't leave a mess.
Navarro?
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
Connelly wants me
to bring in the engineer.
What are you talking about?
The junkie. Otis Heiss.
I'm supposed to take him in.
- What for?
- Something about
an outstanding warrant. He skipped
bail in Noatak or some shit.
Why didn't Connelly
just ask me himself?
I don't know.
Maybe it's below your pay grade.
Come on.
You think I wanna be here
on New Year's Eve
collecting some junkie?
How'd you know Otis Heiss was here?
Oh, he's here?
In the house? I was just wanting you
to point me in a direction.
Yeah. I'm calling Connelly.
Just give him to me.
Jesus Christ, Liz. Does everything
have to be a fucking battle with you?
What the fuck's going on?
- You're coming with me.
- No... you're not.
Listen, look, I don't know
what's going on, Hank.
But you can still walk out
that front door
and everything can still be okay.
Fuck this. I'm outta here.
- Do not fucking move.
- No.
Do... Put the gun down. Hank.
No, I'm taking him.
I'm gonna do this
the way you did Wheeler.
Look, I don't know
what they have on you
but whatever it is, we can fix it.
- Okay? We can fix this.
- You turned my kid against me.
We can't fix that, can we?
Your son loves you. He loves you.
He doesn't wanna see you
do anything fucked up, okay?
Hey!
Back up.
- Back up, Liz.
- Okay.
Stay there.
Jesus Christ.
What's going on?
Lower your weapon, Pete.
Prior, don't. Think about it.
Think.
- Dad?
- I gotta get him out of here.
Prior. Think.
Think.
Come on.
Let's get him in my truck.
Prior. Don't. Think about it.
Come on. I need your help, son.
Prior.
Help me.
You should know something.
I didn't kill Annie K.
I just moved her body.
Blood is blood, Peter.
Remember that.
No!
It's okay.
I'm gonna call Connelly.
- No... You're not calling anyone.
- Yeah, I'm gonna call him right now.
Listen!
If you bring Connelly into this
that kid's going down.
Connelly is in on this.
He will bury every single one of us.
No. This...
- This didn't happen.
- What?
Hank was never here.
He snatched Otis and he shot him
but when he tried
to get rid of the body
he had an accident.
His truck'll be there
but he'll never be found.
- We can't fix this. This is too big.
- Listen, Liz.
- We can't fix it.
- Hank was sent here
to stop us from finding
where Annie died.
We are this close.
The storm will help cover our tracks.
That's why we have to go right now.
She's right.
We gotta clean this up.
No. I'll clean.
No.
- No...
- No.
- No, Pete.
- You gotta go.
You can't do that.
She can't go into those caves alone.
I can't leave you alone.
She can't make it
in those caves alone. You know that.
- That's your dad.
- Listen.
You clean. You clean good.
You know what to do.
Then get the bodies
to Rose Aguineau. Okay?
Tell her I said take you to Julia.
Say it.
Take me to Julia.
Please. Just go.
Move it, Liz.
This is mine.