APF, open up, please.
APF, open up, now!
Please help!
Anne Masu Kowtok?
- Yeah?
- You're under arrest for trespassing
and the destruction
of private property
at the Silver Sky
Mining facilities.
Turn around
and hands behind your head.
- I'm gonna need a minute.
- Ma'am.
Ma'am, I said turn around
and hands behind your head.
She's 10 centimeters
dilated.
Contractions
every two minutes.
Shoot me, but I'm getting
that baby out of her.
Is this a clinic?
It's a birthing center.
The last one in the region.
Do you wanna arrest me
for that too?
Grace, Grace.
Okay?
What's that bitch
doing here?
She's helping.
Bring hot water.
Grace, Grace.
Breathe, breathe.
Okay? Breathe, breathe.
Take some deep breaths.
Deep breaths, okay?
- Put the water in.
- You're doing good. You're doing great.
Deep breath,
deep breath.
Grace, Grace.
On the next big one,
you push, okay?
Give it a really good push, okay?
- Okay, give me a good push.
- Push.
Push!
It's here, it's here.
Okay, okay.
It's a little baby girl, Grace!
My baby.
I wanna hold my baby.
- I wanna see her.
- Takes a few minutes sometimes, Grace.
Give me that.
Why isn't she,
why isn't she crying?
- She'll be fine.
- It's okay. It's okay.
But she's not crying!
- Annie, why isn't she crying?
- She's coming. She's coming.
- Annie!
- We have to do CPR.
Annie, I wanna hold her!
- Okay, come on.
- One, two, three.
What's happening?
What's happening?!
Please! Please!
You take her
from here, okay?
Now we can go.
Here we go.
Hey, hey.
- Hey, Paulie!
- Ha, ha!
Alright. Lookin' good here.
Yeah, yeah, Scotty.
Gotta lock and load.
Lock and load, buddy.
What's up, Paulie?
Bringin' out the big guns, huh?
What the fuck
are you doing?
This is a task op.
Your boys here are a liability.
I'll take all
the help I can get.
Okay, everybody,
gather around.
Alright, listen up.
Suspect is Raymond Clark,
5'11, brown hair, brown eyes.
Last seen wearing
a pink parka.
Consider him armed
and dangerous.
He's got at least a 48-hour head start on us,
so we gotta move.
We're gonna break
into search groups.
Agents Cooper and Lee
are in charge of sweeping the tundra.
They'll proceed
north together,
then fan out
at three-mile intervals.
Trooper Davis is gonna inspect
the mining dredges.
Checkpoints go up
at 15 miles.
Radio chain maintained
at all times.
Now let's go
get this fucker.
Hey, we want
him alive.
Do we?
Hank, this is Danvers, over.
Hank, answer
the fuckin' radio.
Your father's
recruiting civilians.
- Hey, Lulu?
- Yeah?
Will you get
a trooper on the phone
and have him get Hank
on his fuckin' radio?
- Okay!
- Alright, where's my forensic technician?
He's booked
on the evening charter.
And Lund is
still in a coma.
They had to amputate
both his legs.
Still might lose
his left forearm.
Oof. I still need
to talk to him.
Yes, ma'am.
And good luck with that.
When's Clark's stuff
comin' from the trailer?
What's Clark's shit doin'
in the evidence room?
Well,
it's evidence.
Yeah, well, move it
someplace sanitary.
The place is
disgusting. Stinks.
Alright, I'm gonna
need a tetanus shot
just to look
at this shit.
- How many boxes we got?
- Nineteen.
Nineteen.
Alright, well...
call Navarro.
Hit up her Trooper command
and tell him
I'm requesting
a transfer for her.
Okay? Just temporarily.
Uh, I thought you
hated Navarro.
I do.
I hate everyone.
Hate you,
especially now.
Here.
Annie K's cell.
- Crack that, will ya?
- Crack it?
- Yeah.
- I'm not a hacker.
Well, you're under 30.
You got friends.
Why don't you just
figure it out?
Figure it out, yeah.
What?
Ask the question.
What happened the last case
you worked with Navarro?
The Wheeler case...
'cause that was it
for you guys, right?
Alright.
Only one bedtime story.
It was a murder-suicide.
William Wheeler.
He was a bad,
bad motherfucker.
Sexual assault...
armed robbery,
assault and battery.
He was in and out a bunch.
The last time he came out,
he took up with
an 18-year-old girl.
He beat her, hard.
Sent her to the hospital...
twice.
Broken arm...
smashed jaw...
some other things.
We went to his place
a buncha times
but she wouldn't report him.
His story was
always the same.
"Ah, she was drunk, Officer."
"Fell down the stairs, Officer."
We knew how that
was gonna end...
but there was
nothin' we could do.
Then we got the call.
We were too late.
He killed her
and he shot himself.
They were both dead
when we got there.
Navarro couldn't
get over it.
Uh, she was
convinced that there was
somethin' we should've done.
She blamed me, of course.
And it got nasty.
Transferred over
to Troopers, and...
end of story.
Gotta keep icin'
that thing, huh?
It's funny.
League hockey champion
fallin' on his face
in the ice rink.
Alright, go on.
Go get her.
Go get Navarro.
Go tell your dad
to get rid of his hillbilly friends,
or I'm gonna call immigration
on his Russian mail-order bride!
No, nothing!
What about over there?
Nothin', man!
Help us.
Navarro. Calling Navarro.
Are you there, Navarro?
Navarro here.
Let's do this.
What are we
missin' here?
Oh... this.
Spring 2016.
They must've started
their relationship before then.
Yeah, how do
you know that?
See that?
Ariana Grande.
That came out
in May 2016.
And Leah played it all the time.
Her birthday.
Drove me nuts.
And, um, alright,
look at this.
Here her hair's
changing color.
Here she's got the blue tint,
and, uh,
and now it's
fading, see?
- That's a long time.
- Hm.
I mean...
she looks happy.
They look happy.
This...
hot, fun girl
and this total weirdo.
Yeah.
No one sees
'em together.
A secret affair.
Ask the question.
Fuck your games.
Come on,
ask the question.
Why keep it a secret?
Are you still fuckin' that dog runner
bootlegging guy, Qavvik?
- Or are you back with girls?
- You still fucking C...
Anything that can't
run fast enough?
What, freshman?
Hey, yo, freshman,
you better learn how to run faster.
Hey.
Nobody here knows
about Ted, alright?
Come on, Liz...
everybody knows.
Well, you think nobody knew
about their relationship?
Nobody knew they were together?
- Nobody.
- Alright.
Look at this.
Everything else
is selfie or timed.
That's a candid photo.
Somebody was there
with them that day.
There has to be
more like this one.
Yep.
See that?
Ya think that's her hair dye?
It's not a print.
Yeah, we don't
need a print.
Hey, I'm gonna be another 20!
What was that color
you used on Annie's hair?
Ah, right here.
Electric Blue,
wasn't it?
You lied to me.
Yeah, I knew Ray.
And you just decided
not to tell me.
- Your friend was dead.
- Yeah... 32 stabs.
It's a pretty clear message.
Mommy?
Mac and cheese.
You got any mac and cheese?
- Uh, yeah. It's in the, uh...
- Yeah, I'll find it.
Hey, do you know what the name of
that unicorn is on your sweater?
That's Puddles.
That's what they called her
'cause she cried a lot.
All the mean unicorns
called her that
but she was just super hungry.
Come on.
- It's okay.
- We're gonna go make some mac and cheese.
- Does that sound good?
- Yeah.
I'ma tell you
all about Puddles.
All her story about how
she cooks mac and cheese.
- Here, sit down on this.
- Okay.
You need
to start talkin'.
I went to Tsalal to give
haircuts to the men there.
Annie came
with me one time.
Once.
I didn't wanna bring her.
Sh-She wouldn't take a no.
She was, like,
obsessed with coming.
So, fuck it,
I could use the company.
And what happened
that one time?
Annie and Ray
hit it off.
They talked all night.
She showed him her tattoo.
He was, like, fixated on it.
This one?
Yeah, that's it.
- Do you know what it means?
- She dreamt it.
We were in high school.
A buncha times.
She got the tattoo,
the dreams stopped.
Alright. Stir, stir, stir.
And then, all the unicorns
went skating on the lake
that Puddles had made
with her rainbow tears.
Ugh, I love skating.
I thought it was gonna be
a one-night thing.
Pretty soon, they were
hangin' out all the time.
And what about Clark?
Was he... violent?
Anything to make
you think he might
- do something?
- No. He was, he was quiet.
He was... I mean,
he was a little weird,
but... he was crazy about her.
But Annie changed when
they started goin' out.
Changed how?
She didn't want anybody to know
they were together.
And that was weird.
You could've
told me back then.
I would've
protected you.
I was terrified.
Plus, I was seeing
a guy from Tsalal.
Wait... who?
Oliver Tagaq.
Oh, there-there's,
there's no Oliver that works at Tsalal.
He was
the equipment engineer.
He left right
before Annie died.
Um... and, um...
do you know where we
could find this Oliver?
Last I heard,
somewhere out on the ice.
Probably hunting.
I don't think he's lookin' to be found.
After they found her,
I did call the police.
I just didn't wanna talk to you 'cause
you'da known me.
So, I didn't
leave my name.
But I told 'em about Clark.
Who'd you talk to?
Prior, where's your dad?
Over.
He's still out
in the search, Chief.
There's plenty of radio signal out there,
he's hidin' his ass.
I'll get him to call
the minute he gets back.
Yeah, okay, you do that, and, um,
see if you can find an Oliver Tagaq.
He was an engineer
six years ago at Tsalal.
- Got that?
- On it, over.
That son of a bitch
takes me off the case,
and then he
buries this lead?
- Question is, why is Hank fuckin' around...
- Don't "Ask the question" me!
Okay? I'll tell you
why he did it right now.
It's the fucking
mine behind it.
You know I'm right.
- I don't know shit.
- Well, then you're a shit detective.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Whatever you say.
Annie protests against the mine,
Annie gets murdered,
the police shush it all,
do the fucking math.
You do the fuckin' math.
Alright, without the mine,
there's no town.
50% of the population
works for it,
which means half the people
who live here
have got a reason
to silence Annie K.
And what about Clark,
creepy boyfriend?
What, you think
the mine's responsible for him too?
According to your
conspiracy theory,
Tsalal and Clark had
nothin' to do with it.
Is that it?
Not sure yet.
And what about
her tongue?
Now, what's-what's your explanation
for her tongue
poppin' up six years
after she dies?
And what about
the men on the ice?
Why'd they
go out there?
Oh.
Come on.
Don't give me that
voodoo, E.T., cosmic
- choompa-loompa bullshit.
- Are you tryna say "chupacabra"?
Whatever, the magic. It's no magic.
Alright, there's a, there's
a real explanation for this.
Alright.
- I'm listening.
- We're just not askin' the right questions.
We will.
We'll find it.
Who's the one that believes in miracles?
Fantasy Football?
No, Tinder.
- You're on Tinder?
- Yeah, I'm on Tinder.
Who the fuck is
on Tinder in Ennis?
Fuckin' Old Norman Naki
and, ugh, Hank Prior?
No, he's taken.
Poor bitch.
Yeah, I set my Tinder
radius for Fairbanks.
Ya know, I'll take
some personal trips.
I don't fuck where I eat.
You mean, anymore.
Fuck you.
What do you do
when you're lonely?
I watch Netflix.
Come on. For real.
What do you do?
I pray.
You pray?
What do you mean, like,
like, get on your knees,
"Our Father, who art in heaven,"
pray?
Oh, come on. You kiddin' me?
You talk to God?
No.
I listen.
Oh.
Don't you ever...
get this feeling, like...
that sometimes you just
wanna just disappear?
Just walk out...
never stop?
Just go.
Hey.
- Chief Danvers wants you to call...
- She can wait.
Come here
for a second.
Uh, I was cleanin' out the garage
and I found these.
Yeah, I know,
Darwin's only four,
but, uh, you were already a pretty damn
good little skater
by that age, so.
If ya...
take him out,
shoot me a text, huh?
Yeah, sure.
What's Danvers up to?
Uh, she's goin' through
the trailer's evidence.
She and Navarro?
Yeah.
I don't know
what the hell
they're doin'
together.
I thought they
hated each other.
You know
what happened there?
She won't tell me.
No idea.
Hey!
You received
a direct call
about Annie K's
and Raymond Clark's relationship.
A direct call,
and you didn't report it?
Danvers, tell your girl here
to stand down.
You talk to me.
Tell me why the fuck
you withheld information
- from a murder investigation?
- Oh, please.
That woman was sleeping
with half of Ennis.
What did you
want me to do?
Log every dude
she was banging in the region?
You piece of shit.
I swear to God, you're gonna join
- your boys over here.
- No, no, no. No, no, no. Calm the fuck down.
Calm!
And you, go back
to your fuckin' search...
and get rid of your
hillbilly friends.
Or you're gettin'
a negligence report
for your mishandling
of the Kowtok case.
Maybe I oughta file
a report on you
for playing
Mrs. Robinson with my kid.
Hm?
You do your fuckin' job.
That's it?
"Do your fucking job"?
That's all he gets?
- Hey, where you goin'?
- Fuck outta here.
Who's Mrs. Robinson?
Where's my forensic tech?
Well, there's a blizzard
out in North Bay.
Visibility's shit.
No planes are takin' off,
so they're gonna
try again tomorrow.
Ah, tomorrow's
no good.
They're gonna thaw.
And they're gettin' shipped out to Anchorage.
Well, I have an idea.
What?
- I don't know if you're gonna like it.
- Well...?
My cousin lives
in White Lake.
He's a vet.
Works a lot
with large animals.
How long before you
can get him here?
- Well, I can call him right now and see.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Qavvik!
Shh!
Fucker.
What can
I do for you?
Do you know
Oliver Tagaq?
He worked at Tsalal for a bit.
Now he might be a hunter,
somewhere out on the ice.
Tagaq? No.
Well, thing is, I know you know
someone who knows someone.
Homebrew
comes with a network.
You'll ask around?
Mm-hmm... for a price.
You want me
to pay you?
It's called
quid pro quo.
You tell me something.
I tell you something.
Don't get fuckin'
cute on me.
I'm not kidding.
You tell me something
about yourself...
and I'll get
you that intel.
Fuck you, Qavvik.
Always lovely to see you, Evangeline.
Da fuck you wanna know?
Your mom.
- Tell me about her.
- Ask Julia.
Mm-mm,
I'm asking you.
She was local,
wasn't she?
Yeah, from a gold mining
camp that's gone.
She left when
she was 15.
Met my dad
in Boston. Boom.
- Now get me Tagaq.
- That's that accent, Boston girl.
But you
didn't stay.
No.
Dad was bad.
He drank.
He hit her.
Us too. So Mom
took us and ran.
And then we came
back up North.
Alaska girls
always come back.
She was... not okay.
She...
Like Jules?
Yeah.
Voices. Episodes.
Then one day she ran out
and never came back.
- Was she...
- She was killed.
Fucker was never found.
Oh.
Fuck.
Sorry, Eve.
She never told me my Inupiaq name,
you know?
I wish...
Nothing.
Anyways,
there's your intel.
Now get me mine.
They're sick,
they're starving,
they're dying.
The fish, the whales,
the seals,
the caribou.
What are we gonna eat?
We can't pay for the food
in the stores.
Now, even our water's rotten.
They're lying.
They're fucking lying when they say
they're not poisoning us.
We want the truth.
We want truth! We want clean water!
We want clear skies!
We want our animals healthy!
We want the mine to close.
- Close the mine!
- This town was here before them.
- We were here before!
We were here before!
Oh, you're the Chief of Police's
daughter, aren't you?
- No, she's just my stepmom, but I don't support...
- It's fine.
Anybody who cares
is welcome here.
We were here before!
Hey, hey, hey!
Aviaq and Joe Carter's
baby boy passed this morning.
Another stillborn.
Can we have
a minute of silence?
Thank you.
Lee?
- I thought you were gonna help me...
- Hey! I'm changing.
Have you been hangin' out with those people
that are vandalizing the mine?
- No.
- Are you insane?!
- Do you know what happens to those people?!
- I'm not insane.
I just fucking care
about this place, alright?
I don't know what
you want from me.
I want you
to fucking care.
- I do care.
- Bullshit.
I told you to wipe
that shit off your face. Come on.
Did you know Aviaq Carter's baby
was stillborn today?
Sure as hell didn't
care for them, did you?
That shit's comin' off.
- Come on.
- Stop! Let go!
- Get off of me.
- Wipe it off.
- No!
- Now.
Now!
Hey!
Listen...
Tell my mommy.
Oh, fuck.
Hello?
Yes, ma'am, Ms. Navarro?
It's Kenny Hogan.
I'm-I'm coverin'
for Qavvik.
Uh, yeah, he got no signal.
Do you want me to...
No, ma'am. This is
about your sister, Julia.
Is she okay?
What happened?
It's okay.
She's, she's fine.
What did she do?
She started screamin'
that someone was comin'
and she was prayin',
she just started prayin'.
She was...
Hey... Look, I don't know,
it-it was bad.
I'm sorry, I just, uh,
I just thought you'd like to know.
Where is she?
I-I don't know,
she just ran out.
Aren't you cold, babygirl?
How'd you know
where to find me?
You weren't home.
And I know you.
You see that?
That's the water.
The sea.
I think stuff.
Bad stuff.
I know, I know, I know.
I know, baby.
Mama!
Hey, I'm sorry.
- Come to bed?
- I have an exam at seven.
Might as well
stay up.
Am I in trouble?
Come on, Kayla, it's just one case
and it'll be over, and...
And Danvers will
still be calling day and night, Pete.
And you'll run
every time.
Every time.
- You jealous of Danvers?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Exactly. You married a cop.
- No, I didn't.
You were not a cop.
You were just a sweet idiot
who made me laugh...
Well, what if I don't
wanna be a sweet idiot?
I don't tell you
you can't be a doctor.
I'm not a doctor.
I'm in nursing school,
with a kid,
married to a cop.
Jesus, Pete.
Yeah, it's weird, right?
Hey, you think that guy scratched
his own eyes out?
How many hours have you been here
staring at this shit?
Prior, crack that phone?
Morning, Chief.
Uh, this is my cousin, Vince,
- the vet I was tellin' you about.
- Yeah?
Vince, tell her.
- Tell me what?
- Uh, yeah.
- I-I think they died before they froze.
- What?
I-I mean, they didn't
freeze to death.
I've seen plenty
of frozen animals,
and cold makes
their heart rate drop,
their breath
grows shallow.
They basically
fall asleep.
All told, a pretty
peaceful death.
Those guys, this...
this is not how
you die in the cold.
- It's just not.
- What killed 'em?
It's hard to tell
without a chance
to properly
postmortem them,
but looks like cardiac arrest
if I had to put money on it.
- Oh, well, how can you be sure?
- I can't.
I'm just a vet, ma'am.
But I've seen caribous
die of plain fright.
Running, terrified.
Uh, these scientists,
they, they, uh,
they look the same.
So, uh,
Vince...
you think you could do just, like,
a tiny bit of postmortem?
- Chief.
- Just... I'm just kidding.
- Oh.
- That would be super illegal.
Sorry, Vince.
I'll buy you a beer.
- Yeah.
- Thank you, man.
Well... so I guess we wait
and see what information
Anchorage is willing
to share with us.
- Yeah.
- Annie's phone. What about it?
Yeah, uh, we're
workin' on it.
We should get it
back this morning.
- It shouldn't be a problem...
- Oliver Tagaq.
I found him.
- How?
- It's called "Mukluk Telegraph."
- Not for white boys.
- No, no. I'm sorry. The man doesn't exist.
Alright? There's no
birth certificates,
there's no school records,
no taxes, nothing for him.
Oh, so, so, nothing
from Tsalal's records.
Yeah, nothin' on
the Tsalal records.
- There's nothin'.
- Well...
he's living in a nomad camp
on the North Shore.
Alright.
Not everything
is on a computer, freshman.
Fuck.
Hello, sir.
We're looking
for a Oliver Tagaq.
And that would be why?
Well, we believe that he may
have some information,
uh, regarding
Tsalal station.
Sir... Mr. Tagaq
is not a suspect.
We just need
to chat with him.
Not sure
he's around.
Mr. Tagaq?
Alaska police.
Hear that?
Yeah, the genny.
Yeah, he's
around, alright.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, okay.
- That's good.
- What the fuck are you doing?
You're standing
on traditional Inupiaq territory.
- Uh, well...
- Unless you have an order, if you take one step in,
I'll blow your brains out.
Uh... I hear ya.
So, if I go
in the state records...
this property is your land?
It's under your name,
Mr. Tagaq?
You wanna come
and see the deed, lady?
You.
- What's your name?
- I'm A.T. Evangeline Navarro.
No.
Who are you?
I just told you.
Oh, you forgot,
didn't you?
We're here to talk
about Annie Kowtok.
Annie?
Look, I don't care what you
came here to talk about.
If you don't have an arrest order,
you need to leave.
What, you want us to get one?
We can get one.
An arrest for what?
How about the deaths
of the Tsalal scientists?
Your ex-colleagues.
They're dead.
They all died
a week ago.
How?
They died on the ice.
We still don't know
what happened.
- Lund is dead?
- No. No, he's in the hospital.
He's not doing well.
Listen... you can talk to us
if there's anything you know.
- Get the hell out of my house!
- No, we just wanna...
Go, now!
Alright.
- Get outta here. Out!
- We're gone, we're gone.
Go, now! Don't ever come back!
What was all that
shit about your name?
You wouldn't understand.
Chief.
- Danvers.
- Chief, we got a call, from the hospital.
Lund?
Yeah.
The gangrene
spread everywhere.
He needed
multiple amputations.
He lost his eyesight.
We kept him
heavily sedated,
but a few hours ago,
he started waking up.
- Is he communicating?
- He comes in and out.
He's agitated.
Be prepared.
He's hard to look at.
Please be quick.
Dr. Lund... my name
is Elizabeth Danvers.
I'm with Alaska police.
What happened that night out on the ice?
Anders... I'm here.
Okay? Anders.
- Anders.
- W-We woke her.
She's awake.
And now she's out.
She's out there in the ice.
Who's out there?
She came for us...
in the dark.
I'm sedating him.
No. Who-Who's out there?
Who was it?
Who is she?
Who-Who came for you?
- Anders, who?
- There's been an accident
on the police search.
Chief Danvers,
we need help!
Officers?
- Anders... talk to me.
- Officers?!
Fucking hunters are fighting!
Stay with him.
Fuckin' hillbillies.
Security to the waiting area.
We need all security to proceed
to the waiting area.
Who are you callin' a redneck?
What are you doing?!
Alright, cuffs, cuffs.
Let me see your hands!
Hello, Evangeline.
Your mother says hello.
She's waiting for you.
Defib.
Get the crash cart.
Someone get his AVM.
- Stay with us.
- Let's get him intubated.
Pete?
What's up?
Annie's phone.
I cracked it.
I found it.
It's here.
I found, I found it.
My name is Annie Kowtok.
If anything happens to me, please...