Twist and shout
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, baby, now
Come on, baby
Come on and work it on out
Work it on out
You know you look so good
Look so good
Hey, man.
Have you seen my phone?
No, I don't know.
Like I knew you would
You know you twist, little girl
Twist, little girl
New data?
No, same.
You're too late, Veer, I'm finished.
This week, it's your turn.
Hey, Clark. Are you okay?
She's awake.
Yo! Delivery!
Emerson!
Your stuff's here!
I got your Funyuns!
Guys, come on! Goodies are here!
Nobody ever helps me around here.
Come on, could somebody
gimme a hand with this stuff?
Guys.
I need a signature.
Come on, I have to get back.
Anton?
Hello? Anybody?
Hello?
Hey!
Guys?
Ah, ah, ah, ah
Twist and shout
Come on, come on, come on
Come on, baby, now
Come on, baby
Come on and work it on out
You know you look so good
Ah, ah, ah, ah
Susie, where's your hairnet?
Not a whole lotta crab, huh?
Nah, it's been shit this year.
Getting worse every year.
Where's the ambulance?
We don't need nobody dyin' in here.
They're comin'. I was closer.
Y'all get your asses back to work!
Them loads ain't packin' themselves.
Let's go!
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Sir?
Fucker's not gonna die.
He's just too drunk to get up.
Sir? Sir?
- Sir?
- I told you. He's just too wasted.
Did you hit this man, ma'am?
Asshole hit Blair, then I hit the asshole.
With a metal bucket?
What's your name, hon?
Who's your Aaka?
Did you or did you not hit this man
with a metal bucket, ma'am?
Damn right I hit him with a metal bucket.
You puttin' me away for that, hon?
Hell yeah. I mean...
Sir, I'd like to speak
with these women now.
- If he fuckin' dies...
- Now, sir.
Alright, what's the story here?
He hits me, I moved out,
he didn't like it.
She moved in with me, mind you.
Not with some guy.
- Did he...
- No, that's just the job.
Playin' with sharp things
after a first or second shift
on some other job will get you chopped.
You fucking bitch!
- You broke my fucking nose!
- Hey, hey!
- Miss, are you pressin' charges?
- What?
Damn right, she is.
Sir, you're under arrest
for assault and battery.
The fucking bitch hit me!
Fuck you too!
Fucking bitch-pig! Fuck!
I can't talk right now.
You actually on the phone?
You're on the fucking phone?
So this is what this place looks like
on the inside, huh?
You ever been out here?
Oh yeah, Liz, with my
polar chemistry Ph.D., you mean?
Can't find my glasses.
- Any vehicles missin'?
- Nope.
This is it.
We don't think that they
just went out for a stroll?
No.
Well, shit.
Yeah.
Just the third day of dark
and it's already gettin' weird.
Where is that fucking song?
- Where is it?
- Morning, Chief.
Where's...
Yeah, sorry, we can't turn that off.
It's gettin' on my nerves too.
Tried to cover it up,
muffle the sound a little.
There's no buttons.
Can't find the remote.
Those don't open.
That does not open.
Nah, those don't open either.
Look at that.
Not a Beatles fan, okay?
Alright, what do we know, Pete?
A supply guy found the station
empty this morning.
He called it in.
- The scientists' last contact was...
- Speak up, Peter.
I can hear him just fine.
So when was their last contact with town?
It was a week ago.
They called for some supplies.
And who's contacting the families?
Lulu, but they're
from all around the world,
so, ya know, takin' a minute.
And who pays for this place?
Government grants?
You askin' me?
I'll check on the funding.
Look what I found.
It's like they went to take a leak,
never came back.
Alright. Here we go.
Alright. Tsalal Station's been
operating for 18 years,
researching Arctic geology, biology,
and the impacts of climate change.
Ralph Emerson, geology.
Anton Kotov, geophysics.
- All men, huh?
- Yep.
Li Jie, geobiology.
Raymond Clark, paleomicrobiology.
Lucas Merens, environmental chemistry.
Facundo Molina and Veer Mehta, biophysics.
And Anders Lund,
founder-director, structural biology.
They live here all year long?
All alone? Just like monks?
What are they looking for?
Digging that ice up.
I think the origin of life?
That thing.
Sat phones are back there.
These are the cells I could find.
This one was charging,
and that one was just there,
just like that.
- Dead battery.
- Who leaves their cell behind?
Well, it's not like there's a lotta
cell signal out there.
It's not like there's a lotta
anything out there.
Alright, well, let's get the cell records
and the radio log, Pete.
Yeah, that ham seems pretty fresh.
Alright, we're gonna call in rescue.
Let's get the choppers,
ping this site as an LKP,
and then 15 miles POA.
Word'll spread.
Their families will be upset.
And if these dorks turn out to be just out
on some geek expedition,
don't you wanna hold off for a bit?
No, Hank, I don't.
We're late to the party already.
The ham and the sandwich
may seem fresh,
but the mayo is like syrup.
Mayo doesn't go runny until a couple days
out of the fridge.
But your processed cold cuts,
they'll survive the apocalypse.
The things you learn when your kid
leaves their lunch in the back seat
of the car.
You were never much of a sandwich-makin'
kinda dad, was he, Pete?
Clothes in that washer stink.
It's gonna take wet clothes
a couple of days
to stink that bad.
These men disappeared
48 hours ago, at least.
Least.
Alright, let's take a look at that tongue.
Two days. Startin' to discolor.
Maybe it's not human.
It's human, all right.
See there?
That a bite?
No.
Those are marks
left by a repetitive behavior.
Remember that Native auntie
that we found a year ago,
- frozen solid?
- Yeah, yeah.
Outside Saint Joseph
of the Arctic, right?
Yeah. She had the same marks.
Comes from lickin' the thread
when you're fixin' the fishin' nets.
That is a native woman's tongue.
Jesus.
Dead or alive, you think?
Gonna have to wait until the lab
in Anchorage processes this baggie.
In the meantime, Hank?
Yup?
Why don't you hit up command
and see if they got
a tongue-less lady
in some fridge somewhere.
Prior, call Central.
Your father's havin' a brain fart.
Hey.
Lulu, Hank Prior.
Put me through to Central.
Right on it, Hank.
Alright, folks,
Christmas is coming.
Can't stop it.
Ya have your presents lined up?
Yeah. Me neither.
We're gonna take calls, though.
Alright. Anyone out there? Hello?
Hello?
Is there anybody there?
Hello, Travis.
What do you want?
- I left a few messages...
- Hey, Lulu.
...and I'm trying to reach
Dr. Molina's family.
Has he called?
You have a message.
- There's someone in your office...
- Coffee.
...but it's her.
- It's not her tongue.
- How do you know?
It's been six years.
Can't be her tongue.
But it's a woman's tongue?
I don't know.
Right. Let me see it, then.
No.
You got bounced off the case, 'member?
You're a trooper now.
You're not A.P.F. anymore, 'member that?
It's a woman's tongue.
It's an Inupiaq woman's tongue.
And you know this because
your spirit animal came to you in a dream?
Nah, my spirit animal eats
old fuckin' white ladies
like you for breakfast, Danvers.
Careful.
How's daddy Connelly?
Treatin' ya good?
Ah, right. Is that all, Trooper Navarro?
I'm sure you got some
caribou to scrape off the road somewhere.
You never even wanted
to look at her files.
And now you're just
brushin' her off like...
like she's...
Did you get all that?
What file is she talkin' about?
Alright, go look in the cold case files.
Get me Anne Masu Kowtok.
- Hello?
- Is this Elizabeth Danvers?
- Yeah.
- This is Kerri Gillard.
Sheri's mom.
Sheri Gillard, from Leah's class?
Oh, yeah. I can't talk to you right now.
I really, really need to talk to you,
Mrs. Danvers.
I'm gonna call you back later when...
No, we need to talk now! Like, right now!
- She's 15 years old!
- I got it. I understand.
15 years old!
Do you understand?
No, this is your daughter initiating this.
Alright, let's not escalate it.
Let's talk about it in a week,
see if it improves.
- I didn't do any...
- Shut up.
A video? Really?
You know, you don't have to
- freak out about...
- I'm not talkin' about it.
I thought you were
smarter than that, Leah.
Well, you know where those videos end up?
They end up on porn sites.
For the rest of your life,
every single time somebody
- looks you up...
- Okay, well, we didn't post it.
Her mom took her phone
and she freaked out.
- It was just for us...
- Don't be an idiot.
- People break up, 'kay? Phones get hacked.
- Oh, right.
Thanks, Chief Danvers.
All criminal angles noted.
Stop pretending like you give a shit now.
I don't give a shit!
But that woman was screaming
in my face because you...
- "You" what?
- Because you made a video of...
- Of what?
- Of you screwing a 15-year-old girl!
Okay? You made a video
that I had to watch...
Hey. Hey, are you okay?
- Did we hit something?
- Nah. We didn't hit anything.
It's okay. Leah, Leah.
It's just an ice slip. Alright?
Alright, calm down. Calm down.
It's Danvers.
- Chief.
- We got in an accident.
Sending ambulance, Chief.
Yeah, send an ambulance.
Possible injuries. We're at 5th and Front.
Is that fucking Stacy Chalmers again?
- I'm so sorry.
- Stacy, you idiot!
Are you fuckin' drunk?
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Alright, get outta the car.
Get outta the car.
Hey, Mrs. Danvers.
Hey, you don't even have
your license anymore.
My baby! She's not speakin' to me!
Oh, for fuck's sake.
I'm so sorry.
Get your fuckin' hands off me!
Turn around! Come on!
Turn around!
Put your hands up right now!
Move it! Hands fuckin' up!
Fuckin' bitch!
She's 16.
What?
Sheri's 16, not 15.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Agent Navarro, it's been a while.
Hey, Ryan.
You got a break in her case?
I'm not sure yet.
Want a beer?
The ex asked me to watch Evan tonight.
Wanna come over?
Yeah.
So, Annie never mentioned Tsalal?
Never talked about it?
Anything?
No.
You found Annie had some connection?
I don't know, just goin' over
any angle I might've missed back then,
you know?
Last of my stash.
No. Maybe just some water?
Water's bad.
Turned to shit about three days ago.
Annie'd say, "I told you so."
Look, don't take this wrong.
I loved my sister,
and I wish like hell she was still here,
but I'm not sure it'd do much good to go
through all this again.
Listen, you don't really think that, Ryan.
Hey.
Hey, listen to me.
I know it wasn't easy for you.
Annie protestin' the mine,
mine guys going at her.
- It was a mess.
- Yeah.
We got into some shit fights.
I told her,
"You kill the mine, you kill Ennis."
No jobs, no mine taxes,
no schools, nothin'.
She didn't care.
We were barely speakin' that last year.
Do you believe in God, Agent Navarro?
Yes.
Mind if I ask why?
My last tour...
Listen.
It doesn't matter.
Must be nice.
What?
Knowing we're not alone.
No, we're alone.
God too.
- Hello?
- Hey, Navarro. Cooper here.
It happened again.
I'll be there right away.
- Hey, Cooper.
- Hey, Ange.
How's Troopers?
You know, same shit, different badge.
So, she called in hysterics,
said there was someone
inside the apartment,
but the door is bolted from the inside
and the windows are all shut tight.
Thanks for the call.
Yeah, you got it.
It stays between us.
Thanks.
- Hey, Jules.
- Hey, Angie.
What's going on?
Nothing, I shouldn't have called.
I'm sorry.
It was just a little freak-out.
I'm okay.
I'm just tired.
Alright, so...
why don't you come over to my place,
we eat some junk food,
watch "The Bachelor," come on.
I never should've moved here.
- I'm so sorry.
- Hey, Jules, Jules.
Come here. Hey, look at me. Hey.
I wanted you here.
I'm glad you're here, okay?
Listen, I'm not like Mom.
You are nothing like Mom.
You are not her, okay?
You hear me?
If you're worried, we can start talking
some options.
No hospitals.
You promised me no hospitals.
'Kay, so make sure you're good, Jules.
I'm okay. I promise.
I got this.
Alright, so, if you look at the funding,
most of the funding to Tsalal comes from
an NGO, but some of it
- comes...
- I want to go home!
- But if you try and...
- Please!
- Like she's dying.
- So...
Lemme go!
Oh, thanks.
- Here we go.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- What are you doin'?
- Putting us all out of our misery.
The fuck you are! She's still drunk.
Yeah, so, I'll drive her home.
Nah, I'm not letting a still-drunk DUI out
just because sometimes she blows you.
- Hey!
- End of story!
Back in. Back in!
I need some toilet paper!
You know, for the record,
I have a fiancée.
Oh, yeah?
Natasha from the catalog?
She's not from a catalog.
She's from Vladivostok,
and she's coming for Christmas.
We're getting married, just so you know.
A Christmas wedding. That's festive.
- This girlfriend stays in.
- Sorry, Stace.
- You heard the man.
- I hate you!
Yeah, and I need the Anne Kowtok file.
You got it.
- Do I?
- Yeah. It's at your place.
You took a bunch of case files home
after the flood.
I don't think so. I'll check.
- When?
- Soon.
- I hate you all!
- Shut up!
- He has the files?
- I hate you all!
What you doin' down there, Darwin?
Doin' a drawin'?
Oh, what's this?
You do this?
Kayla?
Yeah?
What's this?
Just a local legend.
You leave him at the laundromat
with your grandma?
- Yeah, I did.
- Right.
- You know why?
- Okay.
Yeah, I'm sorry I was late.
It's just the Tsalal thing.
- It's been kinda crazy, so.
- It's fine.
It's all good, but I have classes,
so my grandma's there
to take care of Darwin,
and she happens to like
to tell him stories from his culture.
Alright, so when the stories that
his grandma tells him,
they give him bad dreams,
I can just put you on the phone, right?
You'll talk to him,
explain why it's important.
You're such a white boy.
How the hell did I fall for a white boy?
Oh, no you don't.
Seriously?
I gotta take this.
Fuck!
- Kayla!
- Seriously?
- It's work.
- Work ends at six. That's Danvers.
I gotta take it. Fuck.
- Hey, Chief.
- I need you to get me something
from your dad's.
Sorry, Chief.
No. Please?
Did I hear no?
Weird.
Yeah, I think it was a no.
Must be the connection.
- Hey.
- Hey, Dad.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I promised Darwin
I would show him an old photo of me
when I was his age.
- Ah, okay.
- You mind if I take a look?
Ah, that's fine.
Yeah, careful. Still wet.
That is
really blue.
Well, Alina likes blue.
Too blue?
It's blue, but...
Too damn blue.
No. No, no, no. It's great.
- It's a change.
- Yeah, you want a beer?
No. I'm good, thank you.
Fuck.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Actually, you got anything to eat?
Like, chips or somethin'?
I'm starvin'.
Let me check.
Pretty tapped out.
I gotta grocery shop.
You want an apple?
No, I'm good.
You want to go out, grab a bite?
Nope. I promised I'd put
Darwin to bed, so.
Let me see what you took.
Didn't know I still had that.
Watch yourself on the ice.
It's slick as shit out there.
You take Darwin to see Santa yet?
Not yet, but I'm working on it.
Well, dude, you better be
or else Kayla's gonna kick your pink ass.
I think I liked it better when I babysat
and she couldn't talk back.
Thanks.
So this case is connected to Tsalal?
No.
- No?
- No.
That's all I get?
Chief, my dad is gonna kill me
if he finds out I took these.
Alright, take the Christmas tree box
into the living room.
- Did you eat?
- Nope.
- When have I got time to fuckin' eat?
- Well, you gotta eat.
The body was found on the edge
of the Villages.
Navarro was the first on the scene.
Her name was Anne Masu Kowtok.
People called her Annie K.
Stabbed 32 times
with a sharp, unidentified object.
Star-shaped wounds.
Murder weapon never found.
Missing tongue?
Yeah. Never recovered.
I knew about the dead girl
out in the Villages, but...
I didn't know about the tongue.
Yep, we kept that from the public.
She was a midwife, activist, protester.
You know, fighting the mine like crazy,
drivin' everybody nuts.
Workers, mine folks.
A lotta haters.
But this?
Nobody deserves that.
You lied to her.
Navarro.
You do know the case.
You studied it.
Mind your own business, kid.
You made it my business
when you asked me to steal these for you.
I asked you to relocate them.
Fine. I will relocate them back to my dad,
and you can ask him for them.
You bluff for shit, you know that?
Alright. Okay. Sit down.
It's gettin' cold.
Here's the story.
Navarro was obsessed with the case.
She's got this thing
about women who get hurt.
I don't know.
She didn't get anywhere with it,
but she wouldn't let it go
and started buggin' the wrong people.
Mine people.
Kate McKittrick, specifically.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
Showed up at her house,
started demanding answers,
and she got in a couple of fights
with some mine workers.
Your dad had to take her off the case.
And when I came to town
we started working together, and
she asked me to pick it back up.
And you didn't?
This one was never gonna be solved.
What do you mean?
Ennis killed Annie.
This fucking place.
No killer was ever gonna be found.
That a Tinder match or somethin'?
Fantasy football.
I got two running backs on I.R.
I got a wide receiver who's a klutz.
I don't know who the fuck
I'm gonna start on Sunday.
- Evangeline.
- Qavvik.
Wait, fuck.
Wait!
Fuck, Gi.
Fuck.
SpongeBob? Really?
SpongeBob is cool.
He cleans your teeth.
He lives in a pineapple.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't do that. No.
It's disgusting. No.
I gotta go.
Your sister?
Why, has she been actin' off?
No. She's...
she's just been missing some work,
it's nothing major.
Gotta swing by the booze depot.
Don't go.
You can take a gallon of my homebrew.
Yeah.
I don't wanna go blind yet.
My homebrew brings
all the boys to the yard.
Are you tellin' that to a cop, Qavvik?
Hey.
Next time you call,
I'm not gonna pick up the phone.
Hey.
No, that's my toothbrush.
Well, I need it!
Hey, about earlier.
You mean about you makin' dirty videos?
No.
About people driving drunk.
Ya know, it's really stupid
that we never talk about that day.
We're doin' Christmas this year.
I'm gonna cook.
Ya know, you don't really
have to be my mom, Liz.
Think my dad would've understood.
I'm takin' a shower.
- Night, Manny.
- Night, officer.
She's gonna come right back
begging for this,
and I'm gonna give it to her so hard,
her eyes are gonna pop right off that
fugly face of hers,
and I'm gonna stuff her mouth with all
the fuckin' bills
- I've been payin'.
- Yeah, man.
Bitch broke my fucking...
Merry Christmas, motherfucker.
Mommy?
Holden?
She's awake.
Hi, Miss Irniq.
Thanks for returning my call.
I hope I didn't wake you up.
- I'm not sleeping much these days.
- No, no.
I was just going through some old notes,
filing some stuff,
reaching out to Annie's contacts.
Do you remember Annie
ever mentioning the Tsalal Station?
Tsalal? That place with the scientists?
Hello?
Ma'am, hello?
She's awake!
Ennis Police! Step out slowly.
This is an A.P.F. investigation.
I have a badge.
A trooper's badge. You're trespassin'.
Trespassing, huh?
You gonna book me?
Still really carry it, don't you?
Annie's case.
We carry 'em all.
No, we don't.
What are you lookin' for?
I don't know.
Anything that might've belonged to her.
A shoe, an earring.
A coat?
Alright. You can look around, this once,
but the Tsalal men's case is mine.
What coat?
This one.
So you did look into the case,
didn't you?
- Back then.
- Yeah. It doesn't mean shit.
It's one parka.
Could be thousands of 'em.
Right.
So what are you doin' here, then?
Just followin' up.
The only one with a room of his own.
Well, which one is him?
Raymond Clark.
Yeah, I've never seen this guy before.
He's not in any of our photos.
Nowhere.
How about Annie's brother?
Miner guy?
Ryan.
Yeah, I'll show him a photo.
That's it.
It's not here.
No parka.
- Maybe he had it on when they...
- When they went poof?
You don't really think
they're gonna find them, do you?
You're the one who believes in miracles.
Pickin' up any spirit vibes?
Nope. All I'm pickin' up is
your shitty fuckin' attitude.
Five, acknowledge.
Movin' to sector 2-7-8.
Better watch out.
That case sunk ya once.
The case didn't sink me.
You asked me to transfer to Troopers.
Had nothin' to do with Annie.
We both know what really happened.
Are you done?
Annie's case isn't closed.
It's not closed.
Just let her go.
Let that poor girl go.
"Let her go."
You didn't find her.
You didn't see the hate.
You could see the disgust
in the way they cut her.
Forensics showed that someone kicked her
after they dumped her dead body, Liz.
Poor girl's just lyin' there,
and they still kick her.
Broken teeth, broken ribs.
And then they cut out her tongue.
To shut her the fuck up.
Wouldn't've happened
if she was white, though.
Wouldn't've made any difference
- what color her skin was.
- Yes the fuck it would have.
They would've had the whole
fuckin' police force out
lookin' for a white ass.
No, you're not gonna blame her on me.
And I wasn't even here.
You know who was here?
You. You were here.
It was your case all those months.
You didn't close it.
You.
Exactly.
Did you get the cell records?
No, we got a call.
They found something on the ice.
Chief?
Chief, can you hear me?
Yeah, talk to me, Prior.
Rose Aguineau, Chief.
Rose Aguineau found it.
- Hey, Rose.
- Morning, Missy.
- How did you find them?
- Travis showed me.
Travis.
Travis is dead, Rose.
I know.