WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS WENK]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[BELLS JINGLING]
Aaaaaaaah!
♪ Alouette,
gentille alouette ♪
je te plumerai ♪
♪ Je te plumerai,
Je te plumerai ♪
♪ Alouette ♪
[FLAPPING LIPS]
Huh, I guess you do know
all the words.
Anyway, start the next video,
Beemo.
We got to crack the code on the
Ice King's evil secret tapes!
[GROANS]
Brrr! You guys cold?
Yeah, it's kinda chilly
in here.
[GRUNTS]
What's on those tapes?
I can kind of make it out.
Dang it, Beemo, just turn
to your right a little.
Ugh!
By the power of ice,
I want your cup of cocoa
to fall over!
[GRUNTS]
Yes!
Now turn and pick it up.
Yes. Yes.
[GASPS]
That's... me?
They're watching
my secret tapes?!
[GROWLS]
And they're cozy!
I'll show them.
This snowman looks
pretty good.
Pretty darn good.
[LAUGHS]
[CRYING]
[SLURPS]
[CRYING CONTINUES]
Wenk.
Could / have five
more minutes, please ?
[CRYING CONTINUES]
I think I can break the code,
Finn.
Really?
Yes, I have detected
a noticeable pattern
in the tears of sadness
that fall
from the Ice King's eyeballs.
His tears drop at an equal rate
until the 13th tear,
when the right side drops
two tears instead of one.
- Whoa.
- This is so fascinating.
The 13th letter
of the alphabet is
if I print the letter "m"
every time Ice King says
an "m" word
it looks like this.
Oh, my glob, Jake.
ls this it?
Could this be the Ice King's
evil secret?
What does it mean?!
Some of you won't
survive this.
You'll melt or split in half
or your head will fall off.
But that's fine, because
you're made of snow.
Only one thing matters
today --
getting into that tree house,
getting my tapes back,
and beating up Finn and Jake!
Maybe Beemo.
Yeah, Beemo, too.
Who's with me?
[WIND WHISTLES]
Hey, Why are you guys
So quiet?
Are you mad?
Oh, that's right,
you're not alive yet.
My bad.
[SNOWMEN MOANING]
Give me my tapes back.
No, man! I know you've got
evil secrets on these,
and we're gonna
find them!
Snowmen, attack!
[SNOWMEN MOANING]
ICE KING:
Aah!
Crup, Jake!
We got to unravel these evil
secrets at warp crazy!
Good morning.
You're watching
the evening news.
There's been an unfortunate event.
Let's go talk to some
witnesses.
Princess, what is your name?
Please, let me go home!
So, Princess
Please-let-me-go-home, tell me,
what was it like to experience
this tragedy?
What? I can--
I don't, uh, uh...
Yeah, we're on air,
honey, so spit it out.
I... I don't know what you're
talking about.
Obviously traumatized
and in a state of shock.
Let's go ask somebody else
something.
Upside-down Princess,
do you think
things will change politically
because of today's events?
You're really frightening me!
Well, there
you have it, folks.
People are very upset
that Gunter tried to eat
Ice King's socks.
Very Upset!
That's why Gunter has to stay
in the corner.
Weird.
- [BANGING]
He's sneaking in
through the chimney!
[GRUNTS]
Ah, the element of surprise.
Aw, geez, I'm filthy.
[GRUNTS]
Well, now I'm cleaner,
but I'm also nakeder.
Ooh! Mmm.
[LICKS LIPS]
Just what I need.
[LAUGHS]
Come on, come on.
♪ Daddy, why did you
eat my fries'? ♪
♪ I bought them.
They were mine ♪
♪ But you ate them ♪
♪ You ate my fries ♪
♪ And I cried ♪
♪ But you didn't see me cry ♪
♪ Daddy, do you even
love me? ♪
♪ Well, I wish you would
show it
'cause I wouldn't know it ♪
- Yeesh!
[MUTTERING ANGRILY]
They wouldn't
be in a fruit bowl!
Ooh!
Well, look at you with your nose
shining so bright!
You're so unique!
[CHUCKLES]
I'll name you "Red Nose"
and make you leader
of the pack!
[SIGHS]
Well, now you look boring.
If you want something done
right,
you have to do it
yourself.
[CRYING]
Now give me my evil tapes
back!
They're supposed to be buried...
in the ground!
BOTH:
[SCREAM]
Snow goons!
- Oh, no!
- Don't worry, Beemo.
Aah!
Finn, there's one more tape!
Play it! His evil secret
must be on that tape!
No, Beemo, please
don't play it!
Hello, my name is
Simon Petrikov.
I am recording this tape so
that people will know my story.
Oh, no! Turn it off, Beemo!
Turn it off!
I was studying to be
an antiquarian
of ancient artifacts.
Now I never believed in the
supernatural stuff myself,
just had a fascination
with superstitions.
But everything changed
when I came into contact
with this item.
BOTH:
The Ice King!
After purchasing this crown
from an old dock worker in
northern Scandinavia,
I brought it home and excitedly
showed my fiancee, Betty.
I jokingly put it
on my head,
just for a laugh
or something,
and that's when it started...
the visions.
I fought with them,
shouted at them
until I realized
it wasn't real!
It was the crown!
I quickly took it off
and saw my fiancée
in front of me,
looking at me with such
contempt!
What had I said?
What had I done
when I wore this crown?
All I know is, I never saw
Betty again.
Since then, I now see
the visions always,
whether or not
I wear the crown.
They tell me the secrets...
the secrets of the ice
and snow,
that the power of the crown
will save me with its frost.
I don't yet know
what this means...
As you can see, my skin is
beginning to turn blue,
my body temperature has
been lowering
at a supernatural rate,
to what is now
about 30 degrees celsius.
I don't know
when it will end.
I'm really scared...
I know my mind is changing,
but I'm already too far gone
to know what to do.
I want people to know
that if I do things,
if -- if I do things
that hurt anyone,
please, please forgive me!
Just watch over me
until I can find my way
out of this labyrinth
in my brain
and regain my sanity!
And then maybe Betty,
my princess...
maybe you will love me again.
[VOICE BREAKING]
Please love me again, Betty!
[CRIES]
Drama bomb!
[SNIFFLES]
Now you know my secret!
You know...
that I used to wear glasses!
[CRYING]
Maybe kidnapping Wildberry
Princess will cheer me up.
Wait, Ice King.
Beemo, eject tape, please.
[WHIRRING]
[CRIES]
Here, Ice King.
What's this?
You're giving me a gift?
No!
It's...
Well, these belong to you.
But it's not even
my birthday!
Oh, this is so exciting!
Video tapes!
You know, I had a bunch
of these once,
but I threw them away.
This is great, Finn.
Thank you.
It's from me, too.
Oh, I have presents
for you guys, too!
Here, it's a small pine tree.
I chopped it down
in one fell swoop.
And this is for you.
Uh, thanks.
Oh, isn't this fun?
We're exchanging presents.
We're wearing silly clothes.
There's snow everywhere.
Let's do this every day!
Uh...
How about once a year?
[LAUGHS]
Okay.
That sounds good.
SHELBY:
And so it was decided,
that once every year,
when the weather got chilly,
that Finn, Jake,
the Ice King,
Beemo,
Princess Bubblegum,
Marceline the Vampire Queen,
Cinnamon Bun,
Peppermint Butler, Phil,
a candy cane man,
one of the Gumdrop Girls,
Lady Rainicorn,
Lumpy Space Princess,
that guy, the other guy,
a pig, Tree Trunks,
a two-headed duck,
the old crazy Tart Toter,
the punch bowl,
a booger, and Gunter
would get together
while wearing
really big sweaters
and watch videos on the floor
next to a fire
to celebrate the day
when Finn and Jake
had a ï¬eeting moment
of empathy
for the biggest weirdo
in Ooo.
It was a miracle.
Good night.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest I'
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!