WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS WENK]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SCREECHES]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
Whew.
Finn! Finn!
Oh, my grarsh.
Finn, it was amazing!
- Wha...?
I had a croak dream, Finn --
my croak dream!
Oh... my glob.
[GIGGLES]
F-For real?
With the cosmic owl
and everything?
Mm-hmm!
Whoa.
A real croak dream.
Yeah, man.
There was a rocket ship.
You weren't there.
And there was a Banana man.
And I ran out of air
in outer space.
[CHUCKLES]
Isn't that -- isn't that
great, Finn?
Yeah.
Well, no. I mean,
I don't want you to die.
And where was I?
I'm your best friend!
Aw, come on, Finn!
There's nothing to
worry about.
Think about it.
I don't know any Banana man,
and rocket ships haven't been
reinvented yet.
I'll probably live another
hundred years, easy.
Um... yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I guess.
[KNOCKING]
Someone's downstairs.
I'll take a look.
Pbbbbbbht!
[WINDOW SLAMS]
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREAM]
Who is it?
It's the Banana man.
Pbbbbbbht!
Shh!
What do we do?
FINN:
I don't know.
Is he still out there?
[WINDOW OPENS]
Ah, no. He left.
Phew. See?
I told you
today wasn't the day.
Hey, you want to make
an ice-cream pizza?
Jake, your croak dream
just gave us the upper hand.
We can cheat now!
We can cheat fate.
[TRICKLING]
We'll track down that
Banana man
and crug up his schemes!
And save you!
[TRICKLING]
Finn, when I die, my
individual Earth consciousness
is gonna go
all over everywhere
while glob tallies my deeds.
What?
I'm gonna be
all around you --
in your nose, in your dreams,
in socks.
I'll be a part of you
and your Earth mind.
It's gonna be great!
Dude, stop... saying...
all this... crazy...
nonsense.
It's making me messed up.
I'm 13.
You're messing me up.
No one can change
a croak dream, Finn, okay?
Not even you.
We'll see about that!
Come on!
Wait. Just let him
walk a few more steps.
Why?
Because that idiot's
about to walk right into the sun
and burn up.
And we'll be done with him.
No, man, he's walking
into his house.
Oh, what?
He built his house on the sun?
This guy's insane!
Finn, did you eat
your breakfast?
No. Why?
Because you forgot how
the sun works.
The sun is actually far away.
It's not sitting right
on the horizon.
Oh. Right on.
Let's chase after him!
You got to eat
your breakfast, man.
You need that protein.
Helps your brain.
Yeah, yeah.
Whatever you say, mom.
Let's go!
Come on.
[UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
What's he doing
with that glass?
[CLUNK]
Whoa.
Just like in my dream!
[GRUNTS]
Huh? Hmm.
[GRUNTING]
Yeah!
Here we go! Yo!
Jake, stop talking
about your croak dream.
Makes me uncomfortable.
Dude, just accept it.
No, dude!
What are you doing,
man?! Aah!
Hand me some leaves
and twigs and stuff.
[RUSTLING]
Hmm.
[CLAPS]
I blows]
[FLAMES ROAR]
Aah! Wait!
You're not gonna kill him,
are you?!
No, man!
Just a warning shot,
to scare him
into moving far away
from here!
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BOTH SCREAM]
Hmm.
Yeah! Look out! Whoo-hoo!
[LAUGHS]
[HUMS]
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
[LAUGHS]
Do it! Yeah!
Oh. yeah!
[LAUGHS]
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Ha ha!
[GRUNTING]
Yeah, baby! Move it!
Moving it!
Work it!
[LAUGHS]
I'm gonna try and shoot
this arrow again.
Careful, man.
I want to be alive
for my croak.
BANANA MAN:
There's a move!
[WHOOSH!]
[PLINK! PLINK!]
[PLONK! CLONK!]
BOTH:
Whoa!
[CLONG!]
Don't worry, Jake.
We're gonna get this guy.
Dude, man, I appreciate
why you're doing this,
but you're not gonna stop me
from transcending
into glob world.
I'm gonna cry, man.
If you say that one more time,
I'm gonna...
let's go fetch that first
arrow to reuse.
'Cause we're out of arrows.
[GASPS]
Huh?
Oh!
The rocket from my
croak dream!
Oh, man.
I guess...
I guess this is it.
I've got to embrace destiny!
Shushers!
You're not getting
on that rocket.
[GRUNTS]
Jakel!
You can't stop destiny,
Finn!
Jake!! No!!
[BLOWING]
Huh? No, man!
[BOTH GRUNT]
Huh?
What in the --
[GASPS]
No! N-No! No!
I-It's not ready yet!
[GRUNTING, YELLING]
Yeah!
[GROANS]
No.
Banana man!
Get your butt on board!
We've got a date
with destiny!
No!
Get off!
You can't mess with fate!
No!
I'm not gonna let you die!
- Finn!
- Don't do this!
- Finn.
- No!
Finn.
Let me go.
[SNIFFLING]
Please. Please.
You have to let me go.
[SNIFFLING]
No. Please.
Destiny!!
[CRACKLING]
There's not enough boom-boom
stick hole sticks
in the stick hole!
- Jake.
- Take care, brother.
You weren't by my side
in my croak dream,
but I'm glad you're here
to see me off.
That's right.
I wasn't in his dream.
That means...
[CRACKLING]
Ahh... see you on the
other side!
[ENGINE REVS]
[ROCKET RATTLES]
[SCREAMS]
[GLASS TINKLING]
[POWER SHUTS OFF]
Huh?
[CREAKING]
[CLANGING]
[GROANS]
Am I...
in glob world?
[CRUNCHING]
[SCREAMING]
Jake!
[GRUNTS]
Jake, I'm coming with you!
[SCREAMING]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYS]
[GURGLING]
[SLOSHING]
Hey, don't try to stop me, Finn!
[GURGLING]
No, it's okay.
I'm here to stay
by your side.
Thanks, man.
I knew you'd come around.
[CREAKING]
[WHOOSH]
[GASPING]
[SQUELCH!]
[COUGHING]
Easy there, buddy.
I... just wanted... to borrow
some sugar.
Ooh!
[SIGHS]
Poor Banana man.
So I guess that wasn't a real
croak dream, after all.
Didn't really come together
quite right.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
Hey. So, wait.
In the croak dream, it was
just me and Banana man.
But this time,
you were here, too.
So... it must be destined
to happen again...
when you're not around.
Well, in that case,
I'll just have to never leave
your side ever again
for the rest of our lives.
[CHUCKLES]
Hmm.
What are you doing?
[CREEPILY] I can never leave
your side ever again
for the rest of our lives.
Get off of me!
- Rest of our lives!
- No!
FINN:
I know where you live!
JAKE:
No! Come on!
FINN:
Whoo-oo-oo! Whoo-oo!
JAKE:
I know you're not a ghost, Finn!
Stop chasing me!
Yeah, ha!
Whoo-hoo! Ha ha!
[HUMS]
Ha ha! Wha!
Yeah, ha ha!
[CLAP, CLAP]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!