WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
And so, through my experiments
with cloud seeding,
I've invented...
liquid pyrotechnics.
[FIREWORKS WHISTLING]
That's really cool, PB!
Aw, thanks, puppy-
Isn't it cool, Finn?
[STAMMERS GULPS]
[GIGGLES]
Uh... Finn, no.
Come on, Finn.
Don't be weird.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Look, I'll see
you guys later.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
BOTH:
Ohh!
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
It's letting up.
Hey, Finn, come on.
Let's go do somethin'.
[SIGHS]
Beemo, put on a game.
[VIDEO-GAME MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ I can't keep pushing
this down any deeper ♪
♪ Why do I keep trying
if I can't keep her? ♪
♪ Every move I make is just
another mistake ♪
♪ I wonder what it would take,
because it feels like there's
a hole inside my body ♪
♪ Like there's a hole
inside my heart ♪
♪ It's like this feeling is
gonna consume me ♪
♪ If I keep waiting for this
thing to start ♪
♪ Oh, I feel like
I'm all gummed up inside ♪
♪ It's like I'm all
gummed up inside ♪
♪ It's like I'm all gummed up
insi-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-de ♪
[SIGHS]
Oh, Finn.
Uncle Jake's got to find you
a new love interest.
Finn, I'm going out for a quick...
walk in the woods.
[GROANS]
Beemo, you look after him
with your camera eyes.
If anyone tries to hurt Finn,
I will kill them!
Okay, good.
♪ Gotta find a honey
for my homey ♪
♪ A baby for my buddy ♪
[AS BARRY WHITE]
♪ A lady for my laddie ♪
[VOICE IN DISTANCE]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[NORMAL VOICE]
Woman!
WOMAN:
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
I'll save you, Washtub Princess!
Aah!
[GRUNTS]
You're safe now, miss...
Flambe?!
Yeah, it's me.
Betcha thought it was a dame,
on account of my girlish screamin'.
I did think that.
Ha ha.
Well, thanks anyway, brother.
Hey, you're pretty plugged-in, Flambe.
Do you know any princesses Finn's age?
Oh, yeah, I know just the skirt,
and she's way hot.
JAKE:
She's from Fire Kingdom?
Think I'll die if I go in there.
Heh. Oh, yeah.
[INCANTING]
[SPITS]
Ow!
There -- I cast "flame shield"
on youse.
Also, I spat on youse.
[GROWLS]
Beemo-cam on.
Goldurn you,
tear ducts!
[GRUNTING]
Ugh. Hang in there, buddy.
[GASPS]
[ANGELIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Uh, yo! What up?
I'm Jake -- Jake the do-
Ohhhhh!
Dude, you gotta pretend like
you're of royal blood.
Coulda told me that sooner.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
JAKE:
Good morrow, majesty!
I am Sir Jake,
Baron of the Grasslands.
Hmm.
What is it you seek?
Speak!
Uh... uh...
I come as an envoy of Prince Finn.
A prince?
[CROWD MURMURS EXCITEDLY]
Yeah, and he's the same age
as your daughter.
Hmm?
Bold words, but know you that
my daughter is a rare jewel.
She cannot be wooed by just
any ragamuffin prince.
Um...
Oh!
Prince Finn is...
awesome!
An awesome prince!
That's the best kind!
Silence, my molten mamas.
We are perplexed.
If you are a baron true,
where is your gift?
'Tis common practice among
visiting dignitaries.
Yeah, the gift --
where is the gift?
You're blowin' it, bromide.
A gift?
Sire, Prince Finn sent...
uh, three gifts!
What?!
Hmm.
Three is more than one.
Three's a lot of gifts.
I want three gifts.
Ooh!
The first gift is,
um... um... um...
this water bottle!
Whoop!
[LAUGHS GOOFILY]
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
[GASPS]
Prince Finn has smote my jester!
Pourquoi?!
I do hate my jester.
Uh... Prince Finn hated him, too.
Hmm!
For your second gift,
a... uh... hmm...
[LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh!
A serenade!
That Finn wrote...
for milady.
Ohhhh!
♪ Oh, Flame Princess ♪
♪ I think you're rad ♪
♪ I really want to kiss you ♪
♪ right in front of your dad ♪
♪ 'cause I think you're great ♪
♪ I wanna be your mate ♪
♪ or maybe go on a date ♪
♪ 'Cause it feels like there's
a fire inside my body ♪
♪ like there's a fire
inside my heart ♪
♪ It's like this fire is
gonna consume me ♪
♪ if I keep waiting for this
thing to start ♪
♪ Oh, I feel like I'm all
warmed up inside ♪
♪ I feel
all warmed up inside ♪
♪ I feel all warmed up
insi-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-de ♪
[SIGHS]
"A fire inside my body"?!
I am disgusted!
Give me your third terrible gift
and be on your way!
Aw, Finn.
I'm sorry, bro.
[SOBBING]
Beemo, go away!
BEEMO:
Whoop.
Duck, duck, duck...
goose!
FINN:
Aaaaaaah!
Is that him?
He looks terrible!
Why isn't he here?
Why did he send his buffoon?
Leave now, buffoon,
for you have failed!
No, wait!
Uh... um...
Prince Finn is here!
He's ri-i-i-ight... here!
[HIGH-PITCHED]
Greetings, Flame King.
My final gift is your favorite
thing in the world.
A koala bear?
Uh... yes!
[GRUNTS]
[DEEP VOICE]
Eucalyptus!
I don't like koalas anymore.
Begone!
[SNIFFLES]
Dude, don't cry!
Can't help it.
I'm in love with Bubblegum!
She's too old for you.
- I don't care!
- Come on.
Flame Princess seems into you.
- No, no, no! Only Bubblegum!
[CHOMPS]
Ow! Finn?
[STRAINED]
Finn! Finn!
Finn, stop!
[CHOKING]
[GRUNTS]
Fi-i-i-i-nn!
[GASPS]
- KING: Excellent!
- Huh?
You have indeed proven
yourself.
Any prince ruthless enough
to kill his own buffoon
would make an excellent boyfriend...
Yeah!
...for my evil daughter!
What?!
She's an unstoppable force
of destruction.
Ahhhhh!
Nothing a psycho like you
can't handle.
Congratulations!
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy to meet you, Prince.
You're my prince.
That's so sweet!
- She seems normal.
- Yeah, she seems normal.
Stop whispering!
Hey!
So that's where I came from.
You know, on second thought,
we're...
not really each ether's types.
We're... what?
I changed my mind.
I don't like you.
You... what?!
Uh, nothing!
Bye, Flambe!
Finn! I really messed up!
[CRASH]
Finn, buddy,
you got to help me!
I made a mistake!
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
Aaaaaah!
Who lit that fire?!
I'll kill you!
[RUMBLING]
[GRUNTS]
Bubblegum's rockets!
Don't you touch her stuff!
[FIREWORKS WHISTLING]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[MOANS]
It's a girl!
[GRUNTS]
You!
What's wrong with me, huh?!
You don't like me?!
I like you!
What's wrong with you?!
Don't ever mess with me again!
Who was that?
The princess of the Fire Kingdom.
Dude...
I think I have a crush.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪