WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[ mouse squeaks]
[ penguins chirp]
[all cheering ]
[screeches]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ the fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
FINN:
[ yawns]
All right.
What do you want to see next?
A cheetah!
A fart!
A cookie!
An external hard drive!
Oh, oh!
Change into Finn
but give him my body!
Beemo, your ideas
are boring.
What? Your head on my body
isn't boring.
It's weird.
[giggles]
All right, I'll try to turn
into a cheetah farting.
Pbfffffffffffffffffffffffffffft!
I can't do the spots.
[shimmering, rustling ]
Sparkles in the house?
Let's squish 'em!
[ both grunting ]
BOTH:
Hyah!
Did you squish
the sparkles?
No. They were around
this holo-message player.
It's got a cartridge with it.
Oh, snap!
Well, plop that cartridge
in the slot, playa!
Yeah! Okay!
[ power surges]
[clears throat ]
Hello, boys.
[ coughing ]
BOTH:
Dad!
If you're hearing this
pre-recorded hologram message,
it's because I've passed on
and my spirit sparkles
guided you
to its secret hiding place.
Right now, I'm holding both
of you in my hands.
You're both still little,
squishy babies.
[ squish!]
FINN:
[ crying ]
JAKE:
[giggles ]
[ squish!]
[ crying continues ]
I made you boys something.
It's a dungeon --
a proper dungeon
full of evil monsters,
traps, and magic --
the whole kazoo!
- JAKE: Kickin'!
- FINN: Whoa, kickin'!
Now, this next part of the
message is just for you, Jake,
so, Finn, cover your ears.
Jake, really this dungeon
is for Finn.
I wanna make something
that'll force Finn to
toughen up.
What?
All right, tell Finn to
uncover his ears now.
Dude, take your hands
off your head.
What?!
All right, boys, now, to give
you some incentive,
at the end of the dungeon,
I'm putting the family sword.
It's made out
of demon's blood.
[growls]
- Whoa! What the...?
- Oh, dang!
Give me back my blood,
Joshua!
Kee oth rama pancake!
Aaaaaaaargh!
- Whoa!
- Geez Louise!
DAD:
The dungeon's 80 paces west of here
under a dumb-looking rock.
And, Finn, this dungeon's gonna
kick your tail.
I bet you won't even get past
the first trial,
you whiny baby.
What?
What was that about?
Uh... I dunno.
Duhh. Duhh. Duhhh.
[laughs goofily]
Whoo!
Whoa!
Burgers and hot dogs!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
[ panting ]
- FINN: Wait, Jake!
- But... burgers and hot dogs.
Didn't you say you were
hungry for burgers this morning?
Yeah. So?
And I said I was hungry
for hot dogs?
Mm-hmm. I remember.
I don't think those
burgers and hot dogs
are burgers and hot dogs
at all.
Aaaaaaaaaaah...
Boom!!
[speaking gibberish ]
Yaaaaaaah!
Ew.
Duhhh.
Hyah!
Ahhhh.
Dude!
Look!
Finn, cover up those nubs
on your head.
[ clicks tongue]
Man, again?
All right, Jake, I wanna remind
you what this dungeon's for.
In order for Finn to stop whining,
he needs to be put through a trial
that forces him to take charge
of a situation.
But, Dad, Finn's
already figured that out.
He's a good kid
with a kind heart.
Remember, Jake, this is
a pre-recorded holo-message.
I can't hear you if you're
talking to me right now.
I'm gonna go walk
around!
Okay!
Jake, I need your help.
You got to call Finn
a whiny baby.
- But --
- Butts are for pooping.
Do it for Poppy.
Finn?!
- Over here!
Check it out, Jake.
I found two ways.
This way has some kind
of flower trap,
and that way...
has that guy.
None shall pa-a-a-a-ss!
Ugh!
Let's take the flower path.
Mm.
Wait! Why don't you want
to take my path?
Because you're super
gross, man.
Oh.
[sighs heavily]
Cheer up, man.
We're only telling you you're
gross because we're your bros.
Really?
Yeah. Bros are real
with each other.
And you're gross, brother.
Take a bath.
Thanks, brother.
[laughs]
[ chuckles]
No probs.
Hey, what did Dad say?
Um...
He said he's surprised
a whiny baby like you
made it this far.
What? Why's Dad saying
all that jive?
Mrnh.
Jake, do it for Poppy!
[sighs heavily]
Because you cry
like a baby, baby!
Dude, you're picking
on me, too?
[women giggling ]
Whoa.
I don't even cry much.
I only cry when it's healthy,
like when people die.
[seductively]
Partake of the fruit.
Pfth! Blech! Ugh.
If I didn't cry
when people died,
I'd have a cold butt
for a heart.
[singsong voice]
The fru-u--u-it.
"Waaaah!
I cry when people die!
Waaaah! I'm Finn!"
Partake of the fruit.
Maybe I will partake
of the fruit!
WOMEN:
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah, fruit!
- Dude, don't eat that!
- Why not?
All the people that I care about
in this world
are being wads.
- Ohh...
Don't you blow Poppy's cover!
[distorted voice]
N-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
Whoa.
[ both laughing evilly]
Time to go, baby.
Finn, come on!
I'm gonna hang here
with these fruit babes.
They'll be my best buds now.
[growls]
Yah!
[ pants]
[ both screeching ]
[ farts]
[gas hissing ]
[ both screaming ]
JAKE:
There's another cartridge!
Pbffffffffffffffffffft!
All right, man, Dad told me not
to tell you this, but --
Don't tell him!
You're not real.
[smooch! ]
Dad asked me
to call you "baby"
'cause he wants you
to be tough.
But I'm tough!
My whole body is a callus!
Ugh.
On this next holo-message
we listen to,
when Dad tells you to
cover your ears...
don't.
Hmph.
Hey, hey!
Finn! Jake!
You made it past
the fruit witches.
Hey, did they make you cry,
Finn, huh? Huh?
[laughs]
I bet they did.
All right.
Now cover your ears, Sue.
Jake, I'm almost done
with this dungeon.
I just have one last monster to
fit into this pit I dug.
I got him tied up in this room
I'm building.
It's really hard trying
to fit him in this pit.
He's pretty evil.
[chuckles]
You're gonna have a crazy time
trying to defeat --
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
BOTH:
Dad!
Dad's sword!
Hey, Jake, when Finn finishes
this dungeon,
play this tape
for him.
Finn...
- Ugh!
... this pre-recorded
holo-message...
[ chuckles]
[laughing maniacally]
Finn!
Oof!
[laughing continues]
Dude!
Use your karate biz!
Ugh. I -- oof!
I can't, man!
I suck!
I'm a whiny baby,
and I'm fat
and all those things
Dad said about me!
Dude! Dad loves you!
Ugh!
[laughing maniacally]
Finn, if you're seeing this
pre-recorded holo-message,
it's because you've finished
the dungeon that I made.
I'm proud of you.
You're gonna do great things
in this world.
I love you, son.
[grunts]
[laughs maniacally]
[ message rewinds]
♪ [ beatboxing ] ♪
♪ Yo, Finn -- ♪
♪ I'm proud -- ♪
♪ I love you -- you --
you, son ♪
FINN:
Yah! Hunh! Hyah!
DAD:
♪ Yo, Finn -- ♪
♪ I made -- this message --
for you ♪
♪ [ beatboxing continues] ♪
♪ For you -- for you
The dungeon -- for you -- ♪
♪ This world -- for you -- ♪
♪ This message -- it's --
for you -- ♪
♪ Finn -- You're gonna do
great --great --great -- ♪
♪ You're gonna do great
things -- things -- ♪
♪ You're gonna do
great --great --great -- ♪
[ beatboxing, rewinding stop]
Duhh.
DAD:
I made you boys something.
It's -- babies --
full of -- babies.
[ message rewinding ]
The family sword --
It's made out of -- babies.
You know I don't think
you're a baby, right?
Yeah, I know.
That sword is sweet.
Yeah. I'm stoked to
slay some evil with it.
Joshua,
return my blood to me,
or, by demon's law, I will
cut off your love handles!
Joshua!
We go way back!
Come on!
Just give me back my blood!
Kee oth rama pancake!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaarghh!
FINN:
Man, Dad was cool.
JAKE: Yeah.
[ both laugh ]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander
through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪