WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[ mouse squeaks]
[ penguins chirp]
[all cheering ]
[screeches]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[thunder crashing ]
[wind gusts]
This stanks.
Hey, how much longer till we
get to the mysterious party?
Let me check the spooky
invite sent to us by
our anonymous host.
Oh. We're here.
Party's in that castle.
[thunder crashes]
It's for us!
What's it say?
"Wear me."
BOTH:
"Wear me"?
[ both whistle]
Hello?
BUBBLEGUM:
Yoo-hoo!
Hey, guys!
Princess Bubblegum,
is that you?
Why, yes, indeed.
Although, according to the
invitation, we're supposed to
use mystery names, and mine is
"Lady Quiet Bottom."
My name is
"Duchess Gummybuns."
I am "Professor Pants."
I'm "Cinnamon Bun."
What's the name
on your invite?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, it's "Guy Farting."
"Prince Hotbod"
at your service.
I'm "Randy Butternubs."
So, who's our host,
anyways?
Nobody knows.
Maybe he'll be a steaming-hot
babe with huge money.
Tut, tut,
Lumpy Space Princess.
What would your boyfriend,
Brad, say?
Brad and I broke up
a long time ago.
Duh!
[all gasp]
Now's my chance!
No...way!
But I can make you happy.
Puke off, you big doughnut!
Okay.
Excuse me,
"Guy Farting,"
there's an envelope
on your back.
[grunting ]
Where? Where?
FINN:
Here -- let me.
Did you put that
envelope on him?
No. Nope.
- Unh-unh.
I didn't do it.
No.
What's it say,
"Prince Hotbod"?
[ clears throat ]
"Esteemed Guests,
I am your host.
I am a ghost."
[all gasp]
"By the time you finish reading
this, I will possess one of you
and use your body to murder
every...one in the house."
[all gasp]
Aah!
We got to get out of here!
FINN:
C.B., wait.
It says anyone who tries
to leave will die!
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no!
Ergh!
[thunder crashes]
[all scream ]
He's dead!
Yeah, right.
What do you mean,
"Yeah, right"?
Come on.
You don't remember when
I pulled this same trick
on your birthday?
I used the
fake skeletons to
make you think
everyone was dead.
It looks real to me.
Psh! Classic move.
Dude, I swear
I'm not pranking you.
Cinnamon Bun is dead.
The question is,
who killed him?
One of us is possessed
by a murderer,
and if we want
to stay alive,
we have to figure out who's
hiding a ghost inside
their mortal body.
Beemo!
- Aah!
Use your ghost-detecting
equipment to screen everyone.
[ high-pitched whining ]
[ camera shutter clicks]
I blinked my balls --
my eyeballs.
[ camera shutter clicks]
[giggles]
BEEMO:
Hmm.
What do you mean, "Hmm"?
Nothing.
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
Did you just see that?
LUMPY SPACE PRINCESS:
Oh, I knew it.
I knew it was Jake.
Processing data...
- Ew.
- Huh?
So, who's the ghost, Beemo?
Oh.
Um, I don't have
ghost-detecting equipment.
I just like taking
nice pictures.
Let's find some candles.
If the lights
go out again,
we'll be able to
catch the murderer.
Good idea.
Jake and Beemo,
you guys check downstairs,
and we'll
take this floor.
Okay.
[thunder rumbles]
JAKE:
Lay truth on me, Beemo.
Is Finn pulling some
elaborate prank on me?
No, Jake.
When bad things happen,
I know you want to believe
they are a joke.
But sometimes,
life is scary and dark.
That is why we must
find the light.
Aha!
[ crack]
Found it!
Ooh!
[ chuckles]
Thanks, Beemo.
Beemo?
Help!
Jake, help!
Beemo?
Help!
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Oh, my crease!
Assemble!
Reassemble!
Come on, you guys!
Where's Beemo?
The ghost got him.
Don't you mean you got him...
Ghost?!
You guys, if there really
is a ghost killer,
then we should
stay in a group.
He can't take us all
on if we're in a group.
[screaming in distance]
LSP, where are you?!
Are you okay?
JAKE:
It sounds like she's in there.
LSP:
Aah! I'm dying!
[toilet flushes]
Whew!
Oh, gross. Ugh!
My lumping body's
all hollow now.
I got to put
something in it.
So, where's the food?
What kind of
castle is this?
It's like a poor
people's castle,
with no lumping waffles
for my dump truck!
Chill out, girl.
You find any candles upstairs?
No.
Well, I dropped a lighter
downstairs,
but there's no way
I'm going back for that.
Uh-huh.
Let me remind y'all
that the invite says
"The ghost will possess
one of our bods."
LSP:
Not my bod.
Someone at this table isn't
who they appear to be.
That's right...
"Jake."
So let me ask you a question
only the real Jake could answer.
FINN:
Who is always next to me in my
recurring elevator dreams?
A half-orc Shaman.
Okay, you're Jake.
So, who else was absent
when Beemo got nabbed?
Oh, yeah, right.
I'm not the ghost.
I was in the potty house.
A convenient alibi.
But tell me this...
Why did you break
up with Brad?
Only the real LSP
would know that.
Pshaw!
As if you even know
the answer to that, Jake!
You're right.
I'm just feeling gossipy, and
I want to know what happened.
That's none of your
lumping business!
Sounds suspicious.
I bet you're the ghost!
She did it!
She's possessed!
Tie her up!
Oh, she is,huh?
Well, before we tie up LSP,
answer me this...
LSP:
Brad --
He kissed me on the mouth,
and I was like, "Bleh!
Bleh! Bleh!"
And then I was like,
"Oh, gross!
Go away, Brad!"
And he was like, "Obvi,
you're not ready for me."
But what does that even mean,
you guys?
[sobs]
What does it lumping mean?
[whimpers]
But answer me this,
Princess...
LUMPY SPACE PRINCESS:
What do you want from me, Brad?!
You said I was
the hottest one!
Isn't that enough?!
Why'd you have to --
[sobbing ]
What did I write to you
on your "Happy Birthday" card
two years ago?
Word for word.
Finn, there's no way
I would remember that.
I remember that.
You're not PB!
Tie you up!
[gasps]
What?!
Wait, you guys!
[gasps]
Look!
[wails]
A real ghost?!
Aah! Don't touch me!
Don't touch me!
[ hollow thud ]
Da-a-a-a-a-a-g!
This wasn't supposed
to h-h-happen!
Aha!
I knew you were pranking
me back, you!
Yeah, i-it was
all a setup --
the doors,
Cinnamon Bun and Beemo.
Oh, Striz!
Beemo and Cinnamon Bun should
be in the closet over there.
Guys! Guys, guys!
Come on, you gu--
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Oh, my Glob!
I can't take this,
you guys.
I'm calling my
lumping parents right now.
[thunk! ]
Aaaaah! Aaaaaaaaaah!
FINN:
LSP, what's happening?!
Aaaaah!
Oh, my glob!
I'm not ready!
Get away!
Oh, gross!
Aaaaaaah!
Where did she go?!
Look!
I'm scared, Bro.
[evil laughter]
Run, homey! Run!
FINN:
Open it!
[grunts]
It won't open!
Muh! Aah!
Whoooooo!
BOTH:
Aaaaah!
Oof!
Come on!
Okay.
Oh! Jake!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
I got a splinter!
Jakey!
Whaaa!
Don't let go, man!
FINN:
Oh, no!
Your fancy glo-o-o-o-ves!
Aaaaaaah!
[ plop! ]
Unh!
Jake!
Princess!
[warbling ]
Ugh!
Unh!
[ crows squawking ]
[ panting ]
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Ha-haaa!
Gotcha, dude!
Two for two.
What?!
I figured out your plan months
ago, so I flipped the script.
Oh, yeah!
So everyone's okay --
Beemo, Cinnamon Bun?
Yeah. See?
Whoa! Sick!
You can phase people
into your body?
[speaking Korean ]
I'm ready for you now,
Brad.
Isn't that Obvi?
I'm so ready.
But, PB,
you melted.
It was a wax dummy, Dummy.
Jake switched me out while
lady was distracting you.
Wow. You got me again.
I can't believe that --
With the
hair and the house
coming alive and stuff.
The what?
The walls and chairs trying
to eat me and stuff.
Eh, no.
You must have been so scared,
you imagined that part.
Um...no, I didn't.
Ha ha. Nice try, Finn.
Let's get out of here.
[warbling ]
That one's going
in the vault.
And...
It's gone.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!