WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[ZOMBIES GROANING]
[ALL PANTING]
Hurry, Lady!
[DOOR SLAMS]
[PANTING]
Oh, it's happening again.
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
That's right, Finn.
Princess!
The zombie infection has spread
across the kingdom once again.
And once again,
it's all my fault.
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM: I was testing
a sample of the zombie flesh I had saved
when Cinnamon Bun
came into the lab.
He said he was hungry.
I'm hungry-
Not now, Cinnamon Bun.
I'm busy.
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
And that's when I made my mistake.
I should have paid more
attention to that poor fool.
Huh?
[SLURP!]
Mmm!
[MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH!]
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
The candy-zombie flesh he ingested
was highly contagious.
[GROANS]
[THUD!]
[GROWLS]
Cinnamon Bun?
Where did you -- eeek!
[GROWLING]
Sugar!
I escaped, but I wasn't able
to stop Cinnamon Bun
from infecting
the rest of the kingdom.
The good news is I still
have all my notes
for making
the antidote formula.
Oh, sweet!
Let's board up the windows,
then we can get started.
Owww! Aaaah!
Princess!
Don't worry, Finn.
You have the notes for my formula.
Just let Science do the work.
Science... is...
mmmmoraaaah!
Noooo!
LSP:
Get that zombie out of here!
[WHACK!]
[SCREAMS]
Oh, no.
I am not getting eaten
by zombies tonight.
[MOANS]
Get the lump out of here!
Oh, Princess!
These notes make no sense.
It's all gobbledy gak.
We'll each make our
own version of the formula.
One of us is bound
to get it right.
[RAT SQUEAKING]
Hmm?
Hey, Princess Bubblegulm
trained her rat to dance.
Neat!
[BUBBLE!]
Ah! All right!
Ahh.
Oh, yes!
[LAUGHS]
Done!
BOTH:
Bubblegum, I'm coming
for you!
[ZOMBIES GROWLING]
Mine first.
[BABBLING]
[GROWLS]
BOTH:
Aah!
[GROWLS]
[GASPING]
[CHOMP!]
Rarr!
TOGETHER:
Sugar!
Cram!
STARCHIE:
Oh, my!
That's a lot of zombies down there.
Starchy's glad he's up here,
♪ Doot do-do-doo ♪
Aah! Daaaaaaang itttttttttt!
- Aah!
- Let's get out of here!
Upstairs!
[ALL PANTING]
Jake, try yours and Lady's next.
Move out of the way!
My formula is going to cure the zombies
because I made the prettiest formula.
[ZOMBIES MOANING]
Aah!
[GROWLS]
[SMOOCH! SMOOCH! SMOOCH!]
Ohm my... glob!
Look at those luscious lips!
I got to go lick up
the rest of that formula.
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
My formula!
[GRUNTING]
Formula!
Oh, my glob! Yes!
I'm gonna be so hot!
So freaking hot!
[UNCONVINCING LAUGH]
Yeah!
LSP, look out!
Huh?
I know you want this body,
but you can't have it!
You can't have it!
[CHOMP! MUNCH! CHOMP!]
Oww!
[GROWLING]
[ZOMBIES GASP]
BOTH:
Aah! LSP!
Dang it, Jake.
We only got one formula left.
Try yours and Lady's.
Right.
Let's hope this works.
[ZOMBIES MOANING]
[ALL GROWLING]
BOTH:
Aah!
Whe-- where now?
We can barricade
ourselves in the lab.
[BOTH PANTING]
Did anyone get bit?
I think we're good.
That door's made out of
candy steel.
- Aaah!
- What's the matter?
[GROWLS]
FINN:
Jake! Did he get you?
I think I'm okay.
It's just a little bite.
Uh...
Aah!
- Jake!
- It's all good, sweetie.
I can stretch forever.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, let's hurry up
with that antidote, huh, pal?
Oooooooooooohhhhhhh.
Okay, let's see here.
Nyah, nyah, nyah.
Try one of them books
over by the lab rat.
Ha! Yeah, okay!
Yes!
This book is a glossary of symbols.
[PANTING]
That's great, buddy.
[KNOCKING ON GLASS]
Jake, I think this little guy's
got serious dance fever.
[PANTING]
Don't come near me, sweetie.
Oh, man. I'm out of shape.
I think I should just
stay in here.
You know...
just in case.
Uh-oh!
Hurry, dude!
- I am!
Okay, Jake's probably gonna
turn into a zombie,
which is okay.
I just have to figure out
this formula.
Jake?
[GROWLS]
Jake!
Hang on, Lady.
I'll have the antidote soon.
But whatever you do,
just don't let him out.
He might look like the Jake
that once loved you,
but he's just a zombie.
[SPEAKING KOREAN]
[CHOMP!]
Hey, Lady.
Aah!
BOTH:
[GROWLING]
[CLANGING]
[ZOMBIES GROWLING]
The book!
[POUNDING]
[GLASS CRACKS]
[WHIMPERS]
[SIGHS]
Sorry, everybody.
Sorry, LSP, P.B., Jake,
L.R., Peepee, Poopoo, Doodoo.
[SIGHS]
You know, it's funny.
I don't even know your name.
[SQUEAKS]
Yeah?
What is it, girl?
Sci... ence?
Your name is Science?
Could it be?
Just let Science do the work.
Science... is...
mmmmoraaaah!
Hmm.
[ZOMBIES GROWL]
[UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING]
Is that it'?
[SQUEAKS]
[WHOOSH!]
[PWOOH!]
Here goes nothing.
[DRIP! DRIP!]
Finn!
Jake!
You did it!
I -- huh? Uh-oh.
Aaah!
[CHOMP! CHOMP! CHOMP!]
[GROWLS]
[SLAM! CRACK!]
[GASPS]
[SLAM!]
Don't worry, Science.
I've got a disgusting idea.
Oh, my glob!
I'm sorry about the whole
biting thing.
No, you weren't yourself.
It was really nothing personal.
[CHUCKLES]
Sorry about biting you, sugar.
[SPEAKING KOREAN]
[GIGGLES]
Oh!
And so the royal day of apologizing
has come to an end.
And now I shall present
the royal medal
for heroic bravery.
Finn the human!
- Yes?
Would you please move out of the way?
Science the rat,
you have served your kingdom well.
Citizens of Candy Kingdom, rejoice!
[ALL CHEERING]
Rejoice!
[CHEERING LOUDER]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪