WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[ mouse squeaks]
[ penguins chirp]
[all cheering ]
[screeches]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ the fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Faster! She's in danger!
Who is he talking
about?
I have no idea.
What?!
Then why am I running so hard?
Because...
Because she's in trouble!
BOTH:
Who is?
Marceline!
Faster, Jake!
She's in trouble!
Hey, wizard, how do you know
Marceline?
I'm... her spirit animal.
Oh.
[ both gasp]
Marceline!
What's wrong with her?!
She accidentally cast a sleep
spell on herself,
and now she's trapped
in eternal slumber.
Tell us how to break
the spell.
I'll transport you into
Marceline's mind,
where you will walk
through her memories
and find the memory core.
Then what?
Find the memory of Marceline
casting the sleep spell
on herself.
At your touch,
you and the memory
will be transported back
to reality.
But, like,
if you know all this,
why not just do it
yourself?
Entering a person's mind
can be dangerous,
and I don't have
any arms -- just legs.
[grunts]
Oh, yeah.
Here we go.
Ungh!
What?
What did you do
to my forehead?
When you get close
to the memory,
your forehead will glow.
Here. Take this.
WIZARD:
It's a sack of magic powder.
Sit on the couch and sprinkle
the powder on your head.
Like this?
Yep. Like that.
Feel sleepy?
[ both yawn ]
BOTH:
Mm-hmm.
Good.
Sleep now.
But know this!
- BOTH: Huh?!
If you fail,
Marceline will be trapped
in eternal sleep...
forever!
[ both gasp]
And ever! And ever!
[whoosh! ]
[thud! ]
[ yawns]
Did it work?
I-I can't tell.
I don't feel like I'm inside
Marceline's memories.
Me neither.
Huh?
[ cra-a-a-a-a-a-a-ck! ]
Whoa!
So... if we're
in Marceline's memories,
where's Marceline?
Hmm.
There she is!
Hey, Li'l Marcy.
Who are you guys?
- We're Finn and Jake.
- We're your friends.
Hambo is my only friend.
See?
You need another eyeball
surgery, pal.
Lucky for you,
we found a donor.
Eyeball!
Nurse, hand me the string.
Yes, doctor.
It's our last piece.
Hold still.
I'm hurting you
because I love you.
[ clears throat ]
What are you guys
still doing here?
We're trying to wake
you up.
Do you know where
your memory core is?
Nope.
But there might be anything
behind that cellar door.
And it rhymes
with "memory core."
Ooh! Ooh!
Could be jams and pickles
down there!
Weird.
I think this door leads
to a new memory...
with food in it.
Ooh! Ice cream!
I want some!
Huh?
[grunts]
[ munches]
[door opens]
Come on, Finn.
[whoosh! Whoosh! ]
[ crash! ]
[ munching ]
Yo, man.
Wha?!
Don't eat those.
Bluh!
Marceline!
[sniffles]
Daddy? Why?
Hmm.
- What?
It's our tree house.
This must be when Marceline
lived here.
[ both grunting ]
Easy. Easy.
You got it?
Yeah.
Aah!
[ chuckles]
I'm so glad we're doing this,
Ash.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, hey. Wait.
Watch this.
I've been practicing.
[twinkle! ]
Marceween!
I wuv! I wuv!
Oh, Ash.
[smooches]
[ chuckles]
Who's this guy supposed
to be?
Ash, I guess.
[whoosh! whoosh! ]
[sighs]
[sniffs]
This place reeks.
Yo, man.
Your thing is glowing.
My what?
Oh, my thing.
We must be
close to the core.
I see another door
over there.
Come on.
Wait a sec, Jake.
It's that guy again.
ASH:
Hey. O-Open your eyes.
Look at this, Mar-Mar.
Check it out.
It's my new wand.
These cherry blossoms -- look.
Look as close as you can,
and they're real.
[zap! ]
Wow. Awesome.
Where'd you get the money
for that thing?
Oh, I sold that teddy bear
that you love so much...
to a witch.
You what?! Are you crazy?!
That was my favorite thing
in the whole world!
That's why it's so valuable,
genius --
for potions.
You're not...
a genius.
That's the last straw, Ash!
That's it!
[sniffles]
You're a psycho jerk,
and you've ruined my life!
But -- but not all of it!
It's over, you psycho!
[stomp! stomp! stomp! stomp! ]
JAKE:
This way, Finn!
Check out this whacked-out
memory crack!
It's banaenae down here!
[whoosh! ]
FINN:
The core!
JAKE:
All these orbs must be her memories!
- How are we supposed
to know which one to grab?
- Play "hot/cold" with
your forehead.
- All right. Hot or cold?
- Cold.
Definitely cold.
[grunts]
Warmer.
Hyup! Ungh!
Warmer!
Whoa! Hot!
Hot, hot, hot!
That must be the one!
[groans]
Wha?
Hey! You have arms!
That's right, genius.
Huh?
You lied to us!
Ah, the important thing is
Marceline's awake.
Marcy! Marcy!
You're okay!
Quit touching my hair!
You had a magic accident,
and we saved you
with some help
from your wizard friend.
That's Ash.
BOTH:
Ash?!
He's not my friend.
He's my boyfriend!
BOTH:
What?!
That's right, babe.
Ash, what's going on?
Just picking up my girl
for a night on the town...
at my place.
[ clicks tongue]
Aw, that's sweet.
[smooches]
BOTH:
What?!
Oh, grow up, you guys.
I'm gonna go freshen up.
That's a relief.
[scoffs]
Oh, Ash.
Wha-a-a-a-t?!
Don't you guys get it?
I out-brained you.
That wasn't the memory
of a sleep spell
you brought me.
That memory was our breakup!
It's over, you psycho!
[ pop! ]
That's enough of that.
Oh, no!
What?!
Yup.
Come on, Mar-Mar.
Let's go.
No! Marceline!
Ashicus flyicus.
[whoosh! ]
[zoom! ]
They're gone, man!
He took her!
Don't worry, Finn!
I got the scent!
[sniffs]
[exhales deeply]
Follow me.
This is it?
I can smell 'em
in there.
So, what's the plan?
Um...
okay, you take that shovel
and keep banging it
against that shed
till Ash comes out to see
what's happening.
Then I'll sneak in,
and I'll rescue Marceline.
Nice.
[grunting ]
[ crash! crash! ]
Aah! My house!
What's happening?!
Wha?
No! Don't hurt me!
No! No, sorry! Ju--
[screaming ]
Shh! Shh! Wait!
Aah! Help!
Somebody help me!
[slam! ]
What's all this hullabaloo?!
Help! Help!
Hey, hold it!
You! Get back here!
Oof!
[ coughing ]
Finn?
Finn, what are you doing?
You can't be here.
Ash doesn't like me hanging out
with mere mortals.
Yeah. Okay.
Sorry, Marceline.
I'll go.
I've just got to show you
something first.
[whoosh! ]
[ coughing ]
Pbtbtbtbtbtbtbt!
[whack! ]
Hello? Finn?
BABY FINN:
♪ I'm a buff baby
that can dance like a man ♪
♪ I can shake-ah my fanny ♪
♪ I can shake-ah my can ♪
♪ I'm a tough-tootin' baby ♪
♪ I can punch-ah your buns ♪
♪ punch-ah your buns ♪
♪ I can punch all your buns ♪
♪ if you're an evil witch ♪
♪ I will punch you for fun ♪
[stifled laughter]
[laughs]
Hey, there you are.
Finn, what's going on?
What is this place?
It's my old house.
That magic powder put you
in my memories.
Me and Jake were in yours
before,
but Ash tricked us into
stealing your memory
of breaking up with him.
But it's okay, 'cause I saw
the missing memory.
Now I have a memory of your
memory in my memory.
See?
Oh, I sold that teddy bear
that you loved so much...
to a witch.
It's over, you psycho!
Finn, I think I'd like
to wake up now.
You gonna be okay,
Marceline?
Yeah.
Thanks, Finn, I just --
Yo, Mar-Mar.
What's -- what's
with the chump?
Come on, I said "no chumps."
Ash gets hungies at 8:00.
You need to get back
in the kitchen
and make me dinner.
[growls]
I want a turkey sandwich
with tomato.
[growls]
Also pickles.
Aah! Oh, my -- oh!
[laughs]
Oh, this is --
[grunting ]
I can't see!
[laughs]
[sighs]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!