WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
I'll kill you!
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We're going to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog and Finn the human ♪
♪ the fun will never end ♪
♪ Adventure Time ♪
Jake?
Beemo?
Hey man, whatcha doing?
Ah! Dude!
Don't worry, bro.
We won't tell anyone about the "private time" you spend with your wad of Princess Bubblegum's hair.
You guys knew?
Finn, we're roommates.
Which is why I'm gonna share my beloved keepsake with you.
Pah-parah-bah!
My old baby blanket.
Who are you?
Noooo!
Come on!
I'll get your kid back, toy!
That guy must do crazy squats.
Get back here you thievy door lord!
You butt!
Come on, Bubblegum.
Finn?
Marceline! Are you okay?
Yeah...
Don't worry, we'll get him.
No!
What?
This door shall yield to no command save for a song from a... genuine band.
What is this gripple-grap?
It's the door of the door lord, Finn.
We used to lock them up, but they kept breaking out... because they're door lords.
They broke out because you let them live.
Hm... door said that it'll open for a genuine band.
Let's try music this door open as a quintet.
Can I be the jerk in the band? Because that's an important part of the band's success.
I know how to get through this door.
We're gonna lay down a chill jam.
Hey! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Just keep it cool. Got that, princess?
Hmph.
Oh!
Oh, my face!
Let's see if you hacks can keep up with my raw talent.
♪ Laradadada ♪
♪ I'm gonna bury you in the ground ♪
♪ I'm gonna bury you with my sound ♪
♪ I'm gonna drink the red from your pretty pink face ♪
♪ I'm gonna- ♪
Marceline, that's too distasteful!
Oh, you don't like that?
Or do you just not like me?!
♪ Sorry I don’t treat you like a goddess ♪
♪ Is that what you want me to do? ♪
♪ Sorry I don’t treat you like you’re perfect ♪
♪ Like all your little loyal subjects do ♪
♪ Sorry I’m not made of sugar ♪
♪ Am I not sweet enough for you? ♪
♪ Is that why you always avoid me? ♪
♪ That must be such an inconvenience to you ♪
♪ Well, I’m just your problem ♪
♪ I’m just your problem ♪
♪ It's like I'm not even a person, am I? ♪
♪ Well, I shouldn’t have to justify what I do ♪
♪ I shouldn’t have to prove anything to you ♪
♪ I’m sorry that I exist ♪
It's working! Look at the door!
♪ I forget what landed me on your blacklist ♪
♪ I’m sorry that I exist ♪
It's working! Look at the door!
♪ I forget what landed me on your blacklist ♪
♪ But I shouldn’t have to be the one that makes up with you ♪
♪ So... why do I want to? ♪
♪ Why do I want to... ♪
♪ To... bury you in the ground ♪
♪ And drink the blood from your... ♪ Ugh!
Stop staring at me!
Ugh, you threw me off!
Come on everybody, don't stop now!
The door was responding to our music!
I wonder what it liked... or what was missing?
Well I know what's missing.
Talent. I'm getting outta here, you hacks.
Talentless hacks!
Yikes!
Maybe to be a genuine band we need to be nicer to each other and hang out as buds!
Let's take a noodle break.
Come on, it'll help!
No, wait, don't go too!
I'm just gonna get stuff to cook that.
Cook...?
That was sweet, what you said about being buds.
Mmhm, thanks!
I'm back, yo!
Come here, baby.
Ooh!
♪ Pasta... Water... Getting... Hotter! ♪
♪ A song about noodles? ♪
No!
For our next attempt, I wanna be the lead.
Yeah! Sounds cool, mah bud.
Humph.
Jake, you're back!
Shut your teeth.
I came back for the music.
Beemo, execute song structure alpha.
Marceline, begin playing triple quavers in the mixolydian mode.
Alright, fine.
Wait, what's a quaver?
Now Finn, vibrate your uvula by dampening and undampening your larynx.
Wha-?
Go like this, silly!
Oh!
Okay... Okay.
Jake, are you gonna join in?
Everyone, just stick to my blueprints!
Oh!
One more time?
I may have... hm...
miscalculated.
Hah! Looks like you aren't as perfect as you thought!
Guess you can't judge me anymore.
I never said you had to be perfect!
Alright, time out, guys.
Princess! Princess, wait!
Whatever.
Ugh, I'm outta here too!
Marceline?
You've all forgotten about the music.
I quit the band!
I'm just pretending!
Jake! Everybody, we can beat the door lord!
...Together.
♪ Everyone... ♪
♪ Bubblegum... ♪
♪ I'm so dumb... ♪
♪ I should have just told you. ♪
♪ What I lost... ♪
♪ Was a piece of your hair. ♪
♪ Now it's gone♪
♪ Gone forever ♪
♪ But I guess, what does it matter when I just... ♪
♪ Just had all of you there? ♪
♪ Oh, I just had all of you there with me, my friends ♪
♪ If you're even my friends... ♪
You like this?
This is what was missing!
The truth!
♪ What am I to you? ♪
♪ Am I a joke, your knight, or your brother? ♪
♪ Do you look down on me 'cause I'm younger? ♪
♪ Do you think that I don't understand? ♪
♪ I just wanted us together and to play as a band ♪
♪ Last night was the most fun I've ever had ♪
♪ Even liked it when the two of you would get mad... ♪
♪ At each other ♪
♪ Oh, you... ♪
♪ Are my best friends in the world ♪
♪ You are my best friends in the world ♪
♪ That's right, I'm talking about the two of you girls ♪
♪ And you, Jake ♪
♪ I wanna sing a song to you and I refuse to make it fake ♪
♪ What am I to you? ♪
♪ Am I a joke, your knight, or your brother? ♪
♪ Do you look down on me 'cause I'm younger? ♪
♪ Do you think that I don't understand? ♪
♪ I just wanted us together and to play as a band ♪
♪ I'll forget that I lost a piece of your hair ♪
♪ I'll remember the pasta that we shared... ♪
♪ Over there ♪
♪ Ah ah, you... ♪
♪ Are my best friends in the world ♪
♪ You are my best friends in the world ♪
♪ And that's right, I'm talking about the two of you girls ♪
♪ And you, Jake ♪
♪ I'm gonna sing a song to you and I refuse to make it fake ♪
♪ Make no mistake, I'm gonna sing a song that feels so real, it'll make this door break ♪
It's over, door lord!
So hand over our stuff!
What's he trying to say?
I totally get it!
He may have stolen our treasures...
But by doing so he showed us...
That the real treasure is friendship!
Okay, here's that lock of Bubblegum's hair you love so much.
Oh, you.
Ugh, yeesh.
And here's Jake's blankie.
Here's your controller, Beemo.
Yippie kiyiyay!
Marceline, here's your... rock shirt.
Hey, that's not-
It's mine! That's mine...
You... kept the shirt I gave you.
Yeah... It, uh... means a lot to me.
But you never wore it.
Dude, I wear it all the time!
As pajamas.
Wait. If that's Bubblegum's shirt, what are you missing, Marceline?
...Wait a second.
Wait a second!
You don't have a thing. You just wanted to hang out with us.
No I didn't.
No way, you're caught!
I figured you out.
Ha ha ha ha ha.