WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[ mouse squeaks]
[ penguins chirp]
[all cheering ]
[screeches]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ the fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[ beeping ]
[splat! ]
[ coughs]
[ yawning ]
Hmm, mm.
Ahh.
[ chomp! gulp! ]
[ munch! munch! munch! ]
Mm.
[ creak! ]
[scratch! scratch! ]
[ patter! patter! patter! ]
[ humming ]
FINN: Ice King,
this is the last time
you steal our
sandwiches!
You don't
understand.
If you were me, you would do
things I would do.
Yeah, and if you were us,
you'd kick your fat butt.
I...
Yeah, I would.
But I wouldn't get past
my invincible armor.
Hyah!
Ha ha!
Not a scratch, boys.
Not a scratch.
It's my time to shine.
[ chirping ]
Ah. Hmm.
Hmm.
[sniff! sniff! sniff! ]
Aah!
[wolves growling ]
Who-o-o-o-o-a!
Whoo!
[ chomp! chomp! ]
[wolf yelps]
[grunts]
[growls]
Hmm.
[ yelps]
[ humming ]
[whoosh! whoosh! ]
[ barking ]
Aah!
[ barks, pants]
[ barking ]
[tap! tap! ]
[ barks]
[whoosh! ]
Hmm.
[ humming ]
[whoosh! ]
[ barking ]
BOTH:
[grunting ]
ICE KING: Fools! Fools!
You're wasting your ti-ime.
[sighs]
[sizzle! ]
[ boom! ]
Whoo! Whoo-oo! Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
Ooh. Oo-ooh
[whoosh! ]
[ barking ]
Pbht!
[ pants]
Uh...
[ creak! ]
Hmm-ah!
[whines]
[shivers, whines]
Aah! Whoo-whoo-whoo!
Aah-oww!
Hmm.
[sighs]
[grunts]
[ barking ]
Ooh!
Whoo! Whoo-whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Hoo-hoo-hoo.
[ barking ]
[ barks]
[ panting ]
[thud! ]
[growls]
Hmm.
Hmm-mm-mm.
Yeah.
Ah!
[ chomp! ]
[gulp! ]
Ooh.
[laughs]
[gags]
[warble! ]
Hmm.
Moo-ohh!
Oww! Oww!
Oww! Aah!
Hmm.
[ music playing ]
♪ Do do do ♪
♪ Do-do, do-da ♪
♪ Do-do-do-deedle ♪
♪ Arf, arf ♪
♪ Do-do-doo ♪
♪ Do-doodle, deedle-doo-doo ♪
♪ Do-do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Blah-blah, hey-hey ♪
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
♪ Howdle-do-do-do ♪
♪ Hey ♪
Whoo!
[ blows]
Oww!
Aah!
Ge-e-ez.
[ cries, whimpers]
Woof!
[ mumbling ]
Nyah!
[ bl-bl-bl-bl-bl! ]
Muh-muh, oh, oh, oh.
[ bang! ]
Uh...
Aah!
[ mumbling ]
[ barking ]
[laughs]
[ humming ]
[snores]
[sighs]
[ fizzle! ]
[wolves howling ]
[whimpers, howls]
[ howling continues]
[groans]
[weakly]
Fools... fools!
Mm.
[ding! ]
Hmm.
In-ice-able vince
armor...
[ beeping ]
[whoosh! ]
[ moans, coughs]
[ creak! ]
[ patter! patter! ]
ICE KING:
Help! Help!
Somebody help me!
Oh! Ho-ho!
Oh, sweet mama!
FINN:
Got you now!
JAKE: Yeah!
ICE KING:
Ohh! Ohh!
You can have
the sandwiches back!
I'm sorry! Help!
Uh, ooh. Ooh.
[whimpering ]
Aah!
Huh.
[growls]
[groaning ]
[wolves growling ]
Muh-muh, hmm.
Mm, mm.
[ barks]
[slurp! ]
Muh, muh.
[growls]
Bye-bye.
FINN AND JAKE:
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Nom, nom, nom.
Boy, those
sandwiches look really cool.
Mmm, mmm.
It looks like it'd be really awesome
to try a bite of one of those.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm, mmm-mmm.
Right on, right on.
[sighs]
[wolves growling ]
Oh-huh!
[ barking ]
[laughing ]
You...the...real...good...
nice...home.
[slurp! slurp! slurp! ]
[laughs]
Jake, do you think that
puddle needs our help?
Nah, it's a snow golem, man.
I think he's laughing.
[laughs]
I thought snow golems and fire
wolves hated each other.
Oh, yeah. Big time.
But they learned
to get along.
Yep.
You know, maybe we
could all learn a thing or two
from those sandwiches.
[laughs]
[ barks]
[smooch! ]
Thank you.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies
and bees ♪
♪ We can wander
through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪