WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
[SNORING]
Mnnh-choo.
Mm.
[YAWNS]
[SMACKING LIPS]
What?!
Jake, I told you to stop
staring at me right at the time
when I wake up.
I'm staring because
I can't move my head!
[LAUGHS]
No, really, I can't move.
I can't move, either!
What's happening?!
[DOOR OPENS]
What?
What is that?
- Hey, who is that?
- Who goes there?
Jake, use your
peripheral vision!
[GRUNTING]
Ohh! Ohh! Ohh!
[SNICKERING]
Ice King!
[LAUGHING]
I shouldn't be laughing.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I know --
I'll do the opposite.
Oh, boohoo!
[SNIFFLES]
Oh, this is weird.
What did you do to us, Ice King?!
Whoa, whoa.
I didn't "do" anything to you, okay?
Come on, guys.
I'm your friend.
So why can't we move?!
Ooh! Because I froze you,
with this.
FINN:
"Freezing Potion A"?
I sprayed it on you
while you slept.
Wenk! Wenk!
No!
Gunter, no!
This one likes to break bottles,
don't you?
Tuckity tuck.
Let's move to
the living room.
[HUMMING]
Why are you doing this, Ice King?
ICE KING:
Why'?
Well, because I love you guys,
but you don't love me, do you?
You've tried to kill
us like four times.
I only try to kill you
'cause you're princess-blockin'
me all the time!
Anyway, now that you're frozen,
we can bond and stuff,
and the sooner we do, the sooner
I can spray you with this.
FINN:
"Unfreezing Potion A"?
Uh, I underlined the "Un--"
so I wouldn't mix 'em up.
Just unfreeze us now, man.
Yeah, 'cause we're already friends.
We are'?
Mm-hmm.
What's my favorite color?
BOTH:
Um.
Yellow? Orange?
Ohh, uh.
Lavender, lavender, yeah!
Uh, Rainbow?
You don't love me.
I know a lot about you guys.
Jake, you don't put ice in
your drink because you have
sensitive teeth.
What?
And, Finn, your favorite
food is meatloaf.
How did you...
And, Jake, sometimes
you don't cry because
you're afraid of real emotion.
It's okay.
Let it out.
[PLONK!]
You don't love me.
Wenk! Wenk, vvenk!
Wenk! Wenk!
Bad penguin!
Wenk.
[LOCKS ENGAGE]
You lock your bottles?
[SCOFFS]
In this economy?
[ZWIP!]
Well, I'm gonna go
make some lemonade.
Don't touch my lemons, Ice King!
Ice King!
Jake, look!
[GASPS]
Gunter!
No, Gunter! No!
Wenk.
BOTH:
No, Gunter! No!
Aah, aah!
Aaah!
Gunter, stop!
Wenk, wenk!
What are we gonna do?!
When someone loses one sense,
their other senses are enhanced,
like a blind man who can
smell and hear really well.
I'm gonna try using my
now-enhanced brain sense to make
contact with an astral
beast who will help us.
What?
[CREAKY]
[TWINKLE]
Whee!
[LAUGHS]
Astral beast,
come to me!
Come to me, astral beast.
I've got lemonade!
You want some, Jake?
[SLURP!]
Huh?
Gunter!
No, Gunter!
No bottles!
Look at me!
Wenk.
[LAUGHING]
What am I gonna
do with you?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, you.
[ZZZZAP!]
You're going to have
to wear a leash.
[ZAP!]
This should keep you
out of trouble.
Now, our first bonding activity
will be walking in each ether's
shoes, so to speak.
To better understand each
ether's perspectives,
we're going to dress
up like each other.
Me first!
[RIP! RIP!]
[WHIFFLE!]
[SQUEAK! SQUEAK! SQUEAK!]
[GRUNTING]
[VOCALIZING]
[SLURP!]
[ZAP!]
It's Adventure Time!
I'll save you, Princess!
Let's have babies, Princess!
And let's teach them
to be good babies!
Oh, Princess, sure,
I'll kiss you.
I'm a hero.
Hey, Finn, uh, don't you think
it's weird there's two Finns?
Finn? Not talking?
Now I'm gonna dress like Jake.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
No!!
No, no, Ho, no, no!
Okay, okay.
We'll bond in another way.
So, I wanted to show you
something telling of my soul.
Wenk. Wenk.
I take artful black-and-white
photographs of my penguirfs
body parts.
Photography is art.
Uh, let's see some art.
Okay, first one --
see how Gunter is staring
into the camera?
He's saying,
"Here I am.
Look at me.
Accept me."
Okay, second one --
this is a haunting image
of a penguin's flipper.
Look at how it penetrates
the negative space.
I can't take this anymore!
Dang it, Finn, what
are you doing in there?!
ICE KING:
Oh, yes, this one is very clear.
[TWINKLE!]
Astral beast,
where are you?!
You come here now!!
Whee!
ICE KING:
Yeah, I've thought about it a lot.
Ohh.
And having a little
gallery show might be nice --
a little cheese,
a little cider.
Could be nice,
you know?
Maybe bring a veggie plate.
I think people would
appreciate that.
Key! Gunter! Gunter!
ICE KING:
Yup, could be real nice.
Gunter, psst!
Ps-s-s-st!
Come here, Gunter!
[SMACKING LIPS]
We-e-e-e-n k!
[CLATTER!]
[HONKS]
This next one
is very rewarding.
[PATTER!]
Grab it, Gunter!
Pick it up!
What are you waiting for?
Just grab it!
Wenk.
Wenk, vvenk, wenk.
Wenk, wenk.
Gunter, come back!
- Gunter!
- Wenk?
You are being naughty, Gunter!
You've interrupted
my thing!
Now, you stay right here
and go to sleep!
Sleep!
[SNORING]
Wenk. Wenk.
Aww! So cute.
All right, back to art.
Gunter.
Gunter, wake up.
Go... get...the... key.
[GRUNTING]
Consarn it, Gunter!
Okay, time for a break.
Who wants lemonade?
Ooh, don't want to lose this.
Gunter! Jake!
No!
You're bonding without me!
Wenk.
It's for your own good,
sweetie.
Now, then...
[CLATTERING]
Wait, you're sleeping up here?
Well [GIGGLES] not before
our next bonding activity --
late-night gab session.
Do you want to
talk about girls?
Do you have a
crush on anyone?
Uh, yeah, my girlfriend,
Lady Rainicorn.
Ooohhhhhh!
Don't worry --
I won't tell anyone.
[LAUGHS]
Know who I have
a crush on?
Princess Bubblegum.
You don't say.
Oh, I do
I've liked her for
quite some time.
Feels weird to
say it out loud.
[SNORING]
What?
Ohh, he fell asleep
with his eyes open!
Finn!
Finn, snap out of it!
Astral beast,
where are you?!
Show yourself!
Why not?!
Does this dance please you,
astral beast?!
Does this please you?!
[WARBLE!]
This is it!
The astral beast cometh.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CROWING]
Rr-rr-rr rr-rrrr!
[LAUGHS]
Who's hungie?
Jake, you hungie?
I'm hungry.
All right, fair enough.
Well, how about I make
us some omelets?
That sounds pretty good, actually.
I'm gonna put my foot in it.
Eating a part of me will
bring us closer together.
I'll be inside of you.
[LAUGHS]
Dude, you're back!
Yup. I just got back
from the astral plane.
Where's your astral beast?
It's on its way.
It's gonna be awesome.
What kind of beast?
Well, I'm not sure.
I couldn't see it in
the astral plane.
But I heard it.
It sounded really intense.
[BLOWS]
Maybe a gorilla?
A gorilla, huh?
Aw, junk!
Did I summon butterflies?!
[SIGH]
I'm the worst.
Hey, come on, now.
You're not the worst.
Yeah, I am.
No, you're not --
you're the best.
At being the worst.
Mmnnnhhh!
FINN:
What are you doing?
I'm using my enhanced brain
sense to tell your astral beast
to slap some sense into you.
Oh. That's cool.
I deserve it.
Mmnnnnhh!
No...you...don't!
[SLAM SLAP!]
[SIZZLING]
Well, I don't want to
use too much foot.
It'll overpower the eggs --
take away from the omelet.
Huh? Aaah!
Finn and Jake...
and a bunch of butterflies...
and a sword!
Ohm
[VOICE BREAKING]
What do you want from me?
What do we want?
We want you to unfreeze us,
you lunatic!
No, we're not friends yet.
You haven't eaten my omelet.
Aah! Ohh!
Friends don't eat each other,
Ice King.
That's not how friends work.
Now, unlock this bottle
and unfreeze us!
Ohh!
All right.
I don't know how you're doing
this, but it is impressive.
[WHOOSH!]
Wait a minute.
Which bottle is 'Eh--
[WHOOSH!]
[SHATTER!]
I think they brought me
the wrong bottle.
Gunteï¬s still upstairs.
Gunter! Gunter!
Gunter!
[BOTTLE SHATTERS]
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪