WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[ mouse squeaks]
[ penguins chirp]
[all cheering ]
[screeches]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ the fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Ahh.
[ munching ]
[ chuckles softly]
Good morning,
Breakfast Princesses.
[grunts]
Mmm!
[ humming ]
Oh.
Huh?!
Sis, give me the phone.
[dialing ]
[ ringing ]
Oh, hey, Finn.
I've got another Ice King
situation here.
Oh, yeah?
That would be great.
Thanks.
[slam! ]
FINN:
Ice King!
How many times
have we warned you
about using love potion?
That's why
I'm using honey.
Man, who cares
if it's honey?
You stink anyways.
[laughs]
Yeah, you stink so much,
I'm gonna ground you
for a week.
What?!
You can't do that!
You're grounded
for two weeks!
You're grounded for
two weeks!
Three weeks.
Oh, snaps!
Why?!
I didn't do anything!
Four weeks?
[groans]
Fine!
But I'm only gonna do it
for a week!
That just grounded you
for four weeks.
Oh, dang!
[sighs]
Okay.
What's up
with the peace sign?!
Oh. No, I-I was
just trying to show you
how many weeks you got.
Get out of here,
bubble butt!
[growls]
[ both laugh ]
Awesome.
ICE KING:
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
This is so unfair!
They're the ones who should be
grounded, not me!
Ooh!
I'm so mad I could
just hit them!
If only I could hit them without
leaving the castle.
[ clink! clink! clink! clink! ]
"H...I...T...
M...A...N..."
Ooh!
Perfect.
"Dear, Mr. Scorcher.
I would like you
to hit two people.
Neat name, by the way.
Love, the Ice King."
[laughs]
Aah!
Whoa, you are fast!
And quiet.
ICE KING:
And very good at dramatic silence.
I like it.
All right!
So, how do we do this?
Uh, we shake hands,
or -- aah!
[whoosh! ]
Oh-ho!
Paperwork.
"Finn and Jake."
[whoosh! ]
[ hiss! ]
[laughs]
Whoosh!
Aha. There he is.
Huh? What's he doing?
What the...
I hired a hitman,
not a fireman!
[groans]
Dude, you see my masterpiece
coming together, right?
Mine's whack.
Well, put some
meat in there.
Huh.
What kind of meat is that?
That's Meat Man's meat.
Do you think it hurts Meat Man
when he gives us
his meat?
I don't know.
I can't read his mind.
Phoo-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
No-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
You guys, I --
What do you think
"grounded" means?!
It's wasted, man!
Oh, great!
Now see what you did
to my buddy?!
So help me, Ice King!
Okay, okay.
Ghal!
[whoosh! ]
It's all right, buddy.
We can make another.
Sheesh,
this Scorcher guy's got
some weird
ideas about hitting.
Hey, there you are.
What's that?
I already signed that.
[smack! ]
I thought I told you
to hit them,
not burn them alive,
you big dummy!
Ghal!
It's almost like you want
to kill them!
ICE MAN:
Lucky for them, I stopped the fire.
You know what happens when
you're burned alive?!
Your eyeballs explode!
Blah!
Hey, wha?
[ both snoring ]
Punch, punch.
Punch.
Rainicorn,
don't eat him.
[snores]
[ hiss! ]
[wheezing ]
[gasps]
Ice winds, blow!
Blo-o-o-o-o-o-o-w!
Blo-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-w!
JAKE:
Meat Man...
[snores]
Meat Man, I'm sorry,
Meat Man.
I-I didn't mean it, man.
[snores]
Finn and Jake, I am
just a dream!
I was never here.
Okay, mister, you are really
trying my patience!
How clear can I be?!
All I want you to do
is hit them --
on the shoulder,
or something.
[grunts]
Are you even listening?
Oh, I get it.
Here's double the grease to not
kill Finn and Jake.
[whoosh! ]
[ chuckles nervously]
You trying to hustle me,
Scorcher?
Okay. I'll play this game.
How about this prize piece
for your pad?
♪ I wanna live, live, live ♪
♪ I wanna live,
live, live ♪
No-o-o-o-o-o-o!
Huh. Okay.
How about these bad boys --
night vision x-ray goggles
for when you have
a lady houseguest?
Aw! Come on!
ICE KING:
At least renegotiate the target!
You can destroy my least
favorite princesses.
What about
Lumpy Space Princess?
[whoosh! ]
Ghost Princess?
I can't even hold her
with my love mitts.
Aw, geez!
Uh...
[whoosh! ]
Huh.
Oh!
A-A leg cramp, in my leg!
Ow, ow!
O-Oh, this is so embarrassing.
I'll be right back.
Ow! Ow!
[sighs]
Think, baby.
Come on.
Ah!
All right, let's hit
the hitman, right?
There's got to be a --
Ah!
"Blastronaut --#1 solution for
all hitman problems."
Sheesh! $99.95?!
That's nuts!
[ mouse clicks]
"Scor... cher."
[ beeping ]
[ boom! ]
[zap! zap! zap! ]
Sweet!
[whoosh! boom! ]
No!
Come back, you wussy!
Ooh, that was weird.
[whoosh! ]
Was that your friend,
or something?
[ chuckles nervously]
Look! A supermodel!
Look! A hoverboard!
Look! The apocalypse!
Someone got hit
in the boingloings.
Hit in the boingloings!
ICE KING:
Boingloings! Boingloings!
Somebody got hit in them.
Peace out!
[ cra-a-a-a-a-ck! ]
Oh!
Freakin' butt!
Butt, butt, butt!
Hey, Finn, are you
awake yet?
[ yawning ]
I'm trying.
I had a dream about
Meat Man.
Oh, yeah?
I think I'm gonna stop
eating Meat Man.
Aah! Oh!
You're grounded!
I know, but shush!
[slurps]
[sighs]
[groans]
Okay.
I hired a guy to kill you
by accident.
BOTH:
What?!
I thought he was
gonna just hit you in the gut
and make you spit up
your lunch.
Well, I froze him in ice,
but I think he's free now,
'cause he's made out
of fire...
or he commands fire, maybe?
Good job.
Good job, The Ice King.
[ boom! ]
Oh, my life!
Aah!
Hyah!
Come on, man!
Let's get out of here!
[ hiss! ]
Jake, do something!
He's getting close!
Yah!
Go faster, man!
[ panting ]
Oof!
[ both grunt ]
[groans]
[thud! ]
You alive?
Uh, I think so.
Whew!
That was close!
[ chuckles]
[thud! thud! thud! ]
Uh, hey, guys?
I don't think this ice dome
is gonna last long.
What do we do?
Hmm.
Mm-hmm. Hm.
Ooh! Got it!
I'm gonna kill you guys.
Hey, I'll kill you!
No, wait a minute,
you two!
I won't actually kill you.
I'm just gonna lower your body
temperatures
so you seem dead.
And after we fool that fool
outside,
I'll warm you up --
good as new.
No way, man!
You already messed up
enough stuff!
You'll probably
kill us, too!
Yeah!
We don't trust you!
Zap!
[ both scream ]
You'll thank me later.
Stop!
Time out!
You don't need to do this
anymore!
Look! They're dead!
I killed them myself!
Dead, dead, dead!
Dead, dead,
dead!
They're dead. No pulses.
[growls softly]
So, uh, looks like
you can go home now.
[whoosh! ]
Aah!
Oh, yeah.
O-Of course.
There.
[whoosh! ]
Oh, glad all that's over.
[whistling ]
[grunting ]
[sighs]
ICE KING:
Hey, guys, guess what.
You're grounded...
underneath my butt!
[laughs]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!