WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
Just about done.
Mmm. Oh, boy.
How much softy cheezy
for your deezy?
A little?
A lot?
Blech! None!
But you used to love softy cheese.
I don't want to talk about it.
[WIND BLOWS]
[HIGH-PITCHED MOAN]
- What was that?
- Probably an owl.
Mmm.
Mm-mmm --
[SPITS]
A ghost!
[MOANING]
Doo, it's just Ghost Princess.
Hey, G. P.!
[MOANS]
She's weird, huh?
[AIR WHOOSHES]
[BREATHES RAGGEDLY]
How's it going?
[MOANING]
Are you haunting us?
[ETHEREALLY]
Yes-s-s.
Oh, okay.
[MOANS]
Well, can you knock it off?
Sorry.
It's just I'm doomed
to haunt this mortal plane.
Oh. Let's hear more
about that, honey.
Until I discover
the cause of my death,
my soul can't ascend
to the 50th dead world.
But as a ghost, I have no memory
of my mortal life...
and no idea how I died.
[GASPS]
It's a crime case!
Whoa!
Step back, nephew!
We don't know
that she was "moidered."
That's right!
We don't even know
how she was "moidered."
But I'm the hard-boiled sleuth
that's gonna crack your case
wide open.
Oh! That sounds wonderful!
This way, gentlemen.
Whoa.
Your neighborhood is...
uh...
very peaceful.
It's the cradle of my despair.
Right, right.
Well, here's me.
Our first clue!
"Fee-may-ale."
It's a good start,
but we need more.
Jake, it's time to interrogate
the neighbors.
We'll do it
"good cop, bad cop"-style.
I call "bad cop"!
Aww!
Yo, ghost! Yo, yo!
Yo, wake up, fool!
Yo, yo, yo, yo,
yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
What?!
Yo, ghost, what do you
know about the lady
buried next to you?
- What, you mean her?
She's been here longer than
almost everybody!
He's right!
[SOBBING]
And don't think I don't see
what you do, Ghost Princess.
What?
Sneaking off at night,
scaring peeps, haunting at all
hours --
'cause you can't deal
with your issues!
[$OBS]
[CHUCKLES EVILLY]
MAN:
Leave her be, Boilbee!
Wha-a-a-t?!
A princess deserves empathy --
not your sass.
Ohhh! Ahh!
[GRUMBLING]
Butt out, Clarence.
Some of us still want to feel,
you know --
the vital
[GULPS] magnetism of life,
the vibrating energies that connect
all living and non-living beings.
Nyah!
I don't like your words!
I'm Ghost Princess.
Have we met before?
I feel like we have.
I don't think so, milady,
but I am honor-ed.
What do you know about
Ghosty P's getting murdle-erdled?
Sorry.
I don't know anything.
I can't imagine anyone
who would harm someone
as beautiful as this.
[SMOOCHES]
Whoa. Smooth.
Did you try looking yonder?
That's where the néer-do-well
ghosts hang out.
Right.
Ne'er-do-wellers.
Let's do this, Jake!
You stay and eat cheese puffs.
[BOTH GULP, LAUGH]
Geez.
Look at this place.
It's all bunked up.
Yeah, no wonder this is where
the néer-do-wells go
when they deezy.
I got a feeling these ghosts
are gonna be
harder to shake than
Boilbee.
Yeah. Well, get ready,
'cause this biz is gonna get ridonk.
Cool, man!
Hey, can I be "bad cop" now?
No.
Okay.
Let's check this guy out.
- JAKE: What's it say?
- FINN: "Some Donkus."
Wake up, Donkus!
We got questions!
Dingus!
Time to sing, ya canary!
[GRUNTING]
Bam! Yah!
What you know about
Ghost Princess, huh?!
Give it up, Dungus!
Hey, man, take it easy.
You do your job, Ido mine!
[GROWLING]
Tell me what you know, punk!
[NORMAL VOICE]
Uh-oh. What's this?
A busted knife.
Is this your knife, bro?
Tell me!
Jake -- "good cop"!
JAKE:
Oh, right.
Cool out, "bad cop"!
No! Aah!
This ghost ain't home, man!
[PANTING]
Well, you're lucky
my partner's here... pal.
- He's not worth it, man.
- Hmph!
These ghosts think I'm playing.
They think it's all a big game.
But you know what?
You know what I'm gonna do?
What?
I'm gonna turn this game
upside downH
[ECHOES]
GHOST PRINCESS: So, you really
don't know how you died, either?
CLARENCE:
Of course not. Two, please.
And we might never find out.
But that's okay, because right
now, in this moment,
I'm feeling pretty sweeties, you know?
I feel sweeties also
in this moment, also.
- That's great, Ghost Princess.
I'm glad we can feel this way together
in the face of uncertainty.
Ladies and gents!
The center for ghost-community
outreach and ghostdatescom
present...
Spirit Waves!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[UP-TEMPO JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS]
More beautiful than I could imagine.
Are you talking about Spirit Waves?
I'm talking about you, Princess.
Ya-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-h!
Ghosts!
You ghosts! Come out! Rah!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I think this place is abandoned, man.
They're just hiding
'cause they know they're guilty!
MALE GHOST:
Yo! Yo! That's my grave!
Why are you fops
trashing our spot?
[WEAKLY]
We... thought
you were... hiding.
Dude, we were at
the Spirit Waves show.
Kill these fools!
ALL:
[GROWLING]
Bring it on, you mamas!
CLARENCE:
Hold up! These guys are with me.
A'ight, Clarence, but only
because of that one time
when I did that thing by accident
and you were cool about it.
It's your lucky day, punks.
Whew! Thanks, Clarence!
Yo, I'm sorry we haven't
solved the case yet.
It's all right, Finn.
I'm calling off the investigation.
What? Why'?
I don't feel tormented anymore
now that I'm with Clarence.
Oh, really?
That's -- that's cool.
It's hard to explain,
but it's like we already know each other.
I feel it, too.
Our spirits must be entwined in
the cosmic wheel of time.
Nice.
Let's go to my private mausoleum,
where we can be... private.
Yuck.
GHOST PRINCESSS:
Thanks for your help!
A'ight!
[SIGHS]
Aw, man.
I wanted to crack the case, you know?
Look on the bright side, guy.
We looted all this
sweet grave booty!
Ka-ching!
Jake! You looted?!
That's bad, man!
You're supposed to be "good cop."
Oops. I didn't know it was wrong.
Come on.
Let's put all this stuff back.
- What?! All of it?!
- Yes, Jake.
Huh.
This dagger says, "Renee."
- What's that?
I guess Some Donkus'
real name was...
"Re-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-nce!"
Have we met before?
It's hard to explain,
but it's like we already
know each other.
Is this your knife, bro?
This ghost
ain't home, man!
What is it, dude?
[GROWLING]
We got to dig up the princess.
[GRUNTING]
Look!
Sorry.
Lookit!
"Clarence."
Clarence was "Some Donkus"!
Some Donkus ski-bopped
Ghost Princess!
[DOORS SLAM]
- JAKE: Stop!
Clarence is your murdler!
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
CLARENCE:
Warrior Princess, give up your kingdom!
Never -- not even to you,
my love!
[METAL CLANKING]
Unh!
Clarence, I... ahh...
My love!
N-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
[SOBBING]
I did it?
I forgive you, Clarence.
Take my hands!
Ascend with me
to the 50th dead world!
I can't!
My soul is stuck!
I have to know hovv ldied!
Oh, glob!
My life is like a fart.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Say that again.
My life is like a fart!
I know you, man --
from the Squeezy Mart!
Huh?
Uh, Squeezy Mart?
I'm starting to remember.
I was a broken man.
[GROANS]
More.
I think you've had enough, man.
I don't care.
My life is like a fart.
Huh?
My life is like a fart!
[GLUGGING]
Hey!
Hey, stop that!
Citizen's arrest!
[GLUGGING CONTINUES]
Hey, be careful, man!
[BOOMS]
So, that's why you
don't like softy cheese.
GHOST PRINCESS:
Clarence!
CLARENCE:
Ghost Princess!
[SMOOCHING]
[RUMBLING]
Congratulations, you kids!
[LAUGHS]
Yeah!
- Goodbye!
- Thanks for everything!
- Thanks for everything.
- Goodbye.
[SMOOCHING]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
You sure you're ready
for this, man?
Yeah. Give me one of them
cheesy dogs, man.
[GULPS]
All gone?
Let me see.
Move your tongue left...
Bleh bleh.
- ...and right.
- Bleh.
I'm proud of you, pal --
real proud.
[BURPS]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪