WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS WENK]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
MAN:
Aaah!
Get off! Aah!
We're coming!
Whoa!
[PANTING]
Be careful!
Hyah!
Grab him, Jake!
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Jake!
Whoa! Ugh!
[CRACK! CRACK!]
[STRAINED]
Whatever.
Waaaaaaaaaah!
Oh!
[GROANS]
Ohh.
Oh.
What happened?
Where's the deer?
[ECHOING]
Paging Dr. Ice Cream.
Ice cream for my mou-u-u-th!
[NORMAL VOICE]
Oh, dude!
I broke my stems!
[ECHOING]
Hello?
Jake?
Princess?
[NORMAL VOICE]
What the bliz?
Come on, people.
[GRUNTING]
[WHEELCHAIR SQUEAKS]
Yo!
Is everyone at church,
worshipping glob?
Whoop!
[GRUNTING]
Skills. Skills.
[METAL CLANGING]
Huh?
Bazoobs.
[GRUNTS]
Jake?
Huh?
Oh, Finn, you're awake!
Yeah, I'm awake,
but my jams are all busted.
Right.
Yeah, I saw that.
So, what happened?
Did you save everybody?
Oh, yeah.
I-I think so.
Maybe.
So, Jake,
there's nobody here.
Did you notice that?
Yeah. Pretty freaky.
Don't worry.
Ouch!
They're all hiding.
From what?
From me.
What?!
It's my birthday, man.
Lady Rainicorn put together an
elaborate surprise party.
She told you?
No, but I know Lady Rainicorn.
Ouch!
This is totally
something she would do.
Think about it.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
So, wait, the whole
kingdom is in on it'?
Yes, and they'll
only come out if
they think we'll
be surprised,
so we got to act like we're
totally unaware, okay'?
Okay, man.
And how do we do that?
Just do what I'm doing.
Oh, look at me.
Living free without
a suspicion in the world.
Never in my
wildest dreams would
I guess someone was planning a
surprise birthday party for me.
[LAUGHS]
Pretty tricky, right?
Come on,
let's go back to the hut.
The what?
Come on! Come on!
♪ I got everything I need ♪
♪ Living free on trash booty ♪
♪ No, I don't suspect a thing ♪
♪ Blah, blublah, blublee ♪
♪ Hobo dreams ♪
Whoa.
Where'd you find
time to build this?
I don't know.
It didn't take long.
Hmm.
So, what should I do now?
Collect branches
for the hobo fire, dude.
Okay-
[WHEELCHAIR SQUEAKS]
Ouchies.
A hobo fire,
fire, fire.
Boy, it sure is
quiet around here!
Uh-huh!
I'd probably pee all over myself
if somebody jumped out and
surprised me!
[SNIFFS]
Oh! Oh, I stink!
How long was I out for?
A day or two?
Huh.
What a convenient
place to bathe.
Sure seems like a good time to
come out if y'all are just
hiding and you don't, you know,
want to see me pop my top!
[GRUNTING]
Oh, yeah. That's fresh.
I hope nobody's gonna jump out
of the bushes and peeps my bod!
Heh heh heh heh!
Blblblblblblblbl!
Hmm.
Just got to char out
the rotten parts --
good as new, man.
Stay vigilant.
Eat your protein.
Jake?
Hmm?
I am starting to question your
theory about the surprise party.
Shh!
Don't talk so loud.
They might hear you.
But what if
they're in trouble?
What if something
happened to them?
We should try
looking around.
No!
You'll ruin my
surprise party!
Ow! Oh!
Arsh!
Dude, are you okay?
Just promise me, Finn --
promise not to look around.
[SIGHS]
Okay, I promise.
[MUTTERING]
My birthday, it's gonna be rad.
[HOOF BEATS]
Hey, it's you!
Thanks for breaking my legs,
you dumb-butt.
[SLURPS]
[SNIFFS]
[INDISTINCT VOICES ECHOING]
That sounds like...
Candy people.
FINN:
Jake! Jake!
Mm. What?
I heard a sound coming
from the sewer.
We should check it out.
No, man.
They'll surprise-party
me when they're ready.
Be patient.
I'm being patient!
I waited all day, Jake!
Well, I've been
waiting six months.
[ECHOING]
...six months.
Wait --
what are you saying?
Everything's
gonna be fine.
[YAWNING]
Even if we have to wait...
forever!
Have I been asleep
for six months?
Yeah, but don't
worry about it, man.
[THINKING]
Face it, Finn --
your best friend is gone.
Finn?
[PANTING]
No-o-o-o!
Don't ruin the surprise!
Raaaaah!
Gah! Aah! Aah!
Whoa!
Oomph!
Hyah! Rah! Aah!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
No!
Oh, my glob!
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[GROANS]
Surprise!
Happy birthday, Jake!
Ow!
[INDISTINCT VOICES ECHOING]
Hey, Jake,
what are you doing?
This is how my
party's gonna go down.
Shake it, my friends.
Hey! Hey!
Sure is great
seeing you all here.
Really makes me think.
Ow!
Lady, did you get extra T.P.
for all the "potty" people?
[HIGH-PITCHED]
No.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Well, we might have some party peepers here,
and I want to be sure they don't
wipe their buns on my cake.
Can I join
your puppet party'?
We'll have twice
the puppet voices.
You won't run away?
Nah, man.
I'm with you.
Happy birthday, Jake.
Really.
Finn!
Glad I can
untie you, buddy.
Check it out!
Finn finally made
it to my party!
And I have a
surprise for you.
Close your eyes and don't
open them till I tell you.
[PANTING]
Finn?
You...lied to me?
[CRUNCH!]
Yeow!
[PANTING]
What about my party?
Don't go!
Finn!
Whupppp!
[GASPS]
[GASPING]
Hello?
[INDISTINCT VOICES ECHOING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[GASPS]
[CANDY PEOPLE MOANING]
Finn...
A-a-a-a-a-aah!
Surprise!
You...
you did this?
I did this?
Ow!
They've been waiting for me,
Finn -- for my b-day!
Stop being crazy!
Gobble gobble gobble,
bla-bla-bla, gobble, dooba,
dooba, dabble.
Bb-bb-bb-bb-bb-bb-bb!
[WHACK!]
Oof!
You a he!
I'm a woman!
Raah!
Ooh!
Ring, ring.
Eh, hang on, deary.
Hello?
Baby, I told you
never to call me here.
Oh!
W-what happened?
A deer scronked your head,
and you lost your mind, man.
You imprisoned
the candy people
for your own
sick birthday fantasy.
Look.
What?
No!
It's not even
close to my b-day.
I'm so sorry.
You...
[WEAKLY]
You did not do this, Jake.
BOTH:
What?!
Then who did?
It...was...him.
[BOTH GASP]
Freak deer!
Aah!
[GROWLS]
Jake, you free
the Candy people.
I'll take on the deer.
No-o-o!
“Van!
ALL:
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Thank you.
Heh, heh, hoo, hoo, ha.
Grrrrr!
Oh!
Aah!
Ohh!
[GASPS]
Ugh!
Finn!
Huh?
Donk!
[FLUSH!]
[ALL CHEERING]
BOTH:
Nice!
We did it, dude.
How's your noggin?
Not crazy anymore.
How's your legs?
Mm...still broken.
[LAUGHS]
Thank you for saving
my Kingdom, boys.
The deer wanted our sugar,
but I didn't give him any,
if you know what I mean.
Tch! Tch!
Um...
Phew!
It's stanky in here!
Yeah,
like bad breath and eggs.
Let's go home
so we can get baths.
[ALL CHEERING]
CANDY PERSON:
I'm gonna get clean!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!