WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS WENK]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[SIZZLING]
I blows]
[SLURPING]
Finn, lunch is ready!
Oh!
What are you cooking?
It's good, man.
I learned it from Rainicorn.
I'm not eating that.
It smells funny.
Dude, this took me,
like --
FINN:
Let's go over to Tree Trunks' and get some apple pie.
[CHANTING]
Apple pie!
Apple pie! Apple pie!
Let's go!
Whoa!
[GRUNTS]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
FINN:
Tree Trunks!
Tree Tr--
[GASPS]
Tree Trunks!
Tree Trunks?
[MUMBLING]
Apples.
My apples.
Apples?
You!
You took my apples!
Whoa! Whoa!
Tree Trunks, it's us --
Finn and Jake.
Finn?
And -- and Jake?
It's okay, Tree Trunks.
We're here to help you.
Just tell us what happened.
They took them.
They took all of them.
All of what?
Apples.
My apples that I
raised with love --
from mere seedlings.
Without my special apples,
I won't be able to bake
any more apple pies.
BOTH:
Noooooo!
Don't you worry,
Tree Trunks,
we'll find those thieves
and bring them to justice.
Let me show you
the crime scene.
You see, boys,
scads of apple trees but --
but no apples.
Hmm.
Is anything else missing,
Tree Trunks?
No, Finn.
They didn't touch my rocks
or my birds or my flowers or --
or nothing.
Hmm.
Well, I don't
see any footprints.
What you got, Jake?
No ghost doodies.
Oh. Oh, wait.
Oh, no. No.
Hmm.
Tree Trunks, is there anyone you
can think of who might want to
krunk you up?
Oh, no, Finn.
I take great care
to assure that --
that I'm loved by
even the most heinous...
JAKE:
Hey, guys, I found something!
Look!
[GASPS]
Oh, hey. Hey, Finn.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Oh, hey, Raggedy Princess.
Have you seen
anything fishy going on?
Um, no.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
I've been kind of down
this hole for a long time.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
I got knocked down here
by some Ne'er-do-wells.
It was terrible.
I was so scared.
Ne'er-do-wells?
They stole my apples.
I'm gonna sass those
boys up nasty!
[CHUCKLES]
Awesome.
Where do we find these guys?
Oh, the Candy Tavern, man.
I used to hang out there back
when I used to snatch old
ladies' purses.
[DING!]
Don't worry.
I stopped doing that
a long time ago.
I didn't know it was wrong.
[DING!]
Okay, you two,
let's get going.
[CLATTERING]
Uhh!
[GASPS]
Oh, my!
[GRUNTING]
Uh, does Princess Bubblegum
know about this place?
Be cool, man.
You're gonna queer the deal.
Oh, yeah. Try not to act
suspicious, Tree Trunks.
Okay, I won't.
ALL:
Where --
Oh!
Where's my dang apples?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Tree Trunks,
you're so silly.
But --
but listen.
You wouldn't happen
to have seen any --
I don't know --
apples around, have you?
Seen any apples?
You ask a lot of
dumb-butt questions,
almost like you're trying
to solve something.
What?
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Mm. Clean, too.
Almost like some do-gooders!
Hold on.
We got to go potty.
Dang.
They almost got us.
But I think we blend
in pretty well now.
This --
this toilet paper's drying my --
my mouth all up.
Tree Trunks,
don't eat that.
Here.
You got to watch your man.
Oh, I look just
like an army brat.
What can I do for you?
You know where a guy
might maybe score some apples?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Well, when you put
it like that,
a couple of buddies I know
have some apples for sale.
I'll show you.
Hey, fellas, these folks been
asking about your ...apples.
Okay-
Show 'em the apples, Smudge.
Grab 'em!
You go back, and you
tell your boss to stop
looking for those apples,
'cause they're ours now!
W-what boss?
Your boss -- Dr. J.
We don't know any Dr. J.
Liar!
Ouch!
Come on, Smudge.
[MUTTERING]
Dr. J. Gonna take myapples.
What just happened?
I guess these guys who stole
Tree Trunks' apples also
stole Dr. J.'s apples, and they
thought we were working for him.
Finn, Finn.
Hmm?
This could be dangerous.
And if you want to go back home,
I understand.
But I need to do this.
Yeah, Tree Trunks.
Me too.
JAKE:
Hey, Finn.
Hmm?
What's that on
your face, buddy?
Oh, the guy bopped me one.
Must have had a ring on.
You know, I think I seen that
symbol somewhere before.
Yeah.
Right next door to where
I used to hock stolen bikes.
What?!
I didn't know it was wrong.
Yeah, you see, that guy must
work here or something.
Hello?
Who's the heck happening?
What?
Uh, we're here
about the apples.
Oh. Okay.
Let's see your ring.
Um...
here.
[POP!]
Come on in.
Follow this guy.
My boss is gonna
be real psyched
I found someone
to buy his apples.
A whole crate.
What the --
what's wrong, guy?
These aren't apples.
Oh, it didn't
mean "diamonds"?
All Ne'er-do-wells call
diamonds "apples,"
like calling money "Bread"
or rock-knockers "Butterslaps."
Hey, Wormo, we're back.
What the --
what are theydoing here?
They're here
for the apples.
That's the dang
Dr. J. Gang, Wormo.
Grab them!
Um, Sir
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
I promise if you let us go,
we won't tell no
one about your apples.
Feed 'em to the pig.
Yeah, the pig.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah. All right.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry, y'all.
They're making me do this.
I'll --
I'll try to make it quick.
MAN:
Hold it!
Dr. J.!
Yeah, yeah,
and I want my apples back.
BOTH:
Get 'em, boys.
[SMACK!]
[SCUFFLING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I Crying softly]
Ah, don't cry,
Tree Trunks.
But we're never gonna
find those apples.
Apples?
You guys looking
for apples?
Uh, yeah. Why?
'Cause I can hear a bunch
of apples in this room.
You mean apples
as diamonds?
Nope.
Apples as apples?
Yep.
You mean apples
that we eat?
Yes.
With all due respect,
Mr. Pig, Sir,
my apples were
stolen by a dirty,
rotten criminal who
needs to be put in jail!
I'm just telling
you the facts, ma'am.
What I hear is a whole pig-load
of apples inside that closet.
They sound scared.
Well, I hate to
tell you this, boys,
but there's no apples
in this closet.
You see, uh, I'm the only one
who knows how to open
this closet.
[ALL GASP]
Oh!
So I was the apple thief,
after all.
No, Tree Trunks.
That's preposterous.
No, Finn.
I'm a criminal,
and I need to pay the price.
[RINGS]
Banana guard speaking.
Uh, this is Tree Trunks.
I've done something horrible,
and I want you to come over
and arrest me.
FINN:
Tree Trunks, you don't need to do this.
Thank you, Finn and Jake,
but I won't let myself slip away
from such a terrible crime.
Goodbye.
Tree Trunks...
Uh, this is hard to watch.
I'm gonna look away.
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
This place could
use a scarecrow.
Huh?
Wait. What'd you say?
I said, "This place
could use a scarecrow."
A scarecrow...
no footprints...
All those magpies on the roof...
Raggedy Princess in the ditch...
And all the apples in
Tree Trunks' closet.
Boy, this place could
use a scarecrow.
That's it!
I knew it!
[MAGPIES CHIRPING]
The magpies have been stealing
the apples and accidentally
dropping them in this hole.
And that's why there weren't any
footprints around the tree.
Yes!
And the magpies were able to
steal the apples because
Raggedy Princess wasn't
sitting on the fence post
to scare them off.
Does this mean I'm innocent?
As innocent as a
baby's butt cheek.
[CHUCKLES]
Awesome.
This calls for a celebration.
You know what that means,
Tree Trunks.
I'm-a bake you the biggest and
the tastiest apple pie you
boys ever tasted.
[GRUNTS]
BOTH:
Whoa!
Uh, you boys better stick
around if you want to bite
of my apple pie.
She slapped my butt.
[LAUGHING]
[LAUGHTER]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN :
This party is so crazy!