WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[ mouse squeaks]
[ penguins chirp]
[all cheering ]
[screeches]
♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[ high-pitched humming ]
Huh?
[ humming resumes]
You got a lot of meat,
Wildberry Princess.
Yeah, you know.
Thanks for
cook-a-looking for us.
Oh, you're welcome, Finn,
and thank you for answering
my urgent summons.
Hey, yeah.
How can we aid thee?
[ chomp]
Oh, it's nothing, really.
Someone's trying to kill me.
Pbbbbbbht!
[ coughs, gags]
Still tastes good.
It's no big deal.
Finish your pie.
It is a big deal,
and I demand deets.
Okay.
I'm listening,
but I'm gonna keep eating.
[ munches]
I suspect that I've
been targeted by
the guild of assassins.
Whoa! How do you know?
I found this note stabbed
to my door...man.
[gasps]
Princess, we vow to
protect your juice.
Right, Jake?
[slobbering, munching ]
[ muffled ]
Sometimes I think
there's a monster who
lives in my stomach, and that's
why I'm hungry all the time.
[ chuckles]
[slobbering, munching ]
Uh...princess, let's continue
this briefing outside.
I can't look at his mouth
when he gets like this.
[ belches]
[ clunk! ]
[ munching ]
Mmm!
Princess, want me to
finish off your pie?
[as Princess Wildberry]
Yes, Jake --all my pies.
[ chuckling ]
[ munching ]
[ normal voice]
Hmm?
Hmm.
[giggles]
A tiny cat.
[screeches]
Whoa!
[splat ]
Quiet, or you die!
[gasps]
You're the assassin!
Me-mow -- assassin,
second class.
But once I take
out a Princess...
I "gadruate" to full membership!
Well, I'm no Princess,
sister!
Yes, I know, but since
you've blown my cover,
you will slay
Wildberry Princess!
What?!
I'd rather be injected
with poison!
Oh. Uh...
Okay.
Um...I mean...
I will assassinate
Wildberry Princess!
Good.
Oh, and if you try to trick me,
I'll poison you.
[thunk]
[stuffily]
My nose!
[echoing ]
Wow, it's like warm
garbage up in here!
You...you
done in there, Jake?
Oh! Uh, yeah!
So, um,
Wildberry Princess --
So, maybe it wouldn't
be so bad to be...killed.
W-w-why would
you say that?
Dude!
Are you trying
to freak her out?
I don't know.
I'm just thinking
out loud here.
Are you trying
to freak me out?
Aw, I'm sorry,
Wildberry Prin...cess.
[jingling ]
Uh, you should...
let me...do something.
And...
it will be...good.
What's going on out there?
Take...this!
And...that!
Ooh, how do you like this,
Princess?
Ooh!
Uh, that's...very...good?
I'm gonna pick you
up now and carry you...
to the window!
Jake, what are you...?
No! Stop! Please!
[whistle! ]
[splat! ]
Wildberry Princess is dead!
Shh.
[ting! ]
You did it! Well done!
I guess I'll be on my way.
Princess! Oh, princess!
You're alive!
We saw your crown next
to a pile of dirty meat.
Then we slipped
on the meat!
And I thought I
tasted your juice.
[sobbing ]
But it was just
blood from the meat!
We're so glad it
wasn't actually you!
[snarls]
You liar!
[squish ]
[groans]
Jake?
Okay, Jake.
I've injected you
with half the poison,
and you'll be dead
in 30 minutes,
unless you kill
the Princess,
which is when I'll
give you the antidote.
Finn! Help me!
What's wrong?
If you say anything,
I'll stab you in the brain!
Uh...
Finn!
Sing mom's lullaby!
I'm so tired,
Finn -- from the meat.
Please?
You have to
lull me to sleep.
Uh...
I know you carry mom's music
box around in your backpack!
Dude, I'm not gonna sing
mom's lullaby in front of
other people!
Please? Ple-e-e-ase?
All right.
Real quick, while the
Princess is distracted.
[ music box chimes]
[soft music plays]
♪ Don't be weepy,
sleepy puppies ♪
♪ Slip your slippers
on your footies ♪
♪ In the morning,
you'll get goodies ♪
♪ Puppy hats and
puppy hoodies ♪
♪ No stripes
or polka dots ♪
♪ Heather gray
and feather soft ♪
♪ Baby pink or baby
blu-u-u-u-u-e ♪
♪ All the drawstrings
you can chew ♪
Finn, there's an
assassin in my nose and
she poisoned me and is making
me kill Wildberry Princess!
Dude, stop playing games!
This is serious!
[grunts]
[smack! ]
[squishing ]
"Cat...noise"?
Oh, cats go meow!
[loudly meowing ]
[groans]
Shh!
[ rapidly meowing ]
Shh! Shh! Shh!
[ muffled meowing ]
[ muffled ]
Jake! Jake! What are you doing?!
Sorry.
[whistle! ]
[splat! ]
Me-mow, still asleep?
[snores]
Gonna double-cross Jake...
...and leave him to die.
[snoring ]
[ creaking ]
[ breathing heavily]
[shing! ]
[gasps]
[scratch! scratch! ]
Phew!
If I can just grab
that antidote...
[squish, squish! plink! ]
Aha!
[scraping ]
Puppy...hoodies...
[snores]
I did it.
[ footsteps approach ]
What the flop, Jake?!
[gasps]
Treachery!
Hyaaaah!
Ooh!
Time's running out,
Jake.
Do you want the
antidote or not?
[groans]
What is wrong with you?
Hey, everybody.
Everything's cool.
Everything's not cool!
Wildberry Princess is
still in danger!
Right. Right.
[groans]
Well, we should take
her somewhere safer.
Do not make me give
you the rest!
I know where to stash you,
Princess.
Follow me!
Ooh.
[dramatic music plays]
Here, nobody can
take us by surprise.
Finn, stand here with
your back to the cliff.
I'll stay with W.B.!
Then do what must be done.
[ clicks tongue]
WILDBERRY PRINCESS:
Oh, my!
Look at how close
to the edge I am.
[groans]
Do it, Jake.
Do it!
[ bird chirps]
I...I...
I probably shouldn't!
[zoom! thump! ]
Ugh!
[gasps]
Jake!
I'm...full of...poison.
The assassin!
The name's Me-mow.
If you let Jake die, so help me,
I will kill you, too!
Try it, oaf!
Give me the antidote!
[grunting ]
[whoosh! ]
[shing! ]
Face me, cat!
[ coughs]
[scraping ]
Ugh!
[groans]
[shing! ]
[screams]
Give it up, Me-mow!
You're only making
my face look cooler!
[shing! ]
[scrapes]
You're at my mercy!
Ha!
You think you're hurting
me with that tiny dagger?
We'll see who's laughing...
When you're blind!
[ inhales deeply]
[exhales sharply]
[thud! ]
[shing! ]
[groans]
[gasps]
It's over!
Give me the antidote!
What, this antidote?
No!
You...milk-lapper!
Jake, come lick this tree bark!
I'm coming.
[ bell tolls]
Forget it, kid.
I gave jake enough poison to
kill a dog 50 times his size.
Oh, no.
[sniffles]
[whimpers]
BOTH:
Wait! Oh, yeah!
[ breathes deeply]
[zoom! ]
Dog liver times 51!
A magic dog?
Nooooooo!
How you feeling, dude?
♪ Big liver! ♪
♪ Big liver, yeah! ♪
You've ruined me!
I have to wait a whole year to
retake the assassin's test!
Oh!
Why don't I make
you my royal pet?
Hyah!
[ pop! ]
Oh, dear.
Nice defense mechanism,
Wild B!
Are you naked?
Oh, no.
This is a medical condition.
I need a hospital.
[groans]
We all need a hospital.
[laughter]
[ bird chirping ]
[ ominous music plays]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander
through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪