WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[mouse squeaks]
[penguins wenk]
[all cheering]
[Screeches]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the Dog
and Finn the Human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[both grunting, panting]
It's slipping, dude.
[both groaning]
Phew.
"Rainicornicopia --
An Unabridged History
of the Rainicorns."
[yawns]
Whatever, man.
I barely made it
through the title.
Listen, man, one day,
I'm probably gonna
have half-rainbow pupsters.
I got to be able to share
my babies' culture.
[Muttering]
[thump! thump!]
Huh.
[thump!]
Oh.
Hey, this table is wobbly.
We gotta take it to the Lost
Tinker Goblin of Fog Mountain
to fix it.
Dude, I would love to go
on some crazy made-up
adventure with you,
but I really gotta
read this.
So from here on out,
I'm just gonna ignore you.
[Muttering]
I don't make up
adventures!
Jake, you know that!
Jake!
I don't make up adventures!
[creak! thump! thump!
thump! thump! thump!]
Mm.
Books... books...
kitties... zitties...
witties...
mitties... knitties...
fitties... hitties...
jitties...
pitties...
cities...
oh, no!
Damaged books!
Who did this?!
Shh-ush!
Sorry.
I will avenge
the slightly soiled books.
Gotta tell Jake.
[Rattle!]
Hello?
Is someone back here?
Are you stuck?
Shh-ush-oom.
Hello?
Whoa!
Oh!
Hey, there's pages coming out
of these books!
Shhhhhh!
Who are you dudes?
ALL:
We are the Pagelings!
I am Paper Pete, the leader
of the Pagelings,
but you can call me P.P.
I'll call you Pete.
Okay.
Why are you dudes
in the library?
We are the secret guardians
of the books in the library.
You know those blank pieces
of paper
in the beginning
of old books?
- Yeah.
- That's us!
We revealed ourselves to you,
noble giant,
because you felt our plight
when you saw
the damaged books.
And now is our darkest hour,
for the Moldos have been
growing more bold
with every attack.
Look at the damage done
yesterday
at "The Battle of
Teddy Bear Joke Book."
Wow. Yeah.
They're massing
for a full-scale assault
on every book in the library.
Gosh!
Even the "Rainicornicopia"?
Yes.
I better tell Jake.
Don't you dudes go anywhere.
ALL:
Okay.
Hey, bro.
I've got an adventure.
It's not made-up.
There are these --
these Pagelings.
They came out from --
from books, and they --
they folded
into little animals.
Do you hear
what I'm saying?!
Shh!
You think I'm making
this up?
I'll prove it to you!
[grunting]
Finn! Finn!
You butt chicken!
[grunting]
Jake, wait 'til you see 'em.
Whoa!
[rumble!]
- Oh, my goodness!
- Oh, golly!
Ow!
[grunting]
They were just here!
Pagelings?
Why didn't you dudes introduce
yourselves to Jake?
We don't want to reveal
ourselves to anyone else.
We are the secret guardians --
secret.
Um...
yeah, but Jake is a powerful
giant, like me.
He can help you battle or --
or whatevs.
But first, you must win
his favor.
Do you not want victory
for your people?
ALL:
Yes! We do want victory!
Come on. Follow me.
Jake, look.
He's up here reading a book.
Do something to get
his attention.
Very well.
We shall dance as flowers.
ALL:
Hoopha!
Okay-
[Pagelings humming]
Ooh! Ahh!
Cha! Cha! Cha!
Jake! The Pagelings are
dancing for you!
Just look up for a second!
Finn, all the little
voices you're doing are cute,
but come on, man,
just let me read.
By wearing the beast, we
shall become like the beast!
You can feel them,
can't you?
I can feel
you pinching me.
Just look up for
a second.
Loo-o-o-o-o-o-o-k!
[sighs]
Pagelings, I'm sorry,
but my giant friend is
acting like a clump.
ALL:
Okay.
We can't wait any longer.
We must go back to
the bookshelf
to prepare
for the Moldos' attack.
Yeah, go play
make-believe somewhere else.
I'm not making believe!
[gasps]
We were gone too long!
[chomp! chomp! chomp!]
Wield, my brethren!
Wield!
[all moaning menacingly]
[all grunting]
[Yawns]
I blows]
Aaaaah!
[all grunting]
[all groaning woozily]
You win this battle,
but next time,
We will win it.
PAGELINGS:
Yes! Leave!
Yes! We did it!
Veni, vidi, vici!
So, those little,
squishy guys are the Moldos?
Aye.
This was but
a reconnaissance squad
sent to test our mettle.
ALL:
Mettle!
Uh-huh.
They -- they seem tough.
Their bites sting like
the dickens.
Hmm.
Their bites sting, eh?
I've got a plan, Pete.
Tell me your plan, giant.
Just trust me.
Trust me.
[squish!]
You've discovered the Moldos'
secret lair!
Eh, it wasn't
very hard.
[echoing]
Wippa Wippa waaaaa!
MOLDOS:
The Pagelings have a battle beast!
Attack!
[indistinct shouting]
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
moldy blobs.
I've come here to help the
Moldos defeat the Pagelings.
Traitor!
Hyah! Yah!
Calm down.
This is part of my plan.
Oh! Ha ha!
Then I shall play along,
wise giant.
How are we to trust you?
Well... here -- look!
I brought y'all a prisoner.
It's their leader.
May you rot in tartarus!
May your skin boil
and eyes burst into flames
forever in a pit!
[tink!]
Traitor!
So, do you guys have,
like, a leader or something?
[all murmuring "Mildwin"]
Mildwin!
I'm Mildwin,
leader of the Moldos.
Oh. Uh...
hmm.
[grunts]
Nice to meet you,
your highness.
I'm not a king.
I was democratically elected.
[laughs]
That's adorable.
Now, Finn!
Yah! Hunh! Hyah!
MOLDOS:
Protect the elected official!
[Panting]
PETE:
Well-played, oh, giant.
You have the cunning of Odysseus.
Pete, j-just stop winking.
Yo! Yah! Yah!
Hyoh! Hyoh! Yah!
Shh!
[Panting]
Hup-hup!
Ignore... this!
[chomp! chomp! chomp!]
Hmm?
This tastes delicious!
[chomp!]
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
[grunting]
What did you do to me?!
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
- Uh...
- Aaaaaaaah!
Uh... uhhh...
Come on, you guys.
Knock it off.
[Hisses]
The Moldos got a taste
for you now.
[whimpering]
Gotta do something!
Where can I find ways to solve
problems in a library?
Books?
Aah!
Books! Books! Books!
Ehhhhh!
[panting]
Huh?
[Chomp! chomp!]
What you nibbling me for?
This sweaty stuff tastes
amazing!
A-mazing!
Hmm.
Tastier than battle beast fur.
Yes!
Hey, Mildwin.
- Mildwin!
- What?
I bring a peace offering
from the Pagelings.
Hmm?
[sniffs]
[Moldos talking indistinctly]
Finn, what's happening?
Hang on, buddy.
Paper Pete?
Giant!
Have you wiped out
the Moldo horde?
No, man.
The war's over.
Mildwin, you can keep
my shirt
if you don't attack their
library books.
Agreed, beast.
This filthy garb will feed
my people for generations.
And in 40 years,
you can have my shorts.
Sound good, Pete?
It will suffice.
Sound good, Jake?
[grunting]
Yaaaaaaaaaah!
[snap!]
What -- what the hecks, man?!
What'd you do to me?!
Look, man!
Moldos and Pagelings are real!
Wha-- who cares, man?!
I'm outta here!
Did you finish your
Rainicorn book?
Ugh. I was reading
the same paragraph
over and over
for like 11 minutes.
I guess I'm gonna give up
on learning
everything
about Rainicorn history.
Don't tell Lady.
Oh. What about, uh, relating
to your mixed-species kids?
Eh, I'll just fake it.
Oh.
Well... hey, man,
I think I see some...
um... sun people
in trouble on the sun
over there.
- You making that up?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah! Let's do it!
FINN:
Whoo! Whoo!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!