WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS WENK]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪  With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[HUMMING]
[BEAT-BOXING]
[BABBLING IN STEP]
BOTH:
Yeah!
What's for b-fast, Jake?
Everything burrito.
[GASPS]
I love you, everything burrito.
[SMOOCHES]
[THUD]
[RATTLING]
Aw, man.
I think someone wants to
eat Everything Burrito.
I won't let them
get you, baby!
[SMOOCHES]
Jake, come on!
Get ready!
Ready!
BOTH:
Yaah!
[BOTH GASP]
Peep.
So cute!
Look at their
little faces!
[BOTH LAUGH]
We're not cute.
We're evil!
And we're here
to dominate you!
Get the camera, Jake.
I can't.
I'm paralyzed
by the cuteness!
BOTH:
Beemo! Beemo! Beemo!
Beemo!
What? What? What? What?
BOTH:
Beemo, get the camera!
Beemo is camera.
Enough!
Now...
Bow down to me, Cute King,
and my legion of cuties!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Great shot, Beemo!
Since you won't take us
seriously, we will kill you!
Until then,
enjoy your burrito, Jake.
Huh?
[CHUCKLES EVILLY]
[SHRIEKS]
My burrito!
It's perfectly fine!
No, Finn.
They probably poisoned it!
Naaaw.
They knew my name.
They knew about the burrito.
Man, you're letting your brain
dial turn your fear volume up.
You'll see.
Those cuties are nothin'
but an afternoon's delight.
[YAWNS]
Jake?
What are you doing in my bed?
Oh, nothin' much,
you know, just chillin'.
Wait a second.
Are you still messed up
about those little guys?
A little.
Look, man, what do you say
tomorrow morning we go track
those little guys down and find
out just what their deal is?
Sound good, buddy?
Yeah.
Thanks, buddy.
Man, you sound just
like mom sometimes.
Yeah. Good old mom.
She always knew
just what to say.
Yeah.
Good night, brotha.
Good night.
JAKE:
Finn! Finn!
Finn, wake up, man!
Wha?! Huh?
I think someone's
in the house.
[GRUMBLES]
For real, man!
Shh. Listen.
Uh...
I swear, man.
I really heard something.
[THUD]
[GASPS]
Finn!
I heard.
Okay. Who's out there?
What the?!
That's my sword!
What do they want
with my sword, man?
[CLATTER]
It came from downstairs!
All right. That's it.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go manhandle
those guys' banandles.
What?
FINN:
Well, they broke a window, but I don't see any of 'em.
I guess they left.
Oh, no!
Oh, oh, no!
Jake, what is it?
Oh, no!
It's a dead goat, man!
Its guts are all
over the place!
It's all chopped up
and spread around and --
Oh, no, wait.
It's just a blanket.
I think I left it
here this morning.
[EERILY]
Jake! Finn!
This is the voice of your mom!
I've come back to tell you
how dumb you always are!
I hate you guys so much!
Oh!
Get him, Jake!
Aah! Aah!
[HISSES]
Blauwgh!
[PANTING]
[YELPS]
Jake, I got him!
He's freakin' out, man!
- What do I do?!
- Shake him!
What?!
Shake him around
till he stops!
Okay-
[SHOUTING]
[PANTING SLOWLY]
They stopped.
Okay-
Now tell 'em not to
talk about our mom.
How do you even
know about our mom?
We've been watching you.
Learning your weaknesses.
What?! Why?!
For tomorrow morning.
When our army comes
and kills you both.
You think we're so cute,
when actually we're
the opposite of that!
[CHOMP!]
Waah!
Hold him!
[GRUNTING]
[POOL]
[BOTH LAUGH]
[TWEET!]
Oh, gross!
Well?
Do you believe me now, Finn?
I...
I don't know what
to believe anymore.
Well, that's close enough.
Let's start settin'
up some barricades.
[FANFARE PLAYS]
[SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
There's got to be
a thousand of em!
Wait. Jake, look!
JAKE:
These guys aren't a threat to anyone.
These guys are a
threat to themselves.
[GROANS]
Ow!
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Oh, hey,
it's what's his face.
No! My men!
Quickly, men!
Pick yourselves up
before the enemy sees!
Come on, now.
That's it.
Easy does it.
Ow.
Bravest warriors,
I ask you,
must we have our butts handed
to us by everyone we meet?!
How will we ever splash around
in the brains of our enemies if
you guys can't take two steps
without exploding?!
Bliblob,
I'm lookin' at you!
[BLAM!]
Can I please just get
one victory... once?!
[ALL SOBBING]
Now, don't start that!
Don't you do it!
[ALL CRYING]
[CRIES]
You want to just
smash 'em all?
What?!
No, man, look,
these guys aren't
gonna quit until
they win or die.
And they're not gonna win.
So what if we let 'em win?
Just this once?
What?!
And mess up my stats?!
No, we'd be winning
by helping them to win.
That's a win.
And then they'll be
happy and leave us alone.
All right.
Yesss!
Now let's rally an army
so we can look intimidating!
Who are we gonna call?
All of our friends.
My army of friends, today
we will lose this battle.
But we will also win it!
[ALL CHEER]
When the enemy charges,
crumble like a cookie.
When you feel their
puny punches,
fade like a flower and
writhe in your own blood!
But -- but -- how are we to
bleed if none of this is real?
With faith, Milady.
And ketchup.
[ALL CHEER]
Ketchup is delicious
and deceiving!
And, hey, guys,
let's keep the acting subtle.
Less is more!
No way.
First, I'm gonna fall in love
with one of those little guys.
And then I'm gonna
fall out of love.
And then I'm gonna totally fake
die of a fake heart attack!
Oh! My heart!
My heart hurts because
I fell out of love!
And now I have to die!
Ohhhhhhh!
[FANFARE PLAYS]
[CUTIES SHOUTING]
Get ready, y'all.
Together, we fall!
Unh!
Not yet, Cinnamon Bun!
Yaah!
ALL:
Whoa!
Oh, no! My bloooood!
Whooooa!
[LAUGHS]
Hey!
One last kiss before dying,
my love.
[SMOOCHES]
Farewell forever!
Oh! Oh, my heart!
Aah!
I'm dead!
Victory is ours!
[ALL CHEERING]
Finally...
I can do the victory dance!
♪ La ♪
♪ Lada ♪
♪ La da da la ♪
♪ La da da da da ♪
♪ La la la la-la la ♪
[LAUGHS]
Oh, I'm sorry, everybody!
I couldn't keep it in!
CUTE KING:
No!
This is ketchup?!
It tastes better
than blood.
Or does it?
Hey, Finn, you think blood
tastes better than ketchup'?
Jake, look.
[CRYING]
Aw, nuts.
Cute King, wait up!
We want to apologize
for being fakers.
We did it to protect
you from yourselves.
It doesn't matter now.
No one will ever
fear our strength.
But strength isn't
your strength.
Adorable cuteness is!
Can I use it to
control others?
Um...
Yeah, sure!
Just be righteous about it.
Show me where to start.
♪ Pbht pbht pbht ♪
♪ Pbht pbht pbht pbht ♪
♪ Pbht pbht pbht
pbht pbht pbht pbht ♪
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Huh?
Who could that be?
I command you to
make me a sandwich!
What?!
No one commands the Ice King
to make no sandwich!
What about now?
[GASPS]
[LAUGHS]
Okay!
[BOTH LAUGH]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!