WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to
very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
♪ The battle for supremacy
amongst masters of magic ♪
♪ Wizard Battle! ♪
Jake.
[SNORING]
Wizard Battle
is starting soon.
[GROAN]
I know!
We got here six hours early,
you dork.
Just wake me up when
they start selling hot dogs.
Whoa! What do you know?
[CHOMP! MUNCH! MUNCH!]
[GASPS]
FINN:
The wizards are arriving!
[CROWD CHEERS]
Whoo-hoo! YeahH
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen...
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
...I am the grand master
wizard of ceremonies.
And now...the rules!
Contestants will fight each
other with spells from the eight
schools of magic.
No science,
Science Whyzard!
No weapons, Weaponhead!
Hmph!
To enter Wizard Battle,
you must be ...a wizard!
Whoo, only wizards allowed!
Whoo! Whoo!
Wh-- oh, what?
Ice King!
Boo!
You're a contestant?
Mm-hmm.
You guys come here to
watch me win?
[SCOFFS]
You're gonna lose, man.
You're a loser.
Ha!
I'm not gonna lose.
I've got a foolproof
plan for winning.
I'm gonna cheat.
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[RUMBLE]
GRAND WIZARD: And now,
L's and G's, witness the unveiling of
this tournament's Grand Prize --
a kiss...
from Princess Bubblegum...
[CROWD CHEERS]
[SMOOCH! SMOOCH!]
...on the mouth!
[CROWD CHEERS]
Boo! Boo!
Hmm.
Is it an open-mouth kiss?
No!
Then I choose to
exit the battle.
Yeah.
GRAND WIZARD:
No one is allowed to exit Wizard Battle!
[ZAP!]
[ALL MEOW]
The doors are shut!
The sky barrier is in place!
All of you will kiss the
Princess or die in battle!
Oh, I just can't wait to
taste that sweet Bubblegum.
[CHUCKLES]
Jake, we got to enter the
contest and stop Ice King!
But we're not wizards, mang.
What about the sanctity and
honor of Wizard Battle'?
I'd rather sanctify PB's lips.
Ooh! You don't care
about the Ice King --
You just want to kiss
Princess Bubblegum.
No, I want to save the Princess!
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you do.
I do!
Oh, shush!
[CLATTER!]
Now...where's the Ice King?
[ZWIP!]
[ZAP!]
JAKE:
Over there!
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
[SNIFFING]
Oh, yeah.
We need a plan, man.
Okay, when the wizards
start to battle,
let's go hide behind that rock.
By the rays of the setting sun,
the battle of wizards has...
begun!
[ALL SCREAM]
[ZAP! ZAP! ZAP!]
[ZZZZAP!]
[WIND BLOWS]
[FOOSH! FOOSH! FOOSH! FOOSH!]
Looks like everyone
had the same plan.
[WIND RUSHING]
What are they waiting for?
BOY:
The opposites.
Huh?
The wizards with opposite powers
will take each other on first.
And...
are you a wizard?
Yes. My name is...
Abracadaniel!
[GRUNTING]
Ugh!
[GASPS]
Hi, Abracadaniel.
My name is, uh...
Magic, uh, Fist.
Whoa, this kid
looks like a wimp.
Who is that?
He's my [CHUCKLES] uh,
magic second head.
Well, he's right.
[SIGHS]
I only entered this contest
'cause I thought the
prize would be money,
but it's just a kiss!
You mean...you don't
care about kissing PB?
Ugh, no Way!
If I were the winner, I would
turn my face so our lips [GASPS]
Wouldn't touch,
and I would push Princess away.
Turn...and push!
This guy is great!
Well, I'm going back to my cave
to wait for someone to kill me.
Good bye.
Wait! Abracadanny, don't
you worry about a thing.
I'm gonna protect you.
You will?
Yeah, man.
Also, I have an idea for how
you can help me save PB's lips.
Um, okay.
[ZAP!]
Aaah!
Oh! Look, opposites
are going to battle.
Hyah!
[GASPS]
Cheating!
He's using a weapon!
Why isn't the Grand Wizard
seeing this?
[LAUGHING]
[MEOWING]
Nunchucks, vanish!
Booyah!
Now's my chance to stop him!
Ooh.
Aaah!
Rock Wizard!
[ROARS]
Come to be,
Meteor shower!
Rock Wizard compels you!
Cantrip!
Huh?
Mm!
Aah!
[GASPS]
No!
Jake, 2 o'clock!
Okay, now to stop the
Ice Ki-i-i-ng?
My body is squishy.
That's how I survived.
Whoa!
That's turbo amazing!
ICE KING:
Hyah!
Whaaaa!
Stay close to me, Abracadaniel.
[ZAP! ZAP! ZAP!]
[ZAP! WHOOSH!]
Aaah!
[ROARS]
Cantrip!
What?!
You turned me pink, Bro!
Ugh!
[MEOWING]
[LAUGHING]
Three wizards remain!
Time to get real!
I want to see some
crazy Wiz Biz!
[CROWD CHANTS "WIZ BIZ"]
Wiz Biz! Wiz Biz!
Oh, I can almost taste
those sweet lips!
Wlllah! Wlllah!
[SHUDDERS]
Quick, listen!
Now's the time for
you to help me!
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
ICE KING:
Hey, guys. Guys?
What are you whispering?
Come on!
I got a surprise
for youse fools!
Yeah, that's right.
Just a little closer.
Ooh, what's in here,
in my little sleevie hole?
Watch out, man!
Whoo!
You got this, Danny Boy!
[SLINKY]
[PLOINK]
My nunchucks! No!
Yes!
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
I did it!
I really did it!
[GASPS]
I'm a true wizard!
I have powers too, you butts!
Hyah!
Ice sword!
Ice shield!
Abracadaniel!
[SLINKY]
What?
What'd you say?
Ohm
[CROWD CHEERS]
Good job, Danny.
You're not a wimp anymore.
You should feel pretty good.
I do.
I feel real good!
I'm gonna forfeit now.
I only wanted to
stop the Ice King.
Unh-unh.
I forfeit!
I forfeit, everyone!
[CROWD CHEERS]
[MEOWS]
Whoa!
Abracadaniel wins!
You are the greatest
wizard in Ooo!
Oh! Ooh!
Oh, thank you,
Grand Master Wizard.
I guess, through this trial,
I have become a great wizard.
I-I came here with no
self-esteem and no chances,
a willow wisp of a boy, but I
walk out of this arena a man,
a confident man who deserves
a kiss from a Princess!
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[CREAK! CREAK!]
[CREEEAK!]
No-o-o-o-o-o!!
It appears you have knocked out
Abracadaniel using the most
shameful of all magic,
a power shriek.
[CROWD MURMURING]
But since you are the last wizard,
you are the winner of Wizard Battle!
[CROWD CHEERS]
Go get ready for your kiss, champ.
[SIGHS]
[CREAKY]
Wow, man!
What?
I never heard you
scream like that before.
You were all like,
"No-o-o-o-o!
No one kisses her
but me-e-e-e!"
Yeah, okay, I want to kiss her,
all right? You got me!
The big secret is out!
Okay, Jake! I like Princess Bubblegum!
Are you happy, Jake?!
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[PLONK! PLONK!]
Whoa.
Jake, don't cry, man.
I'm not really mad at you.
[SNIFFLES]
I'm just sick of having to
hide my feelings all the driz.
It's exhausting.
Then stop hiding your feelings, man.
Go out there and smooch it up!
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, all right, man.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
You ready in there?
Yeah, I'm comin'!
♪ Get ready for
the ultimate prize ♪
♪ Watch her lips pout
before your eyes ♪
♪ Never in your life would
you dream of this ♪
♪ Never in your
freaking life ♪
Ugh!
Whoa!
[GASPS]
Ow, dag.
What's going on here?
Uh, Ice King was
cheating his way through
Wizard Battle using nunchucks,
so Jake and I faked being
wizards to save you from
having to kiss him.
And -- and we...
[SIGHS]
I dishonored Wizard Battle.
Oh, Finn,
you did all that for me?
[SMOOCH!]
That's for being sweet...
[SLAP!]
...and that's for cheating.
Finn, you know better than
to ruin the sanctity of
Wizard Battle!
Wizards only, silly.
Okay, everyone, go home!
Start getting ready
for next year!
[WIZARDS GROAN]
Meh.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, well.
Good job.
You got the kiss, man.
Thanks, man.
My face hurts a little.
Don't worry about that,
'cause you look totally cool
right now.
Thanks, dude.
Here, you try 'em.
Okay. Am I cool now?
So fly.
How about me?
Put me on the grid,
scale of 1 to 10.
1 is "Totally gross."
10 is like, "Dang, Ice King,
you look crazy si-i-ck!"
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪