WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[WATER DRIPPING, ECHOING]
Do you think it's right for Marceline
to invite us to jam
without Princess and Beemo?
It's just a jam sesh.
Is that what you're gonna
jam with?
Yeah, man.
Balloon music is the future.
Listen.
[BALLOON SQUEAKING]
[RAPPING]
♪ Shake your extremities ♪
♪ All your arms and knees ♪
♪ I want 'em shakin',
baby, please ♪
♪ Baby, shake your eyes for me ♪
♪ Shake your eyes for me ♪
♪ Shake your eyes
for me ♪
♪ Shake your eyes for free ♪
♪ Now make some bills,
make duck bills ♪
♪ Make 'em ill,
quack me up ♪
- [QUACKS]
- ♪ With some yolks ♪
♪ I like girls
who know the ropes ♪
♪ I like girls who can cope ♪
♪ with the futuristic sound ♪
♪ of balloon music ♪
Pretty good.
I don't think
you've mastered it yet.
Well, duh.
I just started.
Oh, dude.
Here's a note.
What's it say?
"Hey, guys, I had to run out,
but I'll be back.
Blee bloo blop.
Don't go in my house."
- That's it?
- Yeah.
Just "don't go in my house"
in all caps --
written in blood.
Hmm.
[BALLOON SQUEAKING]
What are you doing?
Eliminating desire from my heart.
It helps pass the time.
Come on.
I can't do that.
Let's play cloud hunt
'til she gets here.
No, man, I got a mental block
with cloud hunt.
Yeah, that's what makes it awesome --
'cause I know I'll win.
Oh, what?!
Bring it on, brother!
Now, explain the rules,
'cause I forget.
Okay. I count to 10
and you go hide somewhere.
Then I got to try to find you.
You can hide...
you can hide anywhere in here.
Anywhere in here.
But Marcy's house is off-limits,
because she said so, okay?
- Got it.
Okay, I'm gonna start
counting.
Ready?
Yes.
Go!
One...
two...
three...
four...
five...
Over the mountain
the ominous cloud,
coming to cover the land
in a shroud.
Hide in a bushel,
a basement, a cave,
but when cloud comes a-huntin',
no one's a-save!
No -- safe.
Cloud hunt...
gotcha!
Huh.
Hmm.
Aha!
[WATER SPLASHING]
Jake! Get out of there!
Marceline's gonna kill you!
Jake!
I know this isn't a mirror!
What the --
You're doing it wrong, even!
Get out! Get out!
[CAT DOOR OPENS]
Dude, get out of there!
She's gonna kill us!
She could be home any minute!
Did you read the note?!
I mean, you read the note!
You told it to me!
[RUSTLING]
[GASPS]
[SWITCH CLICKS]
[SNIFFS]
Smells like sourdough in here.
She's gonna kill us!
Once she finds out,
she's gonna tie us up
and eat us like a spider!
You don't think I know that?
Hurmmmmm.
We'll wait for the right moment
and sneak out,
right under her big, fat caboose.
Okay, man.
I can do this.
[GRUNTING]
Shh! Here she comes!
- Here she comes!
- Shh! Shhh!
[SNIFFS]
[SWITCH CLICKS]
Huh.
[DOOR CLOSES, TOILET LID CLUNKS]
[ZIPPER OPENS]
[LIQUID SPLASHING]
Let's get outta here!
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SPLASHING STOPS, RESUMES]
[SPLASHING STOPS]
MARCELINE: Hello?
[TOILET FLUSHES]
She didn't wash hands!
Is someone here?
[SNIFFS]
[SNIFFING]
That's what stinks!
Where are those dweebs?
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
[RINGING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[ANSWERING MACHINE CLICKS]
- FINN: This is Jake!
- JAKE: And this is Finn!
[BOTH LAUGH]
BOTH: We're not home
right now, so...
[BOTH LAUGH]
...leave a message!
[MUFFLED LAUGHTER]
Shh.
BOTH: ...leave a message!
[BEEP]
Uh... y-yeah.
Hey, you guys.
Are you still coming over?
It's jam time, so, like,
call me, 'Kay??
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
[SHORTS]
[SNAPS FINGERS]
[SPLAT]
[RUSTLING]
[RUSTLING, PAPER CRINKLES]
Whatcha doin'?
Turn around.
When she gets this, she'll leave
and we can escape.
Brilliant!
But how's it gonna work?
I'll fly the paper
as an airplane
down the bedroom ladder.
It'll triple-barrel-roll past
the kitchen,
open the fridge
and cook some eggs,
then eat the eggs and unfold itself
as it lays on the carpet in
front of Marceline's door.
Yeah, yeah!
Awesome! Yeah!
[SIZZLING]
[PAN CLATTERS]
No! Nu-- nuts!
[SIGHS]
Well, if they're not
gonna show up,
then I'll just work
on my own stuff, I guess.
[BASS PLAYS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Take one for new concept album
based on 500 years
of my journal entries.
So here's some preliminary notes.
I...
I want to make this the most
emotional album ever --
so private and secret that
I'll never let anyone hear.
This is so wrong.
No one can ever hear it!
Ever!
[DRUMBEAT PLAYS]
Take one.
♪ Hello, journal, it's me ♪
♪ It's been a while since we talked
about my life and stuff ♪
♪ Let's start with my feelings
about my friends ♪
I' Oh, Wait I'
♪ I don't have friends ♪
We've crossed the line!
I'm getting out of here, man!
Yeah! Do it!
MARCELINE:
♪ Because they don't know what it's like ♪
♪ to live forever ♪
♪ and forget who you even are
and what you think about
anything ♪
♪ How can anyone relate to me
when they cannot see what I... ♪
[HISSES]
♪ My vampire eyes see only
blood-red skies ♪
♪ Blood-red skies make tears
inside that I always hide ♪
♪ So ♪
♪ I walk alone ♪
Pin?
♪ my ♪
♪ mental home ♪
- Wha-- What's it doing?
♪ I can't let on ♪
[BOTH GASP]
[CRASH]
Shh! Shh-shh-shh-shh!
Oh, What?!
What happened?!
Ugh!
[HISSES]
Where are you?!
Oh, there you are.
My broom.
[SIGHS]
Ugh. Stupid thing.
Get...
No! Stupid!
Argh!
Ugggh!
Euggggh!
[FAUCET SQUEAKS,
WATER SPLASHES]
- Is it safe?
- I don't know, man.
Go scope the scene.
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC DISTORTS]
What happened, man?
I'm not going back out there.
Well...
what do you mean?
What happened?
Bro?
[HAIR DRYER WHIRRING]
[WHIRRING STOPS]
[YAWNS]
[SWITCH CLICKS]
[SNORING]
Hmmmmm...
[SNORING CONTINUES]
MARCELINE:
Hmm.
[CHOMPS]
- Is she awake?
- Why are you talking?!
I'm wondering if she's awake.
Well, if she's awake, she can
definitely hear you talking!
I'm whispering!
Well, now we're both
quietly screaming!
MARCELINE:
I can hear both of you.
Disguise yourself, fool!
[SWITCH CLICKS]
What are you bozos doing
in my lair?
Dude, I think
she sees us.
What the...
Dude!
You shape-changed
to look like me?!
- Yeah.
- MARCELINE: Hey!
Exsssplain yourselves.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
We were playing hide-and-seek
in your closet,
and you came home,
so we hid in there all day.
We saw... everything.
And, oh, glob!
I mean, whatever you do to us,
I just want to say we're sorry!
So sorry!
Okay. Apology accepted.
What?!
I hide in your house
all the time.
Anyways, no hard feelings, guys.
See you soon.
[SNIFFS]
[HOOTING IN DISTANCE]
Marceline?
Jake?!
[SHOWER WATER RUNNING]
Jake!
Hm'?
Hey, man, did --
[BOTH SCREAM]
[HOOTS]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ and the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ and do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ to a cliff under a tree ♪