WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS WENK]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Hey.
What kind of
coffee do you want'?
[FIRE CRACKLES]
Hazelnut! Hazelnut!
What if your name
was Zul Nut?
And then I would be
like "Hey, Zul Nut! "
That's terrible.
Hey, Zul Nut!
No-o-o-o!
Stop!
[LAUGHS]
[BANGING]
Do you hear that?
Yeah.
[CRASH!]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
BOTH:
Susan Strong!
Finn?
Help Susan.
Of course I will.
Excuse us for a moment,
Strong.
Dude, you know you're my Bro,
but that girl is bad news.
What?! Nah.
She's crazy, man.
She's a fish person.
We don't know that.
Dude!
She tried to eat
Peppermint Butler.
She'd probably do worse if she
weren't so scared of everything.
Whatever.
Look, she needs my help.
And I'm gonna help her whether
you're coming with me or not.
Oh, I'm coming with you.
If only to be disruptive
and obnoxious!
Susan, what can we do?
I need your hero heart
and your magic.
My magic?
Magic of red flower.
[HISSES]
Uhh.
Fish people.
SUSAN:
Long ago, my people live in Beautopia.
But driven out by Lubglubs.
We come here.
We too scared to fight back.
This why we need
your hero heart.
Humans!
[ALL GASP]
I'll be back.
Fish people!
I'll be...um...
a dolphin!
[ALL GASP]
[CHUCKLES]
Come on.
We swim there.
No, you don't understand.
I'm not a fish person.
I'm human.
[LAUGHS]
We go.
[GASPS]
[COUGHING, GAGGING]
[GROWLS]
What?! Hey! Hey! What?
You no gills.
[GASPS]
We take boat.
♪ Oh, I'm on a boat
with a couple of wackos ♪
♪ Shaking my hips and dipping
my fat toe in the water ♪
♪ Dip it in the water ♪
♪ This party's getting hotter ♪
♪ It's so hot it's stupid ♪
So, where are we headed,
Susan?
There.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
No, no.
No, no, no, no.
No, Susan, no!
BOTH:
[SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
[LAUGHS]
That was awesome.
See, Jake?
We can trust Susan.
She's on the trolley.
Keep looking for Lubglub.
No move.
Whew.
We safe now.
What?
Dude, she's crazy.
She's not crazy.
She's cool.
Whatever, man.
This is a crazy cruise,
and Susan is our crazy Captain.
And I'm a crazy clamshell!
Boooo-eeep!
Ooh! Oh! Doin' the clam!
[LAUGHS]
Quit acting like a clam,
you ham.
Mm-mm-mm.
Aah, eh, ooh, unh.
Mm, oh, mm, ahh,
mm-mm-mm-mm.
Ah, ooh, yeah.
Bbbbbbbb!
[CRASHING IN DISTANCE]
Hey, are you
hearing that, too?
Getting close to the
Lubglubs' mashem-ups.
Huh?
Behold.
Balzacs!
[CRASHING CONTINUES]
The clashing gates!
S'okay.
Susan know when it's
safe to pass through.
Uh, Finn,
let's get out of here.
Come on.
She knows this place.
Trust.
Ready when you are,
Susan.
You know, I could just
stretch us over this thing.
Go...now!
Aaah!
Aaaah! Aah!
Aah!
Whoa!
[ALL GROAN]
Oh, good.
Still got some boat left.
She's flippin' crazy.
Come on, Finn.
Let's bail.
Chill out.
Hmph.
All right, Susan.
What do we do next?
Hmm.
Never made it
this far before.
Just got to get
past Lubglubs.
Yeah, what are Lubglubs,
exactly?
They, um, look --
they look like this.
Hm.
That looks like my father.
Now I'm crazy!
Yes, Lubglubs crazy scary.
Humans scare so long,
even Susan.
That's why
glad I meet you.
You have brave heart.
[CRUNCH!]
Thank you.
Hyup!
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
Whoa.
We here?
We at B-Beautopia!
Whoa!
Ominous.
Will be alls good once bring
red flower to city heart.
[WATER SPLASHING]
What's making all
that swishing?
Lubglubs. They coming.
[LAUGHS]
It's just more
pool floaties.
[GASPS]
Shh!
Too many Lubglub to fight!
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
Susan! Susan.
Lubglubs are just pool toys.
Watch.
I'm putting an end to all this
craziness with my pickax hand.
Nyuh nyuh nyuh nyuh
nyuh nyuh nyuh nyuh.
No more craziness.
[HISSING]
Oh.
Uh-ho-ho.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
Oooh.
Jakey beefed it!
[CRUNCH! CRUNCH! CRUNCH!]
[GROWLS]
Oooh!
[CHOMP!]
[WHIMPERS]
Bad news, dude.
There's only two of us and more
than, um ...this many of them.
Got to use the fire
like Susan said.
You okay with that?
Yes.
I'm okay with that.
I'll do whatever
Susan says.
Aah!
Susan!
We need you!
[WHIMPERS]
Susan scared.
But Susan brave, too.
Susaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaan!
Yeah, Susan!
[LAUGHS]
[GROANS]
Susan!
Finn! Jake!
I gots it.
Red Flower!
Throw it to city heart!
Finn, lend aid
to fair Susan.
Jake brings the fire.
Hyah!
Humans and hyoomans
got to stick together.
Huh?
Hmm.
[GRUNTS]
Almost...there.
[GRUNTING]
Oh, so I just
toss it in here?
It's pretty
straightforward.
Okay. Well, here I go.
One...two...three...
[GROWLS]
That reminds me
of my mother.
[GRUNTING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
It's working, Susan.
Jake.
Whoa.
It is beautiful.
You were right, Susan.
This place is great.
Well, we better get home.
Finn, you stay.
No. I can't.
I'm not like you.
[WARBLE! WARBLE!]
Susan.
Come on, Finn!
Let's go!
I grabbed like
100 soft pretzels!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪
FINN:
This party is so crazy!