CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screams)
This Ghost Town
is going to be great.
Now with 30%
more gunfights.
And 40% more
rootin' tootin'.
And the tumbleweeds tumble
at 2:00, 4:00 and 6:00
plus a midnight tumbling
on weekends.
It's so sweet of you to take
us out like this, Homie.
Come on, kids, three cheers
for your father.
-Hip-hip...
-Mom, don't.
-We heard you the first time.
Hip-hip...
Hey, I'm trying to drive here.
Hey, Dad, that light says
"check engine."
Uh-oh. Tape must
have fallen off.
(alarm beeping)
There. Problem solved.
(backfiring)
LISA: Oh, come on!
Relax. She just needs
a little loving.
(engine grinding)
(gasping and screaming)
Ah, they remembered
my birthday.
Come on, come on, come on.
Start, damn you.
Start!
♪ Happy birthday to me ♪
(screaming)
-(groaning) Oh!
-(shrieks)
Two hours?
Why'd they build this
Ghost Town so far away?
Because they discovered gold
right over there.
It's because they're
stupid, that's why.
That's why everybody
does everything.
This should be
very educational.
I want you kids
to pay attention.
Founded by
prostitutes in 1849
and serviced by
prostitute express riders
who could bring in
a fresh prostitute
from St. Joe
in three days
Bloodbath Gulch quickly
became known as a place
where a trail hand could spend
a month's pay in three minutes.
Three minutes?
(whistles)
I never realized
history was so filthy.
First on our tour
is the whorehouse.
Then we'll visit
the cathouse,
the brothel, the bordello
and finally,
the old mission.
Oh, thank heaven.
-Lots of prostitutes in there.
-(Marge groans)
But there was more to the old
west than just sex, folks.
A lot more.
If you look off to your left,
you'll see a real old
west hitching post
possibly used by bandits
possibly during
some exciting adventure.
(all murmuring)
And these planks below us
were often used as a sidewalk
by people who may or may not
have been bandits.
(camera shutters clicking)
That's a keeper.
Uh, yes, sir?
Do we have
to listen to you?
Well... No, you don't
but if you have
any interest in history...
I'm done.
BART: Wow. Have you ever seen
so many robot cowboys?
(yelling)
Hey, robot, get your fat
metal ass down here.
First of all,
I'm not a robot.
And second, I got this
metal ass in 'Nam
defending this country
for lazy jerks like you.
Now what'll you have,
partner?
Let's see. One, two, three...
Six whiskeys.
All right.
We only serve sarsaparilla,
mac-- no alcohol.
Oh.
-You can get drunk when we get home.
-Duh.
(speaking mechanically)
Hey, these cards are marked.
Now look what
you've done.
I'm sorry. I don't know
what came over me.
Let's forget this
whole thing happened.
What the heck is this,
a tea party?
Somebody kill somebody!
(screaming)
What is it with you
and robots?
(grunts)
(playing saloon music)
Ooh, hello, sweet cheeks.
(smacking sound)
Look who's a little cowgirl.
Hey, Mom, look what I got.
Oh, that's cute.
(chuckling) Did you get it
in the souvenir shop?
No, that security guard
is handing them out.
(clearing throat)
Uh-oh. Better run
for cover, partners.
Some varmints are
havin' a shoot-out.
Yee-haw!
You stole my prostitute!
-Missed me!
-Die, yellow belly!
Bang-bang!
(slurring words)
Which way is the gunfight?
(all laughing)
There's old Curly.
He played the town preacher
until we laid him off
but he still hangs around.
Help me, please. I'm sick.
(laughing)
Homer...
But it's funny, Marge.
The guy's sick.
(groans)
(gurgling)
Uh, shouldn't we help him?
He knows what he's doing.
(gulping)
Ah! Can't get a good
sarsaparilla like this
back in Springfield.
It angries up the blood.
You like it, huh?
Up yours!
(honking)
Can I go to the bathroom
before we leave?
(whining) We've got
to get home.
I don't want to miss
Inside the Actor's Studio.
Tonight it's F. Murray Abraham.
But I really need to...
F... Murray... Abraham.
(whistling)
(Grandpa whimpering)
There's a rest area.
Pull over.
Can't stop now.
We're making great time.
(Grandpa moaning)
Can I go behind a tree?
What are you, an animal?
HOMER: Whoever keeps saying
"please stop" back there, better quit it.
(Grandpa groaning)
HOMER: Wow. Get a load
of that toilet.
Please go back.
You can make it
my birthday present.
We're almost home, Dad.
Only a couple more times
over the horizon.
But I might explode.
You just sit
back and relax.
I'm not going
to let anything happen
to my old dad.
Oh, dear god!
This man's kidneys have exploded.
There's nothing left.
Oh, no.
Yep, that's what happens
when you get older.
It's one of those
natural things--
Beautiful in its way.
Uh, actually, his kidneys
were fine yesterday
When he had
his annual checkup.
Excuse me, doctor.
I think I know a little
something about medicine.
Homer, with all due respect
this X-ray reveals a textbook
kidney blowout--
Which would explain
those loud pops you heard.
So... you're saying
I don't need a new muffler?
I don't feel so good.
Maybe I ought
to eat something.
Oh, I'm afraid your
eating days are over.
(chuckling)
Ohh...
How long do
I have to live, doc?
(chuckles)
I'm amazed
you're alive now.
Oh, I blame myself for this.
We all blame you.
Come on, doc,
there's got to be
something I can do
to help my dad.
Well, you could give him a kidney.
A kidney?
Okay, fine.
You see, the waiting list
for a kidney is very long and...
I said fine.
What is it about the word
"sure" you don't understand?
Oh, thank you, son.
Mmm. I'll take the left one.
It's good and springy
though the right one's
not without its charms.
Pork chops, sloppy joes,
hot dogs and pork chops.
Well, Dr. Hibbert said
you have to build up
your strength.
Besides, nothing's too good
for a wonderful,
generous man like you.
Well, that's what I always
thought, but somehow...
Check it out, Dad.
I rented all your
favorite gorilla movies--
Gorilla Squadron,
Gorilla Island Six.
(gasps) Apes-A-Poppin.
Ooh, the airline version.
Can I fluff your pillow?
Nothing's too good for me.
Ah, I'm the luckiest man
in the world
now that Lou Gehrig's dead.
Well, I got to hand it
to you, Homer.
You're really brave to go
through with this operation.
It's not
an operation, Moe.
The doctor says
it's just a procedure.
No, no, no. Making polenta,
that's a procedure.
You're talking about deadly,
life-threatening surgery here.
Really?
You think it's dangerous?
Oh, yeah, and even if you
survive the operation...
Procedure, deadly procedure.
Whatever. The point is
with only one kidney
you won't be able to drink
yourself stupid no more.
Now you're just trying to scare me.
Plus, they'll put
you on one of those
organ donor sucker lists.
Everybody who wants an eyeball
or a spine or a vestigial
tail will be after you.
But I don't want that.
Listen, I'm just going
to get right to the point here.
Can I have your buttocks?
I mean, if you die.
They look pretty comfortable.
Yeah, I guess.
And, uh, are those
your original lips?
Well, actually I...
Hey, quit harvesting
me with your eyes.
Oh, yeah, that would
look so good on me.
Marge, I've been thinking.
What if instead of donating
one of my old, worn-out kidneys,
I gave grandpa that
artificial kidney I invented?
Oh, Homer,
that was just a beer can
with a whistle glued to it.
Oh, but I don't want them
cutting up my soft, supple body.
Why didn't somebody tell me
what I was volunteering for?
This is everybody's fault
but mine.
Oh, I know you're
scared, Homie,
but remember why
you're doing this.
It's for your father.
The man who raised
you and nurtured you.
Jack and Jill went
up the hill and...
Jill came tumbling after.
The end. Good night.
Is that the same Jack
from Jack and the Bean Stalk?
You know, son, I believe it is.
And Jack Sprat--
is that him, too?
Sure, why not? Good night.
Is he the same
as Jack be Nimble
and Jack Frost
and little Jack Horner?
Say, how about a little Nyquil?
All gone.
Oh, I love you, son.
I owe Dad so much.
Those bedtime stories began
my lifelong love affair
with the printed word.
Well, giving him a kidney
is a wonderful way
to show him how you feel.
You're right, Marge.
I'll do it, but if I die
during the operation,
will you do
one thing for me?
Oh, anything, sweetheart.
Blow up the hospital.
Hmm. Well...
I said I'd do it
So I guess I'll have to.
That's my girl.
Hmm.
WOMAN (on P.A.):
Doc Martens to podiatry...
Liability waiver?
Don't read it, just sign it.
Yeah, but all these skulls
and crossbones on here...
I don't usually sign stuff like that.
It simply says you won't
hold us responsible
if you die as a result
of gross negligence.
It's a standard form.
Oh...
I love you, son.
I love you, Dad.
Now, don't you fellas worry.
This will all be over soon.
And... What the...?
We got to get rid of that window.
Where'd he go?
(grunting)
I can't imagine Dad
running away like this.
Leaving his father to die?
Even I wouldn't do that,
and I'm America's bad boy.
It's a heart-breaking situation.
(chuckles sadly)
Am I dead yet?
No.
How about now?
-No.
-Now?
I'll tell you when
you're dead, Grandpa.
Thank you.
(grunting)
Whew.
I'm not worthy to live
among civilized people.
(men coughing and grunting)
Even those guys
look too civilized for me.
(bird caws)
(gasps) I could live at sea.
The sea forgives all--
Not like those
mean old mountains.
I hate them so much.
(men groaning)
The sea won't stand for this.
Uh, excuse me.
I'm fleeing in shame,
and I'd like to look my best.
Um, can I be a mate on your ship?
Preferably first mate.
Well, if you look closely
you'll see this is a taffy shop
shaped like a ship.
Oh, I like taffy,
but I don't deserve taffy.
(snoring)
Hey, hey!
What?
Krusty here to cheer you up
as part of the hospital's
last laugh program.
Last laugh?
So, how about
that hospital food, huh?
I wouldn't know.
I'm not allowed to eat.
Okay, well, let's have a look
at the old chart.
Oh, boy, ooh!
Looks like we're
both short on time.
So I'll go
to the big finish.
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
♪ To me! ♪
Feel better.
Come back, doctor.
(whistle blows)
A tramp steamer, that's perfect.
(panting)
(grunts)
I'd like to apply
for a job-- any job.
If you don't have a captain,
I could be that.
Argh. What other ships
have you been on?
I've been on that one,
the Taffy Shop.
Argh. Good enough.
(grunting)
Welcome aboard...
the Ship of Lost Souls.
The name on the back
says Honeybunch.
Arr. I've been meaning
to paint over that.
Now, come and meet
the rest of the damned.
Did I mention they're...
lost souls?
Well, actually you did.
Argh...
(French accent) Ah, another lost soul
has joined
our world-weary ensemble.
Hey, who are you guys?
(mirthless laugh)
Who are we? No one.
Where are we sailing?
Nowhere.
Do we even exist?
Who knows?
Hey, let me off this thing.
Oh, don't listen to him.
-We exist all right.
-Whew!
We wander the seven seas,
trying to forget.
-Forget what?
-Oh, boy, here we go.
My story of jilted love
is long and bittersweet.
If anyone has to go
to the bathroom, go now.
I don't want you walking
around during my story.
My story's better, it has tigers.
I was born into wretched poverty.
So one day, I stole
a loaf of bread,
put it in the freezer
until it was very hard,
then robbed a bank with it.
(gasps)
And when Mr. Dinkley
saw what I had done
I was banned
from the car wash forever.
Forever? How awful.
I would have killed Dinkley for that.
As you can see
we're a contemptible lot of cads
bounders and tiger stabbers.
Come, stranger--
join our circle of infamy.
Tell us your story of Ennui.
Well, back on land,
my name was Homer Simpson,
and I guess it is here, too.
I promised my dad
one of my kidneys,
but I chickened out
at the last minute
and left him
on his deathbed.
Good lord.
Oh, how could you?
I think I'm going to be sick.
I stole this accordion
from a blind monkey,
but you...!
You disgust even me.
Well, yeah, I know...
(screams)
(whistle blows)
That's the last time I trust
the strangest people on Earth.
(spitting and coughing)
Even the sea won't forgive me.
That's the best sand castle
we've ever built, Dad.
We make a great team, son.
Oh, I wish I had that kind
of relationship with my father...
or my kids.
Well, I guess it's up to me
to take the first step.
-(sobbing)
-Hey!
WOMAN (on P. A.):
Dr. Bombay, come right away.
All right, this is it--
no more living in shame.
I'm going to show my family
the kind of man I really am.
(whimpering)
All right, I'm going to...
(shrieks)
(device beeping)
Aren't you going to give
him the last rites?
That's Catholic, Marge.
You might as well ask me
to do a voodoo dance.
Dr. Hibbert, I thought you'd located
another kidney for grandpa.
Larry Hagman took it.
He's got five of them now
and three hearts.
We didn't want
to give them to him,
but he overpowered us.
Don't worry about old grandpa.
I'm going to a better place...
Shelbyville Hospital.
(grunting)
Oh, who am I kidding?
I'm a goner.
HOMER: No, you're not, Dad.
-Dad!
-(gasps) Homer!
Son!
I'm sorry, Dad.
The way I behaved
was shameful.
I guess fear
made me run away...
But love made me come back.
Bless you, son.
I knew you'd come through for me.
Now, Homer, this may sting
just a tiny bit but...
Oh, son of a...!
(panting and whimpering)
Oh, dear.
(screaming)
Whew! Boy, that--
(screams)
He's waking up.
Oh, Homie, I'm so glad
you're all right.
(groans)
Try not to move, Dad.
You swallowed a lot of motor oil.
I'm sorry I ran off again.
Oh, I guess Dad
must be dead by now.
When I get better
and, after I build those
shelves for the kitchen...
we'll visit his grave.
GRANDPA: Grave, nothing.
I never felt more alive.
(laughing)
(bones cracking)
Oh, boy, I shouldn't have done that.
It's a miracle.
You recovered.
(all chuckle nervously)
What?
Hey.
While we were setting
your broken bones
and putting your blood back in
we helped ourselves to a kidney
and gave it to your father.
You butcher, give it back!
Give me that!
(Grandpa laughs)
♪ Na, na, na-na. ♪
HOMER: Don't you dance
out that door, you--
I'll get my kidney back, old man.
You have to sleep sometime.
I know you're a little peeved
at Grandpa, Dad.
But you've done a wonderful thing.
Yes, you've shortened
your life significantly
so someone else can have
a slight extension of theirs.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Give me a hug.
Ah...
I don't need two kidneys.
I have everything I need right here.
Hmm.
Dad, you're tickling me.
Yes, tickling...
Hmm?
(theme music playing)
Shh.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services