(Heidi)
'Me and Jordan's anniversary
is on Wednesday.'
(Audrina)
What anniversary is it?
Oh, God, six months.
(laughing)
(Lauren)
Is that the exact date,
when you like became
what was it, like,
your first kiss, or?
No.
First date?
When he officially
asked me out.
Didn't he ask you out with
a bunch of lilacs, or lilies?
Yeah. He asked me out with
lilies, and then a note.
That was cute.
How did he do that?
I remember him set that up.
That's sweet.
He was
so sweet.
That was sweet.
What are you guys gonna do?
(Heidi)
I don't know.
I kinda want him
to surprise me.
I've never been with someone
longer than this.
It will be fine.
It's all up to Jordan.
He better make it good.
Do you remember how big of
a deal six months used to be?
Like, if you were in high school
and you were a good girl like,
six months, you gave it up.
(laughter)
♪♪
(Brent)
Hey, Heidi?
Heidi!
Have a seat.
Space.
How do I say this?
We wanna try to integrate you
into working into the clubs.
Oh, great.
Clubs, whole different animal.
Hundreds of people.
Like instantly things
will change for you.
So what we want to do
is have you work Wednesday.
Assisting Elodie,
it's a great, amazing way
to meet people, and...
you know, so be prepared.
(laughs)
Alright. Thanks, Brent.
Hey, you're welcome.
(keys clacking)
(telephone rings)
Bolthouse events.
Hey, you work Wednesday nights,
don't you?
Yeah.
Me too.
What?
I'm gonna start working
Wednesday nights with you.
(Elodie)
You are?
Yay, so you'll be
working this Wednesday?
I don't know if I'll be
working this Wednesday.
(exhales sharply)
What?
(Heidi)
Wednesday is our anniversary.
We were gonna go out to dinner,
and go bowling.
(laughs)
♪♪
♪ I make it up as I go ♪
♪ This is all I've ever known ♪
♪ I make it up ♪
♪ As I go ♪
♪ I make it up as I go ♪
(Jason)
How's it going?
(Lauren)
Hugh, what are you doing here?
(Jason)
Uh, just want to talk to you
real quick...
about the other night.
Birthday party.
You seemed like you were
a little upset when we...
departed from dinner.
(Lauren)
You just hurt my feelings.
You know, I understand,
I'd be sad
if you did it to me too.
Well, no.
I mean, I wasn't, like, mad.
I was just kind of,
like, bummed because
I hadn't been with you all day,
so I thought, like,
since you were
with your friends all day,
like you'd want to spend
more time with me at night.
Yeah.
It was just like
one of those things where
a lot of those people,
like Small, Sean, Taylor,
like all them we haven't
seen for a while.
I kind of got into a situation
where I was, like,
down there talking to 'em,
and they were
telling me something.
It's like if you were like,
"Okay, hey, that's cool.
"Tell me later,"
they'd have been like
"What's your problem?"
So it was just really awkward.
I felt bad too.
I just wanted to get things
cleared up
and just wanna make sure
you weren't mad at me.
I'm not, like, mad at you.
It just, like, made me sad.
No, I understand,
but I'm just..
Okay.
Good.
So...
um...
Glad we talked
things over.
Don't be sad.
(Lauren)
I have to go. I have a test.
(Jason)
Okay. See you.
Bye.
♪♪
(Lisa)
Hi, everyone.
How are you?
We're doing this special
Teen Vogue event with DKNY jeans
and, uh, Jay is going to style
the show for us.
It's a great event,
kicking off LA Fashion week.
Jay has
an incredible vision
and he'll talk about that
a little bit.
(Jay)
Stylistically speaking
we're gonna do a bit of a '60s
Karlheinz Weinberger punk
with a 'bit of a modern
twist to it.'
And you're gonna work
with Whitney and Lauren.
And Lauren is not here.
(Blaine)
Lauren is not here.
She has a test.
(Lisa)
Oh, okay.
But she will be
here for the show?
She will be here for the show
and she will be working
on the project,
and you guys will catch
her up to speed
on everything
that happens here.
Right.
(Lisa)
Okay.
(Woman)
We do have a quiz today,
so uh, when you're finished,
if you could just
bring it up front,
so I can gauge
when we're all finished.
♪♪
(cell phone rings)
Hey.
Hi.
Where are you?
I just got out of class.
(Whitney)
Well, listen.
There's, like, this Teen Vogue,
DKNY jeans fashion show.
It's the most work
I've ever seen.
My God, are you serious?
Yeah, like, you're gonna die.
And it's just you and me
under Jay, the stylist,
so it's like a lot,
a lot, a lot of work.
I need you with me
the next couple of days.
I'll be there.
Thank you for filling me in.
I'm sorry I missed the meeting.
My pleasure.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay, thanks. Bye.
Get Heidi in my office, please.
♪ You don't have to feel ♪
Hey, Heidi.
How's it going?
Good, how are you?
I'm going over all my specifics
for Wednesday night
and I see that you're gonna
start Wednesday night.
Well, I was wondering if
I could start Saturday instead.
(Jen)
No, no, no,
Wednesday night' you're walking
the line outside with us.
We have a lot of little rules
and regulations.
I don't really like our people,
while they're working
to go 'inside the nightclub,
and hang out with their friends.
(Heidi)
Well, what about when
we're done working?
(Jen)
Well, when you're done working,
then the club's closed.
Obviously, there's no drinking.
No Uggs. No flip-flops.
I like girls in heels
but not heels that
they can't move and walk in.
Always have a coat with you.
Always have pockets
so that you...
♪♪
(Lauren)
Morning!
Howdy-ho.
Hey.
(Jason)
Come here.
Let's go grab something to eat.
I'm so hungry.
(Lauren)
I have to go get ready.
(indistinct chattering)
(Danica)
Is Lauren here?
(Whitney)
Not yet.
I think she's coming soon.
(Danica)
Can somebody call Lauren
and find out
when she's gonna get here?
Yeah, I can call her.
Yeah.
(cell phone rings)
Hello?
Hi, I just wanted to make
sure, are you here?
I'm a couple minutes
away.
Okay, just wanted to make
sure you're here soon.
Okay. Bye.
What's going on?
Are you late?
We're not even
late yet.
Like five minutes.
Nobody's gonna die
in five minutes.
I think we're
gonna be okay.
She'll be here
in a couple minutes.
(Danica)
Okay, cool.
Okay, thank you.
(Jason)
Have a good day.
Mmm.
(exhales sharply)
What time did Lauren say
she was getting here?
(Whitney)
When I talked her,
she said she was gonna be
here in a couple minutes.
(Lauren)
Hey.
(Whitney)
Hi. We were just
about to call you.
(Lauren)
Did you guys just start?
(Whitney)
No, they've been here all day.
Really?
Okay.
So you're gonna be
Polaroid girl.
(Lara)
Excuse me.
Lauren, hi.
Hi.
Okay, thanks.
(indistinct chatter)
♪♪
(Lauren)
Heidi!
Hello!
(Lauren)
Hi.
Hi. How you're doing?
Can I use your curling iron?
Only if you use it in here
because you won't give it back.
(laughs)
Oh, I have to work tonight.
(Lauren)
Do you?
On my anniversary.
The first night I have to work.
For how long?
Until 2:00 in the morning.
No.
I was planning on, like,
going out with Jordan, like...
Well, you can still do dinner.
Yeah, but like hardly,
and we have to rush.
I've never been, like...
out at a club without him,
though.
You know, like me working
there and him going out?
That's weird.
Why did you invite him?
Well, 'cause I'd rather him
be there than not, you know?
It's our anniversary and stuff.
Just make the best of it,
you know.
How was work?
I literally
was like five minutes late
and they made, like,
a big deal out of it.
They were all weirded out,
so I just can't, like, mess up.
I'm, like, under a magnifying
glass tonight.
♪♪
(Danica)
Everything needs to be done
in one hour.
Do it carefully, but do it fast.
Whitney will be
directing the dressers
'cause that's the most
important thing,
and then Lauren needs
to actually be waiting here,
taking care of the models.
Okay?
So, Lauren, I'm gonna
put you on this duty.
I can't get a hold of this girl.
Um, maybe you can
just keep trying.
She was supposed to be here
at 8:30, and it's 10:15.
Okay, yeah,
just call over and over.
What about Jessica?
Has anyone called?
I can't get a hold of her.
I just called two minutes ago.
We're having a problem.
I need to get Jay.
(Lauren)
I've called her like five times
in the last ten minutes.
I just keep calling
over and over.
Have we tried
to call her agency?
It is the agency.
Oh.
What do you want to do?
Do you wanna try to slap
somebody else into that look?'
Alright, alright.
Worst comes to worst.
But is the situation,
like, is she gonna freak out?
We'll have to make sure that
all the sizes are correct.
You want me to go talk to her?
We can make any adjustment.
Okay.
How are you guys doing?
(Whitney)
We're done.
(Danica)
So, I'm gonna get
the dressers back here
and you can brief the dressers
and, Whitney,
you're gonna walk tonight.
Let me get the dressers.
♪♪
(Jordan)
Happy anniversary.
(Heidi)
So, are you gonna go tonight?
Yeah, but I was amped on you
being inside, walking around.
And it'll suck not being
part of the party.
Yes, and that's
what Jen said.
"You're not part of the party.
You're outside."
(Jordan)
Since it is our anniversary
I'm gonna give you
your anniversary gift.
(gasps)
They're beautiful.
You know what?
It's been a really, really,
really special six months.
I know.
I've never been
with anyone this long.
(Lauren)
All of you back there!
Don't forget,
no stopping, no posing.
And walk easy and smile!
Be happy.
Who's walking for Jessica?
(Woman)
Whitney's gonna
walk for Jessica.
Where's Sierra?
Oh. She's in the show.
She's gonna take
Jessica's position.
We just need to get her
in the outfit right now
so that if there's any kind of
alterations to be made
then we can get Billy to do it.
(Blaine)
You're walking?!
Yes!
(Woman)
Where's Whitney?
(Lauren)
Whitney?
She's right there. Oh!
(Jay)
Are all the models here?
And our new model, Whitney?
Yeah.
(Jay)
Okay, great. Fantastic.
Let's do it.
And, everyone,
remember who you're in front of.
♪♪
(Grace)
Dude, one way or the other, sir?
Hello? We're not open.
One way or the other.
Okay, you got to go down that
way to ask us something.
Alright,
are you ready?
(laughs)
Oh, great.
I'm a little nervous.
Gee, there's so many people.
(Grace)
Okay, okay, okay.
Are we ready?
This is where you're gonna be.
Come on.
(Heidi) Okay, what do I say?
Who has a table?
Say,
"What's your name?
"How many people
in your party?
"How many guys?
How many girls?"
Before you
let them through.
(indistinct chatter)
(Brian)
Where is she?
(Jordan)
Heidi.
Hi!
(Elodie)
So a big day for you guys
today, huh?
Yeah.
(Elodie)
Six months. Congratulations.
(Jordan)
I appreciate it.
Appreciate it.
(indistinct chatter)
(Jen)
Rob, what is going on
with all these people?
You guys aren't...
listening to me.
Listen to me.
(Grace)
Check in with Heidi.
(Jen)
Will you check in
with Heidi, please?
Where did Heidi go?
I'm having a... cow right now.
♪♪
You look like
you're having fun.
Way better
than the office!
Are you at the door
all night?
Yeah, but we're
almost done.
You coming in
with me?
I think so.
Ooh! Really!
Are you having fun?
Hey, how are you?
(Josh)
What's up, Heidi.
How you doing?
Good. How are you?
(Josh)
Good.
(Heidi)
This is my boyfriend, Jordan.
What's up, man? Josh.
What's happening?
This is Brian.
What's up,
Brian?
I'm Brian.
Josh, nice to meet you.
Josh.
What?
I smell it.
Okay, bye.
(Elodie)
And then we'll call you back
to confirm.
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
Okay, what happened?
(Heidi)
So...
this guy I went
on one date with--
I swear to God, it was one date,
he comes in,
sits down next to our,
in our table,
Jordan, like, gets mad at me.
I didn't ask this guy
to come over.
Oh, my God,
is he super jealous?
I am, too,
so I understand.
♪♪
I'm your dresser, Whitney.
(Whitney)
Oh, my God.
Don't lie. You're excited.
(Whitney)
"Excited" isn't the word.
I feel, every single limb
that is being
worked on right now.
(Make-up artist)
Welcome to our world.
Ugh. You guys do
a really good job.
(Lauren)
Oh, Whitney,
you look so pretty.
Yay, Whitney.
Heather, Shane, Amanda, Jake.
You're in here.
Line up, everybody.
Line up.
Get in your order.
Line up. Line up. Line up.
'Cause we're gonna start
in 20 seconds.
Aah!
(Lauren)
We just need Miss Corrina.
Corrina's in.
Good. We're good!
We got everyone.
♪♪
♪ You got a problem with me ♪
♪ I got a problem with you ♪
I'm gonna trip and fall.
Be like whoo!
(laughs)
Just kind of like,
you're good.
Good luck!
♪ You got a problem with me ♪
♪ I got a problem with you ♪
(screams)
(Lauren)
Yo, Whitney!
How did you do?
(Whitney)
It's fine.
I think it was fine.
Good work.
(Lisa)
You could do that.
Should I introduce you
to Natalie at the model agency?
Amazing.
I saw you hustling back here.
Did it turn out good?
Yeah, you guys did
a great job.
Okay.
You guys do well.
Given a challenge, you rise.
Thank you.
♪♪
You ready?
Let's rewind the night.
Okay.
I was so shocked to see him.
I didn't invite him over.
I just went, "Hi."
I greet everyone like that.
I didn't
invite him there.
I don't care.
I didn't know
he was there--
You're ridiculous.
Alright, fine.
Okay, I was trying so hard,
I introduced you
as my boyfriend.
I tried to keep
getting him to leave.
(Jordan)
Okay, so my ex-girlfriend
comes up to me in a club.
If you went on a date--
(Jordan)
I greet her.
If you went on a date with her.
But, listen,
listen, listen.
-Jordan.
-No, you're wrong.
I don't care
what you say.
You always say this in our
arguments,
"You're wrong."
"I don't care what you say."
Shut up!
Don't tell me to shut up!
Like, I don't
understand you.
Like,
you drive me insane.
Fine, fine.
Then, if I drive you
insane so much,
then why are
you with me?
(Jordan)
Oh, God.
♪ And everything
comes with a price ♪
(Heidi)
Happy anniversary, Jordan.
♪ But how much
can you sacrifice? ♪
♪ And no one else aches ♪
♪ In your shoes ♪
♪♪