- Sunglass time.
- I know, right?
Guys, I'm glad I'm skipping
school for this day.
I love ditching.
It's, like a thing I love.
She loves ditching so much,
she permanently ditched school.
I did.
I have to find
a pretty birthday dress
unless it's, like,
a breathtaking shirt.
I feel like LA, anything goes.
Hey, let's go
try on wedding dresses.
Come on. It's, like,
a really nice store.
Are we all trying
them on for real?
Mm-hmm.
- 'Isn't this the room?'
- Yes.
I feel like my boobs
are too big for this.
- No, they're not!
- Ahh!
Oh, my god,
it actually looks beautiful.
- 'It is surprisingly pretty.'
- Surprisingly?
'Oh, you look so beautiful!'
'You do look really pretty.'
[sighs]
- What'd you do today?
- Nothing.
Nothing to do
with wedding dresses, okay?
[instrumental music]
♪ Another day
for an ordinary superstar ♪
♪ You know that trouble's gonna
come knocking at your door ♪
♪ You put the planet
back together.. ♪
Lisa?
Here you go.
- Hey. Hi. How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Good, good.
- Should we sit down?
Sure. Sure.
'Um, next week, Lara Bonomo,
who's our model booker'
'is coming to town,
and she's gonna do a casting'
of, uh, models
for a bathing suit story that
we're working on.
It's called a "go-see"
in our business.
'You'll set up um, a casting.'
What I'd like you to do is call
as many agencies,
go on as many websites.
Let's get as many pictures of
boys that you think are right.
Is there a certain kind of look
like a surfer kind of look?
You're gonna be looking
for 17 to 20-year-old boys
bathing-suit models.
[both laughing]
Behave accordingly.
- Alright?
- Okay.
[instrumental music]
- 'Hey, Heidi.'
- Mm-hmm?
Will you come in here?
'Please?'
- So will you shut the door?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, so, tonight we have our
William Morris Grammy party.
You're gonna work at LAX, but
none of us are gonna be there.
Jennifer's not there.
It's gonna be, like, you, Grace.
It's almost like we're
competing against ourselves
so we literally have to make
sure that LAX is great tonight.
- Right.
- So, what I was thinking is.
Maybe you should call
some of your girlfriends
'write some people
down that you know.'
And Grace is calling
extra people.
Okay, so it's gonna
be me and Grace.
You and Grace,
doing everything.
- Alright. Anything else?
- Is that it?
I think it's good. I,
I want a full report tomorrow.
- You'll get one.
- Okay. Thanks, Heidi.
[music continues]
'Oh, okay, yeah.
Then e-mail them. Awesome.'
Thank you so much.
Alright, bye.
Okay, so we have Ford,
Wilhelmina.
Cards come in?
Um, not yet,
but we have some questions.
For the um, call sheet
do you already know
what studio the um, go-see is?
- It will be at Quixote studios.
- It will be. Okay.
Oh, that's where Audrina works.
- Okay? Cool. Thank you.
- Uh-huh.
So that will be fun. She'll
be there when we're there.
- That's so cool.
- Hey, Whitney
'What do you want
to see on LA Models?'
Let's look at the men.
[chuckles]
He's kind of cute.
This guy's hot.
(both)
Enrique.
- Introducing Enrique.
- Ooh.
He's cute, but..
you don't like him?
No, I do.
I like all these guys.
Do you want-you want me to leave
you alone for a little bit?
[pop music]
Hi.
Thanks for coming out
and supporting me.
Okay, do you want
to take them in?
Bye, guys. That's all I get
to see of you for tonight.
- We'll be out soon.
- Alright. Alright. Bye-bye.
[upbeat music]
[RnB music]
You know the last two nights
I have slept a total
of six hours, about?
It's 'cause that's your job.
You need to, like
do you ever nap in the day?
No. I work in the day.
- You're a full-time worker.
- I am.
Remember I told you
about the modeling call?
No, you didn't
tell me about it.
We're doing a modeling call
for a bathing-suit shoot.
- For guys or for girls?
- For both.
I told Jason
it was only girls, too
and he's gonna
get mad at me.
But why?
They're, like, young guys.
- Are they kids?
- They're not kids.
They're, like, guy models.
He's gonna get mad at you.
[music continues]
[instrumental music]
- Hi!
- You guys look cute.
- Thanks. So do you.
- This is where I work.
- Oh, my God.
I'll show you
where your stage is.
- Okay.
- You guys are in here.
I know, it's right next to..
Yeah, it's so trippy.
- How far back does it go?
- How far back..?
Like, model.
Hi. My name's Whitney.
And tell me a little bit
about yourself.
Okay.
My name is Whitney, and I'm..
- It still doesn't work.
- It doesn't work?
No.
Oh, and then you put this..
You're a genius.
I'm so bad with this stuff.
- Does that work?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hi, Blaine.
- How you guys doing?
- Good.
So, that looks good,
looks great.
That looks excellent.
This is a pretty intense
casting setup.
I like it. Good work.
Hi. Are you here for
the Teen Vogue casting?
- Yes, I am.
- It's right in this room.
- Okay. Thanks.
- You're welcome.
[pop music]
Okay, I'm gonna do a head shot.
Um..
I would take off your shirt.
♪ Take off your pants
and dance ♪
and dance.. ♪
- Wanna take your shirt off?
- Hell, yeah.
[laughing]
Okay.
God, you're
such a perv, Whitney.
Sorry.
Okay, uh, look at me
straight on, straight on.
Serious.
And smile.
[laughing]
(Blaine)
'How long you been in LA?'
About six months or so.
- You like it?
- Yeah, it's cool.
'Definitely. Come out here to
act, model, the whole deal?'
Yeah, pretty much.
That and music.
What are you guys
all doing tonight?
I don't know.
We're not so sure.
It's Friday night.
We're all going to Bella
like, around 8:00, 8:30.
Well, if you
give me your number.
If you give me
the right number, I'll..
I'll give you
the reject number.
- Yeah.
- It was nice meeting you.
- Bye, girls.
- Bye.
- He's hot.
- Perfect.
- You are good, Austin.
- Thanks, dude.
Thanks for coming in.
- He was really cute.
- How's it going in there?
- Are there people waiting?
- Yeah, a lot.
How long have you been
doing this internship?
Um, since, like, September.
[laughs]
I don't know.
Where's your party at tonight?
- We're finished.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
- Amazing. Good work today.
- Okay.
- So we're done.
Yes.
We'll see you tonight?
- Yeah. Bye.
- Bye!
♪ Get out the way ♪
♪ He's never sorry ♪
Tell me about the boys
in the model scout.
One of the models
is really funny
'cause he was leaving,
and I was like
"you can't leave yet."
And you came in, and I was like
"this is Audrina."
She pointed him out.
She's like,
"the one in the white shirt.."
It was cute, though,
'cause they just clicked.
They started, like, talking.
He might come tonight.
I don't know.
- He was really cute.
- So, we'll see.
Whitney was like,
all the models, she's like
"take off your shirt, baby."
- I did not say it like that.
- "He's my favorite.
I'll take down his number."
'Your job is way
better than mine.'
That is delicious.
Oh, my God.
- Thank you.
- I don't know.
Like the pretty boys
are nice to hang out with
or whatever, but..
they just are boring.
That's why I like,
I like that mysterious
like, I think that's why
I always go for the bad boys.
- You do, too.
- Jason's not a bad boy.
And, like, I like
how he's a little more
rough around the edges,
you know what I mean?
[incoherent chatters]
Y'all want to get the food?
What?
Do you see him?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go say hi.
Do you want to come with?
No, you're all over this.
- We'll be right here, though.
- Bring him back.
Do you want to meet him?
Or I'll bring him back.
Bring him back.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How you doing?
- How are you?
- Good.
- Move, man.
What is his friend wearing?
Remember Lauren?
Come over here.
- Hi.
- I'm Lauren.
- Scoot.
So, what are you
doing out here?
Well, I moved up here to
pursue modeling and acting more.
So, where are y'all
going after this?
We'll see.
- Can you, uh, fix me a glass?
- Ooh, I have an idea.
I'm gonna mix-I'm gonna mix
orange Gatorade
with orange soda.
Sometimes with Jordan,
you got to make things
kind of girlie and light.
First thing he does is put
more Gatorade in it.
Guys, guys, guys. Got a body
like me, got to, you know..
Oh, my God.
We were joking around.
Audrina's got like more
'like she's always got
a new guy or a new date.'
Just random guys.
I mean..
Like, I don't do that.
'It's one extreme
to the other extreme.'
There was a Teen Vogue casting
for like a bunch of male models.
Wait, when and where was this?
Quixote studios,
where Audrina, uh, works.
- There were all these guys.
- What kind of guys were there?
I don't know, I just find it
funny when people are like
"yeah, I'm a model."
I don't know.
'Even when we, even when
we were in New York city'
doing that a lot,
I'd-I'd never say that.
I don't, I didn't even say I was
an actor for, like, my first..
[music continues]
♪ I don't believe
anybody else ♪
♪ Fantasy falling for yourself ♪
♪ I I ♪
♪ I don't believe.. ♪
Did you say something to
Jason about there being guys
'at the Teen Vogue model
scout or something?'
- Yes.
- Why did you do that?
Why would I not say that?
Their relationship sucks.
Lying about a guy being at
a casting, that's just retarded.
They're both insecure, immature.
Just, they're not even ready
to be in a relationship.
So sad..
if you're stuck in that.
- Well, no, no, no.
- New year's eve.
- That was terrible.
- What do you mean stuck in it?
When you're stuck
in a relationship like that.
How are you, how are you
stuck in a relationship?
Because if you love someone
so much, but it's just like..
- No, I don't even.. No, no, no.
- Yes.
If we, if you fought
with me all the time.
How-how can somebody
love somebody..
- See, we're fighting right now.
- Oh, whatever. God..
- 'I'm just so annoyed.'
- 'Why? What's wrong?'
'Right on Lauren's birthday'
Jordan has to be like
"Oh, by the way
did you know that there were
boys at the photo shoot?"
- Jordan told Jason that?
- Yeah.
So, Jason got pissed off?
Yeah, so now Jason's mad.
And it's like..
If he's mean to her
at her birthday like..
But, it's like, this is her day,
you know what I mean?
'You have to know when you say
something like that.'
- Jason gets pissed off easily.
- Good job, Jordan.
Yeah, really
freaking good job.
Just push it. There.
And then maybe these will
fold in the way back.
There.
Ugh!
This is so..
[sighs]
Is everything okay?
(Lauren)
'Jordan just told Jason
there was guys'
at that stupid model thing,
and I hadn't told him yet.
When we went to that club
that night, he asked me, like
"are there gonna be guys
at that model casting?"
and I was like, "no."
I just never told him
and I was gonna tell him,
and I forgot.
'I just..
Oh, makes me so mad.'
And like it wasn't
that I was hiding it.
It wasn't, it was just, like
Jason's just like sensitive,
so I can't just be like
"oh, and there was guys there,
so don't get mad"
because he'll get mad.
Can't you just call him
and be like
"Dude, it's my birthday?"
No, because I don't feel like
arguing with him.
I'm just gonna tell him like,
"be mad at me.
I'm not even gonna argue."
He needs to get over this
little trust ish.
Why do you think
he's so sensitive?
I guess, it's just,
like, whenever we like
all plan a night out,
something goes wrong
at the end of the day, always.
It never fails.
Hello? Hey.
(Jason over the phone)
'Hey, there were boys at your
photo shoot, you liar.'
Please don't fight
with me right now.
'I wasn't mad that
there was guys there.'
'It was the fact that
you lied about it.'
- I'm really sorry, baby.
- 'Baby, I don't care.'
'I could care less
who's there.'
- 'Just tell me who's there.'
- Sorry.
- 'I love you.'
- I love you, too.
- 'Okay, bye.'
- Bye.
- He handled that well.
- That was okay.
He didn't even get mad at me.
Yay.
[exhales sharply]
[music continues]
[doorbell rings]
Who is it?
I thought it was someone else.
Hi. Come in.
- Are you Lauren?
- No, this is Lauren.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
"Happy birthday" flowers.
"Be ready at 5:00.
A car will be waiting.
"Be sure to pack a bag
for school.
Love, Jason."
Pack a bag for school?
What does that mean?
It means I won't
be coming back here.
[music continues]
Happy birthday, baby.
- Got you a little rose.
- Thank you.
- Surprise, surprise.
- Oh!
It's so pretty.
I'm so hungry.
- I ordered it for us.
- Oh, did you?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
'I don't know what you want.
I just knew'
you like calamari
and stuff, so..
- Thank you.
- Of course.
[cutlery clanking]
What do you want to do
the rest of the night?
Whatever you want.
Would you want to go out tonight
or you just want to hang here?
Want to hang out here.
Brian's doing that thing
at Nacional.
- Who is?
- Brian.
Hmm.
If you want to go
to Nacional, that's fine.
I just thought you'd want to
spend my birthday with me.
I do.
Do you want to go meet up
with Heidi and Jordan later?
It's up to you.
I-I don't care. Do whatever.
You okay?
What's bothering you?
I'm just looking around.
It's kind of different.
I never thought I'd do
something like this.
- Just kidding.
- No, it's sweet.
I never had anyone do anything
like this for me.
So you just want to chill
here and we can hang out?
[cutlery clanking]
Do you really want to go out?
I'd rather just spend
the night with you.
No, I just wanna
hang out with you.
I don't care.
What do you wanna do?
- Just hang out here.
- What's up?
I-I...Jason, look at me.
I've told you I would rather
stay here and--
I, okay, then we can stay here.
I don't understand
what you want to do, though.
You wanna watch a movie?
You wanna do something else?
- I mean..
- I-I'll do whatever.
I don't care.
You can't just be with me?
- I can.
- That's all I want.
Just wanna watch a movie, then?
Mm-hmm.
♪ And I'll be someone else ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Cover me ♪
♪ Baby cover me ♪
[water splashing]