- Hey.
- Hi.
- What are you doing?
- Getting ready for work.
I like what you have on.
I think that's really cute.
You're not really
mad at me about
not going to school anymore,
are you?
It's kinda like weird
because it's like the reason
you came to LA
was to go to school.
But I guess when like other
opportunities come up
you got to take them.
I really am excited, though,
for my job.
What are you excited
to do, like?
I don't know, it just
seems like, it would be like..
Like running around all
the time, being really busy
and meeting celebrities,
and being in the clubs
and, like..
I'm so excited.
Good. You should be excited.
You know you are
gonna have to work, though.
I know, I know.
You know, I have
to do homework tonight
''cause I have that big
school assignment.'
Luckily, like
I'm not working too late
so I-I,
I can come home and do it.
Oh, my God,
I don't even know what to wear
to this job,
like, do I wear heels, do I..
Always dress nicer
than you think you should.
It's my first real job.
[instrumental music]
♪ I got the
west coast sunshine ♪
♪ But it don't mean ♪
♪ A thing ♪
♪ I'm getting over ♪
♪ Like I knew that I would ♪
♪ I'm feeling older than ♪
♪ A younger man should ♪
♪ But one of these days ♪
♪ I'll finally make good ♪♪
[telephone ringing]
- Hello?
- 'Hey, it's Blaine.'
'Can you come down to my office
when you have a second?'
- Yeah.
- 'Okay. Thanks.'
- Hey.
- Hi. Have a seat.
Um, so, you know,
when you got this job
I told you there
would be lots of work.
Yeah
And, um, so,
sometimes you end up being
somewhat of a messenger,
so, there is a dress
that needs to get to New York
'and you need to get it there.'
The company
is taking care of it.
They're talking
to travel right now.
You're gonna be
on a red-eye tonight.
- Seriously?
- 'Yeah.'
Uh, at this point,
I have no idea
how long you're
gonna be there for.
- Oh.
- 'Get this dress to Lisa.'
It's fashion week.
That's about it.
- Get out of here. Go pack.
- Okay.
You're done, yeah. Go.
I'll guard it with my life.
- Bye!
[instrumental music]
♪ Doo doo-doo doo-doo ♪
♪ Doo-doo-doo-doo.. ♪♪
- Whoa-oh!
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
You're probably like,
what the heck is he doing here?
I know. This is a surprise.
I saw the huge billboard,
Quixote, and I..
- 'You did?'
- Yeah.
I was, like,
right down the street.
- Cool. That's a nice surprise.
- Yeah.
- This is where you work? Huh?
- This is where I work.
Am I gonna get you in trouble?
No, I'll show you around.
This is one of the stages.
This is all for photo shoots,
right?
Yeah, like they do
all the photo shoots
'they do commercials,
everything.'
There's even
a Maxim shoot, so..
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Wow, I came to visit you
on the right day.
I know,
you get to see all the girls.
And then this is
all the stage managers
and then this is the
wardrobe room for stage three.
Do the models get mad that
the receptionist is hotter?
Aw!
[laughing]
But this is pretty much it.
Well, thanks
for showing me around.
It's a good surprise.
Well, I was gonna ask you
if maybe you wanted
to get, um...do something
tomorrow night.
- I don't know..
- Okay.
Maybe go out to dinner? Yeah?
I work till 6:00, and then..
...you wanna go
like at 7:30 or 8:00?
I usually don't get out,
out of bed till 6:00 anyway..
- ...so that's perfect.
- You suck.
[laughing]
[instrumental music]
- Hi.
Hey.
What is that?
- It's a dress.
- You brought me a present?
No, I have to bring Lisa Love
a present in New York.
[shrieks]
- 'What?'
- I'm going to New York.
My car comes in an hour.
You're gonna get ready
in an hour?
So, what time
does your flight leave?
I don't know,
she just said, he's like
uh, your car
will be there at 7:00.
- I have a suitcase.
- The pink one?
Yeah. I'm like,
how long am I there for?
He's like, well, he said,
it could be a day
or it could be five days,
I'm like..
- It could be five days?
- 'Yeah.'
I don't know
what to wear on the plane.
Why don't you bring
a change of clothes, so you can
sleep in them, and then right
before you get off the plane
or in the bathroom
in the airport, you change.
What do, what do you
wear to, like a show?
You wear the designer.
You're supposed
to wear whatever..
Don't get too dressed up,
though.
You're gonna have so much fun.
'You're working there
for like two days'
and you're already
jet-setting.
[laughing]
Jeez!
Okay, seriously..
Oh, my God.
Okay, I'll call you
when I get there.
- Okay, bye. I love you.
- Bye!
♪ Do better
than I've ever done ♪
do better do better ♪
♪ I'm gonna shine brighter ♪
♪ Than I've ever shone
I'm gonna.. ♪
- You, okay?
- Yep, got it. Thank you.
♪ Sing louder
than I've ever sung ♪
♪ I'm gonna do better
than I've ever done.. ♪
[chuckles]
- Oh, that feels so good.
- Like, it's so hot.
It feels so good.
[shivers]
What about Brian?
Brian? I don't know.
Well, hopefully it will be
better than the date
with Kevin you went on.
Oh, my God! Disaster.
- Oh, my God.
- 'Okay.'
Every guy who's like not from LA
and is from, like,
North Carolina or wherever..
...they're like, I'm such
a good guy and that's just
like, their front,
they just say that..
See, I haven't met
any guys who said that.
Guys who would hit on Lauren
or any of our friends
they'd be like,
I'm a really good guy.
- Just looking for a good girl.
- I hate that.
You're like,
no, you're really a ***
looking to get laid.
[laughs]
That's all they really want.
So, how's school?
- 'I dropped out.'
- No way.
Because why would I go to school
when I already got my dream job?
'I was just like, this
is just not what I wanna do..'
Is Lauren still going there?
Yeah, she goes,
but it's just
you know, school's
not right for everybody.
- I know. I dropped out, too.
- 'I know.'
I was going to OCC and..
That's what
made me feel better, I was like
if Audrina can do it,
I can do it.
I mean, Lauren thinks
that I should go, but it's like
that's what's right for her
not what's right for me.
Do something
that you want to do.
You're gonna benefit from it
and meet so many people.
I just wanna
get us into clubs.
Yeah! So many parties!
That is so cool that
Lauren got sent to New York.
She's gonna have the best time.
♪ Turn the key ♪
♪ And set me free ♪
♪ Then spread my wings ♪
♪ And watch me fly ♪♪
(female announcer)
'I'd like to welcome you
to New York's Kennedy airport'
'where the current time
is approximately 7:37 A.M.'
[instrumental music]
- Hi. I'm Heidi.
- Hi.
It's my first day.
- Hi, I'm Landon.
- It's nice to meet you.
Uh, let me see
if they're ready for you.
Okay. Thanks.
Brent,
are you all ready for Heidi?
(Brent)
'Yeah.'
- Yeah, you can go on back.
- Thanks.
Hi. How are you?
Good, good. How's it going?
- Good. Thank you.
- Sit down. Sit down.
- Are you ready to work?
- I'm ready.
I'm so nervous.
We got to get
a couple things clear.
You're gonna assist
the whole company right now.
Like, if the
events department needs help
with something, if they need,
if you need to go
you know, run somewhere
and pick up something..
- ...that we're gonna need.
- Right.
Like, today
I'm gonna have you help
them with the mail
or whatever they..
'Whatever the mailing
department does over there.'
I don't really know,
but you're gonna work
Monday through Friday, so
whatever we kind of need you--
I didn't know if, um,
it was, like, full-time
I thought that when you
hired me it was part-time.
- I didn't really know.
- 'You're gonna work every day.'
- Okay.
- So..
The way we work
is, you sink or swim.
Alright, so, you can
just grab a seat, right here.
All we're doing is, uh, we're
just stuffing these envelopes
um, two per envelope
and, uh, yeah
later we'll have
to seal them, too.
- That's it.
- Okay.
[rock music]
Do you guys work here,
or are you interns?
I'm an intern.
So, what do you wanna do?
I'm a merchandise marketing
student at FIDM.
Oh, really?
I just dropped out of there.
'Did you? You didn't like it?'
No.
[music continues]
[Superchick's singing
"One Girl Revolution"]
♪ And I'll be everything ♪
♪ That I want to be ♪
♪ I am confidence ♪
♪ In insecurity ♪
♪ I am a voice yet waiting ♪
♪ To be heard ♪
♪ I'll shoot the shot ♪
♪ Bang that you hear ♪
♪ Around the world ♪
♪ And I'm
a one girl revolution ♪♪
I will definitely call you.
Maybe a longer period.
Yes, I would say and I
always try to stay later
and it doesn't always work.
So, definitely.
- Hi.
- Sorry.
- Okay. Okay.
- 'Okay.'
Thanks.
[Vaughan Penn singing
"Angels Fly"]
♪ Do you ever have a day ♪
♪ When you wish ♪
♪ That you could be
someone else ♪
♪ And every word you say ♪
♪ Well you wish that ♪
♪ You could take back ♪
♪ And keep all to yourself ♪
♪ And nobody knows you ♪
♪ Who do you turn to ♪
♪ Who do you turn to ♪♪
[cellphone beeping]
[cellphone vibrating]
Hello? How was your first day?
'Well, it's not what
I thought it was gonna be.'
'Now, they're saying it's, like'
'full-time from 9:00 to 6:00.'
'It's so boring.
I'm stuffing envelopes.'
'This was my nightmare
of a job.'
(Lauren)
'You got to give it
more than one day.'
'I know. How's New York?'
Um, good,
I just, uh, I went
and delivered the dress,
and but I'm leaving right now
I'm going straight, I think
I'll go straight back to LA.
I can't believe they just, like
put you on a plane like that.
They, like
treat it like an errand.
Like, flying across the country
is, like no big deal to them.
It's like going down the street
and picking up photocopies.
(Lauren)
'Plus I have that big school
assignment due tomorrow.'
'We're both having bad days.'
I just don't know how
I'm gonna do this
like and school.
[instrumental music]
♪ Don't go and
try to change me ♪
♪ I'm not the one you.. ♪
Landon, do you think I can
speak to Brent for a minute?
- Yeah, go on in.
- Thanks.
♪ Because I wanted all ♪
♪ God knows
I never meant to hurt you ♪♪
Okay, so,
I want to talk to you.
I didn't know
that it was like full-time.
I thought that when you hired
me, it was part-time.
When I spoke to you
on the phone that day
you were like,
"I'm not in school."
- Right
- Here's the deal.
'We have a real job.
We're gonna count on you.'
It's like you being
here full-time is what
is the best for us because
then you're consistently
here all the time.
We need you, and we want you,
and we wanna make sure
that you are 100% committed
to wanting to be here.
'Okay. I didn't know that.'
And coming in,
I just kinda thought it was
a little bit different,
and I didn't really realize
that, like, I want to do it,
and I'm excited
'to do, like
all the events and stuff'
and you know,
I, that's part of what
I wanna do with my life,
but I just didn't really
'understand that I was
gonna be stuffing envelopes.'
If you wanna be part of this
you have to be committed to it.
Particularly if
you're gonna get involved
more in the nightclub aspect.
'You gotta crawl
before you walk.'
If you're gonna
come here and work
we need you to work.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
[instrumental music]
- See you tomorrow.
- Okay, bye.
[music continues]
(Brian)
This is the first, like date
that I've been on in so long.
- 'Hey, guys, how's it going?'
- 'Hey. How are you?'
'Good. Thanks.'
What would
you guys like tonight?
Uh, the green apple
shochu sounds kinda cool.
- Only women order that.
- Only women? Oh!
- Or we can switch.
- Or gay men.
So, wait, what's the
manliest drink on the menu?
- Try a glass of sake then.
- A glass of sake?
I'm gonna go
with the green apple shochu
because I'm secure
with my manhood.
- And do me a favor.
- Yeah.
Don't tell anybody
about the green apple shochu.
[laughs]
- It's really good.
- You can try.
Take anything of mine, too.
I really like your hair,
by the way.
- Really?
- Yeah.
How long have you lived
in LA for?
Six, seven or eight months.
How long have you lived here?
Um, for about
six months, I'd say.
How's your job going,
you told me that you
wanted to do
something different, right?
I, I love it there,
and it's..
I love all the people there,
but I wanna get a part-time job.
Yeah, every time we do anything
I always feel bad for you
'cause you always
have to work.
I know, I wanna do,
like work part-time
and then get an agent
and go to acting school
during the day
and then go to castings..
Do you have a head shot
or resume or anything?
Yeah, but it's when I had blond
hair, like I haven't done..
Oh, really?
You had blond hair?
Yeah.
[laughs]
[instrumental music]
Did you have a good time
tonight?
Yeah.
- Did you?
- Yeah, I had a lot of fun.
- Uh...
- So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Are you going to bed already?
In a little bit,
if you wanna
come hang out for a little.
Sure.
[instrumental music]
[alarm beeping]
(Heidi)
'Jordan, wake up.'
[indistinct chatter on TV]
It's so much fun
working a 9:00 to 5:00 job.
Six. 9:00 to 6:00, baby.
'Oh, sorry.'
I feel like
I'm in school again.
I have to,
like run to the bathroom
to use the phone.
[both laugh]
Okay.
[chuckles]
Stop! Stop!
Stop, Jordan, no tickling.
Alright, stop!
You're gonna make me late!
Don't go to work.
Just lay in bed all day.
[instrumental music]
- 'Heidi, we need you in this.'
- Yeah.
- My assistant Landon's gone.
- Hm.
You gotta do travel today
for me, Damon
'and getting Rob back.'
Wait, who's the third person
you, Rob, and?
- Damon.
- Damon, and he's here, right?
Yeah, Damon,
who works in the warehouse.
- Okay.
- Does that make sense, Heidi?
- Yap.
- Follow that?
'I think that's it.
I need to get lunch'
'So, Heidi,
will you get me a sandwich?'
♪ How much farther
can we drag ourselves ♪
♪ Maybe something's
in the water ♪
♪ Tell us
if we've gone too far ♪♪
[music continues]
[sighs]
(automated message)
'One message.'
(Jason on recorder)
'Hey, what up, Lauren?
It's Jason.'
'Seeing what you're up to,
haven't talked to you'
'for a while
and I know you live in LA now.'
'You know,
I just moved up here as well.'
'And if you wanna hang out..'
'It'd be great to catch up.'
'Uh, give me a call.'
'Alright, bye.'
♪ My first ♪
♪ Apartment ♪
♪ With hesitance ♪
♪ Feeling like
you're making a mistake ♪
♪ Oh I've made them ♪
♪ I'm sorry ♪
♪ It's an awkward
time to replace ♪
♪ History ♪
♪ With feelings ♪
♪ But I'll suck the pain ♪
♪ Out anyways ♪
♪ I'm hardly alive.. ♪
Your books are due today
your trend book, project one
'our first big project.'
I'll sit back here.
I need to hear you, okay?
♪ And leave me on the bed ♪
♪ I could crawl on my hands ♪
♪ And my knees ♪
♪ Change the way ♪
♪ I do everything ♪
♪ My desires ♪
♪ Crumble away ♪
♪ Leaving me safe ♪
♪ Driving away ♪♪