MAL:
Here's how it is. The Earth got used up.
So, we moved out and terraformed
a whole new galaxy of Earths.
Some, rich and flush
with the new technologies,
some, not so much.
The Central Planets,
thems formed the Alliance,
waged war to bring everyone
under their rule.
A few idiots tried to fight it.
Among 'em, myself.
I'm Malcolm Reynolds,
captain of Serenity.
She's a transport ship,
Firefly class.
Got a good crew--
Fighters, pilot, mechanic.
We even picked up a preacher
for some reason...
and a bona fide companion.
There's a doctor too,
took his genius sister
out of some Alliance camp.
So, they're keepin' a low profile.
You understand.
You got a job, we can do it.
Don't much care what it is.
BOOK:
Previously--
What are we doing?
Oh, crime.
Crime.
When a man engages
in clandestine dealings,
he has this preference
for things bein' smooth.
(screams) No! No, I don't want to
River!
She makes things not be smooth.
SIMON:
I have no idea what'll set her off.
Just 'cause Mal says you're medic,
don't make you part of the crew.
You just play at figurin' what's wrong
with that moon-brained sister of yours--
How is she?
She still won't talk about what it was
they did to her at the academy.
Two by two, hands of blue.
We're looking for a girl--
This girl.
RIVER:
They'll never stop.
They'll just keep coming until
they get back what you took.
If they find us, they'll send River
back to that place.
I'd never see her again.
You gave up everything you had to find me.
You found me broken.
It's hard for you.
I don't want it.
River, you have to eat.
It's good. It tastes like--
It's good.
It smells like crotch.
Jayne!
Well, it does.
We don't even have to go
someplace fancy.
We can just go
to the park or something.
Feed the pigeons.
Sure. Feed the pigeons,
probably get the firing squad
for littering.
Come on.
It's not that bad.
It is. It's a core planet.
It's spotless. It's got sensors.
And where there ain't sensors,
there's feds.
All central planets are the same.
Could you please tell my wife
the fun she's missing out on?
Ariel's quite a nice place, actually.
There are some beautiful
museums, not to mention...
some of the finest restaurants
in the core.
But... not boring,
like she made it sound.
There's a, uh,
uh--
There's hiking.
WASH: Yeah.
And you can go swimming in
a bioluminescent lake.
I don't care if it's got sunsets
24 hours a day.
I ain't setting foot on that planet.
No one is setting foot on that fancy rock.
I don't want anyone leaving the ship.
Come to think of it,
I don't want anyone looking
out the windows... or talking aloud.
We're here to drop off Inara.
That's it.
What's the point of coming to the core
if I can't even step off the boat?
You could have got off with Shepherd Book
at the Bathgate Abbey.
Could've been meditating on the wonders
of your rock garden by now.
Well, it beats just sitting.
It is just sitting.
ZOE: So how long are you
gonna be planet-side?
INARA:
Shouldn't be more than a day or two.
WASH: Big stop just to renew
your license to Companion.
Can I use "Companion" as a verb?
It's guild law.
All Companions are required to undergo
a physical examination once a year.
(hawking)
Could you not do that while we're--ever?
WASH: So two days in a hospital.
That's awful.
Don't you just hate doctors?
Hey.
WASH:
I mean, present company excluded.
Let's not be excluding people.
That'd be rude.
(groaning) Son of a--
SIMON: What the hell?
River, no.
Oh, my God. He's bleeding.
That's deep.
Are you okay?
River.
(groans, breathing heavily)
He looks better in red.
(groaning continues)
(inhaling sharply)
Gorram freak's completely off her axle.
I'm sorry about this. I don't know what--
Shut it. I ain't talking to you.
She gotta go.
Both of them gotta go.
Ariel's as good a place as any
to leave them.
Might even pick us up a reward
for our troubles.
No one's getting left.
She belongs in a bughouse.
You don't pitch her off this boat
right now, I swear to you--
What?
What do you swear, Jayne?
They don't get gone, you better start
locking up your room at night.
Next time little sister
gets in a murdering mood,
it might be you she comes calling on.
Maybe Kaylee or Inara.
You let them stay,
we're gonna find out.
Finish your work, Doctor.
This is my boat.
They're part of my crew.
No one's getting left.
Best you get used to that.
You owe me a shirt.
She's to stay confined to her room
at all times. No exceptions.
Take her to the kitchen,
the infirmary, whatever,
you ask me first, understand?
I do.
When I took you and your sister in,
the deal was you keep her in check.
You can't hold up your end,
we're gonna have to revisit the deal.
She's getting worse.
Isn't she?
Yes.
Just look at the bright side.
Maybe you'll meet a young,
handsome doctor.
He'll ask you out, and--
What's the Companion policy on dating?
It's complicated.
Hmm.
Well, that figures.
Stay out of trouble.
You too. Bye.
JAYNE: (grunts)
How are we gonna find a job
if we don't leave the ship?
Alliance territory--
ain't any jobs worth having.
Or the last three places we've been.
My pop always said,
"Anyone who can't find work
ain't lookin' hard enough."
We ain't even lookin' at all.
SIMON: You can stop looking.
There's a client.
Me.
I have a job for you.
♪ Take my love, take my land ♪
♪ Take me where I cannot stand ♪
♪ I don't care, I'm still free ♪
♪ You can't take the sky from me ♪
♪ Take me out to the black ♪
♪ Tell them I ain't comin' back ♪
♪ Burn the land and boil the sea ♪
♪ You can't take the sky from me ♪
♪ There's no place I can be ♪
♪ Since I've found serenity ♪
♪ But you can't take the sky from me ♪♪
You've got a job for us?
One that'll pay for itself ten times over.
WASH: Forget it. We ain't that desperate.
Do you know what this is?
It's a common immune booster
called isoprobyline.
Street value for a dosage this size--
50 platinum, maybe 20 credits.
Propoxyn. Maybe 80.
Hydrozopan, 200.
And these are just from the med kit
I had with me when I came on board.
At a hospital like the one
in Ariel City...
they'll have shelves of that stuff.
Whatever the take,
it's more than enough payment
for what I have in mind.
So the med vault isn't the job?
SIMON:
That's the payment.
I tell you how to get in, get out,
and what's worth taking...
if you help me get River into
the hospital's diagnostic ward.
MAL: What's in the diagnostic ward?
A 3 D neuro imager.
If I can get River in there,
I might be able to figure out
what they did to her at the academy.
So we get you and your sister
into the "whatcha" thing...
and you tell us how to clean out
the hospital.
Yes.
Not to be negative...
but don't the hospital need that medicine?
Government-run facility.
They'd be restocked in a matter of hours.
She's right. They'll never miss it.
Plus, folks on the rim sure could use it.
It's all very sweet stealing from
the rich, selling to the poor.
But you're talking about breaking into
a highly secure Alliance facility.
How do you plan on
getting around security?
It's not easy...
but it can be done.
You see, like all core hospitals...
St. Lucy's has its own
dedicated security force--
a small batter of local Alliance
federals substationed here.
Every floor, every doorway...
is equipped with sensors.
(beeping)
And at all points of entry,
patient ident scans.
However, once clear
of those checkpoints...
movement within the facility itself
should be relatively unhindered.
The standard layout
should put the med vaults--
Go back to the ident scans.
You and your sister are tagged fugitives.
How do you figure we're
gonna get you in the building?
Through the front door.
Believe me, Captain, getting the two
of us in is going to be easy.
The rest of you--
that is going to be the real trick.
We'll need to procure a few items
off-ship. I've made a list.
Given my status as a fugitive,
someone else will have to--
We have some volunteers. Good.
Before we ever make it to the front door,
we're going to have
to breach the perimeter.
Only official vehicles are allowed in,
so we'll need one.
Now obviously we can't steal
what we need.
Any illegal activity
in the planning stages...
could end this thing before it starts.
St. Lucy's Hospital contracts
with the local municipal dump yard...
for all its large disposals.
It figures.
First time on the core,
and what do I get to do?
Dig through trash.
Couldn't he send me shopping
at the Triplex or--
Ooh! Synchronizers!
SIMON:
Big hospitals mean big waste,
so we shouldn't have any trouble
finding what we're looking for.
(laughing)
We'll have to look like we belong.
(beeps)
All we have to do is slip
a couple of bills into the right hands.
That gets us uniforms,
I.D. badges and key cards.
A little creative forgery,
and we've got ourselves a working alias.
Now, all these items are easy to obtain.
They'll get us up to the door.
Now, in order to get us in--
Patients were cynical,
and not responding,
and we couldn't bring 'em back.
They were cyanotic--
And not responsive--
Responsive--
And we were unable to
Resuscitate them.
ZOE: Yes.
Resuscitate.
Resuscitate them.
Good. Which methods did you use?
We tried pulmonary stimulators...
and--and cardiac--
We--
Infusers.
Pulmonary stim
Pulmonary stimulators
And cardiac infusers.
What about cortical electrodes?
Oh. We forgot 'em.
Let's try that again.
Yeah.
Pupils were fixed and dilapidated.
Dilated.
Dilated! Dilated!
(pounding table)
(speaking Chinese)
Shiny.
We got there,
and the patients were cyanotic.
Not responding.
Not responsive.
And we tried to resuscitate them--
And despite our best efforts, they kicked.
Despite our best efforts...
they--
Which methods did you use?
We tried pulmonary stimulators...
and cardiac infusers.
What about the cortical electrodes?
What is that?
We--We applied the cortical electrodes.
Yep, we used them electromagnetic--
Reaction from--
We were unable to get a neural--
We applied the cortical electrodes
but were unable to get
a neural reaction from either--
Unable to get a neural--
Response.
Response. Hell, I don't know.
If I'd wanted schooling,
I'd have gone to school.
I'll get it.
That's amazing.
You two did an incredible job.
And now for the finishing touch.
If I didn't know better, I'd say
you're ready to save some lives.
All we need are a couple of patients.
Corpses, actually.
For this to work,
River and I will have to be dead.
Huh, I'm starting to like this plan.
We're going to be asleep.
Captain Reynolds and the others
will have to pretend we're dead
to sneak us into the hospital.
Once we're inside,
we'll wake up.
Everything will be fine.
You understand?
You're going to suspend cerebral, cardiac
and pulmonary activity...
in order to induce
a proto-comatose state.
That's right.
I don't wanna do it.
I know.
I don't wanna go to that place.
I don't wanna die.
No. No one is going to die.
It's okay.
The others will take care of us
while we're asleep.
And when we get back--
No. Shh-shh-shh.
(whimpering)
River. River, it's okay.
It's okay. This--
This could be
what we've been hoping for.
When this is over,
I'll be able to help you.
I'll be able to make
the nightmares go away.
Okay?
Okay.
All right. Lie back.
It's time to go to sleep.
We speak only when spoken to.
We avoid all unecessary contact
and we stay together until
we reach the morgue. Understood?
Yes, sir.
Apply the cortical electrode--
Jayne?
Unable to get a neural--
Yeah, yeah, I got it. I got it.
Are we gonna have a problem?
I know what I gotta do.
Not what I'm talking about.
Am I gonna have a problem
with you and Simon?
It's up to him.
Look, you got a little
stabbed the other day.
It's bound to make anyone
a mite ornery. So I figure--
It's a good plan.
What?
The doc did good coming up with that job.
Don't mean I like him any better.
Nothing buys bygones quicker than cash.
Maybe I'll give him
a tattoo while he's out.
Let him do his thing, and you get him out.
No messing with him.
Don't worry about me.
As long as I get paid,
I'm happy.
Applied the cortical electrodes.
Unable to get a neural response.
Applied the cortical electrodes--
We've only got a few hours left
before the morning shift.
Won't be an hour.
WOMAN: (over p.a., indistinct)
What do you got?
Got a couple D.O.A.s.
By the time we got there--
Take them down to the morgue.
We applied the cortical electrodes,
but were unable to get...
a neural reaction from either patient.
That should bring them
out of it in a few minutes.
Once they're up,
get them to the imaging suite,
let Simon do his thing,
then haul it back to the rendezvous.
Fifty minutes.
JAYNE: Got it.
I'll just... sit right here.
(door closes)
(sighs)
(people chattering)
WOMAN: (over p.a., indistinct)
(indistinct)
Ni hao?
I'm in.
Do you have the fugitives?
You got my reward?
Yes. Just like we talked about.
Then I got your fugitives.
Good.
We'll see you shortly.
Congratulations.
You are about to become a very rich man.
WOMAN: (over p.a., indistinct)
Copper for a kiss.
Jesus!
What did you say?
(coughing)
What the hell's the matter with you?
(coughing continues)
Nothing. It's just
the aftereffects of the drugs.
I'll be fine.
Just give me a second.
Well, your sister seems okay.
(vomiting)
You gotta get dressed.
We gotta move.
Two lefts, two rights,
and we're there.
You see anyone, smile.
I don't think anybody
smiles in hospitals.
Of course they do. It's a core.
Everyone's rich and happy here.
Why wouldn't they smile?
Excuse me. Excuse me!
Hi.
Where are you taking those bodies?
Just downstairs to the morgue.
Downstairs is that way.
Right. Must've gotten turned around.
Let me see your badge.
You're doing it backwards.
Walking up the down slide.
(whispers)
Keep her quiet.
This is the recovery ward.
This is where patients come to get better.
They're going to die.
No one is going to die.
He is.
No, he's not.
That man standing next to him
is his doctor.
He's going to help him.
He's not going to help him right.
River, the doctors here...
are the best in the system.
(monitor beeping)
This is one of the top hospitals
in the core or anywhere else.
Where you should be.
(beeping increases)
You have to help him.
River, we don't have time.
He's killing him!
DOCTOR: Code blue!
We got a code. Here.
Stay here.
Don't move!
What do we have?
A 42-year-old double bypass, post-op.
Prognosis was positive.
B.P.'s 60 over 20. Pulse is thready.
Who are you?
NURSE: He's crashing.
Get the cart.
We have flatline.
We've gotta crack him.
We're not cracking a post op.
He's nonresponsive.
Should I call the code team?
Get the infusions and .4 of atropine.
What did you give him?
Just 20 of apresaline push.
Clear.
NURSE: Clear.
He's going tachy.
Yeah, but his heart's beating.
(patient moaning)
(rapid beeping)
(beeping slows)
He's okay.
Explain to me how you justify
administering a vasoconstrictor
to this patient.
Apresaline is a painkiller--
Unless you combine it with dilaftin.
Which any first year should know
is the standard prep medicine...
your patient was taking
before his surgery.
Your patient should be dead.
Let's go.
Walk with me a minute.
MAL: Where are we going?
You see this badge?
It says "doctor."
I say walk, you walk.
Yeah, but where are we going?
You must be new.
Don't get comfortable.
Your type doesn't last long here.
When your supervisor...
hears about the rude and dis--
(screams)
Clear.
Ready?
1205. Here it is.
(beeping)
Zoe.
Must've been demagged.
(electronic hum)
WOMAN: (over p.a., indistinct)
(beeping)
They opened up her skull.
That's a scalpel scar.
They--
They opened up her skull,
and they cut into her brain.
Why?
The only reason to make an
incision in someone's brain is...
to lobotomize them-- to go in
and remove damaged tissue.
Why... anyone would cut
into a healthy brain is--
They did it over and over.
They stripped her amygdala.
Her what?
You know, uh--
You know how you get...
scared or...
or worried or nervous,
but you don't want to be scared...
so you push it to the back of your mind.
You try not to think about it.
Your amygdala is what lets you do that.
It's like...
a filter in your brain that
keeps your feelings in check.
She feels everything.
She can't not.
That's fascinating.
Let's get moving.
We still have 20 minutes.
Wrong. Plan changed when you were out.
We're meeting out the back way in five.
I could use another couple minutes.
I'm sure if we get in touch with Captain--
Captain gave his orders.
We play it by the book.
(screaming)
(muffled shouts)
River, shh-shh-shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
Get her in the chair and let's go!
Shh!
No! No! No!
They come out of the black.
They come when you call.
River, it's okay.
It's over. We're leaving.
Your toes are in the sand.
And your head's up your---
Hey! Back off.
You just make sure
she keeps her mouth shut.
We don't need her screeching while
we're trying to make a quiet getaway.
It's okay. It's okay.
(whimpering)
(sighs)
(chattering)
You should've let me know
when the plan changed.
I told you when you needed to know.
What are you griping about?
You got what you came for.
No, no, I can't go back.
I don't wanna go back.
Shh-shh-shh. It's okay.
We're just going back to the ship.
We're almost home.
Shh-shh-shh.
Federal marshals!
Don't move!
(guns cocking)
River and Simon Tam, by the authority
of the Union of Allied Planets,
you are hereby bound by law.
Take them to Processing.
So, you gonna take me away
for questioning now?
How you gonna play it?
You're under arrest for aiding
and abetting federal fugitives.
Better get a lawyer.
You're kidding, right?
Where's my ruttin' money?
You mean my money...
for apprehending the three fugitives?
I expect I'll be getting it soon.
(groaning)
How much did we get?
Enough to keep us flying.
Can we fly somewhere with a beach?
Maybe a naked beach.
Cut it out. The job's not done
until we're back on Serenity .
Sorry, sir. Didn't mean
to enjoy the moment.
Where are the others?
(chattering)
If those officers hadn't been armed,
I think you'd have had a chance.
A guy shoves me, I shove him.
Not like I was trying to mount a rescue.
Still, I appreciate you trying.
You know what I'd appreciate?
You stop flapping that pretty mouth at me.
I'm trying to figure a way out of here.
I can't do it with you yammering.
They took Christmas away.
What the hell now?
I came downstairs for the shiny presents.
They took the tree and the stockings.
Nothing left but coal.
Would you shut her up?
Don't look in the closet either.
It's greedy.
It's not in the spirit of the holiday.
You shut the hell up right now,
or so help me, I will shut you up.
Time?
Ten minutes past rendezvous.
Something's happened.
Kaylee, are you linked?
Uh, I am... now.
What do you need?
WASH: Find out if there's any kind of
security alert in the hospital.
Hang on.
Could be they're just late.
Not this late.
Jayne would've sent up a flag.
KAYLEE: Nothing from hospital security,
nothing on the local pipeline either.
Although I am getting some weird chatter
from the official 262.
(static, chattering)
It sounds like...
they're talking about ducks.
Code.
Feds got 'em.
Have her bring up
the hospital schematic.
Find me a way into
that security substation.
Wait a minute.
You don't even know for sure
if they're in there.
Gonna find out. Check.
Coming in clear.
WASH: So, you're just gonna
walk in through the front door?
No. You're gonna find me
a way around back.
Get up.
What's going to happen to us?
I said, "Get up."
Agent McGuinness, I'm certain
you're working under a superior...
who's keeping close tabs on this case.
I'm certain of that because
important people don't do fieldwork.
I'm also quite certain your superior
wants me and my sister alive.
Now, I'm not going to move from this spot
until one of two things happens.
You answer my very simple question...
or you shoot me.
We're transferring you to a holding area
until you can be retrieved.
SIMON: Retrieved? By whom?
MCGUINESS: People who want you alive.
People, not me.
Take them.
Wash, we could use
a little direction here.
Working on it.
Kaylee, what do you got?
Tell them to hang a left
when they reach Cryo.
They'll see a door.
WASH: (on radio) All right. Go through
that door and down to green level.
This is exactly what I didn't want.
I wanted simple. I wanted in and out.
I wanted easy money.
Things always get a little more
complicated, don't they, sir?
MAL: Just once I'd like things to go
according to the gorram plan.
WASH: (over radio)
Guys, you might wanna hurry.
Is there a problem?
I think the reinforcements
just arrived.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Going out the way we came in.
There are at least four armed
feds out there.
Six. I know.
We run.
You got no idea where that goes .
We'll find our way.
I ain't chancing that.
I can handle the feds.
It doesn't matter.
They're here.
Gentlemen, that was prompt.
We're almost finished here.
The prisoners
will be out in a minute.
Let me get the paperwork together for you.
Bobby, bring that here.
Not that it'll mean much.
The men were tight-lipped.
The girl was just spewing gibberish.
We got it all down.
You spoke to the prisoners?
Well, yeah.
Had to process them.
There was no interrogation,
if that's what you mean.
Didn't do your job for you.
Did your men also speak with them?
Much as they had to.
(electronic humming)
(humming intensifies)
(men shouting, screaming)
What the hell is that?
(shouting, screaming continue)
Two by two.
Hands of blue.
Two by two. Hands of blue.
(mumbling)
(mumbling continues)
Where the hell's she going?
Must be some sort of exit this way.
I don't see no exit.
Dead.
This one's alive.
I got no intention of running around
like a rat in a maze till we're dead.
We're going back.
(man screaming)
Almost there.
There.
Stand back.
Come here.
Se-niou!
High-tech Alliance crap!
(gunshot)
(screams)
Ah, hey there, Inara.
How was your checkup?
Same as last year.
What's going on here?
Well, let's see.
We killed Simon and River,
stole a bunch of medicine,
and now the Captain and Zoe
are off springing and the others
got snatched by the feds.
(vehicle approaching)
Oh, here they are now.
Tell me we weren't followed.
Nothing in our rearview
the whole way back.
All right.
Take us out of the world quick as you can.
We'll be out of atmo in five minutes.
Hey. How was your thing?
As advertised,
lots of needles and cold exam tables.
I heard you had some excitement.
Oh, nothing much.
Lots of running around,
a little gunplay.
A couple needles.
The next time we come to the core,
I'm staying with the preacher.
If you hadn't come,
you wouldn't be getting your big payday.
So, you get what you needed?
I think I did.
I have the information
I downloaded off the imager.
I just have to go over it,
and, uh, I'm hopeful.
What happened to your face?
Huh?
Oh, uh, nothing.
SIMON: He was amazing.
I can't even begin to tell you.
We wouldn't be standing here
if it weren't for him.
Thank you.
Hey, you're part of my crew.
I think I might cry.
All right. Jayne,
help me with the cargo.
Everyone make yourselves useful.
You got jobs.
Go do them.
It's gotta be our best take ever.
Doc had a good notion.
The boy's got a decent criminal mind.
What are you buying with your cut?
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
The job is done.
I figured it was time for a little chat.
(beeping)
(door opening)
(grunting)
MAL: (on radio)
Seems to me we had a solid plan.
"Scruth," you might say.
But what I can't figure out
is what you were doing
around the back exit.
What? I couldn't go out the front!
I had to improvise!
Open the damn door!
You called the feds.
What? I got pinched!
Which is what happens
when you call the feds.
No, I would never do that!
My hand to God!
May he strike me down
as I'm standing here!
Well, you won't be
standing there long.
The minute we break atmo,
you'll be a lot thinner once
you get sucked out that hole.
Oh, come on, Mal!
COMPUTER VOICE:
Leaving atmo in two minutes.
That ain't no way for a man to die!
Secure air lock door at once.
(alarm blaring)
You wanna kill me, shoot me!
Just let me in!
You know, I hear tell they used to
keelhaul traitors back in the day.
I don't have a keel
to haul you on, so--
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry, all right?
Sorry for what, Jayne?
I thought you'd never do such a thing.
Money was too good.
I got stupid.
I'm sorry, okay?
Be reasonable.
What are you taking it
so personal for?
It ain't like I ratted you
out to the feds.
But you did!
You turn on any of my crew,
you turn on me!
But since that's a concept
you can't seem to wrap your head around,
then you got no place here.
You did it to me, Jayne.
And that's a fact.
What are you gonna tell the others?
About what?
About why I'm dead.
I hadn't thought about it.
Make something up.
Don't tell them what I did.
(sighing)
The next time you decide
to stab me in the back,
have the guts to do it to my face.
Can I come in?
Hi.
What are you doing?
Drawing.
That's really good.
What are you doing?
I, um--
I brought some medicine.
Do you remember why
we went to the hospital?
Is it time to go to sleep again?
No, mei-mei.
It's time to wake up.
Grr! Arrgh!