MAL:Here's how it is.
The Earth got used up.
So, we moved out and terraformed a whole
new galaxy of Earths.
Some, rich and flush
with the new technologies,
some, not so much.
The Central Planets,
thems formed the Alliance,
waged war to bring everyone
under their rule.
A few idiots tried to fight it.
Among 'em, myself.
I'm Malcolm Reynolds,
captain of Serenity.
She's a transport ship,
Firefly class.
Got a good crew--
Fighters, pilot, mechanic.
We even picked up a preacher
for some reason...
and a bona fide companion.
There's a doctor too, took his genius
sister out of some Alliance camp.
So, they're keepin' a low profile.
You understand.
You got a job, we can do it.
Don't much care
what it is.
BOOK: Previously--
You're a shepherd.
Thought the outfit gave it away.
One day, you're gonna tell us all how a
preacher knows so damn much about crime.
SIMON:
My sister's a genius.
There was a government-sponsored academy.
We had never even heard of it.
But it had the most exciting program.
For two years,
I couldn't get near her.
Finally I got a letter
that made no sense.
It was a code. It just said,
"They're hurting us."
I still don't know what the government was
trying to do with her,
so I have no idea
if they succeeded.
BOOK:
That young man's very brave.
Gave up everything to free his sister
from that place.
Two by two, hands of blue.
We're looking for a girl.
This girl.
Badger.
Captain Reynolds.
There's a local. Got some property he
wants to sell off-planet.
What my man Harrow needs
himself is a smuggler.
If you're willing to fight that hard
to protect my property,
I'll have it in your hold
before midnight.
It's good to have cargo.
(mooing)
We're in trouble.
We got cut off.
Cut off from what?
Our platoon, Simon.
We got outflanked
by the independent squad,
and we're never gonna make it
back to our platoon.
We need to resort
to cannibalism.
That was fast. Don't we
have rations or anything?
They got lost.
We're gonna have to eat the men.
Aren't you supposed to be practicing
for your dance recital?
I learned it all.
That's wrong.
It's from the book, River.
No. The book is wrong. This whole
conclusion is fallacious.
(sighing)
So, how'd the independents
cut us off?
They were using dinosaurs.
(speaking Chinese)
Language, young man.
Sorry, Dad. The independents
attacked us with dinosaurs.
Simon lost his head
in the heat of battle.
(chuckles, speaks Chinese)
Because there were dinosaurs
involved, I think we'll let it slide.
Did you get my wave?
I got it. Your text shorted.
I got the whole thing during a board
meeting. Thank you.
If I had a dedicated source box,
it wouldn't short out.
I lost half my essay.
Yes, and you'd have access to any
(Chinese)
that filtered in from the cortex.
I absolutely forbid it.
Dad!
I will not have it in my house.
But since your mother's
already ordered you one,
I guess I should give up the fantasy
that this is my house.
Are you kidding?
You will repay me by becoming a
brilliant doctor.
That's the deal.
Dedicated source box--
brilliant doctor.
When do I
Many years.
Dad, this is so (speaking Chinese).
It's really gonna--
I know. You think I'd let you
work with something second-rate?
Thank you.
You're worth it.
Now, do you think it's possible
for you two geniuses...
to give your tired old dad
a couple minutes quiet?
No! No!
I don't want to go there!
It's okay.
It's not okay!
You can't just dig into me, shove pointed
needles in my eyes and ask me what I see!
All right.
We won't go in.
Look. No test today.
No rutting test.
(sobbing)
Stupid son of a bitch dressed me up
like a gorram doll.
No tests, no shots. Come on.
I'm just gonna give you
a smoother cuttle--
River!
Not him.
(cattle mooing)
(speaking Chinese)
(sobbing)
So, she's added cussing and hurling
about of things to her repertoire.
She really is a prodigy.
It's just a bad day.
No. A bad day is when someone's
yelling spooks the cattle.
Understand? Ever see cattle
stampede when they got no place to run?
It's kinda like a meat grinder,
and it'll lose us half our herd.
She hasn't gone anywhere near the cattle.
No.
But in case you hadn't noticed,
her voice kind of carries.
We're two miles above ground, and they can
probably hear her down there.
As soon as we unload, she can
holler until our ears bleed,
although I would take it
as a kindness if she didn't.
The human body can be drained of blood in
8.6 seconds,
given adequate vacuuming systems.
See, morbid and creepifying,
I got no problem with.
Long as she does it quiet-like.
This is paranoid schizophrenia, Captain,
handcrafted by government scientists...
who thought my sister's brain
was a rutting playground.
I have no idea what'll set her off. If you
have some expertise--
I'm not the doctor. And I'm not your
gorram baby-sitter either.
Gag her if you have to.
Got trade to be done.
You see that?
Fancy vessels such as that don't land here
unless they got somethin' to sell.
If it happens to be
somethin' we need... we take it.
♪ Take my love, take my land ♪
♪ Take me where
I cannot stand ♪
♪ I don't care,
I'm still free ♪
♪ You can't take the sky
from me ♪
♪ Take me out to the black ♪
♪ Tell them
I ain't comin' back ♪
♪ Burn the land
and boil the sea ♪
♪ You can't take the sky
from me ♪
♪ There's no place I can be ♪
♪ Since I've found serenity ♪
♪ But you can't
take the sky from me ♪♪
(speaks Chinese)
It's about time you broke in
them pretty shoes.
Hyah! Get along!
You know, they walk just as easy
if you lead 'em.
I like smacking 'em.
(cattle mooing)
Hope this corral's
strong enough to hold 'em.
Shepherd's a purely
figurative title, you know.
Next time we smuggle stock,
let's make it something smaller.
Yeah, we should start dealing
in those black market beagles.
Hyah! Hyah!
Little soul, big world.
Eat, sleep...
and eat...
many souls.
Cattle on the ship three weeks,
she don't go near 'em.
Suddenly we're on Jiangyin, and she's got
a driving need to commune with the beasts.
They weren't cows inside. They were
waiting to be, but they forgot.
Now they see sky, and
they remember what they are.
Is it bad that what she said
made perfect sense to me?
Come on now.
Let's get you clear of the work.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
I'm fixin' to do some business. I can't be
herdin' these steers and your sister too.
She didn't mean any harm.
I never figured she did.
But when a man engages
in clandestine dealings,
he has this preference
for things being smooth.
She makes things
not be smooth.
Right. I'm very sorry
if she tipped off anyone...
about your cunningly
concealed herd of cows.
I'm startin' to think you got a little too
much time on your hands, Doctor.
I think now I got
a notion regarding that.
Why don't you take your sister
for a little walk?
A walk?
Yeah. Someplace away.
It's probably best we stay close. Alliance
has us marked as fugitives.
Closest Alliance is the cruiser Magellan,
hours out from here,
and I promise you, they ain't comin'
to a backwater like Jiangyin.
Still, I'm not sure
it's such a wise suggestion.
Might not want to mistake it
for a suggestion.
Don't worry.
We won't leave without you.
Does it seem every supply store
on every border planet...
has the same five rag dolls
and the same wood carvings of--
What is this? A duck?
That's a swan. I like it.
You do?
Looks like it was made
with, you know, longing.
Made by a person who really
longed to see a swan.
Perhaps because they'd only heard of them
by rough description.
Do you think this
would make a nice gift?
A gift? For whom?
I just kinda like it.
It's rich, you know.
Oh. For Simon.
I didn't say that.
You don't do a very good job
of hiding your interest.
He's just so shuai.
You just wanna take a bite
out of him all over you know,
Careful.
Morning, you two.
Don't usually see you two
out and about planet-side.
Yeah, we're--we're trying
something different today.
River, uh...
be careful with that.
That's, um--
What is that?
That's a postholer.
You dig holes... for posts.
It's-It's dirty and sharp.
Let's come over here.
"Jiangyin Prairie Paradise."
Good God! They're
askin' money for this crap?
Hard to believe, ain't it?
Glad you're out.
Mmm.
Give you a chance
to have a little fun.
Fun? Right. I, uh--
I consider this fun.
It's fun being forced
to the ass end of the galaxy,
to get to live on a piece
of luh-suh wreck...
and eat molded protein,
and be bullied around by our...
(speaking Chinese)
of a captain.
That's fun.
Luh suh?
Sorry?
Serenity ain't luh suh.
No, I-I didn't mean--
Yeah, you did. You meant everything
you just said.
Well, no. Uh, actually
I was being ironic,
so in-in the strictest sense--
You were being mean...
is what.
And if that's what
you think of this life,
then you can't think
much of them that choose it,
can you?
River?
This is the last time,
last time with cows.
Hey, there's an idea regarding beagles.
They have smallish droppings.
I believe so, sir. Also,
your disreputable men are here.
Better go take their money.
(cattle mooing)
Mornin', gentlemen.
You must be the Grange brothers.
Hope you're in the mood
for beefsteak.
Attractive animals,
ain't they?
They ain't well fed.
Scrawny.
Fei hua. Milk and hay
three times a day.
Fed to 'em
by beautiful women.
That was somethin' to see.
They's branded.
You boys are hittin'
all the sellin' points.
The fresh brand's a dead giveaway.
Claim 'em as your own.
Twenty a head.
That's an amusing figure,
in light of you already agreed
on 30 with Badger.
That's before we seen 'em. They're
atrophied.
Standin' on a ship for near a month.
My comprehension is the less muscle,
the more tender the meat. Thirty.
Problem?
No.
About a minute from now,
we'll agree on 25.
(twig snaps)
Seem a mite jumpy to you?
Morning, officers.
I'm thinkin' maybe
we walk away entirely.
I'm thinkin' you do that,
and we got ourselves trouble.
Mornin', ladies. Serious trouble
of the "you owe us" variety.
I can go to 25.
Well, we'll be takin' a loss.
But you seem like clean
and virtuous boys. Done.
Marcus and Nathaniel Grange,
you are both wanted...
in connection to the illegal
killing of Rance Dervin.
You are bound by law
to stand down.
You know, I'm startin' to find this
whole planet very uninviting. Yeah.
♪♪ (lively jig)
Come on!
Get up here, girl!
(whooping, cheering)
Careful with that!
Seems we have ourselves a situation.
Who are you?
Just a bystander.
This your beef?
No, sir.
You're lookin' at the proper
owners right there.
Hmm. I'd like to see
some paper on that cattle.
(grunts)
Graves! Look out! Over here!
Hurry up!
Here we go.
Never goes smooth.
How come it never goes smooth?
♪♪ (continues)
(bullet ricochets)
Get down!
(grunting)
(audio slows)
Hey, stay with me,
Shepherd.
That's--That's quite
a lot of blood, isn't it?
It just means you ain't dead.
'Fraid I might be needin'
a preacher.
That's good. You lie there
and be ironical. Stretcher!
Jayne!
They goin'.
Of course. They got what they came
here for.
You get the cash?
What's going on?
Oh, God! Shepherd.
Shepherd, can you hear me?
Don't look good.
Wash, get down
to the infirmary, ma shong.
Gotta try to stop
this bleeding.
KAYLEE: Don't you worry, Shepherd.
Captain and Zoe got lots of experience
with this kind of thing.
Seen a lot worse in the war.
Shepherd?
Oh, God!
He ain't breathin'.
(gasping)
He ain't dead.
But he is bad off.
Now we gotta see what
we can do to help him.
(speaks Chinese)
Wash, I want you to go to town. See if you
can find that (Chinese) doctor.
Hurry.
Faster. Gotta go faster.
Wanna get there before dark.
Get where?
Where are we going?
Shut up!
If it's ransom you want,
I-I can arrange something.
No talking!
Look, you don't understand!
My sister--
Your sister is fine, Simon.
She's not fine.
Didn't you look at the letters?
Look at the letters.
Well, I'm looking at letters--
These phrases, they don't sound
anything like her.
Some of these words,
they're misspelled.
She started correcting
my spelling when she was three.
She's trying
to tell us something.
I think there's a code.
(chuckles)
A code?
Yes.
I always thought it was River who
was lost without her big brother.
Now I'm beginning to wonder if it isn't
the other way around.
Did you have a good time at the
Darbanvilles' ball this year?
What are you, uh--
River thought it was duller
than last year.
But since we don't know anybody
named Darbanville,
I'm having trouble judging.
Did you even read these?
Well, of course I did.
It's one of her silly games.
You two are always playing.
She is trying to tell us something that
somebody doesn't want her to say.
Simon, this is paranoid.
It's stress.
If they heard you talking like this at the
hospital,
it could affect your entire future.
Who cares about my future?
FATHER: You should.
You're a surgeon in one of the best
hospitals in Capital City...
on your way to a major position,
possibly even the Medical Elect.
You're gonna throw
all that away?
Everything you've
worked for your whole life?
Being a doctor means more to you
than just a position.
I know that.
A few months time, you'll turn around,
and there she'll be.
Nothing is going to keep
you two apart for long.
(bird squawking)
No! Oh, no!
Found you.
Get him!
River, no!
River, run! Run!
Found you!
Go!
Bring her!
(grunting)
Where is the doctor?
Why isn't he with you?
He wasn't in town.
Wasn't anywhere.
He was in town.
We saw him there.
Him and River. I can show you--
The town's not that big. Believe me when
I say he wasn't there.
Knew it. Probably saw
them cops, turned tail.
Doctor could be called a lot of things.
Coward wouldn't be one of them though.
You don't think they were arrested,
do you?
Worse than that, probably.
Looks like they got snatched.
Kidnapped?
I went by the sheriff's office. If we'd
checked the posted alerts,
we might've known it.
Settlers up in the hills take people
sometimes, usually tradesmen and the like.
And now they got
themselves a doctor.
And we don't.
We're going.
Wh-What are you doing?
What about Simon and River?
Forget them. We already
lost two people today.
If I can help it,
we won't lose a third.
Wash, get us in the air.
We're lost.
Lost in the woods.
It's gonna be okay.
They'll find us.
Once the captain realizes what happened,
they'll come.
See there?
No one's comin' for you.
You just keep movin'.
That bad?
Battle wounds are nothin'
new to me, preacher.
I've seen men live with a dozen holes
in 'em this size.
Is that right?
Surely is.
I knew a man who had a hole
clean through his shoulder once.
Used to keep a spare
hankie in there.
Where's the doctor?
Not back yet?
We don't make him hurry
for the little stuff.
He'll be along.
You could hurry a little.
Well, there's Greenleaf.
They'd have med help there.
Too far. More than 10 hours.
Guy's worse off than that.
You know where you can find
what you need.
Don't recall inviting you onto the bridge.
You didn't.
Mal, you know where you can find a doctor.
You know exactly--
Inara, he was dumb enough to get himself
grabbed in broad daylight.
Don't have time to be beating
the trees, looking for him now.
No assurance we'd find him or that he
wouldn't need a doctor himself.
I'm not talking about Simon.
I'm talking
about medical facilities.
That's not an option,
nor is it a discussion I much want to
have at the moment.
It doesn't matter what you want.
He's dying...
and we need a doctor now.
Look at what we got!
Got ourselves a doctor.
A real doctor.
Stand up straight.
WOMAN: They brought home a doctor.
Thank the Lord.
MAN: Come on! We have to go
down there and see!
MAN: What is it?
"Dear Diary, Today I was pompous,
and my sister was crazy.
"Today we were kidnapped by hill folk,
never to be seen again.
It was the best day ever."
Now we're talkin'.
Amazing we kept 'em
this long.
Can I
Sure.
He's out, though.
He did this for me once.
(sighs)
How's he doin'?
I cleaned it out,
wrapped it up.
Best I could do.
I don't know.
Well, we're headed
for help, right?
Captain will
come up with a plan.
Well, that's good. Right?
Possible you're not recalling
some of his previous plans.
We left them back there.
Yeah.
Don't seem right.
You sure this is
where you want to be?
Oh, I'm fairly
certain it ain't.
(radio static)
Be sure to ask nicely.
Alliance cruiser Magellan, this
is Firefly transport Serenity...
requesting permission
for docking.
MAN: (on radio) Firefly transport
Serenity, stand by for docking orders.
In here.
I don't figure it's
as fancy as you're used to,
but it's what we got.
I got you a doctor.
Oh, praise the Lord.
Doralee here'll
show you what's what.
What's your name?
Simon.
Well, hello there.
Who are you?
This is River.
River, just, uh...
just sit down...
over there.
Has there been a--
Is there a sickness here?
Nothing special. Just people get sick
or injured.
Mostly people heal on their own,
but sometimes--
Sometimes you need a doctor.
WOMAN: (coughing)
Bring me light and any supplies you have.
You sanguine about the kind of reception
we're apt to receive on an Alliance ship?
Absolutely.
What's "sanguine" mean?
Sanguine. Hopeful. Plus, point of
interest,
(bell buzzing)
it also means "bloody."
That pretty much covers
all the options, don't it?
We're requesting aid.
No other purpose.
We got papers.
What's your business?
We're a supply ship, freelance.
Had an accident this morning.
A crewman got hurt.
We need medical help.
Fast would be better than slow.
Official seal's out of date,
Captain... Harbatkin?
We ain't been through a checkpoint in a
while, sir. You gonna see to my man?
How did this happen?
He--
Bystander in a gunfight back on Jiangyin.
You can check.
Not he nor any of ours
were the aggressors.
We aren't an emergency facility, Captain.
Our services aren't available simply
to anyone--
Get... my...
my ident card.
Get this man
to the infirmary at once.
Keep that bandage clean
now, you understand?
DORALEE: She's not quite right, is she?
SIMON: She's been through some trauma.
She's recovering, though.
She won't get a good conversation
out of Ruby. I can tell you that much.
That little girl's mute.
Do you know the cause?
Was she born deaf?
No. She was fine until two years ago
when she stopped talking.
A place like this
might be good for your sister.
Quiet, safe. A place where
folks take care of each other.
Mmm, yes. Seems like a lovely little
community of kidnappers.
The Lord says judge not.
They took us off the street.
Sometimes life takes you places
you weren't expectin' to go.
Life didn't bring us here.
Those men did.
You were on a transport ship,
right? Takin' a journey?
It's the way of life in my
findings that journeys end...
when and where they want to, and that's
where you make your home.
This isn't our home.
If it isn't here,
where is it?
(sighs)
This place gives me an uncomfortableness.
So what do you figure? Shepherd's got some
kind of connection with the Alliance?
I know what it looks like. Still, it would
surprise me if he did.
See? That's my whole problem
with pickin' up tourists.
They ain't never
what they claim to be.
Does seem like everyone's
got a tale to tell.
River?
What's wrong?
River's gone.
So's the girl.
Ruby.
I'll check out back.
River! Don't--
What is that?
For you.
Oh.
I picked them.
WOMAN: (coughing)
Here.
They'll stain your dress.
You have to eat.
Hodgeberries.
Do you remember when we found those
giant hodgeberry bushes
on the Cambersons' estate?
And we thought they'd
grown wild, but--
It was a long while ago.
I took you away from there.
No.
I know I did.
You don't think I do, but--
I get confused.
I remember everything.
I remember too much.
And some of it's made up...
and some of it
can't be quantified...
and there's secrets--
Hey. It's okay.
But I understand.
You gave up everything
you had to find me.
You found me broken.
It's hard for you.
You gave up
everything you had.
Mei-mei, everything I have
is right here.
You need to eat,
keep up your strength.
We won't be here long.
Daddy will come
and take us home.
And I'll get better.
I'll get better.
These are better than
the Cambersons' berries.
They are...
except they're poison.
(laughs)
You believed her. Made a face.
You are such a brat.
You get to bed now.
We should probably think
about doing the same.
It's been a big day,
what with the abduction and all.
Well, y'all don't
have to sleep here.
There's a house
set aside for you.
We've been looking for a doctor for a good
while, so things are ready.
Really?
Her sister got killed.
Her mother got crazy,
killed the sister.
That one lived.
Ruby talked to you, honey?
It's true
what she's saying.
Poor woman went out of her mind,
tried to kill her two girls.
Ruby lived.
Sweetheart,
you are an angel.
No one's been able to get Ruby to speak
even a peep.
(laughs)
It's a miracle! That's what it is.
Ruby doesn't talk.
Her voice got scared away.
(crickets chirping)
I hear crickets.
I don't understand.
If Ruby didn't talk,
h-how do you know--
My sister's--
She's very good at--
What's wrong?
"And they shall be
among the people.
"And they shall speak truths
and whisper secrets.
And you will know them
by their crafts."
What are you talking about?
"Thou shalt not suffer
a witch to live."
Have you completely lost your mind?
Pretty nearly.
We got the wave at the Friedlichs. I had
to leave your mother at the dinner table.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You know, I would never have tried to save
River's life...
if I had known there was
a dinner party at risk.
Don't you dare
be flippant with me.
I spent 2,000 credits
to get you out of here.
I had to walk through that door, which
goes on my permanent profile.
Are you trying
to destroy this family?
I didn't realize
it would be so easy.
Dad, I didn't do anything.
You were in a blackout zone.
Talking to someone who
might be able to help River.
And I'm going right back there.
(speaking Chinese)
This is a slippery
slope, young man.
You have no idea
how far down you can go,
and you're not taking us with you.
Meaning what?
I won't come
for you again.
You end up here or get
mixed up in something worse,
you're on your own.
I will not come for you.
Now, are you coming home?
(bell clanging)
This is lunacy!
You're supposed to be the teacher here.
What exactly is it that you teach?
What's going on, woman? Why are you
knocking us from our beds at this hour?
The new doctor's sister's a witch! She
read Ruby's mind, saw things she couldn't.
No, River is not a witch!
She's just a troubled girl.
I'm sure that's true.
You're not a witch, are you?
(speaking Chinese)
I'm the patron here.
Do you know what that means?
Yes. You're in charge.
Ever since
the old patron died.
That's right.
He was sick...
and he was getting better.
You were alone
in the room with him.
(gasps)
No!
PATRON: This girl reads minds
and spins falsehoods!
She's a witch, and we must purge the devil
from her! With fire!
(screaming)
MAL: You're gonna be fine, Shepherd.
Alliance patched you up.
Alliance?
Yeah. They let us come,
and they let us go.
What kind of ident card gets us that kind
of reception and send-off?
I am a shepherd.
Folks like a man of God.
No, they don't. Men of God make everyone
feel guilty and judged.
That's not what I saw.
You like to tell me
what really happened?
I surely would...
and maybe someday I will.
(sighs)
It's good to be home.
Badger just hailed us.
Getting impatient for his share.
Wants us to drop it to his men
on the Kowlan fed base.
That'll be a hell of a lot easier to do
without the two most wanted on board.
Life would look to be simpler
with us not carrying 'fugees.
He is right, you know.
Yeah. Simpler.
(chattering, shouting)
Take me instead.
Take my life for hers.
The witch must die.
God commands it.
MAN:
Up here!
No! Get away from her!
She has done nothing to you!
If she dies tonight, it won't
be God's will that killed her!
It'll be you! Your lunacy!
Your ignorance!
(townspeople murmuring)
That's not gonna
stop us, Doctor.
Postholer.
Digging holes for posts.
Light it.
Time to go.
(spacecraft approaching)
(townspeople murmuring)
(gasps, shouting)
Well, look at this! Appears we got here
just in the nick of time!
What does that make us?
Big damn heroes, sir.
Ain't we just?
Sorry to interrupt, folks.
Y'all got somethin'
that belongs to us,
and we'd like it back.
This is a holy cleansing. You cannot
think to thwart God's will.
Y'all see the man hangin' out of the
spaceship with the really big gun?
I'm not sayin'
you weren't easy to find.
But it was kinda out of our way,
and he didn't want to come.
Man's lookin'
to kill some folk.
So really it's his will y'all
should worry about thwarting.
Gotta say, Doctor, your talent for
alienatin' folks is near miraculous.
Yes, I'm very proud.
Cut her down.
The girl is a witch.
Yeah, but she's our witch,
so cut her the hell down.
Hey, Doctor. Glad you're
back now on the ship.
Thanks.
I've moved him to his room.
How's he faring?
He's gonna be fine. Yeah.
They took good care of him.
Good to know.
So finally a decent wound
on this ship, and I miss out.
I'm sorry.
You were busy trying to get
yourself lit on fire.
It happens.
Captain?
Why did you come back for us?
You're on my crew.
Yeah, but you don't even like me.
Why'd you come back?
You're on my crew. Why are we
still talking about this?
Chow's in ten.
No need to dress.
MAL: So the shepherd says to the
Companion, "A good goat will do that."
(laughter)
Great.
Grr! Arrgh!