MAN: After the Earth was used up,
we found a new solar system,
and hundreds of new Earths
were terraformed and colonized.
The central planets
formed the Alliance...
and decided all the planets
had to join under their rule.
There was some disagreement
on that point.
After the war, many of the Independents
who had fought and lost...
drifted to the edges
of the system,
far from Alliance control.
Out here, people struggled to get by with
the most basic technologies.
A ship would bring you work.
A gun would help you keep it.
A captain's goal was simple:
Find a crew, find a job.
Keep flying.
Over here!
(grunts)
(yelling, cheering,
hooting)
Yeah! Too tall!
Too tall!
Jayne!
Little man!
(yelling continues)
Ah!
Yes!
JAYNE: Come on, little man!
Ha ha!
Shoot it!
(yelling, laughing)
Right behind you--
Yeah!
JAYNE: (shouting,
indistinct)
Hello.
Who's winning?
I can't really tell.
They don't seem to be playing
by any civilized rules that I know.
Well, we're pretty far
from civilization.
INARA:
How's your sister?
She's good. Better.
She has her days,
and she still won't talk about what it was
that they did to her at the academy.
INARA: Perhaps she's not
sure herself.
Open!
Aah!
Good eye! Good eye!
She dreams about it.
I know that much.
Nightmares.
WASH: (grunting) Right behind you.
And now, on the run,
on this ship...
I don't know if I'll be able to help
her here, and I need to help her.
Simon, you are.
Leaving your whole world
behind?
That's incredibly
selfless.
JAYNE: Nice!
Yeah.
(shouting, grunting continues)
I selflessly turned us both
into wanted fugitives.
Well, we're all running
from something, I suppose.
(alarm sounding)
Proximity alert.
We must be coming up
on something.
Oh, my God.
What can it be?
We're all doomed!
Who's flying this thing?
Oh, right.
That would be me.
Uh, back to work.
So that makes us one man short.
Yeah. Little Kaylee's
always one man short.
Ow! Hey!
Say, Doc, why don't you
come on down, play for our side.
Inara won't mind.
(beeps)
Aah!
Wash, you have a stroke
or something?
Near enough.
What happened?
(speaks Chinese)
Anybody home?
I've been hailing her, but if whoever's
there
is as healthy as the guy we just ran over,
I can't imagine anybody's gonna be
picking up.
Bring us in a little closer.
Get you close enough
to ring the doorbell.
What is it?
It's a ghost.
♪ Take my love, take my land ♪
♪ Take me where
I cannot stand ♪
♪ I don't care,
I'm still free ♪
♪ You can't take the sky
from me ♪
♪ Take me out to the black ♪
♪ Tell them
I ain't comin' back ♪
♪ Burn the land
and boil the sea ♪
♪ You can't take the sky
from me ♪
♪ There's no place I can be ♪
♪ Since I've found serenity ♪
♪ But you can't
take the sky from me ♪♪
MAL: So, what do we figure?
Transport ship?
Converted cargo hauler.
Maybe a short-range scow.
You can see she don't
wanna be parked like that.
The port thrust's gone, and that's what's
making her spin the way she is.
A short-range vessel
this far out into space?
Retrofitted
to carry passengers.
Travelers pick them up cheap
at government auction.
A few modifications, and they serve
well enough
for a one-way push
to the outer planets.
Settlers.
Cram 15, maybe 20 families on a boat that
size, you pack 'em in tight enough.
Families?
Tell you what I think.
I figure that fella we run into
did everyone on board.
Killed 'em all.
Then he decided to take a swim, see how
fast his blood would boil out his ears.
You're a very "up" person.
Shouldn't we report this?
To who? The Alliance?
Right. They're gonna run right out here
lickety-split and make sure these
taxpayers are okay.
Then we'll have to.
If there's folks in need of help, why
aren't they beamin' no distress call?
It's true. There's no beacon.
Which means it's likely no one's looking
to find her.
All the more reason for us
to do the right thing.
How's about you just say a prayer
when we slide on by?
Shall I remind you of the story
of the Good Samaritan?
I'd rather you didn't.
But we'll check it out.
Could be survivors,
and if not, well, then,
no one's gonna mind if we take a look
around and see
if there's not something of
value they might've left behind.
Yeah--No, uh,
someone could be hurt.
(buzzer)
Where do you think
you're headed?
Thought I'd offer
my services,
in case anyone on board
required medical attention.
Well, the captain and Zoe
are goin' in first.
We'll holler if we need ya.
Somethin' wrong?
Hmm?
Oh. No. No, I--
Well, I--I suppose it's just the thought
of a little Mylar and glass...
being the only thing
separating a person from...
nothing.
It's impressive what "nothing"
can do to a man.
Like that feller
we bumped into.
He's likely stuck up under our belly
about now.
That's what space trash does you know--
kinda latches on the first big
somethin' stops long enough.
Hey, now.
That'd be a bit like you and your sister,
wouldn't it?
(buzzer)
Entering adjoining
air lock now.
Okay, Wash, ask Serenity
to knock for us.
(buzzer)
Emergency power's up.
Dashboard light.
MAL: Whatever happened here
happened quick.
Everything was left on.
Ship powered down
on its own.
No sign of a struggle.
They're just
Gone.
Sir.
Personal log. Someone was in the middle
of an entry.
(loud static burst)
(gasps)
(panting, whimpering)
(sobbing)
(sobbing continues)
Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay.
It's okay. I'm here.
(continues panting,
sobbing)
Bad dreams again?
I--I can't sleep. There's too much
screaming.
River, there is--
there is no screaming.
(whispers)
There was.
Hey. Grab your med kit.
Let's hoof it.
Mal wants us both over there
on the double.
They found survivors?
Didn't say.
Right.
Uh, I-I'll ask Inara
to look in on River.
Whatever.
I ain't waitin'.
I'll meet you over there. But don't take
forever. Still gotta get suited up.
(buzzer)
(door slams)
(gasps)
(labored breathing)
Hi.
(grunting)
(panting)
Um, what are you doing here?
And what's with the suit?
(continues panting)
You're hilarious.
SIMON: Sadist.
All right, enough.
Ain't got time for games.
As long as you're here, you may as well
lend a hand. You can roll with Kaylee.
Let's be quick about this people.
All right.
A few loads each. No need to be greedy.
Where are
all the people?
Ship says lifeboat launched more
than a week ago.
\We're gonna assume everyone got off okay.
Anyway, we're just here to pick the bones,
so you two start in the engine room.
Jayne, you take the galley.
You, um, have this on wrong.
(laughs)
Sir, I count 16 families
signed on.
Lifeboat wouldn't hold
a third of that.
I know.
Wash, any luck?
Think I found something that pretty well
matches that class.
The layout looks about right.
Seems to me any valuables,
if there are any,
would likely be stored
somewhere...
"C" Deck, aft.
Good work. Keep the engine running.
We shouldn't be long.
River? It's Inara.
Are you hungry,
sweetie?
River?
SIMON: Aren't you the least bit curious?
About what?
Well,
what happened here.
I mean, why would anybody abandon their
ship in the middle of nowhere like this?
For all sorts of reasons.
Just not mechanical.
What? There ain't nothin'
wrong with this.
Not that I can see, anyhow.
Whoo!
(chuckles)
Well, there's a good one.
(grunts)
Hold the bag open.
This looks to be it.
(beeping)
Locked.
Well, now, I'd say that's like to be
a very good sign.
MAL: Here.
Gen-seed, protein,
crop supplements.
Everything a growing family needs...
to make a fresh start
on a new world.
Hard subsidies
for 14-plus families.
That's--
About a fortune.
Forget the rest.
We just take this stuff.
Gonna need a hand
hauling it out of here.
Sir, even on a lifeboat...
you'd think those who escaped would find
room for some of this.
MAL: Nobody escaped.
ZOE: Sir?
Nobody.
My God.
(speaks Chinese)
I know what did this.
Get her out of here.
Jayne?
MAL: Jayne, drop what you're doing
and get to the engine room.
I want you to take Kaylee and the doctor
off this boat.
Don't ask questions.
(yelling)
MAL: (on radio)
Jayne?
(gunshot)
Captain?
Captain.
(gunshot)
Zoe!
Came from above, sir.
The galley.
What?
KAYLEE: We heard shootin'.
River, what are you--
I followed the voices.
Don't ever leave the ship. Not ever.
Handle her, will you, son?
WASH: (on radio) What in the (Chinese)
is going on in there?
Not now, dear.
What'd you see?
(panting)
Didn't.
Came at me from behind.
Big, though.
Strong.
I think I might have hit him.
You did.
MAN: No. No, no.
MAL: Shh. Easy, now.
No one's gonna hurt you.
No. No mercy. No.
Any more than we already did.
No mercy.
We got lots of mercy.
We got lots and lots of--
(groans)
SIMON:
Oh, yes.
He's a real beast.
It's a wonder
you're still alive.
Looked bigger
when I couldn't see him.
I wonder how long
he'd been living like that.
Don't know.
He must be real brave to survive like that
when nobody else did.
(sniffs)
Yeah. Real hero, killin' all them people.
KAYLEE: What?
No, we don't believe that.
We don't, do we?
Captain wouldn't have brought him on
board, were that the case.
SIMON: Pulse is rapid.
Blood pressure's high side of normal--
to be expected.
Weak.
They were all weak.
Other than the bullet wound, there doesn't
appear to be any exterior trauma.
Though that crack to the head you gave him
probably didn't do him any good.
(grunts, panting)
Cattle.
Cattle
for the slaughter.
Dope him.
I don't think that--
Just do it.
No mercy.
No resistance.
(groans)
(grunting)
(needle gun hisses)
Open up.
See what's inside.
(panting)
(whispers)
No mercy.
So? How's our patient?
Uh, aside from
borderline malnutrition,
he's in remarkably good health.
So he'll live, then?
Which, to my mind,
is unfortunate.
Not a very charitable attitude, Captain.
Charity'd be putting a bullet in
his brainpan.
Mal!
It'd save him the suffering.
All right.
No one goes in here.
Nothing more we can do for him,
not after what he's seen.
What do you mean?
That ship
was hit by reavers.
Reavers?
(speaks Chinese)
INARA: Mal, how can you know?
JAYNE: He don't, that's how.
No way.
It was that other fella,
the one we run into.
Like I said before, he went stir crazy,
killed the rest,
then took a walk in space.
Just a second ago, you said
Don't matter what I said.
Wasn't reavers. Reavers don't leave
no survivors.
Strictly speaking,
I wouldn't say they did.
What are you
suggesting?
Don't matter we took him
off that boat, Shepherd.
It's the place he's gonna live
from now on.
I don't accept that.
Whatever horror he witnessed,
whatever acts of barbarism,
it was done by men,
nothing more.
Reavers ain't men.
Of course they are.
Too long removed from civilization,
perhaps, but men.
And I believe there's a power
greater than men.
A power that heals.
Reavers might take issue
with that philosophy,
if they had a philosophy,
and if they weren't too busy
gnawing on your insides.
Jayne's right.
Reavers ain't men.
Or they forgot how to be.
Come to just nothin'.
They got out to the edge of the galaxy,
to that place of nothin',
and that's what they became.
Why are we still sittin' here?
If it was reavers, shouldn't we be gone?
Work ain't done. Still substantial money
value sittin' over there.
Oh, I ain't goin' over there
with them bodies.
No ruttin' way.
Not if reavers messed with 'em.
Jayne,
you'll scare the women.
SIMON:
I'll go.
I've dealt with bodies. They don't worry
me.
I'd like to go with him.
Maybe see what I can do about putting
those folks to rest.
Those folks are already restin' pretty
good, Shepherd. Reavers saw to that.
How we treat our dead is part of what
makes us different...
than those did the slaughtering.
All right. You go say your words.
Jayne, you'll help the doctor and Shepherd
Book cut down those people.
Then you'll load up the cargo.
I don't believe this.
We're sittin' put for a funeral?
Yes, Jayne, that is exactly
what we're gonna do.
Not gonna have these people lookin' over
my shoulder once we're gone.
I ain't sayin'
there's any peace to be had,
but on the off chance there is,
those folks deserve a little of it.
Just when I think
I've got you figured out.
That was real pretty, Captain,
what you just said.
Didn't think you were one
for rituals and such.
I'm not. But I figure it'll keep
the others busy for a while.
No reason to concern them
with what's to be done.
Sir?
MAL: It's a real burden
being right so often.
What is that?
Booby trap.
Reavers sometimes leave 'em
for the rescue ships.
Triggered it when we latched on.
And when we detach?
It blows.
Okay, so we don't detach.
We just, I don't know, sit tight until--
What, reavers come back?
Looks like they've jerry-rigged it
with a pressure catch.
It's the only thing that'd work
with all these spare parts.
We could probably bypass that easy,
we get to the D.C. line.
You tell me right now, little Kaylee.
You really think you can do this?
Sure. Yeah.
I think so.
Besides, if I mess up, it's not like
you'll be able to yell at me.
(nervous chuckle)
No. No!
(mutters) No mercy.
(panting)
(laughing)
Aah! Aah!
(whimpers)
Ohh! (continues whimpering)
Shh.
(loud crash)
(screaming)
(grunts)
What's goin' on?
Well, right at this particular moment,
I have to say, not a thing.
Right?
KAYLEE: Not a gorram thing.
Looked like a thing to me.
Thought we might have had a situation,
but it looks to be taken care of.
Let's get that merchandise
put away.
Everyone's home, Wash.
Let's go.
(alarm sounding)
No, no, don't you say that.
It's the reavers.
The gorram reavers come back.
Get that stuff stored.
Like it's gonna matter!
Just do it!
(alarm continues)
Reavers?
MAN: (over speaker)
Firefly-class transport,
you are ordered to release control
of your helm.
Prepare to dock
and be boarded.
Looks like civilization
finally caught up with us.
CREW MEMBER:
Initiate molecular run.
No mandatory registration markings
on the bow.
Make sure we cite them
for that.
Sir, we've identified the transport ship
they were attached to.
It was licensed to a group of families
out of Bernadette.
They were due to touch down
in Newhall three weeks ago.
Never made it.
Once we secure these vultures, we'll send
a team over, check it out.
Sir, didn't we have a flag on a Firefly
a while back?
Check.
Oh, here it is.
An alert issued on an unidentified
Firefly-class...
believed to be carrying two fugitives--
a brother and sister.
What are they wanted for?
It's not available.
It's classified.
Forty thousand of these old wrecks in
the air, and that's all they give us.
Well, I'm not about to have any surprises
on a routine check.
We run into these two,
we shoot first.
Brass can sort it out later.
So what was it?
Open the stash, pull out the goods.
What? I just got done putting it in.
Yeah. And now I'm telling you take
it all out again.
Why for?
I got no notion to argue this.
In about two minutes, this boat's gonna be
crawling with Alliance.
No.
We've gotta run.
Can't run. They're pulling us in.
If they find us, they'll
send River back to that place.
To be tortured.
I'd never see her again.
Stack everything in plain sight.
Wouldn't want it to seem like
we got anything to hide.
Might give them Alliance boys
the wrong impression.
Or the right one.
That too.
Now, go fetch your sister.
What?
Why? Are you gonna put her
in plain sight too?
Don't get touchy.
Just do as I say.
Is that why you let us stay, so you could
use us as bargaining chips?
Knew there was a reason.
You are not giving her to them.
Don't be a fool, son.
Do as the man says.
Well,
quite a lot of fuss.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think we were dangerous.
Is this your vessel?
It is. Bought and paid for.
I'm Captain Malcolm Reynolds.
And is this everyone, Captain?
By way of crew, it is.
Though in our infirmary you're gonna find
a fella we rescued off that derelict.
Saved him,
guess you could say.
Mmm.
Straight to the back,
next to the common area.
And these items,
you rescued them as well?
MAN: (cackling)
Looks to me like
an illegal salvage operation.
It does?
That's discouraging.
Alliance property too.
You could lose your ship Caprain.
But that is a wrist slap compared to
the penalty for harboring fugitives.
A brother and sister. When I search this
vessel, I won't find them, will I?
No children on this boat.
Mmm.
I didn't say children.
Siblings.
Adult siblings.
I misunderstood.
Mmm.
No chance
they could have stowed away?
No one would blame you
for that, Captain.
I know how these older-model Fireflies
tend to have those troublesome little
nooks.
Do they?
Smugglers and the like tend to prefer them
just for that reason.
(whispering)
We will continue this conversation
in a more official capacity.
I want every inch
of this junker tossed.
"Junker"?
Settle down, Kaylee.
But, Captain, did you hear what that
purple-belly called Serenity?
MAL: Shut up!
MAN: Get him outta here.
COMMANDER: You are a Companion.
INARA: Yes.
And you were based for years
on Sihnon.
It's only in the last year that you've
been shipping out with The Serenity?
It's just Serenity,
and that's correct.
In a few weeks it will be a year.
Why is this important?
I'm just trying to put the
pieces together.
It's a, uh-- It's a curiosity,
a woman of stature such as yourself...
falling in with... these types.
Not in the least. It's a mutually
beneficial business arrangement.
I rent the shuttle from Capt. Reynolds,
which allows me to expand my client base,
and the captain finds that
having a Companion on board...
opens certain doors that might otherwise
be closed to him.
And do you love him?
I don't see how that's relevant.
Well, he is your husband.
Yes.
You two met
through Capt. Reynolds?
Captain was looking for a pilot.
I found a husband.
Seemed to work out.
You fought with Reynolds in the war?
Fought with a lot of people in a war.
And your husband.
Fight with him sometimes too.
Is there any particular reason you don't
wish to discuss your marriage?
Don't see that it's
any of your business is all.
We're very private people.
WASH:
The legs.
(chuckling) Oh, yeah. Definitely have to
say it was her legs.
You can put that down.
Her legs, and right where her legs meet
her back. Actually, that whole area.
That, and above it.
Six gerstlers crammed
under every cooling drive...
so that you strain
your primary artery function,
and you end up having to recycle secondary
exhaust through a bypass system...
just so's you don't end up pumping it
through the main atmofeed...
and asphyxiating the entire crew.
Now, that's junk.
Have you seen what she wears?
Forget about it.
Have you ever been
with a warrior woman?
Pirates. Pirates with
their own chaplain.
There's an oddity.
Not the only oddity this end of space,
Commander,
where things aren't always so plain
as on the central planets.
Rules can be a mite fuzzier.
These fugitives that we're looking for--
the brother and the sister.
They were last seen on Persephone.
That a fact?
They also left port aboard
a Firefly-class transport,
just about the same time that you
shipped out with Serenity.
Well, Persephone's
a big place.
Yes. Yes, it is.
And that Firefly isn't.
And if anyone's hiding
anywhere on it,
we will find them.
So, I figure by now you been over to the
derelict, seen for yourself.
Yes.
Terrible thing.
If you want my advice,
you won't tow it back.
Just fire the whole gorram thing from
space, be done with it.
That ship is evidence. I'm not in the
habit of destroying evidence.
Course not.
Be against the rules.
I'm gonna make a leap here...
and figure this is your first tour out
here on the border. (sniffs)
It's a very loyal crew
you have there.
But then,
I can tell by your record...
you have a--a tendency to inspire that
quality in people... Sergeant.
It's not sergeant. Not anymore.
War's over.
For some,
the war'll never be over.
I notice your ship's
called Serenity.
You were stationed on Hara
at the end of the war.
Battle of Serenity Valley took place
there, if I recall.
You know I believe
you might be right.
Independents suffered
a pretty crushing defeat there.
Some say that after Serenity
the browncoats were through,
that the war ended
in that valley.
Hmm.
Seems odd you'd name your ship after a
battle you were on the wrong side of.
May have been the losing side.
Still not convinced it was the wrong one.
Is that why you attacked
that transport?
What?
You're still fighting the same
battle, Sergeant.
Only those weren't soldiers
you murdered.
They were civilians, families,
citizens loyal to the Alliance,
trying to make a new life, and you just
can't stand that, can you?
So we attacked that ship, then brought the
only living survivor to our infirmary.
Is that what we did?
I'd ask him,
only I'm not sure he'll be able to speak
with his tongue split down the middle.
(mutters in Chinese)
I haven't seen
that kind of torture since--
well, since the war.
I should have known.
You and your crew
are bound by law.
Formal charges will be transmitted
to central authority.
Commander, I'm not what you need to be
concerned about right now.
Things go the way they are,
there's gonna be blood.
Get him down! Let's start the pressure.
(nurses, attendants shouting)
Get a line in.
Go.
All right.
Come on, go.
(screams)
Reavers?
That is what I said.
You can't imagine how many times
men in my position hear that excuse--
Reavers did it.
It's the truth.
You saw them, did you?
Wouldn't be sittin' here talkin' to you
if I had.
No, of course not.
But I'll tell you who did--
that poor bastard you took off my ship.
He looked right into the face of it
and was made to stare.
It.
The darkness.
The kind of darkness
you can't even imagine.
Blacker than the space
it moves through.
Very poetic.
They made him watch.
He probably tried to turn away.
They wouldn't let him.
You call him a survivor.
He's not.
A man comes up against
that kind of will,
the only way to deal with it,
I suspect, is to become it.
He's following the only course
left to him.
First he'll try to
make himself look like one.
Cut on himself,
desecrate his flesh.
And then...
he'll start actin' like one.
(beep)
(sniffs)
Let's have two M.P.s up here to escort
Sergeant Reynolds to the brig.
Let's go again.
Later... maybe.
The captain said
once the coast is clear,
we should lay low
in the shuttle.
Come on.
Coming back.
Yes. Yes, of course he is.
They all are.
Your ship and its contents
will be auctioned.
The proceeds of the sale will be applied
to the cost of your defense.
(whispering)
Get him out of here.
Go to full lockdown.
I want guards on the nursery.
It won't matter. You won't find him.
But I know where he'll go.
Wait, no.
Don't. Don't.
River, it's okay.
Wait. Wait... here.
They've gone.
Come on.
Don't-- (whimpers)
River, it's okay.
No.
Come on.
Don't--
(whimpers)
River you don't have to
be afraid.
Why would he
come back here?
Looking for familiar ground.
He's on the hunt.
All right,
let's get him to the brig.
No, no, no. I should go with you.
That's out of the question.
How many more men you feel like
losing today, Commander?
Nobody knows Serenity like I do.
I can help you.
We let him go first.
Right.
You want to, uh--
Thanks. Now I'll really
have the advantage.
We don't know how long it's going to be.
I don't think we should move around much.
I'm just gonna grab
some food--
(whimpering softly)
Someone's coming.
(screams)
(soldier groans)
(grunting, yelling)
(neck snaps)
(panting)
You save his gorram life.
He still takes the cargo.
(speaks Chinese)
He had to.
Couldn't let us profit.
Wouldn't be civilized.
Grr! Arrgh!