MAN: After the Earth was used up,
we found a new solar system,
and hundreds of new Earths
were terraformed and colonized.
The central planets
formed the Alliance...
and decided all the planets
had to join under their rule.
There was some disagreement
on that point.
After the war, many of the Independents
who had fought and lost...
drifted to the edges of the system,
far from Alliance control.
Out here, people struggled to get by with
the most basic technologies.
A ship would bring you work.
A gun would help you keep it.
A captain's goal was simple:
Find a crew, find a job.
Keep flying.
(men laughing)
♪♪ (belly dancing music)
Your move.
That's a bold move.
I live on the edge.
Nice work, dumb ass.
(chuckling)
I've given some thought to moving off
the edge. Not an ideal location.
Might get a place in the middle.
MAN: Toast!
Toast!
Quiet!
Shut up!
(music stops)
I'm, uh-- I got words.
I'm saying this...
is an "ass-picious" day.
We all know
what day it is.
Suspicious?
What day is it?
A glorious day for all the proud members
of the allied planets.
Unification Day!
MAN: Yeah, yeah.
The end of the scumbag independents...
and the dawn of a new galaxy.
Yeah!
Captain.
Just feel the need
for another drink.
What month is it?
(speaking Chinese)
Hey. You gonna drink
to the Alliance with me?
Six years today,
the Alliance sent
the browncoats runnin',
pissin' their pants.
You know, your coat is kind of
a brownish color.
It was on sale.
You didn't toast.
You know? I'm thinkin' you're one
of them independents.
And I'm thinking you weren't burdened with
an overabundance of schooling.
So why don't we just ignore each other
till we go away?
The independents were a bunch of cowardly,
inbred piss pots.
Should've been killed
off of every world spinnin'.
(glass thumps on counter)
Say that to my face.
I said...
you're a coward and a piss pot.
Now, what are you
gonna do about it?
Nothin'. I just wanted you to face me
so she could get behind you.
Drunks are so cute.
Oh.
(speaking Chinese)
WOMAN:
Jayne?
Hey, I didn't fight
in no war.
Best o' luck though.
Fine. Let's do this.
(shouting)
Wash, we got some
local color happening.
Grand entrance
would not go amiss.
Is Jayne even awake?
Whoa, whoa. Ha-ha!
Oh, ho-ho. There's just an acre
of you fellas, isn't there?
This is why we lost, you know.
Superior numbers.
Thanks for
the reenactment, sir.
JAYNE: Hey, hey.
Them ain't "kosherized" rules.
I'm thinkin' somebody
needs to put you down, dog.
What do you think?
I'm thinkin' we'll rise again.
MAN: (over loudspeaker)
Every man there go back inside,
or we will blow a new crater
in this little moon.
Damn yokels can't even tell a transport
ship ain't got no guns on it.
Blow a new crater in this moon.
(laughing)
My thanks, Wash.
Nice save, as always.
A pleasure.
And how are our passengers?
They're fine.
So, what happened?
Another terrible brawl?
Oddly enough, there was.
Are you getting my wife into trouble?
Wha--
I didn't start it.
I just wanted a quiet drink.
Funny, sir,
how you always seem to find yourself in an
Alliance-friendly bar come "U" Day,
looking for a quiet drink.
See, this is another sign
of your tragic space dementia,
all paranoid and crotchety--
breaks the heart.
Did we at least make a contact?
Ladies and menfolk,
we have ourselves a job.
Take us out
of the world, Wash.
Got us some crime to be done.
♪ Take my love, take my land ♪
♪ Take me where
I cannot stand ♪
♪ I don't care,
I'm still free ♪
♪ You can't take the sky
from me ♪
♪ Take me out to the black ♪
♪ Tell them
I ain't comin' back ♪
♪ Burn the land
and boil the sea ♪
♪ You can't take the sky
from me ♪
♪ There's no place I can be ♪
♪ Since I've found serenity ♪
♪ But you can't
take the sky from me ♪♪
(whimpering)
(screaming)
(instruments clattering)
River?
River, it's okay.
(sobbing)
It's me.
You know who I am?
(exhales)
Simon.
Were you dreaming?
Did you dream about the academy?
It's not relevant.
If you can talk about
what happened there--
I know it's hard, but the more I know,
the faster you'll get better.
This isn't home?
No.
No, we can't go home.
If we go home, they'll just send you
back to the academy.
This is safe for now.
We're on a ship.
Midbulk transport.
Standard radion
accelerator core,
class-code 03-K64.
Firefly.
Well, that's something.
I can't even
remember all that.
SIMON: Need a weave on that?
It's nothin'.
I expect that someone's face
feels differently.
Well, they tell ya, never hit a man
with a closed fist,
but it is, on occasion, hilarious.
Hmm. I suppose so.
So, the, uh-- the fight didn't...
draw any, um, any attention?
No feds. Just an honest brawl
between folk.
None of us want the Alliance on us,
Doctor. That's why you're here.
I thought I was here
because you needed a medic.
Well, not today.
Mal.
Bad.
In the Latin.
Shepherd Book.
Captain.
How's the girl?
Still a little whimsical
in the brainpan.
Seems calm enough though.
(instruments clattering)
SIMON: River.
That young man's very brave.
Yeah. He's my hero.
Gave up everything to free
his sister from that place.
Go from being a doctor
on the central planets...
to hiding on the fringes
of the system.
There's not many
would do that.
Suppose not.
There's not many would
take him in either.
Why did you?
Same reason I took you on board, Shepherd.
I need the fare.
(chuckles)
There's neither of us can pay a tenth of
what your crew makes on one of your jobs.
Are you referring to our perfectly
legitimate business enterprises?
I'm wondering why a man so anxious to fly
under Alliance radar...
would house known fugitives.
The Alliance had her in that institution
for a purpose,
whatever it was, and they will
want her back.
You're not overly fond
of the boy, so why risk it?
Because it's
the right thing to do.
Oh, would you
look at this.
Kaylee!
I'm beginning to wonder if you yourself...
know why you're doing it.
What about you, Shepherd? How come you're
flying about with us brigands?
I mean,
shouldn't you be off bringing religiosity
to the fuzzy-wuzzies or some such?
Oh, I got heathens
aplenty right here.
If I'm your mission, Shepherd,
best give it up.
You're welcome on my boat.
God ain't.
Where in the hell's
that girl?
Do you want me
to put it up?
No, that's okay.
You have such lovely hair.
I'm sure the doctor would agree.
Who? Simon?
No, he's much too--
I mean, I'm just--
Do you think it looks better up?
(chuckles)
We can experiment.
We might even get wild later
and wash your face.
You ever do this for your clients?
Very occasionally. Not all of them have
enough hair to get a brush through.
Have you ever had to service
a really hideous client,
with boils and the like?
A Companion chooses
her own clients.
That's guild law.
But physical appearance
doesn't matter so terribly.
You look for
compatibility of spirit.
There's an energy about a person
that's difficult to hide.
You try to feel that--
And then you...
try to feel the energy
of their credit account.
It has a sort of aura.
What did I say to you about barging into
my shuttle?
That it was manly and impulsive?
Yes, precisely. Only the exact phrase
I used was "Don't."
Well, you're holding my mechanic in
thrall, and, Kaylee,
what's going on in the engine room?
Were there monkeys? Some terrifying space
monkeys maybe got loose?
I had to rewire the grav thrust...
because somebody won't replace
that crappy compression coil.
Get the place squared away.
It's dangerous in there, and I ain't
payin' you to get your hair played at.
(speaking Chinese)
We work
before we play.
You're servicing crew now?
(snickers)
In your lonely, pathetic dreams.
What do you want?
We have a job. Congratulations.
This job wouldn't be on
a decently civilized planet...
where I could screen some
respectable clients, perhaps?
"Respectable clients."
That seems a contradiction.
Don't start.
There's, um--
We haven't got a location yet.
We'll be landing
on a skyplex in a bit.
Run by a fella called Niska.
Never heard of him.
Well, I have, and while we're there,
you'll stay confined to the ship.
Is the petty criminal perchance ashamed
to be riding with a Companion?
Niska has
a very unlovely rep.
He's got work for me,
fine. But I don't--
I'm not sure
you'd be safe.
Mal, if you're being a gentleman,
I may die of shock.
Hmm.
Have you got time to do my hair?
Out.
MAN: He's fine.
Crow, they can come in.
Eh, Malcolm Reynolds
is which?
I'm Captain Reynolds. My first mate Zoe.
This is Jayne.
Very nice.
I am Adelai Niska.
You have seen Crow.
He loves to stand
at the door to say, "Boo!"
We got word you might
have a job for us.
Yes!
Yes, an exciting job.
A train...
has, uh, something I need.
You have worked
a train before?
We did a few.
Are you going to ask me what it is I need?
As a rule, no.
Yes. Good.
You have reputation.
"Malcolm Reynolds gets it done"
is the talk.
Well, glad to hear that.
You know what is reputation?
Is people talking.
Is gossip. Uh--
I also have reputation.
Not so pleasant, I think you know. Crow.
Now, for you, my reputation
is not from gossip.
You see this man?
Uh, he does not do the job.
I show you
what I do with him,
and now my reputation
for you is fact.
Is solid.
You do the train job
for me.
Then you are solid.
No more gossip.
Right.
Ooh. You do not like
I kill this man.
Hmm. Oh, no.
I'm sure he was a...
very bad person.
My wife's nephew.
At dinner
I'm getting earful.
There is
no way out of that.
So--Oh!
The train job.
Come in.
Here, in fifth car,
two boxes.
Alliance goods. You don't mind taking
from Alliance, I think.
From your reputation?
You get on train at Hancock,
headed for Paradiso.
You take boxes off
before you reach Paradiso...
and deliver to Crow... here.
Half money now. Crow give you other half
at rendezvous point.
Anything goes wrong, then your reputation
only gossip...
and things between us...
not so solid.
Yes?
How long till we hit Paradiso?
Another 20 minutes.
We should be in the foothills
in five.
Let's get to work.
He's a psycho, you know.
Niska.
He's not the first psycho
to hire us.
Nor the last. You think that's
a commentary on us?
I just have an image in my head of a guy
hanging from the ceiling.
I got an image of it not being me.
Let's do the thing.
Hi.
Shepherd.
Good day.
(sighs)
So... how do you
think it's going?
The caper?
Mal knows what he's doing.
How long
have you known him?
I've been on this ship
eight months now.
I'm not certain I'll ever actually know
the captain.
(chuckles)
I'm surprised a respectable Companion
would sail with this crew.
It's not always this sort of work.
They take the jobs they can get,
even legitimate ones.
But the further you get away from the
central planets, the harder things are,
so this is part of it.
I wish I could help.
I mean,
I don't wanna help--
Not help help, but--
Not with the thieving, but--
I do feel awfully useless.
You could always pray
they make it back safely.
I don't think the captain
would much like me praying for him.
Don't tell him.
I never do.
Go on straight through.
WOMAN:
Keep moving.
Sir, is there some information
we might maybe be lacking...
as to why there's an entire fed squad
sitting on this train?
Doesn't concern us.
It kind of concerns me.
I mean, they're not
protecting the goods.
If they were, they wouldn't be
letting people past them.
You don't think that changes
the situation a bit?
I surely do.
Makes it more fun.
Sir, I think you have a problem with
your brain being missing.
Come on.
We stick to the plan.
We get the goods. We're back on Serenity
before the train even reaches Paradiso.
Only now we do it under the noses
of 20 trained Alliance feds.
And that makes them look
all manner of stupid.
Hell, this job
I would pull for free.
Then can I have your share?
No.
If you die, can I have your share?
Yes.
Hey.
Oh.
Hey, Doctor.
You really should
just call me Simon.
Oh, I'll do that then.
So... what
are we doing?
Oh, crime.
Crime.
Good.
Okay. Crime.
It's a train heist.
See, we fly over the train car.
The captain and Zoe sneak in.
We lower Jayne
onto the car,
and they bundle up the booty,
and we haul 'em all back up.
Easy as lyin'.
So you've done this before.
(laughs) Hell, no.
But I think it's gonna work.
The captain (speaking Chinese)
when it comes to plans.
Uh, is--You know, is there anything I
can-- something I should be doing?
Staying the hell
out of everyone's way.
No call to be snappy, Jayne.
Are you about to jump onto
a moving train?
Captain ain't around. I'm in charge.
Since when?
Just 'cause Mal says you're medic don't
make you part of the crew.
You just play at figurin'
what's wrong...
with that moon-brained
sister of yours till we call for you.
Dong ma?
Right.
(motor whirring)
You shouldn't be
so rude to him.
Why? 'Cause he's all rich and "fancible"?
He's not rich.
The Alliance crashed his accounts
when he snuck out his sister.
Yeah, well, we could all be rich
if we handed her back.
You're not even
thinking that.
Mal is.
That's not funny.
JAYNE:
He ain't stupid.
Why would he take on trouble like those
two if there weren't no profit in it, hmm?
Captain's got a move he ain't made yet.
You'll see.
Time for some thrilling heroics.
Niska's sources
better be good.
Shining.
(grunting)
(groaning)
Find the cargo.
All hail
the great Alliance.
(grunts)
(weapon cocking)
Fifteen seconds.
(yells)
Go!
Go! Go now!
Come on.
(engines accelerating)
(murmuring)
(shouting, coughing)
Aaah! God!
Where are the others?
They shot my gorram leg!
Jayne.
Are they still on the train?
Are they gonna be okay?
FED: Everybody off!
(people chattering)
Come on, come on.
Everybody off!
This way.
FED:
Move it.
Our man
didn't get a look.
Well, geez. Can someone find out
what they took?
MAN: Randy!
Keep those people together!
Quiet 'em down!
It was the medicine, sir.
All of the supplies.
They stole
the gorram medicine?
We've been waitin'.
All of it?
WOMAN:
Every ounce.
(crying)
It's all right.
Oh, God help us.
Son of a bitch.
MAN: What's the fuss?
WOMAN: All-network alert. Cargo theft.
Medical shipment lifted off a train in the
Georgia system en route to Paradiso.
Six crates
of Pescaline "D".
Right. That'll get you a tidy fortune
on the black market.
Tag it received, bounce it back.
Locals can deal with it.
Sir, there is a regiment
holding in Paradiso.
They were on the train
headed to the installation.
Then get them back on the train
and get it moving.
Who's holding them there?
The sheriff requested a few
to help him investigate--
These are federal marshals,
not local narcotic hounds.
They've got
better things to do,
and so do we.
JAYNE:
Gorrammit, let's get us movin'!
SIMON: Now, I'm not--
I'm not finished.
Why you got us parked here?
This ain't the rendezvous spot.
It is now.
Niska's people are waitin'.
They're not partial to waitin'.
Let 'em read a magazine. We don't make the
sale until Mal and Zoe are back.
These are stone killers.
They ain't cuddly like me.
I'm not flying anywhere
without my wife.
She'll be okay.
She's with the captain.
There. You see?
Everybody wins. Aaah!
Doc, I need a pop to quiet this pain some!
(grunts)
All right, but what about
the authorities?
We're sitting here
with stolen Alliance goods.
Won't they be looking for us?
If they buzz this canyon, we'll
hear 'em before they see us.
I figure we're good for a--
RIVER: They won't stop.
They'll never stop.
They'll just keep coming
until they get back what you took.
Two by two.
Hands of blue.
How's about you shut that crazy mouth!
Is that a fun game?
Now, I'm in charge here,
and I'm tellin' you how it works.
We don't get the goods to Niska on time,
he'll make meat pies outta the lot of us!
I ain't walkin' into that.
This Adelai Niska
you're talkin' about?
Now, how would a shepherd
know a name like that?
As I've heard it,
he made a deal with the captain.
If the captain's not there
to finish it,
if Niska finds out
he's being held...
and may speak
as to who hired him,
I think we're better off
being a little late.
(people coughing)
This is a nightmare.
Nothing points to us yet, sir.
That ain't
what I'm talkin' about.
(wailing)
Whatever happens,
remember I love you.
Sir?
Because you're my wife.
Right... sir.
Honey.
Car three, row 12.
Mr. and Mrs. Raymond.
Can you tell us what's going on?
We've been here for so long.
Did someone on the train get killed?
No, no, no, no.
Nothin' like that. Uh--
Says there your fare's
paid for by a third party?
My uncle. It was
a wedding gift.
Wedding gift.
Spending your honeymoon
in Paradiso?
Actually, we're here
looking for work.
That right?
My uncle said...
he knew a Joey Bloggs out here,
said he might have an opening.
Thought we'd try our luck.
You a miner by trade?
Either of you?
No.
Not really.
Hmm.
Haven't seen many folk choose
this life weren't born to it.
Well, work is real scarce
for a couple just startin' out.
How come there's
so many sick here?
Bowden's malady.
Know what that is?
Affliction of the bone
and muscle. Degenerative.
Very.
Every planet that's been
terra-formed for human life...
has its own little quirks.
Turns out the, uh,
air down underground,
mixed up
with the ore processors--
Perfect recipe
for Bowden's.
Everybody gets it.
Miners, dumpers.
Hell, I got it. I ain't ever
set foot in a mine.
But it's treatable.
There's medicine.
Pescaline.
At least you can live like a person,
you get it regular,
but our shipment got stole
right off the train you was ridin' in.
Which is why you won't be
seein' a parade in town today.
Stolen.
Well, didn't I see
an entire regiment...
of fine, young Alliance federals
on the train?
You did.
Same regiment let their medicine get
swiped right outfrom under their noses,
then took off for their own camp without
so much as a whoopsy-daisy.
That sounds like
the Alliance.
Unite all the planets
under one rule...
so that everybody can be interfered with
or ignored equally.
Alliance ain't much use to us
out here on the border planets,
but... they ain't the ones
who stole the medicine.
I ever find
those people,
they ain't ever gonna see
the inside of a jail.
I'm just gonna
toss 'em in a mine,
let 'em breathe deep
for the rest of their lives.
Can't argue with that.
Hmm.
(groans)
You mind tellin' me, uh, when it was...
you last spoke to Joey Bloggs?
Never did myself.
Right. Your uncle.
Now, it was indicated to you
that, uh, Joey had an opening?
Any job would do.
That's funny your uncle never went to
mentioning the Bowden's problem,
or that Joey Bloggs...
ate his own gun
about eight months back.
Did he?
Yep.
Blew the back
of his head right off.
So... would his job
be open?
That's it!
We waited long enough.
Let's get this bird in the air.
No rutting way.
SIMON: You should sit down.
We can't leave the captain and Zoe.
They ain't comin', we can't walk in there
and get 'em, so they're done.
Let's fire it up.
What's going on?
Strap in. We're takin' off.
We're not.
Captain'd do the same if it were us.
Not in a million years!
Shut it.
Listen to me.
You know what the chain of command is?
It's a chain I go get and beat you with
till you understand who's in rutting
command here.
Now, we're finishing
this deal,
and then maybe, maybe we'll come back
for those morons,
got themselves caught.
You can't change that
by gettin' all... "bendy."
All what?
You got the--the light from the console...
to keep you--
lift you up.
(chuckles)
Oh, they shine like...
little angels.
Did he just go crazy
and fall asleep?
I told him
to sit down.
You doped him.
It was supposed to kick in
a good deal sooner.
I--I just didn't feel comfortable
with him in charge.
I hope that's all right.
So, how do we get the others?
Jayne was right about them
not making contact.
Chances are they got pinched
gettin' off that train.
We can't just waltz in
and pull 'em out.
Someone respectable enough
might be able to.
What the hell--
Don't you dare speak to me!
Sheriff, I want this man
bound by law at once.
That's assuming
he hasn't been already.
No one's been bound.
Not yet.
Thank God
you stopped them.
Did you honestly think you could access
my accounts and I wouldn't find you?
And, Zoe, what would your husband say
if he knew you were here?
I--I was weak.
So I take it
they ain't newlyweds.
(scoffs)
Hardly.
Malcolm's my indentured man
with three years left in his debt.
I imagine we'll have to add another six
months after this little adventure.
(murmuring)
Pardon them. Don't think a one of 'em's
ever seen a registered Companion before.
I apologize for my manner.
SHERIFF: Not a bit.
Should I contact my ship?
Do you need to hold them
very much longer?
Looks to me like
we're about done here.
We had some, uh,
unrelated trouble.
His story had kind of an odor to it.
Yes.
It's not the only thing
about him that does.
Thank you
very much, Sheriff.
Come along.
That's a hell of a lady.
(door closes)
Her files were all in order?
I ran 'em twice.
Huh. Let's get started
with the rest then.
Hey.
How'd it go?
She hit me.
We tried to get him into the infirmary.
He's just heavy.
Kept the engine running. We're good to go.
We're not going.
Not--What?
Not--Why?
We're bringing the cargo back.
What?
What do you mean, "back"?
I waited for you guys!
WASH: What are you talking about?
What about Niska?
Won't this put him in more or less
a killing mood?
There's others need this more.
Let's get it on the mule.
My shuttle's faster.
You risked enough flying in there once.
And I don't want to get slapped no more.
Far as Niska goes,
we'll explain to him...
the job went south
when we return the money.
You wanna explain,
now's your chance.
You didn't make
the rendezvous.
Ran into
a few complications.
You are thinking of taking
Mr. Niska's money...
and his property maybe.
Uh, interestingly, neither.
I don't understand.
Yeah. Look. Here's what it is.
Deal's off.
We changed our minds.
You entered into an arrangement
with Mr. Niska.
There is no mind changing.
I'm afraid that's where you're wrong.
We--We just--
We can't take this job.
So you just relax.
We'll get you the money Niska gave us,
you return it, and we'll call it even.
There is no even.
Is that right?
(gunshot)
(groaning)
Nice shot.
I was aimin' for his head.
We'll have to
drag 'em from here.
We can leave 'em
just off the street.
Notify the sheriff once we're in deep,
deep space.
Why not tell him
in person?
SHERIFF: Got word of a ship not far out.
Came lookin'.
Didn't expect
to find you comin' back.
to be comin'.
Nothin' missin'.
You were truthful back in town.
These are tough times.
A man can get a job.
He might not look too close
at what that job is.
But a man learns all the details
of a situation like ours,
well... then he has a choice.
I don't believe he does.
Let's get these crates back to town,
make ourselves useful.
(engines starting)
Now, this is all the money
Niska gave us in advance.
You bring it back to him. Tell him the job
didn't work out. (spits)
We're not thieves.
But we are thieves.
Point is, we're not taking what's his.
We'll stay out of his way
as best we can from here on in.
You explain that's best
for everyone. Okay?
Keep the money.
Use it to buy a funeral.
It doesn't matter where you go
or how far you fly.
I will hunt you down, and the last thing
you see will be my blade.
Darn.
Now this is all the money Niska gave us--
I get it. I'm good.
Best thing for everyone.
I'm right there with you.
You should've let me
do this sooner.
I've had plenty worse.
It's just--Ow!
Sorry.
Just be careful.
Pretty fast thinkin',
dopin' up Jayne.
Can't say you made
a lifetime friend.
I'll deal with him.
Yeah, I'm not
too worried about you.
How's your sister?
The same.
One moment she seems perfectly cogent,
the next,
she speaks nonsense.
SIMON: It's like a child.
So difficult to diagnose.
RIVER: Two by two.
I still don't know what the government
was trying to do with her.
Hands of blue. Two...
So I have no idea
by two.
if they succeeded.
Hands of blue.
Two by two.
Sorry to keep you waiting. There's always
one crisis--
We're not interested.
We're here about a theft.
The medicine.
On that planet.
Word came up that was returned.
We didn't fly...
86 million miles to track down a box
of Band-Aids, Colonel.
We're looking for a girl.
This girl.
Grr! Arrgh!