MAN:
Get your flame over to the right!
(indistinct shouting)
(gunfire continuing)
MAN: Sergeant, Command says air support is
holding till they can assess our status.
Our status is we need
some gorram air support.
Now get back online,
tell 'em to get in here.
WOMAN: That skiff is shredding us, sir.
MAN: They won't move without a
lieutenant's authorization code, sir.
SERGEANT: Here, here's your
code. You're Lieutenant Baker.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Now get me some air support!
Pull back just far enough
to wedge 'em in here.
Get your squad to high ground.
Start picking 'em off.
High ground is death
with that skiff in the air.
That's our problem.
Thanks for volunteering.
Bendis, give us some cover fire.
We're going duck hunting.
(explosion)
Just focus!
The Alliance said they were gonna
waltz through Serenity Valley
and we choked 'em with those words.
We've done the impossible
and that makes us mighty.
Just a little while longer--
our angels are gonna be
soaring overhead raining fire
on those arrogant cods, so you hold!
You hold! Go!
(explosion in distance)
Really think we can bring her down, sir?
You even need to ask?
Ready?
Always.
Bendis.
Bendis!
Rut it!
(grunts)
(gunfire continuing)
♪ ♪
(whirring)
Yeah! Yeah!
Zoe!
(indistinct shouting)
ZOE: Nice cover fire.
Did you see that?!
Green, what's our status on...
Zoe.
Hey...
listen to me.
Bendis, look at me!
Listen,
we're holding this valley no matter what.
We're gonna die.
We're not gonna die.
We can't die, Bendis And you know why?
Because we are so very pretty.
We are just too pretty
for God to let us die, huh?
Look at that chiseled jaw, huh?
Come on.
(roaring overhead)
Won't listen to me, listen to that.
Those are our angels
coming to blow the Alliance
to the hot place.
Zoe, tell the 82nd...
They're not coming.
Command says it's too hot.
They're pulling out.
We're to lay down arms.
But what's...
♪ ♪
MALCOLM:
The vault's sealed.
Okay, I'm gonna boil it.
Jayne,
give me the sticky.
(exhales)
Okay, we get the goods,
we're off this wreck and back
on the ship. No worries.
Everything looks good from here.
Yes.
This is a fertile land
and we will thrive.
We will rule over all this land
and we will call it
This Land.
I think we should call it Your Grave.
Ah...
Curse your sudden but inevitable betrayal.
(cackles)
Mine is an evil laugh.
Now die!
(growls)
Oh, no, God!
(growls) Oh, dear God in heaven.
(alarm starts beeping)
Oh, motherless son of a bi...
Full pressure--
the goods must be intact.
Okay... looking good.
WASH: Captain, we got incoming Alliance
cruiser bearing right down on us.
(speaking Chinese)
Ta ma de.
Have they spotted us?
I can't tell if...
Have they hailed us?
If they're here for the salvage,
we're humped.
ZOE: If they find us at all,
ZOE: Thieving ain't exactly...
JAYNE: I don't like this.
Wash, shut it down now--
everything but the air.
Kaylee. Kaylee!
Go to blackout.
We're being buzzed.
Shi, going dark.
Okay, now I can't get down.
ALLIANCE COMMANDER:
So what am I looking at?
It's a carrier, blew out
a few months back.
Lost all hands, but it was only run
by a skeleton crew anyway.
Damn shame.
No point in checking
for survivors?
MAL:
Wash, they slowing down?
That's a neg.
Doesn't look like
they're interested in us.
We should be eating wake
in a minute or two.
Sir, there is a reading on that thing.
Some residual heat.
Do a sweep.
(speaking Chinese):
Aiya! Huaile.
Captain, we're humped.
Prep the ship now.
We move these in, double time.
Kaylee, fire it up.
It's a transport ship,
Firefly class.
They still make those?
Illegal salvage.
Lowlife vultures picking
the flesh off the dead.
OFFICER: Should we deploy
gunships and bring her in?
Do it.
Cry, baby, cry.
Make your mother sigh.
Engaging the crybaby.
Captain, I am picking up a distress signal
13 clicks ahead from a...
Sounds like a personnel carrier.
Definitely a big ship, sir,
and she's without power.
Wash, we're on. Go.
Hang on, travelers.
Let's moon them.
They're rabbiting, sir.
Should we continue deployment?
Our gunships would never
get back to us in time.
All right, let's go help these people.
But put out a bulletin on the cortex
and flag Interpol:
A Firefly with possible
stolen goods onboard.
Maybe somebody'll step on those roaches.
WASH:
We look shiny, Captain.
They are not-- repeat--
not coming about.
Close one.
JAYNE: Any one you walk away from, right?
Long as we got the goods,
I call this a win.
Right.
We win.
♪ Take my love, take my land ♪
♪ Take me where I cannot stand ♪
♪ I don't care, I'm still free ♪
♪ You can't take the sky from me ♪
♪ Take me out to the black ♪
♪ Tell 'em I ain't coming back ♪
♪ Burn the land and boil the sea ♪
♪ You can't take the sky from me ♪
♪ Have no place I can be ♪
♪ Since I found serenity ♪
♪ But you can't take the sky from me. ♪
Well, there we are.
They're awfully pretty.
WASH:
I'd say worth a little risk.
JAYNE: Yeah, that's
pretty risky sitting you did there.
That's right, of course,
'cause they wouldn't arrest me
if we got boarded.
I'm just the pilot.
I can always say that
I was flying the ship by accident.
You know, they're pretty under...
(Chinese) Bizui.
Problem, sir?
Couldn't say.
But we'd best be getting rid of these
before we run into
another Alliance patrol.
What the hell they doing
this far out anyhow?
Shining the light of civilization.
How long till we reach Persephone?
Three, four hours.
Can we shave that?
We're down to the wire on fuel cells.
We run hot, we might not even make it.
Okay, play it as close as you can.
This catch is burning a hole in my hull.
Think that cruiser might've ID'd us?
Let's hope not.
Contact Badger,
tell him the job's done.
Don't go to mentioning
the cruiser, though.
Keep it simple.
Sir, we're sure
there's nothing wrong...
It's fine.
I just want to get paid.
All right, let's get
these crates stowed.
I don't want any tourists
stumbling over them.
We're taking on passengers
at Persephone?
Yeah, t\hat's the notion.
We could use a little respectability
on the way to Boros.
Not to mention
the money.
Pain in the ass.
No, it's shiny.
I like to meet
new people.
They've all got stories.
Captain, can you stop her
from being cheerful, please?
I don't believe that there's
a power in the 'verse
that can stop Kaylee from being cheerful.
Sometimes you just want to duct tape
her mouth and...
dump her in the hold for a month.
I love my captain.
I know something ain't right.
Sweetie, we're crooks.
If everything were
right we'd be in jail.
It's just that
the captain's so tense.
The man needs a break.
In fact, we could all
use a couple days' leave.
We still got to drop the goods.
And when we do
we'll fly off to Boros,
rich and prosperous.
Well, less poor,
but with enough to find
some sweet little getaway.
Oh, wouldn't mind
a real bath.
Yeah, and a meal that
included some form of food.
Just a couple of days,
lying around.
You with the bathing,
me with the watching
you bathe.
If the captain says
it's all right...
What if we just told Mal
we need a couple of days
instead of asking him?
He's the captain, Wash.
Right.
I'm just the husband.
Look, I'll ask him.
Don't forget to call him "sir."
He likes that.
MAL:
Who likes what?
It's nothing, sir.
Has the Ambassador
checked in yet?
WASH: No.
I think she had
a pretty full docket.
Well, after you talk to Badger,
let her know
we may be leaving
Persephone in a hurry.
Inara has our timetable.
She should be checking in.
I can tell her to cut it short,
meet us at the docks.
No, no. Don't want to get
in her way if we don't have to.
Somebody on this boat
has to make an honest living.
(panting)
Oh, my God.
INARA: Sihnon isn't that different
from this planet.
More crowded, obviously
and I guess more complicated.
The great city itself is...
Pictures can't capture it.
It's like an ocean of light.
Is that where you studied...
to be a Companion?
I was born there.
I can't imagine ever leaving.
INARA:
Well, I wanted to see the universe.
Do you really have to leave?
I mean...
I... my father is very influential.
We could... I could arrange
for you to be...
...experience has been more than...
it was very good.
Thank you.
The time went too quickly.
Well, your clock's probably
rigged to speed up
and cheat us out of our fun.
Serenity, this is Shuttle One.
What's your ETA?
Inara, hey.
We're touching down
at the Eavesdown docks
in about ten minutes.
I'll join you there. Thanks.
Looking forward to it.
We missed you out here.
Yeah, me, too.
(indistinct chatter)
♪ ♪
This shouldn't take too long.
Put us down for departure
in about three hours.
Grab any supplies
we're low on, fuel her up.
I'd sure love to find a brand-new
compression coil for the steamer.
Yes, and I'd like to be
the king of all Londinium
and wear a shiny hat.
Just get us some passengers.
Them as can pay, all right?
Compression coil busts were drifting...
Best not bust, then.
Zoe.
(Chinese) Zhu tamin
ya min.
Zhu yi.
We will.
(indistinct conversations)
Going on a trip, grandpa?
Need safe passage?
We're cheap.
We're cheap, we're
clean. The Brutus--
best ship in the 'verse.
What's your des, grandpa? Come on.
We're hitting the outer rings.
I never married.
What?
I'm not a grandpa.
Let me see your teeth.
Yes.
You're late.
You're lying.
What did you just say to me?
You're well aware we landed
two hours 'fore we planned to,
with all the goods you sent us after,
intact, ready to roll.
So your decision to get tetchy
and say we're late
means you're looking to put us
on the defensive right up front.
Which means something's gone wrong.
It didn't go wrong on our end,
so why don't we start again
with you telling us what's up?
You're later than I'd like.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
If you'd gotten here sooner
you might've beaten the bulletin
that came up saying
rogue vessel, classification "Firefly"
was spotted pulling illegal
salvage on a derelict transport.
Didn't ID us.
Doesn't lead to you.
No, it doesn't.
But a government stamp
on every molecule of the cargo
just maybe might.
Oh, you noticed that.
You were gonna hand over
imprinted goods
and just let me twist,
is that the case?
We didn't pick the cargo.
And I didn't flash my ass
at the gorram law.
There's no deal.
That ain't fair.
Crime and politics, little girl.
The situation is always fluid.
Only fluid I see here
is the puddle of piss
refusing to pay us our wage.
(weapons cocking)
It doesn't have to go this way.
You know you can still
unload those goods,
so I can't help thinking there's
something else at work here.
What were you in the war?
That big war you failed to win?
You were a sergeant, yeah?
Sergeant Malcolm Reynolds.
Balls and Bayonets Brigade.
Big, tough veteran.
Now you got yourself a ship
and you're a captain.
Only I think you're
still a sergeant, see?
Still a soldier.
Man of honor in a den of thieves.
Well, this is my gorram den
and I don't like the way
you look down on me.
I'm above you. Better than.
Businessman, see?
Roots in the community.
You're just a scavenger.
Well, maybe I'm not
a fancy gentleman
like you, with your...
very fine hat,
but I do business.
We're here for business.
Try one of the border planets.
They're a lot more
desperate there.
Of course
they might kill you,
but you stay here
and I just know the Alliance
will track you down.
I have that feeling.
Wheel never
stops turning, Badger.
That only matters
to the people on the rim.
You're gonna come with us.
Excuse me?
You like ships.
You don't seem to be looking
at the destinations.
What you care about is the ships and
mine's the nicest.
She don't look like much.
Well, she'll fool you.
You ever sail in a Firefly?
Long before you were crawling.
Not a nought-three, though.
Didn't have the extenders,
tended to shake.
So, uh,
how come you don't
care where you're going?
'Cause how you get there
is the worthier part.
Are you a missionary?
I guess.
I'm a Shepherd
from the Southdown Abbey.
Book.
I'm called Book.
Been out of the world for a spell.
Like to walk it a while,
maybe bring the Word
to them as need it told.
Well, I'm Kaylee.
And this here's Serenity.
And she's the smoothest ride
from here to Boros
for anyone can pay.
Can you pay, or...
Well, I got a little cash and, uh...
Ooh, grandpa.
I never married.
I don't understand why we didn't
leave that son of a bitch
in a pool of his own blood.
We'd be dead.
Can't get paid if you're dead.
Can't get paid if you crawl away
like a bitty little bug, neither.
I got a share in this job.
Ten percent of nothing is--
let me do the math here--
nothing into nothing,
carry the nothing...
So we find a buyer on Boros.
There's got to be...
Boros is too big.
It's crawling with Alliance.
They could just be waiting for us.
You really think Badger'll
sell us out to the Feds?
If he hasn't already.
Alliance catches us
with government goods,
we'll lose the ship.
That's never gonna happen.
Sir, we could just dump the cargo.
JAYNE:
No rutting way.
We ain't had a job in weeks.
I didn't sign on with this crew
to take in the sights.
We need coin.
Jayne.
Your mouth is talking.
You might want to look to that.
I'm ready to stop talking...
You're right, though.
Last two jobs we
had were weak tea.
We got nothing saved
and taking on passengers
won't help near enough.
We don't get paid for this cargo,
we don't have enough money
to fuel the ship,
let alone keep her in repair.
She'll be dead in the water.
So we do like Badger said--
the border planets?
I'm thinking Whitefall,
maybe talk to Patience.
Sir, we don't want to deal
with Patience again.
Why not?
She shot you.
Well, yeah, she did a bit.
Still...
So we find somebody else.
Horowitz.
He can't afford it.
Holden boys.
They wouldn't touch it.
You want me to go through the list?
Capshaws are brain-blown.
Gruviek's dead.
He's dead?
Town got hit by Reavers.
Burned it right down.
I ain't going anywhere
near Reaver territory.
Them people ain't human.
Whitefall is the safest
and the closest.
Been a long time
since Patience shot me
and that was due to a perfectly
legitimate conflict of interest.
I got no grudge.
She owns half
that damn moon now.
She can afford what we got
and she might just need it.
I still don't think
the old lady's the way.
MAL:
I'm not saying it won't be tricky,
but we got no kind of choice.
Welcome aboard,
Mr...
Dobson.
Got to keep our heads down,
do the job,
pray there ain't no more surprises.
Please be careful with that.
Mal, this is Simon.
Simon, this is our captain.
Captain Reynolds.
Welcome aboard.
That's all we got?
Now we have a boatload of citizens
right on top of our stolen cargo.
That's a fun mix.
Ain't no way in the 'verse they
could find that compartment.
Even if...
Even if they were looking for it.
Why not?
'Cause.
Ah, yeah.
This is gonna go great.
If anyone gets nosy, you know,
just... shoot 'em.
Shoot 'em?
Politely.
WASH:
Inara, just in time.
Let me guess.
We're in a hurry?
Looks like.
Starboard hatch green
for docking.
Locked in five, four...
WASH:
The Ambassador has returned.
We got a full house, Captain.
Kaylee, I'm locking it up.
All aboard.
♪ ♪
MAL: Meals are taken up here
in the dining area.
Kitchen's pretty much
self-explanatory.
You're welcome to eat
what there is anytime.
What there is is
pretty standard fare, I guess.
Protein in all the colors of the rainbow.
We do have sit-down meals
next one being at about 1800.
I think Shepherd Book has offered
to help me prepare something.
You're a shepherd?
Thought the outfit gave it away.
Is it a problem?
Of course not.
It's no problem
'cause it's not.
No.
As I said,
you're welcome to visit
the dining area anytime.
Apart from that I have to ask you
to stay in the passenger dorm
while we're in the air.
The bridge, engine room, cargo bay
they're all off-limits without an escort.
Some of my personal effects
are in the cargo bay.
I figure you all got luggage
you're gonna need to get into.
As soon as we're done here
we'll be happy to fetch them with you.
Now I have to tell you all one other thing
and I apologize in advance
for the inconvenience.
Unfortunately, we've been
ordered by the Alliance
to drop some medical supplies
off on Whitefall.
It's the fourth moon on Athens.
It's a little out of our way
but we should have you on Boros
no more than a day off schedule.
What medical supplies?
I honestly didn't ask.
Probably plasma, insulin.
Whatever they ain't got enough of
on the border moons.
Alliance says jump.
All right.
Zoe, you want to take them
to the cargo bay?
Yes, sir.
Anything else you need, just ask.
We, uh, live to serve.
Did you send word to Patience?
Ain't heard back yet.
Didn't she shoot you one time?
Everybody's making a fuss.
Oops, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
(gasps)
Ah, the Ambassador graces us
with her presence.
Hello, Mal.
I see we have some new faces.
Hey, you.
MAL:
Ambassador.
this is Shepherd Book.
I'd have to say this is the first time
we've had a preacher onboard.
Well, I wasn't expecting to see
a state official, either.
Ambassador.
(Mal laughs)
I'm missing something funny.
Not so funny.
"Ambassador's" Mal's way...
She's a whore, Shepherd.
The term is "companion."
I always get those mixed up.
How's business?
None of yours.
She is pretty much our ambassador.
There's plenty of planets
that won't let you dock
without a decent companion onboard.
This isn't a problem
for you, is it, Shepherd?
Well, I... I certainly...
It's all right.
I mostly keep to myself...
when I'm not whoring.
Don't you want to meet
the rest of the bunch?
Why don't you make sure
they want to meet me first?
So, how many fell
madly in love with you
and wanted to take you
away from all this?
Just the one.
I think I'm slipping.
♪ ♪
I'm starved.
This is incredible.
It is great.
It's not much.
I had a garden at the abbey.
Thought I should bring what I could.
It's very kind of you
to share with all of us.
Well, it won't last.
And they're not the same
when they're frozen.
The important thing is the spices.
A man can live on packaged food
from here till Judgment Day
if he's got enough rosemary.
Captain, you mind if I say grace?
Only if you say it out loud.
So, does it happen a lot?
Government commandeering your ship
telling you where to go?
That's what governments are for--
get in a man's way.
Well, it's good
if the supplies are needed.
We're just happy to be doing good works.
I hear a lot of the border moons
are in bad shape--
plagues and famine.
Well, some of it's exaggerated,
and some of it ain't.
All of those moons
just like the central planets
they're as close to Earth-That-Was
as we can make them.
Gravity, atmosphere and such, but...
Once they're terraformed
they'll dump settlers on there
with nothing but blankets,
hatchets maybe a herd.
Some of them make it.
Some of them...
Then I guess it's good we're healthy.
You're a doctor, right?
Oh, uh...
yes, I was a trauma surgeon
on Osiris in Capital City.
Long way from here.
You seem so young to be a doctor.
Yeah. You're pretty young
to be a ship's mechanic.
I know how.
Machines just got workings
and they talk to me.
That's a rare gift.
Well, not like being a doctor.
Helping fix people, that's important.
Little Kaylee here just wishes
you was a gynecologist.
(Jayne laughing)
Jayne...
you'll keep a civil tongue
in that mouth or I will sew it shut.
Is there an understanding between us?
You don't pay me to talk pretty.
Just because Kaylee gets lubed up
over some big city dandy...
Walk away from this table right now.
What... do you pay him for?
What?
I was just wondering
what his job is... on the ship.
Public relations.
♪ ♪
(knocking)
(Chinese)
Qing jin.
If I'm intruding...
Not at all.
I expected you.
Couldn't really say the same.
So, would you like to lecture me
on the wickedness of my ways?
I brought you some supper,
but...
if you'd prefer a lecture
I've a few very catchy ones prepped.
"Sin and Hellfire"...
one has lepers.
I think I'll pass.
(chuckles)
But thank you for this.
The Captain said you might like it.
I was surprised at his concern.
For a lowly whore?
It was unjust of him to say that.
Believe me, I've called him worse.
Anyway... I suspect he has more interest
in making you uncomfortable than me.
He's not wildly interested
in ingratiating himself with anyone
yet he seems very protective of his crew.
It's odd.
Why are you so fascinated by him?
Because he's something of a mystery.
Why are you?
Because so few men are.
(flushing)
WASH:
Mal, you might want to get up here.
What is it?
Signal.
Somebody went on the cortex
hailed the nearest
Alliance cruiser.
Tell me you scrambled it.
All to hell.
But I don't know
how much got through.
Alliance got a pin in us for sure.
(Chinese) Ni ta ma de.
Tianxia suoyoude ren.
Dou gaisi.
We got a mole onboard.
Forget your toothpaste?
(groans)
Are you out of your mind?
Just about.
What'd you tell them?
Tell who?
I got exactly no time for games.
What do they know?
You're a lunatic.
And you're a gorram Fed.
BOOK: Hate to say it, Captain...
...but you've got the wrong man.
Son of a bitch.
Drop that firearm,
Captain Reynolds.
(sighs)
(scoffs):
This is not my best day ever.
Simon Tam, you are bound
by law to stand down.
What?
The doctor? Oh.
Hey, is there... is there a reward?
Get on the ground.
Get on the ground!
Lawman, you are making a mistake.
I think you best get
on the ground, son.
The man seems a mite twitchy.
BOOK: I think everybody could stand
to calm down a bit.
This isn't your business, Shepherd.
The boy's not
going anywhere, lawman.
As I understand it,
it's pretty cold outside.
MAL: Not to worry.
We can put Lord Fauntleroy here in
one of the passenger cells.
He won't make a peep...
Get the hell away from that weapon!
You think I'm a complete backbirth?
You're carrying a fugitive
across interplanetary borders
and you think I actually believe
you're bringing medical supplies
to Whitefall?
As far as I care
everyone on this ship is culpable.
Well, now...
that has an effect on the landscape.
Please, we're very close
to true stupidity here.
I got a cruiser en route for
intercept, so talk all you want.
You got about 20 minutes.
Might have less than that.
Yeah, threaten me.
For God's sake...
You think I wouldn't shoot a Shepherd?
Back off!
MAL: Just take the kid!
Get your hands off...
Stand the hell down!
BOOK: Everybody, just stop it.
Why's every...
BOOK: Stop it.
What...
Kaylee!
(groaning)
How do you feel?
A little odd.
Out of the way.
You're not killing this man.
Not right away...
He's no threat.
What?
Oh, well...
That ain't hardly a mosquito bite.
Big mosquito ...
Move.
Not gonna happen.
I ain't joking with you, preacher.
ZOE: Jayne!
Just tie him up. Do it!
SIMON: Can you move your feet?
Kaylee, stay with me.
Stay with me.
Can you move your feet?
Are you asking me to dance?
She's going into shock.
Kaylee, meimei,
you have to focus.
The gun, Shepherd.
Please.
(screaming)
The infirmary working?
Yeah, we got it stocked.
WASH (over comm):
Captain, we've been hailed by a Cruiser.
Ordered to stay on course
and dock for prisoner transfer.
(sighs weakly)
Change course.
Run.
Hell with you.
You brought this down on us.
I'm dumping you with the law.
Mal...
She's dying.
You're not gonna let her.
Yes, I am.
No, you can't.
No way the Feds'll let us walk.
Then we dump him in the shuttle
and leave him for them.
Everybody's so mad.
It's okay, baby.
Do you know what a stomach
wound does to a person?
I surely do.
Then you know how crucial
the next few minutes are.
You let her die,
you'll never make it to the Feds.
She'll still be dead.
You rich kids--
you think your lives are
the only thing that matters.
What'd you do?
Kill your folks for the family fortune?
I don't kill people.
Then do your job!
Turn the ship around!
Enough!
Mal, do it.
Don't you ever tell me
what to do on my...
(sobbing)
Zoe, change course.
Help me get her up.
Wash...
change course and go for hard burn.
We're running.
♪ ♪
You have an extractor?
Got a laser saw.
No, that's not good enough.
Uh, my room, red bag.
This is over, you and me are
gonna have a personal chat.
Won't that be fun.
Dope her.
(breathing shallowly)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
I can't do any more
until she stabilizes.
Will she?
I can't say yet.
I want to know what's going on here.
Well, then why don't we find out?
What are you...
No!
Stay away from that!
Aah!
(groaning)
Where's the Fed?
Secured.
Shepherd's with him.
Seems to think he's not safe
alone with me.
No!
Well, let's see what a man
like you would kill for.
SIMON: No, don't!
Huh.
I need to check her vitals.
Oh, is that what they call it?
She's not supposed to wake up
for another week. The shock...
The shock of what-- waking up?
Finding out she'd been sold
to some borderworld baron?
Or... I'm sorry.
Was this one for you?
Is it true love? Because
you do seem a little...
(screaming)
Oh!
(panting)
(whimpering)
River..
Hey... No,
it's okay.
It's okay,
It's okay.
I'm here.
(whispers):
Simon?
Simon, they... they talk to me.
They want me to, they want me to talk...
No, no, they're-they're gone.
They're gone, they're gone.
I don't want...
They're gone.
We're safe now.
We're safe.
I'm here.
(sobbing)
(whispering): Come on.
What the hell is this?
This is my sister.
SIMON: I am very smart.
I went to the best
Medicad on Osiris.
Top three percent of my class.
Finished my internship
in eight months.
Gifted is the term.
So, when I tell you
that my little sister
makes me look like
an idiot child...
I want you to understand
my full meaning.
River was more than gifted.
She...
She was a gift.
And everything she did--
you know, music, math,
theoretical physics,
even... even dance-- there was
nothing that didn't
come as naturally to her
as breathing does to us.
And she could be
a real... brat about it, too.
I mean, she used to...
There was, uh, a school--
a, uh... a government-
sponsored academy.
We had never even heard of it,
but it had
the most exciting program.
The most
challenging.
We could have
sent her anywhere.
We had the
money, but...
she wanted to go.
She wanted to learn.
She was 14.
I...
I got a few letters at first
and then I didn't
hear for months.
Finally, I got a letter
that made no sense.
She... she talked about things
that never happened--
jokes that-that we never...
It was a code.
It just said...
They're hurting us.
Get me out.
ZOE:
How'd you do it?
Money.
And-and luck.
For two years, I
couldn't get near her.
Then I was contacted
by some men--
some underground movement.
They-they said
that she was in danger, that...
that the government was...
playing with her brain.
If I funded them
they could sneak her out in cryo,
get her to Persephone,
and from there,
I could take her...
wherever.
Will she be all right?
I don't know if she'll be all right.
I don't know
what they did to her.
Or why.
I...
I just have to keep her safe.
That's... quite a story, son.
Yeah, it's a tale of woe.
Very stirring,
but in the meantime,
you've heaped a world of trouble
on me and mine.
I never thought...
No, I don't imagine you thought.
In consequence of which we got a
kidnapped Federal officer on board,
we got the Alliance
hard on our trail,
and Kaylee...
How much does the Alliance know?
I can't say.
I killed the message pretty quick,
so they may
just have had our position.
Or they might have
personal profiles
on each and
every one of us.
Till that Fed wakes up,
we won't know.
So what do we do?
The job.
We finish the job.
I got word from Patience,
she's waiting for us.
We circle round to
Whitefall,
make the deal, get out.
Keep flying.
What about us?
Kaylee comes through,
you and your sister get off at Whitefall.
And if she doesn't come through?
Then you're getting off
a mite sooner.
That'd be murder.
Boy made a decision.
He didn't shoot her.
No, but somebody else on this boat did
and I'm scratching my head as to
why we ain't dealt with him.
ZOE:
Kill a Fed?
Can you think of a stupider thing to do?
He can ID us all.
You want to throw me
out the airlock, fine,
but River is not a part of this.
Can we maybe vote on the whole
murdering people issue?
We don't vote on my ship,
because my ship is not
the rutting town hall.
This is insanity.
I happen to think we're a ways
beyond that now, sir.
Come on, we're gonna
talk this through, yeah?
I'll not sit by while
there's killing here.
JAYNE: Captain's got a mean streak
you best watch yourself...
(speaking Chinese):  Nimen de bizui!
The way it is is the way it is.
We got to deal
with what's in front of us.
Mal, you know those two wouldn't survive
a day in Whitefall anyway.
You throw them out,
I'm leaving, too.
It might be best you do.
You ain't a part
of this business.
What business
is that, exactly?
I'm a dead man.
I can't know?
Is it gold?
Drugs?
Pirate treasure?
What is it that makes you
so afraid of the Alliance?
You don't want to go
down this road with me, boy.
Oh, you're not afraid
of them?
Well, I already know you'd sell me out
to them for a pat on the head.
Hell, you should probably
be working for them--
you certainly fit
the prof...
Saw that coming.
Now, I'm in a tricky position.
I guess you know.
Got me a boatload
of terribly strange folk
making my life
a little more interesting
than I generally like.
Chief among them,
an Alliance mole.
Likes to shoot at girls
when he's nervous.
Now, I got to know
how close the Alliance is--
exactly how much
you told them before
Wash scrambled your call.
So, I've given Jayne here
the job of finding out.
He was not
specific as to how.
(whispers): Now, you're only
gonna scare him.
Pain is scary.
Just do it right.
Do you have any idea
how much trouble you're in?
Gee, I never been in trouble
with the law before.
No, not like this, you haven't.
You think this
is just a smuggling rap?
The package
that boy is carrying...
It's a girl.
She's cute, too.
'Cept I don't think
she's all there, you know?
Course, not all
of her has to be.
That girl
is a precious commodity.
They'll come
after her.
Long after you bury me,
they'll be coming.
Oh...
(chuckles)
I'm not gonna
kill you, Dobson.
What's your first name?
Laurence.
Laurence. No, I'm just
gonna cut on you
till you tell me
how much they know.
They know everything. They know
every name, every record.
They know how many...
nose hairs you've got.
Ah, see, now, they don't
know a damn thing.
It's all over your face,
I ain't even...
I was gonna get me a ear, too.
Aren't you an
officer of the law?
Well, don't they teach you
how to withstand interrogation?
You can't even
tell a damn lie.
Okay. I can see
you're not an idiot.
Wish I could say the same,
Laurence, but...
this is disappointing as hell.
Let me speak a language
you will understand.
Money.
This girl is worth a lot of money.
I mean, a lot.
Now, you kill me,
there's nothing.
But...
if you help me out...
you'll have enough
to buy your own ship.
A better one
than this piece of crap.
Does helping you out
mean turning on the Captain?
Yes, it does.
How the hell'd they find us?
I thought you said
we could get around them.
It's not Alliance.
You sure?
Yeah, it's a
smaller vessel.
Commercial?
Uh, yeah.
I read it
as an older model Trans-U.
I didn't think
Trans-U's still operated.
They don't.
Give me a visual.
They're still too far out to...
Get me something.
I'm picking up
a lot of radiation.
They're operating without
core containment.
That's... (speaks Chinese)
That's suicide.
Reavers.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, oh, God.
MAL (over intercom):
This is the captain.
We're passing another ship.
Looks to be Reavers.
From the size,
probably a raiding party.
It could be they're headed
somewhere particular.
Could be they already hit
someone and they're full up,
so everyone stay calm.
We try to run, they'll have
to chase us-- it's their way.
We're holding course.
We should be passing
them in a minute.
So we'll see
what they do.
Zoe, you come on up
to the bridge.
Wait, I-I don't
understand.
You never
heard of Reavers?
Well, campfire stories of
men gone savage on the edge
of space, killing...
They're not stories.
What happens if they board us?
If they take the ship,
they'll rape us to death,
eat our flesh,
and sew our skins
into their clothing.
And if we're very, very lucky,
they'll do it in that order.
(exhales heavily)
There's a magnetic grappler.
They get ahold of us
with that...
Just tell me if they alter course.
They're holding course.
(sighs)
I guess
they weren't hungry.
Didn't expect to see them here.
They're pushing out
further every year, too.
Getting awful crowded in my sky.
KAYLEE:
Hey, Captain.
Hey.
Hey, little Kaylee,
what's the news?
I'm... shiny... Captain.
A-okay.
And I can't feel much
below my belly, though.
It's getting cold.
Well, you just got to rest.
Something's gonna break down
on this boat real soon.
Who else I got to fix it?
Well, don't you
worry none.
Doc fixed me up pretty.
He's nice.
Don't go working too hard
(mixed Chinese/English):
on that crush, xiao meimei.
Doc won't be with us for long.
You're nice, too.
No, I'm not.
I'm a mean old man.
He wasn't gonna let me die.
He was just trying...
It's nobody's fault.
Okay? Just
promise me
you'll remember that.
I'll keep it in mind.
You are a nice man, Captain.
You always looking after us.
You just
got to have
faith in people.
Ah, she is a real
beauty, isn't she?
It's just
a standard Companion
immunization package.
Thank you.
I'm not sure if it'll help in this...
It won't hurt.
The supplies down there
are pretty rudimentary.
Is there anything else
I can do?
I don't think so.
But I appreciate it.
Kaylee's very dear.
To all of us.
I... I'm sorry.
For my part
in what happened.
See... I've-I've never...
I mean, I-I
don't know how to...
You're lost in the woods.
We all are.
Even the captain.
The only difference
is he likes it that way.
No, the only difference is
the woods are the only place
I can see a clear path.
What's your business here?
It's my business.
The usual.
I gave the boy a free thrust
since he's not long for this world.
What are you doing
in my shuttle?
It's my shuttle. You rent it.
Then when I'm behind on the
rent, you can enter unasked.
Thought you were leaving anyhow.
Well, I guess
that depends on you.
You'll ruin her,
too, you know.
This is the thing I see
you're uncomprehending on.
Everyone on this ship--
even a legitimate
businesswoman like her--
their lives can be snatched away
because of that Fed.
You got a solution for that?
You got a way around?
I don't.
Comes time, someone's
gonna have to deal with him.
That should be you.
But I don't think
you got the guts.
And I know you
don't have the time.
What do you mean?
Kaylee's dead.
♪ ♪
(panting)
That man's psychotic.
You are psychotic.
No, but you should've
seen his face. Oh...
I'm a bad man.
And Kaylee's
really okay?
Yeah.
Tell the truth, I didn't
expect her to heal this quick.
Doctor knows his trade,
I'll give him that.
(beeping)
Being hailed.
That'd be Patience.
We're close enough for a vid.
Put her up.
Malcolm Reynolds.
Hello, Patience.
I have to say, I didn't look to be hearing
from you anytime soon.
Well, we may not have parted
on the best of terms.
I realize certain words
were exchanged.
Also, certain... bullets.
But that's air through
the engine. That's past.
We're business people.
Besides, your days of fighting
over salvage rights
are long behind you, what
I hear. What are you, mayor now?
Just about.
You telling the truth
about that cargo?
'Cause your asking price is a bit
too reasonable for that much treasure.
It's imprinted-- Alliance--
hence the discount.
Oh, government goods, huh?
That doesn't work for you, no harm.
Just thought you could use...
Alliance don't scare me.
Just collating data,
as they say.
I like that
you're up-front about it.
We can deal.
I'll upload coordinates for a rendezvous
point outside of town.
See you in the world.
(clicks off)
I believe that woman's
planning to shoot me again.
She meant to pay you, she'd
a'haggled you down some.
Just a little effort
to hide it would've been...
Sir, we don't have
to deal with her.
Yes, we do.
JAYNE: Here's a little concept
I've been working on:
uh, why don't we
shoot her first?
It is her turn.
That doesn't get us
what we need either.
There's moons on this belt
we ain't seen.
We could try our luck...
Our luck?
You notice anything particular
about our luck these past few days?
Any kind of pattern?
You depend on luck,
you end up on the drift--
no fuel,
no prospects...
and begging for
Alliance make-work.
And towed out to the scrapbelt.
That ain't us.
Not ever.
Patience has got the money to pay.
And she will,
one way or another.
There's obstacles in our path
and we're gonna deal
with 'em, one by one.
MAL:
We'll get through this.
We will.
♪ ♪
Nice place
for an ambush.
That it is.
Hey, here you go.
I buried 'em good.
The equipment's
back on the boat.
Testing.
Testing. Captain,
can you hear me?
I'm standing right here.
You're coming through
good and loud.
'Cause I'm standing
right here.
Yeah, well... But
the transmitter's...
All right, Patience is gonna
figure we buried the cargo
which means putting us to our
ease before there's any action.
She'll come at us from the east.
Talk the location out of us.
She'll have the coin
to show us first.
We get it, give the location.
Snipers hit us from there
and there.
You figure they're in place yet?
Should be.
Feel like taking a walk
around the park?
Sure you don't just want to
piss yourself and back down
like you did
with Badger?
Walk soft.
I want Patience thinking
they're still in place.
Don't kill anyone
if you don't have to.
We're here to
make a deal.
Don't think it's
a good spot, sir.
She still has
the advantage over us.
Everyone always does.
That's what makes us special.
(whispers):
Lawman, it's Shepherd Book.
I believe you're
in more danger than...
(grunts)
Ah.
(chuckles)
Mal.
How you doing, boy?
Walking and talking.
Is that Zoe?
You still sailing
with this old bum?
Awful lot of men
to haul three crates.
Yeah, well, I
couldn't be sure
my Mal here wouldn't be looking
for some kind of payback.
You understand.
We're just
on the job, Patience.
Not interested in surprises.
(thump)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
I don't see my cargo anywhere.
And you're not gonna
till I'm holding 200 in platinum.
Oh, come on, Reynolds.
I'm supposed to take it on faith
that you got the goods?
MAL:
It's pure, Patience.
Genuine A-grade
foodstuffs.
Protein, vitamins,
immunization supplements.
One of those'll feed
a family for a month.
Longer, if they don't like
their kids too well.
Yup. That's the stuff.
So where's the rest?
Simon?
What's wrong, sweetie?
Look at you,
all woke up.
Oh, I'm sorry about what
happened before,
but make so much as a sound,
the next one goes through your throat.
(whimpering)
MAL:
Then east half a mile,
bottom of the first hill,
you'll see where it's been dug.
I reckon I will.
Well, then.
Yup.
I'd appreciate it
if y'all turn around and ride out first.
Well, you see, there's
a kind of hitch.
We both made out on this deal.
Don't complicate things.
I got a rule:
I never let go of money
I don't have to.
Which is maybe why I'm
running this little world
and you're still
on that dinky old boat,
sniffing for scraps.
Got the money back.
There's no need
for killing.
We're just gonna
walk away, sir?
Guess that's up
to Patience here.
Could be messy.
Not terribly.
(chuckling): Mal, you just
ain't very bright, are you?
That's quite a rifle.
Boy must be your best shot
to carry that.
PATIENCE:
He's called Two-Fry.
Always makes it
quick and clean.
Two-Fry.
Nice hat.
(men shouting)
You should think
about asking the captain
to drop you somewhere else.
Whitefall ain't exactly
civilization,
in the strictest sense.
You don't have to
worry about me.
Oh, Zoe's out on a deal,
I always worry.
So, it's not out of my way.
KAYLEE: He took her.
He took River.
(beeping)
Oh, don't.
Don't you dare.
MAN:
Watch behind you!
(grunts)
(shouting)
(whirring)
(grunts)
(speaking Chinese):
Hun dan!
(shouting)
Watch yourself! Go!
Hyah!
(grunts)
(screams)
Zoe?
(groans)
Armor's dented.
Well, you were right
about this being a bad idea.
Thanks for saying, sir.
Mal, don't you take another step!
(neighs)
Now, I did a job.
I got nothing but trouble
since I did it,
not to mention
more than a few unkind words
as regard to my character,
so let me make this abundantly clear.
I do the job...
and then I get paid.
Go run your little world.
JAYNE:
Mal!
It's Wash!
We got a ship coming in!
They followed us!
The gorram Reavers followed us!
(grunting)
No, don't!
Don't move.
WASH:
Reavers!
Reavers incoming
and headed straight for us.
We are in the air
in one minute.
I guess they got hungry again.
You gonna do that?
You gonna kill a lawman
in cold blood?
I know what you did
for your sister.
I understand-- it doesn't
make you a killer.
I don't want
to hurt anybody.
I have a job
to do.
To uphold the law-- that's
what we're talking about here.
Come on, come on.
Where the hell are you guys?!
There's nowhere you can take her
the law won't find.
Nobody is going
to hurt her.
Unless you hurt me.
No, I said!
I said don't-don't move.
It's your call.
I'm not playing anymore.
Anybody makes so much...
(gunshot)
MAL:
Jayne.
Wash, we're on.
(whimpering)
How close are they?
About 20 seconds
from spitting distance.
Well, lose 'em.
Give me rear vid.
ZOE:
(Chinese): Ai ya.
(chinese): Women wanle.
How close they need to be
to fire those grapples?
JAYNE: Come on, Wash,
you dumbass, dodge 'em.
If everyone could just
be quiet a moment...
I need Kaylee
in the engine room, please.
ZOE: Can she even---
Get her in there now.
I want you to get
in your shuttle.
Get the civilians
and be ready to go.
We can't just
leave you here.
I thought
that was the plan.
Mal, don't do this.
We get boarded,
you take off,
head for town.
We might be able to stop them
from following you.
They'll kill you.
Inara...
go.
How we doing?
I don't mean to alarm anybody...
but I think...
we're being followed.
You three
come with me.
I think I can
help Kaylee out.
Should I...
Take her.
Keep her safe.
Can't keep this up.
They get a bead,
they're gonna
lock us down.
Kaylee, how we doing?
We're gonna need
a little push here.
You want me to go for full burn?
Not just yet.
But set it up.
You know where
the press regulator is?
Head of the class.
(coughing)
We're ready for full burn
on your mark.
Full burn in atmo? That won't
cause a blowback, burn us out?
Even if it doesn't they can push
just as hard, keep right on us.
Wash...
you got to give me an Ivan.
I'll see what I can do.
Kaylee,
how would you feel about
pulling a crazy Ivan?
Always wanted to try one.
Jayne, open the port
jet control.
Cut the hydraulics.
Where the hell is---
Look, look,
Look where I'm pointing.
Okay.
Now, it's real simple.
They're on us.
Kaylee.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
KAYLEE:
Okay.
Everybody hold on to something.
Here's something you can't do.
Now!
(grunting)
I knew I hired you
for something.
(whoops)
(whooping continuing)
Ain't no way they can
come around in time to follow us now.
We're good, people.
We're out of the woods.
(whoops)
Yeah!
That's my girl.
That's my good girl.
We should have just enough left
in us to hit a fuel station.
We'll need to do
some patching up.
I hope we got paid today.
We did.
ZOE: Sir?
I'd like you to take the helm, please.
I need this man
to tear all my clothes off.
Work, work, work...
(sighs)
You should really have the
young doctor look at this.
It's not so bad.
Well, I'm sure
you'll be fine.
I didn't say that.
Is this what life is...
out here?
Sometimes.
I've been out
of the abbey two days.
I've beaten a lawman senseless,
fallen in with criminals.
I've watched the captain shoot
the man I swore to protect.
And I'm not even sure
if I think he was wrong.
Shepherd...
I believe I just...
I think I'm on the wrong ship.
Maybe.
Or maybe
you're exactly where you ought to be.
The shot I gave you
will help you sleep.
I slept for so long.
Just a little while.
And then we'll find a place.
We'll find a safe place.
I didn't think
you'd come for me.
Well, you're a dummy.
JAYNE:
The girl's a problem.
The lawman said they'd
keep looking for her.
Something about her brain
being all special.
Important to the
Alliance brass.
Sooner we dump them two,
the better.
I suppose so.
Funny how the lawman
got out of his room.
You having tied him
up so well and all.
I didn't have nothing
to do with that.
Anyhow, it all
turned out just fine.
Buzzards are the only ones
that are gonna find him.
But he did try
to make a deal with you, right?
How come you didn't
turn on me, Jayne?
Money wasn't good enough.
What happens when it is?
Well...
that'll be an interesting day.
Imagine it will.
You need me
to look at that?
Just a graze.
So, where do you plan
on dumping us?
There's places
you might be safe.
You want the truth, though,
you're probably safer on the move.
And we never stop moving.
I'm confused.
No, wait. I...
I think maybe you're confused.
It may have become
apparent to you that
the ship could use a medic.
You ain't weak.
Don't know how bright you are
top three percent, but...
you ain't weak,
and that's not nothing.
You live by my rule,
you keep your sister
from doing anything crazy,
you could maybe
find a place here.
Till you find a better.
Uh... I'm trying to put this
as delicately as I can.
How do I know you won't
kill me in my sleep?
You don't know me, son, so
let me explain this
to you once.
If I ever kill you,
you'll be awake,
you'll be facing me
and you'll be armed.
Are you always this sentimental?
Had a good day.
You had
the Alliance on you--
criminals and savages.
Half the people on the ship
have been shot or wounded,
including yourself.
And you're harboring
known fugitives.
We're still flying.
That's not much.
It's enough.
Grr. Argh.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH