BOOK: After the Earth was used up,
we found a new solar system
and hundreds of new Earths
were terraformed and colonized.
The Central Planets formed the Alliance...
and decided all the planets had to join
under their rule.
There was some disagreement
on that point.
After the war, many of the independents
who had fought and lost...
drifted to the edges of the system,
far from Alliance control.
Out here, people struggled to get by with
the most basic technologies.
A ship would bring you work.
A gun would help you keep it.
A captain's goal was simple--
Find a crew.
Find a job. Keep flying.
Come on, admit it.
It's true.
No, I won't,
because it's not.
I use swear words, like anybody else.
Oh, really?
See, I've never heard you. So when is
it that you do all this cussing?
After I go to bed, or--
I swear...
when it's appropriate.
Simon, the whole point of swearing is that
it ain't appropriate.
Hey, there, Inara.
Heading off for some
glamorous romance?
(chuckling)
Let's hope so. See you two tomorrow.
Don't let Mal get you into too much
trouble while I'm gone.
Bye now.
Have good sex.
What?
(clattering)
Oh!
Now, this would be a perfect
time for a swear word.
What... happened
in here?
Needed to find some tape.
So you had to tear my infirmary apart?
Apparently.
My God. You're like
a trained ape.
Without the training.
Jayne.
I told you we're setting down on the
Canton factory settlement
on Higgins's Moon.
Yep. That you did.
Canton don't allow
guns in their town.
Yes, sir. That's why I ain't
strappin' one to my hip.
No. That's why you ain't
strapping one anywhere.
Oh, listen, Mal, I was in Canton
a few years back.
I might have made me
a few enemies thereabouts.
Enemies? You?
No! How can it be?
Just don't like the idea of goin' in there
empty-handed, is all.
Why are you still arguing
what's been decided?
Okay, Inara. We're atmospheric.
You are good to go.
Thanks, Wash.
Disengaging
in three,
two, one.
Canton really stinks.
That's what makes it such a great drop
point.
No one comes here that doesn't have to.
I vote we do this job
really, really fast.
Kessler's our man. He's holding the goods
we're to deliver.
We go in, make contact--
Easy-peasy.
Zoe, you're holdin' down
the fort.
Call ahead to Bernoulli,
let him know he'll have his merchandise
end of the week.
Don't I usually stay with the ship?
I outrank you.
Have fun.
So, this is a place
where they--
they make mud.
Yep. Clay, really. You'd be surprised how
many things it ends up in.
Serenity's got more than a few ceramic
parts in her.
Really?
Yeah.
Huh.
Captain, don't you think
Simon should come with us?
What? K-Kaylee, I don't think
it's a good--
BOOK: Go on, boy.
See the sights.
I can watch over your sister.
I believe...
we've been developing a rapport.
I-I don't know. River--
Go on.
I'm a shepherd after all. I should be able
to keep my eye on a flock of one.
We're not going that far, Doctor, and you
might maybe make yourself useful.
Come again?
The management here don't take too kindly
to sightseers, which is why we're...
posin' as buyers.
There ain't a one of us looks the part
more than the good doctor.
I mean, the pretty fits,
soft hands--definitely
a moneyed individual.
All rich and lily-white, pasty all over--
All right!
Fine. I'll go.
Just stop describing me.
You're the boss,
boss.
He's the boss now? Day keeps gettin'
better and better.
Area's employees only.
Best be getting back to the landing unless
you have business here.
Yes.
Yes, I--I'm looking...
to buy some mud.
Well, then. (chuckles)
You've come to the right place.
Course, we can handle
any volume here.
We've over 2,000 workers,
mostly indentured.
We pay them next to nothing.
That way we can pass the savings directly
on to you, the customer.
SIMON:
Savings.
Uh, excellent.
That's, uh--
Because as I said before, I'm gonna--I'm
gonna be needing quite a bit of it.
I, uh--
I'm a buyer.
The best of its kind.
Uh, we mix it, we brick it raw
right here on the premises.
Uh, you add the right catalyst,
you kiln it proper,
this stuff's 10 times stronger than steel
at half the weight.
Yes.
I've heard great, uh--
What happened to Simon?
Who is this diabolical master of disguise?
He's learning.
It's, uh--
MAL: Excuse me, boss.
I'm sure the foreman has
things need attending.
Why don't we wander a bit,
take a look at the operation?
Then you can figure on whether
we get an account here.
Yes?
Yes. Yes, we'll uh--
We'll-We'll wander a bit.
Fair enough. Come and see me
when you're through.
All right. Let's head toward the town,
find our man Kessler, get this job done.
Boy's gonna get us killed.
Let's just do this deal and get.
His disguise isn't
half as funny as yours.
Who are you supposed to be, anyway?
You haven't been here in years Jayne.
You really think
you need that getup?
No one's gonna
remember you.
I think it's possible
they might.
Son of a bitch!
♪ Take my love, take my land ♪
♪ Take me where
I cannot stand ♪
♪ I don't care,
I'm still free ♪
♪ You can't take
the sky from me ♪
♪ Take me out to the black ♪
♪ Tell 'em I ain't
comin' back ♪
♪ Burn the land
and boil the sea ♪
♪ You can't take
the sky from me ♪
♪ There's no place I can be ♪
♪ Since I found serenity ♪
♪ But you can't take
the sky from me ♪♪
Jayne?
Yeah?
You wanna tell me
how come there's a statue...
of you here lookin' at me
like I owe him somethin'?
Wishin' I could, Captain.
No, seriously, Jayne. You wanna tell me
Look, Mal,
I got no ruttin' idea.
I was here a few years back,
like I said,
pulled a second story, stole a lot of
scratch
from the magistrate up on the hill,
but things went...
way south.
I had to hightail it.
They don't...
put you on a pedestal
in the town square for that.
Yeah, 'cept I'm looking at some very
compelling evidence says they do.
This must be
what going mad feels like.
I think they
captured him, though.
You know,
captured his essence.
Looks sorta angry,
don't he?
That's kinda what I meant.
(whistle blowing)
FOREMAN: Shift four on duty.
Shift four on duty.
Uh, hey.
I got an idea.
Instead of us hangin' around playin' art
critic till I get pinched by the man,
how's about we move away
from this eerie-ass piece of work...
and get along with our increasingly
eerie-assed day, how's that?
I don't know.
This here's a spectacle might warrant
a moment's consideration.
Everywhere I go,
his eyes keep following me.
Come on, gorram it.
We got a job.
Let's go do it,
get the hell outta here.
I crossed the magistrate of this company
town. Understand?
He ain't exactly
a forgivin' sort of guy.
Magistrate Higgins, I may presume.
You may.
But I only make the people I own
use my title.
Mr. Higgins... (kisses hand)
will do fine.
And you can call me
Inara, Mr. Higgins.
It's a rare pleasure,
your visit to my little moon.
Journey wasn't too taxing?
Not at all.
I'm refreshed and ready.
Shall we begin at, say, 7:30?
Perfect.
I have a feeling it will take all your art
to deal with this particular problem.
Every problem, Mr. Higgins,
is an opportunity in disguise.
What are we up to, sweetheart?
Fixing your Bible.
I, um--What?
Your Bible's broken.
Contradictions, false logistics--
Doesn't make sense.
No, no.
Y-You can't--
So we'll integrate non-progressional
evolution
theory with God's creation of Eden.
Eleven inherent metaphoric
parallels already there.
Eleven.
Important number. Prime number. One goes
into the house of 11, 11 times...
but always comes out one.
Noah's ark is a problem.
Really?
We'll have to call it "early quantum state
phenomenon."
Only way to fit 5,000 species of mammal
on the same boat.
Give me that.
River, you don't...
fix the Bible.
It's broken.
It doesn't make sense.
It's not about...
making sense.
It's about believing
in something.
And letting that belief be real enough
to change your life.
It's about faith.
You don't fix faith, River.
It fixes you.
(paper tears)
You hang on
to those, then.
(people chattering)
(strumming guitar chord)
JAYNE: Can't be a statue of me.
No reason for it.
Flies in the face
of every kind of sense.
Won't argue with that.
(spitting)
(speaking Chinese)
Mmm. They call it mudder's milk.
(gags)
All the protein, vitamins and carbs of
your grandma's best turkey dinner,
plus 15 percent alcohol.
It's horrific.
SIMON: Worked for the Egyptians.
What's that?
The ancient Egyptians.
Back on Earth-that-was.
Not so different from the ancestral form
of beer
they fed the slaves to build pyramids.
It's liquid bread.
It kept them from starving...
and knocked them out at night, so they
wouldn't be inclined to insurrection.
Wow. Simon, that was
so... historical.
Now, what's a gussied-up fella like
you doing in a place like this?
Shake your head, boy.
Your eyes are stuck.
Git!
(gasps)
You wouldn't be looking for Kessler?
Just havin' a brew.
I knew a Kessler.
Knew?
He was a good
middleman.
Low-profile.
Didn't filch.
Last week, the factory foreman
and his prod crew...
heard he was movin'
contraband through town.
Gave him a peck of trouble for it.
What kind of peck was that?
The kind where they hacked off
his hands and feet with a machete,
rolled him into the bog.
They peck pretty hard around here.
Listen. My client off-world
is waiting for his delivery.
If the goods are gone--
Not to worry.
Your man's merchandise
is here, safe in Kessler's hiding place.
We just gotta figure out
how to get it across town...
without being seen by the foreman
and his prods.
I advise we all just
lay low for a moment.
MAN: ♪ Jayne ♪
(Jayne mutters in Chinese)
♪ The man they call Jayne ♪
(people whooping, cheering)
♪ He robbed from the rich
and he gave to the poor ♪
♪ Stood up to the man
and he gave him what for ♪
♪ Our love for him now
ain't hard to explain ♪
♪ The hero of Canton
The man they call Jayne ♪
♪ Now, Jayne saw
the mudders' backs breakin' ♪
♪ He saw the mudders' laments ♪
♪ And he saw
the magistrate takin' ♪
♪ Every dollar
and leavin' five cents ♪
♪ So he said You can't do that
to my people ♪
Uh, Jayne?
Yeah, Mal?
You got any light you'd like to shed
on this development?
♪ Stole everything
Boss Higgins had to steal ♪
No, Mal.
No, this must be what going mad
feels like.
♪ He stood up to the man
and he gave him what for ♪
♪ Our love for him now
ain't hard to explain ♪
♪ The hero of Canton
The man they call Jayne ♪
♪ Now, here is what
separates heroes ♪
♪ From common folk
like you and I ♪
♪ The man they call Jayne
he turned 'round his plane ♪
♪ And let that money hit sky ♪
Oh, begorram,
that's where that cash went.
I stole that money from Higgins
like the song says.
Lifted me one of his hovercraft,
but I got tagged by anti-aircraft,
started losin' altitude, had to dump them
strongboxes...
stay airborne.
Sixty thousand,
untraceable,
and I drop it right square
in the middle of mud farmer central.
We got to go to the crappy town
where I'm a hero.
♪ The man they call Jayne ♪♪
(whooping, cheering)
Hello?
In here, River.
Um--
I'm--I tore these
out of your symbol,
and they turned into paper,
but I want to
put them back, so--
Sorry. What's that?
(screaming)
River! River, come back!
(screaming continues)
Preacher, what the hell
did you--Whoa.
Captain, now they're
off the subject of me,
shouldn't we be gettin'
the hell out of here?
I'd say that's a reasonable request,
given the circumstances.
Ruttin' mudders.
(people chattering)
MAN: There he is.
(all cheering)
Jayne! Jayne! Jayne!
(chanting continues)
Give me some milk.
Don't you understand?
He's come back!
It's Jayne!
What the--
Hero of Canton won't be drinkin'
that (Chinese).
He drinks the best whiskey
in the house!
(all cheering)
What the hell's goin' on? Is this how
people lay low where you're from?
Not generally, no.
Listen, friend.
I came here to make sure
a deal went down solid.
Not to get chopped up by the Canton prod
crew and fed to the bog.
I understand
your concerns, friend.
This here's all part
of our new plan.
(cheering continues)
Captain, how exactly is this part of--
Still working the details.
(door opens)
Inara, allow me to introduce
my son, Fess Higgins.
Hello, Fess. Mr. Higgins,
this shuttle is a place of union.
I'm sure you can appreciate--
What is this?
I brought you here to bed my son,
not throw him a tea party.
Sir, a Companion greeting ceremony is a
ritual with centuries of--
My son is 26 years old,
and he ain't yet a man.
Twenty-six. And since he
can't find a willing woman--
Mr. Higgins, you're not allowed here.
What?
As I said, this room is
a consecrated place of union.
Only your son belongs here.
Well, I'm--
Now, why don't you go on
and let us begin our work?
Now listen here, young lady--
Good night, Mr. Higgins.
Well, that's a bit
more peaceful.
Will you sit?
To Jayne!
ALL: To Jayne!
To me!
Woo-woo-woo-woo!
To the mudders!
(all cheering)
(yelling in Chinese)
(drunkenly)
You know, I've saved lives.
Dozens.
Maybe hundreds.
I--I reattached
a girl's leg.
Her whole leg. She named her hamster
after me.
I got a hamster.
He drops a box of money--
he gets a town.
(drunkenly)
Hamsters is nice.
To Jayne. The...
box-dropping,
man-ape-gone-wrong thing.
You know,
you are pretty funny.
And you're pretty...
pretty.
What did you just say?
I just said that you're pretty.
Even when you're covered
in engine grease, you're--
No, especially, especially when you're
covered in engine grease.
It's time to get out of this nuthouse. I
got some plannin' to work out.
Now, Captain? Things are goin' so well.
I suppose.
Jayne's certainly feeling
better about life, but--
I said, things
are going well.
Oh. Well.
Well, I tell you what.
Jayne is stuck here
with his adoring masses.
Why don't you and Simon hang around and
keep an eye on him for me?
RIVER: They say the snow on the roof
is too heavy.
They say the ceiling will cave in. His
brains are in terrible danger.
River?
Please, why don't you come on out?
No!
I can't.
Too much hair.
Is--Is that it?
Hell, yes, Preacher.
If I didn't have stuff to get done,
I'd be in there with her.
It's the rules of my order.
Like the book, it symbolizes--
Uh-huh. River, honey, he's putting the
hair away now.
Doesn't matter.
It'll still be there.
Waiting.
Honey, we're home!
Where've you guys been?
Mal, Bernoulli's chomping at the bit.
Says he wants
his merchandise yesterday.
We got a few wrinkles
to work out on a deal.
Did you know that Jayne is
a bona fide folk hero?
Got a song and everything.
(speaking Chinese)
You've been drinking, husband.
That he has.
Don't make it any
less the case.
Are you telling me that Jayne--
It's true.
True enough we can
use it anyways.
We talked a few pillars of the mudder
community into having a little...
Jayne Day celebration
in town square tomorrow.
(snickering)
It should buy us enough of a distraction
to get the stolen goods out...
from under the foreman
and his crew of prods.
You're really gonna have to
start again. Jayne's a what?
This whole thing--
Uh, it--
It is embarrassing.
My father's right again, I guess. And to
have to bring you here--
Your father isn't right, Fess. It's not
embarrassing to be a virgin.
It's simply one's
state of being.
As far as
bringing me here--
Companions choose the people
they're to be with very carefully.
For example,
if your father had asked me to come here
for him,
I wouldn't have.
Really?
Really, Fess.
But you're different
from him.
The more you accept that,
the stronger you'll become.
So the magistrate, he let you folks
keep all that cash?
He did. And it pained him,
that's for dead sure.
When he found out, he sent his prods in
to take it back from us,
but the workers resisted.
Fought the law, huh?
If the mudders are together on a thing,
there's too many of us to be put down.
So in the end,
he just called it a bonus.
That's one hell of a bonus.
And then, when we put that
statue of you in town square,
he rolled in,
wanted to tear it down,
but the whole town
rioted.
You guys had a riot?
On account of me?
My very own riot?
I can't believe
you're back.
How could I stay away?
Hey.
Magistrate Higgins.
My son's out there.
I pray to God
losin' his cherry.
There's a problem
in Worker Town, sir.
Jayne Cobb's
come back.
(knocking)
(man groaning)
Evening, Stitch.
What do you want with me?
Nothin'. You've done your
time. You've paid your debt.
It's time you were
on your way.
(grunting)
Here. I believe these
were your personal effects.
(grunting)
You keep me in that box four years,
and you give me
a loaded gun?
You got the urge
to use it, no doubt.
But I'm not the one that brought you in
on that robbery.
I'm not the one who partnered up with you,
then turned on you
when his plan went south.
How high up was that shuttle when he
pushed you out? Thirty feet?
Jayne Cobb cost you
four years of your life,
plus a perfectly good
eyeball.
And here's the poetical portion--
He's back in town.
This very day.
Best of luck
in your new life.
Hey, Captain... Captain!
Hey... Mal.
Mal, I, uh--uh--
No, n-nothing happened.
No, there was, uh-- There was--
There was some drinking,
but, uh, we
certainly didn't--
I would never--
Not with Kaylee.
What do you mean, not with me?
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Where's my hero?
♪ My love for me now
Ain't hard to explain ♪
♪ The hero of Canton
The man they call me ♪
Eggs. The living legend
needs eggs.
Or maybe another milk.
No. The livin' legend needs to come with
us. He's got a little appearance to make.
He does?
That's right.
This job here's gone
way past long enough.
Well, you go on now. I got me important
hero-type stuff to do.
Where are you goin'?
I'm goin' with you.
Mmm, I don't think so.
No, maybe you ought to stay here.
It's about the time for a civilized person
to have his breakfast.
That's the sort of thing would be
appropriate, don't you think?
(sighs)
Excuse me. Could I, uh--
Could I see a menu?
MAN:
A what?
You're very quiet.
I'm sorry.
I just--
I just thought I'd feel...
different... after.
Aren't I supposed to be
a man now?
A man is just a boy who's old enough
to ask that question.
Our time together,
it's a ritual,
a symbol.
It means something
to your father.
I hope it was not entirely forgettable
for you.
Oh, no. It was--
But it doesn't make you a man.
You do that yourself.
(knocking)
HIGGINS: Fess! Fess Higgins!
Get out here!
So, that's where the little Jayne
celebration we got planned comes in.
Should give us enough time
to get the goods back on Serenity.
I don't know.
You think we should be using my fame
to hoodwink folks?
You better laugh when you say that.
No, really, Mal.
I mean, maybe there's something
to this.
The mudders--
I think I really made
a difference in their lives.
You know--
me, Jayne Cobb.
I know your name, jackass.
You know they threw a riot on my account?
MAL: A riot?
Morning, kids.
Is that Jayne? Is that really him?
Wash, pinch me.
I must be dreaming.
Aw, hell, I'll pinch ya.
Just get on over
to town square, Jayne.
Your fans are waitin'.
ZOE: Do you really think we can get this
stuff across town without being noticed?
MAL: Got to find it first.
Here we go.
Let's get it
dug up.
A criminal hearing?
Yeah, my father's ordered me to attend.
You see, there's this man--
Well, it happened when
I was growing up here.
He stole a ton of money from my dad and
gave it to the poor,
to my father's workers.
He's become kind of a folk hero in Canton.
Go on.
Well, he's back. Apparently, he landed
here yesterday.
Yesterday?
Oh, no.
I-I know this man.
He's--
He just has this idiotic sense of
nobility, you know?
He can never just
let things go.
He thinks he's this
hard-hearted criminal,
and he can be unrelenting,
but there's a side
to him that's just so--
You mean,
you actually know Jayne?
Jayne? Jayne Cobb? You're talking about
Jayne Cobb?
Yes. Jayne Cobb,
the hero of Canton.
The only person I ever saw
who stood up to my father.
(stammering)
My dad had him traced back
to his ship.
He had port control put a land-lock on it.
Jayne'll get back
and find out that he's grounded.
I sort of hate the idea
of his getting caught.
Yes, that would be bad.
(clears throat)
Uh, could I just get the...
check, please?
Heard tell you run
with Jayne Cobb.
Excuse me?
You're gonna take me to that dirty,
lowdown shingle of a man.
Listen, sir,
I don't know who--
"Sir"? Look at me,
you pantywaist idjit.
I just spent the last four years steamin'
in a hot box,
and you're "sirrin'" me?
Folks say you're
part of Jayne's team, so--
Where is that
no-good reptile hidin' hisself?
Tell me, boy, or I'll cut off every last
bit of them good looks.
Oh, not done yet,
young'un.
That's gonna
cost you an eye.
(people chanting)
Jayne! Jayne! Jayne! Jayne! Jayne! Jayne!
Come on. Come on!
(chanting continues)
WASH: They love their boy.
MAL:Just drive by nice and slow.
Come on, sir. Let's just get--
The magistrate says no.
We hold position.
Understand me?
Zoe, pack down
the cargo.
Wash, you heat up
Serenity.
We're blowin' this mess
inside half an hour.
Already there.
Let's go get
our wayward babes.
Jayne! Jayne! Jayne! Jayne! Jayne!
Jayne! Jayne! Jayne! Jayne!
Speech! Speech! Speech!
Um--
(people shouting)
I'm no good with words.
Don't--Don't use 'em much myself.
(people chuckling)
But I want to thank you all for bein'
here and, uh, thinkin' so much of me.
Uh--
Far as I see it,
you people been given the shortest end
of the stick...
ever been offered a human soul
in this crap-heel 'verse.
But you took that end,
and you--
well, you took it.
(all murmuring agreement)
And that's--
Well, I guess
that's somethin'.
(cheering)
Wow.
That didn't sound
half bad.
I'm shocked
my own self.
(people screaming)
Stitch Hessian.
(chuckling)
Well, hey, there,
Jayne.
Thought I'd make you watch while I
butcher me one of your boys.
He ain't a-one of mine.
Where you been hidin'?
You gone got yourself
lookin' mighty hideous.
(chuckles)
Oh-ho.
Yeah.
Now Jayne gets his.
Honey.
Kaylee?
So what's this about a hero of Canton?
Was I hearin' that right?
Four years of lock-down
plays tricks on the ear.
I ain't a hero,
Stitch.
Just a workin' stiff
like you.
Oh-ho.
(chuckling)
Yep, he's right.
Jayne is.
Fact, we used to work together,
he and I.
(trigger cocks)
(people gasping)
Now, why don't you just let
old Stitch speak his piece?
Go on, then.
Whole lot of money in a magistrate's safe,
weren't there, Jayne?
Got away clean too.
But then our plane
took a hit, and we're goin' down.
We dumped the fuel reserve, dumped the
life support.
Hell, we even dumped the seats.
And there's Jayne,
the money and me.
And there was no way he was gonna drop
that money.
He did. He dropped it
on the mudders.
By accident, you inbred dung head.
He tossed me out first.
For six months we run together.
He turned me out before I could scream.
You'd have done the same.
No. Never.
You protect the man you're with.
You watch his back.
Everybody knows that.
Well, except
the hero of Canton.
You gonna talk me to death, buddy?
Is that the plan?
Mm, this is the plan.
Yaah!
Get up.
Get up, you stupid
piece of--
What'd you do that for? What's wrong
with you? Didn't you hear a word he said?
All of you!
You think there's someone
just gonna drop money on ya?
Money they could use?
Well, there ain't
people like that.
There's just people like me.
Wash, we're on. Get us the hell off
of this mud ball.
WASH: Uh, yeah.
I'm, uh, workin' on it.
(buzzer buzzing)
(speaking Chinese)
Hello, Wash.
Has there been a problem with takeoff?
Is there a problem?
(bell dings)
(engine powering up)
No. We're fine.
You did what?
I sent an override
to port control,
lifted the land-lock
on Serenity.
I oughta wipe that smile off your head.
How dare you defy me, you--
You wanted to make a man
out of me, Dad.
I guess it worked.
Just keep walkin',
preacher man.
KAYLEE:
You gotta be steely.
You can't be lettin' men
stomp on you so much.
It wasn't exactly
a plan.
You ain't weak.
You couldn't
beat him back?
Or would that
not be appropriate?
You're never letting go
of that, are you?
Well, you confound me some,
is all.
I mean, you like me well enough,
and we get along, and--
And then you go all stiff.
I--I'm not, um--
I didn't--
See? You're doin' it
right now.
What's so damn important
about bein' proper?
It don't mean nothin'
out here in the black.
It means more out here.
It's all I have.
I mean, my way
of being... polite...
or however it's--
Well, it's the only way
I have of showing you that I like you.
I'm showing respect.
So, when we made love
last night--
When we what?
You really are
such an easy mark.
Don't make no sense.
What--
Why the hell'd that mudder have to go
and do that for, Mal--
jumpin' in front
of the shotgun blast?
Hell, there weren't a one of 'em
understood what happened out there.
They're probably sticking
that statue right back up.
Most like.
I don't know why
that eats at me so.
It's my estimation that...
every man ever got a statue made of him
was one kind of a son of a bitch or
another.
Ain't about you, Jayne.
It's about what they need.
Don't make no sense.
Grr! Arrgh!