[upbeat music]
Miss!
So close...yet so far away.
Now if I sink this, I win,
proving contrary to what
science fiction movies claim,
humans rule robots.
I can see the future,
so I know you will miss.
Can you really see the future?
Or was that just lame trash talk?
I can see the future.
You'll be 6 feet tall,
standing on a 2-foot chair.
Just for that,
I'm using my lucky ball
and making this putt,
and I'm doing it with style.
Master Richie, the hole is right here.
Give it a minute.
Look at that, a hole in one.
Master Richie, you are a cheater.
I believe the correct term is "winner."
Once again proving that humans
are superior to robots.
Fine, enjoy your little victory.
You may have won the battle,
but I will win the war.
War?
What war?
I've said too much.
Richie, we have massive problems!
Are you talking about
what Irona just said?
Because I'm a little nervous too.
No, your bank balance
plummeted a million dollars
in the last ten minutes.
That must be a mistake.
I don't make mistakes
when it comes to money.
Women, social cues, yes.
Money, never.
So are you saying some lowlife scum
hacked into my account
and is cleaning me out?
It's Darcy, but I wouldn't use
such polite, gentle words to describe her.
If you give me the okay,
I got a guy who could
make her disappear.
Murray!
The guy's just a travel agent.
I was thinking we could
book her for a month
in a youth hostel in Turkmenistan.
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
What's up?
T-Nice is up in this mini mall unit.
Hey, Darcy, I assume
you saw the bus stop bench ads
and showed up for
my milk shake release party.
Um, no, actually I was walking by,
and noticed an unusually short line,
so I stopped in.
Where is everyone?
None of my friends are here?
None of my family are here?
None of the people I paid
to fill the room are here?
Well, that's awesome
you're getting a shake,
but I thought they only
named them after celebrities.
That's what they told me too,
before my six-month
letter-writing campaign.
Well, I want to be the first to order one.
I don't see the Tahj Stokes.
It must be under "T-Nice."
Nope.
In third grade, a couple of
kids called me Tahj Barrage.
Is it under that?
I don't see it.
Bulldozah's Son?!
Low cal?
No one's gonna order this.
The manager's going to fix this
or receive another sternly worded letter.
Darcy, are you out of your mind?
Do you realize how much
you're costing Richie?
Hold on, Murray.
You don't have to panic about everything.
Just take a deep breath
and let Darcy explain
before flying off the handle.
I just wanted to taste
all billion varieties
of milk shakes this place serves.
So I ordered one of each.
You are aware they offer free samples.
Yeah,
but my best friend is a trillionaire.
Why would I accept charity?
Feel free to fly off the handle.
You have completely lost it this time!
This is unforgiveable! You are always--
[cha-ching]
Hey, where do you think
you're going, young lady?
I have a date.
[laughs]
Nice try.
But you're gonna need
a better excuse than that
to sneak out to some study session.
[doorbell chimes]
See? I really have a date.
Later.
Wait, wait, wait, I have to meet this guy.
I might not approve of him.
Oh, I'm sure you'll approve of him.
I'm just worried
he won't approve of me
after he meets you.
Then we agree to agree.
Dad, this is Camden.
Camden, this may or may not be my father.
Mr. Rich, it is a pleasure to meet you.
[chuckles]
Please, call me "Cliff."
Or "Barry." I always liked that name.
Okay, time to get going, Camden.
Before we depart,
I presumed you wouldn't
allow your daughter
to go out with a boy with whom
you were not acquainted.
So I brought a copy of my resume
for your review.
Just to assuage
any lingering reservations.
Ah, no pictures?
I'll allow you a minute to peruse that
while I call my grandmother.
Every night I sing Amazing Grace
to her before bed.
Okay, Dad, I'll be back by 10:00.
I love you. Bye.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
you're not going anywhere.
I'm sorry, but this guy
doesn't impress me one bit.
What? Why not? He's an angel.
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
He even has the voice of one.
Sure, he's polite and smart and charming,
but he doesn't seem fun.
Dad, Camden's totally fun.
When we met at the beach,
he was correcting kids' sand castles
to make sure they were architecturally
and historically correct.
That's where I know him from.
That guy caved in my moat.
So about my date--
You're not going.
He may have destroyed my moat,
but he's not destroying my family.
Darcy, you have
a serious spending problem.
And likely a very serious
cholesterol problem.
Great news.
By washing dishes,
I was able to shave 14 bucks off the bill.
Murray, you don't have
to clean dishes for pennies.
Actually, I took these pennies
from the take-a-penny, leave-a-penny bowl
down at the convenience store.
Wow, you are literally a penny pincher.
Darcy, don't call him names,
no matter how accurate they may be.
At least I'm not the one
flushing Richie's money down the toilet.
What was I supposed to do?
He was out of toilet paper!
You really did that?
Spendthrift!
Tightwad!
That's enough.
If I wanted to be around
name calling and negativity,
I'd spend time with Harper. Guys--
Is this going to take long?
My break is over,
and Gus is expecting me
back in the kitchen.
Guys, you're making me sick
with your fighting.
You guys need to come to a middle ground
when it comes to money.
So for the good of our friendship,
Darcy, you will go the next month
without spending a dime.
- No!
- Yes!
And Murray, you will go the next month
spending a million dollars a day.
- No!
- Yes!
I guess that doesn't help me.
It just felt right
to celebrate your suffering.
Hey, Richie, I have to say
you forcing me
to spend that million dollars
did put a little pep in my step.
Wow, it's great to see you
without your eye twitching
and your forehead all sweaty.
So what'd you spend the money on?
Stocks and bonds
that have returned a profit
of $2 million!
Can I get a Jim Cramer "boo-ya!"
Murray, the point of this
was not to make more money.
[laughs]
Oh, dear Richie,
the point of everything in life
is to make more money.
That's it!
From this moment forward,
not a dollar can go
towards an investment.
I want you spending senselessly,
stuff like cars, trips to space,
robots.
Oh, because I am nothing
but a senseless purchase to you?
No, no, I didn't mean it like that.
Right, you meant "senseless purchase"
in a polite, respectful way.
Richie, you can't do this to me.
It's for your own good.
I'm sorry to be so hard on you,
but you're gonna have to suffer through
spending a million dollars a day.
But it could break me.
Like the time security
escorted me out of my stockbroker's office
and told me to spend
Christmas with my family.
Hey, Harper, you still upset about Camden?
You're being so unfair.
He's perfect.
It's just that he uses all those big words
he probably doesn't know the meaning of.
He's so hoity-toity.
Is that the right word?
I don't even know what it means.
Congrats, Dad,
you finally used it correctly.
Now would you mind
celebrating in another room?
'Cause I'm still kinda mad
about the whole Camden thing.
Maybe I judged Camden too quickly.
I mean, I didn't even find out
the important stuff about him
that makes him who he is.
Like, his favorite cartoon character.
Does he prefer pizzas or calzones?
And how would he go about
getting gum out of his hair?
What would that tell you about Camden?
That last one was for me.
I dozed off while chewing
some watermelon blast.
So if Camden answers
all of these extremely important questions
and gets the gum out of your hair,
you'll let me date him?
Eh, it depends on his answers.
I mean, no daughter of mine
is dating a calzone guy.
Dad, you love calzones.
Yeah, but I'm not proud of it.
You seem to be handling
the spending freeze well.
You aren't curled up in a ball screaming,
"Why me?"
like the time your favorite
boutique's website went down.
That was a dark seven minutes of my life.
But I've been keeping busy,
like I always do.
By shopping for must-haves
and I-don't-really-need-it-
but-why-the-heck-nots.
So you completely
disregarded what I said?
No, just as you told me,
I didn't spend a single dime.
Like this purse, I bought
with 100,000 nickels.
I can't believe this!
Darcy, from now on
you are completely cut off.
You can't do this to me! It'll break me.
Like the time security escorted me
out of my favorite boutique
and told me to spend
Christmas with my family.
It is possible to have fun
without spending any money.
That's just something
rich people tell poor people.
You look exquisite, Harper.
These are for you.
They're gorgeous.
Okay, you must not be a gladiola girl.
It's not that. We have work to do.
Ahh!
What are you doing to my chinos?
I'm Cliffifying you.
Are you suggesting that I portray myself
as unrefined and buffoonish?
Ahh!
Not buffoonish.
We're talking full-blown buffoon.
Just talk about cartoons.
Oh, and you hate calzones.
What?
Hello, Mr.--
Barry!
Hey, I love that name.
So you back to take out my daughter?
Well,
I just couldn't stop thinking about her
while I was reading... the funnies.
And mindlessly watching cartoons.
I did that today too!
Only I didn't read the funnies.
I just looked at the pictures.
So many words.
Wow, you guys
have so much in common.
Like, Camden was also just telling me
how he hates books
because of all the words.
Right? Can't stand 'em.
The only people who
read books are hoity-toity.
Wait. Hoity-toity?
Um, yeah.
Was that the wrong word to use?
Beats me.
I have no idea what it means,
but I just throw it in all the time
'cause it just feels right.
You know, Harper, maybe I did have
the wrong first impression of Camden.
He doesn't seem too hodgepodge after all.
Great, well, we have a date to get to,
so see you.
Whoa, not so fast.
Before I give my final approval,
I think I should spend
some one-on-one time with him.
But he's my date.
I want to spend one-on-one time with him.
Dude, wanna go chuck some rocks?
I never thought you'd ask.
Really, I never thought you'd ask.
Irona, I'm sorry I cheated in golf.
It's hard for me to compete
with someone who's programmed
with the perfect golf swing.
Yes, give credit to the programmers.
My flawless execution of the programs
has nothing to do with it.
Richie, we have major problems.
Is it your new look?
'Cause I'm not really feeling it on you.
Who cares about looks?
I'm talking about money!
I crunched some numbers
and discovered someone
is draining your accounts.
Darcy, please tell me
you're not messing with me.
I don't joke when it comes to money.
Gender roles, wacky observations, yes.
Money, never.
Wow, you've really embraced
this not spending money thing.
I'm proud of you.
Well, you won't be proud
of your friend Murray.
He's wasting money of yours
that could be making you more money.
He's not wasting it.
He's learning to loosen up.
The best thing about
having money is spending it.
[sighs]
Oh, dear Richie, the best
thing about having money
is it makes it easier to make more of it.
Money Murray's making it rain
Benjamins all up in here.
I know you're my boy and all, man,
but I still think it's messed up
that you got your own milk shake
and it's not low cal.
Murray?
It's Money Murray now,
'cause I'm dropping serious
greenery buying rounds.
I see you're really letting loose.
By unnecessarily wasting money.
Yolo, homegirl!
Murray, I was planning
on returning this outfit
after I wore it.
Ease up, boo.
Solid use of "boo," dog.
You're out of control.
Give me back Richie's credit card.
You can take that card
'cause I'm straight cash, homey.
Okay, stop fighting.
No, fight.
Turn against each other, humans.
It was just a game of mini golf, Irona.
Darcy, Murray, this was
supposed to bring you together.
I really thought you'd learn
something about each other.
I learned Murray's an overindulgent fool.
This shorty's straight weak sauce.
Spendthrift.
Tightwad.
[blows air horn]
Air horn app.
Best 99 cents I ever spent.
99 cents?
Guys, what do I have to do
to get you to stop fighting?
Threaten to make us
drink Bulldozah's Sons.
Ew, I'm not taking that chance.
- I'm out of here.
- No, Darcy!
Yo, why you throwing shade at my shake?
I thought we were boys.
You coming with me
to this next party or what?
Yeah, let's roll.
But--
Murray, don't--
Man, it's depressing in here.
Shouldn't you be partying
with rock star Murray?
What are you doing?
Crossing off
"partying with rock star Murray"
on the list of things
I never thought I'd say.
I came over 'cause
I figured you'd be upset.
I grew up with money,
so I know what it does to friendships.
Wait, having money has cost you friends?
Many times.
I mean, I've also lost friends
because of my personality.
But you seem like a good kid,
so you don't have to worry about that.
Money just makes people
forget what's important.
Wow, Tahj, you really know
what you're talking about.
So what have you done to deal with it?
You just have to move on.
Luckily, when you have money,
there's always a line of kids
waiting to step in and be your friend.
But I don't want new friends.
I want my old friends back.
In that case,
you need to get a time machine,
go back, and never become rich.
And unfortunately, they don't exist.
Trust me, I looked into it
after that milk shake debacle.
Wait! That's a great idea.
A time machine is the answer
to getting Darcy and Murray back.
Man, you're in some serious denial.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have a few letters to write.
I'm getting myself a star
on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
[cha-ching]
So how'd it go?
Can I finally date Camden?
Heck yeah, you can date him.
You can even marry him.
He got the gum out of my hair.
He had this genius idea of using scissors.
I knew he'd impress you,
one way or the other.
Thanks, Dad.
Great job.
You totally fooled my dad.
Harper, you don't understand.
Your dad helped me re-evaluate my life.
I can't believe I wasted
so much time reading books
when I could have been watching cartoons.
They're just like books.
Except they're drawn characters
who move and talk
and are funny and stuff.
You're joking.
Have you ever tried rock chucking?
Dad!
How could you?
No, no, no, don't blame Barry.
He taught me how to loosen up
and how to burp the alphabet. Wanna hear?
You broke Camden.
Ooh, I go by "Terry" now.
Barry said I give off a Terry vibe.
[clicks tongue]
I'm happy for the two of you.
You guys clearly deserve each other.
So is it cool with you
if we go chuck some more rocks?
I'm going up to my room to study.
Do whatever you want.
So...
last one to the tree house
is a rotten egg.
Oh!
Murray.
Darcy.
[engine revs]
Hey, guys.
I'm glad you showed up.
I just wanted to say bye.
Bye? Where are you going?
Back in time.
I miss being able
to have fun with you guys.
And since you guys
always fight about money,
I figure if I just go back
before I had any
we could be good again.
Pfft.
You're tripping, playah.
When it comes to our friendship,
better safe than sorry.
And by "safe" I don't mean for me.
Because from what my engineers tell me,
this thing is basically a death trap.
Hold on.
You've seen science fiction movies.
This kinda messing
with the time-space continuum
only leads to disaster,
like interplanetary war
or robot enslavement.
Oh, do not worry about that.
Those movies are fiction.
Pure fiction.
All right, guys,
let's hope this thing works.
Time to enter one month ago Thursday
on my destination entry system,
which just so happens
to look like my old flip phone.
All right.
Five, four, three,
two...
- Richie!
- Don't go.
I don't wanna see you get hurt.
Neither do I. We care about you.
So you guys agree on something?
Murray and I may disagree about money,
but we agree that we're all best friends.
I only criticize Darcy
because I care about her.
I learned that from years
of watching my mom and dad.
If you don't go back through time,
we will stop fighting.
We can get along, right, Murray?
Absolutely.
Richie, just step out of the time machine.
I'm so relieved.
Not just that you guys have come together,
but that I don't have to risk my life
in this super legitimate time machine.
You were saying?
The point of all this
was to have my friends back.
Darcy, feel free to spend my money.
And, Murray, feel free not to.
I have to admit,
spending money is a lot easier
than saving it.
Maybe for you.
I had trouble spending so much.
It's hard out there for a playah.
At least I don't have
to dress like a dweeb anymore.
Dweeb?
For once, I actually thought
you looked quite nice.
I have to give it to you.
In that suit,
you don't look like a complete loser.
Backhanded compliments.
Wow, we've made progress.