Master Richie,
it is past your bedtime.
I had to give my whales,
Dollar, Dollar,
and Bill Y'all,
a bath.
Maybe it would have
gone quicker
if I had some help.
You know I cannot go
into the salt water
unless it's on a beach
with oil and tonic.
Now, time for bed.
In you go.
Why are you rushing me?
Oh, no reason.
[snoring]
[soft clanking]
[footsteps]
Hello?
Is someone there?
Go back to sleep,
Richie.
This is all a dream
that you
definitely won't remember
in the morning.
[snoring]
[clicking, tapping]
Hello? Darcy?
I bet it was Darcy.
There are $7 million
in gold bars missing,
and she's
the only explanation.
- $7 million?
- Yup.
Then it can wait
till morning.
[beeping and buzzing]
What are you guys
doing now?
Apologies, Master Richie.
I am just wiping
my memory.
I accidentally saw
your father
in his underwear.
[shudders]
Well, can you do that
in another room?
I'm trying to sleep,
or at least I was
before you put the image
of my dad in his underwear
in my head.
[eerie moaning]
What is it now?
Darcy, Murray, Irona,
whoever is in here,
I'm trying to sleep.
[eerie moaning]
Uh, guys?
Hello?
[rumbling]
[screams]
Richie?
Hey, buddy.
You okay?
You having a nightmare?
Want me to stay here
until you fall asleep?
Don't worry.
I'm probably not going
back to sleep.
Ever.
[cash register dings]
- My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create
a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car,
and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
my dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
Thanks for pulling
my car, Irona.
I could have driven it,
but, well, you're here.
Master Ri--
[whirs]
Why are you bringing
all of your bed stuff in here?
I just thought
I'd sleep here tonight.
There's that great ocean view,
the ice cream bar,
and most importantly,
no ghosts.
Ghosts?
Oh, right, ghosts!
There must have been a ghost
in your room last night,
and should you be missing
any gold bars,
I'm sure it was the ghost.
I have too many keys
on my key chain.
Richie, can I talk to you?
It's not about ghosts.
It's about ghosts!
Look, I don't want
to scare you,
but ghosts are
very, very real,
and they are in this house
right now.
What?
Are they looking at us
right now?
No, they sleep
during the day.
It's the silence at night
that wakes them.
Oh, no!
Well, that explains
the terrifying, creepy,
evil noises last night.
There's no way
this place is haunted.
It's way too nice.
Ghosts prefer
dingy shanties,
like where Murray lives.
There's something creepy
going on in my bedroom.
I'm not going back
in there.
You're being ridiculous.
How about Murray and I
spend the night
to prove there's nothing
to be scared of?
There's plenty
to be scared of.
GMOs in our food supply,
antibiotic-resistant infections,
the bullies at Sunday school
who always take my bagel money,
and, oh, yeah,
ghosts.
Well, I guess
if you guys are there,
it won't be as scary.
Ahhh!
[both scream]
You got a ghost.
Need power.
You and you alone
have the power
to make changes
in your life,
but it starts here
in your...
whatever robots have there.
Thank you, Dr. Bill.
You encouraging words
have reenergized me.
Dr. Bill?
I'm a big fan.
I watch your show
whenever I'm home sick.
I always feel better after
the two-hour nap it induces.
What is he doing here?
Irona's been having
some self-esteem issues.
I brought Dr. Bill in
to lift her spirits.
My battery's not what
it once was.
Irona, it's not
what's on the outside;
it's what's on the inside
that counts.
My battery is
on the inside.
Oh.
[beep]
Hello,
Harvard admission board.
My name is Harper Rich,
and as you will surely see
from this video application,
I was born
to spend my life
amongst only the best
and brightest--
Yee-haw!
Whoa!
[chuckles]
- Dad, what are you doing?
Playing cowboy.
And feller here
is playing horse.
[whispers]
He's not a real horse.
Thanks.
But I'm trying to record
my early acceptance application
for Harvard.
I don't want to run the risk
of ending up at State.
Our state school
isn't bad.
But it's
within driving distance.
Did you bring the home videos
of me as a kid?
I need to work them
into my application.
I sure did.
Got a picture album too.
Dad,
these are all black.
Yeah, unfortunately that's how
they've always been.
The camera I bought
came with this thing on the lens
that totally ruined
all of our pictures.
A lens cap?
Dad, you were supposed
to take it off.
So we have no pictures
of me as a kid?
We have tons.
Look, here's your first
Halloween costume.
You can't see it,
but you're adorable.
What about home videos?
Tell me I can use those.
You can use them,
but they're all black too.
You can hear some stuff,
like Richie yelling something
about a cap thing.
Oh!
Dad, I need childhood videos
to show the story of my life.
I'm so sorry
that I messed this up.
But my memories of you
as a little girl are so special,
I'll bet I can re-create them
using pen and paper.
Hold on.
You said "re-create."
Yeah, why?
Is that the wrong word?
Is it "recreate"?
I never know the difference.
Maybe I can re-create
the videos and pictures.
No need.
I already did.
See?
Here I am walking you
to your first day of preschool.
Wow, I was skinny
back then.
Richie, I'm going
to make sure it's safe.
All clear.
Okay, so far,
so good.
So why are you
wearing that again?
Murray told me
to blend in.
You're being ridiculous.
- Murray?
- Murray.
Look, I'm not really scared.
Master Richie,
I received the ghost spray
from that witch doctor
in Aruba.
Ghost spray?
I didn't order that.
Be sure to get
under my bed.
Come on.
There aren't any ghosts in here.
You have no idea
what you're dealing with.
I've faced these
supernatural beings before.
My great-great-grandmother
haunted us for months.
She kept wanting us
to try the soup.
We're full, Doris!
We're full!
As usual, the only abnormal
thing in this room is Murray.
It's not haunted.
Maybe I was just
hearing things.
[echoing moan]
Like that.
What is that?
It's the end.
I'm prepared.
Are you?
[moaning]
[horn honking]
[alarm sounding]
Irona?
[rumbling]
I'm out of here!
[moaning]
It's locked!
What's happening?
I don't know.
Hey, let me out!
I'm a ghost too!
Aah!
Whew!
Good thing I had
that secret passage put in.
Well, I guess now
it's just a passage.
That was crazy.
Your room is actually haunted.
I told you!
I'm never setting foot
in there again.
[laughs]
Hear that?
Ghost laughter.
No, that was me.
Richie, I think
I may have figured out
why your room
is being haunted.
It was built
directly above a burial ground.
What website are you on?
Ugh, why do people
always build stuff
over Indian burial grounds?
No, it's much worse.
This isn't
an Indian burial ground.
It's a pilgrim burial ground.
Well, that's a refreshing
change of pace.
Maybe we can make peace
with these pilgrims.
It looks like Thanksgiving
has come early this year.
Who are you right now?
I'm your best chance
at staying alive.
[cha-ching]
Okay, smile,
'cause these are the books
you really wanted
for Christmas.
What kind of loser
wants books for Christmas?
Me, at eight years old.
All right, I'm ready
to re-create these pictures.
Dad, why are you dressed
like a caveman?
This is what I wore
in the '90s.
Who's the little girl?
That's Noah, but as far
as Harvard's concerned,
she's me
at eight years old.
She looks nothing like
you did.
She doesn't have pigtails.
She's not sucking her thumb.
She doesn't have that crazy
orthodontic headgear on.
[chuckles]
I had an overbite, okay?
'Cause she sucked
her thumb.
She still does
whenever she gets really upset.
Okay, go sit
next to Noah.
I need a video of you
giving me my beaker set.
Pfft, I never gave you
a beaker set.
I know.
You gave me a set of bird beaks.
What a loser.
This is
very important to me,
and you guys are refusing
to cooperate, and--
- [chuckles]
- Told you.
Greetings,
pilgrim spirits.
We are here to offer you
a homemade Thanksgiving feast.
Wait a minute, you didn't
say anything about homemade.
I just brought
some canned corn.
Recess is over, Richie.
Get it together.
Yeah, come on,
Richie!
[moaning]
[alarm sounding]
Great,
now you've upset them.
Quick, pull out
the pumpkin pie.
That's homemade, isn't it?
The crust is,
but the filling,
yeah, that's canned.
Why didn't you have your
personal chef prepare the meal?
I don't make my employees
work on Thanksgiving.
[moaning]
Let's get out of here!
It's locked!
Quick,
to the not-so-secret passage!
[all scream]
Irona is possessed.
How are we
supposed to escape
with the ghost
controlling her?
Okay, I have
the perfect plan.
Darcy, you distract her.
Richie and I
will escape.
What happens to me?
It's probably better
if you don't know.
Wait, I might know
how to power down Irona.
You had the remote
this whole time?
Maybe my room
isn't haunted.
Maybe Irona
just has a virus.
She did go to Coachella
last weekend.
Hopefully the worst
is behind us.
[moaning]
Or it's right
in front of us.
Now, no matter what happens,
don't let go.
It's going to get a little crazy
on the other side.
[moaning]
Dollar, Dollar,
Bill Y'all?
[moaning]
Wait, ghosts aren't making
those noises.
My whales are.
Hello? Whales.
That's kind of what
I've been saying the whole time.
Okay, so this is
where I skipped
Bobby Jenkins' birthday party
in order to solve
Masser's infamous
ABC conjecture.
Yeah, because I'm sure
you were invited to that party.
Yee-haw! Whoa!
Well, listen,
I know how important
that there application
is to you,
so Cowboy Cliff
contacted Aunt Gracie
and got you a home video
of you as a little girl.
Does that mean
I can go home?
Please tell me
that means I can go home.
Harper, I've given my lines
a thorough review,
and I'm ready to inhabit
the role of your father.
Who's this dude?
Uh...
Sir Steve Flemming,
in the role
of Dr. Abernathy Rich.
- You are?
- Harper's dad.
Ooh, busted.
Shush.
Dad...
- Yeah?
- Yes?
Real dad, I just--
Wait, Harper,
Did you replace me?
Well, it sounds bad
when you say it like that.
It's pretty bad
no matter how you say it.
Okay, take five, guys.
Dad, I--
- No, I get it.
You're embarrassed that your
old man isn't smart and stuff.
Come on, feller.
[clicks tongue]
Let's go someplace
where we're appreciated.
♪ Oh, give me a home ♪
♪ Where the buffalo roam ♪
[cha-ching]
So the whales
leaping out of the water
is what must have caused
the house to shake.
There were never
any ghosts.
Like I was saying.
If it was all
from the whales,
what made the lights flicker,
the room go crazy,
and Irona get possessed?
Well, belugas emit
powerful clicks
and high-frequency sound waves
that have been known
to interfere
with sensitive
electrical equipment.
So you're saying
their sounds interfered
with Irona's processors?
And since she can control
everything in your room,
she caused all of your stuff
to go haywire.
Aww, it's so cute when you
guys finally figure things out.
How can we know
for sure?
We fire up Irona
wearing some high-tech
sound-wave-impervious gear.
Okay, time to power
her up.
Irona, this is
your rock bottom.
Time has come for you
to take your power back.
Oh, please work,
please work, please work.
Thank you, Dr. Bill.
Yet again, your words
of generic common sense
have given me power.
So, Irona,
how are you feeling?
Normal?
Better than normal,
Master Richie.
In fact, I'm feeling
quite attractive
in my ravishing new hat.
It really brings out
my rivets.
Now we need
to find out why my whales
are acting out
like this.
Most likely, their issues
are rooted in their childhood.
Mine certainly are.
Enough, Dr. Bill.
I do not have any 5s.
Go fish, muffin.
Dude, not your daughter.
And please don't
call me "muffin."
Finally, you're back.
Guys, it's time to go.
I really messed things up
with my dad.
Don't fret.
Our bond cannot be broken.
Okay, well, I'm breaking it,
so hit the road.
[Christmas music]
Here you go, Harper.
Merry Christmas.
It is a thesaurus?
Is it
a stainless bevel protractor?
You're going to have
to open it to find out.
Wait, let me take
a picture first.
Okay, smile.
[camera shutter clicks]
Ah, that's going to be
a great one.
I can't wait to see that
in a frame.
All right, go ahead.
Toilet paper?
What could be more fun?
Uh...
Toilet paper fight!
Whoo!
[laughing]
So that was
my childhood,
and while I'm extremely proud
of my academic achievements,
I hope the Harvard
admission board can appreciate
that I didn't spend my free time
solving mathematical theorems.
I was doing something that,
as I become more focused
on getting into college,
I've forgotten how to do,
and that's having fun.
Luckily, I have someone in
my life who's really good at it.
And I reckon it's high time
to vamoose.
This isn't a moose.
It's a horse.
Yee-haw!
[laughing]
Guys, in order to find out
what's up with my whales,
I downloaded
a beluga translation app.
Irona, launch the app.
♪ There's no reason
to be scared of the dark ♪
Not my night-light app.
The whale translation app.
Ask the whales
what's bothering them.
Right away,
Master Richie.
[moans like a whale]
[moans]
Ah.
What is it?
What did they say?
They want me to have
a month off.
I am serious.
It is what they said.
Irona!
Okay, I will say this
as gently as possible.
Dollar, Dollar, and Bill Y'all
hate living in your house.
That was gentle?
They would prefer
to be in the ocean.
[moans]
As much fun as they have
with you,
they want to be swimming
in the open ocean.
Plus, they say
fresh sardines are much better
than the canned ones
they get here.
What?
Do you know how expensive
fresh seafood is?
Oh, Murray.
I feel terrible.
Well, I guess there's
only one thing for me to do.
Let me take
that month off?
It's time to release
Dollar, Dollar, and Bill Y'all.
I want what's best
for them,
and if they aren't happy
with me,
they don't belong here.
It's been fun, guys.
I guess this is good-bye.
If you are brave enough
to say good-bye,
life will reward you
with a new hello.
Good-bye, Dr. Bill.
Hello!
No, seriously,
get lost.
[chuckles]
[whale moaning] I'm going to miss Richie
But I won't miss the ghosts
haunting that place.
[rumbling]
[horn honking]
[alarm sounding]
For reals?
[singsong]
They're back.