[gasps] I cannot believe rx-37 is cheating
on Octodyne Betacore!
What are you doing, Irona?
Just dusting.
Certainly not watching the marathon
of "As the Microchip Pulses."
Either you're lying,
or you're as bad at dusting
as I am at biology.
I got a "D" on my test.
Apparently, DNA is not what gets
a movie an "R" rating.
Richie, did you tell Murray
to put me on a spending freeze?
No, why?
Because he froze all of my credit cards!
Pretty smart, huh?
Not only will this little trick
cut down on impulse purchases,
but can also be used
to reduce pain and swelling
from impact injuries.
Ow!
Ahh, soothing.
Murray, how long is she supposed to wait
to use those cards?
Oh, days, months, years.
It took centuries
for that Siberian woolly mammoth
to defrost.
That gives me an idea!
Sending Darcy to Siberia?
I've already looked into it.
The Russians won't take her.
Ow!
Ahh.
Well, I'm gonna take a trip to Antarctica!
If I can find some frozen
ancient life form,
my biology teacher will
definitely give me an "A."
Free trip? I'm in.
I'm not.
That place is my worst nightmare.
Sure, it's cold, but you'll be
fine once I buy you
the latest cold-weather gear.
It's not the cold I'm worried about.
It's those creepy penguins.
They're birds that fly underwater--
It's unnatural.
Have fun. I'll be here...
nice and warm and safe from
those freakish fish-birds.
Murray's not coming?
Suddenly I'm even more excited
for this trip!
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
Except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with--
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
What a waste of time!
A whole continent without any shopping!
Darcy, the trip was a huge success.
If Irona's sensors are right,
this block of ice contains
a discovery that will forever
change the landscape of science
and, more importantly,
raise my biology grade.
If you need me, I'll be on the couch,
- dusting the remote.
- Sorry, Irona.
I need you to document this.
Set up the camera.
Of course, master Richie.
I understand why you would need
help simply removing a lens cap
and pushing a button.
Given the prints in the tundra,
whatever is encased in this ice
very well may be a primitive,
less-evolved link to the humans
that exist today.
[shivering]
[both] Murray?
You were certainly right
about the primitive
and less-evolved part.
[imitates whooshing]
Dun-dun dun-na-na!
Dad, what are you doing?
"Dad"? I'm not Dad.
I am...super, mighty middle-aged dude!
I can climb most flights of
stairs without losing my breath.
Then you're definitely not my dad.
I found our old costumes
and thought we could play
superheroes like old times.
Check it out.
My super utility belt still fits!
Dad, as much as I'd love
to run around the neighborhood
with you in tights and a cape,
Tulip and I have a girls' weekend planned.
Aw, that's a bummer,
'cause I had a surprise for you.
I hopped on the mighty
middle-aged dude mobile...
Aka your bike.
Went to the toy store,
and got you this awesome
invisibility cloak for 40 bucks.
[cell phone plays classical tune]
Hey, Tulip.
Are you as desperate to get this
girls' weekend started as I am?
Say hi from me.
What? Are you serious?
Yeah, she's your best friend.
I'm just trying to be polite.
I guess I understand,
but I think you're being unfair to me.
And I hope your grandmother
makes a full recovery.
Tulip is so selfish.
I can't believe she's can--
Well, I'm off to girls' weekend.
If you need me, call me.
Don't go in my room
since I won't be in there.
Wait a second.
Thanks to my super, mighty
middle-aged dude powers,
I'm sensing something's bothering you...
and I'm due for a colonoscopy.
- It's nothing. It's...
- Harper.
Tulip totally flaked
on our girls' weekend.
Aw, Harper, I'm sorry.
I know how much girls' weekend
meant to you.
So maybe I can fill in for Tulip
and do it with ya.
I'm already wearing tights.
I'm well aware.
But you're not a girl, so
girls' weekend isn't happening.
So it looks like
we're playing superheroes.
Want to hop on the handlebars
of the mighty middle-aged dude mobile
and look for crime...
or an ice cream truck?
Girls' weekend it is.
Care to help me out?
Murray's freezing!
Serves him right
for what he did to my babies.
Mommy will never let that bad man
near you again, my sweeties.
Murray, how did you end up
in a block of ice in Antarctica?
You said you weren't leaving the house.
I wasn't going to, but...
I was slaving away, hard at work...
♪ Do I have to buy you a diamond ring ♪
♪ Send you flowers and a choir to sing? ♪
♪ They said you were easy,
but they were lying ♪
♪ I ain't got you yet,
but I'll keep trying ♪
♪ I'll keep trying every day,
I'll keep trying every ♪
[record scratches]
When I casually came across
an unopened letter.
Thanks to my innate gift
for money management,
I sensed it was a check
that I should open immediately.
"Check. Open immediately."
Realizing Richie would lose
a ton of interest
if the check weren't deposited
until he got back,
I headed off to Antarctica
to get his signature
with no delay...
Well, with little delay.
The second I set foot in Antarctica,
I slipped on the ice, slid down a glacier,
and the next thing I saw
was a bright light
and a bunch of disappointed faces.
It reminded me of when I was born.
Your parents wanted a girl?
No. Why do you ask?
I can't believe you went
through so much trouble
for one check.
It must be pretty big.
Oh, it is.
It's...
Oh, no, the check!
I must have dropped it in Antarctica!
- I'll be right back.
- "Right back"?
It's halfway across the planet.
I'd circle the earth
ten times over for that check.
Wait! It's not worth it!
[flatly] No. Don't go.
Wait. I thought RX-37 was
married to Octodyne Betacore.
She is.
Ooh, this is getting good.
Come on, Darcy, we've got
to get back to Antarctica
to rescue Murray.
Wait. Before we go,
there's something I want you to consider.
[light music]
♪ ♪
♪ Murray's being buried
in the snow as we speak ♪
♪ Not a bow tie in sight ♪
♪ So I think I just might
go clean out a boutique ♪
♪ Now my credit cards ♪
♪ Aren't the ones encased in ice ♪
♪ Finally Murray knows ♪
♪ That when it comes to clothes ♪
♪ I'm not one to play nice ♪
♪ The scrawny kid is off the grid ♪
♪ We don't need him, we never did ♪
♪ He can't forbid me ♪
♪ From spending as I please ♪
♪ So let him freeze ♪
♪ Murray's gone ♪
♪ He's gone ♪
♪ Richie, it's an easy call ♪
♪ Zilch to dwell on ♪
♪ He's gone ♪
♪ So I can go hit the mall ♪
♪ Murray's gone ♪
♪ I say hooray ♪
♪ So let's go blow a million bucks today ♪
Wow, Darcy. That was amazing.
So you're on board with letting Murray go?
No. Your little song
didn't convince me
to let our best friend freeze,
but impressive vocal range.
Okay, good luck.
I'm sure you guys will be fine.
Helicopters are pretty self-explanatory.
So...
girls' weekend...
it's the weekend...
and we're two girls.
Dad, you don't have to do this.
Yes, I do. I'm your father.
That's the problem.
Just pretend I'm one of the girls.
What would you do if Tulip were here?
Talk about boys,
complain about our families,
mostly talk about boys.
Okay, let's talk about boys.
Isn't that Harry Styles just adorable?
Don't you just want to run your fingers
through that silky hair of his?
Dad, stop!
I can't talk about boys with you.
Okay, let's talk about makeup.
I love those powders and sticks
and other makeup-y things--
Totally covers up my 5:00 shadow.
I appreciate you trying,
but you and I are never gonna
talk about makeup or boys
or try on each other's clothes.
[scoffs] Girl, please.
So...
What do you think?
I think you're totally stretching out
my favorite dress!
Don't worry.
You get to try on my clothes too.
I grabbed a pair of sweats from my hamper.
Heads up for the nacho cheese
on the thigh.
Oh!
Dad, I am not trying on your clothes.
Wait. There is one outfit
of yours that I wanted to try.
Harper?
Where'd you go?
Harper!
Murray! Murray!
- Oh, no!
- What? Do you see him?
- Is he hurt?
- No.
But I just found out baby Beep-Bop
is not Octodyne's child.
Put down the tablet! Eyes on the horizon!
We need to find Murray!
I have a way to bring him right to us.
I'm going to dump a bunch
of cash out the door,
and if I know Murray, he'll come running.
All right, use the ones.
It's not that cold out there.
Money?
[penguins squawking]
Rise and shine! Day two of girls' weekend!
You're seriously still wearing my dress?
Yeah, I couldn't get it off.
Look, I felt bad
about how things went yesterday,
so I did some research on girl stuff,
and I thought I'd give you a mani-pedi.
So come and sit in the chair...
and then put these cucumbers
over your eyes...
and listen to this relaxing music
while I paint your nails
a lovely shade of lavender.
Wow, dad. This is great.
I mean, I wish we could've started
a little bit later in the day,
but I'm still impressed.
Yeah, I would've liked
to start a little bit later too.
[sighs]
But since I rented the equipment,
I got to get it back
to the hardware store by noon.
"Hardware store"?
[paint gun hissing]
Aah! Stop spraying!
I can't figure out how to turn it off!
The switch is covered
with pre-primed lavender exterior paint!
Dad...
I appreciate you trying,
but girls' weekend is officially over!
I'm sorry, Harper.
I was just trying to have
some fun with you.
These days, you're too mature
to play superheroes,
and, obviously, I'm not mature enough
to do what you want to do.
- Dad, wait.
- Is girls' weekend back on?
No, your slip is showing.
Thanks.
Thank goodness Murray was able
to put aside his rational fears
and stay warm with those penguins.
Yeah, but...
[lively music]
- ♪ I never-- ♪
- Not now, Darcy.
I'm worried about Murray.
He didn't say a word on the flight home.
Yes, it was magnificent, wasn't it?
Master Richie, I have an urgent matter
to discuss with you.
Irona, I don't want you
wasting any more time
on that old TV show.
RX-37 was never pregnant,
and baby Beep-Bop is really her sister.
There, now you don't need to watch.
I cannot believe
you just spoiled that for me.
Well, you know your precious Santa Claus?
He pours that milk you leave
down the drain.
He is a soy milk man.
Ha. In your face.
That's not a spoiler.
I'm actually happy about that.
Santa needs to tone up that midsection.
Well, I did not come to talk
about the show
which you have now ruined.
I came to discuss--
[honking]
That.
Murray, what are you doing?
[honking]
Seems normal to me.
Why is Murray honking?
That is the exact honk
of an emperor penguin.
Ha! Spoiled it for you.
That's not a spoiler.
That's actually helpful information.
- Thanks!
- [sighs]
So why is Murray acting like a penguin?
Can I please answer in a song?
No!
What's going on?
Every time I try to talk to Murray,
he honks and waddles off.
[sighs] We already saved him once.
If it's meant to be, he'll come back.
If it's not,
we can legitimately say we tried.
We have to find him.
Master Richie, I did some research
on what may be afflicting Murray
and on what a spoiler is.
Bruce Willis' character saves the planet
in Asteroid Invasion 7.
- Ha!
- Obviously.
He saved the planet in the other six.
He does?
Oh, I had not seen those yet.
Thanks for spoiling them for me.
Wait. Irona,
what did you find out about Murray?
Well, there are many cases
of people who take on the traits
of animals that care for them
during traumatic experiences.
I suspect that is what happened with him.
So, because penguins kept him
warm in Antarctica...
He thinks he is one.
Crazy, I know.
That is humans for you.
You were looking for some wild
scientific discovery
for biology class.
You'll get your "A" if you turn in Murray.
So, Irona, if I don't want
Murray to be scared of me,
there's only one way
for me to approach him.
Once again, I am reminded
if I just did my schoolwork,
my life would be a lot easier.
Dun-dun!
Harper, what are you doing?
I am not Harper.
I am super, mighty teen-aged chick.
I am able to take selfies
at the speed of light.
[camera shutter clicks]
[scoffs] Ew. Retake.
Can totes do a better duck face.
[camera shutter clicking]
Harper, what are you doing?
I thought you didn't want
to play superheroes.
I thought about what you said,
and I don't want you thinking
I'm too mature to have fun with you.
I used to have the best time
playing superheroes with you,
and I'll never be too old for that.
So what do you say, Dad?
"Dad"? I'm not Dad.
I'm...
[grunts]
Super, mighty middle-aged dude.
So, super, mighty middle-aged dude,
what master villain do we have
to protect the world from today?
The Waddler--
An overgrown penguin
who's infiltrated our lair
in a plot to take over the world.
Pretty creative.
I didn't make it up.
He's right there.
That's not the Waddler. That's Richie.
Get him!
Boom!
Pow! Oh!
Ah, my back!
Super, mighty middle-aged dude's
back is his one weakness.
[grunts]
That and his knees,
and he can't eat spicy food any more.
[grunts]
It's okay.
I'll do it.
Get away from me, Harper.
You two are being weird.
I am not Harper.
I am super, mighty teen-aged chick!
I'm gonna beat you up and then
spread evil rumors about you.
[laughing evilly]
Murray?
[honks]
Honk, honk, honk. Honk, honk.
[honking]
Honk, honk.
[honks]
Honk.
Honk, honk.
[honking]
Ha! Got you!
By the way, that was really honking weird.
[honking]
You didn't have to scare the little guy.
You're lucky I went with the net.
Plan "B" was the club.
[honking]
It is all right, sweetie.
Irona will save you from the evil humans
and their spoilers.
I've got it. We can donate him to the zoo.
We're not putting him in a zoo.
We need to help him, like Irona.
When you are done here,
you can go knock out
a couple loads of laundry.
Irona, why is Murray dusting?
I am a robot now, Master Richie.
What? Since when?
Ever since I comforted him,
he's been saying he's a robot
and doing all my chores.
Well, I'm glad this wacky turn of events
found a happy, permanent solution.
Cheers to that!
I'll take a cold lemonade.
Come on, chop-chop.
Wait. This makes sense now.
[both] It does?
The penguins cared for Murray
when he was stranded out in the cold,
and he acted like a penguin.
And when Irona cared for him
when you traumatized him
by holding up that club,
he started acting like a robot.
So you're saying if we care for him
through a traumatic experience,
he will change back to normal?
Okay, let us not do that.
- We are doing that.
- Fine.
You care for him. I'll create the trauma.
Hello, Brittany?
Yeah, I can't make it
down to the boutique today,
so will you put those handbags,
the tiara in the window,
and the rest of the boutique
on Richie's tab?
Thanks, doll. [smooches]
It's okay, Murray.
You're gonna be okay, buddy.
It's working.
Keep pretending to order stuff.
Yeah, because I'm pretending.
Hello, Ricardo?
I can't make it
down to the dealership today,
so can I just give you
Richie's credit card?
Stop! Darcy, stop wasting Richie's money!
Murray, you're back!
I missed you, dude.
Thanks for saving me, Richie.
Now allow me to save you
millions of dollars.
Ha! There.
[light music] Not again.
♪ ♪
Richie...
♪ I liked him better as a penguin ♪
♪ When he'd only speak
in honks and squawks ♪
♪ There's a pair of shoes
that I desire to acquire ♪
♪ Which requires Murray to kick rocks ♪
♪ I need them, they're simply divine ♪
♪ But I know he will just moan and whine ♪
♪ Murray's better as a penguin ♪
♪ I'd even take him as a robot ♪
Just stop, Darcy.
Okay, fine.