Richie, you are amazing.
What a great idea you had
to fly to Hawaii just for lunch.
That was your idea.
My idea was to order a Hawaiian pizza.
[humming]
Harper, are you humming,
or did years of frowning
make your lips fuse together?
Nothing you say is going to keep this
from being a great day.
Finally someone, besides me,
is recognizing how amazing I am.
I'm getting an award for motivating
and tutoring struggling students.
Any chance you could motivate me
to become more interested in this story?
[laughing]
Darcy, Darcy, Darcy,
you sweet little parasite.
The school board is naming me
volunteer of the year.
Congrats, Harper.
So did you just come in here to gloat?
Yeah.
Maybe one day you'll learn
how to be a good person
who gives back.
Richie gives back.
Yesterday, he gave a guy $10 million.
Actually, that was for my yachtacopter.
The traffic in the marina is unbearable.
Some people spend money,
and some people care about the children.
Now, out of my way, pipsqueaks.
Darcy, I'm not some
self-centered egomaniac, am I?
Master Richie, Richie Rich One's wing
just clipped the platinum statue of you
and crashed into the pool
shaped like your face.
You still need me to answer that question?
[cash register dings]
y name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
I guess Harper's right.
Since I've gotten all that money,
I haven't used it to do any good.
I mean, do I really need a yachtacopter
when there are needy kids out there?
Yeah, you're right.
You don't need a yachtacopter,
but I do.
You know, Master Richie,
if you are interested in helping others,
I could connect you to PETE.
The gardener?
No, People for the Ethical
Treatment of Electronics.
Thanks to that organization's hard work,
it is illegal to test makeup
on a video game console.
Does that happen?
No, and it never will, thanks to PETE.
Here. Before you make your decision,
there's a quick video
I would like you to watch.
[melancholy music playing]
Every day, over 200,000 computers
are thrown into the trash.
Every 15 seconds,
a cell phone is replaced.
But for some, it is not too late.
[crying]
Hello, Richie Rich.
You may know me as your maid.
Do you have it in your human heart
to rescue a helpless piece
of outdated technology?
Wow, Irona, that video was really moving.
So you are going to offer
a new lease on life
to a discarded electronic device?
No, I'm sticking with
the kids, but it was moving.
[cha-ching]
Hey, Mr. Rich.
What are you working on there?
Puzzle. But it's really complicated.
Been working on it for hours.
I still can't figure it out.
Hand it over.
Wow. Genius alert.
Huh.
You know, I just joined this organization
called The Little Brothers.
It's a group of kids
who mentor lost, wayward adults.
And you seem way...
wayward.
Aw, thanks.
Well, if it means you helping me
with stuff like that puzzle, I'm in.
Great! This is so exciting.
I'm your new Little Brother.
I know! I'm pumped!
I always wanted a little brother.
[gasps] Want to get bunk beds?
I call top bunk! I call the top bunk!
Congratulations
to our volunteer of the year,
Harper Rich.
[applause]
I am so honored to be honored.
- Harper?
- Richie?
What are you doing at my school?
- Your school?
- Yeah, I just adopted it.
Isn't it cute?
Richie,
I've been volunteering at this school
for over a year.
Of all the schools around,
you had to pick this one?
It's the closest to our house.
You know I'm lazy.
You're ruining my moment.
I thought you'd be happy. You were right.
I've been too self-centered
and egotistical,
so I'm giving back
by adopting this school.
Why would I be happy?
You're ruining my moment.
I get it. I'm sorry, Harper.
Continue with your ceremony.
I'll wait until you're done
to give each student
their own brand-new tablet.
[all cheer]
New ones, because perfectly functioning
refurbished models are not good enough.
Stop giving him what he wants.
Eyes on me.
Off the stage, Extra Homework Girl.
Where's my new tablet?
You get a tablet, and you get a tablet,
and you get a tablet!
Excuse me, I didn't get my new tablet.
Darcy, you don't go to this school,
and I just bought you a tablet last week.
Yeah, but it lost that new tablet smell.
Well, at least I still have my award.
Oh, actually I'm going to need that back.
Uh, this kid's giving out stuff.
Sorry, Harper.
Do you want a consolation tablet?
I guess that'd make me
feel a little better.
Actually, we are all out.
Tough luck, kid.
Okay, the first thing I'm going to do
is help you build your résumé.
Is that anything
like building a tree house?
- No.
- Good.
I mean, you build a tree house out of wood.
Then you put it in a tree.
That's got to be weird
for the tree, right?
No weirder than spending
the night in a bunk bed
below your friend's dad.
Maybe we can just focus on your resume,
you know, listing your work experience.
Making this sandwich was a lot of work.
Uh, I'm afraid I know the answer,
but have you ever had a job?
I once worked as a horse whisperer.
[whispers] Horse.
Okay, let's move on.
What is your dream job?
Parakeet. I'm always flying in my dreams.
Okay, is there any job
out there you've always wanted
and is real?
I always thought it would be awesome
to be one of those sign spinners,
but I'm pretty sure you need
a fancy degree for that.
Hmm. Sign spinning might work.
Why don't you give it a shot
with one of these pillows?
[exhaling]
Relax, Mr. Rich.
You're sweating, and all you did
was pick up a pillow.
Give me a break, kid.
Normally I'm napping right now.
Okay.
Here goes nothing.
I'm spinning!
Actually, I think you're
supposed to spin the sign,
not the--
Okay, as your Little Brother,
I'm committed to sticking things out.
And if no one else will hire you, I will.
How do you know no one else will hire me?
Let's just call it a hunch.
[cha-ching]
Harper, what did you do to my room?
Nothing.
Came in here,
and it was already like this.
So where is that award
that is rightfully mine?
Around my neck--
I mean in a safety deposit box.
Master Richie,
how come none of the students
wanted me in their white-water raft?
Probably because you weigh 2 tons.
I will have you know I'm down to 1.8 tons.
You took the kids white-water
rafting on a school day?
Can't take them on the weekend.
The river gets so crowded.
Richie, you're not helping these kids
by showering them with gifts and trips.
I don't know, they did seem pretty happy
when they were screaming, "Whoo-hoo!
This beats memorizing facts
with Extra Homework Girl!"
Well, I'm sure river rafting
really helped prepare them
for their big, statewide
history exam next week, so--
Wait, wait, wait. What exam?
Oh, it's not important.
It just determines who
moves on to the next grade, so--
Wait, there isn't
a white-water rafting section
in that exam, is there?
No, but continue to have fun
destroying their lives.
Oh, I will.
No, that's not what I meant.
I'm not all about fun and games.
Here's the cart
of fun and games you asked for.
Not the best timing there, Irona.
[cha-ching]
[chuckles]
Not too shabby, huh?
It's my first time wearing this bad boy
since my prom date situation
didn't pan out
like I had hoped.
I had hoped it would have panned out.
And it didn't.
Let's just get to work.
Hold on. I brought you something.
24 years ago, this was a red rose.
It's beautiful, Mr. Rich,
but we really need to focus here.
Recently I've been losing
clients to my main competitor,
Saul "The Human Adding Machine"
Rubinstein.
Hey, I went to high school with Saul.
Great guy.
Well, he's also stealing my clients.
Can't blame your clients. Great guy.
Could you just run upstairs
and grab the box of receipts
outside of Richie's room?
It would really help me out.
No problem--want me to do that
before or after lunch?
It's 10:30,
so before lunch would be great.
Ooh, taskmaster.
Well, if I'm going to squeeze that
and a nap in before lunch,
I better hop to it. [exhales]
[cha-ching]
Hey, hey, hey, be careful.
Okay, guys, recess is over!
Do you know
what's more fun than having fun?
Studying for a statewide exam
that will determine your future!
Dude, you're starting to sound
like Extra Homework Girl.
Because, if you don't pass this test,
you can get held back a year.
Another year of getting free stuff?
[chuckles] Heck, yeah, I'll take that.
[deep voice] Yeah, what Alfonso said.
By the way, you giving away
any jewelry today?
'Cause this homeboy likes
rocking chandelier earrings.
Nice try, Darcy.
Oh, man, it took me
three days to grow this 'stache.
Come on, guys. This is important.
Okay, whoever studies gets a pony.
Who wants a pony?
Okay, who can tell me which Italian city
is the birthplace of the Renaissance?
[Australian accent] G'day, mate.
Australian exchange student here.
I just wanted to make sure
I'm getting a pony.
Nice try, Darcy.
Crikey.
Guys, stop messing around.
Dude, why are you so upset?
We don't need to pass
some stupid history test.
We've got you, and you've got money.
That's not enough. Money isn't everything.
Master Richie, I found some spare change
in the couch.
Irona, would you please
stop wheeling things in that undermine
the point I'm trying to make?
I've ruined these kids.
I think I've cost them their future.
I would not worry about their future.
According to my sensors, a giant asteroid
will destroy the planet on July 7, 2016.
Whew. That's a relief.
Wait, what?
Hey, Harper, are you busy?
For you, I'm always busy.
I need your help with something.
Your students have the state
history test coming up,
so shouldn't you be off shopping with them
on the Champs-Élysées?
Look, I messed up and messed
things up for those kids.
And so who was wrong?
Me.
And who was right?
- You.
- Mm.
Good talk. Now get out.
Look, I need you to help me fix this.
Why would I help you?
Once again, you swooped in
with your money,
stole my award,
and the sliver of recognition
I was finally going to receive.
Look, I was trying to follow your advice
and give back.
I thought I could do that with gifts
and trips and vaccinations,
you know, for the trips.
Where were you taking those kids?
Look, the point is, they needed someone
to inspire them.
They needed you.
I'm sorry, who?
You.
Come again?
Look, please help
these kids pass their test.
Don't do it for me. Do it for them.
Well, as someone else
whose future was destroyed
by you coming into their life,
I do feel for them.
All right, I'll help.
- Under one condition.
- Anything.
I just want to get a recording of you
saying that whole "I was wrong,
you were right" thing.
I want to make it my ring tone.
[cha-ching]
Hey, guys.
Hello!
Harper.
[screaming]
Thank you, Harper.
Guys, I came to tell you something.
You got us tickets
to a One Direction concert?
No, Darcy.
Darn it!
I came to tell you guys
we're going on another trip.
[cheers and applause]
Ooh la la.
We're stopping at historical places
to bring history alive
and prepare you for your test.
all: Boo!
Sacre bleu.
We pre'faire to go zere to
simply shop, Monsieur Richie.
Believe me, I know what
it's like to stare at a textbook
and doze off,
reading about places and people
I've never even heard of.
Oui, oui.
Darcy, out.
So we're going to Florence, Italy,
to walk around the birthplace
of the Renaissance.
Then Florence will mean something to you.
I don't know.
Going, learning, walking--
this is starting to sound like work.
There's no reason why work can't be fun.
We can raft down the Nile River
and learn about the pyramids.
Whoa.
Extra Homework Girl is coming?
Her name is Harper, and it was her idea.
Actually, I have the kids
call me Miss Rich, so--
No wonder they don't like you.
Look, Harper's coming. Now, let's go!
Cliff, where are all the receipts
for these client files?
Don't worry-- I have a new system
where I feed them all
to the angry filing cabinet.
The what?
Here, I'll show you.
Just give me a few receipts
that you want to keep.
- No!
- Ooh, she's hungry today.
Hey, you're ruining my system.
You're ruining my entire business.
[gasps] I give you a corsage,
and you scream at me?
Because of you,
I'm losing clients to Saul.
To be fair, he's a great guy.
That's it.
I can't have you as my assistant any more.
[gasps] Because I'm promoted?
Little Brothers don't give up
on lost, wayward adults,
so I'm not going to fire you.
Thanks. Fire make Cliff sad.
But I think I do have a way
to help my business
and take advantage
of your unique skill set.
Are you going to tell me
what it is, or should I guess?
You are going to be a sign spinner.
Oh, are you kidding me?
Top of the world, ma!
Hey, how come this says
"Saul's Money Management"?
[horn honks]
Really? Saul's sign spinner
hit you in the face with the sign?
[phone ringing] Please hold.
Hello?
You're leaving Saul
because his sign spinner
knocked over your taco cart?
[phone ringing]
Please hold.
Saul's sign spinner wandered into traffic
and fell into your convertible?
Please hold.
[phone vibrating]
Murray here.
Saul?
You're quitting and moving to Alaska?
I'm so sorry to hear that.
[cha-ching]
All right, guys, your test scores are in.
Now, before Richie opens that envelope,
no matter the results, I just want to say
- how very incre--
- You passed!
And you passed!
And you...
better luck next year.
And you passed!
Thanks for helping us, Richie.
So are you going to
congratulate us with anything?
No, but I do have one last gift.
I'm out of costumes, but what's the gift?
- A million-dollar...
- Yes!
- Donation.
- Aw.
To make all your learning as fun
as our trip around the world,
I'm building you
the Harper Rich
Interactive Learning Center.
That's awesome, but who's Harper Rich?
Extra Homework Girl.
Thanks, Richie.
You've done a ton of work for these kids,
and you deserve it.
You also deserve this.
[phone vibrating] Who was wrong?
- Me.
- And who was right?
You.
Don't you just love my new ring tone?
And now to print out
my Justin Timberbot tickets.
[beep] Error message?
Oh, come on.
The printer is connected to the network.
You stupid piece of junk.
Irona?
Please do not report me to PETE.